Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Hello. It's the amazing Atheist here. What does he sound like?
It's about, right? It's like, well, you know.
It's TJ here and I just, you know, video games are okay. It's okay to be bad at video games, women.
I'll still date you.
Maybe he talks about video games.
He must mention them. He must mention them occasionally.
I don't think he's a gamer. I think he...
Come on. Maybe he's played Fallout New Vegas or something.
I genuinely don't remember. I mean, was he involved in Gamergate at all?
He must have talked about it in some capacity.
Oh, he definitely talked about it. I can't remember his content from back then.
He's sort of, he's strange. He was like anti SJW to a point and then sort of turned into like a leftist more recently.
He's friends with Lush and stuff. He's always been like pro the people and fuck the police.
And it just so happens that at the time it was like...
He's like even more milk toast than like shoe on head now.
Yeah. Well, I don't actually know. I don't watch his stuff too much.
I just see him on Twitter. I don't know. Whatever.
I was gonna do hello, I'm the Nostalgia Critic. I was like, no, no, that's old. That's old hat.
We've all heard that before. What's someone else?
No, no, but we gotta go back though, you know.
You're right.
You're right. We have to...
I'm the Nostalgia Critic.
You're one might say we have to go back to the past.
I remember the past so you don't have to.
I have. So you don't have to the past.
Man, did you... You saw my tweet, right? You saw my tweet about...
Yeah, the chin. His fucking beard.
His goatee that is slid like it's wispy on his chin, but it's like more built up on his neck underneath his chin.
That picture that I tweeted, it's usually like... That one, it's like particularly short.
I think that picture is from... I think it's from To Boldly Flea. It's from one of the movies, but yeah.
He always... It's consistent. I think it... I'm not sure if he thinks...
Well, I think he thinks it looks good. I don't think it's supposed to be like,
I made my character look bad on purpose or anything.
But he consistently... When he's the critic, he consistently cuts his beard that way.
And the goatee extends like down under the chin, like onto the neck.
And I don't know if it's an attempt at like sculpting a face shape.
I mean, you can tell if he shaves around that area. Like he deliberately makes it that shape.
Yeah. Yeah.
I was confused because I had not noticed that. I googled image like nostalgia critic or Doug Walker.
And I couldn't see an angle where that was as prevalent as the one you posted.
Yeah. Yeah. You can't see it in Google Images because all the Google Images pictures are like head-on.
You can't see it head-on. You have to see it from the side or slightly underneath.
And then you can't... You can't miss it.
Hold on. It was... This was...
I'm only looking at my discord because someone posted a retrospective...
Oh, yes. Jess from my server posted a retrospective from a YouTuber called DireGentlemen.
That is a... Dan Olsen did his thing about the wall pretty recently.
And then a little after that, DireGentlemen posted this thing about the review must go on, which I didn't even know existed.
Do you know what that is?
Mulan Rouge review, wasn't it?
No.
I've seen a lot of his stuff.
No. The review must go on is... I'm going to recap.
There's a bunch of retrospectives on this specific topic, which I've watched like three of them like yesterday.
I just think they're so funny.
Was it just like about the drama?
No. It's more specific even than that. It's about when he did...
Was Toboldly Flea the one where he kills the critic?
Yes. That was the last canonical big stupid movie.
Yeah. They did Toboldly Flea, killed the critic, and then this was an attempt at sort of jumping...
Yig Studio style, changing the channel to making content that nobody wanted in the form of...
He started a new series called Demo Reel.
And he did two episodes of it. Nobody liked it.
Mike Michaud, the guy that owns his character, was like, you got to go back to the thing that makes me money, dude, right now, or I'll kill you.
And he said, fuck.
So then in defeat, Revue Must Go On is basically the finale to Demo Reel, in which it is a post.
It is sort of a retroactively decided that actually Demo Reel was only like a fantasy in the mind of the critic.
And like the demonic spirit of the critic visits the main character of Demo Reel and tells him like, you're fake.
I am what's real. Bring me back. You must do it. And Doug says, no.
No, I hate reviewing movies.
It's so dramatic. And he does the face. He does the dreamworks face so much to be like badass.
I don't remember that video now that I think about it.
But it's...
But when like...
Oh, it's a fake out. The nostalgia critic's back. Oh my God.
But it's really, it's really clear.
It was actually based at the time.
I mean, there were definitely things to say about it.
I can't remember. I think I must have been, I think I must have been excited at the time because I was still a fan of his.
I mean, if you wanted to see more critic, if you wanted to see more critic than I'm sure you were like, yes, he's bringing it back.
Yes.
But...
A pog.
But when you really think about it and this, I'm sort of spoiling, I'm doing the opposite of burying the lead.
I'm kind of digging up the lead and spoiling it.
But like, basically the thesis of this video and it's, it's, it seems other videos have had the same thesis.
It's like, when you hear how he talked about it at the time, it's really clear that he wanted to move away from the critic and start making original content
and failed so spectacularly that, that demo reel and the review must go on is basically a huge, it's just a huge cope in which he on screen sort of grapples with
and like in real time sort of convinces himself that, no, I actually really wanted to do the critic the whole time all along.
That was just burnout.
I mean, it could be kind of half true.
I mean, the demo reel from what I remember hearing about it was just like the sorts of skits he would put in Nostalgia Critic but without the movie review aspect of it.
So like, what if we just had a skit about like Batman doing something and I was Batman.
I went, haha.
Like that, that's the extent of like the intellectual content of demo reel.
And so it's like, well, as long as I can do that while I do reviews, then I can do Nostalgia Critic again.
And that's what he's been doing.
Yeah.
Terrible skits with actors dressing up in silly bad costumes on shitty green screens acting out things from the movie so they could say, ah, it's not very good, is it?
I see those other people in his stuff, like all those other people that are in like the wall review and I'm like, what's their story?
Like, what do they think about all this?
Like the post scandal, like new crop of people who are all there and all sort of really look the same.
I think, well, I remember that there was a lady who was there for like a few episodes of Nostalgia Critic.
Nostalgia Critic was like, okay, I'm ending Nostalgia Critic, I'm going to start a new show, we're going to get a studio, we're going to get actors, we're going to do skits about fucking movies or whatever.
He hired, I don't know their names, he hired the black guy and then a lady.
I know the black guy's name is Malcolm and that's the only one whose name I know.
Malcolm, yes.
He's a staple, I think he generally likes it but he seems more of a normal human being, so he gets paid so why not?
That guy seems like a freaking nerd, that guy's got big dweeb energy.
A big old fucking dork on screen every time I see him, I want to shove him in a locker if you ask me.
Yeah, go on.
True, true.
She left and to like go and do real acting work, she had like a goodbye video.
It's like, yeah, I'm going to move on to like a brighter future because it was so obvious that she was like, I don't want to be stuck working under the Nostalgia Critic.
I'm trying to get an acting career going, so I'm gone and then there was a new lady.
This was a lady who was on like three episodes of Nostalgia Critic, he said.
She was on, I think she was on Demoreal and then on like a few episodes of Nostalgia Critic, maybe for one, maybe for a year.
I can't remember exactly and then she left and then there was the new lady, the shorter one.
She's been there for years afterwards.
This was pre-scandal or post-scandal?
I think this was pre-scandal, the not so awesome document, yeah.
Definitely pre-scandal, I think she was just like, oh god, this sucks.
I kind of want a different acting job and thank fuck, I found something, I'm gone.
Goodbye.
It's not the Dire Gentleman video, there's another video that he links by a YouTuber called LadyEmily,
called the Failure of Channel Awesome's Demoreal, that is more specifically in depth about what the series is.
There's a part where the lady in Demoreal goes on what seems to be a sort of improvised and presumably heartfelt rant
about how people don't take women in acting seriously and how it bothers her.
And so I can believe that maybe this was someone who was really serious about acting,
who Doug picked up from a, I don't know, a casting call service or something,
and maybe she was getting started and then after a while she was like,
this isn't the legit gig I was looking for when I signed up for this, I've had enough.
Which does make it curious why Malcolm is still there after all this time.
Could he not escape or did he actually enjoy it? That's the question.
I mean, I've heard people say that Malcolm is pretty much just like a normie,
like I don't think Malcolm is like an aspiring actor or anything, like he's just a guy.
I've heard he's a furry too.
No, it was, we talked about Fena and The Wall Review last week
and then I think it was Discount Gumshoe and my server was talking about it
and people were saying that the word on the street is that Malcolm is a furry
and that Doug probably knew about Fena from Malcolm.
That's like, people think that's the connection there and I don't know.
This is just what I hear.
How embarrassing, it's true.
I mean, well, I don't know.
I mean, he'd have to hear about it.
Imagine knowing Fena.
Oh, yeah, I mean, sure.
I mean, yeah, I'd never heard of this person before The Wall.
I wonder what Fena thinks about, like I wonder if being in The Wall Review
has been like a net positive?
Because like, I'm sure that tons of people would never have known about Fena.
I don't know, like there's a niche that surely would have known
but I'm sure there's a whole new audience that is aware of it.
But I think that like the number of people who, of all the people who learned of Fena
from The Wall Review, most people probably hate it.
I mean, they're...
I mean, you were talking about the Nostalgia Critic fan base,
like the people who actually watch every video and enjoy them.
But The Wall Review transcended just the fan base.
Like The Wall Review made it a wider impact than that.
That was largely not good, you know?
Yes, absolutely.
But like of the Nostalgia Critic fan base,
I think more of them than less of them would have like seen Fena
and been like, ah, interesting.
Maybe so.
Maybe going to check them out.
I wonder if the kind of person who's still like an unironic
that guy with a glasses fan in, you know...
God, when did that The Wall Review drop out?
No, it's older than that, right?
I think it was 2020.
Well, let me check.
Wait, this is crazy.
That's crazy.
Maybe it was 2019.
Oh no, it was September 2019.
Okay.
I mean, I wonder if the kind of person who's still an unironic
that guy with a glasses fan in 2019,
like is that Fena's demographic?
Like, is there already crossover there?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
He talks about satellite city in The Wall Review
as though it's just expected that you know what that is.
So, I mean, I don't know.
Maybe they had already cross-pollinated and there was no...
It could be that everyone who knew Doug already knew Fena
for whatever reason.
And only the haters now are learned of it through that.
God, it's so funny.
People with no self-awareness are so funny.
I'm so glad.
I'm so thankful for people like Doug.
It's always been a little weird,
because I don't think Doug is totally not self-aware,
but he does continue the show and the character
that he does all this stuff.
He's not 100% not self-aware.
He's like the character of the critic
is an exaggerated version of himself,
but himself is still kind of a weird guy
and that doesn't realize how awkward he sounds
in vlogs where he's talking normally.
He's sort of like,
that's sort of a cringy nerd kind of person,
but I don't know.
There's something about Doug
when he's like...
It would be hard to think of...
If I listened to Doug talk in any of his videos
for more than a few minutes, it always happens.
It consistently happens.
The one that's coming to mind is...
It's the Wall Review when he describes...
When he's like, quote,
the movie ends on such an open vagueness.
It's like a weird way of constructing that sentence
that's like, you know what he means,
but it's not quite right.
And it's just the way that someone who's not very smart talks.
It's like, he doesn't quite...
He just doesn't quite like value...
Language enough to respect its rules.
And this is a script.
It's not like he's going off the cuff
and speaking off the cuff and that just came out.
He wrote that down in a script
and then delivered the line deliberately.
That's what he thought he should say.
It's an obvious...
He was there first,
so his clout is mostly luck-based.
Sure.
He built...
And then since he's got an audience,
it's like the amount of effort he needs to put in
didn't ever really need to increase.
Yeah.
Because he got such an early big audience
that as long as I'm wacky,
then it'll work.
It doesn't need to be smart, really.
Just like the Procrastinators podcast.
I tell ya.
We got our fans.
Our expectations have been set so low.
The bar is so low.
These piggies will just keep turning up every week
and eat more slop from the trough.
Got them.
There's nothing you can do.
Hey, when it works, it works.
It's free.
It's just free.
Rent-free.
Rent-free, am I right?
We upload to YouTube rent-free.
I don't know what that means.
I mean, we're in their heads rent-free.
I mean, they think to themselves,
God, what are those guys going to talk about?
They think to themselves, oh, God.
What is this fucking show?
It sucks.
I don't like any of it.
God, it's so bad.
Clicks on your video.
Rent-free.
We think PZP.
More like Pussy.
They say it.
They say it to their friends, and they tell their friends,
and that's how words spread.
Oh, God.
You don't want to listen to this podcast.
It's bad.
It sucks.
That's right, but that's just how we get it.
We're so bad that you can't shake it,
that you just can't stop.
God, I heard like five seconds of that one podcast,
and I just keep thinking about how annoying it was,
how annoying.
This is called the PZP?
I got a complaint about it.
Hey, make an angry review of our podcast.
Make a video talking about the fall of the PZP,
and about how it's bad now.
It used to be good, but it's bad now.
And then post it on Reddit.
There are people, I forgot we have a subreddit.
I also never ever check it, but yes.
I used to look at it occasionally,
and then the other day, someone linked me one of the,
it was tectonic improv, actually.
He wanted to mention something to me,
and to illustrate his point,
he linked me to a thread on the PZP Discord server,
and I was like, oh, my God, that's right.
We have one of those.
Is it r slash the pro...
r slash the pro...
Yes, it's r slash the pro procrastinators.
Still somewhat active, believe it or not.
Unbelievable.
Wait.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
New threads every few days.
There they go.
There they freaking go.
I'm actually...
Shit.
We could read this on stream.
I mean, there's not...
Someone asked, Ben, Davoo, and Trixie,
parentheses did you used to live together, right?
Uh, yes.
Steve, Steve Nuge, the answer is yes.
Um...
Is anyone, is anyone, is anyone subbed
to best guy ever's Patreon?
Does he go into detail about the recent PZP
Canton situations in his solo podcast?
Uh, I don't know.
Okay, this isn't...
This is actually not...
This is all stuff that you could know.
If you just listened to our four hour podcast
where we answer voicemails for two and a half hours,
it would be easy.
There'd be no need.
There'd be no need to suffer through the wasteland
that is r slash the pro procrastinators.
But, I mean, you do you, I guess.
Yeah.
Oh, and I'm a moderator.
That's cool.
You know, speaking of our crumbling, dying show
where we are in the grave,
both feet in the grave, hands in the grave,
only our mouths are sticking out of the ground
and that's how we're talking.
Sucking air, yeah, sucking air and talking a little bit.
I am a little bad in medical ways.
I'm okay for this show.
Yeah, you're still sick, huh?
Yeah, the fact that I'm still sick is the problem.
I'm going to the hospital tomorrow morning
with like a...
I printed out a list of like tests that a doctor said,
you should get these tests done
just to make sure we know what is going on with you
because this shouldn't have been going on for so long.
Because I had, I'd gone to the hospital already.
I'd taken medicine for the thing
and it hasn't cleared up.
So, if this is maybe the last time you'll ever hear
on the internet, I'll die in fact.
No, no, no.
No, no, I wouldn't...
If I was actually dying...
I don't know, I think the worst thing it could be
is like diabetes out of nowhere.
Diabetes?
Because I've been like dehydrated
and being unable to keep water,
getting into my body no matter how much I drink.
That feels like...
Is that a diabetes thing?
That's a diabetes thing.
It's like a kidney thing.
I've been looking up a lot of things.
It's like, what is exactly going on with me?
It's basically been the last week.
It's like...
I got...
It sucks.
It sucks, but it's all been on my mind.
I don't want to get too scared
because you know how it is.
You look on medical sites, you say,
so I have this one thing.
The worst possible things it could be are at the top.
You look up...
My tongue's kind of itchy.
You go on WebMD and it's like...
Tongue cancer.
Brain cancer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, I've narrowed it down to a few things it could be,
but I'm obviously not a professional,
so I'm just going to go to the hospital,
say, please figure out what's wrong with me.
I don't know what to do, and then they'll go, okay.
So, are you just dehydrated all the time
and that's the issue?
Kind of, but it's like a gastrointestinal something or other.
There's maybe something wrong with my kidney.
There's something causing the dehydration.
I don't know whether that's linked to whatever's happening
with my kidney.
I don't even know whether my kidney is involved.
Dehydration causes kidney problem because if you're dehydrated,
your kidney has no...
It gets fucked up because it needs...
Your kidney has to filter your blood or whatever
and dehydration makes it less dilute,
which makes it more concentrated
in whatever bullshit it's got to do.
Yeah, the thing with diabetes, I skimmed it,
so I'm not entirely sure.
I couldn't recite what is diabetes,
but I think what it is is the water goes straight through you
without getting absorbed into the body
because the kidney is trying and failing
to do something with the blood sugar level,
and so it thinks, oh, I've got to flush something out.
There's too much sugar here.
I've got to flush it out.
You go to the toilet more often,
but the water doesn't stay in you,
so you don't get hydrated even if you drink
like more than two liters of water a day.
And that's what's been happening.
I'm dehydrated right now as I'm drinking.
It sucks.
I don't know what to do about it.
Do you take like a multivitamin or anything?
I take the multivitamin tablet thing a couple times.
Maybe I could take one out a day.
A couple times.
I don't know.
Well, I don't know how bad or good it was doing.
Maybe I should just be doing it anyway.
I mean, I feel like almost everyone
should take multivitamins.
There's basically almost no reason not to.
I guess what I was thinking is I didn't want to...
Multivitamins, they say on them is like,
it's not a food substitute.
It's like to go with food.
If I eat the right food,
it should actually clear up the problem.
If I just take multivitamins all the time,
I might be just sort of delaying something
instead of actually fixing anything.
And so I've been trying to eat better.
I've been cooking spinach and whatever.
Sure.
But if you're like, maybe before,
maybe you were eating bad
and you were getting 25% of the vitamins you could be getting,
but then you're like, I'm going to eat better.
And then it's like, okay, now I'm getting 75%.
It's like, okay, great.
But if you take the multivitamin,
then that's guaranteed 100%.
So why not?
I guess I should take it.
I mean, I'm not sure what the correlation,
the link between the vitamins and the dehydration would be.
I feel like vitamin deficiency
might result in not being able to retain water.
I don't know.
I could be wrong.
Yeah.
There's such a thing as being pre-diabetic,
which is like you're not actually diabetic,
but you're like at risk of it.
So I don't know.
It's probably good to find out sooner.
So maybe if you're in some stage of pre-diabetes,
something can be done about it.
It would be a shame if you let it sit
and you just became diabetic when you didn't have to.
Yeah, that's why I'm going to go to the hospital.
But that's basically the reason why
I don't have anything to talk about this week
is because basically every day it's just been like,
oh, I'm still ill.
God, I've got to do something about that.
Oh, jeez, I'm so weak.
I feel like I can't move.
I can barely do stuff.
Oh, I did something, but it's like 6 p.m.
Maybe I should call a doctor.
Oh, jeez, Rick.
Oh, boy.
And that's been it.
That's all I've been trying to do.
I'm just trying to exist.
I mean, I've been procrastinating
on making that dentist appointment.
I've been saying for a long time,
I've got to go to the dentist.
I got cavities.
I know I got to get them drilled.
I would like to get a whitening or something on my teeth.
My teeth are looking a little dingy.
I want to go to the dentist.
And the last time I saw my parents, my mom,
my sweet old mom was like,
oh, here's some, don't tell your father
I'm giving you this money.
I'm giving you some money for a dentist appointment.
Don't forget to schedule your dentist appointment.
I said, thanks, mom, and I haven't done it.
And I got these several $20 bills
that she handed me sitting in my desk drawer
that I promised I would use to get a dentist appointment.
And I haven't done it yet.
I promise I'm going to do it.
I swear, but I'm lazy.
And I have been, I know I keep saying this.
I know I keep saying this,
but I have been, I really am in the final stretches
of working on the secret project.
It is like, I wish I could say what I've been doing with it,
but that would be given the game away.
I'm not ready to give the game away quite yet,
but I am like, I'm on the cusp.
I'm on the cusp and I've been like,
that's all I've been doing the last couple of days.
It's really been annoying me
because this whole month has basically been,
okay, I'm a bit sick.
I should wait until I get better, try to get better.
Oh God, when am I going to get better?
And I haven't been working enough on anything.
One, because I feel like I need to rest in order to recuperate.
And other times it's just because I feel so weak
that I can't even do anything.
And it sucks.
My secret project is definitely on hold
and that's annoying me a little bit
because it's quite close to being presentable
and I can't yet do anything.
Can't yet tell anyone.
I think mine might be ready
by the time this episode comes out.
I feel like I might have said that before,
but God damn it, this time I really mean it.
This time I really mean it.
You better do it.
One of us has to have a project that isn't secret anymore.
No, I know.
Yeah, but I can't say anything else about it just yet.
Another unfortunate casualty of me being debilitated
is that I'm probably not going to be able to draw the comic
for the deadline, the Kato Anthology.
I did want to mention that I think the day this episode comes out
this Friday is the last day of April
and I think that's the deadline for the Kato Institute.
That's the deadline.
Anthology, the Kato Anthology, link in the description.
If you want to see that on the day that your submission is due.
Yeah.
On the one hand, there's like,
in order to feel good, you must set goals and complete them.
Yeah, that's true.
I should try and finish this goal I set
doing these six pages in a month.
For context?
Surely that would be doable.
In case anyone doesn't know,
it's a comic anthology that's looking for submissions
and going to submit something and it's open to everyone.
Everyone's encouraged to look and then draw a comic in one day.
Get it in by midnight. Bam.
Do it.
Okay, sorry.
I think that the best case scenario is that I go to the doctors tomorrow,
they do all the tests, they say,
okay, you have this or you don't actually have this,
but I clearly have something.
So they say, here's the medication for it.
I take it, I feel good.
And then for the rest, I can like cram,
like drawing into the end of the month.
That's like, how many days is that?
So like after Monday, I've got one, two, three, four.
Four days, draw six pages.
Ah, geez, that's quite a lot actually.
Because I've got to draw and then color them.
I want them to look nice.
I can fucking do that though.
Four days, four full days.
As long as I feel good, then everything will be fine.
But the most important thing is my health comes first.
I was kind of stressing out over getting this comic done.
And I've sort of, on the one hand,
dismissed the idea that I will like force myself to get it done.
Because at the moment, it could be bad for me to work hard.
I don't want to get worse.
But yeah, if I feel good, then I can sprint right at the end.
Right on.
I'm sure they...
I feel like those guys would be super chuffed
to put something of yours in there.
In that their anthology.
I think they're PCP heads.
I think they like us.
Oh, no.
Oh, it's true.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Actually, they specifically asked me for one.
Actually, they specifically wanted to put the white lion in there.
Which, I don't know, if you don't know, that's a comic that I made like...
God, it must be like seven years ago now.
They were like, can we put that in the anthology?
And I was like, yeah, I mean, sure.
Why not?
Why the heck not, my dudes?
So that's what I'm putting in there.
They wanted it. They wanted to see it.
And I want them to see as well.
Yeah.
And then I guess that will be concluding the deadlines on that.
And then I got to draw the cover.
I should probably draw the cover before the end of the month, actually.
And then I guess they're going to be launching the Kickstarter for that soon after.
Probably pretty soon after that.
I'm not exactly sure when.
Well, hey, I am sorry that you're feeling shitty, Gib.
That sucks. And I hope they can fucking sort you out.
Yeah, I mean, I hope so.
It was confusing because I like, at the call 111, the emergency hotline for like medical stuff,
you say, what's the problem?
I tell them the problem and they say, okay, we're going to get a doctor to call you
and then you can talk to the doctor on the phone about it.
And I did that.
I told him what was going on.
I told him how long it had been.
And then he said, hmm, that seems a little strange.
And at that point, I was like, fuck, I've probably given him the wrong impression.
I probably exaggerated the wrong thing, made him think it's one thing where it couldn't be like a contradicts.
It's like, shit, have I made an error in observing my own self and what's going on?
Because that's the biggest thing I always worry about when I go to the doctors
because they ask you questions about what's been happening.
And I don't know.
I just feel bad.
You just like stick a needle in me and call it like cured.
Like, can you just do all of it?
No, I have to be the one to give them the information.
Otherwise they can't fucking do anything.
They don't know anything about what's going on.
And then he says, okay, this seems a bit strange.
I'm not sure why this would be happening.
And then he gives me a bunch of tests in a text and I printed those out.
And I'm going to just go to the hospital and give them.
I'm going to go up to the lady or the man or whoever is at the front desk and say please.
I don't know what these papers mean.
There's just loads of words on them.
They just say test.
Just do them.
Please just do these tests.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know what I'm doing.
And then they'll be like, okay, shut up, calm down, go to the waiting room.
That's probably what's going to happen.
I get a little anxious about like doing it properly because I'm like, oh God,
what if I go to the wrong hospital?
What if they want me to go to this other hospital that's closer to where I used to live?
Because that's where my name is on record still.
Do they want me to go to a specific hospital?
Can I just go to a hospital and say please?
I have no idea how this is going to work,
but I'm sure they will be able to point me in the right direction anyway.
And it shouldn't be a problem.
I should stop worrying about it.
And you know, the best thing is I don't need to worry about it cussing anything.
That's the main thing.
I just need to be socially anxious and awkward in real life and that's the main problem.
And then they're going to stick with me.
Rub it in.
Rub it in, why don't you?
Yeah, yeah, you know, I'm just like, you know, I'm going to patch up as good as new
and I'm going to be fucking rich because of it.
They're going to give me money, in fact.
They're going to give me money.
Fucking communist Europe.
They pay you to get sick.
Why would you want to incentivize that?
We need innovation, not infection.
That's my slogan that I'm going to run for fucking governor of, I don't know,
some shithole Southern state on.
The, the, the, you know, that remind, remember, stop me if I've talked told you this before,
but remember when I got the kidney stone and I went to the hospital and then I got a bill.
They sent, they sent me a, yeah, they sent me a bill for like $6,000.
Because I didn't have insurance.
Yeah, they sent me a bill for like $6,000 because they didn't have insurance.
And then I was like, well, I'm just going to ignore this.
Okay.
No, this is not, this is not necessarily smart, but this is what I did.
I said, like, I'm just going to kind of hope this goes away.
So I didn't, no, this, this story has a surprise ending.
Well, I mean, you know, the story goes on.
Who knows if it's actually over, but I think it has a surprise.
A surprise ending.
This, so I was like, I just, I just, I, this must be a joke, you know, $6,000 for like
spending like three hours in a hospital bed.
This is like a joke.
And I think it's stupid.
And I'm just going to ignore it.
I'm laughing.
God.
So it's $6,000.
Presumably it would have been less because if I had insurance, because like the insurance
companies have covered something and also like insurance companies just have like, they
have it all like pre worked out.
My understanding is that hospitals just have like unbelievably huge prices that things
cost all the time.
But like insurance companies just have it all sort of pre negotiated that it's like
less than that.
So they don't have to pay what a normal human has to pay because it's just, and it's
just expected that everybody has insurance.
Something.
So if you don't, it's like your quadruple fuck.
But so yeah, I got a bill for $6,000.
And then I was like, ignore it.
And then like weeks later, I get a bill from a collections agency that's like, no, we're
we're fucking serious.
We got a fucking, you got to send us this money.
And I was like, um, okay, I'm scared.
So I went and I Googled it and they can't, it's not like a charging interest.
I believe it's illegal to charge interest on a medical bill, at least in Massachusetts.
It is.
So I'm like, it's not like I'm losing more money by not paying it.
So I'm just, I'm just going to ignore it and, and just see what happens because I'm
like, I don't think the situation will can get any worse.
The worst thing that can happen is I take like a credit hit, like my credit score goes down
because I don't pay this bill.
But I think that it worked and the bill is gone.
And I, the reason why I think this is because at some point I was browsing Twitter and I
saw like a, a TikTok, I think a reposted TikTok of someone asks, what is something you know
about?
Like what's a law that you know about that feels illegal or something you, you learned
that feels illegal to know.
The guy answers and he says, in America, most hot or hospitals are nonprofits.
Technically, which means that by law, they must have a charity care clause, which means
that if you are poor to a certain degree, they are obligated to give you care without
making you pay for it.
And I think that maybe I, because this was like a couple of years ago, I was making like
$12,000 a year or something.
So like very, very little.
I think I definitely was below the poverty line.
Definitely would have, if anyone would have qualified for that, I think I would have.
So I think I just technically qualified for charity care.
And probably the reason why I haven't heard anything about this bill in months is that
the collections agency in the hospital were like, if they did any digging on my finances
at all, looked at my tax records at all, they were like, oh, this guy doesn't make any money.
He's like, he cleared the bar that we like legally can't charge him this money.
I think I won.
I think I beat the system.
All you gotta do is to be very poor.
It got him.
I'm not going to say, I don't know, how do I say it?
It does make certain problems go away.
It does.
I'm not being poor enough.
Yeah, it's weird though.
Imagine if I had made like a few more thousand dollars a year.
Again, this is just what I think happened and maybe tomorrow I'll get another letter
that like this collections agency is garnishing my wages or something.
I kind of don't want to look into it because I don't want to kick the hornet's nest on this.
Maybe they're just really busy with shit and it's COVID and now they have all these claims
and I'm just low on the priority list and they'll get me in due time or something.
I mean, it's one of those things where it's like, in order to follow up on something like this,
they need people hired to do all of that digging and finding you and asking you and like sending
a tough guy around to your house to like put the kidney stone back, like shove it down your throat.
Shove it up my dick again.
Well, I mean, that's what a collection agency is.
A collection agency is the fact that such a thing exists is like humanity truly exists in a fallen state.
If you're a business, you're like, hmm, well, this guy owes me money,
but collecting on it would be work.
One of our employees would have to contact this guy.
We have all these legal, we have to send them a certain number of notices
and give a certain amount of notice before filing suit against them and that's all labor.
So we're going to outsource that labor of harassing this guy for the money that he owes us
and in return we give them a cut, basically, is what a collection agency is.
And so you would think that they'd be prepared to do that work unless there's some legal technicality
that means that I actually don't have to pay it, which means that they won't get anything
or there's just other, there's so many other claims that they think are either for more money
or are more likely to actually pay out that they're going to prioritize them over me.
I would imagine that even if you are liable to pay.
It's kind of the same principle that lets you get away with shoplifting
because a lot of the time the minimum wage employees that work at a store,
it's just not worth their time.
They're not paid to stop you from stealing.
So I think a lot of the time, even if they saw you doing it, they're not going to do anything
because why would they?
This is a principle that holds true across society.
If there is some legal precedent for like sometimes if somebody's poor enough,
you can't collect from them, that would sort of dissuade collection agencies
from following up on leads that would require money
or at least it would dissuade the hospital from paying the collection agency
that money to go and do that work if there's a chance that you don't have the money.
And they're just like, it's been long enough. Fuck it.
We've got other things to worry about.
I don't know if this TikTok is to be believed, then it seems like I definitely...
You know, the TikTok says like go to the hospital's website
and you can look up their policies and you can find it.
And I never actually did that for the hospital I went to, which I should have.
I am tempted to do it on stream now, but it would probably take too long.
So maybe I will do that afterwards.
We're not streaming, Ben.
Whatever.
Oh, but you know what? I'm going to stream because I need to pee.
No. No.
No.
I'm going to pee. I'm going to do it.
God, are you still on microphone?
Do I need to distract the audience for a while?
I'm going to give you a preview of the voicemails that are coming up.
The first voicemail this week is called Ben Gay.
So that's exciting.
By the way, I'm really relieved there's not...
Let's see. Speakfibes sorts them into pages.
How many per page? It's 20 per page.
Last week we had like three full pages of voicemails, so that was dog shit.
Fuck all of you.
I don't care about you that much.
This week we've only got a page and a half, so we've got...
I'm telling them about voicemails.
This week we have a more reasonable amount.
We're back to reality.
So that's good.
Okay.
What were we talking about?
Hospitals.
I meant to check that hospital's charity care policy, but I never did.
I'm just kind of...
I kind of just am hoping that my theory, that that is what happened, is true.
Because it would be very convenient for me if that bill just like,
eh, we technically can't make and pay that.
Eh, damn.
But damn, imagine...
It's fucked up, though.
People...
If you have more bills, if you have a house that you got to pay taxes on,
and you got a family, and you got kids you got to take care of,
and you got all these...
Maybe you got parents, elderly parents or something, or whatever it is,
that makes your expenses higher.
Such that you need like a job, like a real job,
because I don't have like a quote-unquote real job.
You need...
Some people got expenses that only a real job can pay for,
and if you are like that, you might be...
You might have less disposable income than I do,
even though you make more money,
and therefore also...
I might qualify for such a thing as this, but you don't,
because your income is higher,
even though you're maybe poorer than me,
because your money is going somewhere that you have to be putting it into.
And that is frustrating.
That sucks. That sucks so bad.
I guess it's difficult to gauge what is your disposable income,
because you can decide how much you want to spend on things like food.
You know, it's like...
To an extent.
It's like you could go out to fancy restaurants, I guess.
There's a...
I would say...
There's an upper and lower limit to these things.
I mean, I would say if you are making a choice to spend more on food
than you need to be spending on food,
then I would say that that extra you're spending is part of your disposable income.
I guess, but what is the threshold for the minimum amount of food money?
What if you just live in a place where the food is a little more expensive?
It would be what...
Well, I mean, you can't really...
Yeah, I would say it's...
I don't know.
The minimum amount of food you have to spend is what I spend.
They sell food per dollar to calorie ratios.
I wish they did.
That's how I choose what I buy.
I looked because I looked it up and I'm like,
ah, no, this pack of like three dozen hot dogs from Costco
is like the best calorie two dollar ratio.
So now what I eat for half my meals is two hot dogs and a slice of cheese.
It's good.
It's good. I like it.
Fuck.
What was I saying?
No, I had a thought.
Oh, I don't know.
Yeah, some people can make...
You can make more money, but still...
Oh, because Bernie, it's like Bernie always said,
you know, most people in America, like they can't afford a $500 expense.
And then that includes people who are like working jobs.
They work harder than I do.
They probably make more money than me,
but they also have expenses it goes to.
And those people would be completely fucked if they had a kidney stone
because suddenly they would be hit with a $6,000 hospital bill
and they wouldn't have what I hope is a genuine ability to wriggle out of it
through a financial technicality that I'm hoping that I have successfully done.
This is a real sword of Damocles right here.
For who?
$6,000 sword over you.
You're not sure whether it's there.
It's like a shrodinger sword, sword of Damocles.
You're right.
I assume it's no longer there, but if I...
Yeah, I'm like, hmm, you know, if I...
Imagine you're Damocles and you're just like,
I haven't seen that sword in a while.
No one's mentioned it in a while, so maybe it's not hanging over me.
I just won't look up.
I'm just not going to look up because, you know, if it is there,
I don't want to know about it.
Yeah, that's exactly what it is.
I will look...
I'm going to look up the hospital's policy and see if I can find it
because the TikTok said...
No, this TikTok says I'm good.
No, this TikTok says that I'm going to be okay.
Maybe look up the rule, like the law that they said in the TikTok
instead of looking at the TikTok again.
Yeah, well, the TikTok says...
The TikTok says where to look for these policies,
so I should do that.
Just?
Definitely.
Just to see.
Yes.
I mean, I guess in the way you put it,
is looking it up the policies would be looking up at the sword of Damocles
to check whether it's there and you don't want to do that.
Yeah, I mean...
But you should do it.
God.
I mean, I could...
I mean, the real look would be like...
I could literally call the hospital or contact the collections agency
to ask, do I still owe you all that money?
But no, I'm not going to do that.
No.
No fucking way.
Everyone told me...
Especially looking over your shoulder, seeing this as an assassin,
a kidney stone assassin.
My parents told me...
To sure it can up your dick again.
My parents told me, like, Ben, you got to pay that bill
because, like, you know, they're going to charge you interest
or, like, oh, it's going to affect your credit score.
But I think they were wrong.
I think I fucking outsmarted it.
They told me, like, oh, Ben, your aunt is an accountant.
Contact your aunt.
She can help you pay the bill.
She can help you get a payment plan.
You know, they'll have...
They're happy to get anything.
You can agree to a payment plan that's only, like, $20 a month or something.
And I was like, oh, okay, I don't want to pay $20 a month,
but, like, I guess if it's that or nothing, I guess I'll do it.
I think I...
And now I'm glad.
I'm kind of glad that I didn't do what everyone told me
was the responsible thing,
which is contact the hospital,
get on a payment plan for $20 a month.
I think I wriggled out of the whole thing.
I think I fucking warmed my way out of...
Even the mildest of consequences.
The furtive Ben St. so easily forgotten.
For the audacity...
For the audacity of having a kidney stone
that I needed to...
That I was in such extreme pain for that I had...
They put me on a morphine drip for it.
I survived.
I think...
The bill included things like a scan.
And I honestly don't remember them, like, doing a scan.
Like, some sort of, like, magnetic imaging to, like, see, like, is my kidney...
Is my fucking ureter blocked by a kidney?
I don't remember them doing a scan.
The bill says that they did,
and that's what cost, like, several of the thousands of dollars.
It's horseshit. It's bullshit if that's true.
But, like, that's what they said.
I don't know.
I don't know, but every time, every time, like,
one of my parents, like, brings up,
they're like, did you ever contact the hospital?
I'm like, no.
Well, I did, I did for a while, because I was at...
I did a few times to contest the bill.
To be like, I called them up and I'm like,
it says that I got a scan.
I don't think you gave me a scan.
I'm pretty sure that's a false charge.
I'm pretty sure you just, like, charged me for a scan that you never did.
Is that true? I don't know.
I could have been zonked out on morphine and they did it,
and I don't even remember.
That's possible.
I'm just gonna go with the narrative that this is a fake charge that they fucked up.
I'm gonna gum up the works by contesting as much as this as I can
before it moves on to, like, they're garnishing my wages
and taking me to court or whatever.
So I did that, and then I contested it.
They were like, okay, we'll look into it,
and then I never heard from them again.
Never heard from the collections agency again.
So I could call them up and be like,
hey, whatever happened with that dispute I filed,
but no, I won't.
I don't know. I feel like I won.
I guess it's a good thing that nobody listens to the PCP,
otherwise they'll find out if this was like a Matt and Mega podcast.
Fucking HR person, like some pencil pusher at that hospital
is like listening to this show and they're like, wait a minute,
that's that one guy.
That's that guy. I have his file right here.
I remember that voice of that Ben St.
What a, I don't know.
Fingers crossed, I guess.
Fingers crossed that I scraped by.
I don't know, man. I don't know.
You know, I got a different topic.
I got something to talk about.
I said I didn't have anything to talk about this week,
but I got something.
Maybe this is like stupid,
but I was thinking about my characters from Veilhape.
We got Pump, we got Alleyoop,
we got Siby,
and then we got Tiki,
and I was thinking, hmm,
the blue lady, yes.
Oh, Tiki, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is Sib the little purple thing?
Siby's the little purple guy, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Siby and Tiki both, actually.
Siby less so, but I was thinking about
how they are
based off of video game characters
that were themselves based off of
sort of reductive
racial stereotypes.
I was realizing that Tiki
does have a bit of a black face
going on with her lips.
And I was like, ah, jeez.
Wait, hold on.
Is that a bad thing?
Am I harassed?
I mean, she looks like a Tiki mask,
and like, I don't know,
when I google Tiki mask,
they kind of look like that.
They do.
But like, I was just thinking,
because like, Siby is like,
you know,
Inspiro, the little guys who have the eggs
or whatever and you chase them
they're always running away from you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I think that is like
an Arabian stereotype
of some kind where it's like,
ah, like the Middle Easterners
with their cloaks
and shrouds
and stealing treasure
and running around with it.
And I'm like, ah, jeez.
Like, obviously it's not terribly racist
in like the portrayals of the game.
Oh, these little blue guys
with the nasty little faces.
Yeah, the little blue guys.
It's not like a malicious, intense sort of thing.
It's just sort of like a racial coding
that has survived from times when they were
I mean,
portrayed like that in media and it's like,
okay, I liked that game
and I liked the little funny guys,
but like, I realized where it comes from
and I don't necessarily know whether it's a bad thing
if I keep Siby.
But Tiki's a little more like,
I don't know,
I don't know anything about this.
This is just me coming to some sort of realization
that it might be construed as a bit
like coded
African tribe
and insensitive with the lips thing.
I don't know.
It was like that
when you got canceled for the fucking
tweet about
how to draw
African characters
or like those sorts of lips
in anime or whatever.
The Usob tweet.
I was realizing that Tiki has those lips.
I'm like, ah, shit.
I got a redesigner, but I was trying to redesign her.
I couldn't figure out exactly
what would be the best way to do it.
I don't know.
What do you think? What do you think about all that?
Well, isn't
I mean, Tiki masks
are a Hawaiian thing, right?
They have
similar like African masks,
but
it's a different style.
This thing in my head at the time
is like Tiki totems
and also African masks
and
it's sort of Akua Kuu from Crash Bandicoot
and the Shaman from Populous
the Beginning.
Tiki.
Let's see.
Is there like a Wikipedia page
on Tiki masks? I don't even know
like what
I think they're Hawaiian.
Tiki masks are Hawaiian
but they don't look like
they're a little different.
They seem to have a lot of open mouths
like screaming.
When I Google it
I'm not sure
which of these images
are authentic
what does a Tiki mask
historically look like
versus what is
an image someone made based on
maybe like a bastardized
sort of
version that
a pop culture conception
of what it is.
So I don't know.
I mean, I feel like
the general gist is pretty
clear.
If she's supposed to be Hawaiian
and she's got big lips like
the masks and the masks
have that
I mean
Usopp is actually supposed to be
half black so I don't know
there's the
I really hate this
I really hate this whole thing.
I know
I kind of hate it as well
but I can't see it now.
I guess I'm just sort of like
I'm wondering about
the right thing to do
because like
obviously my intent was
pure I did not
in any way
it didn't mean it to be like
racially coded in a bad way
because Tiki is cool so I like her anyway
so it's not even like a negative
stereotype it's just that
she looks kind of like
the lips thing the fish lips
as they say.
I mean it's not even her human face
it's like a wooden mask
true yes
I do have a canon face underneath
so it's not like
it's not like you drew a human
with like exaggerated
you know gollywag lips
this is like a mask
from a culture
which again I'm not exactly sure
what the masks look like
native historically
well there's so many types
I guess it's sort of
mostly it's very simplified
in my drawing
but like the
meant to depict faces for various reasons
so many different types
of cultures
all over the world I think
some African masks are like
the equivalent of like the Greek
happy
and sad faces for like theater
so it's just sort of a thing
it's just like an exaggerated version of a face
I don't know
I don't think anybody
would ever have a problem with it
but maybe there's a chance
so like there's maybe a way to
to
like change her design
in a way that's just slightly
less bad or
slightly more good or I don't know
if you're a viewer of the Procrastes
podcast you should read
and then tell me what you think
of this
I think
I'm gonna
risk a slightly controversial opinion
here but I think
that maybe if no one
has been offended
that it's not worth
thinking
about how to avoid offense
I don't know unless it's like
unless you know for sure
that something would bother people
why even worry about it
and I mean usually the way that you know
that is because someone says
I am bothered by this
well I
I mean I'm going mostly off of the
the tweet thread
with the people talking about the lips
I'm like yeah I guess that is
like even if it's unintentional
even if it's like just how it is
for the record I don't
I don't think I was completely
wrong in what I was trying to say
I just think I said it in an overly
hostile way
which is needless
yeah
but regardless
the main guy, the first guy
sort of had a point and at least some people
they just
react to these things in a way
so it's like
obviously belljap is very very very
niche only a small portion
of even my fanbase has read it
so it's like
like if there were
people who didn't like it
they probably haven't just found them yet
like they probably haven't found me
I don't know
you could
ugh god
I
I just think that if there's
since I
have an inkling that maybe it could be
a problem
it's not that I
want to avoid cancel culture
before it happens or anything because like whatever
um
it's that I want to
just solve the
problem before it becomes one
before somebody finds it to be offensive
if you know what I mean
um
yeah
like I can see that it's like
it's on the level
it's on what do you call it
on the boundaries of like potentially
being a thing
it's not like I could be destroyed
by this character design or anything
I just feel like it's like
it's
what's the word?
it's pushing it
if you were worried about getting in trouble
I would say don't
nothing bad is going to happen
if you're worried about like
yeah okay
if you're worried about like is this
perpetuating something I don't want to perpetuate
then I don't know maybe
I mean yeah I'm sure you could probably
take a little bit to just to not even
remind
anyone of that it wouldn't take
it wouldn't even take that much I don't think
I don't know exactly how you do it
yeah I mean I was
I was trying for a bit and I was like
coming up to a brick wall I had like some
little ideas where it's be like
changing
the reason I drew it like that in the first place
is just because it's the easiest way
to depict a like
a lip
shape but bigger
and I didn't really think about what that was implying
potentially
but like if you look at like masks
they don't all have
I mean the tiki masks
I wasn't really going for them even though she's
cool tiki which is kind of like another thing
it was like conflating
just like oh it's tribal so it's like it's
multiple whatever cultures
just throw them all together
it's mostly a video game character thing
than it is like a cultural
thing and that's I feel like that was a mistake
well not
a terrible mistake but like it's something
I can work on to like
if I'm gonna draw from real life
culture in the future
I should be a little more accurate
with it so that it's not like a character
of that culture
you know what I mean
yeah I guess
I guess it's a common pitfall
that uh
yeah you're right
yeah I just
like imagine you're a
you're a Maori tribesman or something
and you see this and it's like
this like I don't know
Hawaiian or African style mask
and it's like oh yeah this character's name is tiki
like a tiki mask and you'd be like
oh there's another fucking idiot
there's another fucking idiot white person
who doesn't know what the fuck they're talking about
yeah I mean it's true
I really wasn't thinking about it
yeah like yeah now that I can't
now that I have a brain I could think about it
I'm like well
I should just change her just change her somehow
I want to keep her the same
mostly I like the mask
like rectangle head shape
yeah the eyes are cool
mm-hmm
maybe her name can change
I don't know whether I want to go back and like retroactively
change Belle Jape as well
because it's a little little edits to do
I don't know whether it's worth it
wait like what
like every instance of her name
if I change her name I have to
I wouldn't have to but I could go back
and like change it on the website
I don't really know what I want to bother with that
mm-hmm it could just be like
oh that was just a thing I did
yeah I mean
I don't know on the one hand
yeah I don't know
that's like
I guess I would
if you decide like the name
is different I guess changing the character's name
is one thing
that would just be just basically a big
like a find and replace job
um yeah
I don't know I'm neutral about that
uh okay as long as
as long as it's not like
oh I gotta go back and I gotta like you know redraw
this panel and redraw this panel and redraw this panel
oh yeah I'm probably not gonna redraw
yeah like that's a that's a fucking trap
that's a fucking black hole
and also yeah it's finished
it's it's not like a
yeah yeah
replacing the text is simple enough
it'll just take a few hours
for an hour I don't know
um I don't know
her full name was tiki wiki mickey mouse
which was like
like supposed to be silly
yeah and uh
like it's a wikipedia it's mickey mouse
like mickey mouse
and her first name is tiki
it's just like uh that's dumb
that's like the sort of thing you come up with
when you just sort of like uh
name uh I don't know
tiki wiki
on the one hand
I don't know
I don't I don't
say this to like double down on the idea
that like this character is a deeply
deeply problematic and offensive
I'm not trying to do that but it is
what jumps to mind is like
is that name sort of like a
ching chong ching chong ching kind of like
yeah that I was thinking
about that it's like
I was just like
when did I make that
I think but because belgium was like
I don't fucking know I'll make a comic
I guess I started drawing stuff
I put her in there because I wanted
that sort of a character
god I don't know
she had potions hell I mean if you're
when brood they were scientifically brood
ooh how interesting if you're
if you're serious about it I would
say honestly I don't know
if there's anyone like this that listens
to the show but if anyone is
like Maori which is where tiki
comes from I don't like ask if you
could find someone like that and be like
what do you think about this character like is this
does this is this like
offensive looking is the name offensive like
what could be
changed
it's yeah the
whole thing about it being offensive like I know
people will hear me talking
about this and they'll be like oh you're so scared
it's not there's nothing wrong with it
yeah just
you're just scared of the mob the twitter mob
like you're just you're just
look at look at give virtue signaling
over here like yeah it's not
I want it's that I'm I'm
I'm more conscientious of these sorts
of things than I used to be when I made it
and I'm like
I understand I understand
the process is zero
it's not
okay if I if I may if I may opine
for a moment I think what you're saying
what I'm getting
is that it's not that you're like
afraid of the twitter mob
afraid of being cancelled afraid of
backlash or whatever
and it's not that you're like oh no
I gotta I gotta virtue signal I gotta
show everyone how woke I am
by now I gotta show ever I gotta
show everyone how woke I am by erasing
by erasing this
this Polynesian representation
from my media or white people
only
it's that like
it's that you've thought about it and you've been like
maybe this characterization
to some people who know
something about it
maybe they would think I look stupid
by this right
yeah yeah I understand
it's just there's ways to be
to be more based
about these things
sure I would genuinely
if you if you can find anyone I would
I would ask someone who knows about this
stuff
I'd be curious what do they have
to say about it what is their opinion
yeah
fascinating because then I was looking
at like Aku Aku from Crash Bandicoot
and he is like even more
but like there hasn't been as much
I think I found one article
people being like
Aku Aku from Crash Bandicoot
yeah
I don't even know what he looks like
oh okay it's that guy
right it's that guy he's a
wooden mask he's got the feathers in his head
and you know
eyes but he's got like the big red
lips and it's like he does
he does if you never
if you never thought about it before you may have never noticed
but whoops
yeah could be kind of
could be kind of a
could be kind of a huh moment
so like well I don't know
I don't know I don't know I don't know I want to
push back on this I want to push back on this a little bit
a little bit because if he's supposed
to be
like a fucking eastern
what's the islander if he's supposed to be
like an islander
then like it doesn't make sense
to be like that's an offensive african
stereotype because like he's not
I mean that's another aspect of it
is the the conflation of
like different cultures just because
they are not western
which is the thing I am also doing
in this whole thing I'm like
yeah you know it's only
so based I can be I can't I can't erase
all of my faults
but like I don't know
no certainly I think
most people like most of everyone
just enjoys Crash Bandicoot and it's a fun
game and nobody cares about the idea of cancelling
a ku a ku because who cares it's just like
yeah you jump around you're a crazy
fucking
orange guy in that game
true that's what I'm
that's what I'm saying that's what I'm saying
yeah but just because
it you know
it's I guess it's just
just because nobody necessarily
gives a shit I give a shit
just because nobody gives a shit
about changing my own thing because I have the power
to do it just because nobody gives a shit
that's a funny thought
what I'm trying to phrase it
in a way that's making me laugh like just just because
nobody gives a shit that it's wrong
or something or bad
doesn't mean that I
that it's not a problem or I don't know
it doesn't mean that it can't be
fixed even though nobody thinks it's a problem
it's really just like
there's a way to be more based
that that's my main thing
yeah sure because it's it's lazy
it's a lazy
a cartoony like no
thought put into it
facsimile of that kind of a
tribal
mask wearing person
is ticky
there's so much
more nuance to the cultures that
this is very vaguely
derived from that I could put into the character
design that would be better
I think
yeah
I can't say that there's like
absolutely none
that no aspect of it is like
like worried about
cancel because like
there's a little bit there's a tiny little bit
I mean that's the spark that started it
nothing's gonna happen
the worst literally the worst
case scenario would be
someone like
someone repost it
and is like this is a this is deeply
offensive and then people
say like I am yes I am offended
and it gets spread around a lot and a bunch
of people see it they're like this
this give and take character
this give and take character so fucking
racist and then they come and they harass
you about it and the New York Times
and the New York Times
literally literally and I
don't say this to be like
actually you should be more racist because
it's actually gonna help you because it gets more eyes on
you but at the same time
no it's like it's literally just free publicity
and then it gives you
and then it get no I'm serious this is why
it's bullshit all the all the right wingers
that are all like the cancel mob is come
for another it's all bullshit because they know
they know that the cancel mob coming
for you is literally just an opportunity to
grandstand about how canceled you are
and to perform
well you have one or two choices you can either perform
like an apology and have a redemption arc and
make people like you or you can
publicly defy the
you know the vitriol you can publicly
be like hey fuck you woke mob
hey I'm conservative and then
and then your fellow morons will be like
I respect that so much like oh yes
yeah he's pretty he's defending
my western culture I love this man I'm
gonna I'm gonna subscribe to his substack
yeah it's it's it's not
I think when I say that there's a like
a little bit of me that's like worried about
the cancel thing it's not about
the mob coming after me
and saying you're bad it's about
me hurting someone in the
first place I just rather not
that have that happen ever
if somebody has like a grievance with
me or something I do that is
like I don't agree with
like there's no way that that could be
like construed as bad
it's obviously not bad and then
the mob comes after me then I'll be like
shut up but if it's like
something like Tiki like
that's kind of that's a little bit
and I'd be like yeah that is a little bit
I would just I would just agree with it
if it's a criticism like that and if
I can agree with that idea
then I think I
I think it's worth working on it
before anything happens just because I
can that makes sense
yeah if you if you are thinking
about it and you're like hmm
here's a hypothetical criticism that
someone could give me and
you know what I agree with it
I guess that's that says something
it's
like I don't know I think it's
pretty pretty obvious that
it could be a problem at some point for
some person I'd rather it not
yeah well that's it
that's that's my you know
get cancelled now I feel I feel like
I feel like you've I feel like
you're giving I feel like
you're exploring the question
in the in a
in the in the way it
deserves to be interrogated
so that's good
I guess
good virtue signal points
get mmm yeah
you're 100 damn I didn't
know Gib was so woke oh my god
but
if you get so if you get enough woke
points you get your third eye
you can start to see the the the
the blood-borne beasts all over the place
the insight finally
finally
you can start to you can start to
um
you can start to see all the offensive
racial caricatures that we erased
they all they start appearing
like ghosts they were there
all along invisible
and then I get my Zenpacto
and I start slaying them that's a whole
other thing
there's like I'm just imagining like
you you get woke you
get woke you go on Twitter you get woke
you virtue signal about
like you know whatever
and then suddenly your third eye opens
and there's just all the there's all these ghostly
just like gollywogs just like
I don't know
lumbering around just like in your in your
house
I don't know
they were just just waiting
just waiting to be discovered
oh my oh man
the ghost the ghost
the ghost of Aunt Jemima the ghost of Aunt
Jemima is there it's like now you're ready
you're ready to receive your quest
I get
my Zenpacto I go Bankai and it's
reparations that's the name of the sword
I don't know anything
about bleach
but I think it's funny
Bankai
is just like the like Super Saiyan
but Bankai
is a super sword that you what like manifest
in the spirit realm or something
Zenpacto is your like spirit
blade and it just does like a special
something or other
and then everyone's got a special
second form and it's got a different
special ability and it changes shape
or whatever
and all Zenpactos have a name
all your swords have a name
and mine would be reparations
so every Zenpacto
has a Bankai
which is like a Super Saiyan version
of the sword
you have to be woke enough that's what they do in Bleach
that's right that's how
you unlock the it
that's how you get it yes
we should genuinely
idea for a manga
it's bleach but
the way you unlock your powers is by being more
woke
whoever has the most virtue
unlocks the power
oh god there's a
there's a story there's kind of how it is in every
like hero story like you need to be
the most virtuous
courageous hero
yes you need to say
um
I think things are a little fucking bad
and then you get your
super powers well you get
no
most stories like that you get super power
it's not by it's not by like recognizing
the problems in the world it's by like
it's by like
becoming I don't know
protecting any given love interest
or protecting your love interest
oh the town is going to get flattened by
a big guy with a foot
I'm going to kill him oh I'm so
fucking woke right now
it's either about your interpersonal
bonds with your friends or whatever
or it's about your um
your like confidence
your believing in yourself
it's about
whether you have the whether you have
the wherewithal to ask the
cute girl on a on a date
I think you may you can probably
unlock in certain media you can probably
unlock super powers by doing that
yeah it's that or you're like
um you go to
demon power
you just have something
um
if you if you if you're if you're just like
I don't know is that is there any
is there any like shonen
that's like I have super powers
but only when I'm being like a completely
immoral like douchebag
like I have a demon
inside of me that gives me
super strength and lets me shoot laser beams
but only
when I am like
but only when I'm being like a
base randy and objectivist
and like just acting in my
um what's the what's the phrase
my rational self-interest
only when I'm disregarding
the the the well-being of others
I
I can't think of anything specific
but I feel like that character type
probably does exist in like a
an anti-hero there should
there should be the villain that has a redemption
arc where the power is derived
from bad things but when they change
sides they become weak for a bit
imagine imagine like use their power
remember um at the end of bakuman
when they basically just make
death note but their version of death note
is the thing with like the white demon
and the black demon um
the angels yeah their angels
or whatever I imagine
like is it called a fellow
I think would that would be a clever name
maybe that's just what I would name it
um whatever
the board game no it's called
revered yes
yes no it's called reversi
but reversi is another
name for the game a fellow so
I'm like right but but only sort of
yeah yeah yeah it's called reversi
um I imagine
that but like the the white demon
the white demon gains his power
from like being communist from
like I don't know from like
collect collective
thinking and like
valuing like like like
everyone whereas like the black one gains
his powers from like from disregarding
others will be I don't know there's maybe
maybe someone's done that before I don't know
the ultimate communist
the ultimate communist or socialist
or whatever like
super power of all time is
Goku's spirit bomb where he has everyone
put their hands up
it's literally
it's literally democratizing
the battle because like if
enough people like really want Goku
to win this fight
against Frieza or whatever because like the entire
universe is like hmm
so you're saying I can I can choose whether
I can vote for Goku by giving him some of my spirit
energy yes please
fill out the ballot put it in the mail
and
yeah it's
literally just like voting
voting with your power
yeah a good a based
a based
a based socialist base
realized Goku
he still believes in the power of
electoralism it's a little cringe
uh
is that character arcs
archetype sort of because he's like
he's a villain who uses firebending
hatred to fuel this firebending
but when he comes a good guy
he loses his ability to be
strong with fire and he has to figure out
a different way from the dragons
to firebend
like the base way
Zuko loses his firebending
when he becomes good
when he joins the good guys
he used to
just fuel it by anger and rage
and then he learns with
Aang at the dragon temple
the dragon dance to like
get pure firebending
like the the cool kind
I don't even remember that at all
that was a really cool god I love
I have a child I've been such a good show
wait does he get
does it like change his firepower
when he's like getting it
from like a pure place or something
when he's getting it from like
it's
I don't know if maybe it changes
visually but like it's more
powerful
it's sort of like the
the difference between the
I don't fucking remember
it's good pretty bit yeah
cool
hey that was a pretty good show
that was a pretty good show I think I watched
college or something
it's been a long time I've seen it
my roommate's rewatched it last year
I haven't watched it like a couple years ago
it's a good
fucking ride because it's
like obviously
starts off a little
slow with the few
filler-esque episodes
but like the
the narrative builds upon itself
like everything that happens
you know it's all part
of the one big story and the longer it goes
the more stuff gets called back
to and things that have happened
come crop up again and characters you've seen
before it's like ah
it's just been building it's like an escalating
tension
goes all the way to the end and there's no
bullshit unlike in Korra where there's
lots
yeah I never watched Korra
heard a lot of mixed things so
I probably never will
Korra's okay
but that's just the thing
it's okay in this in the universe
that had Avatar the last day and but
Korra is like a disappointment
but it's fine there's a few nice moments
there's some characters I like
a lot of them are just sort of minor
like enjoyment
like the comic relief characters
the new
soccer the new Zuko kind of
they're
they're whatever
I think Tenzin
Tenzin is like Aang's son
Aang's second son
or third son
he's the coolest
he's trying to re-resurrect the air nomads
Korra herself
is alright and then there's
some other funny characters
I remember
there was like an evil airbender
at one point he did some really fucked up stuff
in like season 3
damn that's messed up
he stole the air out of a person
fucked up stuff
it's like he airbended the air out of
someone's lungs and they suffocated to death
like dude
Aang would never do that
that's pretty good
this is new airbending
this is new fucked up airbending
it's like evil airbending
it's like bloodbending
but the air version
it was cool
say we've been going for an hour and a half
do we want to go to voicemails
yeah
I think I'm done with things I gotta say
I got
I've said too much
yeah let's just get started
whatever
alright you got them open you got them ready
I'm getting to them
okay
alright I'm here
the first one is called Ben Gay
3 2 1
go
Ben Saint more like
Ben Gay
nice
next voicemail is called
RV can still happen
3 2 1 go
hey Ben so last week you were going on
about how the void grifters can't afford
an RV because they don't have the money
well first of all you're right
they can't afford an RV
but that doesn't mean they necessarily
can't get an RV
I mean they can open a credit card and then max
it out or they can
go to a money lending service and then deal with the consequences
later I mean
it's a bad decision to end up in a shit ton of debt
but I mean
what has Yig ever been known for making good
decisions
there's a will there's a way Ben
it can still happen
you don't get enough credit on a credit card
to max it out that much
like I opened a credit card
last year
and they gave me like $2,000 worth of credit
so that would never be
enough
some people have suggested that
they could rent the RV
and I have looked into it
and RV rentals
seem to cost like $100
a day
or more so
that just seems insane
if the RV was gonna happen I think
someone would have to be buying it for them
so
are they like still having
are they still saying like we're gonna do the RV
it's funny
was that just a thing they said once
and they've just let it sit
they said it over and over again
like they said it they said it a lot
that they were gonna do they were gonna get an RV
and move into it
they are on a trip
right now
to Elco Nevada
and there is
they have not shown the vehicle
they have they have not shown the vehicle
that they are traveling in
uh
perhaps deliberately
Riley made a tweet the other day
that was like damn
the RV lifestyle
is awesome I would recommend it
but he doesn't actually say
that there is an RV
and I think there is definitely not one
but it's like
I hope I'm not reading too much into it
but it kind of reads like he's sort of pretending
that they have one
I don't know if they had one
they probably would have shown it
wouldn't they?
of course you would
well they said
in one stream they said
if we get the RV
oh we're never gonna show the RV
because then if you knew
what our RV was then people could
call the cops on us and report us
and fuck with us and dox us
which is just huge
cope
just laying the groundwork for them to pretend
you wouldn't need to
take a picture of
the license plate
take a picture from the inside
RV is just
you could take a picture from the inside
you could take a picture
out the window
you could show the make and model
nobody could fuck with you unless they knew
exactly where you were
and they could maybe call
if someone really wanted to fuck with you
and they knew
exactly where you were
even narrower than the town
they would have to know exactly what town you're in
and what part of town you're in
and maybe they could call the local police department
and be like there's a stolen RV
in this one parking lot somewhere
got em
that's what it would take
there's no reason not to show
the RV
anyway
but
let's hold aside the point because all you need to know
is
about the RV is you just need to go to
isthereanrvyet.com
and just to keep
yourself updated on the
RV status
and I'm just checking it right now
is there an RV yet? No
it still says no so there's no RV
I've staked my entire reputation on it
so you know it's trustworthy
the first time you tweeted this
I was like ah gee
this is a little far
but at this point the longer it goes on
the funnier it becomes
see
I knew that's what would happen
I said this because
they said they're getting this RV
they
last month they said they were getting it at the end of the month
this month they're saying
they're getting it at the end of the month
I know they won't do it
it's a game of chicken
how long
are they going to insist
see I know something
about saying you're going to do things at the end of the month
myself how long are they
going to keep saying end of the month end of this month
end of this month we're really doing it
and every single month that it goes on
in which I'm just over here like
hey
there's no RV there's never will be
there's even a website now
by the way Crack made the website
he's a genius
they're together in like minutes
he
and like the longer there's a website and the longer
the longer they insist upon
this one version of reality
while I am over here championing
uh
facts over feelings
the funnier it gets
so I've done this whole bit
I've done this whole bit with an eye toward the future
and it's
it's paying off in spades
it kind of reminds me of Nate
telling me in Munchy that we'll never
make
a Gay for a Day the album
we said we would make an album at Radcon 3
and it took us a long time
it took Munchy coming to London for us to record
the album
but Nate would always say you'll never do it
I don't believe you will do it
I was like cut you
you're an asshole
talking about us like that but then we did it
I think it was
was he being serious
just like you won't do it or was he like
I think it was his way of like encouraging us
to do it by
not believing
outwardly that we could
or that we would because it's like
it's one of those things that does
require a lot of effort and we
after Radcon 3 was over we were far apart
it was like how are we gonna coordinate this
I've never made an album before I don't know what the fuck I'm doing
Munchy
does not know how to sing at all
so he doesn't know what the fuck he's doing
so the only way it could exist
is if we're in the same room and we're just
fucking around with instruments
so it was a terrible terrible album
but we did do it
yeah
like I kind of
know
that by making a thing out of it
and being like there's no RV
there's no RV
there is a
they won't do
this won't happen but there is an outside chance
that maybe like it'll push them
to actually do it to just
approve me wrong which they won't
they can't do it they don't have the means
but if through some weird
chicanery they did
and I was proven wrong
I would still consider that a win
because I want the RV saga
to happen because it would be so
much funnier than
them just
than what's actually going to happen
which is they just kind of like stop mentioning
it less and less
and then
maybe one day they're like
we never really meant to do that
that was just kind of a joke that we were saying
that was just kind of a what if
we didn't really say we were
that's what's really going to happen
and that's boring and lame so I hope that they do prove me wrong
but they will
pressure's on and they're going to fold
I'm in it for the long haul
I've already won
the game
was won already
before it even began
that's my
tactical genius
ok anyway
next one is called
plus three two one
go
horrible it is
ooh I want to know
to the best of my knowledge
Nate has like never
even spoken to Riley
I could be wrong
but I am not aware of like
any interaction at all
yeah I mean even if
he had he wouldn't come on the pcp
to talk about it
he definitely wouldn't do that
he didn't want to talk about it in our like
he is nothing
zip
no Nate never wants to say anything about anything
next voicemail is called
ten dabs out of ten void chaser
review
three two one go
so I just watched the
first hour of void chasers
oh my god
well hi I assume that's how it's meant to be
consumed in the first episode of void chasers
you know I went in with
kind of pretty low expectations
but I like the concept
I didn't hate it
I'll probably watch more
so here's some of my notes
so they wrap a bit
I think it seemed like
it was tough to tell when it was edited
in or not but there were definitely
some sections that were just kind of like
music videos in the middle
I skipped those
they go to Houston
that's where JFK was shot
and they walk around there for a bit
Riley has like one joke
he tells people in Houston
that he's the
super spreader and it's just because he's wearing a cape and all
Dallas
ends with a really bad B roll section
this is like the first long section of the music
and then they spend
way too long at an Arizona rest stop
and then their car gets stuck in a ditch
and
and B says the N word
no
overall it wasn't awful but
the audio was going to fucking stab me
and I hate it
like they could do good audio
they have the equipment to do decent audio
they just don't know how to use it
so
I mean
I guess thanks for watching it so I don't have to
I know
I'm the
I'm the void critic
I don't know
I avoid it
I
I annoyed it so
you can avoid it
what?
okay
next voicemail is called call of the void
3 2 1 go
dangers
all around us
and we are acutely
aware of it
the fear that steel beams might fall
and crush your head
the awareness that you could throw your phone
out of your car window and never see it again
seeing a cop's firearm and imagine yourself
being a small child of color
so as to tempt him into executing you
the momentary impulse
followed by fear and revulsion
at the notion is called call of the void
call of the void
I had to listen to the whole podcast
to see if y'all figured that out but you didn't
so okay here I am doing this
alright love you bye
yeah okay
the thing we were talking about last time
about like
thinking about
stuff killing you and shit
I guess it's called call
is there maybe there's a joke to be made
about the void gazers there
I don't know
whatever thanks for the info
buddy
next voicemail is called incoming
transmission 3 2 1 go
eh
colonel I've infiltrated the base
security was tight
but I managed to sneak into the vents
the mission to execute
tactical espionage on
Nate's succulent boy pussies
progressing smoothly
his chambers are just up ahead
what the
I invite you
into my room
my boudoir of sex objects
that you may enjoy please
oh fuck
I don't even know who died there what happened
but he
I mean
okay well he didn't
this was not a Nate fucker
he was not there to fuck Nate
he was there to perform espionage
on the boy pussy
so I guess he
covered and he got in there
and then did Nate kill him
no I think Nate fucked him
this was a rare case of this guy
didn't want to fuck Nate
but then he had no choice
that's the trick you have to not
want it you have to play hard to get
that's the all yes it's the only way
it's the only way to capture his
interest
okay next voicemail is called crushed
joy 3 2
1 go
hey guys
it's crusher a long time listener
well you know until
Trixie decided to make the
why I should say the inward video
about 2 years back and then I stopped
but after learning about the information
that they were no not kicked off
more left angrily from the
podcast I started listening again
I gotta say it's great to hear all your voices
I missed y'all for about 2 years now
hey anyway I wish you guys the best of luck
with however this
goes thank you
thank you did she
make that video
the is that was that on her channel
I don't I don't remember I vaguely remember
that well I think
there was a video was it a rant
no no no I think
that on the studios it was
like a conversation between Trixie and Riley
about how they're like trans
black no no
but that was more recent
but I mean I don't know
this guy said it was 2
years ago so it must
have been older than that
I vaguely remember
her talking about like
I was raised in like
black schools black neighborhoods
and I grew up saying the word
so it's okay and I'm like
yeah yeah I remember that
I there's um
I someone
was doing a I'm sorry
I forget who it's someone in my discord
was doing a
a rewatch of
PCP and keeping an N word
tally
who
it was like
yeah it was um
they were just seeing who says it the most
and I think like
early on it was Nate
surprisingly was the one who says it the most
early on but then there's that
Trixie goes on like the rant about it
and she like flies ahead
of the competition
um
I don't but that was like still early that was like
within the first like you know few dozen episodes
or so so I assume the
counter has been updated since then
um
yeah I don't
specifically remember I remember that
a video about
why she should say the N word
exists on somewhere
but I don't exactly remember the content of it
um
anyway glad you're listening and glad you're having
fun
my dude
the next voice mail is called fix your server
Ben
3 2 1 go
Ben the people in your server
are unhinged
and need to be checked
there's this guy in the server
fucking Tony Tony chopper
oh wait
fucking
Trixie
this is the opposite of what I thought you were saying
by accident apologizes
corrects himself
and everyone fucking jumps down his throat
fucking oh it's not good enough
your total voice was too defensive
you know all this stupid bullshit
and then Doon Koon comes in
who is trans by the way
tries to defend the guy
give him the Ben for the doubt and they ban Doon
you need to get your people in check
because they're fucking insane
no
see
I can see why you would say that
devoid of context
but these people
like
the pro and on people have like specifically
like irritated my mods
they have like specifically antagonize them
before I don't blame
I don't blame my mods
for having
no patience with them because they have like
they have gone out of their way to annoy here
in the past so
I feel like that's an important
detail that maybe you are not privy to
but it's true
uh
yeah
no I support
I support all these decisions
next voicemail
is called where are the blue rays
Beatrice 3 2 1
go
hey so do you know if the bleep
in the weed blue rays ever came out
um no because
if they didn't then that's two sets of blue rays
a certain someone knows her fans
uh
two can't wait till she calls them entitled
and stupid for wanting a thing they paid
for again
anyway don't rebrand the show
uh
just keep going with the pcp it's fine
um
what does he mean two sets I thought the plebe in the
weed was the one
the plebe in the weed
yeah it was I mean I assume
one blue ray for all the different
seasons of the plebe in the weed they plan to
film
oh maybe
okay um
yeah I mean
I have no more to add
that was the thing we talked about is that Digi
got uppity
that people
this guy knows
but yeah whatever
yes it was it was partially about
this guy know he knows the answer
he knows the answer
that she already did all these things
and said all these things and feels this way
and isn't going to do anything about it
you'd know you don't need me to
explain this to you you cheeky fuck
um
uh
seetol from
the proanon
did personally buy
and send Trixie
a blue ray
burner
I promise
nothing will happen as a result of that
um
but it is a funny
there should be a
there should be a sister site is there an rv
yet dot com needs a sister site
is there a blue ray burner
dot com
to which the answer is yes did the blue ray
a ray a blue ray burner arrive
it did it did
so we already know
um
well wait
why would you see it
well is there proof
that they picked it up or brought them
brought it with them on their road trip like
well
how do we know Trixie has it right now
maybe maybe she sold it in the yard sale
I think okay I believe
that seetol got confirmation
from Trixie that she did receive
the
I don't I I think
so I guess I could be wrong but I feel
like
or at least that like the package was
delivered or something yeah
because there's been
not there's been like at least
one moment I can think of where like
Trixie has not checked the
p.o. box that she has for a long time
yeah like maybe it would
have been stuck there or something but if there's
confirmation then that's fine it's possible
I believe so
um
I just need to
pee again quick oh my
god
okay
I'm just you fuck it I'm listening
to the next one it's called new speed
run three two one go
calling all speed runners for those of
you who have already done
the Nate shower speed run
and are looking for something
new to tackle
the pro and on has proposed
a get banned from
bin cord speed run
simple rules don't just
blatantly use slurs
don't spam try to be
creative
to get banned from the server as quickly
as possible make sure you record it
obviously
post it somewhere
and yeah
good luck okay first
this is so annoying
um
so
this is
don't use any slurs don't spam
a few people did this they were
making sock puppet accounts doing it over and over again
they were
just spamming the chat and they were using slurs
so both of those
things were happening
I literally had to lock down
my discord because people just kept doing it
so I had to
like un
yeah
so there's no longer any active invites to my discord server
and it's specifically because
of this
and honestly
the goal
to like grandstand and pretend
that you're doing this in like some kind of ethical way
no you're an
asshole you're just obnoxious
the discord server
is locked so good job
good job
on this whole speedrun
it was such a funny joke
well it's over it's over because
you were shitty about it
not even funny
it's just annoying
stupid
that was another one about my
it was another one about my pro and on people
they were doing a get banned
from bends discord speedruns
funny idea in
concept in practice it's just really
annoying and offensive and just
disgusting and
yeah I've never really understood
like the speedrun getting banned
like I know it's supposed to
illustrate like oh this discord is
like unreasonably
ban heavy but like
if you go into any place and you break the rules
and you get banned really quick
that just means that the moderation team is on
on their game I guess
it would be really easy
to pretend that the ban chord
is just like such a like a hyper
woke or whatever just like
just like a hyper reactive like
uh step out of line and we bring the
ban hammer down kind of place
if you pretend like this individual does
that you don't spam the chat and you don't
use slurs but be honest you do
you all do you kept doing it
jokes over you ruined it
uh next voicemail
I'm mad I'm fucking mad
next one is called just an opinion
three two one go
just finished
rewatching the one piece lecture
good lecture
bad topic
I don't think one piece is a good lecture
topic it's like a
900 chapter
something manga that's better
experienced first hand
than second hand you're absolutely
I think the other lecture topics like
kingdom hearts was a great one
because you don't want to play through
the 10 different games on five different
consoles with like
25 different mechanics
to learn the story
it's long and convoluted
and written by an insane person
guilty gear
you don't want to play through the fighting game
and then you're not oh there's
canon lore and non canon lore
and we won't tell you which switch
you can play all the guilty gear games and not
understand the story at all
sonichu almost impossible
to read due to like the type setting
and like non sequiturs
and chris just deciding
this is happening now
great when it's told to you second
hand by another person
so I decided to put it out there
you guys do great work I love
the lectures
think one piece was a bad topic I think
it should have stayed on the cutting room floor
I agree
100% yeah that
was a lot of the issues I was having with
like ideas I would have
for lectures because it's like
that it needs to be something
that you would otherwise not want to
experience like even tales gets trolled
is maybe a bad idea for
a lecture because it's fun to read
yeah tales gets trolled is a
I agree yeah I agree
I mean it's
I think fewer people
I don't know
I mean I think that one is a little bit redeemed
by the fact that less just the story is
so bonkers and bizarre
someone just kind of tell it to you is at least
entertaining
one piece is like
I mean it's just
I mean it's like a traditional shonen
manga it's basically just like
relating the story of just like a good
manga it's fine
like it's fine and all it's not
imagine doing like a lecture
lecture
just read berserk
you don't need to yeah just read berserk
like the
endless war rfck
lecture that you and munchie did
I can't remember how like effective it
was because it was very like rambunctious
but like that is a perfect
topic because it's so much stuff that happens
that is hard to like
it's not very well archived
and documented that's yeah yeah yeah
not at all you would like there's so much lore
that has happened there and at this point
like there's so many inside jokes
and like references to like previous things
that like would be so
difficult to get caught up
on that's why I was like
I think yeah endless war lore
is like a perfect that's
something that is like extremely
like complicated and
difficult to get to grips with
on on your own
without someone explaining it to you
one piece is not like that I mean it's long
but I mean the lecture is
long honestly
separate issue is just that the one piece lecture
is too fucking long even if it were a perfect
topic like five hours is just too long
but yeah I mean it's a huge
as a YouTube video you can
get it in chunks I guess
I guess sitting there for five
hours was too was too long for sure
I guess I guess that's true
anyway yeah my
my risk a lecture was like it was
it's on the cusp because
Homestuck is very complicated but I don't think
I got enough
into the complicated stuff to
make it interesting
and a lot of a lot of that
you can just get from reading Homestuck
yeah
I mean
at least
I mean it's easy if you just
want to understand risker
then
yeah but it's not that hard to make I just
I just read the comic and I understand risker
and so I'm just really telling
pirates yeah it's like I think it's kind
of the same as tells gets trolled it's like
if you did if you didn't want
to read it then sure
you might get something out of
the lecture about it
it is probably better to just read it
but I can imagine someone who's like I don't want
to read Homestuck it's like
it's like it's like five thousand pages
long it's like a million pages
it's yeah if that one's like
medium medium
topic choice
but next voicemail is called
friggin
colon cooties
friggin cooties okay
three two one go
hey procrastinators it's friggin
so I realized recently that out of the 30
of us at the rad con meetup no less than
five have come out as trans girls
most recently myself
no I'm not saying that you're responsible
same for us that's one in six
there's certainly some correlation so like
what the fuck
any theories as to what's going on
and most importantly who's
next
I got
I got two words
for you
the Jews no I'm sorry
terrible
I don't even understand that's
a complete non sequitur
well that's what
that's what people say though
I mean it's the joke is like
that's what people say it's like
it's all a plot like it's all a Jewish plot
it's this
yeah that's people say it's the same
it's like oh they too I don't know
we can traditional
traditional masculinity or something
I don't know
no um
I don't understand this either
um
what's your what's uh Minerva
oh the double double cast I
think it's I think it's sort of like
yeah it's a it's a culture yeah
the Jews the Jews have
created a cultural movement
in which in which every man
now must be a woman or else be
canceled by the woke mob for the crime
of being a white man so everyone is
becoming a woman to avoid that
and this is going to destroy
the white race
clipped
yes
yes uh no I think it's
it's just because
people who
uh trans
tends to follow
similar circles
like they they they resonate
with similar topics and groups
I think the PCP
it's like it's it's sort
of uh sort of really
I mean it's for for one
comes mostly initially
from Brony culture from us being
Brony youtubers you know what
a lot of people in that culture
are you know what anyway so it's like
I was gonna say I don't I was gonna say I don't
understand it and I don't get like
why the like so many
of like the PCP
and the PCP audience are trans
but now that you say it no if I had
to condense it down to one word yeah brony's
brony's is probably the reason
why it's like every
like it brony's was
going around before
being trans was known as a thing
like I think if it went the other way
around brony the the
pony show would come up and then
trans people would but I wonder
maybe I don't know but I
I wonder
because a lot of our audience came from
the brony days but not all of it
I wonder if
a lot of the people who are trans
were also brony's
I wonder if like
I wonder if it's like the people who were brony's
are also those people
and like not so much well that's why I'm
saying it's like it's
it would have been those people and
yeah yeah yeah yeah
people like we made the PCP
we're still the same people that we were
in the horse cast we had our audience
made the PCP we made
that kind of content
Trixie was doing anime stuff so we got a lot of anime
fans in there
and you know all that sort of mixes
like it's niche cultures
sort of quote unquote
social outcasts you know not
normies
and then
there's like a base of people
who follow the PCP
from finding it and liking it
and it's just the
similar types of people
congregate to the same types of
things I think
I would imagine that the incidence of
transness
among the terminally online
is much higher than
among the general population
just for starters
for I mean I think
definitely a lot of it is just
knowledge like
exposure to the ideas because
people
thought about it if they hadn't
heard other people
I mean I think it's two reasons
I mean one I would say that
people who are less
just less
normy inclined to begin with
what's the word I'm looking for
people that are less like
normal
I don't know just less like
social outcast
yeah yeah people that are social
outcasts are more likely to be terminally
online and probably
a lot of trans people are just like
that for just various reasons
a lot of trans people like I mean I can
speak for myself and then in bronies
in particular never felt right
never felt comfortable
in my own skin
especially in
teenage years with puberty and all that
I don't know
whether that necessarily means anything
like I feel like that's a common
a common thing with trans
at least trans women
I think trans men as well
probably or it's just like
you just feel
a lot of
social unease
because the thing you're expected to be
is uncomfortable but you don't know
that there's another way to live
yet
so there's that
but then the other side of it
is probably that like if you are
terminally online
you have more exposure to
trans culture and trans people
and people talking about it
and therefore you
there are probably people who are not
very online
who will never come out as trans
who might if they were
exposed to it
maybe because they just don't know
which you know
that's what they say
people would point to this
my enemies
would point to this and be like
there it is
this is the cultural Marxism at work
they're spreading the virus
of thought that is corrupting
our
white people
but
right this is what they would say
I would characterize it differently
I would say like okay
that's one
you could call it but like
consider that this
being trans
is a
I don't know you could choose to look at it
like before
they found out about it on the internet
this person was not trans
and now they are they have been
changed or
look at it like this person
had a problem
or this person felt a certain way
didn't understand it
or like the way
but then like you know
online discourse or whatever
recontextualized the way they thought about it
in such a way that
they came up with a solution
that they would not have otherwise
which is being trans
right coming out as trans
and it's
really just like
I don't know
it's not that the person is different
it's that like a solution
or a course of action
was suggested to them
and I mean it's up to the person
whether
if that's what makes them happy right
if they're happier
if they're happier being out as trans
being a woman or whatever
then I would how can you look at that
and be like oh the world would be better
you know I'm a transphobe
I think it would be better
because they
they're doing
everyone's got to do
what is good for them makes them happy
and if you
it's not good if you just
never get exposed to it then you never
come to that conclusion
like you're not happier
for it
with regards to transphobia
I think a lot of it is just sort of
a difference of empathy
like the idea that
being trans is just sort of
changing who you are
so that you could be happier with yourself
regardless of what you end up
being or where you start
it's just sort of like doing things that
you know socially or societally
it's like
you're not expected to be like that
but now it's more okay
to try things to make yourself feel better
and it's like the end goal is to feel happier
with yourself
people who are transphobic
usually I think just don't care about
other people they care about themselves
and a lot of the male transphobes
hate trans women because
they are
they are basically
just misogynists who want women to be
pretty for them they don't care about
people
they're just like I don't find
these women who are trans to be
sexually attractive enough for me
that's why I hate them
that's why they shouldn't exist
that's why they should stay as depressed males
and it's like that's
I feel like it's just that they don't have empathy
for other people generally speaking
I mean the transphobes
line of thinking is like
okay
you see
like a trans woman
and you're like
they're like I don't know
maybe they're like I was depressed
but now I'm out as trans
and I'm happier and they're like
you
they're like you made
I don't know they think that you become
sad
you become unhappy
by becoming
exposed to
the idea that you can be trans and that's real
and they think that that is the source
of the unhappiness
versus like
what I think most people
would say is that you
you
recognize that you had something that was making
you unhappy and being trans
is something that you do
to
to alleviate it
yes and this is like a
fundamental misunderstanding
that underlies a lot of transphobia I think
I see it all the time
but I think the root cause of
the dislike of it is
the misogyny
there is like
hatred of trans men
but it seems less loud
because
I don't know just various things
well that was a
that was a rabbit hole
I don't remember what we were talking about
oh cooties yeah yeah yeah
wait I don't even remember what this
that was the voice from
bronies the short answer it's cause you were all bronies
and now your girls
get over it
okay next voicemail
is called
see see the way
see the reason why I have
definitely dodged the trans bullet
is because
I was never in it for the ponies I was only in it
for the money baby I was only in it for the clout
I was just faking the whole time
oh boy
okay next next one is called
the jelly trials
three two one go
hi PCP
jelly beaner here
I wanted to make a clarification
on the quote unquote
Ben cord raid has this been referred to
I was not making
multiple alts
and repeatedly going into the server
and also
the speed runs the first one was
Eleazar the editor of the PCP
and the second one was
Dune
full disavow
they're awful people stay away from them
agreed
I don't know who I don't know who made what
account I don't know who made what account
was there a whole thing
there was a whole yeah there was a whole thing I had
oh you were in the bathroom
yeah I had to shut my discord
not shut it down I had to lock it down and delete
all the invites because people
I don't know I don't know who did what
I don't know which individual
said what or spammed what
made accounts named what or whatever
but people kept doing
it
and it was it was despicable
it was disgusting I had to
I had to shut down all the invites and lock my server
down to stop it
um cringe
maybe maybe you had
it's I it's a funny
concept it's a funny concept
and if you had the best of intentions
when you
made the speed run
joke I get it
I'm not mad about that
I am I am a little upset about
the lengths to which it was taken but I understand
everyone is only responsible
for their own actions
and I don't know who did what so I can't really
assign blame to anyone in particular
um I did blow up a jelly beaner
in the discord about
this because I thought it was like
entirely his thing I'm sure it wasn't
entirely him doing it though
in hindsight so whoops
um but yeah
game's over discord's locked down
get fucked everybody
um next voicemail is called
uh it's an arrow it's a left
arrow okay
three two one go
the left
yes that's the
left agreed
next voicemail is called
mozilla fennekin plural
three two one go
hey
sorry about the mess
everyone knows that the voicemails are the main
content of the podcast so
why do I do a live episode with live colleagues
would be an interesting change of the form
for now anyway gotta go
I have a meeting with a mind switch
so why does that have to do with
understanding what you're saying
I got it um I mean
I mean we could
yeah I mean we've done we did live
PCPs at radcons
before so it's not like we've never done one
I think it's just the call in
feature we would need to
have a discord server for it oh wait
no we didn't do that in redcon
for we had people
we had super chats
yeah which are kind of the same
um
maybe
I don't know we'd have to set up
like a discord server we couldn't do it through
wait we did all oops all guests
I think that's
that was something wasn't it
yeah like a ton of people
it's not yeah I mean it's not exactly
um
live call ins
but it's something
I guess I guess the thing would be
is that the show would have to be live
and then we would do like call ins
this person people would have had to listen
to what we were talking about to have a relevant thing
to say about it mozilla fennekin
mozilla fennekin just wants to turn the
PCP into void gazers because
they do live call ins
um
and uh I don't
I have in the
I haven't found them very I haven't found them very
interesting live call ins
the call just goes on and on and on I like
that they're pre called so that they're like
the person just says what they need to
say and then they're done I don't need to have
a whole back and forth with every fucking
one of you freaks
um
okay yeah
sounds like a lot of work
uh next one is called
bass joker five
oh boy god I can't I can't
fucking wait three two one
go you know
Batman
you say that you're a master
in jiu jitsu
but I have to wonder
are you a master in
push it soon
that uh
um
I don't know joker
I don't know about that one I feel
I'm not laughing that one's a little
I'm not I'm not no that one didn't hit
that one didn't hit query he's lost
his luster oh no he's his first
ever his first ever flop
bass joker's impeccable
win streak
has been uh has been
sully I think it was a little
a little too strange because Batman
doesn't do jiu jitsu it is not a thing
he does
that there's no there's no like it's
true like there's no aspect of that
it's just like what rhymes with
shit and poo and the joker
says it
I I
I I bet in at least
one uh story
somewhere references made
to Batman knowing jiu jitsu because he is
like a martial artist you know okay
he grab he grapples but that
that would be more
um uh what's the word
hidden
knowledge what's the word for that
hidden hidden power obscure
uh the the
hmm
didn't he well I mean I guess
in in dark night I don't know
if they talk about jiu jitsu specifically
well I know about Batman is that he
punches guys and he's
Batman and that's all I know
those are two important facts
about Batman
uh okay
the next one is called
be autism opinion
meh 3 2
1 go
hi um I'm very very sorry
um I'm I'm the DS guy I'm
very sorry that I said I didn't care
about B but now I kind of care because I just
got to the autism debate and here's my here's
my two cents um okay I feel
like B has kind of
like
taken the meme too far
how do I even explain
I feel like I feel like she's like
uh she's
she's been in like autism
meme culture for so long that it kind of
like became reality
like yeah I'm pretty sure she's undiagnosed
if she is diagnosed and like I'm just stupid
I'm just like an idiot I'm pretty sure she's
undiagnosed it just feels like she's
like exhibiting the things
that like she knows I don't know maybe
this is really insulting no if it is
then I agree
sorry
this is
no I
I don't know I can't read minds
I can't see into B's
thoughts or anything
I mean are they saying like
potentially the
she's playing up
autism because I feel like
yeah I
that's the feeling I get is that she is that
she believes is that she believes
in it
she believes that her undiagnosed
autism is such a real
thing that she like makes it real
in her own mind
at least by sort of acting in a way
that is like I don't know
weird in a way that I think
reinforces the idea
that she's autistic or something
I don't see evidence for that
but I can see why you would think
that's possible
I can't point to any like
there's the proof there's when she did it
it's just you can't know
when I think about that I think
like that sounds right
that sounds accurate
but I can't prove it
damn
I can't prove anything
in particular but like
the word neurodivergent
is vague enough
that I feel like it fits
like Digi is not
totally normal
in the way she interacts
nobody's totally normal
we had this conversation before
I know I know but like
you can't
you can't just say like
I'm just pushing back on the idea that she's faking it
like how could she be faking
like being into this
it's more subtle than just faking
that's why I'm not sure
what I'm talking about here
I think
what I'm extrapolating from this voicemail
is it's sort of like a self
sort of like a self fulfilling
kind of like thought process
wherein
a belief
a belief or a desire
or something
to have a certain condition
creates an incentive to act
in a way that would
suggest that it's real
and it's sort of like
auto hypnosis kind of thing
I don't know
you can't just be like oh this person acts weird
this person is
different
hence neurodivergent
I mean
that's like
there could be any number of reasons
a person could have
a perfectly normal
neurology
bizarrely
I don't know because they've been
conditioned
I guess I just don't know what is the end
goal of understanding this
like if it turns out that
this is true
what would Trixie need to do
or is there anything you would have her do
differently
well I would try to act more normal
like I don't know
no I would just refrain
I would just refrain from
refrain from
giving
diagnoses
that you have no
expertise or basis for
for
giving
that's it
I mean I don't know
I can agree with the diagnosis thing
yeah okay
thank you for the voicemail
next one is called
Fena 3 2 1
also thank you for
ragging on Fena I fucking hate Fena
I fucking hate Fena more than I hate most things
in the world I fucking hate Fena
I fucking hate Fena
I hate Fena I hate him
I hate his cartoons I hate him I hate the guy
so thank you
I mean yeah
I mean thank Dan Olson
I guess for like
I mean I guess I had seen
I had watched the jar
I hope I'm not repeating myself
I had watched the jar podcast
about the Doug Walker
wall thing so I had seen the cartoons before
they don't really
talk as much about
they don't criticize the animation as much
as like Doug does or as Dan did
but
yeah no it was when Discount Gumshoe
was like there's more to this whole
he directed my attention to the channel
itself and I just went and I looked at it
and like the more I looked at it
the more I'm like
this is this is bad and it's uncanny
and it's like
and it's fucked up and I
and I hate looking at it
and I don't know
you're
I hope
I would hope that most people can see it
I
I think there's a
certain level of like polish
there's a certain level of polish on the way
that it looks that like at first glance
I think a lot of people's
gut reaction is to think that it is like
professional it has a certain
veneer of professionalness to the way it looks
but like the more you
look at it the more you start to be like
something's off something is
weird and I can't quite put my finger on it
something's bugging me about the way the stuff
looks and then of course like
the dialogue is all is awful
you know of course
that's
anyone should be able to see that
unless you're like an unironic Doug
Walker fan in the year of our lord
anyway
fan is really funny fan is really
very good
love it next one is called
welcome to the underwater world what kind of
creature are you
three two one go
oh god
has this something from before
I
be a dramatic organ
I mean
if I could choose one I would choose
I mean probably something
that lives a really long time and has few natural
predators like blue whale
or something I'd be a brain eating
amoeba
awesome
I would be a
a krill a single krill
in a in a cloud
or a yeah
I've always loved sharks
so sharks are cool
I really
like
I do really like Nautilus's
just because they're so like weird looking
like you look right at them and you're like what is
going on with this thing like what
why is it shaped like that
so I'm tempted to say Nautilus
Nautilus
yeah
I mean
oh yeah yeah
the thing that's like a pokemon is based
off it
yes um
which I think so
I don't remember which pokemon
uh yeah
wait
which fucking pokemon is it
it's got like a oh god I don't
just type in Nautilus pokemon
yeah that's shellmet I think
a little bit or
no
it's a little cross between shellmet
and omenite
no it's not no not
shellmet shellmet is a bug omenite
yeah yeah omenite is
I mean omenite is more of a
does a Nautilus have a shell
I think it's that hard back
thing is like the exoskeleton shell
thing
like he grows it
no yeah it is
uh yeah
no omenite is basically a Nautilus
you're right
I like these but
I think they're probably like not
good to be
like they don't do anything and they probably don't live very
long and they probably are
easy prey they look
they look pretty useless
no I'd probably go with a blue whale
or whatever kind of whale lives the longest
wait I would be
the funny cute like
youtube thumbnail clickbait
cute
squid or octopus these funny old guys
um which ones
I would be an adorable
uwu little tiny octopus
um
wait an adorable
uwu little tiny wait where'd you
post it oh
are those actually its eyes
I think so
they they almost
look like they almost look like fake
eyes like like that a moth would have
on its like back to like
scare predators
maybe I mean I know like
um octopi have
like human-ish eyes
this guy looks a little strange
a little too anime
a little too uh
rockly the the eyes though like
yeah they look anime because like the eyes
are not like round they're like
kind of globby
shaped like why
why do they look like that
hmm
oh yeah here's a here's another one here's the
I
god damn it it's not loading I'm like scared
I'm like scared to look up like
pictures of sea creatures because some of them are like
actually like alarming
and like make me panic
uh true but like
these guys are cute the little
little squeaky squeaky
like scared
um like
fluttershy octopus
I have I mean I've seen like
lists that are like a fucking orange
the size of a tangerine it looks
like a little creamsicle
that's that's pretty cute I like that
um no I've been I've been looking
at like lists of like scariest
sea creatures and I'll like I'll scroll
I'll scroll down I've done this before
and I'll scroll down and I'll pass
one that is like so
scary that I actually like panic
and I have to like
look away from the screen I have to like close
the thing because like I can't
because it's like
it's causing me to
I don't even want to like I don't even want to look
them up because I I've had this reaction
before and if I look them up again I would
have it again and like
they're just they're just like the worst things
on earth oh
oh even before I scroll down I see
I'm seeing some
what the fuck
it's the it's the it's the
many many
thin teeth
thing yes that's going on
a lot of the time
yes they look
brittle but
dead
I got it again yeah they look dead
they look dead
I just
I I I I I
scrunched my window up really small so I
couldn't see any image results
and I typed in scariest sea creatures
and I just scrolled down ever so slightly
just to see like the first four
image results and just one of them was
like I don't want to look at it I don't want to see it
no no thank you
and I'm closed the window and I'm never going back
it's a fuck it's like
an undertale like creepypasta spooky
design like wouldn't it be
fucked up if there's blood everywhere
on Sam's
it would it really would though
huh
it reminds me of
like those creepy Garfield animations
where Garfield is like
is like a Cthulhuid
beast that is terrorizing John
and his dreams and he's actually like a weird
a weird Lisa-esque
monstrosity yeah yeah yeah
I know what you mean those those are so fucking
scary and cool
have you seen that have you seen that
Ed Ed and Eddie
cartoon where like the
Ed's are like all like cultists
and they're like snapping the
jawbones off of the other kids
and like making
a big ball of jawbones
so they can eat the jawbreaker
because it's a jawbreaker
yeah they kill the other kids
by snapping their jaws off
I've not seen that that sounds
a little spooky it's a little creepy
it's a little creepy yeah
it's a little spooky if you want to get spooked
where was I
oh yes um the next yeah
blue whale blue whale for me
next one is
alt-right propaganda
this is exciting three two one
go
Howdy
about the shoplifting thing
I understand you know
if you shoplift from Walmart
right I know what he gets hurt
it's a victim who's crying
however I don't know
if this is just a southern thing
but
people who work retail
are held responsible for the
shoplifting so even even
Walmart especially in say
gas stations
I worked at a Walmart for
a while and
there was a
shoplifting epidemic
on the level of Ben St. walking in
to a Walmart
and I got fired because I did not
see people shoplifting
but they figured it out
victimless crime
more like victim is dying
what
I don't get it um
okay
I
am like
I don't know how fucking gas stations run their business
right
but like
I am pretty sure
I am pretty sure that that is should be
is and should be like a labor violation
I don't think
I mean maybe people do it
but I don't think you're legally allowed
to like fire your employees
because like
a shoplifter stole something
well I can
believe that it's not legally allowed
but I can also believe that they could
come up with some other reason
to get rid of them
if they felt like they were slacking
during their shift
they've got stolen
like I can imagine it also does happen
why would I mean
why would you think
I mean is the I mean
if you're a boss I guess you'd be like
hmm my employees
are too lax
about this shoplifting thing I need
to hire a new team
that is like
gonna give it a more of 110%
that's gonna be like more
active about preventing shoplifting
or something I don't know
maybe
it probably does happen
I'm sure it's happened before
but it's just
it's just like a doomed I mean
the problem there is the boss
the problem there is not the shoplifter
the problem is the boss who thinks that they can
just cycle through employees
and hire people to do
work
outside of their pay grade
and IE
apprehending shoplifters
like that's not in the job description
of like a Walmart floor employee
and it shouldn't be expected of them
so I understand
I understand that this consequence
might occur
but I would I mean I would put the blame
at the boss's feet
not the shoplifter
yeah
there's like there's a greater evil here
next
this mail is called
hypotheticals
3, 2, 1, go
you know I've been listening to the
procrastinators podcast for a while now
and Ben's saint guy is always
going on about these hypotheticals
well
Ben, what if I hypothetically
put my dick in your ass
huh
would you come
would you? yeah
I guess
that's how it works right
the dick touches the prostate
and that's and game over
you're gay
she
yes
answer yes ok next voicemail
voicemail investigative unit
3, 2, 1, go
hi Diane this is special agent Smith
of the voicemail unit
called in
with a few startling
bits of
evidence
we've run voice samples on a few of the past
voicemails
and we've got some shocking
some shocking findings Diane
no
don't I don't want to
episode 257 drama
about
one hour 36 minute mark
we have a caller
that is very excited
about the civil war are currently happening
voice analysis shows this
caller may in fact
be endless chess
on episode 259
at the 2 hour
41 minute mark no explanation
we have a caller
very excited about her 3DS
we
we can say with almost
entire certainty
that this caller
is so rancher from the loudest podcast
we will continue to collect evidence
and work our way
into making arrests
bye Diane
I miss you dearly
I'm a little curious
about the one he said could be endless jazz
because I have no idea why there's no way
fucking voice mail into the pc
there's no way Jesse would ever make
a voicemail
it's impossible
I don't know if the DS
the DS person was the same one
okay they were the DS from earlier
they called him this time too
I mean I've met so rancher in real life
and talked to her I honestly
it could I don't know it could be her
if it was her would I know
I probably wouldn't
I don't know
it's her in fact yes it's canon
it's canon
uh well
okay well
I hope that we put those fucking criminals behind bars
next one is called
oh god there's a bug
I missed it it's a little nat
little fruit fly fuck
next one is called Ben screen this one
um no I will not
three two one go
hey Ben
um two quick questions
you said last week
that the brony lecture was going to be
the story of how you guys became friends
partially was that like
actually a big part of it
or is it just you guys became friends through brownies
it partially touches on the formation
of the horses that's something I've always
been kind of curious about
and would love to hear the details of that
so like
do that as like a topic
kind of thing please
we've talked about this
also
I don't remember
what my other question was
yeah we've definitely talked
about the formation of
our stupid group
before multiple times
the lecture
it talked about like the formation of
the um
the brony analysis community
in general but you know special
emphasis was placed on the horseshoe crew
and us forming the pcp
because that was a whole you know obviously
she was like more privy to that and that was
central to her experience of it
so yeah it does go into that
if you don't know analysis community
uh there was there was
Trixie
um and I think
Jesse had made drowning in horse shoes
or or like a drowning in footwear
video where he dressed up as
Colt Corona
for that one thing
um Tommy Oliver
well they were they were all
Tommy and Trixie
were like the first
of our group doing it
it became famous and then it was
uh t-bap give and take
uh drowning in horseshoes
came up around season 4
at the same time
making similar sort of an analytical
content
we noticed each other we all preferred
each other's content over
like the rest of the community
we all had we all had the same
we all like had an attitude
about it where we didn't take it too seriously
and yeah we were
like we were fucking around and we were
silly and we were self-aware and a lot
of the other in the brony community
of the analysis community were like
not as
self-aware or just generally
more brony
than man
more brony than me yeah yeah yeah yeah
so so we
we just you know
senses of humor were like ah that's
you know this guy's got funny jokes in their
video mm-hmm something like
that yeah that's that's the that's the
short version um
next voicemail is called strong
opinions 3 2 1
go oh
my other question was do you
have any strong opinions
on goat sea I was inspired
by the gay and the asshole guy
I love it
it's great and it's it's it's
it's uh we should have that guy on the
pcp
next voicemail is called Ben
read one piece please 3 2 1
go
okay great
well now I'll never read one piece just
despite you
okay awesome
next one is called to those owed
raise 3 2 1 go
so this is a message that one
guy had told Ben not to tell Trixie
that he's mad at her about not getting his
blue rays mm I just gotta say dude
you fucking should be mad and you should let
it be known that you're mad
you put down a shit ton of money to make these
blue rays happen I agree and now she's going
around calling you entitled for
wanting the fucking it's a completely
legitimate thing to be upset about she shouldn't
just get away with it you shouldn't let her
off the hook because she's quote-unquote
going through a lot
Trixie is a woman who is almost
fucking 30 she should be
able to fucking handle it
um
fucking don't simp for her demand
your fucking blue rays or demand your money back
I love you voice voice grail
voice grail
I will say true
to that I don't know about voice grail
I that that I don't
know if that guy who
messaged me said that like
it was because Trixie's going through a
lot but like yeah I
have seen some people share the sentiment of
like oh don't criticize Trixie
she's going through a lot she's transitioning
and like yeah true
on the one hand true but on the other hand that
kind of stuff is like that's your fucking
responsibility like
it's you're responsible for your own
shit like if you if you made
a if you made a promise
or an agreement beforehand the fact that
like oh you've you've discovered
that you're trans and you're going through that doesn't
like alleviate any of that at all
yeah like it's not it's not trans related
what like it's it's not
a trans related thing if it's like
oh I promised I would make a video
saying I am a man and now I'm trans
and I don't want to release that and just like
I you know what I don't worry about
it um that's a strange promise to
to have but like
trans doesn't mean your promises
other than like other things
don't need to be
uh yeah honored you know
they don't they don't
it's not like
yeah it doesn't
absolve you of doing work
yes okay
yeah all right I think that's
I think that's
pretty clear
uh okay next one is called
I forgot the thing
three two one go
oh and I forgot to add
PCP forever Tom will never die
call me back
PCP forever
Tom will never die
uh
yeah Tom will outlast us all
it's it's it's canon
next one is called
Bleachfan17
three two one go
is this
do you recognize this
it's a song from the OST
yeah
okay
if it rusts
it can never be trusted
if its owner fails to control it
it will cut him
yes pride is
like a blade
leech volume 8
the blade and me
wow
that's so deep
it's true though
just like
if it rusts
it's not true I disagree
because
you know what can rust
is iron
the iron
the weight on the bar
the weight on the bar in the
squat rack that can rust
but you can always trust the iron
the iron never lies to you
god I gotta start working out again
I'm so fucking pathetic
I'm such a fucking pathetic little man baby
yep with my little body
that only moves normal amounts of
true true
um
it's it's time
it's warm again I can go back
to my basement without suffering
next voicemail is called
little Christians running to
megalovania
one go
so my my my dad
is a gym teacher
at a small christian school
and
for the for running for
he has music play right
and so then he has like you know
christian rock whatever
he thinks of my childhood
and uses that as a basis for what music to play
so like you'll hear like
smooth mcgroove legend of
zelda tracks going on
you'll hear like children running to the
fairy fountain theme
it kind of echoes through the school a little
and not only that
but I thought this was a
this was my time snatch opportunity
I told him
to use megalovania
and it happened
in this small christian school
on almost a daily
basis you can hear megalovania
playing through the halls
as as as children
from from pre-k
to senior
in high school and they must know
they must know what it is to run to megalovania
things can look bad in the world but
this shows that there can be true happiness
unfathomably based
unfathomably incredibly based
god levels of base right there
a lot of those kids must know what the song
is
definitely some of the older kids
if it's just children
who are going to have memories of that song
and they will eventually discover it
it would be way funnier
if it's like little kids
if it's like teenagers
I think a lot of them would be like
why is the gym teacher playing the
undertale soundtrack
so good
okay next one is called
fiddle me dittle baby
three two one go
konnichiwa
this is samuraisama
the mighty
aryancy
kawasaki samurai
kiyoto ninja
and mistery tea
prepare
first attack
on nobeno sento san
traitor
of nipo
we plan to battle
proto
write down
on noscroll
then nobeno sento san
steal
battle scroll
fuck you
return the samurai
ninja tea
battle scroll
okay until next time
sayonara
were they going to battle
each other
or were they all going
I think they're saying that you stole
mister tea's battle scroll
they wrote
a battle plan
on a scroll
and
so okay
but I stole the scroll
before they were all in alliance
against me because
they have allied against me because I stole the scroll
so when they wrote the battle
plan they were enemies
so they must have been
it must be battle plans for them to battle
each other
or you like individually
no no because I was in alliance
I was they trusted me back then
this is only when it was stolen
only once it was stolen that everything changed
they desperately want me to return the scroll
they've allied with each other
so that I'll return the scroll so they can fight each other again
no I can't
I have to keep it to protect
I have to protect them from themselves
I'm saving lives here
I see
hmm
the plan has backfired
I'm more resolute in my scroll hoarding than ever
next voicemail
I think it's the last one
is called slash everybody
slash wants to rule the world
three two one go
on the previous episode of the podcast
Ben and Gimper arguing on
DG's self-diagnosed autism
and
the conclusion they all came to
was essentially that
if a metal professional did not
diagnose
then at best it can be called
in the question of what it is
of that diagnosis compromise is the word y'all used
and I as a transphobic
alt-right fucker
I have to ask
can this not be applied to both
and DG's transness
I can't speak
for give and take
but I feel as if
because DG had not sought therapy
or anything involving her issues
I wonder if
there's another
her gender dysphoria
is not valid because
not a medical professional
the
being trans is not a
being trans is not a diagnosis
it is not a disease
it is not like a medical
like
issue that is like treatable
it's like gayness
like you can't
it's not like a disability to be gay
it's just sort of silly
it's like being gay
yeah no you can't
you can't be diagnosed as trans
being trans is something you
I guess
decide that you are
they do annoyingly and a lot of institutions
have like
people to diagnose transness
so that you can get
like the
hormones that you would need to transition
because a lot of
medical institutions are a little
I don't know
they're unsure about it and they haven't updated in a long time
even though the medicine
the knowledge is there
but it's just like the bigger
not all the doctors know
it's just only specialists do
and you always
haven't caught up yet
okay
correct me if I'm wrong
gender dysphoria
gender dysphoria is literally
just that you feel bad
about your gender
basically
I'm not like an expert
okay
I think
someone can correct me if I'm wrong
it's not like autism
you can diagnose yourself with gender dysphoria
because the only criteria for having it
is do you feel bad
and if you do then that's gender dysphoria
right?
I think so
essentially yes
I want
I hope that this question
is asked in good faith
I mean
I think the alt-right
maybe would be exaggerated
a little bit but not too far off the mark
so I'm a little
little sus about this guy
I'm open to discussing
this if people are genuinely curious
because
there's a lot of stupid
assumptions made about
being trans
and it's like
it's not a
it's not untrue
if it's not diagnosed
gender
is a
you can't diagnose someone's gender
it just doesn't make sense
gender is a thing that you
choose
or that you choose to be
or you
yeah right
gender is a role that you
choose to accept
society
that you live in
dictates what
men do and women do
and there's gender signifiers
that you can
ascribe to
and some you might not
mix and match you can do what you like
and gender
dysphoria is where
the gender that you are told to be
usually just based on your birth sex
is something that you don't
want to do
and you want to do instead do
something else or the exact opposite
you know the other gender
in the society
in which you live
the gender part of it
is based a lot
needs a lot of context
and because of that it's not like a brain
thing
I mean it's a problem
that you feel
that you don't
feel comfortable
doing specific things
but like the exact science of it
I'm not entirely sure
but you can tell when you're upset
you can tell when you're upset
I think it's easier to tell when you're upset
than it is to tell whether or not you're autistic
but you know honestly I'm not even sure
I don't think
somebody experimenting with their gender
is like an invalid thing to do
whether or not like if there's
some medical
diagnosis that is like
yes you have gender dysmorphia
or gender dysphoria or whatever
I don't think it's wrong for anyone who doesn't
have that to try to do any
gender stuff if they feel like it
there's like no reason for it to
be considered wrong
to not be diagnosed
for that
to do whatever you like regardless of
whatever
again I'll give this guy the benefit
of the doubt that he asks his question in good faith
but this is the same kind of
reasoning that you can use
to invalidate trans
people's gender when you say
oh but you weren't diagnosed
with dysphoria
you need a doctor's diagnosis
to prove
that you have dysphoria
you can't prove that you have dysphoria
it's like do you feel bad
and like I don't know to be like
oh no you don't have a real gender dysphoria
it's like well what are you saying
anybody who goes around saying
I'm saying I feel bad
and you're saying no you don't
you can't prove it you can't prove that you feel bad
it's like well you're right
I can't
anyone going around like deliberately
dead naming someone because they haven't got
a medical note for them from their doctor
saying I should
treat you the way you want to be treated
I should not upset you
like that's stupid
it's sort of equivalent of saying
please don't annoy me
could you stop being really mean to me
and somebody saying
well I mean the police haven't told me that I can't
be annoying there's not a law against it
shut the fuck up
you're a piece of shit
the word for this is trans
medicalism
and it is a kind of stealth
it is a kind of stealth transphobia
that disguises itself
as an interest
it disguises itself
as an interest in facts
over feelings
well
sorry to use a confusing word just
but it misdiagnoses
the issue
by assuming that gender is a
medical condition
which it is not
it's far more
it's a social construct
well it's a social
it's a social condition
not a medical one
sure right
treat me please so that I don't
feel terrible please don't
bully me
please treat me
with respect is not like
something you can say
do you have a note from your parents
saying I can't bully you
saying I shouldn't
respect you
it's never an excuse
for transphobia ever
okay
well I feel like we have
I feel like we have blown the lid off
of this one we have blown this story
wide open what a scoop
and that's the last voicemail we did it
Patreon.com
slash the pro-crastinators
for bonus episodes
oh we have got
that we have got another behind
the scenes cut content
clips bonus episode coming out
soon I don't think it's out yet
but I believe he says he's got enough material
so that will be dropping soon
five dollars gets you that
and all our previous bonus episodes
of which there I don't even remember how many
um and
oh god I for fuck
I forgot to make minecraft
membership
Patreon
I'm gonna do that
do that tonight
I'll do it soon
but I want to work on my project
but I said I would do the
minecraft thing
do the project
I'm your boss and I'm saying do the
no no the project do the minecraft thing
you said do the project
no you're fired
I'm gonna work on the project
too many people have been
stealing
too many people shoplifted our bonus episodes
yes and you're fired now
they've been sharing them
they've been sharing them on file sharing websites
they've been sharing them on kaza
anyway
spend us a voicemail
at speakbub.com
but not too many
because this episode is long
they're also long
do people want them shorter?
no I don't think people want them
shorter
they can always just like
stop when they get bored
which is immediately
unsubscribed
just like yig studios
if you don't like our content you should just
unsubscribe losers
if you don't like our content you should go to
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
and pledge five dollars
and pledge five dollars so that you can complain to us
there because that's the only place we're gonna listen
yes
okay
I think that's it for today
see you next week
everybody
love you
goodbye
you