Welcome to the PCP for all your game and developer needs. Game and for you.
There were bells, do do do do, but I never heard them ring. No, I never heard Elden Ring.
Elden Ring.
Hit the Takamizaki.
Elden Ring, soon it will be Elden Ring.
Oh, let's go then.
Okay, let's go. All right. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Welcome.
The only podcast where we didn't play Elden Ring.
We didn't play it.
Sorry.
No, we're not sorry.
Call this episode cool.
It's cool because it's unusual and mysterious and exotic to have not played Elden Ring.
What if we called this episode Elden Ring and we just talk about Elden Ring as though we'd
played it just based on things that we picked up from the internet and pretend that we know what
we're talking about?
I mean, it would be so easy because Elden Ring is Dark Souls again, but there's a horse and jumping.
It's Dark Souls. Is there jumping? I know it's Dark Souls. It's Breath of the Wild Dark.
Can you climb stuff? Can you climb up walls?
No, no, no. The jumping is like Sekiro jumping. You just sort of go up and down.
I didn't play Sekiro.
I didn't play it either, but I saw it.
But like, I was like, a lot of games come out and it's like, oh, no, no, no, no.
Don't spoil. But like, what the hell could I be spoiled for with Elden Ring?
There's Dour Knights and Sad Castleman, and they're like, this is so bad.
And then you kill them, or you don't, and you get experience points. There's nothing to spoil.
I know exactly what it would be like. It's just a lot of it, you know?
I know that if you hug the lady, you get an HP debuff, but you should do it anyway
because it's the right thing to do or something.
Why'd you get a HP debuff? Is she poisonous?
I think she might. I mean, you know, having expert on the game that I am, I believe she's
like a demon or something. She's some kind of, she's evil, but like, you should do it anyway
because it's like a moment of like human connection in a video game, and you, the player,
are a virgin and you want that. I'm going to roll a Sigma as my class.
It really, it really makes you think about Ludo narrative dissonance.
Yeah, yeah. You have a play, hey, you have a play Ludo.
Is that a card game?
It's, I think it's a game with a popping, like a little dome with a popping like dice in it.
Like trouble?
And you click the thing and it's like, you got your color pieces.
No, I don't know what that is.
I think, I think, wait, I think they might call Ludo trouble in America.
You have little colored green, yellow, whatever. You've got to get them all the way around the
board and the back into your thing. And if somebody lands on your space, you get sent back.
You have to roll a six to get them out of your starting position.
It is, trouble is derivative of the Indian board game Ludo.
Okay.
But is Ludo derivative of that or is it?
This is now the Ludo show.
Ludo is a strategy board game for two to four players.
The players race their four tokens from start to finish according to the roles of a single die.
Okay, it's very clearly the same game.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Nelly.
Oh, you're seeing what I'm seeing?
I'm I, are you seeing this far right propaganda?
I haven't had a board like that. I had like a circular one. I guess they changed it.
We have to return to tradition.
God, cancel culture strikes again, cancel culture strikes again.
They took the swastika off my Ludo board.
Wait, where's my Ludo?
Where's my Ludo?
Give me back my Monji.
I want my Monji, bro.
They're all, they're all this like, they're all the symbol, the funny symbol.
Ludo UK, let's see if there's a different one.
No, no, they're all the same.
Oh, whatever.
I could swear there was like a circular one that we went in a spiral instead of like,
like right angles.
Well, never mind.
Yeah, we can no longer play this game because it is all right.
And therefore we will be corrupted and instantly become racist by playing it.
I agree.
That I couldn't have said it better myself.
Trouble is just that, but they put the die in a little bubble that you got to pop
and it flops around.
And I think there's fewer, fewer spaces.
Yeah, yeah.
Man, the whole, man, the whole gimmick of trouble is, is literally just
that the die is in a little bubble that you push.
Okay, I guess I had trouble, but they called it Ludo in the UK.
Whatever, fucking, fucking names of things.
Do you, they call it soccer over here.
They call them, they call them biscuits, you know.
They kick the biscuit bowl in the soccer field.
Do you ever watch, do you ever watch a movie called, oh fuck, was that movie called?
Like pick any movie that I know the name of?
No, there's a, but was one in particular.
It's, fuck, it's based on a comic.
I didn't know it was based on a comic.
Spider-Man.
No, it's about, it's about an author.
It's about a, it's about like a, it's about like the main character is like a struggling author.
Tin tin.
And, and like the bad guy in the movies is like famous author dude and they're, they're in England.
And there's like a romantic triangle and a spoiler.
Like the movie ends when the evil, rich, famous author gets like, I think he gets like crushed
to death by like a stampede of horses.
Fuck, it's called like, um.
Idea of what this is.
It's not Notting Hill.
It's not Bag End.
It's uh, it's the furry movie.
Fuck, movie based on a comic about authors in England.
I bet this will find it.
No, not V for Vendetta.
No, not Sin City.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Um, the, the, the real life exploits of Sir Arthur Conan Doyle and his real life nemesis,
Moriarty, who's real.
I saw this movie, uh, someone just put it on one time and uh, I watched it and I was like,
that's pretty good, I guess.
Do you remember any of the actors from it?
No, because they were British actors and none of them were like big stars.
Um, I was just surprised because I learned like years later, I saw the comic book version.
It's, it wasn't like a comic book comic.
It was like an indie like graphic novel and it's just not the, not the kind of thing that gets,
not the kind of thing that gets uh, it gets a movie, it gets a movie adaptation.
Yeah, I'm, I'm looking through these Google search because I really just want to say the name.
Uh, I'm going to lose my shit when I, when I find it.
I read this cool, um, graphic novel slash document, uh, like biography of this photographer who
went to like, um, I think it's just called the photographer and it's like half pictures of this
photographer's expedition to Afghanistan.
Oh, Over the Hedge was based on a comic book, that's weird.
Over that, uh, Dreamworks or I think it's Dreamworks.
Um, and it's like, he, he's like a photographer for this expeditionary force of like,
um, medics who go into help people regardless of affiliation.
They just go into like a war-torn country.
I think it was Afghanistan or Syria or something.
The fountain?
What the fuck?
And it's like, it's photographs that he took and then like illustrations of explaining the,
you know, like comic book, like sort of tinting looking.
Really good, really good, cool story.
Real life.
The photographer.
The photographer never heard of that.
Graphic novel.
I recommend that one.
I did, when I was, when I was on my kick of watching, uh, movies about people that just
talk, someone recommended Ghost World, which I did know was based on a comic book by,
not David Klaus, uh, fuck, who's, no, maybe it is by, by David Klaus.
Ghost, I don't know, it's pretty good.
Ghost World, film, uh, Scarlett Johansson, based on, yep, yeah, Daniel Klaus, not David Klaus.
Yes, the guy, same guy who, uh, who, uh, Cheesy gave me that comic book of, which I really liked,
uh, David, David Boring.
David Boring was the name of the book.
Daniel Klaus was the name of the, of the creator.
Um, I am going to perish searching for this, uh, it's, how many, how would you describe what it
looks like?
The comic, the comic book looks like a, it's very like, it sort of has like a very kind of
Euro comic drawing style, sort of like, like Matilda or like a road, road doll book illustration.
And it's, and it's not, it's not in panels.
The pages are text, but with, you know, sort of like illustrations, sort of in little
pockets, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, yeah.
So it's, it's almost more of an illustrated novel, but it's, it's illustrated enough that
it's basically a graphic novel, not Persepolis, a ghost world, not The Invisibles by Grant
Morrison, not From Hell.
I'm, okay, I'm, I'm looking for, like, I'm looking through art, love and rockets.
Okay, it's, it's this kind of thing.
I'm in like a, a, a, a, I'm on an article, The Rolling Stone.
Oh my god.
Graphic novels made into movies set in England.
I just remembered because there's a line, because the British comics adapted into film,
because they're, they were the, like the shitty douchebag author.
The, the main character is an American guy who's living in England and he like mentions cookies
and the, the douchebag is like, we call them biscuits here.
This guy fucking sucks.
But wait, we have cook, oh, whatever.
Do you have, are they different?
We have cookies, which are the, we call it, like chocolate chip cookies are cookies, but
other types of cookie are, we call them biscuits.
Like the default, like nondescript biscuit is a biscuit.
But when it's got chocolate chips, there are cookies instead.
I'm going to make some two ingredient cookies.
I'm not keto anymore.
I've given up on keto.
I'm just, I'm just low carb and I have, I'm not, I'm just low calorie and I avoid carbs.
I avoid unnecessary carbs.
Oh shit, no, no more keto.
Your, your character traits are, are dwindling.
Yeah, I know.
I have, without all my stupid little affectations, like what, what do I even have left?
Uh, you know, um.
A shell of a man.
Shell of a man.
It's true, sad, but true.
Um, I'm going to make some two ingredient, I'm going to make some two ingredient cookies.
You know what those are?
I assume a thing you put two ingredients in.
They're usually circular.
Do you know what, do you know, do you know what the two ingredients are in the two ingredient cookie?
A flour and egg, I don't know.
No, egg and oats.
No, no, sorry, I'm stupid.
Banana, you mashed up a banana.
Mashed banana and oats.
That sounds pretty good.
Uh, it's okay.
It's a bit, uh, it's not very like, it's a bit, uh, a bit chewy.
You know, it's not very like, it doesn't really taste like a cookie, but like whatever.
Um, and then you, I'm good, but I got, I bought mixins.
I'm going to be a little, I'm going to be a little naughty.
I'm going to be a little naughty.
I'm going to have mixins.
Uh, uh, I got, I got some chocolate.
I got some chocolate and I got some, uh, Reese's cups.
I'm going to chop them up, put them in there, see if that, uh, see what happens.
We'll never know.
I've also, I've also been thinking about making some biscuits.
I kind of want to bake some like really thin, like extremely snap snappy biscuits,
but I don't know of what flavor.
I just want to be able to snap a biscuit.
Cause usually when I bake biscuits, they're too thick.
Are they ginger snaps?
Ginger snaps would be good.
Yeah.
I love ginger, I love ginger snaps.
Ginger snaps with like a very thin layer of dark chocolate on one side.
Now that would be epic.
You know what's not epic is that I can't find the name of this goddamn.
This is going to be like the whole, the whole podcast.
You're going to be Googling.
Wait.
Okay.
Movie where a snooty British author is killed by horses.
Oh, we have a trope for that.
And TV tropes.
Charge of the light brigade?
No.
Why don't you search for that clip?
Like we call them biscuits over here.
Hmm.
We call them biscuits here.
It's called something like, like Notting Hill or like Buckingham Palace or uh,
Oh yeah.
In Australia, they got Anzac Bickeys.
Those sick fucks.
Anzac Bickeys.
Anzac, Anzac Bickeys.
What?
It's just, it's like, it's like, it's a particular type of cookie.
I don't even know what kind it is exactly, but like,
it's named after like, it's named after some,
it's like a military battalion or something.
It's named, it's like named after some shit that happened in some war or another.
I don't know.
I, I, oh, I typed in, we call them biscuits and I got C biscuit, but that would not be
the right clip movie.
I can't do it.
I can't.
This is all I got this week.
This is all I have to talk about this week.
Well, you know what?
While you're thinking about that, I will reiterate.
People play the punk and alley video game.
If you didn't catch it as the last episode, I am making a video game now,
which apparently means I'm copying Ben St. yet again.
Oh yeah.
One comment.
It's like, uh, just doesn't whatever Ben does.
The mouth.
True.
I mean, like making comics.
I think was kind of inspired by you, but I wanted to make a video game since I was like 10.
I mean, Tom was making, I said this in the chat.
Tom was making video games before either of us were.
So I guess I'm just copying Tom.
Yeah.
So I don't know what that guy was thinking about, but very funny.
Fucking it's where there's going to be a, I got it.
I found it.
I was wrong.
It's, it's not named a place name.
It's named Tamara Drew.
Tamara Drew is the name of this fucking.
Oh my God.
Like Nancy Drew.
It's not spelled the same way.
Oh my God.
Tamara Drew.
Well, let me find a picture of the comic.
And you'll hear a comedy by Stephen Frears.
Here we go.
You know, you didn't, you didn't specify, but the fact that you talked about authors in England,
I assumed it was Victorian England and not like contemporary.
I mean, maybe in like the seventies, but yeah, it's more, more or less contemporary.
We call them, we call them biscuits here.
You son of a bitch.
And then you fucking yank.
We call them biscuits.
Oh, you call them biscuits, do you?
I'll kill you.
I'll show you.
I'll let my, I'll let these damn horses out of their corrals and stampede you to death.
Yeah, it's like, it's been a while since you've seen the movie.
Is that a young George R.R. Martin in that image?
It looks like it, doesn't it?
But he, I think the, I think the plot of the movie is like the guy is a dick.
The guy's a dick and he sucks.
And then in the end, he's like, he's gonna like, yeah, heck, heck, yeah, I'm gonna do it.
Yeah, I'm gonna cheat on my wife.
Yeah, I'm gonna run away with this, with this interloping younger woman, this Tamara Drew lady
who's got us all, who's got us all, who's thrown our social circles into disarray with her raw
sexual energy.
I'm gonna fucking elope with Tamara Drew.
And then in all that kerfuffle, like some, something happens and a bunch of horses escape
from around the stampede, this guy just killed, he just dies in an accident.
And everyone's like, well, that's funny that that happened because that guy sucked actually.
He didn't like die because he's an asshole, except like, sort of in a very indirect way.
It just so happened that he died in an accident and we're all just like,
shame, but like, fuck that guy.
You know what?
The fact that I remember this movie like a decade later should tell you that it was great.
I never read the comic.
I never read the comic though, yeah.
Comic looks pretty good.
It's got a some, what, what do you call it, quality?
Like it's realistic, but like, not too, they're not worrying too hard about everything.
It's put it together well, but like, you know, literally trying to be realistic is nice.
Now this is a movie that's just about people talking to each other about stuff.
Now, here's a, now here's a film like that, if ever there was one.
Did I ever talk about, did I ever talk about Locke,
ever talk about the movie Locke on here?
With an E.
Yeah, with an E.
I don't think you have.
It's the one where the entire movie takes place in the guy's car while he's on a drive on the highway.
I don't know that.
Oh, that movie rules.
Okay, well, if I didn't tell you about it before,
yeah, it's what I just said.
The whole movie is just set like, in this guy's car and he's just taking calls and making calls
and he's on his way.
I don't think it's a spoiler to say that he's on his way to see his son be born.
He's about to have a son born and like, he's getting calls from his wife,
who is not the mother of the child.
So he's got to like break the news to her and he's got to like talk to his kids because he was like,
because he was like supposed to be like watching the big game with them.
And he's got to like call this woman who he had like a one night stand with and he's got to like
talk to her on the phone and be like, yeah, I'm on my way.
Want to see that son be born and whatever.
He's got to talk to like the doctors.
And then also at the same time, there's like, he's like a construction contractor
and he's got like a build like, like this building is about to be started.
The construction is about to be started.
They're about to do a pour.
They're going to do a big pour, which means they're going to lay down like the concrete
foundation for this building.
It's going to be like the highlight of his career.
But he gets like fired over the whole thing.
He gets fired, but the poor is still on.
So he's got to like be talking on the phone to his like assistant guy who's like drunk.
He like got drunk and he's like, oh God, like it's all, it's all going to go,
it's all going to go pear shaped unless you can, unless you can reach like some guys I know and
they can like, and they can sort like the details out before it happens or else it's all canceled
and my life's work goes up in smoke.
So he's, he's just in his car, just making all these phone calls about all this shit that's
happening.
Is he like stuck in traffic?
No, he's just driving.
He's, he's just driving, but it's all, it's all very like time sensitive.
It's all like, this has to get sorted out tonight because like the poor is happening
in the morning and like, you know, it's very tense.
The stakes, the stakes are well established.
It do be like that.
And that is, I don't, feels, feels like, I mean, I'm sure it's a fun movie, but I can't
help but feel like, like I would remind me of all this shit that's going on in my life,
even though it's not nearly as like intense as that.
And I'd be like, Oh no, more than two things are happening.
Oh geez.
Oh God.
Can't deal.
Well, yeah.
I mean, I guess so.
But like, it's fun when it's someone else.
That's, I kind of want to watch that.
It sounds like a fun.
I really like it a lot.
Like a, I guess sort of a challenge to make it engaging visually, even though it's,
yeah, it's just a car, guy in a car.
Well, have you ever, have you ever seen, have you ever seen my dinner with Andre?
Nope.
That's another one.
It's just two guys sitting at a table talking about stuff.
And it's just the stuff they're talking about is interesting enough.
Is that feature length?
Yeah.
Dang.
Uh, they have stars.
Scenes set in like, like a tool, like shown any other place or is it just that one set?
Well, while the beginning is like, it's the guy who plays the Sicilian in The Princess Bride.
You know who I'm talking about?
Nope.
I've never seen a film.
You've never seen The Princess Bride?
No.
Damn.
Okay.
Well, he was also the teacher in Clueless.
Never seen that.
Oh God.
He was also, um, oh, he's in a bun.
He's in a lot of movies.
You'd probably recognize him.
Okay, whatever.
Anyway, I forget his name, though.
But it's that guy, like the beginning is him like walking to the restaurant to meet Andre,
to have the titular dinner with Andre.
And then the movie is just them at the table talking about stuff and Andre telling all this
weird shit that he did for the past like 10 years.
Oh, it's this guy.
Is he in the guy in that film with the guy who says, you don't know what you think it means,
the word, you killed my father, you know?
Yeah, that's Princess Bride, you fuck.
Oh, I haven't seen it.
I just know that clip.
That's the guy, you know, one of the two rules of engagement.
Never get involved in a land war in Asia and never go up against a Sicilian when death is on the line.
He-man.
Yeah, that's, uh, that's him.
William Sean on Andre Gregory.
Classic line.
Is Andrew Gregory that guy?
I remember he's in...
That's the other guy.
It's, um, I...
Sean?
Something Sean?
Wallace Sean.
That sounds familiar.
He's in some movie, and I forget what movie it is, but I remember he plays a, uh, like a casino,
like Blackjack dealer or something.
And it might be like one of, it might be like one of the vacation movies,
like Chevy Chase in Vacation maybe.
And he says like, like, the main character loses all his money.
He's got like one chip left, and he asks, and he asks Wallace Sean, the black, the dealer,
like, how much, how, what can I do with one chip?
I've got one chip left, and he says, oh, I don't know.
Buy a bullet and rent a gun.
Oh, whoa.
I, I went to his, I love that line.
I went to his IMDb, known for the Princess Bride, my dinner with Andre.
The Incredibles.
He was the voice of, of, uh...
Syndrome?
No, Robert Parr's boss, like, I'm not happy, Bob.
Oh, the little, the little shorty.
Not happy.
Yeah, like that guy.
Oh, wow, okay.
And also, he did the voice of Rex in Toy Story.
Yes, I knew that.
I knew that.
Yep, that's him.
And also Young Sheldon, something, something, I'm scrolling through.
Is he, is he, is he in Young Sheldon?
Or is he the narration?
He's done so much.
Two hundred starting credits.
Yeah, he's in a lot of stuff.
Wait, what does he do in Young Sheldon?
Dr. John Sturgis?
Oh, he's just, oh, he's just some guy.
Oh, he's old now.
Oh, shit.
I hate when actors get old.
Yeah, it's funny.
You, you Google it and think, oh, I've seen it in that movie.
And then it like, close to death, like skeleton face, like, oh no.
Time passes.
Yeah.
I mean, he's, I was, I mean, he's, he's kind of always looked old.
But now he looks really old.
He's not like, he's not like, like, who's the guy who plays, what's the name
of the Star Trek Enterprise?
Um, Picard?
Picard.
Fuck, what's that actress name?
Oh, uh, the Patrick Stewart.
I knew it.
Yeah, Patrick Stewart is, it was the example, everyone.
Patrick Stewart and, uh, uh, the guy who was, uh, uh, James Bond and Indiana Jones'
dad, uh, Patrick Stewart.
No.
Fuck, I know this.
He looks like Alec Guinness, but he's got a Sean Connery.
Sean Connery.
Yes.
Those are the two everyone says, uh, they just like, they've always looked old and
they've just continued to look old in the same way until now.
Although now Patrick Stewart is getting all squinty.
And now that he's like fucking 90, uh, damn.
I hate it when people get old and die.
Lemau.
That sucks.
Well, it's better than getting young and dying.
That's true.
Wallace Sean is looking, uh, no, he's.
He's looking all right.
It was just sort of like, uh, I didn't know what he, I didn't know what he looked like.
And then it's like the most recent photo when you type in his name.
It's like, oh, yeah.
I mean, he's, he's visibly, he's, he's visibly much older.
So he's not, he didn't stop aging like those two did.
Fucking.
But that's okay.
Uh, marriage story.
Wait, marriage story was a good film, wasn't it?
I didn't, I didn't see that one.
This is the, the, when, when Kylo Ren gets married to, to Black Widow.
Oh, just like in, just like in Ghost World, it's got, right?
Scarlett Johansson is the lady, right?
I think so.
I saw Scarlett Johansson is the girl in, uh, she's the friend, the blonde friend, I think in, uh,
in Ghost World, it's, yeah, Scarlett Johansson is the blonde friend, and the main character is,
I forget her name, but she was also the girl in, uh, American Beauty.
Um, and then also, also, um, I don't know, that one's got, uh, the guy, that one's got the hello,
how do you do a fellow kids guy in it?
Oh, um, I don't know, that one's got the guy, that one's got the hello, how do you do a fellow
Oh, um, I, uh, Steve Buscemi.
Steve Buscemi, yes, there we go.
This is fun trying to remember who the fuck these people are.
I'm, wait, I was gonna, there'll be a video game about this, our, our normal game.
What's, what do you call it when it's like a video game, but it's not on a television?
Uh, oh, shit, what's the word?
Uh, that is pastime, uh, uh, the, the Ludo something?
Oh Ludo, that's how we got on all of this.
Um, I was gonna make another connection to something else that was in something else that
some, someone was in and degrees of Kevin Bacon.
Uh, was I going somewhere?
I just want to do, I just want to remember the name Tamara Drew.
Yeah, I think it was because of the guy we were talking about Britishisms.
We call them biscuits over here.
I'm going to see, I feel like maybe the guy who played the douchebag.
No, he's not that famous.
He's, he's an actor named Roger Allam.
So no, not, not someone I've heard of.
Yeah, I don't, they didn't get, you know, this was not a high budget movie.
They didn't have a, they didn't, they didn't have A-listers, but that's okay.
I like it when a movie doesn't have A-listers.
If I see an A-lister, I'm like.
Gay-lister.
Takes me up, more like, yeah, more like gay-lister.
It takes me out of the movie.
Uh, it's pretty rare.
It's pretty rare for, for there to be an A-lister and for me to, you know.
I think it's.
Not just, not just see him as the actor, you know.
Sure.
I mean, that's for some actors.
Yeah.
Like when you've seen Orlando Bloom before, every time you see Orlando Bloom again,
you're like, oh, it's Legolas.
Oh, it's that guy.
I feel like.
Or it's like Bill Will Turner or whatever.
Like the, or like Leonardo DiCaprio.
Oh, it's Leo.
You don't see the, you don't see the character he's playing.
But some, some actors that are prolific and like A-list, like Gary Oldman always feels
like whatever character he is.
Yeah.
Uh, I mean, Gary Oldman, I get, now I guess he's an A-lister.
Uh, I mean, I guess if you're a good actor, I don't know what I think.
Yeah.
But I think more, yeah, true.
But I think more, you can, you can do it.
You can do it.
But I think more movies, I wish that more movies and higher budget movies just hired
actors that nobody had ever fucking seen before.
I think that would be cool.
Yes.
Although I don't watch movies, so I don't really have a stake in this at all.
I guess that's, I guess I don't watch a lot of movies.
Well, I was watching movies for a little bit there.
Maybe, maybe one of these days I'll watch a bunch more movies.
No, you know what I think I want to do is a, I made a little note on my to-do list.
I kind of want to go to the library.
I kind of want to go to the library and get some books, some actual physical books for
pages.
You've talked about this already.
Have you?
Have I talked about this?
Have you still not gone?
Well, no, I'm doing, I'm doing.
You got to study up for the biggest exam.
I'm, I'm in doing a slime and punishment.
Oh, of course.
Speaking, speaking of which, I, I'm like, I'm basically, I'm on like the last one page of
the, I said this before, I'm, there's the game, I had to do the page leading up to the game.
Those are done.
Then there's the game.
Then there's the post game scene, which is basically the end.
And that is basically done.
It's, it's not quite done, but it's, it's all, it's like so close to being done.
And then I have an ending, which I don't know what it's going to be, but I think I'm starting,
I've had some ideas.
I have some ideas for that.
And I don't want that to take a long time.
I think I'm dragging my feet.
I think I'm suffering from a psychological malady that I have suffered from in the past,
where when something gets really close to being done,
I, I like resist doing it.
You resist like the actual finishing of it, or like you're, you're, you're adding things
or you're changing things and tweaking shit.
No, that's, that's different.
I mean, like I just don't want to, I just don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it because finishing something you've been working on for a long time is,
uh, well, uh, uh, releasing it is like change.
It's like a change, it's like a change of state in your life.
And that's scary.
Yeah.
You transition from I'm working on this thing to, oh, that thing's done.
That thing's over.
Yeah.
You kind of need to, I think it's like, you've got into a rhythm with a project that you work
on for a long time and then you don't want to disrupt your daily, um, you know,
your workflow, the things you do every day.
Um, so sort of unconsciously, you just want to keep it the same.
And so having it to do was part of your, your, what you were thinking about.
And then, and all, but it's weird because like there's things I want to do.
I feel the same way sometimes, but like there's like things I want to do.
And I'm like, okay, well, I got to do this thing first before I can do that thing.
And I just don't make the jump.
It's, yeah.
Uh, I mean, yeah, obviously, obviously finishing it is, um, it's good.
The most, the most reasonable thing to do.
It's a bit, it's a bit of like resistance because like, oh, scared of, scared of change,
right?
Obviously.
And then also like nervous, like, oh, what if it's a flop?
What if everyone hates it?
What if like it sucks?
What if, uh, you know, the reception is not good?
Uh, maybe I just shouldn't release it.
Uh, maybe I just shouldn't finish it.
Uh, never mind.
That and also the effect of, um, you know, uh, the like, oh, if you, if you talk about a thing,
it feels like you already did it.
Yeah.
I have a bit of that because like the game is, the game's done and it's been done.
And I've, you know, I've, I've given it to my patrons.
My patrons have played it.
So a bit, I have a bit of the like, oh, I kind of already finished it.
I kind of already showed it to people.
Uh, you know, I know it's, uh, I know it's not, uh, true exactly, but it kind of feels that way.
So I don't know.
For a bunch of reasons this week, uh, I think I've dragged my feet a little.
I haven't really been dragging my feet.
Like I got like, uh, I got like 13 more, uh, like pages done, which is not nothing,
but I feel like I could have finished it this week, uh, but I didn't.
So yeah, I mean, I, I feel like that sometimes a lot of the time.
I mean, yeah, I, I finally, I haven't like made an announcement of this,
but I finally finished those ghost costumes.
They're all done.
They're all, they're all done.
I saw you, uh, yeah, all 34 of them.
And, uh, next step is to look through the Kickstarter things and get all the addresses
and ship off a bunch of other packages.
And I'm like, but for a while there, getting the ghost costume stone was like,
okay, I've got to do this.
And I did like, I was doing them consistently.
And then one day I was just like, uh, I, uh, I did three instead of 10, which I did the day before.
Hmm.
Sometimes you just don't do anything.
I mean, heck, if you did three a day, that would take what 12 days to get them all done.
Yeah.
Whatever, whatever.
It took me more like a week, which is pretty good, but it's like, I, I, I,
since I did 10 in one day, I really felt it when I couldn't do 10 in another day.
And I'm like, what the fuck's wrong with me that I should have done this
in November?
I should have done this while I was waiting for other things.
But like, there are, my, my mind was like consumed by the, the pumpkin alley game demo.
So like, I have excuses, but it still feels like lots of things could have been done earlier.
If only I was working better.
There are, there are days, I've said this before, there are days, uh, working on slime and punishment
where I get like eight, eight pages done in one day.
And there are some, and there are some pages that take me eight days to get done.
The ones that I just, the latest ones that I posted on Twitter as of this recording,
the ones with, uh, Phantom, uh, Meeting Keg at the, at the Clover Cafe in Ponyville.
Uh, those ones took me forever.
Not because, not because they're like super complicated or anything.
It's not that.
It's like, you know, did I stop me if I said this before, but it's, it's not that, uh,
it's not that they were complicated.
The reason they took me a long time is just because I had a very specific vision for them.
And I just had to be, I was just very fussy about they have to be positioned like this.
He has to look like this.
And just because I had to get it right and I had a very specific idea, it took me a long time
versus other pages where I just kind of have a general idea of the gist of what it's meant to
get across.
And I can just kind of draw whatever.
And if it's like close enough, I'm like, okay, that's good enough.
That's fine.
I don't have to like redraw and redraw or anything.
Whereas like with those, I had to like redraw.
I like, I kept having to redraw Keg's like position and like this is his gesture in his
face and just like get it just because I want to communicate a very,
I don't want to communicate, you know, if the face is off, then like the whole scene is weird.
I mean, I mean, the whole scene is weird, but it's supposed to be weird in a specific way.
Yeah, that's, uh, that's it.
Anyway, I tweeted this week, I tweeted this week that, um,
or was it last week?
No, it was, it was, it was this week.
I tweeted, if you, if people end up not liking the ending of slime and punishment,
remember, I, it's that, it's my, my heart told me to write, I followed my heart.
It's, I didn't do it.
It's not my fault.
If the ending, if you hate the ending, uh, it's my heart's fault.
I didn't have a choice.
My, I've been drawing the ending and it's, I, I've talked about this before.
It's deeply uncomfortable.
The final scene makes me, makes me uncomfortable, uh, to look at it and think about it, but it's okay.
It's good because it's my vision and I can't, and it doesn't matter if I don't like it.
It's not about what I want.
I, I, I genuinely feel, I was thinking about this.
I feel like writing slime and punishment was not, I was not like thinking of ideas.
I didn't like have ideas.
Well, that's not true.
Occasionally I would have an idea, but it was more like I just had to discover it.
I would suddenly realize, oh, of course, that's how it must be.
Yes, yes, I see.
Yes, of course, it was always this way.
Uh, now I just, I had just forgotten,
but now I remember that this is how it has to go.
That's how it feels sometimes.
Um, yeah.
I hope the twist is that ultimate pumpkin comes back and kills phantom horn randomly.
Ultimate, ultimate, you know, I was thinking about ultimate pumpkin.
I, I will spoil that, uh, ultimate pumpkin does not, does not make an appear, I'm sorry.
That's, I wish he did because I was thinking about ultimate pumpkin because when phantom is
walking through, uh, Ponyville, I remembered, you know, lol, all those other, all those joke
characters we made up on T-Bap, like horse fister and ultimate pumpkin and silver spoon,
or not silver spoon, uh, silver lining, silver lining.
Yeah.
Uh, I fondly remembered those guys, but, uh, I was like, well, I mean, there's really no,
there's really no need for them anywhere in this story.
Not even in the background.
Didn't they have like visuals?
You know what they look like?
I feel, I feel like, um, yeah, they could have been in the background.
Yeah, they could have been, but they weren't.
The, I do, I actually think that like phantom has gone on a journey and he has basically become
a super powered like monster and, uh, I kind of think that now him and him and ultimate pumpkin
might have, they would have, they would have, uh, maybe, maybe they would, I'm not sure if
they would have fine common ground to discuss or if they would come to, to blows and battle each other.
I'm not sure something would happen.
Ultimate pumpkin clearly is like a hero.
Yes.
So he would stop you if you went too far.
Oh, I mean, phantom.
Yes, if phantom went too far, perhaps.
Yeah, uh, I don't, I mean, I don't think phantom would phantom did, you know,
cause a, a bit of a public disturbance and lights and buildings on fire, but he didn't do it on purpose.
You know, he's, his, his heart's in the right place.
Unlike mine, which tells me to draw the deeply uncomfortable scene that the comic ends with.
Okay, I, I haven't reread all the slime and punishment,
but so I'm just going to summarize the, the comic and you tell me if I got anything terribly wrong.
So phantom horn and strawberry milk are looking at, uh, Pony version of Chris Chan star night star
night star.
She throws them through a portal to endless war and you know, lack of calm.
That's right.
They learn about slime.
They do all that.
Yes.
Then they love, they learn to love slime.
They learn to love slime.
They're in the slime.
They learn about capitalism and how when you got, when you got, and how when you got slime, it just works.
They go into the, the sewers and they learn about the, they learn about, they learn about death
and how actually with slime death is cool.
And so is communism, but also capitalism just works and the free market.
Is the most efficient way of distributing slime.
Okay.
So they learn all about that and they're in there.
And then I forget what happens.
Some sort of like multiple dimensional stuff happens.
Then it's, then there's a bubble and it goes flip and it goes, whoa.
And then, then I, I don't know what's going on.
I can't remember.
The mult, the multiple dimensional stuff is that, um, Chris Chan, Sonichu shows up.
They, they, they learn to love slime and they become productive gangsters, citizens.
And then Chris Chan, Sonichu shows up, uh, just because, because Chris said so.
And, and then she gets a slime sample and takes it to Nightstar and then off screen.
This is not seen.
It's, it's discovered later.
They develop the, the antidote for slime.
Bicarbonate rain.
Yes.
The bicarbonate sugar, soda water.
And then they bring the storm comes and then, uh, uh, that has multi-dimensional
consequences that destroys a lot of timelines or destroys the city in a lot of timelines.
And then, uh, they all have to reassemble back in the beta timeline.
And then S revert is moving the city from the beta timeline back to the alpha timeline
to resume operations as normal.
Uh, and then, and that's basically it.
That's, that was the end of the comic until recently.
And then the new, the new updates are.
And then Phantom's revenge is like, dang it, I'm going to kill you, uh, the Phantom Horn story.
Yes.
Everyone is, uh, uh, Nalakakam and Quickville are now at war, but it's hardly a war because
Quickville was no match.
And it's basically, we're just, we're just mopping up all the survivors at this point.
Uh, Chris Chan Sonichu was of course crushed underneath the city as it fell back into place
on the coast of the Grand Canyon and filled it with slime, obviously.
Uh, so they're leaderless.
They're like a head, a chicken without a head, just running around.
They're like, uh, they're like the, they're like the drone army in Star Wars.
When the head drone droid is, uh, is killed, they just, they can't, they don't have, uh,
they're fucked.
They're all fucked.
Um, uh, yes, but, but that's all kind of in the background.
Phantom has to go and settle his own score, uh, with, he's got to find
Nightstar and make her pay.
Make her pay for throwing them into Endless War or, or, or, or like killing the slime.
No, he, he was mad.
He was initially mad about her throwing him through the portal into Nlakakam.
And it was a pretty evil thing to do, but then he learned to love slime.
So he's not mad about that anymore.
No, he's mad that she was, he's, he's, uh, he's mad that she was complicit in the, uh,
in the slime, in the Soda Rain Holocaust.
Right.
She, she developed the antidote and she, and she must pay for her, for her war crimes.
I see.
And that's, and that, and that's the story.
That's the story.
It's, it's, you know, it's, it's a, it's a, it's a classic tale.
It's a hero's journey where he wants, what he initially wants is to go home to Ponyville.
But then in the end, he discovers that what he needs is just to learn to love slime.
Yes.
Uh, he's, he's, he's, he has a, he has a character arc.
He's in his Ponyville and he's just like, I don't have a horn and that's me.
That's Phantom Horn.
This sucks.
Makes me, I wish I was a unicorn, but you know, I am kind of, but it's not real.
That sucks.
And then at a chance encounter, he, he falls into a slime world and he just loves it.
And then it's taken away and so he has to fight to get it back.
Or the, yeah, I guess he fights, they all fight to get it back.
Uh, yeah, he, um, uh, well, he, I mean, he doesn't really, I mean,
it's like all those other characters, like, uh, the Jane Crocker with a gun and, and, and
the little crack and Jane Crocker with a gun and whoop, whoopity, whoopity.
Yeah.
God, what the fuck?
So many characters that are not like terribly explained in the comic that are like happening
in the, we're happening in the discord over like months.
Yeah.
A lot of, a lot of it is base.
A lot of it is like, um, Killer Sonichu.
Killer Sonichu is just Jane Crocker with a gun who had stolen the Sonichu medallion
from the beta timeline version of Chris Chan, who it, who became corrupted by slime,
quote unquote, corrupted, uh, who was, that was a player named Cabricon.
That was just their like alt.
Yeah.
That was their killer alt because they were a rowdy normally.
And they drew Killer Sonichu and I was like, yeah, I'm using this.
I have not seen them around, uh, but, uh, I don't know.
Maybe they were a good artist.
So they were a good artist.
So I hope they are still drawing.
Yeah.
Uh, a lot of really good, a lot of really good artists, uh, from the old, from the,
in the old guard of, uh, of the endless war crowd.
The endless war peep, the endless war people has changed.
There's a new, there was the old guard and there's the new guard and the new guard has
stayed kind of consistent for the last like year plus maybe, maybe even two years,
but there's, there was definitely a like an old crowd and there's a new crowd
and there's some crossover between them.
Uh, yeah, I don't know.
That's, I don't know.
I'm not, I don't have any further point to make about that other than that.
It's true.
I, I remember Uwupiti, right?
It was like the little mascot you made during your Vapors Kickstarter.
Okay, Uwupiti.
Got, wait, I'm trying to think where did Uwupiti originate?
We called it Uwupiti not because he was like Dupiti,
but that was just like a funny name to give.
Uh, Uwupiti's pronouns are it, it's, uh, thank you very much.
Oh, sorry.
Uh, yeah, I decided that all, all Slymoids default to it.
They don't default to it, to it's unless, unless they, unless specified otherwise.
And their, uh, their honorific is not, uh, Mr or Mrs, but it's a, it's Mx and it's pronounced
mixture as in like, I think that's pretty, I think that's pretty clever because they're like,
because they're like mixed up in a big VAT, you know, they, they come out of the slime
Corp of Vats.
I thought I was pretty proud of myself when I came up with that.
Um, uh, mixed, mixture Uwupiti is, uh, what was I saying?
Okay, I, I made, I made Uwupiti up.
It didn't have a name originally.
I keep wanting to call him a he, lol, but now I can't or I'll sound like an
asshole.
Uh, uh, uh, I came up with Uwupiti.
The idea, I was going to guilt Chris.
I think I wanted to guilt Chris into like retweeting.
Oh, I wanted to guilt Chris into retweeting the vapor suit kickstart.
So I made this like adorable little, little slime creature like, oh, the slime, the slime
Wayne killed my whole family.
The slime Wayne.
Oh, that's right.
That was happening.
The slime Wayne, uh, displaced my community.
Ooh, uh, oh, if only Christian would retweet the vapors to kickstart.
And she never did.
And I was like, oh, he's like Uwupiti.
She, it had to, uh, was like, oh, if Chris doesn't, doesn't retweet the kickstarter,
I'm going to kill myself and throwing myself into this vat of acid.
Oh, she didn't retweet.
Oh, I guess, uh, what's the point of
going on?
That's right.
Okay.
So I was, I remembered that during that I made a tweet where I had like Katie, my slime girl,
save Uwupiti and put him in a jar.
And that's why they're in a jar later.
Yes.
And also, I forgot it was Katie, but yes, I remember that.
Later on, uh, in the alternate, in a killer, killer sonichu gives killer sonichu gives
phantom horn.
And this is the surviving phantom horn from an alternate beta timeline, uh, gives phantom horn
the all the alpha timeline version of Virginia, uh, whose owner was killed.
That's the main phantom horn.
The story follows was killed by the rain.
But his, his Virginia gets given to the alternate phantom, as well as Uwupiti, who is in a bottle
along with a bunch of piss, a bunch of, a bunch of slime court piss vats, uh, is just in there.
I forgot that.
And also, uh, Tom made that, that animation.
Do you remember that?
Of that, that 3D animation of, uh, uh, fuck, what's, what's the, what's the wreck?
Oh God, I got the COVID brain fog.
Azumi?
Azumi, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Like that COVID brain fog, uh, of Azumi rescuing Uwupiti from the vat as well.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
We both had that idea.
So I think, I think, I guess in the alpha timeline, it was saved by, uh,
Kate, oh my God, I can't, I can't think today.
Kaylee?
Katie.
And, and that was the, the one that's in the jar with the piss.
And then I guess the one that Azumi saved became Forman Uwupiti?
Maybe?
I don't know.
Yeah, I guess that, I guess that makes sense.
At a time, I think I was like, I had written a bit of like Red Noir because it was like,
it was like, it was a big thing going on with the, the, the Chris Chan, uh, bicarbonate rain
colliding with endless war saga.
It was very funny.
And so I had like, oh, it was raining.
What about like a noir film?
What if written man was a noir guy?
I can't remember why I came up with that, but that was part of the, the fun was that
it's raining and it's bicarbonate rain and he was going to try and figure it out.
When it, when it's raining in a, in a city, you gotta put on a trench code and solve a mystery.
And I remember, I remember like writing down like a big like mystery for him to solve and it
would be like so fucking in depth and it would involve slime corp and everything and red man
would be like solving the mystery.
And like, because Azumi, because Tom made that thing, Azumi would be involved.
Azumi would be doing things and it's like, okay, what factions are there and what,
who's Katie aligned with?
Oh my God, there's so much stuff there.
And it's, it was too complicated.
And also you hadn't finished slime and punishment.
So I didn't know where it was going and I didn't know what to do.
So I just sort of gave up.
Yeah. Yeah, that's too bad, but it's understandable.
I guess it took me like two years.
I didn't think it would take me that long.
I mean, now that it's about to be finished, I guess I could like retroactively finish Red Noir.
I did always, I did always want to see Red Noir finished.
I always thought it was pretty cool.
I like, maybe Red Man is in like one of the timelines that just gets completely
destroyed and everyone dies.
Oh, use, I mean.
Dimensions, what I mean.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, there's, I think it's, it's a bit, I think, I'm just trying to think if there's
a difference between dimensions and timelines, whatever.
Um, the, you saw, I mean, you, I know you saw the, um,
the slime and punishment update that is just a Red Man comic.
Yes.
With the guitar.
Yeah, I thought, I thought that was pretty funny.
I thought that was pretty clever.
I was like patting myself on the back like, haha, haha, I did it.
Big iron, big iron, big iron.
So all these references, all these fucking references.
Nobody who, imagine not knowing anything about like Endless War or the PCP or anything.
And you read that, you read those pages.
What, what, what, I don't know.
I don't even know.
It's for the hardcore fans.
I think so.
I really think so.
Man, I don't know.
Man, I hope my book sells a million copies, but it can't.
It's, it can't.
But I hope it sells to a few people.
I hope it sells to a small number of people who really appreciate,
and I hope they all buy 10 copies each.
That's my, that's what I want.
Yeah.
Hang on, I need to pee.
Okay.
Getting that, I'll just, I'll just opine to myself then that getting that book made
is going to be really hard.
Let's, okay, I'm gonna, I'm just gonna, we, weeks blend into each other,
and I, I don't remember whether I talked about this at last episode.
I say that more and more every, every time.
Uh, I think I did mention this, that I decided that I think I'm gonna switch from
a homestuck book, or a problem sleuth book style running commentary on the bottom of every page
to a infinite jest style, uh, footnotes and annotations in a, in a section at the back.
And, uh, that's actually gonna be a lot of writing.
I mean, I guess I'll, I probably, I'll try not to overthink it.
It's not gonna be like I'm writing a story.
It's just gonna be like writing off the top of my head,
like whatever I think about, oh, here's what I have to say about this page.
Okay, but it's actually gonna be a lot,
because like I'm probably gonna have something to say about,
maybe not most pages, but like a lot, a lot of pages
require, or at least would benefit from, some additional context,
like what we're talking about today.
Oh, are you talking about?
That's actually gonna, the stuff?
Yeah, the foot, the footnotes and annotations that I'm gonna have to write for the book.
Like this, like this stuff we're talking about right now.
I want to include all of this in a little like section at the back to explain like,
hey, if you haven't, if you're not familiar with the context of the story, let, let me explain.
Well, you see, Uwupati was created as a psychological weapon to manipulate
Christian Wesson-Chantler into retweeting my Kickstarter.
For an unrelated comic.
Totally, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so.
It failed spectacularly, and Uwupati died, except he didn't, except it didn't.
I caught myself.
It did fail spectacularly, but also it was a huge success because everybody loves Uwupati.
And I should make a plush.
I should make an Uwupati plush.
Should steal your idea.
I should steal your idea.
You know what?
I should just copy Gibbon.
I should just like do whatever Gibbon take does and just make a plush of a thing.
You'll have to play royalties because I came up with the idea of making plushes.
Well, okay.
Well, you have to pay royalties because I came up
with the idea of making you pay royalties to me for doing a thing that I did.
So you see circles, circles within circles within spheres, sparkles, sparkles within
cubes within rectangles.
I have been I've been playing a little too much Noida.
I've been playing a little too much Noida this week.
I've been like getting to I've been looking at a page and being like,
I don't want to draw this.
I don't want to think that drawing drawing these these these this chapter is uncomfortable.
And for all the reasons re stated before, I feel demotivated from working on it.
Therefore, oh, just a little Noida, just a little Noida.
You can't do just a little Noida.
It's like you can't do just little Noida.
It's you're committing yourself to like a month straight of playing that and perfecting it like
you did last time.
You play you play a little Noida.
Well, I'm trying I'm trying to win fast.
I'm not trying I'm not trying to do like long runs where I make the sun and whatever.
I'm trying to get I'm trying to get streaks.
So I'll be like, OK, I'll just play a little quick Noida.
Try and win as fast as I can.
Try and win in under an hour.
OK. Oh, I lost.
Oh, well, better try again.
I lost. Well, better try again.
Oh, I won.
Well, oh, I won.
Well, OK, better try again and see if I can get a streak going.
Oh, I lost.
Well, better start a streak.
Better try again.
Yeah, I almost got my record.
I brought my fastest win record down.
It's like an hour and five minutes, though.
So I could win it under an hour.
You shouldn't think I had an incredible run.
I had an incredible run yesterday that I died
in a very stupid way, as you often do.
And I was really mad game game just gave me game just fucking handed me everything.
Game handed me the win on a silver platter and I still managed to die.
That's the way it goes.
I saw this video where this guy had to physically take steps in the real world
and then spend those steps in a Pokemon game.
So like if you ran out of steps in the Pokemon game,
he would have to do like a jog and like rack up steps
so that he could use them in the game.
And it was like a playthrough of a Pokemon.
I think it was like a diamond shining diamond or whatever.
Wait, rack up steps?
Like how many steps does it take to beat Pokemon?
But I use the steps from real life.
Was he doing like a...
Wait, what?
One of the Pokemon games tracks your steps.
I don't know which one.
Oh, like an exercise tracker?
No, no, no, in game.
Like how many steps you take just as a like a metric.
Oh, okay.
Because of that, he can like keep track and he uses his like a fitness app
or whatever to track his steps in real life.
So it goes on like a jog and it's like exercising.
Exercising.
Like you can only use in the game as many steps as you did in real life.
Yes, yes, that's the idea.
Maybe you should do that for Noita.
Maybe you should like to put some sort of soft cap
on how much Noita you can play.
You have to do something to like allow yourself.
I can only guzzle as much brine in Noita as I do in real life.
Yes.
That'll put a hard cap on my operations for sure.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
I shouldn't...
I don't blame Noita.
I blame myself.
The Noita is just a symptom.
Me playing Noita is not keeping me from working.
I'm choosing not to work.
And then in the absence of that, I'm playing Noita instead.
And that's on me.
That's a...
It's not a problem with Noita.
It's a problem with me.
But I literally am...
The last page I have to do of the like post game scene
It's four panels, but they all have the same background.
Like it's four images that take place in the same background.
So the background is like mostly drawn.
I just have to like finish drawing the background
and then draw Phantom walking in the four different positions in it.
And then that scene is done.
So like that's all I have left to do on that.
And then I think the last...
The ending I'm thinking...
If I go with the idea that I have now,
I don't think I'm even gonna like have backgrounds.
I'm gonna make it very like...
Very minimalist.
Except for maybe like...
Maybe like a scene or...
No!
Maybe it's...
Actually, I'm not sure if that's true.
I'm kicking around some...
Taking around...
I'm kicking around some ideas and they're solidifying.
You know what it is?
It's just gonna be the end of Neon Genesis,
Save and Gillian with the White.
I'm taking a long time...
I'm taking a long time on purpose
because it's letting ideas slosh around and cohere in my head
about what the ending should...
About what the final, final ending should look like.
And indeed...
And indeed the concept has evolved as I've just kind of...
Yeah.
As I've just kind of let it simmer in my mind for these several weeks.
I feel like I get impatient for some things where I'm like,
it's gonna end and I want it to be good,
but I know that I can't make it be good.
Oh, just fucking throw something together and post.
That's how I do...
That's how I write my emails to like important people.
I'm like, oh, this has to be good.
That's just to be professional, but I can't do that.
Just send.
I know what you mean.
Like if it's something important...
Sometimes if it's something that you feel like is important,
you gotta just be like, well, I don't know how to make this good,
so I'm just gonna do whatever.
Yeah.
And it'll just be how it's gonna be.
Which is like, it's simultaneously a good way to get things done,
but also really annoying because then...
If only you spent a little more time, you could have made it so much better
and I'm like, oh, that's true, but also I would have never finished it.
Yeah, in the long run, it's better.
It's kind of better to just do shit and not worry about it.
And if you do more shit, more of it will be good.
True.
Yeah.
So I'm not too worried about my approach there,
but it does feel like people get the wrong impression of my potential
because I stopped short of really going for something a lot of the time.
And then when I actually do try a bit, it's like, wow,
this is the best thing I've ever seen you do.
And I'm like, well, you think this is impressive for me?
I could do this the whole time, you motherfucker.
Yeah, but you didn't.
I didn't because I was...
I was thinking, I think I was looking at some artists on Twitter.
I was looking at some drawings.
Drawings of a character.
If you're an artist on Twitter, you might have a character that you draw
and maybe you draw them in a cool outfit or in a cool background
or just like they look cool.
Yeah.
Like just draw a character looking cool, doing something cool,
or not even just looking a cool way.
And I don't know.
I think there's something wrong with me because I see something like that
that's just kind of like good for its own sake.
It's just like kind of just something that just sort of looks good
and people just like it because it looks good.
And my reaction is like, what's the fucking point of that?
What a waste of fucking time.
I think I may understand what that is.
Yeah.
It's like it's not part of...
Like it's just sort of, I think it may be that there's so much of that on Twitter.
There's so many good artists posting good art that they made and they're skilled
and you just scroll past it because you've seen it already.
You've seen stuff that's similarly good.
And you're just sort of numb to quality.
And it's like, well, surely there could be something else that this good art could be doing for me,
which is really selfish actually.
But I'm numb to quality because there's so much well drawn and well conceived
and attractive and cool art.
Honestly, like amazingly good artists are just the dime a dozen.
There's a billion of them on Twitter.
It's like crazy.
And I feel similar.
It's like, shouldn't I be like plugging right now?
Shouldn't I be like going insane?
I'm seeing this thing and it's like, this is a really cool design, really well done.
I couldn't do that in a million years.
Just keep scrolling.
Don't even like it.
Don't even retweet it.
No, we have whatever.
Saw something better yesterday though.
Saw something just as good.
So like, yeah, it's like, I don't know.
I think the way to succeed as an artist, I feel like, is just to churn out a lot of things
that are good and that people like.
You just keep making pieces that people like.
That's how you make good art, I guess.
Well, that's how you make social media success is that you have a consistent stream of good
quality stuff that like.
I would say even before social media, that was probably the way to do it.
I mean, you wouldn't sell or show before the internet, you wouldn't do that sort of stuff.
You would draw all the time if you're an illustrator, but you would get freelance work, I think.
Well, you would probably, I mean, you would probably just like build up a portfolio,
but you would only put like 5% of the art you actually make in that to show people to get jobs,
right?
But you would be, if you didn't have a job and you were an artist, you would probably be
painting stuff and then maybe you would probably try to sell them, right?
You would try to sell your paintings in some.
I mean, an art is very broad, so it depends, but like, I guess so.
Yeah, I guess you wouldn't necessarily be a painter exactly.
Yeah, okay, sure.
But I don't think, what I mean is I don't think success always, like you don't have to do it
that way.
You don't have to be putting out things that are of high quality,
of like no specific reason, just sort of like an image, I like it, you put it up there.
You could make images that suck, but like have more interesting aspect to it, like what I do.
That's why I do comics is you can have a bit of context and it makes the fact that the drawings
are not like the perfect drawing.
It doesn't matter so much because you can get attached to the character or the story that's
happening.
Well, I just feel like, I feel like, you know, it's a pretty, I think it's a reasonable expectation
of an artist that you make, that you put out a fairly consistent stream of high quality work
that is attractive to people and that appeals to people, right?
And I think the fact that I feel sort of allergic to that is probably just terrible.
It's probably just really bad for me and my success in life.
Like you feel allergic because you couldn't imagine you doing something like that or you
wouldn't want to?
Well, because my response, because I feel negatively about that sort of thing, but that's
like the kind of thing that is like good, that I'm like, oh, sure.
Oh, just make attractive character art that appeals to people that people like and want
to share and stuff.
Well, good for you, I guess.
I used to make me sick.
Come back when you were a real artist like me after you've spent two years doing a fucking
Sonichu, a fucking big, weird, stupid, like, I don't even know, it's a fan comic, but it's
sort of like, it's sort of like, like a, I guess it would partially call it a sort of
like performance art in that it was sort of improvised on the fly in order to evoke a reaction
from a specific person, a lot of it was.
I don't know.
Whatever it is, I spent two years doing it and if you didn't fuck you.
I mean, we already knew that like mass appeal does not come from extremely niche things and
success often requires a bit of mass appeal or at least some avenue by which you can tap that
market like.
I feel like what's what's something like slime and slime and punishment needs
like an event like evangelists, it needs like Bards like explaining it like the way that like
Vati Vidya like explains Dark Souls to to people or Dark Souls in general, the people
you know, it's sort of on its own.
Yeah, yeah.
Dark Souls has Vati Vidya Five Nights at Freddy's has Matt Pat.
You need you need one of those for slime and punishment.
I feel like on its own it will it's just it's just met with it'll just be met with bemusement.
Like what what am I supposed to make of this?
You know, so that's why I got a right.
So that's so that's why I got a right footnotes and errata and stuff but like is that enough?
I don't know.
I guess my hope my guess my hope for like the Kickstarter right because like the way that I
want to turn this all into a I didn't waste my time is I don't want to sell make a book and
sell a book do a Kickstarter sell the book and so I guess I hope that just the that just the
the niche-ness and the inscrutability of it will be curious enough of a curiosity enough of a novelty
that maybe people who don't even know me might hear about it in some way maybe when I do a
big push to like yeah push the Kickstarter maybe people would hear about it and be intrigued by
it and be like yeah sure I'll pick it yeah what's this I guess I'll grab one let me see what it's
all about that's what I hope and I just don't know if it's true I don't know if it'll work out
if it doesn't I'll feel disappointed you know yeah I I've I've been feeling I've been feeling
trepidatious about the Pumpkin Alley possible Kickstarter as well yeah because it's like
like it's a very different thing to like fund a video game yeah and to know how long it's gonna
take how much money is required where to put it and like yeah whether or not I have currently
enough notoriety with this to get it to that level because like what did what did my um
load of ghosts it got like around six thousand almost six six six six six I think pounds pounds
yes um which is amazing um yeah further just a lot of ghosts but like Radcon four or something
Radcon three I forget which one they made like made like 30 grand yeah Radcon four made like 32
or 34 thousand yeah and and like okay well we'll need a lot more than just that for a video game
but like how do I how do I I don't think enough people know about it so what if it fails what if
we just don't get we can't get enough money to make Pumpkin Alley I don't want to I don't want to
risk that I want to risk it like oh well I guess we can't make the video game I uh so I'm a little
scared I'm a little scared hmm I mean video game kick starters have a sort of uh track record you
know what I mean they have a lot of them a lot of them over promise and and and things go and
things go pear shaped well I guess a lot of them do but like I'm I'm I'm looking at things like a
hat in time and Hollow Knight and and a lot of those projects they had a lot of publicity before
the Kickstarter started so I feel like I need to like make the circuit make the go to some games
conventions and show off the demo and then slowly be working on bits and bobs here and there before
before I like actually say okay video game now but like I don't know it's it's really rough it
seems like yeah it seems like a lot of the big success stories out of like indie uh uh crowdfund
gaming yeah they were like already successful before they even came out like uh Lisa had a big
push uh like Jim like Jim Sterling was pushing Lisa uh you know Andrew Hussie and a bunch of other
people were pushing Undertale uh Toby later and then later Toby Fox and a bunch of other people a
lot of people were pushing like Yeek uh and like how do I I guess those I guess I guess the Yeek
guys had made a game before just like a game that nobody played so I don't know so I don't know how
they got all these uh it's it's I don't know how you get I don't know how you get this shit well
you just got to get publicity and to do that you got to have a cool thing to show people and I feel
like starting a Kickstarter before I have any like the the PCP audience is so small now compared
to where it was before um in terms of like people who would see the podcast and be like oh cool it
gives making game uh so much smaller than it's it's shrank for sure yeah and like I can't rely on
all the all the Nate all the Nate heads and the and the digi heads have all uh have all migrated
to I don't know eat glue some somewhere else I guess yeah and then like it would be cool but like
if the if they could shout it out but like I can't I can't rely on that and even then uh
well I guess Nate is about the same but Trixie is no longer a big draw a big like uh
force in like she tweets about something nobody pays attention anymore I don't think there's
a small small fan base that she has no and so like her her the big the biggest the she made her
her biggest tweet uh in a while the other day uh saying like uh my uh video is gonna be late
because of someone in my family died and everyone was like oh I'm so sorry for your loss got it got
a hundred likes it was it it was a big it was a big tentpole moment well I mean it sucks that someone
did he died but yeah sure uh it's probably like probably an uncle or something uh um gotta gotta
go to the funeral or whatever but yeah it's like uh if if there was like youtuber power I I guess I
could message a few people but like not really I would I would need to like gain some some notoriety
from the the ground up kind of not like completely from the ground up I'm I'm lucky and have like
the platform I already do uh yeah so I can push it a bit but like it's gonna take some doing before
I feel like it's it's like going to work for a Kickstarter yeah but I don't know I don't I don't
want to wait too long either so uh duh that's been on my mind it's yeah I mean yeah I guess
man I guess I guess trying to hmm you you make sense it makes sense to be like well I gotta you
know I want to have want to try and have as much cloud as I can before I launch the project
but how but how much can you get right I like damn if I knew if I knew how to get if I knew how to
get that cloud if I knew how to get those connections get like big people tweeting about my my project
or whatever like yeah man part of me wish I knew too part of me is like well I mean I could always
just become a super mega star youtuber by doing hypocrite again which is like it's everything's
a gamble that may not work at all but yeah it was it was the thing like video game reviewer of that
sort of a type of game uh fan base built from that would be interested in a pump canali yeah so
like that that's something I've been thinking of like should I should I cynically go back to
making hypocrite videos for that I don't feel like the time investment is worth it though
because to make good videos is very time intensive if your heart wasn't in it I don't feel like
they would be good no no I mean it wouldn't be like no it wouldn't be like um
I feel like the reason I got burnt out on hypocrite was more that I was just sort of chasing
algorithmic success and monetization and I didn't really have a goal I was just like
talk about this I'll talk about that yeah I feel like if I'm doing it for the purposes of funding
a video game there could be more motivation behind it and it would be fine uh yeah so like
I'm just thinking I just uh yeah fair enough I just I don't know if uh I don't know if it
really makes sense to you know that's like a like I see the connection but it's kind of like a
totally different thing like I don't feel like that's the most direct way of like getting support for
your game dev is to like throw yourself entirely into review review videos on youtube you know what
I mean true it's not obviously a good thing even if it is the biggest like number generator for you
I mean it's it's really just like how do you get people to know about anything I have a youtube
channel I don't know whether it's like because it's been dormant for so many years if it's like
you have some plakarismically unviable anymore I think that sometimes that happens to
dormant channels they just don't get pushed even if you start making new videos
um but like maybe like game dev logs sometimes get a lot of attention if they're interesting
so this is that that's like I'm torn I'm torn between stuff like I could spend my time
working on other projects which are also niche comic stuff yeah and I don't know how much that
would help I could stream more often I could become a streamer like I'm just thinking of like
how do you get this shit out there I mean some people do uh like just they make games and they
just stream themselves working on their games I haven't seen any of those I mean I've seen devlogs
on youtube but I haven't seen streams about it though yeah I mean Matt yeah I was gonna say
Matthew Matosis does that but Matthew Matosis was like a already huge youtuber well yeah sure he's
kind of big but I mean he can't he can't be the only one uh I mean every viewer of the
progress knitters podcast should share and talk about pumpkin alley and send it to all your friends
well I agree I agree with that uh that's an easy thing to do just say hey play this demo
there we're gonna make a hot fix actually some time in the future next few days um or maybe it's
already out uh just to to improve a little bit of the the jumping and a few glitches
so play the play the new version when that's out even if you played the old version it won't be
that much different but uh do it man um I feel like damn okay I not not well I guess sorry to
change the subject but it just dawned on me again how much I it's I think I I I would say it fucked
up because I had reasons for doing everything that I did and I don't think it was like a bad idea but
I did really I did really kind of uh uh pop my own bubble a bit with like the game because I was
I'm I was really excited to see how everyone would respond to the game I was really excited to see
people like maybe talk about the game maybe compare like oh how did how did it go for me like how did
I oh how did I do it oh how did you do it wait oh does that work okay maybe I don't know I was I was
anxiously hopeful that maybe I would see some discussion about it maybe it would get
people engage right see people engaging with it uh but I really popped my bubble by sharing it
with the patrons which I don't really regret doing but I really I don't even really think about it
anymore I really feel as though oh everyone's seen it already oh everyone's already played it
it's not true no I definitely they they certainly have not played it almost nobody has in the grand
scheme of things uh only probably like maybe 20 20 people have played it if 20 something like that
um but you know they they all told me what they thought and so like eh whatever eh never mind
I'm joking um but um gosh it will be pretty exciting even even though it uh it irrationally
feels like it's already happened it will probably be pretty cool anyway when I release it for real
I should I really what what gets me motivated is focusing on that feeling of oh but it's going
to be so good when I release it oh it's going to be so good when it's actually done and I put it out
and you know people can see it and I can hear people's thoughts about it and stuff so you know uh um
I did kind of kill I could kill that a little bit by sharing with the patrons but I mean my patrons
deserve it so I should not punish them by uh slacking and uh uh uh dragging my feet just because I
did that to myself yes okay video games this I think I think definitely this week
I think I think I definitely will have it done this week like like the final the final page that
I was describing the four panels that have the same background I will probably get that done today
like it's it's really close and then the final update there's no way I won't finish it this
week like there's just no way never say that unless unless unless you play noita for another 25
hours unless I have some wacky idea that ends up being like oh like that would be really good
but it would take a lot of work you know it would be really good uh uh another animation
oh another video game I was considering uh possibly some sort of um ending with kind of a
sort of a sort of powers of 10 zoom out you know what I mean do you know what I'm talking about
uh no I mean I mean like like a zoom out from like oh shows the planet oh shows the galaxy oh
shows the universe oh shows the dimensions oh shows the like you know it's all like it's all
inside of a thing inside of a thing inside of a thing uh honestly that and then it's probably
wouldn't even uh it's it's did you bronies eye at the end oh my god you spoiled it
yeah I well no that's not like that was gonna be the joke but that was like one thing I was
thinking like okay yeah what what what if I do a sequence yeah like like a zoom out zoom out zoom
out and then in the zoom out there are a bunch of like stupid things and and one of them would have
been yeah inside did you bronies eye uh but that wouldn't probably wouldn't have been the last thing
I don't know what the last thing I mean it's a reference to an old t-bap joke it's a reference
actually there were oh no no I had another idea I I guess I'll say it fuck it because I don't know
if I'll do it but I was thinking no you know I don't want to say you know what actually I actually
I actually don't want to say it because I probably will do it and I don't want to
I don't want to spoil the feeling you know I don't want to do more of what I've already
done to myself killing my yes my drive to complete it so I'll just I know what it is phantom horn
is zooms out and phantom horns fucking something
he's fucking the that's it damn fuck shit not elisar bleep that out elisar we can't have them
no elisar elisar elisar please elisar save me elisar punish give yeah bullying me
hey you give my good friend elisar just told me that you believe been saying please stop it thank you
I'm can you west I don't know that's my week I didn't do anything
I uh I have been as I said I finished the uh the ghosts most of the days was just sort of like
setting up the the sewing stuff and just sitting there listening to ukraine podcasts and in the
I still don't um uh hearing about all that stuff while I was just like sewing little ghosts up
I still don't really know anything about ukraine I mean I hear stuff that's happening
I don't uh I don't have like a I don't have like an informed opinion uh you know I guess my
you know my take was like war bad rush is doing war that's bad so Russia bad glory to ukraine
lamal uh but also like I don't know I've heard some people say that America and NATO kind of like
sort of set this up on purpose I've heard some people say like uh no no no is is that I don't
know if that's like some some nonsense what I've heard is that there are people simping for Russia
because they've like this Russian propaganda that makes this invasion out to be like
um like a necessary evil because of American encroachment or something NATO expansionism
but like fundamentally Putin just wants this country to be part of his Russian empire and
there's no like justification for that the people of Ukraine did not want it which is why there's a war
and that's about as simple as it can get if if Ukraine wanted to be part of Russia
then they could vote on it they could just you know they could do something about it but like
they don't the democrat the the the democratic or democratically elected leader of Ukraine
uh does not want to be part of Russia yeah and he was like voted in with a large majority
and so as far as I see uh the invading to take back the like this land that used to be part of
the USSR has no justification beyond but I want it I it's mine I am the big Russian man I want it
and it's like come on shut up you dumb fuck right yeah okay uh yeah I just uh you know I
I that's mostly what I hear uh but like I you know haven't looked into it enough to have an informed
opinion on why the like oh this is actually like NATO's fault thing people are are wrong or right
or anything I just uh I mean NATO NATO is a coalition it's like a like an organization of
countries nearby Russia who are scared of Russia and do not want to be invaded by Russia
right and they are backed or like US is part of it um and I think people who just hate the US
think that like the countries within NATO are like puppet states for the US and so they're like
oh it's just the US meddling in European in European affairs when it's it's much more like
these European countries would like to remain like themselves they don't want to be swallowed
by Russia that's the whole reason they joined NATO and it was like a voluntary thing and they
I don't know there's a lot there's a lot there's a lot to hear about it but like
the the idea that these it's all the the US's fault and therefore Russian bombing
and and killing civilians take over Ukraine is in any way justified is very strange
and I don't really know where their heads at yeah because I haven't seen like any
credible evidence of any kind that like what Russia is doing is uh good not that like like
you could say the US is meddling and maybe that's true but I haven't seen any evidence
specifics but like let's say it's true Russia is still also doing a bad thing
by meddling in Ukraine I think it would be better if neither the US nor Russia was trying to do it
to do anything I see so it's like there's no there's no justification for the invasion even
if America is being a sneaky beaky which is very likely because the US is a bit of a sneaky beaky
all over the world we are we can be a bit of a sneaky beaky it's uh it's a well-known thing
yeah uh okay that all makes that all seems cogent yeah uh I want to uh hey what are we gonna do
about Spotify and Apple podcasts and stuff uh I don't know how to do it I Tom Tom does it
we just got he's not we gotta he's just not he's just not answering me he just hasn't been around
lately we just gotta go over there and get him out of his wheelchair kick him down and say where's
the podcast and he'll say oh I'm making a video game instead I just uh I just I like I I've been
up I've been uploading the the podcast to YouTube for the last few weeks which like you know
it's okay I'm not complaining but like yeah I don't know how to do he had like a thing he had like
a webhook uh rss thing set up that like I think it automatically did the uh like Spotify Apple
podcasts uploads and stuff and I just I don't know how I don't think I even have access to that
and I don't know how to use these uh platforms and I've never interacted with them I mean have
you DM'd Tom about it I I haven't DM'd him but I've added him in the chat maybe he's more receptive
to DMs I don't know maybe he has the chat he showed up or something he showed he showed up to uh oh
he doesn't want to he doesn't want to talk about uh Spotify but he'll show up to he'll show up uh to
when Jesse complains uh that's stupid uh but whatever I get I get I guess that's fine that's
how you want to be um man just just uh just help just help just help me out Tom people keep asking
me I just got a message on Twitter it's like Ben please upload them I want the episodes on Spotify
and I'm just like I don't I don't know how I don't know how to help with that uh
I don't want to sound I don't want to sound like ungrateful or anything for like you know
if it weren't for Tom uploading them to those other things then they just simply wouldn't be there
yeah so I appreciate it and all but I can't you know I can't do it I mean I get I guess I could
learn but I don't want to I don't want to figure I don't want to learn Spotify or Apple podcast or
whatever uh well uh go into Elden Ring and invade him and kill him oh it's right that's the only
that's the only way you gotta leave Elden Ring messages on the floor saying Spotify question
yeah yeah you just gotta get soapstone messages or uh or whatever hmm it's uh it's you gotta add
you gotta add him on Elden Ring it's the only social media he's using right now there now there's
an idea hmm uh well yeah maybe I'll DM him about it uh might be a little could be helpful I don't know
uh do you want to maybe go to voicemails um I want to briefly say to people waiting for their lord
of ghosts book um I've got uh something to have no no on Monday tomorrow but after that I'll be
uh packaging and sending out a big amount of uh the packages now that the ghost costumes are done
I'll make a a kickstart a like update about that um uh and I hope you like it and I hope there's no
problems in the postage I'm excited Ben you haven't given me your backer like uh mailing address
stuff I don't think oh oh like on Kickstarter yeah do I have to respond to the survey yes I mean
I mean I could just tell you yeah but like it's easier but I can do this yeah yeah um
did you send out like a like a backer like a request for information yeah I sent out the survey
I'm when was it a while ago it was a while ago yeah oh I must have missed it uh yeah okay I should
do that uh everyone should do that yes um yeah all right I'll have to fucking
log back into the log back into my old my Kickstarter account that I haven't uh looked at in a while
all right uh yeah let's do uh let's do voicemails shall we huh yes okay um oh no I'm logged out of
speakpipe uh you know I'll just post them in the chat okay because it just it just makes it easier
because then I don't have to repost them for uh what's his name Eleazar Eleazar yeah yeah
god I it's like I got the COVID brain fog today what the fuck you're just getting old Ben
I'm actually got it yes I said you're getting amnesia is it co is it COVID brain fog
I mean I didn't I didn't I didn't sleep like at all so maybe that's why but I feel it's
worse than usual today oh god oh god you know I read an article man oh yeah I saw oh god yeah
I had stopped thinking about it and then I saw an article about COVID brain damage
and how like yeah it makes you stupider it damages your brain and it makes you stupider
permanently I didn't get it well okay I guess I get permanently is I mean like you know who knows
but they they did um they did tests right they tested people they did cognitive tests uh
on people like before and after uh you know infection and they did yes they did find a
significant like change in performance in people afterwards but also did did they account for
anti-vax status like what sorts of people are they okay I don't think it accounted for I think
this was like pre vaccine right I think uh it it okay the worst cases like the worst cases of it
showed like a they gave it in terms of like standard deviations of like you know a typical
score on these tests you know it dropped like you know more than a standard deviation it I think
it said that like the the effect was equivalent to about like seven IQ points uh in the most in the
strongest cases um but on the other hand those were it did correlate like like how severe was your
case to the effect like like it's it's like the effect was present even in people that
had mild cases but it was like it was like much stronger it was it was stronger like the more
severe your disease had been like like if you'd been hospitalized if you'd been in intensive care
you know if you'd been put on a respirator you know the effect was stronger and all that
so I mean I guess I guess I can take heart because my case was mild so if it was gonna happen
it's probably a small effect and who knows you know some amount of it is probably not
permanent anyway so maybe maybe I only lost two IQ points and I'll get one of them back I don't know
you know yeah I mean whatever you can you can like grind free xp put those those IQ points back
just take full time yeah yeah you know what you know what you're absolutely right that's exactly
true and I don't have anything else to say about it okay anyway enough enough about that let's hear
from the first voicemailer son of Marowak three two one let's jam given I played your demo it was
awesome I really liked it yeah it's pretty good I collected all the uh those purple token things
one bit of not criticism just please criticize I don't know what you'd call it uh there was a bit
of um glitchy you like I could like I had to like reset my position because punk would just
fall in place yeah this took place in the third the last like big room where you jumping around
on the side point there are those two or three rocks that allow you to jump up to the highest
platform yeah and I could not or um I uh got to a point where um was like cut in between uh the
rocks and I couldn't jump because she was just stuck in place so figured if uh that helps you at
all yes yes we we've looked at this uh the the hot fix that will be out or is soon to be out um we
made a change where if you are stuck in the falling state and your position has not updated to anywhere
significantly different the game will understand that you are stuck and you will you'll be able to
land and you'll be you'll be able to land on that part and then from there you can jump away oh
so we we fixed that that doesn't happen quite so much anymore really that's interesting so you can
just so hmm that that kind of seems like that means that there's now a lot more places you can land
um yeah maybe I mean a lot of the a lot of the geometry was just sort of like uh put it there
whatever if people really want they can jump but it's not supposed to be there for jumping on
um and it's fun to like not restrict the player um but like yeah like the actual level design
we're probably gonna make it so that you can't sequence break quite so easily we're gonna like
uh you know have like very not like super linear but like linear enough that you don't like skip
most of the content of the level if you jump up to a certain platform um which can happen with
with the thing you can jump over and skip a lot of stuff but that's not really a problem for the
demo but getting stuck a lot yeah was definitely a thing so we've solved if you're infinitely
being falling animation or or like sliding animation you you stand as long like after a few
seconds it'll recognize you as being stuck not moving and you're able to like being the landing
state it will think of it as floor until you move away that you jump jump away and then
it'll be normal again this was this was actually that was a thing actually you know what I forgot
but I had a similar thing in the slime and punishment beta demo there was there was uh
it was possible to it was possible to spend all your slime and all your potrons and just have no uh
and just have no ability to do anything and you basically just couldn't take a turn uh so
yeah and to resolve that I what I do I added the menu you can go to the menu and you can
just restart you can just like quit uh that's sort of like the proof but oh but also there's now
like option there's options in in there's menu options that don't require slime so even if you're
out of slime I mean you can if you want you can just you can just dab you can just keep dabbing
until you die I guess uh if you if you would prefer if you want to go out like a champ uh
I mean you know obviously I couldn't you can't get rid of the I can't remove the ability to run
out of slime because that's like a core mechanic so I was like well it was it wasn't it wasn't the
fact that you could run out of slime and and be fucked like that's that's good that's a feature
not a bug the the problem was that it would feel like oh well now I can't do anything and it's
basically a soft lock uh it's not like it's not like I lost it's just like I cannot progress the
game state uh yeah I think I mean you've already made the game but like a way to make that quicker
would be like if you run out of slime you just die instantly uh I can you know I considered adding
I considered adding a suicide command that would basically be identical to just going into the menu
and restarting but it's I didn't do it because it seemed like uh it would just be I don't know
I would have to do a bunch of work making like a whole new animation for it and adding it to the
menu and all that stuff and it it just like kind of duplicates a function that already exists
it's just a it's just a restart button which there already is one of those and I mean if you
want to just kill yourself you can just you can just let yourself be killed you know it's not it's
not it's not hard uh wait what fuck oh god brain fog covid covid's back what did you say what did
you say what am I responding to oh my god I didn't say anything no from before that you said I said
you said something you said once your slang goes to zero you could just die instantly and I would solve
that problem of of needing to wait for well for death like oh like if you try to attack with zero
slime it just kills you something I bet yeah I mean in the in in endless war if you try to
attack with zero slime it just you just don't so you know I was trying to duplicate the right
the commands from that game so yeah so it's just you just get a little pop-up command it's like
not enough slime to attack nope nope you can't fucking do that so let's can't fucking do it
next one is called performance artists there it is uh three two one go one episode two nine one
you all talked about whether dry dump December is after bringing up the possibility of it being
performance art as well as the idea that aren't as anything intended to evoke an emotion in its
viewers which got me thinking is bullying art it's a performance intended to evoke an emotion in
its audience you know you could say that somebody I would say bully someone very like there's an
art to bullying if you want to get the the right emotion out of someone is is bullying intended
to evoke a reaction in the victim or is bullying intended to invoke evoke a reaction in the bully
I is it is it to make the bully feel good um I mean normally I feel like it's like the reaction
does the job of making the bully feel good for being powerful or like putting someone else down
right yeah yeah I think so it is for the bully's benefit that they do I think so or otherwise
social clout you know people laughing at someone else makes them feel good I feel like you would
bully there's no other reason yeah I feel like the point is not generally the point of bullying
is not to evoke a a complexly nuanced feeling of self-hatred and poor and low self-esteem in a
in a in a in an audience of one so to speak unless it's maybe it's art it's not yeah not about
the feeling you evoke in the victim but about in like you know the people that see you bullying
they think it's really funny like ha ha yeah that that nerd deserves this yeah you could you could
do a performatively bullying thing yeah yeah virtue signaling they call it I don't know what that
means what's the opposite of virtue uh vice vice signaling vice signaling vice signaling maybe
look everyone goes whoa what a what a scowl scallywag what a what a rogue what a lovable rogue
with a dark streak to him it's hot yeah that that's the my my art my art I'm an artist and my art
and uh it exists to evoke a feeling in the audience that I am hot and that you should have sex with
me uh it's it's avant garde um lamal okay next one is called uh vvv revelations to ben saint
about ben saint from gibbonisqtpie at patreon.com okay three two one go
this is going to be completely irrelevant by the time you hear it but the thing that I was saying
in regards to the picture talking shit about no this is update on yin sorry from like years ago
when he was just griping about gripes it's not in that he holds against you he just was talking
and I was like oh I need to hear more people saying stuff like this about ben saint okay wait
no no no this was not no no this was sorry this was vvv revelations sorry this was the correct one
okay uh thanks for clarifying if you want to hear people say stuff about ben saint
uh I don't know go to ben sevies discord that's true maybe someone will say something about me
after I release slime punishment then again maybe not uh so look forward to that I guess
or maybe don't I don't know okay next next voicemail uh is called update on yig three two one go
somebody asked trixie why did you take boy gazers off the main yig channel and she responded
and I guess she didn't respond to it but someone else responded saying well you know it doesn't
it doesn't really feel like it belongs on this channel or whatever you know it doesn't meet the
channel crazy basically meaning that you're right ben so uh yeah she's a fucking idiot of course I'm
right I see yeah yeah uh doesn't doesn't fit doesn't fit the the direction of this channel which
despite all that stuff I said for like a whole year uh is just anime videos now sorry just
anime videos now never mind all that other stuff ha ha ha oops it always felt like like all of that
stuff was clearly side channel content like new and interesting yeah like experimental content
and and the the the digi bro the the digi nay the trixie uh main channel was always like the front
facing the front of the store like this is where I get my viewers yeah of course and and but yeah
of course you can't everybody but everybody told her that like bro this goes on the side channel
this is side channel content what do you have a side channel for and I what was their logic it was
like that's where all the viewers are so I'll put it it's yeah it's that they'll like it I guess yeah
it's it's literally just it's like it's like a child logic it's like uh yeah it was like well I
it's like I have more subs on the main channel though so more people will see it like okay
okay like literally just like forgetting what the purpose of a side channel is
subscribers are a harsh mistress it's true it's sad it's sad but true but not actually sad
it's funny uh anyway uh there's a part two update on yig part two uh there it is three two one go
and I say we make her do you an apology for being such a fucking tool
yeah hey yeah why didn't anyone think of that yeah do uh uh what's the website where people
write their signatures what change.org like oh yeah yeah yeah sort of change.org petition
and have been uh Trixie apologized to Ben St. yes yes uh definitely uh you just need to get more
signatures than she has subscribers get 300 000 uh signatures on that and I'm sure and I'm sure
she will be and I'm sure she will see the error of her ways um it's okay no no hard feelings
because uh I just got all her money I just got all her money that she would have made
from being on the podcast it all just went to me instead and Gib I guess uh so you know
water under the bridge that soothes the pain uh next next video is called uh
Spooty Meng's Spooed Verse three two one go who is your favorite spider man
and why is it noir noir I did is he is he one of the spider man in the spider verse the like
oh I'm uh I'm red man noir uh literally red noir because he's red I mean there's a there is a
black spider man right you see is that like spider noir I know I don't know the that's
the miles morale miles tails prowl is no I mean I mean there's a I mean there's a spider man with
like a black costume is that Miles does the did they give the black he's got a black costume okay
okay I mean that's fine it looks cool it doesn't cool not as cool as Gwen though Gwen looks awesome
spider Gwen's costume is so fucking cool yes we cannot we can all agree on that she's the best
the best looking uh but if I had to actually pick my favorite spider man it would be the 60s spider
man from the 60s spider man tv show in color because it's so goofy looking and this one like
a hundred thousand memes of that show oh the old one with like the them pointing at each other
yeah that's where it's just the funniest he's just I just love him that's where the song came from
right spider man I didn't know yeah maybe it's where it's from I it's probably the first spider man
media that is has vision like audio so probably yeah yeah yeah probably um very funny uh yeah it's
pretty good uh I guess I watched the tobey maguire movies or I watched like two of them and I I guess
those were pretty good those are my close second tobey maguire spider man I don't think I've seen
any other spider man movies than the tobey maguire like the first two tobey maguire ones
saw the one with the goblin the one with doc ock oh you didn't see the third one where he does the
funny like venom dance no I don't is venom in that one venom and sand man are in that one
no I didn't see that one no so uh I've seen the the meme the scene of him like being all emo or
whatever and like being all cocky yeah it's fun yeah yeah it seemed funny seemed funny
seemed like one of those scenes seemed like a scene kind of like the laughing scene from
final fantasy 10 that's awkward on purpose and like they clearly made it awkward on purpose
but people point to it and laugh at it as though it's like awkward by accident you know what I mean
uh I think so I feel like people make fun of that people made fun of that scene of tobey
maguire like strutting around looking like quote unquote cool as though it's not obvious that he's
meant to look like a doofus yeah to people yeah it's because of the way people react to him in the
film is like oh they're embarrassed about what he's doing and he's like oh yeah it's like it's
clearly not a good feeling that look I feel like I've seen people talk about like how the movie was
cringe or that scene is cringe because like well it's supposed to be cringe I guess it's cringe
that yeah like he's being cringy but he thinks he's not and that's the cringy part but not not
from a filmmaking perspective I feel like I've seen people thinking that it's that it's that way by
accident I don't know I think I like tobey maguire a lot because the peter parker nerd aspect of that
performance is much more believable the other guy is like Andrew Garfield and the new guy
tom holland they they look like pretty boys they look like like they're like they could be like
jocks peter parker tobey maguire looks like a doofus and that's great he does look like a doofus
a little bit I mean he's handsome he's handsome but like that the performance but he makes a he makes
a goofy face yeah he's good at that he's good at looking like a goofy guy I mean that's a that's
a talent okay the next one uh there's an image but there's also a voicemail okay let's listen listen
to the wasn't a voicemail three two one go how do I send a link how do I send a link I guess you
get it out yeah okay so here's the image every step you successfully complete will kill one person
however failing to complete a step kills three other people will you not participate and let
three times as many people die or will you show me your dance of death okay so it's dance dance
revolution with buses and the people as like the you did it so you have to do a dance and as you
murder people and keep up with the dance properly otherwise more people will die this this is just
this is just the trolley problem ethically speaking this is just the trolley problem but it's dancing
instead of pulling a lever so yeah I guess I guess you gotta dance yeah I guess sorry I guess I dance
it's that it's just like that moment in spider-man where where the green the goblin has the
yes full and the bus and the you never know when a villain will offer you a sadistic choice
here's here and here is spider-man will you dance spider-man will you show me your dance of death
hey man yeah mndray tell me more about your adventures in the african sahara
hmm okay sorry what's that guy's name Wallace Wallace grommet classic good good good good good guy
Wallace Shaw Wallace Shaw right right uh I think I had the thing Sean yes Wallace Sean
Wallace Sean the sheep Wallace grommet Sean the sheep yep uh next voicemail is called uh
it's another image link but there's also a voicemail for some reason three two one go
band gross I hate you I hate that you said that right in my ear in my right ear
in one of my two audio channels in my left ear who's right three well me you're you're left
am I wearing my headphones backwards hang on hang on no I'm wearing mine right wait I
am I wearing mine backwards no I'm wearing mine correctly I on my on my headphones there's
like an L and an R on each side oh you took the L oh you took the L I did take the L
the L wing and you put it right on your left ear like a like a good soldier uh well I heard it
in my right I don't know uh okay next voicemail was there a link you said yes yes here it is uh
right there I wish everyone into crypto goes to hell no matter what says Timmy Turner uh yes uh
time for uh play the jingle Eleazar if there is one it's time for Ben's crypto corner it's time
for fairly odd parents corner uh my crypto update this week is that uh I looked at it
and I saw that it was uh it went up when the war in Ukraine broke out uh it went up a bit
but then it went right back down again so uh that's it okay play the jingle update over
what's that corner it's down to it's down under 40 it was it was it's under 40
it shot up above 40 to like 44 it was down to like 36 then it was hovering around 40
then it shot up above 40 to 44 now it's back down to about 30 to 39 40 45 56 207 98 uh
okay that's radio not here I come me for a while uh what what huh we got something to say
punk no no I know no no no no yeah yeah that's what I thought yeah that's what I thought let's listen
you sit your white ass down and listen okay to this next to this next voicemail
three two it's called 2022 three two one go just a little warning I did some digging for
some old files and um turns out this voicemail bullshit goes back a lot further than I realized
you're gonna see some dates and you got you gotta see some dates I don't know I don't get it okay then
well that well the next one is called uh 2011 so I guess this was a voicemail but this guy
made and didn't send in 2011 that was before we were even the horseshoe crew wait a minute
yeah and then the one after that is called 2008 so uh hmm all right let's give it a
oh god these are a minute and a half long all right let's let's try it uh 2011 three two one go
it's a just a new pokemon
my name is oblivion full I have written this script I've created this very special message for you
as you may have noticed my voice may be starting to sound a little straight
so it's a baby oblivion for you
so does normal because my voice regularly scrolls up after it's starting to sound a little
shine I think you don't have anything to worry about I know you
cause you just this oblivion full fucking around with a voice change
for
yeah it's that raw like like
directionless teen fun I love I love having directionless teen fun it's
just like when you're just you just don't you didn't nothing matters but you're
having fun anyway next one is 2008 oh my god two one go you are a
biotical and I have a human that you're not the same scream or our or else
I'll never save you Elliot this is your doom because you have betrayed me Chris
Chan and Elliot's yes you did remember you made me be chewed by the dinosaur
shut up Elliot I'll hit you
I don't know why I really like that.
It's just like, so it's oblivion fall would have been in 2008 oblivion fall would have
been about one year old I think so yeah that that about tracks.
Cute. Kind of cute.
Kind of cute. Glad you enjoyed yourself. All over our damn podcast. I'm sure a two-year-old
you would be thrilled to know that maybe 2,000 people would hear that. That's if
everyone listens all the way to the end. Questionable. Next voicemail is called
what the fuck Texas three two one go. Texas. Yeah it's about that Texas is past
yeah a lot of some anti-trans legislation which is it like I think it
mandates or at least makes it very much encouraged to out trans children to the
authorities or to their parents if like a person at school teacher knows that
they're trans they have to or a medical professional I it's some it's some
bullshit to like get trans children like cured from their transness by parents who
would want them to go to like conversion therapy camp you know that sort of a
thing really stupid I haven't really looked into the specifics excellent but
it is it is very like like explicitly anti-trans and there's nobody likes it I
don't know how it my plan my plan is working perfectly I'm passing all this
anti-trans legislation to kill Trixie the golden with in Texas oh fuck you mother fucker
oh shit well better luck next time okay yeah I heard about that I also heard is
this is it related to I think it's not just Texas but a bunch of states have
passed up some quote-unquote don't say gay oh yeah something something like they're
like like no books that have like gay people in them yeah it's it's like it's
like state-approved like book burning of queer like yeah sure and and it's
insane goddamn goddamn political correctness am I right goddamn cancel
culture strikes again am I right we got a fight cancel culture with am I right
my fellow base base red-pilled disaffected liberals yeah that seems pretty
bad yeah hopefully it doesn't happen oh no it's okay okay yeah everyone's fucked
up all right undo it but I don't all right anything hopefully hopefully they
don't actually like like do it though hopefully they just kind of like I've
seen at least one article of something bad happening as a result of the bill
being passed already hmm I don't like it when bad things happen no no no no I'm
I'm against those as a rule I I just want to but I just want to make my stance
perfectly clear on bad things as a trans woman I think bad things are terrible
terrible things are even worse as a cis man I acknowledge that bad things are
terrible but but who am I to say really but but but but but nuclear war is actually
very survivable when you you know yeah did you see that guy on Twitter there
was some guy on Twitter who had a thread about how like nuclear war is actually
pretty survivable you just got to start preparing for it I guess he sorted
there's sort of a point to be made there it's sort of true but also like to what
end are you saying that I guess there is a certain there was a certain strain
there was a certain strain of liberal at the moment that is hysterical over the
Ukraine stuff to the point that they are like we should just we should just start
nuclear war like we should just do nuclear war against Russia it's gonna it's
gonna happen anyway why delay the inevitable we got to take them out like
there's just no other solution I mean I agree that he should be taken out but
like it's so much simpler to like keep the sanctions in place and let Russia
just starve itself out of all its money because it's not like economically in a
very good position already yeah it could not the funny thing about like the
the invasion is that it very much felt like Putin wanted to end it by just
posturing and like bluffing about an invasion and hoping that they would back
down and you know not talk with NATO Ukraine should not talk with NATO and
if you do will invade and NATO was like a fuck you hey what are you doing and
like Putin was like okay I've made the threat they've called my bluff I guess
I'll just have to do the invasion and he's like the the initial invasion force
was really under like prepared to go in yeah it feels like it was a bluff that
just got out of hand I feel like we'll stop them more than actual like combat
we don't need to start doing any of that stuff I watched I watched oh a video
another video by Patrick Boyle the finance guy he had a video about like
sank the sanctions on Russia and about like yeah I guess they had he said that
the war is costing them like 20 billion dollars a day and that like most of their
money was in like overseas like most of Russia's like monetary assets were in
like some of it was in Russia some of it was in China so that's safe from
sanctions but like like two-thirds of it is like overseas and has now been frozen
and they can't get it and they only have maybe like a few hundred billion
dollars left yeah and like they just they just can't keep doing it unless they
get some more money they'll keep like the the war going until they literally can't
pay for it anymore they may take over Ukraine but they will not be able to
like hold it for any significant length of time to do anything I feel like they're
going to like posture they're they're gonna threat like if you dare do
anything we'll we got nukes you know and it's like oh shit they got nukes but
like they do they do got nukes though they're gonna like run out of like money
to launch the nukes they're gonna press the nuke button well there are no power
left no like we can't we have no money to buy batteries to power the nuke
launcher though it's it's like whether or not nukes are fired is really just
down to whether Putin is like sane or not and we don't really know that but
like in terms of like going to war with them like actually with our own stuff
that would warrant nukes being used by Russia which would end the world
wait like if we like if we use nukes on them you're saying that if we started using nukes or
even just like missiles and Russia would have more of a reason to actually use their nukes
but right now when they're just doing a little invasion it's just that you know we do a little
we be doing a little invading little we do a little invading we do a little invading we do
a little blowing up of civilian hospitals and stuff I mean I mean you gotta break a few eggs
you gotta break a few eggs to kill a few chickens you know yes yes so but like nukes
from Russia's perspective are such a wild like it's it's literally just a suicide button they
would not add like advantage Russia in the the invasion they would just cause retaliation and
world like apocalypse so like Putin would have to be actually insane to do a nuke
unless he was being physically attacked by like an army in which case he might actually do it
maybe so today's it seems like sensible responses just keep the sanctions on until he runs out of
money I mean until he until he retreats that is boy gosh I mean damn though like can you imagine if
they just started firing nukes like can you fucking imagine I could imagine I guess I probably would
be dead very soon after I hear about it because I do you think London might be a target London
yeah London might be a target I mean I mean I mean you know I'm a bit it's a bit uh I guess
it depends on like what kind of bomb it is I wonder about this like like if they nuked
Boston like am I like close enough to this to the center of the city that like I would be
would I be vaporized would I be like you know would I get a would I get fall out like what
what would the impact on me be the uh for instance Boston was nuked I watched a video in my recommendations
the curse cuz I video about what if you were nuked yeah it was years old so it was like everyone
damn that's what I want to know that's exactly what I want to know is you watch that video
yeah I mean fine it's it's it's graphic but it's like informative so you will you will learn uh
what I mean because I know because I like it's like it's not like everybody in uh you know uh
Hiroshima and Nagasaki like died I mean a lot of people did but like a lot of the city was just
was like damaged but it wasn't it wasn't like completely like craterized you know no I mean
there's a part in the middle where you will be turned to atoms and after that yeah there's like the
wind uh the air pressure would like knock houses down and then the mushroom cloud would go up and
then the wind would be sucked back in so another like shock wave would go back and then also before
the wind there would be like a heat wave so things that could catch on fire within a large
radius would just spontaneously catch fire you might not die from that but like your skin would
burn like in like a like a sunburn like instantly Jesus and then after that there would be there
would potentially catch fire that would burn your skin right it would burn your skin it would be
your clothes would be on fire um Jesus Christ it's like a it's a nightmare and then after that um
there would be very little potential for aid for a very long time after like all of the because
you can't get not because of that I mean infrastructure would be damaged a roads would
be blocked people would be trying to get like um and helicopters can't really come any can't really
get that close for a while so you would have to like walk out of the city you mean for like days
uh could be days could be months I mean I can't remember exactly what they say but watch the
video it's it's good and scary maybe I will yeah maybe I will uh I feel like if London the center
London was nuked I would not be hit because I'm in the suburbs but I would definitely uh probably
get radiation poisoning afterwards and everything would be terrible forever hold on let me see
let me just uh I'm just I'm just curious I'm gonna see like how far am I how far am I from like the
the center of downtown Boston let me just let me just get a quick uh quick uh quick idea here
okay uh where am I type my address in here
uh two that's 2 000 feet that's one mile that's that's okay I'm maybe like
I'm maybe like four miles like three or four miles out from like central downtown Boston
I don't know what do you think that means for my odds I can't remember the the the
the thing in the video what are they what was that like a radius of about they yeah they don't
put it on screen they talk about it like they say of a radius of about something something
miles would be this then this radius would be even it would be radiation there would be like
black rain black like toxic rain I think can happen like in like s uh rose grim dark when she
gets the in Homestuck and and it's like it's the toxic particles from the explosion radioactive
would get turned into like sooty like black rain which would come down and just you know
infect you with radiation it would be terrible reading yeah I was reading like
I did read a little I think it was like a government uh instruction thing about like
what to do if they're if a nuke happens and they said like number one like get inside
stay inside if you were outside uh first thing to do take your clothes off get rid of your clothes
wash your clothes take a shower get any like residue off of you it's like a priority number one
yeah uh assuming that like water mains have not been burst and you actually have water
yeah true yeah true uh geez that is actually kind of a big if now that you mention it it's it's like
the the the the damage to infrastructure is not just like the roads will be inaccessible it's like
power will be out water might be not running and people might like die of thirst before anything
else jeez if they're stuck in a city in between like in rubble and and all that
you got to be very far away from a nuke to not instantly feel the effects
that's hold on how far is safe from a nuke how far is safe from a nuclear bomb the moon
okay damage zones after a nuclear oh god oh hey no this is great this is not great
oh this is no this is lovely no this is one well uh well actually
no here this is what i wanted check check check check check check this shit out check this shit out
i'm checking it here i posted it uh okay so it depends on the kilotonnage of the of the the um
the payload obviously so for a 10 looks like for a 10 kiloton bomb i would be
i would be nukes or just bonds
uh well i mean this is from a website for uh damage zones after damage zones after a nuclear
here i'll post the website damage zones after a nuclear detonation idealize maps
so yeah for a 10 kiloton bomb i would be either in the light damage zone or just maybe just
out outside of it that would be on the like on the periphery of that that that coveted light
damage zone baby why is all right i'm trying to find sites and they're like saying um you can't
read our site we don't want you to so i left
wait i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna do oh you you get pay walled not pay walled it was just
sort of like uh we're just we're just being stupid right now uh okay hold on i'm gonna
i'm gonna i'm gonna find out exactly i'm gonna find out exactly how uh how far this is this is
gonna be great yeah i'm about three i'm like three and three quarter miles three almost four
miles so i'm like right on the outer edge of a the periphery of a 10 kiloton light damage zone so
i'm good light light light damage who cares about all that all that might happen is like all your
windows will explode that ain't nothing okay okay let's hear it light damage zone are you are you
reading uh what it's describing here let me let me go to the here i'll read it out loud light
damage zone damage is caused by shocks similar to those produced by a thunderclap or sonic boom
but with much more force although some windows may be broken over 10 miles away the injury associated
with flying glass will generally occur at over pressures above 0.5 psi what this damage may correspond
to a distance of about three miles from ground zero okay so maybe there could be some injury from
broken glass from ground zero for a 10 kiloton nuclear explosion damage in this area will be
highly variable as shock waves rebound multiple times off of buildings the terrain and even the
atmosphere as a responder moves inwards windows and doors will be blown in and gutters window
shutters roofs lightly constructed buildings will have increasing damage litter and rebel will
increasingly move towards ground zero there will be increasing number of stalled and crashed
automobiles that will make emergency vehicle passage difficult blast over pressures that
characterize the light damage zone are calculated about 0.5 at psi at the outer boundary this is
not that descriptive all it's just saying is that yeah maybe some windows will be broken
probably not many but yeah no shit more windows will be broken as you move closer to the damage
zone thanks for explaining that for me just pre-break your windows
so yeah might have some broken windows
but would there be fallout it might depend on like the wind like it might depend on like the
way the wind is blowing I mean there was a little bit of a scare earlier about Chernobyl
because Russia like took Chernobyl area and like Chernobyl like spread when it when it
melted down you know way back when that happened like it was like radioactive dust
flew all over Europe and that was just that was just a power plant that wasn't even a bomb
yeah so like the dust from a bomb a nuclear explosion in Boston depending on on how nukes
spread that around I would imagine the dust would spread all over the US depending on wind patterns
and then yeah I mean all over the east coast probably yeah hmm no I'm sure it wouldn't cause
any problems no it'd be fine talk about 9-11 talk about uh this would be this would be way cooler
than 9-11 if they knew if they knew this is depressing uh I mean they're probably not I mean
they're probably not gonna do that they're probably not but like we can't know that until the future
they're probably there's probably not gonna be nuclear war you know probably not an
gonna be nuclear war if there was I feel like Boston is not the highest priority target like
what are the odds they would target Boston out of all places I mean probably not the highest
not the lowest either it's probably like maybe eighth or ninth down the list
Washington DC New York City uh Los Angeles probably not that's more of an entertainment hub than
anything else uh I guess well actually I mean if they're going for the east coast
actually Boston would probably be like yeah pretty high up on the list but why would they go for
the east coast why not the west coast um okay well the thing I think about is like
there's there's no use worrying in your day-to-day about nuclear Armageddon because
uh like I I don't think you could really do anything about it you could you could maybe prep
for it I guess you could fill your bathtub with water then slurp it out when when the time comes
I'm I mean yeah that's right that's correct I don't know it's not to like act like it's not
going to happen but to not like stress out over it because yeah I mean maybe it'll be sure I mean
I can't do anything about it
I don't know I don't know okay well I feel like we've covered this
I feel like we've said all there is to be said about nuclear Armageddon
the PCP is your premier source of news and in fact you don't need any other coverage
than what we offer you right here uh the next next uh voicemail oh sorry I skipped one whatever
this one's called farmers have no standards three two one go dudes if you want to have like confirmation
that kiwi farmers have no moral standards then look no further it's been saying its own thread
people are literally defending Trixie over the fact that Ben is profiting off the blue rays
therefore her work and clearly avoiding the fact that she's spent like half a decade procrastinating
on making the blue rays and failed delivery on other quick start of promises yeah pretty wicked
stuff so continue to buy more blue rays off of Ben when Trixie fun weeks through mode it'd be totally
hilarious the the yeah kiwi farms will it's funny because obviously like in Trixie's thread
they hate Trixie they'll say whatever they'll say mean things but then in in my thread which
has not updated in a while it's been dead for like quite a while uh but yeah like it in any given
person's thread they'll just say they'll say bad things about so-and-so and they'll do they'll do
they'll do whatever they have to do they'll praise whoever else they they need to in order to make
the person that they're here to hate on look bad they they'll just they're just there to hate uh
which is you know i guess that's more like wiwi farms more you know i'm glad somebody said
more like wiwi yeah that's good um so uh yeah pretty cringe pretty cringe
uh um dur uh anyway uh right the one that i skipped is called
the one that i skipped is called i just i posted it sorry i'm dumb it's called
nicola tesla was right it will transform your entire dna three two one go oh no a tone
yep there it goes what am i now it's okay because what i've already fucked my dna up
all those all those spike proteins already i get more or less chromosomes that's what i want to know
okay i'm more i'm more covet than men uh you got more i hope i got more chromosomes so i can be like
the like ancient egyptians that were like 30 feet tall and that's why they built statues that size
because they were life-size because they had no chromosomes that's why they built the pyramids
they just picked up the bricks and put them down yeah they were just really big they were just
building they were just trying to build like a chair but then they were like uh but let's just
make it pointy on top i guess just because it's funny but where's the giant egyptian skulls and
skeletons well they went such this well they went back to the home home they're either in
atlantis or they went back to the home planet of the hebrus or they were uh they joined satan in
when they did the lucifer experiment or you know there's don't ask stupid questions there's reasons
for all these things uh uh maybe maybe just thinks has like a giant skeleton inside it
oh he's he's hold he's holding all the giant bones yeah all the giant bones are in there
if only there were some way to dig through solid rock alas we'll never know uh the next one
oh shit well there's an image but there's also a uh a whatever voicemail it will transform your
entire dna wow the 528 hertz frequency we found the magic frequency oh here it is
crazy 528 hertz this whole time wow nobody's done that before that this the hertz they just
haven't tried that one who who would have guessed all this time i've been blasting 528 hertz
over the airwaves i didn't even know it was going to transform all this dna that's crazy
all right let's listen to the voicemail three two one go
eww
okay okay cool thanks next voicemail is called nomar club uh print from shitty dating advice
at oldpcp.com yes we remember when we used to sometimes give dating advice that was funny
that was pretty epic yeah that was it was amazing it's just every once in a while we gotta we gotta
bring it back uh okay next one yeah no uh three two one go hey what's up guys sorry i haven't made
a voicemail in a while or ever and i started listening around retcon 4 and uh although i
catch that with basically all the backlog i still haven't heard the lore about bansaint being the king
of fives how about that oh and uh if you feel like going into it i was dating for you how was
all the past couple of years going and all and before that do you concern yourselves with portal
trifos like dating and like do you even care the king of fives thing that was like a
joke that a friend made about me because i guess he thought that all the girls i was
seeing at the time back then i guess he just didn't think they were very attractive oh i get it yeah
but you know that guy i i mean um i'll i'll just say it that guy that guy's a chubby chaser that
guy only likes fat girls so i mean you know different strokes for different folks i guess
i don't know if i don't know if i don't know if we i don't know if everybody would agree with
his assessment but that's okay he's entitled to his opinion uh it's fine you know i'm not gonna
judge i'm i don't judge him i don't know why he had to fucking do me like that but okay it's ah
my heart ah okay um cramp anyway um dating is bad and i haven't done it uh in a while uh listen
i'm making my masterpiece all right making my masterpiece i got no time for trifling
okay no time for trifling can't let bitches get me down uh
uh man i was thinking man some people
some people like have a conversation about like what are we gonna eat today
some people do that like every day like with their with like with their girlfriend whatever
with their their husband or whatever some people talk about that all the time
um can you imagine i well i guess so but uh wouldn't be that much to imagine i don't
know why i would bother imagining it i just um just glad i don't have i'm just glad i don't
have to do it i'm glad i don't have to like have a conversation about it i'm glad i'm just glad
you know i kind of i like i kind of like i like being in control of my own destiny i like that i
don't have to uh worry about like another like what another person's doing or what they're eating
or what just for instance what they're eating i just have my shit in the fridge and i just go
to the fridge and i eat it and i don't have to think about anything else i have no other considerations
and that's good that's how i like it uh so that's what i think about dating
uh the food the food the food concerns are just too pressing i can't deal with it
um dating is a scary um yeah i don't feel like i uh i'm cool
women therefore bad women are bad and they should they should leave me alone
uh that was a joke uh that was joke that's just i'm not actually
such an it's a joke i'm actually even such anistic um sorry sorry women women listen
late ladies sorry i'm i'm so sorry you have it so you have it so rough already and i'm just
and i'm just making it even worse for you uh i i shit is there anything else to say about that
i don't know uh what's the app tinder i hate it that's my opinion on dating just makes me sad
just makes me depressed looking through that i haven't i haven't looked at it in a while you know
i have like i have like a shit i think i might have had like a renewed a subscription to it or
whatever uh this past year without even noticing because i just wasn't paying attention uh i have
like that i haven't looked at it in a long time uh there was a time when i used it a few years ago
to pretty decent success and then i don't i don't know if i changed or the app changed
but then like i tried using it again uh maybe a year or two ago and it was like total total
failure like i definitely heard of like like because the whole point of their business model
is that people are lonely and they stay alone so you have to pay out the ass to get like actual
matches um yeah and they've just increased that aspect of the app more and more well i well i did
like okay i'll say it yeah i did i remember you did but like like have you did that was the last
time you did it were you paying that was the yeah the last no the first time when i was using it for
free it was when it worked oh and it was fine yeah and then two years two years ago i put some money
about two years or something like that i put some money into it whatever i got like a premium membership
i i got some super likes or whatever whatever bullshit i think i paid like maybe 70 for like a
year subscription or something you know whatever yeah pretty lame but whatever i did it uh and
it just it just i just i just i think i got nothing and it's just and it uh and i was just uh
i swear it used to work i swear i used to get results on it and then the site when i went
back to it just nothing just i don't know i have no i don't know why i have no again i don't know
if i changed or the app changed or what uh hobo fuck hobo was my fault i like to think it's not
my fault um yeah i don't know i don't know about that anyway i haven't thought anyway that was
disheartening and i haven't thought about it in a while uh yeah okay next one is no voicemail
just an image these i like these fish these pog fish like mud no no watch average ben enjoyer
yeah just coming out of that out of them out of the mud yeah out of the slime yeah he's he's he
knows what's up these these two idiots these two idiots are just uh they wouldn't know
quality content if it uh if it fucked him in the air uh and so it will right now uh anyway
next voicemail is called comrad discount uh let me get that right here
there it is okay three two one go hello comrades nicole i would like to buy a copy of
road to red gun however nicole i do have a lot of money because nicole i buy lots of vodka
so nicole i would like to know nicole i get comrad bonus or comrad discount for nicole
is nicole comrad let nicole i know um i mean i don't care uh if you make me a funny
if you send me if you send me a message or an email that's funny enough
yeah i'll probably give you i'll probably send you one for a discount yeah whatever i don't care
that much i'll give you like ten bucks off just pay for shipping whatever i don't care uh but uh
just make an effort honestly if honestly if uh yeah when people ask me like hey uh i can't uh
i kind of like don't want to like pay a full price like can i get a discount i'm usually just like
yeah fine you know because i because like most people don't want to most people wouldn't bother
if you're if you want the thing enough if you want the thing enough
that you're coming and asking me for it but you're a kind of like embarrassing yourself like
i'm poor though but like i really want it i'm usually just like oh this person actually wants
this person's putting some effort in oh they want the thing oh they should have the thing
okay i mean you you already got them printed so you just need to shift them anyway so
i i still have maybe like 40 i still have maybe like 40 copies in a in a box maybe 30 something
something like that i've got i mean i may never move them all and that's okay um okay next one
is called oh it's no voicemail it's just a question is tom the new former pcp member
uh no he's just hasn't been around lately he just hasn't yeah i mean
i assume he has said that the like the new pcp recording time is too early for him
and nothing has been done by anyone to change that he did or so he did he did say that but he
didn't like say that he wanted it changed back yeah so i mean i mean if you i mean if he wanted
to change back because he wanted to be on we could do that but he i don't know yeah
whatever he would he would he could if he if he were in if he wanted to we could talk about it
but he has just has not been a presence like i said he has not uh responded to any of my
questions about the Spotify stuff or anything i don't know maybe it's saber spark stuff maybe
it's elden ring uh maybe it's a little column a little column b uh next voicemail is called
jesus christ superstar wait uh wrong number here jesus christ superstar three two one go
hey ben is jesus christ superstar your favorite musical probably yeah i've noticed that you've
referenced it a lot over the years just curious yeah i don't watch i haven't watched a ton of musicals
or anything but i really really liked the old 70s uh jesus christ superstar yeah i've i've
since uh seen that film yeah it's pretty good i love it i was so into it uh lino all the songs
it rules i'll continue to reference it probably for the rest of my life uh next one is called
you've forced my hand okay three two one go since you couldn't understand my one dollar mic
i became a cyborg to output clean mp3 files okay enjoy the recording of police report
i happened to intercept with my aunt tenney so why did you break into this house the owner is
beyond poverty there is nothing to steal they are even churning cards that's how bad it is
churning cards is what rich people do actually what do you see an attractive female with unusually
large breasts this isn't female this is ben saint the owner of this house i couldn't stop thinking
about this picture ben saint with large mommy milkers so i've been sneaking into his house for
last few months and added estrogen into his sparkling water what is a noble goal you are free to go
young man uh what do i think i think uh there's a lot uh going on here all sides make some good
excellent points um you know what speaking of sparkling water let me grab one out of my little
mini fridge sure it would be nice if it was as easy as that just put a little e into into some water
hey by the way i don't know if that guy maybe is listening but this is the mini fridge that a guy
bought me after i uh won noida on twitch that one time uh so if that guy who bought me a mini
fridge for beating noida is listening uh thanks for the mini fridge dude crazy yeah uh that was
crazy man it's how often do you stream these days gibb like occasionally yeah just occasionally i
streamed like twice in a row the other day i saw you tweeting that you were you were gonna be streaming
yeah uh i think uh probably not streaming ever is probably a big mistake for me because like
you know sometimes people would watch it and sometimes people would get excited and sometimes
people would do things like pledge me some money or buy me a mini fridge uh and that was pretty crazy
i feel like by i feel like i might gain here's it's like like 80 20 rule i feel like maybe i would
gain you know 80 percent of the benefits of streaming if i streamed maybe 20 percent as much
like me if i just maybe did a stream like once a month maybe people would appreciate it yeah of
course whereas so it's probably it's probably stupid that i that i never do it like on my channel
i mean when i when i stream a lot of the time i don't really know what to play yeah and then
i'm doing it and i'm like oh there's technical problems oh it's it's oh i don't know what to
say it's like it's it's not always some part of it feels like it could be nice and and relaxing
and just chilling out but i get i get a little worked up about like people enjoying it or not
when i really shouldn't yeah probably just enjoy yourself and then people will
hopefully enjoy it as well along with you i mean no noida is like the only game that i play anymore
like the these days uh so i mean i guess i was gonna stream a game it would probably just be
yeah i've been playing like Animal Crossing Pocket Camp which is a mobile game it's not something
to stream not that i would figure out i would know how to stream it from my phone and then the other
thing i've been filling my time with is solitaire online and it's like what a stupid set of things
that i'm constantly doing uh surely i surely could be playing like some cool thing for people to
talk about possibly possibly i should never feel like we'll never know we'll never know yeah um
i i don't know maybe i'll change my life around in some way after i finish slime and punishment
or maybe not guess we'll see uh anyway next voicemail is called gib good wow
three wow three two one go so anyway it's kind of unfair that bin gets all the attention gib
you are cutie and that game demo is pretty pog thanks always wanted to chuck useless liberal
zoomers with their iPhones at collectibles as anarcho communist spitting literal fire
you fulfilled my childhood dream thank you hell yeah you're welcome this reminds me uh i meant
i'm curious i was curious i was gonna say this after uh the first voicemail from uh marowak
uh about collecting all the fairy bits how i wonder how long it takes most people i feel
like as i was looking for those last bits a long time i feel like i was dumb the last bits that i
found it took me about two hours to get the last ones and the last ones that i found were in a cave
that were at the beginning they were near the beginning of the game so i had you said that
yeah i had missed an early secret and then i just it took me a long time to go back and fit and find
it again because i had those like so i yeah i've been i've been looking at like people's playthroughs
and and stuff if you by the way if anyone wants to like record a video uh playing the game i will
watch it because i need to know what people like tend to do when they're playing the game for the
first time uh good good good research potentially yeah yeah for sure because a lot of people do see
that after a second um but some people do just what past it it is sort of you mean that secret
that secret yeah i completely completely didn't even notice any damn thing she's gotta be super
smart that's what you gotta do unfortunately gib the the covid brain fog reduced my iq point by
exactly the one point that made the difference unfortunately it uh yeah i failed my uh my spot
check well this game is not for you there's no easy mode no i lost i lost the game i mean i i beat it
but i i beat it like bad so i lost the way to the way to lose the game is to beat it oh i didn't
find the last lizard or no there's more lizards there's more lizards there's more lizards than the
ones you found has anyone found uh i don't know has anyone found the most lizards i i haven't seen
posts about it uh so i don't think so i don't think anyone's found steel viper steel viper
showed me the red lizard she was like hey i found this lizard and then didn't tell me where well you
go to play the game you go to find it i told her where i found my god damn lizards oh oh well uh
uh that's just damn the first person to prove the first person to prove they have found all the
lizards um i will shout out on twitter i will say well done yeah uh maybe i'll give people a chance
maybe i'll maybe i'll give people a chance to shoot for that uh because uh i mean i'm at four
and there's at least one more uh did you say there was maybe you didn't i forget if you said how many
there were or not i forget as well but i won't say it i will i will allow people to be frustrated
and not know anything yeah some someone will be like i found this many and that'll be the
right number and you'll be like oh okay you did it well there well there's at least five i know
um yeah okay next one is called the real tommy oliver posting there is i'm shady
perhaps three two one go
ben i've warned you but you didn't listen i am minting all your stuff on the blockchain right
now and i am going to sell it all for huge all my stuff ha who is that some mustache guy
tommy oliver but why did you shoot me maybe this is just a hippie bleeding hard artist in me
but i think there's more to life than profit call it soul call it passion call it just chilling the
fuck out but i like being able to leave my job at the door sit down on the couch and just play a
fucking video game then you shot the wrong person we all just slaves to those in power
fighting for breadcrumbs that follow their table
i love the imagery of tomm shooting someone just immediately talking like a youtuber yeah
maybe i'm doing a little bit of a tuber voice explaining the rationale
yeah yeah um that's what saberspark would be like if he shot you like i'm just saying
all all i wanted was a was a was a reboot of sponge bob but they had to make them babies
for some reason and i don't get it uh unloading a clip into uh into me for some reason about that
uh okay next one is called i got yo intro dog right here three two one go welcome to the pcp
for all your gay men developer needs gay men for you yes intro we found the new intro
oh wow just just just put a sick beat over it and uh we're good to go uh uh ellie is our
you know what to do next voicemail is called don't forget your website and then a cute little
emoji wait let me post the emoji i like i like these
yeah a little japanese one little japanese one i like them um i i i did i i used to be a patron
of japanese emoticons dot com uh but i stopped because i kind of quit using those i kind of quit
using them uh they were sort of a thing that i used a lot for a while but i sort of fell out of the
habit and i was like well i just gotta let that website die uh i was one of like six patrons
that it had uh now is five um next uh no uh anyway yeah here it is it's called don't forget your
website three two one go could you upload the mp3 podcast to your website pretty please
i uh i don't know how i've never done it before tom did it
tom wasn't if only tom wasn't busy barging into people's in voicemailers rooms and shooting them
dead um he could he could get the the audio sorted i would do it if i knew how i would i would do
it if i knew how dudes i it's uh it's a bit of a bummer it's a bummer that people like uh
you know they want the episodes on these uh platforms and they can't get them
i mean uh sorry uh shit um okay uh yeah okay we've been over that anyway next one is called
ain't it really sus when people use they them for out trans women three two one go
oh was that sound effect was it a i don't know um uh yeah sometimes it's a little bit sus it's um
sometimes it can be sometimes it's uh i would say that i sometimes accidentally without really
thinking default to they them um for for for trans women um yeah not because you know of any of like
oh transphobia reason it's just sort of like they're different now and um i've gotta like i i use they
them like for people normally anyway but when it's a trans woman you should make an effort to not use
they them and instead use the or trans anyone i mean if you use it for everybody like like
i think it's if you use she she her he him whatever i mean if you i mean if you use if you're using
they for everybody yeah it's okay but nobody but nobody it's it's it's like i that's why i wouldn't
say it's sus i would say yeah you can tell when somebody's avoiding when saying a pronoun that's
yeah when they don't want to say when when you when you know it's sus when you know that they know
that this person is a she and you and it seems like they're deliberately not saying yeah there's
you just say it once it's fine but like yeah it's not it's not it's not sus it's not sus in and of
itself but it can be a little it can be a little sus for sure um uh sure yep okay nothing else to
say about that uh next one is ben's weekly reminder play delta rune chapter two oh yeah i should uh
do that yeah yeah you should stream it you should stream it we've been saying we should
stream it for months now well no i mean you could stream it and then i would watch oh
oh my god i'm like a ben saying stream damn i guess i could just i guess i could just stream it
huh because it would be like so old and everyone would be backseat gaming it's like i can't believe
ben saying doesn't know what he's doing true um fascinating a fascinating proposal uh hey you
want to know what's making me sad right now what what's making me sad right now gib is that last night
i got hungry and i ate and i ate half my calories for the day after midnight before i went to sleep
ain't that ain't that just uh ain't that just tragic don't that just make you cry so you can't
eat anything or like you can only i can eat a bit i can eat uh yeah i i can eat like uh like
500 more calories left which is not that much do the rest of the day i'm gonna have like a big
like chicken nugget mcdonald's delivery i just need a big chicken nugget party sometimes you just
need it you know what if i'd save my calories like a good boy i could have a big chicken mcnugget
party but uh unfortunately you know what i'm not even that sad i have a great i actually have a great uh
because i've i've uh my i've found all the best things to buy i make uh i make wraps now i'm
making uh i'm making sandwich wraps with low-carb tortillas these wraps that i'm making they're
like 150 calories a piece i can eat so many wraps in a day i can eat so many wraps it's crazy
it's amazing it's great uh and they're delicious i love them uh i just wish
all the only thing i could ask for is i could eat even more but alas it's so strange to hear
ben sainte say he loves like a carbohydrate and does not specify that it is a keto version well
no they okay but they are actually it's low it's low-carb uh it's low-carb tortillas okay it's just
it's just that i'm not eating them specifically because they're low-carb it i'm eating them because
they are low calorie as well it's like 40 calories per wrap which is like it's nothing it's nothing
they're so filling it's delightful um what was i talking about that was totally off topic uh anyway
uh yeah i ate i got wait no i'm on the tangent so i'm going on it i finally i finally got uh
fucking hana ferds hana ferds always says that they're in stock from all these weird flavors
of one of my uh my new ice creams my new low low calorie ice creams nix nix ice cream they always
say they have cherry chocoflaka they always say they have rocky fjord they always say they have
swedish munchies they always say they have swedish apple pie flavor they never do they don't have
any of that shit they're lying so i finally i ordered from wegmans and they did have cherry
chocoflaka they did have rocky fjord they didn't have the other ones but that's okay and i got them
and they were great they were too good so i ate them last night and now i only have 500 calories
left for my whole day and that's she's tearing me up she's tearing me up this is what i this is
what i'm up this anyway this is this is what i'm up to these days okay next one is called uh
ben saint's first album there it is wait one more thing one more thing i gotta complain i gotta
complain more about ice cream look at listen look at this shit all right look at this shit
you're gonna this is gonna blow your fucking mind i sure it sure will this is going to obliterate
your mind all right look at this i bought some of these just because i was like i guess i'll try
him and just see what they're about this is from a company called dream pop plant-based dream bites
right yeah dream pop makes dream bites they dream pops are like a popsicle version of these
these are like a chocolate covered you know a little all right as you can see they don't call it corn
as you can see they don't call it uh ice cream they call it frozen dessert because it's plant-based
so you know whatever that's fine um i bought a cup of these these cost the same these cost
these are like five bucks for this cup it looks like it's a pint of ice cream it's not the cup is
small and it's like mostly air it's full of air there's only like a dozen of these fucking little
things in them and they're smaller than they look on the box and the final thing you see how look at
their shape they've got that crazy d20 ice isohedron shape well they don't fucking look like that
they're just little like rectangular blobs it's it's not even close and i'm like it doesn't like
man i was so mad i was so mad at these it was all air it was all fucking air they didn't even
fill the fucking cup it's not a flex that your cup of ice cream is only 300 calories when there's
no fucking ice cream in it bro when it's just empty dog you have not made a low calorie product
you have simply sold me very little products they got you they got me they tasted all right
they tasted pretty decent even there just wasn't there well this wasn't very much of it although
i will say it was kind of tart the like berry uh frozen dessert inside was kind of tart it was
nice with the chocolate i think the berry flavor is probably the only one that seems good because
i think that's sort of like sorbet flavor would be really weird with the other flavors that they
offer which is a birthday cake vanilla and a cookie dough i don't know i don't think that would work
as well with like the sorbet kind of kind of texture okay that's my that's what i have to say
about dream bites i would not recommend them uh no when i say dream bites i'm talking about the
youtuber and i don't like him is that a youtuber do you not remember dream oh yeah no yeah no yeah
i remember the minecraft guy he was bad he cheated at minecraft he cheated in a speed run and that's
bad that's bad the thing about him is is that that that animation he made where he like he he
treated the animators really badly and like forced them to crunch to get it finished and it looks
really weird yeah and he throws his weight around like he's some big hot shot because he's a big
subscriber he's got big subscriber uh what is it adam from why adam yms said he thinks dream
seems like a pathological liar and uh i think that sounds that's that rings true and i don't
see any reason not to believe that so uh i'm just gonna go with that yeah he seems like a psychopath
uh yeah uh fuck him uh next voicemail is called was the last one did we play the last one no we
didn't uh 79 it's called ben sains first album three two one go ben you have an amazing voice
you should make an album sing all your favorite songs or hell just do originals
ben sains sings the hits i would like i would like to uh i would like to be like a singer
i think i would like to maybe be in like a band i think that would be cool but i would want to sing
and i don't really play any instruments very well i mean i guess i could figure it out i play
instruments we could start a band but i wouldn't want
i would want to do gigs i don't know no i say that out loud but now i think about it
i was like oh but it'd be so embarrassing what if we weren't good what if it wasn't good
what if we bombed oh no oh no it's a nice idea and i could enjoy it but like
i'd have to be really proud of the of the of the art that i was displaying you know i wouldn't
just do it like with you know i wouldn't just do it like randomly that sucks well how else do you
do it i don't know i'm kind of talking myself out of it now uh sometimes it seems like something
i'd like to do but uh also i don't know if i have the commitment to such a thing to actually
go through with it and i mean how would i even how would you even do it anyway uh
you go up to a venue and you say i got a band or can we play at the thing yeah sure sure
but how do you get a band uh you talk to a person you go up to a person who's uh
standing around you say do you play an instrument do you play an instrument and eventually you'll
find would you would you like to play a company for accompaniment for me the star the lead singer
who does nothing else you write the songs and i'll just perform them thanks
yeah okay i knew you would like that thank you let's do it i guess i guess you just go to places
like open open mic nights and talk to the participants and if people say hey that was
really really good what you did there you do like a karaoke i'm looking for a singer in my band
i don't know if you know i don't know if i'm good enough i don't know if i'm a good enough
singer to be like a singer in a band i don't know if i have like those chops like i think i'm okay
but i think i'm i'm not like i'm i'm i'm okay and i don't know if that really cuts the mustard
uh i i then again i guess a lot of vocalists are not actually great singers you know you don't
necessarily you don't necessarily have to be a great singer to to be a you know i mean a to vocalize
a song that people like i mean famously like freddy milk mercury doesn't really have that much of
like a range but he's he's so good at what he does that it and it works really well for queen
yeah yeah i guess is that true about freddy i didn't know that but like you know i remember
hearing that and i guess i just believed it so maybe i'm talking out of my a s it could it could
be true i don't i don't know i've never i've never heard anyone say that about freddy but like maybe
like he's he's great and it's like i think it was some sort of singing maybe it's not range
i'm talking about but like in terms of like singing skill i don't know how you measure that you know
what yeah it's not a diss freddy mercury sounds great um i guess a better example is like uh what's
his face from the fucking oh ac dc oh yeah he sounds like a screeker screecher but like it works
so well for ac dc who's who's the i mean young or is that the other guy i don't know a lot of the
music lore that i know i got from a tot in the shadows videos i'm thinking of like the guy who's
saying um eve of destruction like that guy kind of sucks but he had a hit uh like his his voice
is kind of bad um same with um oh who's the guy is it bob dillon like bob dillon doesn't really
have much of a like his voice yeah he's a he's a songwriter more so than he is like a vocal man
but yeah writes really good songs right yeah you don't need to be good at anything to do
everything exactly that's that's my whole career in a nutshell i like i realized one day i don't
actually have to be good at anything just do shit and i hope it works out and you know what it did
it was true um well okay uh next next voicemail is called is this uh yes clearing something up
we have like maybe six or seven left i think oh my god uh we got yeah we got like seven left
okay oh i posted it twice okay clearing something up three two one go hey guys just clearing something
up here there's nothing you know last week when i said uke studio is dead i meant like trixie or riley
i meant like they're literally dead so all these shitty new content like i killed them basically
kill the channel i just meant like that's the idea is dead okay okay fair enough um no i meant i
meant i literally murdered them um next one is called the gen nine fire starter is based on a red pepper
three two one go
okay uh yeah yeah i get yeah i guess i i see i didn't realize it at first but yeah it i see it
it may it still makes me wonder if he's gonna be like fire grass type but i don't know people have
said fire ghost because ghost pepper yeah yeah that would be that would be amusing i suppose
i haven't done that before fire ghost yeah that'd be pretty cool um and that would mean like one of
the other starters would be something psychic or something dark i mean maybe people have said
that um the cat will be grass fairy which would be pretty cool yeah yeah is there already a grass
fairy pretty sure there must be some i mean so lots of fairy types look like they're grass
type oh whimsicott yeah whimsicott is grass fairy um i like whimsicott uh
and uh you know i think uh was it um was it was it izzy's tweeted that um
the yeah red ghost pepper guy disproves the zodiac theory but like
not necessarily like he could turn into like a serpent there's gonna be a zodiac killer in the
new pokemon game do you know about like how all the fire starties are uh are um they're animals
all the fire starters are animals from the chinese zodiac or they have been so far i did not know
that was there a cow fire um i i don't think so hold on um fire you'll see for you'll see it
and it'll be like oh yeah yeah totally totally true all right you know cindy quill is a little bit
of a stretch actually yeah it's not a mouse it's supposed to be uh like a like a bat like a badger
or like a like a like a like a wolverine right um i thought it had leaves uh what's the thing that
isn't a hedgehog it has the spines a porcupine porcupine maybe yeah i thought that the fire was
like spikes yeah maybe it's supposed to be like that i kind of thought it was a badger whatever it's
i mean it's not a rat yeah that's that's a that's a stretch that's a stretch and
i don't know like i could totally see this pepper thing turning into like a serpent of some kind
which would oh you know could you know a finnican being the dog is wrong very wrong it's like it's
it's like like sort of the same but like dogs and foxes are very different like if there was
a dog fire starter they would definitely be using that instead of finnican and then finnican would
go nowhere hmm are dogs are foxes not dogs they're they're like canine adjacent like it's really
it's it's a very superficial similarity i feel like there like pig and pig and torchic rooster
like those all make sense but that one's more of a stretch than i think i think i think cindy quill
is a bigger stretch but bigger stretch yeah but but finnican yeah anyway i'm just i'm just saying
i'm not sure i feel like it's completely disproved if we if we accept it thus far i feel like this
new one is not you know let's wait and see what the final evolution is obviously it was some kind
honestly if it were some kind of fire snake i think that would be pretty cool uh yeah yeah
okay next one is called also ben do a soul link nuzlocke and then this is three two one
one okay um you know i heard about soul link nuzlocke's from um cough and a frame those guys
from the old rfck crowd yeah marin pan chimes in about the zodiac thing the crocodile could become
more snake like male crocodiles are called bulls okay if that would be some real bullshit if like
they they tried to claim it's a bull because of some nomenclature shit so no but yeah it could
be snake it could be snake like um i kind of hope it does i think it's cool idea uh yeah a frame in
cough told me they were doing a soul link nuzlocke and i guess what that is it's two people nuzlocke
at the same time and they each catch a pokemon you know you each catch a pokemon on your route
or whatever and then your the two pokemon that you each catch on the same route are soul linked
and then if one of you who's dies if one of you's dies then the other one has to release
their linked guy so it's so it's like if somebody sucks yeah so if you're if you're a partner if
your soul link partner sucks you just have to fucking deal with it as well crazy um i don't know
i don't know if i would like it very much it's very frustrating i feel like you're doing the
nuzlocke and then you get a message like oh yeah you're gonna have to kill like that pokemon yeah
it's just i don't know it's it's just like a nuzlocke but also someone else is like fucking up
and and it's like ruining your day
i mean i guess i guess it could be fun but i'm not i feel like i feel like i would rather
if i was gonna make a nuzlocke harder i would just impose more restrictions on myself you know
i wouldn't put my fate in the hands of someone who might just completely screw me over
or completely randomly you know what i mean me yeah i think i would rather do that um
okay next one is called i'm out of breath few uh wait here it is okay three two one go
okay uh next one is called and the idea for the next radcon okay three two one go
and i got a brilliant idea for you i know you said you guys are thinking about doing radcon five
so if you do and you decide to do that tricksy lecture you gotta not just talk about how she
destroyed her channel and all that you also gotta talk about the fact that she would cry when she had
to pay taxes or she treated the boo like shit or anything you can think of honestly just destroy
her make everyone hate her completely ruin her more than she already has if i could do that
if i could do that i already would have i've done the best i can i can't do anymore i'm sorry
i'm sorry uh did i meant did i mention that thing may may told me that uh the trixie used
taxes yeah trixie used to cry when she would bring up taxes oh joy makes me so happy um
um anyway next one is called uh where was i ben talk about your shitty fucking apartment more
it's funny okay there's no voicemail attached to that it's just a question um well my shitty
fucking apartment uh it's uh okay i kind of have all right uh i think it kind of looks like a dump
right now and by dump i mean like it's full of trash and like it's not like dirty trash it's not
like food waste it's not stuff that's gonna rot or anything but there's like a big pile of boxes
that i've like saved there's a big there's a big like pile of like bags because like i save my i
save paper bags and then some of the paper bags many of them in fact uh one two three four five
six seven of them in fact are just kind of laying around with uh with sparkling water bottle empty
sparkling water bottles filling them i guess i could take them out to the recycling if i wanted
but i mean i've got more floor space that i'm not using so why not just fill that floor
space with more bags of empty sparkling water bottles you know what i mean uh yeah sure whatever
so you know my room is uh it sucks to begin with and i'm not doing it any favors okay that's
that's what i have to say about that um
okay the next one is a youtube link and it says seven hour video this is what i meant to say
had better be on the blu-ray at gmail.com what is this whoa those tits whoa those tits
oh it's whoa those tits i love those tits so much right that's the line uh i mean if it's from if
it's from the the piece the the plebenweeb well the blu-rays contain the plebenweeb and thus
all component parts of it so there uh next one is called oh this this is the last one this is a
new one that was that arrived five minutes ago so good job you squeaked in at the last second
this is called revelations dimensional merge from owo at uwu.com three two one go
gino samuels chris chen documentary just came back and it's at about 2017 i think in the timeline
not long until it touches on ben's involvement at the very least slamming punishment and the
war on quickbill gino samuels doesn't you know cover every piece of chris chen media that every
bozo put out but these might be significant and that documentary gets about 500k views on average
500k really that's some you know some cue reforms people but that's also a lot of normies a lot of
new viewership might be coming this way i don't know we're already kind of preparing for it in rck
and actually what do you think about that what do you think of the documentary yeah i haven't uh
how it handles chris three or whatever i don't know uh brocrastinator's micro server five bucks a
month come do it come it's good it's fun there's pokemon okay thank you buddy we have this fun we
we said we were gonna we were gonna stream last week i've been i've been pretty busy i'm like pushed
for it uh yeah i have bits just been like i have just been what i just want to finish my fucking
comic after i finish slamming punishment we should definitely stream or i'll want to stream for sure
yeah sorry uh i think that i think that was for maren pan yeah sorry i have been uh distracted
we will we will do more we'll hang out on the stream on the minecraft server again in a bit
but anyway uh i haven't watched the geno samuel documentary i haven't literally not watched any
of it so is that the that's the extremely long form many the one that's 78 million parts yeah the
one that's like 60 parts long i think it's yeah um uh i don't know if it's gonna like yeah he might
mention uh he might mention um slamming punishment he might mention rfck maybe i don't know how
in depth he goes exactly i would imagine just based on the fact that there's so much
like content already in the documentary that you would get at least like a sentence because
christian did those like drawings for the card game well she did the cards and then
i mean was on a video where you it talked you interviewed her or something yeah i was like
in the call i can't remember what that was about that was related i think to to that stuff yes it
was related to the the rain and all that um yeah yeah i would i would uh yeah i think i'm likely to
get mentioned um you know i wonder i wonder if i have the game out by then if uh maybe uh he would
mention the game that would be kind of neat um so like uh geez i don't know what i don't have to
say about it uh the the the brain fog COVID brain fog COVID i'm more COVID than man it changed my
whole DNA um i don't know uh it's it's gonna be uh funny uh maybe uh i mean okay the cards the cards
uh i don't know like has he mentioned the cards because like a lot of what chris drew okay a lot
of what chris drew for the slime stuff was in the form of the twilight sparkle secret ship
flick folder cards and like most of those cards i don't know maybe this is just my opinion but they
seemed like completely irrelevant like who fucking cares uh like they do have like lore on them and
they do have like new characters on them honestly there probably is a lot there to like unpack if
you really wanted to honestly hmm you know what wonder if there's a lecture idea in that now that
i think about it uh those there were a lot of cards and they had a lot of like information
that was just like why would you ever read these fucking cards uh so i feel like maybe they the the
slime stuff the the rfck stuff might be mentioned along the same breath as the cards and like who
fucking cares about the cards so i could kind of see rfc the slime and punishment getting
shafted a little bit like that um but i don't know maybe if i make the video game maybe gino
would see the video game and maybe if he was impressed maybe he might give it a some some
discussion in the in whenever he gets around to talking about it i don't know gino i just i kind
of assumed that gino was a piece of shit because like every chris chan youtuber is a fucking garbage
monster demon uh who i just hate with every fucking fiber of my being and i just assumed he was one
like that too but i've been told that he's not as bad as like the other guys so i don't know maybe
he's fine actually i don't know lamal
okay i guess that's all i have to say about that uh and that was the last voicemail
i want to go and eat mcnuggets so bad i guess i'll go and i'll make i can make myself a little uh
a little turkey turkey caesar turkey caesar uh salad wrap with a little uh some greens and tomatoes
oh health health food huh is it you know it's not even you know you're better than me
no i just you like good food huh is that how it is no no i hate it no it's gonna
darn i wish i had those nuggets uh
uh geez um nugget pressure
um okay yeah that's it we've yes we've done another fucking four hour
the demo the free demo definitely play pumpkin alley the demo if it's out by now
which is not entirely impossible play phantom's revenge if not play it next week
uh play our video games pcp the pcp stands for play our video i don't know i don't know
i had this idea a while ago being like doing like p3 which is like e3 but with the procrastinators
and then we would like have uh like a pretend like oh we're doing video games there's a big
announcement we're on stage you you mentioned this i don't remember if you told me about it
or if you said it on the show but i think yes i put it in the chat at some point
because like tom was doing something it's like what what if we had like trailers what if we like
did a big old p3 honestly i mean why not like why wouldn't we do that like we're all
we're we're three podcasters who all make video games now so like
why wouldn't we do something with that um
you know uh yeah uh yeah is it rebrand time is it rebrand time is it time to change the tombstone
into like a pixel polygon into uh well we're not like gaming isn't low resolution that's not the
same thing speak for yourself i don't like i don't like how video games and low res 8 bit is
synonymous i'm gonna find a video game gamer i do anything but pixel art i'm gonna literally kick
your ass super nintendo video games peaked with the super nintendo best three solvent oh no no you
you said super nintendo not nintendo 64 not nintendo 64 that was bad no that was that was bad
well yeah yeah no no well yeah well actually yeah that's because it actually peaked with the ps2
and that's the where the games really are should be
hmm yeah i don't know um uh okay whatever you know you get what i'm saying though a video game
theme rebrand i don't know maybe you could have uh you could be in like 16 bit i could be ps2 model
and tom could be a ps1 model yeah oh yeah oh yeah true uh is that does that correlate to like
or ages yeah i am the oldest and tom is a little bit younger than me and you are a little younger
than him so yeah i guess it's uh uh the three generations three generations in one image grandpa
father and son all together daughter oh right sorry how dare you i saw a picture well well you
can't mix the you can't mix genders they all have to be the same i saw a picture of eight generations
of women it was like old lady on the brink of death and then just a regular very old lady
and then a kind of old lady and then a middle-aged lady and then a sort of adult lady and then a
young adult lady and then a teenager and then a baby that had just been born
it was like eight generations in one picture it was gross i hated it so you know that's what we're
doing i wonder what it feels like to look at your past and and and future sucks i hate it
okay that's the show goodbye i'm so tired i've just lost my ability to say words goodbye
end of the episode patreon.com slash the procrastinators uh the end goodbye