Hi everyone, Ben Thany St. Tano here, the worst procrastinator. Welcome to episode 221.
We're coming up on a 222, we're coming up on a milestone. Anyway, with me today, finally,
I'm not lonely this time. I've been saved. I've been saved from a shallow grave, Gibbontake.
Hey guys, I could have been on last week's episode, but I thought, I thought, uh, better
or not. I saw Ben Saint there and I was like, you know what, I'll let him dig his own grave this
time. I added everyone and you were like, no, I don't have anything to say, so I'm not gonna be on
The Pro Crastinators Podcast this week. And I was like, that's never stopped me. I know.
And then we got Tom Oliver. The Pro Crastinators Podcast Incorporated would like to issue a
formal apology for having such an embarrassing show last week. Not all of the Pro Crastinators,
like we're not a unified front on that. Once you know under capitalism, corporations are people,
so the corporate entity is speaking right now, disconnected from all of us.
I would like to apologize for taking so long to give the people what they've been waiting
for with the solo Ben cast, baby. Um, oh God, this, I just realized we haven't recorded a bonus
episode this month, have we? No. Are we gonna? I guess. Nate's been MIA and everything's falling
apart. We gotta do it. Are you guys robotting out or is that me? That's you. Shit, yeah, you guys
sound like crap. Okay, but we can make do. Uh, uh, so, uh, we should, I guess maybe after the episode,
we should talk about a bonus episode, but, but, but, but okay, but okay, we don't have to talk
about that right now. That's inside baseball. How's your guys week been? How's everything going?
How are you, how are you feeling? I'm feeling emotions. Um, yeah. Uh, all right, here's, here's
my one big announcement, and it's not an announcement. It's just sort of like a thing that's been on
my mind. A while ago I said, I'm going to do the Tezuka manga submission thing. And I still am.
I'm still trucking along, trying my best. Um, but I think all of July and June has been
like, like snails pace slower than the slowest, slow guy that could ever be considered someone
who is trying to do art is me. Uh, play, play the Gibbs stupid fucking idiot corner, uh, jingle
again. While I said that this is the stupid idiot corner. Are you stupid idiot dude? Is that a
re, is that a real jingle? It is. I assume it is. Do we have a real jingle for that? I think we honestly
do. Yeah. Good. Okay. I think we do. I don't, I don't listen to the show. So I don't know what,
what, what goes on here. No sane person should. And yet we are, he is, and yet we're not sane people.
So you think we would listen to it. Um, but uh, fucking I, I've been dragging my feet. I listen
to the show in the extent that I get in the call, I wait for everyone else to stop talking so that
it's my turn. And then I start talking until I can't say anymore. And then I, and then I tune
out and listen for another silence to fill. That's, that's the extent of my engagement.
I'm a very good listener. Clearly. Shut up, shut up.
I was dragging my feet. I was, I was getting all anxious because like the closer it gets to the
deadline, the, the more likely it is that I'm not going to be finished in time. And over, hanging
over my head was the fact that I had said publicly, I'm going to, I'm going to make it. I'm going to
do it. And, and that like singular thing, I think was like dragging me down more than anything
else was this idea that I had said publicly that I'm going to do this thing. And if I fail,
if I don't reach the deadline, um, then, uh, everything will be like terrible and I will be
a laughing stock and people will kick me out and onto the streets and they will say, give you shit,
you suck. And I was like, Oh no, that can't possibly be the way this goes. Uh, and so that
seized me up. And I was just sort of depressed for two months because as soon as I had one problem
that sort of hampered my, you know, creative flow, I didn't get in, I didn't, I didn't think
right. Uh, the anxiety of not getting it done forced me to just get worse and worse until I was
just not, I was catatonic. My, my headphones cut out for a minute there. What was the hurdle? What
was the, the problem that you were? The, the hurdle was that I, uh, well, I mean, literally I, I just
hadn't been, I've been trying to write a story and I just wasn't happy with it for a long time.
And I just also, you know, wasn't doing any of the, the writing like sitting down with a pencil
and paper and trying to write something, just nothing was coming. And so as the time ticked on
became more and more like anxious, like if I fail, it's, it would be, it will look bad. It would be
a bad look. And the, the fear of a bad look got me even more anxious and made it harder to come up
with stuff. But finally, I think I've come up with a story that I like, um, that has like a,
an structure and it's good. It's just, how long, how long is it? How long is it?
I don't know how long it will be. Um, I'm not, I've never really been good with like translating
story to comic page count. Gameplay. Okay. But, uh, I'm, I mean, I, I, I think if it's the 55 maximum
page count, um, I probably won't be able to get it done within the next month, unless I draw
constantly and hurt my hand. 55 pages in a month would be, you would, I mean,
uh, that's a lot. That's, that's, that's just preparing you for the, uh, the show and jump
life. You know, that's just what your life becomes at that point. Yeah. Yeah. Um, you gotta,
you gotta get, uh, you gotta give, um, you gotta hire an assistant. You gotta hire an
assistant is what you gotta do. Yeah. The thing really was that, uh, I was going downer and downer,
getting more and more depressed and anxious about the fact that I would be labeled a failure by my,
I don't know who, I guess, like the, the, the amorphous blood that is the public
and, and that would kill me inside. And then one day I was just like,
like, you know, why am I sad? I'm not dead. Everything's kind of all right. It's, it's just,
it doesn't matter. And then, then after that, like two days after that, I came up with a story. So it
really was entirely like the deadline that was killing me, the, the, the fear of failing the
deadline. And that's my story. Don't ever put a deadline on yourself. Ever. Ever. It's always bad.
Yeah, I absolutely agree with that dog. Uh, um, I, I mean, I, I think I've, I, I can relate
a bit recently, um, for a while. I just, I just couldn't muster up the motivation to, or not
the motivation, just couldn't, or just like the focus, like couldn't generate the focus
to like make, to make the slime and punishment finale. I don't know. And then I, uh, I don't
know, at some point I was just, and then like the longer I went without sitting and doing it,
the more I felt like, Oh, I hate it. I hate thinking about it. I don't want to think about it
because it makes me feel bad to remember that I should have done this a week ago or a month ago
or whatever. Yeah. Uh, yeah. I still haven't like sketched like any of the pages. I've still
have sketches from way back when it was a different story. And, uh, that could use, I could reuse
some of those, but like in terms of like what I can show nothing, I have nothing to show yet,
which seems bad, but I, um, I'm, I'm, I'm kind of over it. I'm just going to make what I make
when I come up with you and it will be whatever it is. Maybe you already do this. And if so,
I apologize for mansplaining. Um, but, uh, you should consider trying like make like
consciously making the effort to draw as little as possible. Do you do that already?
Do you know what I mean? I've talked about this before. Like in the comics, like as few
backgrounds as possible, include as little of the character as possible. Oh no, my, my philosophy
ever since, uh, uni where I learned this from a specific animator that I can't remember the name
of, but he like, I think he is like the creator of like rhubarb and custard, this old TV show.
Rhubarb and custard sounds delicious. It's just like a dog and a kid. I don't remember.
Um, but like the animation style, I think was the guy, that was the guy, um, was like
so minimalist and yet worked so perfectly. Um, and his, his philosophy, which is I, what I adopted
for, for all of my films that I made during uni was, uh, to just try to like the best thing you
could do as an animator is get away with drawing as little as possible and, uh, you know, making
doing as little as work as possible to get the maximum effect because you don't need
robbery. Like if you're, if you're drawing a background, why are you doing that? You don't
need to, it doesn't exist. You don't have to draw the background if you, if it's not relevant to
what's being shown, if you only draw the things that actually need to be there. And I'm like,
yeah, I really enjoy that frame of mind. One, because it's easier and two, because when it comes
to like slogging away at a background and I'm drawing trees with leaves on them, I'm like,
I don't give a fuck about this tree. Why am I drawing all of these leaves on it?
I don't care about this tree. I care about the guy in the foreground saying,
fuck the world. Like that's the part of the story that's important.
It's based, it's based because yeah, it's, it's easier and it's more, and yeah, you focus more on
like the things that matter in the story are probably the things that you care about. And so
you'll be drawing, you draw the things that matter. And also just because it's easier, you know,
you finish more stuff faster. And every time you finish a page, you're like,
yes, I did it. I done it. I got it. I got the serotonin. I got the whatever brain chemicals.
And then you can, you get more of that faster and faster until you're a fucking
junkie for it until you're a speed junkie. If you know what I'm saying,
yes. That's the plan. That's the plan. Yeah. Yeah, based. Yeah, based.
But also, I mean, that I think I've explained before that my character designs are all like
minimalist. Like the current like, if you know the Clarissa design that I've posted on Twitter
a million years ago, she doesn't have, she has hair covering her face because I don't like drawing
faces. You can't see her eyes. That's the best way for a character to be. They just have a little
mouth. That's it. Drawing eyes can be a little, I think I like drawing eyes. I think I tend,
yeah, no, I like it. No, you're stupid. No, that's dumb, dude. No, you fucked up.
If you look a pump, she's got triangle eyes. She doesn't have pupils.
Alley Oop is like the very easy, malleable like cartoon circle with a bigger, smaller,
dark circle in the middle. A lot of ghosts are the same. I like things that are really simple
looking. Back in the pony days, when I had to draw an eye, I learned how to draw that big pupil
with the big iris and the big like, like, like shiny, shiny spots reflecting the light on the
surface. And I, and I really enjoyed like the depth of it. I really enjoyed the like, oh yeah,
you can, you know, it's actually not that hard to like make it look like, yeah, this is like a big
fucking like shiny, shiny slime hole in like an eyeball. And like, it looks great. And you love it.
I think there's been time, I think there are a couple frames in the champion where I went too
far and I made like some characters look like really weird, have really weird like way too big
pupils and eyes. I'm thinking of that specifically, that one, what was his name, Damien. Damien,
there was the one I was thinking of. I think I went back and changed because I looked back
because like his eyes are fucked. I went too hard. I fucking remember talking to you about
that eye and you said, no, what's wrong with it? I, yeah, I think it took, it took a few people
mentioning it to me for me to be like, oh, maybe, maybe multiple people. He's just, he's just,
he's just so cutesy big eyes. Like, he, I don't think he looked cute. That was the thing. He
didn't look cute, but it looked like he was supposed to be cute. Right. Yeah, it was like a weird,
you know, whatever, whatever. I drew like a 65 page comic and I had one bad panel, exactly one.
That means my batting average is insanely high. So many hits, no misses, effectively no misses,
vanishingly small number. And then over on my comic is no bad panels in any of the things I've
done ever. So, you know, no, that's, they're all bad. They're all bad panels. They're all bad
panels over at gibbentake.site. See, the secret is you can't have bad panels if you don't draw
panels at all. You could. No, no, you're right. Shit. Fuck. Owned again. Art is once again,
the problem and not the solution. Tom, remember when you spent like a year modeling that room
to put in the comic? No, no, I don't. I don't remember this. You're kidding. Wait, no, for
Sorcerer's lost. You do. You do. That was when that was when you got into like the idea of using
3D. Yeah. Oh, the tavern. That didn't take, that took like a year. Wait, no. Yeah. Okay. I was,
I was exaggerating when I said a year, but like, I feel like there was like a whole,
it felt like to me, like for a long time, I was seeing like progress pictures of like
modeling the barrels and like, oh, putting the textures on the barrels and, and like, you know,
oh, like, oh, trying, like Poe trying to pose the character in the space, like trying to place the
scene in the panel or whatever. There was a couple like posts of just like putting out content,
but like the whole, the whole background was done in like a week was not very complicated.
So maybe, you know what? Maybe I mean, the real attack here is just that you spent,
you spent a week making a background and the comic never got finished. Like that's, that's,
that's really the pain point you want to go for. Yeah, you're right. So, you know what? I think I,
I think I just remember that whole, I remember that whole Sorcerer's lost era as like tavern era,
like, because I kept, I just kept seeing that tavern, like all the posts that were like tavern
related, you know? So I think maybe I just assumed you were modeling it the whole time,
but actually no. It was, it was done pretty, pretty swift. That was, that was an important
stepping stone to realizing polygons are better than pencils and pens, strictly better, strictly
superior. This is why we shouldn't allow them to teach computers in schools because it leads to
degeneracy, like not drawing comics in panels. Yes. I feel like the fall of Western civilization.
First, for the way that I tend to draw things, learning 3D would be far more difficult because
it takes like one second to draw Aliyup. It would take a while to model her. It takes me,
I think I'm with you on that. I think I can draw faster than I would be able to
do a background because I think I'm pretty good at the like, okay, if I do find myself having
draw like a big background, then that can take me forever. And it's a nightmare. But I would, I mean,
I don't know. It really depends on the background, right? Because if you're using, it does, if you're,
have a location you're going to like come back to throughout your entire series, it probably makes
sense to do a model or something of it. So you don't have to continue drawing it over and over
again, make sure that the layout stays consistent. But if you're just like going to a place for a
chapter, just fucking draw it. Yeah. Yeah, usually that's, that's what I mean. Usually it's enough
to draw a background once. And then from then on, you can just do characters, maybe with like one
object, maybe with like one or two, like very minimal like background details to like sort of
remind you of where you are. I feel like, like a flow plan would be more useful to refer to
because like if, yeah, I did do a floor plan of like Magda and Vincent's room before I started
the comic because I was like, okay, wait, where's, where's the bed? Where's the desk? Like, where's,
where's the coat rack? Where is everything in relation to each other? And then I always like
refer to it and just like to keep everything consistent. Because I'm thinking like, I feel
like you can tell when an image has been drawn using like a 3D, like tracing a 3D model.
Yeah. Because, because the, the, the camera that is used to capture it is always the same. Like
in, if you draw it, you could like add your own like weird angle to it and, and, and, and change
it in ways that 3D space cannot warp without looking silly.
Uh, you're right. That's true. I mean, you, you can tell more or less. I thought that Tom,
I thought that Tavern did a pretty good job of looking hand drawn from a lot of angles,
but yeah, you're right that you can.
Uh, do you remember that there's a while ago, I remember the fucking Joe Joe's bizarre adventure
anime was 3D now. And there was a behind the scenes look at one of the poses from the opening
or something. And they had to completely break the model in order to fit the arm in the way that
he was posing it on, uh, in, in the camera angle. Because 3D don't work like that.
Well, I mean, technically in the drawing, you're breaking his arm too. It's just,
you can draw whatever you want. So.
Yeah. I'm not, I'm not just saying like 3D is bad, but I'm like, I'm, I find there's,
there's too much of a coward to say that Tom, you're a freak. You've, you've, you've left the
path of wisdom. The third dimension man was not meant to meddle in the third dimension.
All right. I think it might be blasphemous.
Well, I spite God.
Fuck. Damn it. I hate it when people spite God.
Hey, hey, Ben.
Hey, Ben, atheism.
No, shut up.
Shut up.
Don't say that. Eleazar.
They don't call him Ben Saint.
Say three Hail Marys.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
Secular.
Seccy Row.
Wait, what?
Huh?
Video games?
Video games.
This week, every time I go downstairs, every time I see, I go downstairs, I see one of them playing
Bug Blast and they're getting all their, getting all those bugs all over, rolling around in the bugs.
That's unfortunate.
Yeah. Yeah.
But I don't know. It is what it is.
And then I look and I go.
I go to video games.
I look at the, I look at the guy.
I think of the games that I'm a fan of, like nostalgic for, that I grew up on.
I'm like, oh, oh, I love a diso game.
And then I hear, I hear the common consensus, generally disparaging.
Game bad. Game bad.
Game bad, game not so good, actually.
If you think about it, it sucks.
And I'm like, I'm like, no, no.
Clearly.
Hey, idiot, clearly you've never actually thought about that game you like.
Because if you did, you would know it was bad.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I'm like, oh no, my childhood, my favorite games being destroyed.
My problematic faves.
And I listen to these videos, these analysis, these critiques, these people, these genuine humans.
And I hear them say these things.
I'm like, that can't be the fucking case.
This is unfair. This is wrong.
And then I realize that I agree with everything they're saying because it's very well-argued.
And I slump down in my chair and I'm like, there's no hope for this world.
There's no hope for me because there's no way I can argue myself out of this paper bag.
There's no, there's no.
All you gotta do, Gib, just to be like, yeah, I agree, but I like it anyways.
I know, but it's so annoying to have been on the wrong side of history.
By not being a Mario fan or something stupid like that.
There's a wrong side of history in that case.
It's all personal preference.
You can, like, whatever the fuck you want.
I know, but I do like the critiques and analysis.
So it comes up, like, compared to, like, the length and breadth of the video game sphere,
all of the games that came out in this year and all of the games of this genre, this particular one, my favorite,
is the ugly duckling and the one that nobody likes and nobody remembers.
And it's like the awkward bunch, the awkward one of the bunch.
And I'm like, no, that's me. You're saying that about me.
But I don't have any argument to say, actually, it's good because it isn't good and they're right.
And I'm sitting here seething that me is not good.
Me bad game. Me doesn't hold up.
And I throw my toys out of the pram and I jump around and I shit.
Well, that's understandable.
If only if only I could have been a based devil may cry head and and everyone's be like, oh, that's a classic is I'll be like not in my head like, yeah, that's a classic.
Instead, I'm sitting here being like, dude, shout out the hedgehog was good.
Oh, it wasn't.
Dude, but but you got Russian clank. You got slide. You got like so many games.
I do have a lot of games. I do. I do. But it's the few ones that I'm like everybody has that one game.
That wasn't good. I was wrong. No.
It's like that little feeling, the little feeling of like, oh, well, then, well, then.
Then you just got to that's when you got to make a fucking video.
Hey, guys, sorry, I haven't made a video in a while. I know, I know, I know.
I'm going to be I'm going to be the the guy who defends that one game that everyone says.
But I think it's cool. But I'm too smart to do that because yeah, okay.
Because I because I know I know in my heart of hearts that I am actually like if I look at it like in a really critical way, the only person that could like this is someone who is emotionally attached to it due to nostalgia and not because of that.
A lot of the time, a lot of the time that is just the case for certain things, not everything.
I think so like there's no way to defend Shadow of the Hedgehog, but like in a way that is interesting or genuine question.
Genuine question. I mean, do you not think there are things about it that made you like it?
That you could be like, well, here's what I like. I guess I could.
There are things that are good about it because I really responded to them and enjoy not arbitrarily but for a reason.
Well, yeah, there is. I mean, it's not just Shadow of the Hedgehog.
That's just like the easiest go to example of this sort of thing.
But it's it's not that I couldn't make a video saying I like this game that most people don't like.
It's that I think that is it's not a defense of all of the things that people don't like about it.
And if I just say, here's the things I like and here's the things I don't like.
It's the same as all of the other videos that are critiquing it.
It's just that it comes from the other direction.
Like I would say exactly the same things that everyone else says.
But you would just say but you're you're you're the number of points you assigned to each.
Yeah, like the things I like count more than the things that other people like about the like overall me likey.
But running. There's this there's this YouTuber that I discovered not too too long ago, maybe a couple months ago called Running Shine.
And he has he doesn't have that many videos, but he has a re one of his really good ones is about Sonic Adventure, like the first one that everyone makes fun of.
Because everyone's nostalgic for Sonic Adventure 2, but he has this long video explaining about how Sonic Adventure is awesome.
And it's a great video. And you know, he does he does.
He acknowledges like, okay, the yeah, the voice acting is pretty bad.
The delivery is pretty bad. The coaching is bad. The direction is bad.
However, the voices themselves are good and tales sound like a child.
And he points out a couple of instances were like, hey, in this part, the voice acting really works well and conveys an idea.
And here's why and he's like, there's what and you know, it's great.
I fucking love running shine. He's he's sick.
He does that for like Tony Hawk's underground. He did one about he did one about Yic, although he was pretty negative about Yic or Y2K.
I'm not sure how you actually see that game. You guys still there?
Yeah, I'm talking to myself here.
I'm just I'm just taking your advice and I'm tuning you out completely waiting for a silence so I can say something completely unrelated.
You've taught me how to podcast so well.
So now we've entered the era where the podcasting has become a game of chicken, where it's just how long can we get away with can we each get away with not talk?
How little can we say?
And just and just hope that someone else will fill the space.
That's what the bonus episode will be. Well, I'll just have to like, try and say as little as possible.
Bonus episode. Like, who can endure the most awkward silence before having to break?
I mean,
challenge except
not to be not to put not to put not to pull a major anything.
But do you guys want to hear about a dream I had?
Oh, God. Oh, God. Is this what the bandcast was like? Is this the level of quality drop to the Ben?
I think the Ben cast was short, sweet, terse to the point and get in, get out.
If efficient, get your money's worth.
That I delivered value for money.
What happened? What happened to you bringing up your dream?
Less value for money, but value.
Nonetheless, more smaller volume, higher density, greater overall.
Smaller volume, higher price, you know.
Yeah, you know, more, more air, less chips.
Just don't think about it too much.
Call it diet.
What happened to me was that I've been having a couple of really vivid dreams and I know exactly why.
It's because my sleep schedule got fucked up and I've been sleeping during daylight hours.
And, you know, when you, when you, when you're sleeping in the light, you're more likely to dream.
And also there was one time where like, I woke up and I was like, no, I'm going back to sleep.
I want to go to sleep even though I didn't need to sleep anymore.
And I kept trying to like force myself and I ended up like kind of drifting in and out and I had a bunch of dreams.
I had a dream about being in like a virtual reality Hogwarts sort of place.
And I put on a VR headset and everyone's face changed.
And I was like, I was playing like an A, an altered reality game in this like art deco fucking rapture looking ass school.
But the thing that was best about it were these beams of light that were shooting up from buildings into the sky.
They were like, they were like flat planes of light, these beams, and they would hit the clouds and they would reflect, refract through the clouds at cool angles.
And they looked sick. They looked sick.
That sounds like the Homestuck land.
That was land of beams art deco and beams.
That was the first stream.
And now I feel now I feel like that took overly long.
And now I'm afraid to get into the second one because I don't want to be boring.
Well, I mean, nothing happened in the first stream.
You were in Harry Potter. What's the second?
It was mostly it was mostly it was mostly just about the scenery.
The second dream.
I this one made me feel really bad because I and it's not because of anything that like happened in it.
In the dream, I just had a good feeling.
I felt a great sense of like excitement, purpose, that's depressing, camaraderie, friendship.
Yeah.
And it was great.
And that and when I woke up, I was like, devastated.
I was like, it's gone.
None of it was real.
I'm just in my room.
This this stream was like, I was in like a cave.
I was in like a cave system, but it was part of like a game.
It was part of like a like a puzzle game, like like one of those like trap rooms that like a bunch of people are in this cave.
Or in the room and they have to like puzzle their way out.
But it was like a whole bunch of people.
It was like hundreds of people and we were all in this like cave system.
Like searching through objects, solving puzzles.
There was some slime.
There was some slime in some places.
It was pretty cool.
And like I walked over there was a big cavern that sort of had water in the ground and I walked around the corner and I found I walked through a little tunnel at the end.
And I found like the the final room in the in the place and I had this like this like computer console on the wall and there was like a code to be solved in there and I didn't know how to solve the code.
I was like, it's some kind of like Sudoku block puzzle thing.
And like when you put certain blocks together, the blocks like sort of and then they resolve into like a part of an object, but the objects can complete.
And you have to create the whole object by putting all these blocks, but they often have to have to match numbers.
And I was like, this is too hard. I can't do it.
But I was like, wait a minute.
It's okay because like we're all in here.
We're all in this together.
You know, we can all we can all put our heads together.
Some like someone can solve.
It doesn't matter if I can't solve it.
You know, we're a team.
We're a community.
And somebody did and they put it together and the thing returned into a gun and somebody took and somebody had the object.
It was trying to resolve like this magic gun and somebody took the gun and fired it and firing the gun transformed the whole cave system into like or part of it into slime caves.
It was all slime.
There was all the walls were slime.
The pillars were slime.
There were still side rooms that had objects and then these and we were and there were suddenly there were like all these new objects appeared.
There were like VHS tapes and cassette tapes and books and papers and like binders.
And suddenly I knew that's like we have to find the right object and I start just picking up things like I'm in a VR game just picking up things and turning them over my hand and throwing and like which one of these is the right object.
This is like key.
This is key.
There's one more console puzzle.
We have to solve it.
We have to solve this puzzle and I need to find a ticket.
What I'm looking for is a ticket and I like a golden ticket.
Like the Willy Wonka's factory and then I find something that's a piece of paper and I pick it up and I go to a guy like an old guy with glasses kind of like a chubby guy just like a random guy.
I don't know.
He was he was very specific looking but but I have this piece of paper and I'm like hey is this the ticket and he's like this sucks.
I hate this.
He's like this.
He's like there is no ticket.
There is no game.
There never was and then I like and then everything goes dark.
It's black and there's like a sort of sense of there are some objects.
I'm in some kind of room and I'm like this is a test.
I'm I think to myself.
No, no, no.
This is a test of my resolve and I am meant to not believe that the game is not real because if I believe the game is not real.
Then I lose so I have to believe in spite of the fact that it seems that the rug is being pulled out from under me and then like the lights came on and the room was gray and there were these figures they were all in a circle.
They were like low poly humans.
No faces.
They were all in a circle around me and they were like dancing.
And I'm and I'm looking around and I'm like, no, I just have to not believe it.
This is not real.
The game was real.
The cave was real.
The puzzles were real.
The slime was real.
So it's a gray room.
These gray figures are all dancing around me and I start to sing and I start to sing this very specific song and I woke up.
Well, I and I sing the song like in spite of it to like show that like, I don't know, to like ward off whatever illusion this is because and then I wake up and I'm like, oh no, there was no kid.
He was right.
There never was a game or a cave or anything.
It was all an illusion.
In reality.
Did I lose?
Did I just lose the game?
Did the doubt that the people were like the dream killers, they stopped you dreaming and you wake up.
Yeah, or something.
And I have this I have this note.
I have this this page of notes here.
Like I woke up and I was like, this feels important.
And I wrote down all these notes, the notes that have our caves, slime room, puzzles, console timer.
Last day, day before code crack console game become gun question mark unlock final day form searching through VHS tapes.
Floppy's find a ticket.
No game never was everything great.
Dancing figures in a circle.
This is a test.
Start singing.
Wake up.
I even I remember the song.
I remember the tune and I even like recorded myself singing it.
It's short.
Would you have it?
I'm going to be.
Yeah, I have it.
I could just sing it right now.
I would be really embarrassed.
It would what would be really embarrassing if this tune was just like a popular pop song.
And I just like, and it was like, oh, that's just some song.
Like everybody knows that song.
You idiot.
But but like if it is, I don't know it.
Maybe I just heard a snippet of it.
Okay.
Should I should I sing my dream song?
Yes, you're committed to the bit.
You have to conclude it.
Okay, I'm nervous.
This is embarrassing.
But this is this was the dream song that I sang against these low poly gray figures that attempted that attempted to horn.
Swaggle me into believing that all my work was for nothing.
It was like, it was like, um, I believe, I believe in what's begun.
I believe in what's to come.
I believe in those that run.
That was it.
Does that tune ring a bell?
No, but yeah.
Well, I guess my dream brain just just made it up.
You had a you had a you had a Queen moment.
You had a Freddie Mercury moment.
You got to turn that into a rock opera.
Um, you're right.
I guess you're right.
What else am I supposed to do?
Your talent has been unveiled.
You're a master musician all this time.
I wrote a top charting pop ballad.
And that's that's it.
I'm I'm sure about I'm sure about the lines.
I believe in what's begun and I believe in what's to come.
I'm not a hundred percent sure the last one was I believe in those that run.
That sounds weird.
I'm not sure if that was it.
But that's what I remembered as best I could.
Anyway, I woke up and I was like, God, I hate my life.
I hate everything.
Why can't I just go back to the puzzle caves?
That was the shit.
Everyone was united in purpose.
Everyone was everyone was on each other's team.
You know, we solved we literally solved racism with slime and puzzles.
And that's what it took.
Yeah, that's what it took to build solidarity among the working class.
Who can say what which is real the slime puzzle world or the reality we live in now.
Maybe the great people were the ones who put you to sleep.
I that's honestly, honestly, I hope I hope and believe that you're right.
That this this is the illusion that has been cast on me.
A real Ben real Ben is is in a coma in like the in like the hospital ward
is somewhere in like that they built in these slime caves to take care of
participants in the puzzle game, you know, that fell under the weather.
He's in a coma.
They're hoping he'll come back any minute.
Meanwhile, you know, the console was solved.
The next item was resolved out of the block Sudoku puzzle.
And, you know, the room has taken some other form now and further adventures are afoot.
And I'm missing out, God damn it.
I have to go back.
Rubik's gauntlet Rubik's gauntlet.
It was such a, I don't know.
It left.
I would just woke up with a very, a very strong emotional reaction to having experienced this.
And I and I didn't like it.
That's that's what's up.
Have you tried playing a Sudoku Sudoku puzzle to like to like wake yourself up?
And then like I solve it and it resolves into a gun.
And it's like, you know what you have to do.
That's the real shit.
It's like, it's like that.
It's like that.
That meme of like the noose and through the noose, you see your anime waifu, right?
But like it's a slime cave.
It's a Sudoku puzzle.
Well, that was pretty cool, I guess.
I hope that I told my dream story in as compelling a fashion as one would hope for.
It conjured up a few images in my mind.
The caves and the puzzles maybe think of like a multiplayer uncharted game.
It had a, the room had like a square.
I remember that like the whole area was square.
And but parts of it were cave and parts of it were room, but it was all contained in a square area.
And like the starting area, like the starting area and the final room with the console with like the code, the block puzzle in it.
Where they were right next to each other, but you know, they had a wall between them.
So you had to go all the way around the square to get from one to the other.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
And like, and like the last room before a few little, little like final rooms that sort of you would walk through to get to the lab was like a big area that took up a lot of the space.
And it was this big like cave system that got became a slime cave after the first, after the second, the penultimate find the puzzle was solved.
That feels good.
The most fantastical part about that dream was definitely the fact that everybody was working together.
I for common goal.
I, I, I have no, there was no context about like why all these people were here.
I'm pretty sure we were here of our own volition.
Like we had all deliberately come here to solve these puzzles.
What if what if you're just one of all like many people who had that exact dream slam gun puzzle dream?
Like the like the old guy with the glasses who told me there is no game.
He was just like another doubter.
He like someone had told him that there was no game and he was about to be taken by the gray low poly people as well.
I hope I have a fucking cave puzzle slime gun dream tonight.
I hope I fucking hope you do too.
I hope that a lot.
I go into the dream and I find Ben Saint there surrounded by gray people and I kill them all.
Yes, yes, bring you got to bring me back.
I, I, I think it's funny that.
They're like the block puzzle.
I was like, I have no idea.
This is like completely beyond me.
It's like, um, there's an episode of Batman the animated series where someone traps him in a dream.
This is like going to be really spotty.
Remember, I don't remember which villain traps him in a dream, but he doesn't know that he's dreaming.
This is like someone's scheme to like defeat him is like they're going to give him basically put him in the matrix, right?
Give him like this perfect life in the dream that he won't want to wake up from.
So Batman will just stay asleep forever.
Um, but like the way that Bruce Wayne realizes because he's not Batman in the dream, like he still has his parents and all that.
The way that he realizes that he's dreaming is he opens up a book because he wants to read and like the book is full of like fucked up, like gibberish, like squiggles.
And he's like, what, what, what the fuck is this?
And it turns out that like, um, the explanation in the episode is that like it's some kind of reductive shit.
Like, oh yeah, dreaming is right brain reading is left brain.
So you can't read in a dream because they don't use the same part of your brain or something, which there's probably like some truth to.
Um, but it was like that it was like looking at this block of the Sudoku puzzle.
I was like, I cannot even begin to understand any of these like letters.
This is complete gobbledygook and I'm going to need some other fucking guy to solve this part of the experience for me.
It's weird how your brain thinks that you can't understand, right?
It makes you feel like disconnected from yourself when it's like, yeah, my brain conceptualizes this and yet I do not understand it.
I can, it's like you get the emotion, the emotional reaction of confusion.
Like it's like you can sort of create that out of nowhere, but like the specific, the specifics of what you're confused about it.
You don't even know.
It's like, it's like my mind just like sort of wanted to put in this place this object that like sort of symbolically represented like something you cannot solve.
And so it just kind of layered a bunch of like elements together like a grid and like symbols and like moving blocks in a like a sort of square configuration and put it over like a little like, um, it was over like a little door hatch or something like, I don't know.
Yeah, and my mind just put these things together in a way that like sort of related to each other in space, but there was no like further connection.
They were just kind of layered on top of each other to create the effect of, I don't know, I don't know what to do with all these things together.
They're just, they're just things.
They don't make any sense because like, you know, they were, they were not conceived of in a, in a like a way to really achieve any end.
They're just, they're just arbitrary, more or less.
I don't know.
Dreams are weird.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Shout out to Mage.
Shout outs to Mage.
You know, clearly I'm a hypocrite.
Clearly I'm not, I'm not above it because here we are.
Here we are having Ben's Dreamcast.
Oh no.
I love Dreamcast.
Powerstone 2.
What a classic.
I never had, I never had a Dreamcast.
Dude, get a Dreamcast.
It has no copy protection.
You can just burn isos to CDs and it'll play.
That's, that's fucking cool.
Life hack for the instant Dreamcast question.
Wow.
Damn.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's great.
Actually.
Um, well, all I did this week was think about cool things because I said, fuck it.
I'm taking a break from social media.
I did barely logged onto Twitter, barely went on YouTube, didn't do any of that shit and just was doing real life stuff, like making cool things, conceptualizing cool things and not worrying about
Is this going to be good for Twitter?
It was just like, oh, ideas were just free flowing and I had so many cool ideas like, oh man, I should get like a raspberry pie and like 3d print, like a shell for it.
That looks like a Sega Genesis make a little mini Sega that you can just like throw retro pie on there.
Like this would never be for anything, but it's like, it'd be so cool to just do because now I can do that.
And I was like looking at like how to like solder shit and like become like cooler.
And I was like, whoa, when you just like don't care about if it's marketable, you all of a sudden like have so many cool ideas.
Hmm.
Are you are you soldering like a 3d print stuff?
Well, I'd be like soldering like connections to a raspberry pie and then you would go into a CAD program.
Oh, wait, a raspberry pie is like a fucking is like a what is that I was thinking of like a food.
A raspberry pie is like a little micro computer.
You can get like you can get like a raspberry pie zero for like $5 and then you can run games and like Linux and stuff on there.
So you can like use a raspberry pie is like the like electronics for like, you know, DIY projects and stuff.
So it's like, what if I took a little $5 raspberry pie and 3d printed a shell for it that like looked like a retro console and then like just like.
Solder some little like connections on there and like have it play video games and it would be cool.
That's handheld.
That's unbelievable.
Yeah.
That sounds insane.
I was thinking of just 3d printing like a micro like bar top arcade cabinet and then like wiring up some like joysticks and buttons and then put like a
Zooming game on a little bar top cabinet and I could do that.
It would be cool.
You could you could sell it as like a little like tiger tiger handheld.
Yeah.
You can you can get like, you know, like five inch seven inch displays and they go through like a pass through that plugs into the raspberry pie and then they
output video and it's just like, oh, this is pretty sick.
This is pretty legit.
I love that idea.
The idea of like a like a desktop arcade cabinet where you can play a zoomie little buttons.
Yeah.
It's just like and and ninja suffering.
You'd have to get like a vertical screen.
Yeah.
It'd be cool.
It just has one button.
You should put.
Hey, Tom.
Here's I'm going to I'm going to backseat dev for you.
I'm going to tell you exactly how you design your game to make it.
You have you have like one.
I mean, as a zoomie has like levels, right?
It has like discreet.
It has like stages.
Yeah.
Well, in each stage in each stage, you put a little arcade cabinet in there that you can find.
And then as a zoomie, you can play a little bonus game of ninja suffering of like increasing
difficulty.
And if you win, if you get to the end of it, you get like, I don't know, a fire flower,
a mushroom.
Sick.
That's that's how you that's that right there, Tom.
Listen, I know you I know you are kind of new with this whole thing, but that's how you
that's how you make the good game right there.
Well, I'm glad you could spare some of your sagely wisdom with me.
Me too.
World's a better place.
I was playing.
Oh, what's that one?
Not Wings of V. What the one where you're the girl and you climb in the mountain.
Celeste.
Because it was in because it was in the racial justice package or whatever.
I played through a bunch of it.
And that game has a little spot where you find an arc like an arcade cabinet and you can
play what I surmise must be the like original prototype Celeste that was probably like on
Newgrounds or something.
Right.
Yeah.
And it's funny because playing the arcade version of that I played through the whole
thing.
I beat it and it actually spoiled the twist that comes later in the game where in your
double jump gets updated, upgraded to your dash jump gets upgraded to a double dash jump
because that happened in the that that version.
And I was like, well, clearly they did it in the prototype.
They're going to do it in the final version too.
And they did.
Well.
Shit.
Suckers.
If only if only they had fucking Game Guru Ben Saint to give advice and to not spoil the
big twist.
Yeah.
And then.
Oh, and also the only way that Izumi can collect all seven chaos emeralds is she gets
one from each of these bonus stages.
And then she she becomes super Izumi.
Where do you come up with these ideas?
It's like that was like right off the top of your head.
The good game.
I just I don't know.
You know, I just I get my ideas from the world around me.
I look at things like the sun and I think what if that was a video game and then I come
here and I tell you about it.
I interpret.
You know, I don't go outside.
I think that's where my my failing comes here.
If you want to make the good video game, I strongly advise staring directly into the
sun for as long as possible until inspiration strikes.
I mean, everything that we know came from the sun.
So like everything is in there.
Everything is in there.
That's why they tell us to look away from it because that's where enlightenment.
They want to light.
That's why it's called enlightenment.
They want to keep you stupid.
They want to keep you educated, stupid.
They say don't stare at the sun because they know that the working class will become
too powerful to crack the code.
We'll stay and go outside and stare at the sun.
We will take over.
We will win.
We all come from the sun and from the sun to the sun.
We must return.
You know, Elon Musk is trying to get us further away from the sun to Mars.
But I think we got to be heading closer.
I think we got to move inwards.
Jaden Smith was right all along.
What if mirrors aren't real because our eyes aren't real and we don't need them?
What if my room isn't real because the slime cave isn't real?
No. This episode is getting too intense for me.
Impossible.
Tom, you should make Grand Theft Azumi where she goes around and she checks people out of their cars.
It checks me.
It sounds like a revolutionary idea.
There are no bad ideas.
She gets into the car and she drives and she crashes it a lot and it's open world.
So you can go around, you go to a strip club as a tiny little raccoon person.
Wait, so you're saying have a game without levels?
Yeah.
No. That's too radical.
It's not too radical.
Half-Life did it.
Oh, shit.
What is this episode going to be called?
It's going to be called...
It's not real. The episode is not real. That's the title.
The Slime Cave.
The Sun.
Sun Dev.
Stare directly into the sun.
Just like PCP stare directly into the sun.
That's what it's called.
I hope we get tons of voicemails of people taking our advice and threatening legal damages.
Speaking of which, are you ready to go to voicemails?
We have a lot, actually.
Do we?
We have like a shit ton.
Why?
If they all angry at you.
I don't know, maybe.
I guess we'll have to find out.
I guess I got to open up speedpipe.com slash PCP voicemail.
You really do.
You really, really do.
The first one we've got today is called I Will Give Ben Something to Fear.
Oh.
Yes.
Wait, is this like...
I'm looking forward to it.
On page two, because I'm looking on page one and I don't even see it.
Yes, it's on page two.
Are we really going through all of these?
I will do it.
They don't take long. They take 30 seconds.
We have 25 voicemails, Ben.
I'm ready.
I'm ready for it.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
We'll be litigious.
We'll be discriminant.
Spartan.
We'll be Roman.
We'll be...
Those are the same thing.
Just go.
Every statement, waste more of our time.
I will give Ben Something to Fear.
Three, two, one, go.
Some pussies call him again, but not really.
Ben, this isn't a joke.
I am going to fucking beat you up when I see you.
I am a six-four, 280-pound monster.
Boxer football player.
I am going to kick your teeth in.
I am going to fuck your mouth.
No.
You're not a sexual wick.
Not my teeth.
This is not a joke.
This is actually a threat on your livelihood and lifestyle.
Okay.
You see, I really appreciate about that one.
And good job, by the way.
Mission accomplished because I am terrified of having my teeth fucked up.
I'm afraid of my teeth.
My teeth make me scared when I look at them in the mirror.
And I think, oh, where will they end up?
Punch and beat the shit out of.
Beat the shit out of by a six-foot-four football monster.
Let's hear from YouTube in three, two, one.
Hello, cringe department.
You're going to want to see this.
I don't know what he's showing.
There's no link.
I think he's just referring YouTube to us for the cringe department.
So there we go.
Thank you.
Thanks for letting them.
Sick.
Leftism in my PCP in three, two, one, go.
What's this?
This cannot be a cool, calm and productive conversation about leftism in my procrastinator's podcast.
Is this what this episode was all about?
I will not.
I need my room temperature IQ takes from somebody that read three quarters of The Fountainhead
when they were in middle school and then never touched a book again.
I feel like they're referring to someone specifically, but...
Hashtag both sides.
I wouldn't want to name any names.
I don't know what he means.
I don't know if he's referring to a specific episode.
No, despite what you might think, the Ben cast was not just an hour long screed about needing a democracy in the workplace or whatever.
No, I will add this into it.
I promise.
Believe it or not, I restrained my golf.
Wasn't that in the Digi and Ben you talked about stuff, didn't you?
Did we?
I mean, before I appeared.
Wait, Digi and Ben?
Was that recent?
Yeah, like two weeks ago.
It started with Digi and Ben and then Gibbon was halfway through.
I didn't realize Digi was on episode recently.
She was, believe it or not.
I know, stranger things, miracles really do happen.
Let's hear from...
I think I must have had a stroke or something because suddenly I'm having the sensation of smelling and tasting buffalo wings.
Oh.
And I want one.
Oh, Ben, don't have a stroke.
Please don't.
No, no, no.
I think I'm actually just thinking like, what if I had some buffalo wings right now?
And then like that desire is so powerful.
There's overriding my sensory data and just filling my nostrils that, yeah, you know, you know you want to smell that.
You know, you said, but before we go on to Todd's dildos, you mentioned that you've been having great ideas and having like being creative and doing cool shit this week.
Well, not me because last night I got back into it and I worked all night trying to finish the last shot.
I'm on the last shot of a slime and punishment finale.
Hell yeah.
Before that, for like a week, I was just like drunk all the time and I was just like ordering takeout like twice a day.
I spent $250 on like buffalo wings in like a week because I just love them so much.
Good Lord.
Is that keto?
Okay.
The thing about keto is that everything's keto if you eat little enough of it.
Well, you didn't eat like a ton of buffalo wings.
It started good.
It started with good intentions because I realized like, okay, one small order of buffalo wings is about like 35 grams of carbs,
which like if I don't eat any other carbs, like that's fine.
That's under the limit.
So that's okay.
If I eat clean other than that.
I thought the limit was 20.
I've heard like the strictest one I've ever seen is 20 more.
I think a lot of people say 50.
50?
It kind of depends on the.
Yeah.
Man, I was doing strict 20 the entire time.
I thought that was like the hard and fast.
There is, I don't think you need to go 20 all the time.
I think I've seen like, I'm pretty sure that I've seen like old like keto diets like prescribed to kids for epilepsy,
you know, cause that's where it comes from.
I think I've seen like, like old school keto diets like that, that are like 50 grams.
That opens up a lot more options.
Yeah.
So, so it started like, I can get away with one.
I can get away with one.
And then I was like, but maybe I could also just eat it for every meal because it's so good.
And then like, you know, fuck it.
I'll get, I'll get this.
I'll get the sweet sauce.
I'll get the honey barbecue.
You know, you know, nothing's, nothing matters.
God's fake.
Anyway, it was, it was a week of debauchery.
It was a nightmare.
But I'm back.
I'm back.
I'm on the wagon again.
So I just wanted to relate, I just wanted to relate that story to you and say, you know, life's better when you're post food.
When you're not post food, you wind up like me.
You spend $200 on buffalo wings.
And you just, you live, you live your life thinking about what could have been.
So it's cautionary tale.
All right.
Todd's dildos in three, two, one, go.
Hey, this is Todd from Todd's dildo.
Yeah.
I, I get it.
I get it.
A very, very funny, very clever.
I'll pass your message along.
So, so for those, for those who don't know, Nate loves dildos.
Nate loves dildos.
Yes.
This is a, this is a reference to the well-known fact that Nate is just a big, he's just a collector.
Like it's not a sexual thing.
It's not weird.
Don't make it weird.
Yeah.
Uh, Nate, Nate moved, Nate moved to Virginia and like, uh, um, he like didn't like tell anyone.
He like, he like kept it a secret.
Like it wasn't a secret, but he didn't say anything about it.
Didn't bring it up in the chat.
Didn't even tell Digi, like until the day that he showed up.
He just kind of like moved in secret.
He didn't really mention it.
He didn't really mention it on Twitter.
He said, he said for like a week or two that like he wasn't able to stream.
Uh, and then he, he, but he didn't say why.
And then he didn't tell Digi until the day that he, that he got to Virginia.
I don't know.
I don't know why he's like this.
I, I can't imagine it's just sort of like, it involves a lot of work and he just doesn't
want to spend any time on the internet telling people about things.
So it's just like, I'm just going to do it.
Does it take that?
Does it take that long though?
I don't know.
I feel like it's maybe told as patrons or something in like his Patreon podcast that
he does.
I haven't listened to those.
Does he, does he do a patron podcast?
Yeah.
Doesn't everybody now?
Everyone stole my idea because it's the best idea ever.
Oh, that reminds me.
I wanted to mention, I feel like I haven't brought this up, but I was going to say this
when you, when I, when I sang the dream song and you, and you said like, ha, you're a composer.
Um, did I mention, did I tell either of you that while I was doing my last patron podcast,
I talked, someone asked me about, have I ever tried to make music?
And the answer was yes.
I, I made a song for the, for a Homestuck music contest.
Did I talk about this on the show already?
No, I've never heard of that.
Yeah.
There was a, there was a Homestuck music contest.
It was, and it, people were invited to like contribute tracks for what ended up becoming
the album colors and mayhem.
Do you remember that one?
I do.
Yeah.
But they didn't say that it was going to be a troll themed album.
They said submit a track that is themed around a character.
They didn't say troll.
Colors and mayhem is a troll themed album, but they just said a character.
So yeah, I like downloaded fruity loops or some fucking music program and I just threw
it together.
And I made that, and I made a track about Typhius, the Denizen.
And, um, you know, and like I themed it with wind, like I only used, I only use wind based
instruments.
Like there's like a, like the melody is like a pan flute and like the background like tracks
are like, uh, it's pipe organ.
It's like a big like churchy pipe organ, you know, obviously cause Typhius has the organ
in his layer and there's like, there's like wind sounds in the back.
And I went through through my old emails and I found it.
I found the track and I, and I put it on the last, um, uh, patron podcast post because I
had mentioned it in there.
And, um, I actually think it's kind of okay.
It's not like all amazing, but I think some of the little bits in there are actually pretty
good.
Do you guys want me?
Should I post it?
I'm not, I'm not going to play it on the episode.
I will.
Yeah, I got it.
No, I'm not going to put in the show notes.
It's for patrons only bitches.
Well, then what, what were you going to do?
I was going to ask if you guys want to be here.
Oh, I will lord my exclusive access over the peasants.
Okay.
Um, well, I probably shouldn't look for it right now cause that would have to go through
my files.
We still have 22 more fucking voice mouths to go.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
And speaking of which next one, Ben, you ruined my life again in three, two, one, go.
Do not support Ben's thing.
He is evil.
He is anti-American.
First of all, viewers, folks, uh, you're going to want to sit down.
What?
What is happening?
He thinks passion fruit is good.
You asshole.
They look like animal creatures.
Have you ever looked at the passion fruit up close?
No.
That's a yurk.
That's not a...
What the fuck?
It's disgusting.
You...
You monster.
That's enough of that.
Yeah, enough of that.
Have you guys ever eaten a passion fruit?
I have not.
I have never eaten a passion fruit.
I think I know what the taste is though, from juice or something.
Really?
I, um, they have the most incredible smell.
They smell incredible.
They taste incredible.
Yeah, they're like...
It's like, it looks sort of like a hard plum and you open it up and like it's full of snot.
Like it looks disgusting.
It's full of slime.
It's a slime fruit.
But it's so good.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It looks like frog spawn or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like eggs.
Um, I have...
I have some...
I bought some flavorings for gummies and I made...
I made a batch of gummies that I...
They didn't end up coming out quite right.
They didn't...
They didn't cohere enough.
They sort of just kind of stayed as goop in the molds.
They didn't become solid.
And I was really disappointed with that because the flavor was incredible.
I would like...
I had to like...
I had to dig the goop out of the worm molds with my hands and just like eat it off my fingers
because it was so good.
Passion fruit is so good.
It's the greatest...
It's the greatest thing I ever invented.
It was passion fruit.
You're welcome.
And I went on Twitter and I said,
if you don't like passion fruit, unfollow me right now.
Get out of here.
And I guess this guy...
All your followers.
Gone.
Oh, they're gone.
Cut in half.
That was the last straw.
They got...
I could...
I can forgive.
I can forgive being an Antifa terrorist, but I cannot forgive.
There are some lines you just don't cross with.
Bad fruit takes...
Okay, next voicemail.
I'm looking forward to saying the word fuck exactly one time.
So saying the fuck word exactly one time.
Three, two, one, go.
Fuck.
Nice.
I'm pretty sure that was Doon Koon.
Given us exactly what was promised.
That sounded like Doon Koon to me.
This next one is a...
Oh, I'm scared.
But it's the name of the voicemail is a link.
I'm going to try the link.
The link is an audio file.
The link...
The link is to an audio file.
Which I guess we can put in the show notes.
Wait, should we just play the audio file?
I guess.
Right?
Oh wait, this is just what you said.
This is just what you said last episode.
Let's listen to it.
Yeah, okay.
It's only like 20 seconds.
Three, two, one, go.
White people probably don't say it.
But I'm not going to...
I don't have the power to enforce that.
And I don't think that I can say...
The words you use, ultimately it's up to you.
Myself, I don't think I should say it.
A few moments later...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
N-A-B-A-C-P.
It is angry about Caucasian people.
I'm sorry, it's a funny joke.
It's a really funny joke.
I just wanted to quote a really funny joke.
And you can't not say it and quote the joke.
When I hear N-A-B-A-C-P, I just think of that scene
from Charlie Brown's Kwanzaa.
And I didn't use the hard R, so it's fine.
Ben, I think you just got canceled.
No!
Ah!
Ben, who's the real hippo crit around here?
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
And the hippo crit really was the best guy ever.
And Tom Oliver really was the digital bro.
Oh, God!
Ah!
All right.
Can we move on?
What did they say in the actual voicemail?
Oh, right, there was an actual voicemail.
Oh, it just says, please listen to audio on the link.
Okay, we did.
Okay, so please listen to the audio on the link.
Yes, listen.
No, I'm not a hypocrite.
It's just like Walt Whitman said, I contain multitudes.
Do I contradict myself?
Then I contradict myself.
I am a fucking, I am a constellation of flavor.
Okay.
Bitch.
Yeah.
Next one.
I think it's fine to say it in context.
And I said-
I'm not a cop.
It's basically a context of reference I was going to say.
Listen.
I didn't finish saying it.
I, I, I, I, that's most, that's mostly how I feel.
That's like, that's mostly how I feel.
Wait, fuck.
I was going to, I was going to, I was going to, I said in that, I said, I'm not a cop.
I said, I'm not a cop.
So don't be a cop.
And by being a cop, I mean, criticize me in any way.
Because that's, that's what, that's what cops-
Sounds about right.
That's my, that's my understanding of what the police, like that, that's why everybody's,
that's why everybody's protesting the police, right?
Because like they, they say mean things about them and like bully them on Twitter.
Yeah.
Like you're, you know, that why did you make videos about Winnie the Pooh?
That's cringe.
And I say, shall we, shall we listen to?
Yeah.
Open, open wide for the red pill.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Ben, Benjamin Netanyahu over here.
That's free.
This questions for you.
Do you believe in white privilege Do you believe that white people as a class have a
structural advantage and influence over Western society. Okay, now if you believe
this, why do you have such a problem when people apply that same standard to Jews?
I don't, I don't really believe that it's the same. It's, it's, I don't, I believe,
God, this is like a serious question. No, I think, I feel like he's conflating things. Like,
the idea of white privilege is that- I understand, I understand the point he's making. Okay. I mean,
okay, let's- I mean, if you walk into a place and you have white skin, you are treated better
than like, on average, like average of the entire America, you're treated better than a person with
brown skin, like face value, sort of judgment. Jews do not have like a specific look that you
could easily, like immediately identify them as, aside from the, the types of clothes they wear.
Well, a lot of them look, a lot of them look white. Well, a lot of them just look white. Like,
there's like, okay, okay, I don't know, see, I don't see how those two things could be,
like, because you can't like, clock a Jew immediately, and then treat them better or worse.
This is, you know, this, what I think is wrong with this, what I think is, has gone wrong with
this question, is that it is, it is reductive. It's not that like, it's not simply that white
people have privilege, or white privilege, and Jews do not, black people do not. Like,
that's not where the question ends, because the various things that people perceive about you,
and the roles that you inhabit in society, these are all interconnected. So like, there is,
there is some overlap between like white privilege and Jewish privilege, because a lot of Jewish
people look white. You know, maybe if, okay, let's, let's go full stereotype and just say like,
oh, you're like a, you're come from like a family of like rich banking Jews that are like connected
in Hollywood, or whatever, right? Like, obviously, obviously that position confers some privilege.
I would say, I would say that like, materially, if you come from a background that's wealthy,
that confers a great deal of privilege in its way. I think that culturally, Jews probably don't have
the kind of like, a cult, the sort of cultural privilege that whites do in quite the same way.
Jews aren't seen as the default in the same way that, you know, the white man is or whatever.
But like, my answer to this question is intersectionality. That's the answer.
I think also there's like, there's a different kind of like camaraderie. The, you know, white people
don't really have camaraderie within their race, because that, you know, they, the white privilege
has nothing to do with what some of them do, some of them do. But like, in the same way that if
you're a Greek and you go to a Greek food market and there's a Greek guy behind the counter, he's
more likely to like give you a discount because, you know, there's just sort of like a camaraderie
of culture. So like, the Jewish people have that with them in the same way that any culture, like
the close net in maybe in a country, like I'm talking like in England, like Greek people seem
to like other Greek people more than they like others, I guess, not like a racist way, but just
sort of like, they treat them a little better or treat them a little nicer. So like, there's that
aspect of that to the Jewish privilege, if there is, you could say the Jewish privilege, but like,
white privilege doesn't, does not have the same, it's not the same thing. It's, you can't say like,
oh, you treat white people better, because like, you want to give back to the white culture,
white community that is not really a, not really a thing in the same way.
The thing about, the thing about whiteness is like, like being, being like Jewish or
a black or African American or, or I don't know, Greek or whatever, like those things are about
what you are. Being white is about what you are not, which is you are not any of those other things,
except you are not in one of these groups that is not white, you know, black people, not white.
I see this is what you look like. Hispanic people, Hispanic people,
well, it's what, it's what you look like, but it's like, do you look like a thing
that is not something, well, I mean, some, some like, some, some Hispanic people are also white,
like Italian people, like most people would say they're white, Greek people, maybe most of the
time, Irish people, most people would say they're definitely white now, but they weren't always
considered to be white. It's like being, like being white is just belonging to an in-group,
the boundaries of which are sort of malleable, a little bit, a little bit arbitrary.
I don't know, there's a lot, there's a lot you could say about that question.
And I don't have all of my points neatly aligned to like explain, but I think we said
more enough. I think, I think, I think we answered the, I think we answered the question at the
very least. We saw, and then doing so solved racism. Let's listen to weird, quacky statistic.
I hope it's, I hope it's 13%, 50, whatever, whatever the, what's the thing about black crime?
Okay, but three, two, one, go. Whoa, despite making up 13% of population. There it is, there it is.
No, hit me with, hit me with 41% next. I want to hear 41%. That one's a classic.
I don't even know what it is, but I don't care.
40, 13, what is it? It's like, despite making up 13% of the population,
black people do like 50 something percent of the crime. 41% is like 41% of trans people kill
themselves. Haha. Great, great stuff. It was, I knew it was going to be one of the two.
But you know what? It's good to be reminded because the thing about numbers is that there are facts,
and there's no such, there's no such thing as interpretation. There's nothing to be,
there's nothing to be considered. There are only numbers to be compared in value, absolute value.
Number big, number small. Which, which bar on the bar graph is taller and which is smaller?
And that's it. That's the answer to the question. Why is white privilege real and not
Jewish privilege? Because bar graph, because number. Okay. Persona 5 opinion shrunk to 23 seconds.
You're welcome. Three, two, one, go. Persona 5 has like a shit story, but it has really fun
combat. Okay, the real world sections are boring as fuck. But once you go to the brain worlds,
playing the video game, the JRPG shit, it's fun because the gameplay is really deep and fun.
That's it. That's my opinion. Number out of 10, I don't know, like seven, I guess, but I haven't
beat the game yet, so that might change. Why is this guy so dedicated to giving us his opinion of
Persona 5? Because it's easier than making a video about it. Just make a, you should have made a 23
second video in which you just said that. Put it over footage of the game, put your little
cartoon avatar in the corner, get 10,000 views, done. Because I don't know what it is, and I'm
scared and confused. My opinion of Persona 5 is that it has good graphic design, 10 out of 10.
That's true. The menus look sick as fuck, and it's a JRPG. And if the game feels good,
then the game feels good. The game basically just is menus, so yeah. Yes. Putting their effort
Next up is a hot take. HBO Max is based, and here's why. Parentheses streaming service.
Three, two, one, go. HBO Max is based, and here's why. They got Cartoon Network, Adult Swim,
and all the Ghibli movies. It's fucking based. I didn't have like cable TV growing up, so I never
got to watch all the based cartoons. So now I'm just watching cartoons. It's fucking amazing,
bro. Watch cartoons. Fuck anime. Anime is cringe. Watch cartoons. Except Ghibli. They're the good
anime. Okay. I was going to say you said Ghibli. Okay. Watch cartoons online has existed for like
10 years. Yeah. Why would you pay money? Why would you pay money for anything? That's a cringe take,
dude. Is it? Is it? Is it? I think there might be a, is a normie thing. Like I, I, unless I'm like
specifically invited to do so, and I'm feeling in a wild mood, I never watch things on a TV.
I feel like I'm maybe, yeah, I feel like that's maybe kind of a weird internet person thing. I
feel like most people watch things on a TV. It's because it's, you need to usually find stuff to
watch on the, on your computer and putting it on the TV requires some amount of effort. I don't
want to. It does. Yeah. It's been like the times that like I've tried to get a movie and show it like
in my house on my TV. It's like, yeah, oh, I got to get a flash drive. Oh, I got to get the file,
get the torrent, put it on the flash drive, put it on my friend's computer. He gives his computer
up to the thing. It sucks. I don't remember where I got it. I think it came with like an eBay thing
I bought like years ago, but I have this thing called a Microsoft display adapter. And it just
plugs into an HDMI port on my TV. And then you can just wirelessly mirror any PC to it. And it's
like so easy to watch torrents and stuff on the TV because it's just like, do you want to connect?
Yes. Bing. There it is. Go. I guess, I guess what I'm, what I'm thinking is like, yeah, if you're,
if you're, if you're not a norm, if you're kind of a normie, if you're not like, if you don't
feel like deep diving into like like learning how to torrent stuff or whatever, you don't know how
to do that. Just buy HBO Max. Cringe. I guess it was buy HBO Max. Yeah. That's, that's a, that's a,
you know, valid, valid. You guys are rebuilding cable on the internet and tearing down everything
that the internet was cool, which was being anti cable and anti all that corporate interest
shit. And you're bringing it all back because people don't know how to use bit torrent.
You disgust me. I mean, on the one hand, on the one hand, if people genuinely get value out of
having it like convenient and available and all that, like, I guess that's the only good thing
about HBO Max is that it makes it easier for people to rip the stuff from the service and put
them on torrents and higher quality. Yeah. On the other hand, and I think I believe this more
strongly, it was cooler. It was cooler when just everything was free. It was cooler when the
internet was just communist. It still is though. It's just a little bit more obscure. Just a little
bit more. I get, yeah, yeah, it's, it's like that. It is that just there are, there are some,
there's a little more corporate crackdown on it and there are, there are more people who are
choosing not to do that. There was the golden age of lime wire. Then we had bit torrent and that
was pretty good. Then then now we have these like sketchy weird streaming sites that are like kind
of crap, but like it also is kind of convenient that you don't have to download anything if that's
what you want to do. I would just much rather deal with watch cartoons online than I would with
having a Netflix subscription, an HBO Max subscription, a Disney plus subscription,
a Peacock subscription. Like, like why? Yeah. Like that's like what, like $70 in streaming
service costs? It's, it's, it's so, it's like, it's so obviously. Plus my Amazon Prime or my Spotify
and like all this shit and it's like. Yeah. Like monthly subscriptions for all of these things. It's
so like unbelievably obviously going to crash and burn with the amount of money people are expected
to pay monthly. And your Xbox Live and your Switch streaming and your PlayStation Plus.
That cannot continue. Like it, why, why do they keep doing it?
These companies have this like really strange obsession with owning the entire pipeline.
Like instead of just being like, oh, Netflix exists. Let's leverage this platform and use it
in conjunction with the content that we do. It's like, no, no, no, no, no. We need to make
all the money. So instead we're going to make our own Netflix that's shittier and
batter because we're not a software company. We're an entertainment company. But this is
we're going to force it down people's throats. This, this is that, this is that illusion of the
possibility of continual growth. That is the reason why like this is, this is the, this is the,
this is one of the problems with capitalism is that like when you're a corporation or whatever,
your goal is not just to continue to make money, but to always continue to make more and more money.
And yeah, it does lead to, this is probably like a relatively benign example of it. But like, yeah,
like all these companies want to own, they don't, they don't just want to make money
selling product. They want to own market share in new market. They want to command a segment,
a sizable segment of the market because it's not just about, it's not just about
owning stuff. It's not even just about creating revenue. It's about when you own market share,
you have influence and you can like throw your weight around more and gain more market share.
And the more of that you have, the more you can lobby and the more you can like influence legislation
that will allow you to abuse your market share more and more, allow you to abuse your continually
more and more monopolistic ownership of the market. Isn't it strange that monopoly
which does lead to just completely unsus... That is like the end goal of every company by design.
It is. It is. And we broke up. We used to, we used to fucking break these things up.
Teddy Roosevelt, everyone thinks he was pretty cool for busting all these trusts,
but now it's like, oh no, we, Jeff Bezos earned every penny and we got to give him tax breaks
so we can make, keep making jobs. Fuckers, nationalize Amazon, fucking nationalize Tesla,
coup Tesla. Did you see Elon Musk saying like, will coup whoever we want for lithium?
No. Well, he said that. Did you see, this is unrelated, but did you see,
did you see Elon Musk? And I know you didn't, but I'm going to say it. Elon Musk said,
pronouns suck on Twitter and his wife Grimes was like, please stop this. Give me a call. I
can't endorse hate. I know this isn't you. And it was really funny. How and why the fuck did Elon
Musk get with a person so strange? I don't really know anything about Grimes. I know nothing about
her, but just like the way she carries herself online is extremely weird and they do not look
like a couple that is a match. It's very odd. Somebody said that like,
edge lord and, edge lord and care lord, you know, it never works out. That relationship never
works out. I read somewhere that apparently Grimes had been like questioning her gender or something,
like not too long ago, making it like, was he talking about that when he said pronouns suck?
Hmm. I don't know. Very funny. Fuck Elon Musk. Elon Musk divorce would be
possibly even funnier. Well, no, probably, no, definitely funnier than Jeff Bezos divorce.
That was actually pretty boring. And just kind of annoying. Elon Musk divorce would be,
who gets to take, who gets to take care of fucking 7x9 QRA or whatever. You know what I mean?
The kid, the kid has fucked up me. The Tesla will do that.
They'll just, yeah, yeah, they'll just pay an engineer to just design an electric powered
parenting, parenting bot. They'll just put it in the car and say like Tesla, drive out to see.
Tesla, raise child. Okay. Okay, master.
All right, we still going with these? Yeah, we're still going, baby.
You are using Twitter in a way that makes you, I mean, really an hour and a half in.
You are using Twitter in a way that makes you feel bad in three, two, one, go.
Twitter is not shit. You guys are just using it in a shitty way. Okay. So like, it seems like what
you do is you open it and you go to like the trending tab or you go to your whole political
shit. Don't follow politics on Twitter. They can't even speak full sentences. It's like 140
characters or whatever. And like on the trending page, it's all still the same shit. It's like
either politics or pop culture bullshit or whoever is canceled this time. You know, don't do that
shit. Just follow like artists you like or games you like or I don't know, anime, whatever, man.
Just follow cool shit. Follow based on epic stuff.
Wow, what a big brain. That's exactly what I do. The problem is I Twitter is a platform is fine.
The people on Twitter are annoying. And the problem is there's discussions about annoying
things and you the people you follow for cool art also have opinions and they have to share them.
And you're pulled back into the conversation, even if you're there, not to have that conversation
because you're not in the right mindset for it because you're there to consume content, not to
think. It's like, guys, just just only think about things that are frivolous because the
serious things are just make you sad. Then just don't think about it. It's counter revolutionary
is what it is. Yes, I follow fucking political people on Twitter. Yes, I'll fucking see Dave
Sarota tweeting about the new like the new horror that is coming down the congressional pipeline
and is like passed unanimously in the Senate or whatever. And I'll say I'm not and I'm going to
keep doing that. I don't really look at the trending tabs unless I see something that's really bizarre
and it's just like why and then I'll look at it and be like, oh, that sucks. I don't I famously I've
changed my trending tab to a different language. I sit Twitter to a different language that one
that I can't read. So trending tab doesn't make any sense ever. But and I follow like basically no
one. I catch up on people like I type in Ben St into the search bar to find out what Ben St's
saying. I was going to say, I can't believe you unfollowed me, bro. I unfollow everyone, basically.
That hurts. That hurts deep. Because it's because when I go to Twitter, I don't want to be like
you don't want to see me go on Twitter and say fuck you if you don't eat passion fruit.
No, you're a piece of shit. The thing is like I have like the optimal Twitter viewing experience
and even then it's like it's not good because if I want to indulge in knowing about what Ben
St's talking about, which is usually some sort of politics and you know, seeing if there's a
little drama going on. The funny thing that what's that guy, JK Rowling, simp man.
Glynner? Yeah, Glynner. Like what's he up to? Like Ben's probably talking about it. I type in Ben
St and it's like an action that I am deciding to do. If I follow Ben, I'm bombarded with it
whenever I go to the site no matter whether I'm interested in seeing that sort of stuff,
which is why following people is a bad idea. But even when you don't follow people.
I have to do that even with the people I do follow. It's not like I'll be caught up with
what a person is doing. If I want to see what one of you guys is doing, I don't just look at
my feed because I don't follow a huge amount of people but I follow enough that it's hard to
keep track of. So yeah, I have to go to the search bar and type in someone's name and be like what
are they tweeting about? What's fucking Tom or Gibbon or Digi or something or tweeting about?
Curious. It's good if you have no public persona that people will...
Like if you're not a public person and you are very, very, very stringent with who you follow,
then yeah, it could be fun on Twitter. It just is not for most people.
I don't know. I'm not on Twitter. Like I understand if you want to like browse it
for art and you follow artists that you really like. I do follow some artists,
but I'm not really on Twitter to look at art. I'm on Twitter to like read what people are saying
about stuff. Like I'm there to engage with the kind of thing that I think this caller would
consider to be like the bad stuff, the bad part of Twitter. I mean then you're probably having a
grand old time. That's the purpose of Twitter to me. I mean you're using it for the right reasons.
That is what it was designed to. It was designed to be the news, to get people the news and like
have updates for the news in real time. What are people like? What are the birds saying? What are
all these tweeting? I'm more interested in what are people talking about. The problem is that the
platform is also being used by artists and it's terrible. But I'm there to see cool shit too.
I'm there to see like oh they like protesters in Portland burned down a construction site that
was building an addition onto a juvenile detention center. I was like yeah that made my day. So
you know it's not all bad. There are glimmers of hope in the darkness. No I'm doing it right.
Fuck you. Next one is DigiBro is pretentious. Three, two, one, go.
I don't know what the point of this is. Did did did Digi say something? Is this talking about the
PCP or is this talking about I think something on Digi's channel? There's no way. I just assume
like Digi's content is you know everywhere. There's lots of people who are who are all too eager to
say you know what Digi? I'm unsubscribing. This content is not what I want anymore. So I assume
I don't think that's I don't think that's what this this this person said Digi talked shit
about the voicemails. So it must be about we only do voicemails on the PCP. Digi doesn't do them.
I think no am I confused? I don't remember a voicemail where someone called in and asked hey
Digi what do you think about the wind rises? I don't think that's I don't remember this. I think
maybe Digi has in the past dismissed voicemails as being dumb but we all have. This voicemail
sucks. All of us have done that. This voicemail sucks ass. This person didn't think it through.
They didn't have a clear message or theme that they wanted to convey with it. It's a mess. It's
chaos. It's soup. Next. Alternate. Alternate platforms. Question mark. Three, two, one, go.
How much money are you making from these alternate platforms compared to YouTube? Like you're on
what Spotify, iTunes, Google Play, whatever. I don't know. Just kind of look the can you look
those numbers up right now? See like how many people are watching compared to how many people
watched on YouTube and the money and shit like that. Because I mean, if you're making more money
from these other platforms, why not just stay there? I don't think Tom. Do we make do you have
any data? Do you have any data on that? You have data on views but you by design make no money from
podcasts. So so we don't we don't make any we don't make any money on like iTunes or Spotify
or Google Play or whatever. There is no revenue stream. Only through Patreon. They are they are
purely there for convenience. Is Spotify, wait, which one's Spotify? The orange one.
It's the green one. Oh, wait, I was thinking which one is the orange one? Are we on are we on
SoundCloud? No. Should we be on you have to pay you have to pay monthly to get enough space to
upload the episode. Really? Remember, we have to keep deleting voicemails. Oh, that's right. So if we
had full to be totally thought. Oh, that sucks. That sucks, major dig. There is a there is a
podcast on Spotify that I listen to is called the relentless picnic, but they only upload like
they make a pretty decent amount on Patreon and they probably so they can probably afford it and
they always they only upload like once a month or so. So okay. That makes sense. Okay, what about
what about like numbers like we don't get to Spotify if you had
one that in the last week. So this week, we've had 1469 starts, 1333 list streams from 295
unique listeners. I can dial down to all time. 1507 listeners, about 30,000 starts in 21 or 22,000
streams. So what's a start? So a start just means you started the stream. And then a stream
means they listen to a significant amount of it. I see. So so there's like, so there's maybe like
200. Okay. And this is two. So 300 people in the last month have listened on Spotify and this
is during the last week. Okay. Okay. But this is during the time when the podcasts are not on
YouTube. So that's going to be like inflated. Like normally, I'm sure it would have been way lower
than that. Um, well, okay, that's just one of the platforms. We're also on Google Play and iTunes
and stuff like that as well. So I'm sure they're dispersed among different options.
Yeah. Yeah, true. Yeah, true. When you go to the website, what is it? What does it play on
automatically? It just it doesn't play anything by default. You choose an episode.
Isn't no, no, no. But when you go to, when you go to the procrastinators.com,
it's like post July 4th, Bencast. And then there's, is that just like a raw MP MP3? That's just the
MP3 uploaded to WordPress itself. It's not connected to any platform. Okay. I see. I would,
I would bet that a lot of people that are going to these alternative platforms are just listening
to it right there. It seems like the easiest way to do it. I mean, if you subscribe to a podcast
on Spotify, it'll get a notification for time to go live. So I'm sure a lot of people probably do
that just for like, Oh, I don't have to go look for it. It comes to me. Yeah. That would, that
would make a lot of sense. I don't use, I don't use iTunes or Google Play or Spotify. So I don't
know anything about anything. Uh, okay. Next up, we've got God to in a row, Margar, Margar.
All right. First, first one from Margar. Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, Margar here. I like to expand on something that Digi said a few episodes ago
about thesis statements in your voicemails. So many of your voicemails that you guys are sending.
Yes. Do not get to the fucking point fast enough. I've only sent like a few voicemails up till now,
but even doing it week after week, it's not that hard to get an idea across and ask a fucking question.
I mean, I swear to God, most of these are not worth listening to. Get your message across
or shut the fuck up, please. The PCP has never pretended to be anything
other than a kangaroo court. And if you think that making good voicemails is any defense against
being caught up in the PC prison industrial complex, then you are mistaken, my friend.
Oh, by the way, last episode, Doon Koon sacrificed his voice grail status to free
All Die Corporation from voice jail. So a lot of drama happening there. A lot of movement on that front.
What a badass. Okay, next from Margar. Three, two, one, go.
Margar here. Ben, do you intend to make me a Margar in a case for why the abolition of the
voice jail is required? I have performed no offense and have consistently been.
And I feel that if I were to be put in court, it would be a kangaroo court. And there's no
justification for my being caught up in all of this red tape. And frankly, I think that this
is this is ridiculous. Release me immediately. Justice for Margar.
That's what I said. Now to listen to the rest of the voicemails in their entirety.
Most of which will not be worth listening to. But yeah, all you got to do. I don't think you
even need to script it out. Just like, think about like, hmm, I want to say this and then think about
you know, what, what, what do I want to say about it? Okay, I have a clear idea of what I
want to communicate in my voicemail. I don't know. Yeah, have a theme. Next up is
half our Ben St. Corr colors. And there is a link to an image of old Digimon toys.
Whoa. Now you're speaking my language. Yeah. Yeah, I want them all.
Did you have did you have a digital? I had multiple.
I me and Nate each had a Digimon. And this was before the cartoon. Yep. Same. Same.
I don't remember. I remember I had a red one and he had a blue one. And none of they didn't
look like any of these. So I must have had a different model. They released like one version
of these in America. But there was like multiple iterations in Japan. So these might be ones over
in Japan. Yeah. Yeah, none of these are the ones we had. But yeah, these three of these are Ben
St. Corr colors. The black and white ones really cool. The purple and black ones really cool.
These are I like that like RFCK like green and pink one. That's pretty nice.
Let's let's hear the voicemail. Shall we three, two, one, go. All right. So several times on the
podcast, you talked about your issue of feeling the need to look at a screen pulling up Twitter,
feeling bad. So you get off Twitter, wait 10 minutes, feel the need to look at a screen cycle
repeats. So here's an idea. VPETs, you look at the screen, but then instead of getting Twitter
and that toxicity, you get your little guy and you help him grow. Well, you might think, hmm,
which one? Maybe the Ingellium Tamagotchi or something. Well, that has giant shipping prices
because you have to import that. But Bandai of America has recently released only $20 for the
American Digimon version 20th. Now the Wave 3 is coming out soon and these colors are completely
Ben St. Corr. Look at them. I left it as the link. Next, Radcon. Do like a Royal Rumble thing to see
who the best digital monster parent was and see who the weakest parent was. See if Ben or Digi is
the better parent and who's the better at bullying their unironically on a joke. I have one of these
in my room, right? Right. And within arm's reach, I have one of the 20th anniversary Digi mods.
So is it doesn't look like one of these different color? Because he just said that's a new version
they're releasing. Mine's blue, much like Nate's probably was because it was a they were styled
in the original America. Yeah, I feel like I feel like if I had time to prepare, I could I could
have the perfect Digimon. I feel like it's not that complicated. About the 20th anniversary Digimon,
they changed it so you can raise multiple Digimon at the same time. There's like multiple trees
instead of just one and the growth is much faster. So instead of it taking days, it takes like one
or two days to get like a full adult. There were multiple trees in the old American release. But
there's like 50 different guys you can get on this one. Oh, shit. Yeah. And you can raise two
eggs at the same time. And it's like it's it's it's intense. It's it's hardcore. Honestly, maybe
maybe rat radcon five stretch goal. Digimon roll. I'm about it. I'm about it. I'm about it. That
sounds awesome. That sounds really cool. Actually, yeah, I'll do it. I'm down. Okay, next up,
pancakes. Love is cringe. Three, two, one, go. Listen, love is cringe, especially parental love.
You know, I was on a bus yesterday with a father playing with his little daughter,
and I was like, I nearly puked in my own mouth. And you know, when someone has
to say someone over and said, Hey, yo, cringe, bro. That's why my parents are the most base
ever because all they ever does is leave them out of doorstep. And hey, if you listen up there.
Nice. Nice. Pretty base.
I have to agree. Parental love is is is not is not even based. You don't even have to earn it.
Come on, you should have to earn everything in life. Like, you know, you should pull yourself
up by your bootstraps and prove to your parents. Oh, I was thinking the other way around enough
of an enough of an asset to be to be loved by them. You should have to earn your keep.
From from the perspective of a parent, it is it is cringe to love your child.
It's more based to throw them down a down a deep pit and see if they come out.
Isn't it like proven like when a child's born, like there's like a chemical like reaction in
the parent's brain that makes them like makes them cringe? Yes. Yeah, like makes them make
them love you. Like that's not even real. It's just like chemicals. Like I'm saying,
I'm saying it's cringe of you, the child to expect a handout from these from these parental
authorities. Yeah, I'm saying you need to do better and you know, give back.
So yeah, hard, hard agree. Hard cakes on this one hard.
Oh, that's gonna get a hard R for me, my dudes. Okay, next up,
pro quest, you know, is an animus. Three, two, one, go.
Oh, my boyfriend, though, didn't come in, come inside my boy pushy. Oh,
he didn't wear a boy condom. Am I going to get bad pluggers now? I is too young to be a boy
mother. Can I get this a boy portion? Oh, whoa. Can I pay my colleges with my boy pushy washy?
I don't know. Can you? Perhaps I could offer him some of my tasty boy milk? Oh, whoa.
I'm not one except the pint of my sticky boy syrup instead. Oh, whoa. I'm not the one to be
asking these questions. Well, this is why parental love is cringe. If you if you raise this. Yeah,
it's time to stop. This parents mistakes were made. This is what happens when kids are given free
communist handouts of parental love that they didn't have to work in the mines for.
This is the fall of Western civilization. This is what you get when you don't when you don't
work in the mines. This is what you get when you don't go to war.
What I'm saying is that humans are the virus. We need a good war.
Pestilence should definitely be, you know, encouraged in the poorer sections of society
so that the well bred nobles can continue and humanity can evolve. This is this is the
this is what's meant to this is the chaff meant to be left on the miller's floor.
Or if there's ever been an excuse for boy abortions after birth. This is one.
Yeah, baby. Yeah. Malthusianism. Here we go.
Is the PCP deep or bleak? Hmm. Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP. Most likely Ben St and maybe give and take. I don't know about anybody else.
But I had a question. So I got into the PCP when I was around 11 years old. Oh,
God, I'm so sorry. A little lolly.
All right. So I'm just thinking if I got into the procrastinators podcast at 11 years old,
was I mature at 11? That is technically groom. You have mature enough for me to start enjoying.
What? This was not the that's a different question than you titled your question, you you fuck.
Yeah, but 11 year old. Like, like, like if is the question can is it like understandable for an
11 year old to be into the PCP? Like, are we so immature? And so that is the audience we.
Oh, is that the question? I think was this person just mature? And we're just immature? Or are we
just immature? The question is, were they mature for their age to get into the podcast? Or are we
immature? And that's why it resonated with them. I think we're just really, really cool. And we
and we transcend. We just appeal to everyone. We transcend maturity. The procrastinators podcast
is focused, tested to appeal to the widest possible demographics where we can make the most
possible money. So it's kid, it's kid tested mother approved. There you go. I'm just kicks
his three words. PCP is three words. Maybe there's a t shirt in the future. Dude, kicks
unironically based unironically a great serial. It really is. You can't you can't go wrong with
it doesn't get enough love. It's simple. But that's that's part of its charm.
Just like life. I love life serial. I thought you meant life was simple. I was like, what the
fuck are you talking about? Life is like kicks is like life. It's just simple. It's just a little
ball of corn. You know, yeah, yeah, with a little sugarcoating on how does a fucking 11 year old
find that like click on a PCP video? Well, it's like, it's started with the Steven
Universe episode and all the downhill from there. Would it would have been would have been through
like digi or someone else? Like like maybe maybe like how how it's it's just
the same way how unusual that I guess I don't know what children do. I guess I don't think it's
that unusual. I it's the same way that people would that, you know, parents would give babies
iPads and the baby would have no idea what they're doing. It would just click random things or be
on autoplay. And that's how babies ended up watching all those weird like family finger
songs videos about like pregnant Elsa with Spider-Man in the supermarket and like Joker 3D Joker with a
gun like shooting people just just made by an algorithm, you know, just just to get just to
get those clicks, just random noise, no all noise, no signal. That's that's how it happens.
That's how it occurs. In case you were wondering, I hope that explains why didn't we get hundreds
of millions of views from the PCP episodes then, huh? We weren't we weren't we weren't we should have
maybe maybe we were getting we weren't getting the babies. We were getting like the slightly
older than babies. I wonder if we would have gotten like a huge audience of babies who would now
like just be reaching the time where like they start to get like an allowance and they start to
have a tiny bit of disposable income and no like necessities to spend it on. I wonder if they go
to patreon.com slash the procrastinators. That's right. That's that's right because they hear it
and they think I must do it. They and like if we had just titled our episodes things like, you
know, Marvel, Marvel Spider-Man, Avengers, Elsa, Frozen, you know, song, baby, child, you know,
just think like that was just every episode was just a string of like highly searchable words.
We missed our window. What a shame. We did. Well, I don't know. Is it is it too late? Well,
they crack down on child content or content that is gathering data on children you because
they can't do that. Oh, fuck. That's right. Fuck. That's right. Shit. Damn. We could have built a
mansion with that baby money. The best kind. We got a hone on this baby market. No. Yeah,
you're right. We missed our window. We fucked up. Okay, this one is called I forgot my question.
Can't wait. Three, two, one, go. How do you fucker cop not killer? I'm the guy who's going to be a
Ben St. in real life and I have a question. Question is again, it's too scary.
I hate I hate this audience. Hey, audience, I hate you. What do we say about a thesis statement?
Listen to Margarh. I feel like, okay, you know what? You know what? Because Margarh was so right,
because Margarh was so on point. Margarh, I'm going to step in. We've been waiting for months
for YouTube to just cut the red tape, cut the bullshit, quit lying, just unlist the video.
Just today, did you, I don't know if you happened to check the email, the procrastinator's email,
but just like last night Nate sent another email being like, hey, it would be really easy to solve.
YouTube caused this problem and like destroyed all this content that people paid for.
Like you could just do it and I'm going to keep asking for updates on it like until it's done
because it needs to be done and you caused this problem, please fix it. And you got another email
that's like, sorry for the delay. I understand that, you know, this the long response is
it was like misspelled the word unacceptable. It said, you know, we're again reiterated,
we're working with a limited team due to the response to COVID-19.
It's an algorithm. It's not a real person responding.
I don't know. I don't know that. I don't know if I believe you. I think it is a real person.
I'm more and more convinced that it is simply a real person and I just think
they're copy pasting. It's a real person. It's a real person, but they're copy pasting like that.
Yes. Yes. Here's the hand response plus or minus like a few different words.
I think they are just sort of coached. I think they are just kind of like coached or
told to follow a template. Yes. I think they should I just read the email?
Well, why? Yeah, sure. He brought it up for some reason. It said, hi, Nate. Thanks for getting back.
I definitely understand that the length of this being resolved is not justifiable
and I would like to apologize for this delay. As much as we would like to have this resolved as
soon as possible, but we are unable to, since we, this is a nightmare, since we are unable to,
since we submitted the report to the appropriate internal team that is working on this,
rest assured, I am also keeping an eye for this since this is ongoing for a long time.
I will circle back as soon as possible. Let me know. Should there be anything in the meantime?
Best Martin. This is really funny because yesterday I was watching Jimquisition videos
and there's an episode of Jimquisition where he talks about getting sponsorship offers from
companies that clearly do not know who he is and clearly are not familiar with his content,
but they're clearly just spamming channels with, you know, offers or whatever. And he
specifically mentions that they all say like, hey, just circling back to get back to you.
Just circle back to this. Yeah, I'll circle back to this. And there it is. On the same day,
it appears in this fucking response email, that phrase. It's probably like, like one guy who
made like a course, like it made a DVD on how to do emails to customers who are angry. It must
have got just like circulated, like everybody in every company uses that DVD to train their
personnel. That's very professional language. That's very professionally. Don't say,
don't say you'll come back because that sounds like jizz and that's gross. That could be considered
pornographic. That could be sexual harassment. Say you'll circle back like it's highly recommended
just just to avoid any any even the appearance of untowardness. Anyway, I brought this up because
why did I bring this up? Yeah, why did you write it up? I brought this up because
just like we are waiting for YouTube to cut through the red tape and just fix the problem.
I am going to step in for Margar and cut through the red tape and say, you know what,
Margar, your application is processed. We can forward you to the end of the line.
We can Disney express pass plus you pass the waiting lines. You have successfully landed
in voice jail. Congratulations. You're there. We did it. We got you through the process.
The system works. The system works, my friend. You made it. Margar. Congratulations.
These are the people who are completely terrible. We got to pass.
Some people spend their entire lives trying to get to voice jail, but this guy did it.
Okay, next one. Next one is from Cross at GameCon626 at gmail.com. Okay, three.
Is that part of his name? Is that supposed to be public? I don't know why it has an email attached
to it, but it does. Three, two, one, go. Someone mentioned Vosh like they followed him and I was
just wondering what you guys thought about him. I first heard of him when I saw a video he did
bashing Lily Orchard and then I skimmed his channel and found that the vast majority of his
content appears to be focused on antagonizing and calling out other people, though this is
just going off of the titles of his videos. Not only this, but he uploads more than once a day
on average and all of his videos seem to just be him live streaming, talking to his chat or arguing
with someone he's in a call with. I decided not to check out any more of his videos and even told
YouTube not to recommend him to me as all of this struck me as a very unhealthy channel,
not only for the viewers, but also for Vosh himself because I don't think that spending hours
every day and talking about people you claim to be problematic and getting mad about them publicly
is productive or good for helping anyone gain a stronger understanding of other people's
perspectives and resolving those disagreements. What do you guys think is my first impression
of Vosh inaccurate? Do you agree with my reasoning for not watching his videos? What are your
general thoughts of him? Thanks in advance and don't feel like you need to rush the rad content.
I have not watched a lot of Valsh, but I have seen a video or two of him
deconstructing something like those. I had no strong negative reaction from watching whatever
video it was. He was sort of deconstructing an argument and saying why it was not correct or
something. I was pretty smart and I just moved on. I can't really remember much.
What's your opinion, Tom? He's pretty good. I listened to a bunch of his videos. I was
binging them for a while. I don't usually tend to watch Left Tube that much. There was a couple
there was a month and change where I was watching a lot of Vosh and Philosophy Tube just to be like
to expand my palette of ideas because that's always fun to do. It was good. It brought new
ideas into my brain. That was good. I liked that. I felt like Vosh was probably the best way of if
you want to get somebody into Left ideas to send them Vosh because he's not prissy or
trying to be squeaky clean in his presentation. He's down there in the fucking mud with everybody
else. I appreciate it. He's a little bit dirtbag. He's not full dirtbag left, but he's kind of got
that aesthetic. He just feels like a real person. He's not putting on airs by having to make sure
everything's squeaky clean. I appreciate that because it made the ideas much more digestible.
I don't know. It felt like someone talking with you instead of talking at you from on high
from their position of virtue, which was good. Do you want to finish?
I was just going to say that I can understand why someone might think that it's unhealthy in terms
of consumption of the content. Vosh clearly seems like a dude who can handle being in conflict
with multiple people at the same time. He clearly gets off and has fun at doing what he does. I
wouldn't worry about him, but I can absolutely understand getting burned out on watching somebody
for hours on end and just picking fights with people because I eventually stopped watching
them all the time because I got burnt out watching someone pick fights with people all the time.
I was the same with Destiny for a while. I assume they're somewhat similar. They seem to be
talked about. Vosh spun off. He's like a spin-off of Destiny. He was active in Destiny's chat,
and then he started doing his own videos from what I understand.
It's the same thing. They're fun for a bit, but to watch that sort of content every day would get
exhausting. Yeah. This was a while back, but I binged Destiny. I never made the leap from
I'll watch a compilation or I'll watch a highlight video. I'll watch one of the good clips that
have a lot of views that are like him really taking down someone who really deserves it,
and it really makes a good case for something. I watched a lot of those, and I love those,
but I'm not going to tune in to watch. I don't want to watch him live. I don't want to watch him
just tune it. I have tried, and it's boring. It's rarely anything that I'm interested in,
and it's the same with Vosh. Someone recommended me Vosh, and I eventually checked him out, and
I binged a lot of his good old highlighted videos. I would never watch a stream of that
because I tend to because Vosh is up close. I have no interest in watching Vosh play
fucking Dark Souls 2 or whatever he's doing. No. His takes are mostly good. In the highlights,
they come off pretty good, but then on Twitter, I don't understand. I see that it seems like Vosh
will take down people that I think are bad, and I think that's good. But then I see on Twitter,
it seems like maybe not so much anymore, but he had a little beef with Thought Slime, and I like
Thought Slime. Why do you beef with Thought Slime? Then he had a little beef with Peter Coffin,
and I like Peter Coffin. Why are you beefing with him? I saw him calling Peter Coffin a class
reductionist, which I don't think he is, and I think that sucks. I don't really understand a lot
of the combativeness that seems to be there, but I don't actually see it in the Vosh content that
I have seen. I don't really understand what this perpetual beef machine seems so bizarre,
and I don't really understand the workings of it. It might be a Ben St. situation where he
seems a lot more angry and fighty on Twitter than he is in real life as a non-stream.
Maybe Twitter brings out more antagonistic aspects of his personality. I don't understand.
It seems to me like Thought Slime and Peter Coffin and Vosh have way more in common than they have
that they disagree on, and I kind of wish that were more like, because I don't see them interacting.
Well, I saw one interaction positively. It was when they had that hilarious thing,
this hilarious moment. Thought Slime made a video about a guy, and the guy responded,
and the guy was such a weird dweeb, and he basically criticized Slime itself
and said that the working class doesn't like Slime. The working class wants to get rid of Slime.
I can't take this guy seriously when he calls himself Thought Slime, because Slime is gross.
And I saw Vosh respond to that as a thing. So weird. And then Thought Slime, he said
Borger King. He pronounced it Borger King. And this guy assumed from that that this guy didn't know
what a hamburger was, and therefore had never had never worked fast food. It's like, I don't know.
It was very funny. So like, I saw Vosh's reaction to that, and Vosh was like, hmm, okay, I guess maybe
I'm on Thought Slime's side. And it was like, yay, left unity. But like, why? Why was the why
was this a rift that needed to be healed? You guys have so much more in common. Why was it?
It's bizarre to me that there would have been any bad blood there in the first place.
And I don't understand it. I don't like it. But I kind of don't really engage with that side
of it at all. Like when I see that, I sort of just look away like, oh, no, no, no,
two people that I like are fighting. I don't want to hear about it. I hate that.
Reminds me of the old classic YouTube poop beef between Waxinator and Guy Buchan that I never
really truly understood to my favorite YouTube poop creators. And they just didn't like each other
for some reason at some point. I was like, oh, no, that's bad.
Did they have like an ideological disagreement? No, it was like one of them exiled the other at
some point and it just was bad blood. I think maybe it was just some bad blood that built up
over time. Not like their content or like my YouTube poops are good and yours are bad. No,
mine are good. Yours are bad. This is exactly what happened. Seems like it probably is what happens.
YouTube poop elitism. Anyway, that's what I think about Vosh. Hope that was enlightening.
Next one. Ben cast best cast. Hmm. Interesting. I wonder what we're in for now. Three, two, one, go.
I'm fucking tired of these goddamn pussies telling me and coming on the podcast and going,
oh, this is the worst the podcast ever been. This is the worst the podcast ever been. Oh,
it's the best the podcast ever been. This is the best. There's just like, Ben, it's just Gib,
Tom, did you want it? It's just people that are like, they're good at talking and they don't talk
over other people and they're not fucking annoying all the time. Like like a certain someone who
wears fucking glasses. This two months has made me realize I don't even like Nate. I don't even
like it. You know, he's probably still good. I don't know. But the podcast is just better. And
these people are like, oh, don't release the solo Ben cast. The greatest podcast ever done. We all
know it's a great podcast. Don't be afraid of your feelings. I know we all know the Ben cast was
the height was it'll never get better than this. We've peaked feelings don't care about your feelings.
This guy might have been on Twitter. I think there was someone on Twitter that was also
like, I like the podcast better without Nate. And like, you know, if we have, you know, thousands
of people listening to these, probably, yeah, it doesn't surprise me that a few people are like,
you know, I, I prefer it this way. There's always been people having their old like, here's my PCP
tier list. Here's the guys that I like hearing about the most. And it's always different always
is always completely different. There's never been like a total consensus on who is the best
and the worst of this funny, stupid little group. It's funny that this guy says that Nate talks over
people because I have seen people. I feel like the sentiment is a lot that me and Nate talk over
people. I wonder you do definitely you do I. Yeah, earlier, earlier, the beginning of this,
I was taught maybe it's because of the latency. I did it like one. I did it like one time. Yeah,
I did it once. Yeah, but like, I feel like that's also because of latency, like me hearing you
later than because I'm further away or something. I'm going to blame. I mean, just in the whole,
that whole Vosh thing, I kept no, no, fuck that you don't know. There were a whole bunch of times
that I wanted. I was ready to interject with my opinions that they, but you guys had more to say
and I was like, okay, okay, yeah, let him continue, let him continue, let him continue, wait until
they're done. Then I can say my bit. Then I can say my Pete. I don't know all of the times that
you've restrained yourself. All I know is the times that you have interrupted. What about all those
times I didn't wear a dress to school? Nobody ever talks about those times. The, that's a
Simpson's reference, by the way. The, the, the, no, I think we need to blame everything on Nate.
I think the answer is that people think that I talk over people because I just, because Nate
talks over me and I have to try and talk over him. You know, to get my point across, that's my
hypothesis. You can't prove it's wrong. It doesn't matter. Anytime you say, no, but what about this
time you talked over someone unrelated to Nate? I will say, no, that's the, that's the exception
that proves the rule. Every time, every, every all counter examples are just the exception that
proves the rule. So there you go. I think, I mean, the patent that proves the rule. I think,
I think it's kind of refreshing. I don't think it's bad to have, you know, we're going through,
like, I was on almost every episode in the, in the past, I miss him. Nate's on almost, has been
on almost every episode. I don't think it's wrong to be like, Oh, you know, this person who is on
many episodes, he's not around anymore. Oh, there's a different vibe now. Maybe we, we can,
we can appreciate that. That's the thing. Um, okay, cool. Glad, glad you like, glad you've been
enjoying the episodes. Friend. Um, next one. Yep. You're closing in on the end.
Oh, two more. Next one. I'm like, wait, hold on.
Okay. No, my house is not burning down. Uh, smelled smoke, but it's, I think someone's
saying you're having a stroke. I'm having a stroke. I'm having a stroke. I'm having a stroke, baby.
Next one is vocals are instruments. Three, two, one, go to the guy that said that hip hop is
becoming worse just because the topic of the lyrics shifted from rapping about being poor to
rapping about being rich. Uh, fuck you, buddy. You should be voice jailed. If you want to listen to
the lyric or miracle bullshit, go listen to J. Cole or Eminem. Your voice is a fucking instrument,
and that's how it should be used. Us chads will continue to bump Uzi, Carti, and
woo.
Uh, I never said that I, I, when I was talking about the voice mail, who said that?
Yeah. When I was talking about, um, what, because I, I'm just like repeating what I have seen other
people said. I, I, which maybe I shouldn't even do because these are not really my opinions.
I don't really have an opinion on the hip hop scene. I think that if it's true that people are
talking more about being rich than being poor, then that's not a problem with the musical
aspect of it. Cause I absolutely agree that vocals are instrumentals. Uh, it's just like
it doesn't appeal to, that's, that's a change in the theming of it and the change in the aesthetic
of it. And in the politics of it, maybe, maybe even that I don't like because I would, I think
being rich is fucking gay. Uh, I don't know. What do you, what do you guys think?
I think vocals are instruments. I always prefer in fact that, um, I, like the words in a song,
I've never been one for like, like reading the lyrics. I was just like the way things sound.
I agree. I'm a sound boy.
Yeah. There are tons of songs I've listened to for like decades and I don't know all the lyrics
to it because I just kind of like having the vocals blend into the instrumentation and just
like being able to listen to them as sound and not as words.
Yeah. I take it all back. I take it all back.
Well, the thing is you need to learn the lyrics in order to sing along.
Uh, so if you want to sing along and sound like not shit.
And what are you saying? What are you implying? That's false. I don't, I don't know what you mean.
I'm implying.
No, I'm just going to, I'm going to do the whole song. I'm going to do the whole song.
I, I can, I can get enough satisfaction not knowing the words, not understanding what they mean
if it's in like a different language and just kind of hum along like that.
Yeah. No, it's fine. No, I agree. Yeah. Just go. That's why humming is based.
So, hey, vocals are instruments. Uh, no, we, no, we agree. No, we agree. Please don't,
please don't beat me up. Please don't get that six foot four football monster.
He's already coming. That, that, that dies been cat.
Please, please can we negotiate?
I like how, I like how Margar is in voice jail for just some pretty, making some pretty like
some pretty mild. I don't even remember what, why I put him. Yeah, we didn't shoot the messenger,
but we did imprison it. But this guy, this, this, this football monster, he's not, he's
just made threats against my physical safety, but I'm too, I'm too scared to put him in voice
jail. I mean, if I call the police, I'll just make him mad.
If you put him in voice jail, he's going to be closer to you. You want him to be as far away as
possible. Uh, yes. Voice eskaban. Uh, yes, exactly. Wait, no, no, eskaban. What's the real version of that?
I have just, uh, alcatraz. Alcatraz. I have just started like sweating profusely for reasons that
I don't understand. Ben, you're having a stroke. This is so many red flags coming up. Every, every,
every episode I have, every episode I have a stroke, every episode I have a stroke. How many
more? I think it's, I think it's the Karongi virus. Is sweating, is sweating a Karongi virus thing?
It's a symptom of sorrow which we're in. It's a, it's a symptom of heat and, and or fever.
Oh God. Wait, wait, wait. I took my temperature. I took my temperature before the episode. Let me,
let me take it again. One more voicemail and Ben's going to drag this out as long as possible.
Oh my God. 200 degrees. Well, according to this meat thermometer,
my temperature may have risen by a degree or two. Yikes. Yo, God. We're going to do this voicemail
before Ben St collapses and dies. We gotta, we gotta wrap this up quick. Okay. Darren,
Darren the Red. Three, two, one, go. So I was drunk, listening to Hatsune Miku cleaning the
kitchen, jamming my ass out. I hit the orange justice and dislocated my knee. What's the most
embarrassing way you guys have been injured? Um, that's not embarrassing. I mean, that's pretty cool.
That's based. Uh, I mean, do you count me, uh, breaking my tooth, biting that sign in the RFCK
lecture? That seems, that seems valid. It's a little embarrassing. I broke it on paper. I feel
like a more embarrassing break of your bones, Ben, is, is when you just walked, like you heard
something in Radcon 2 or Radcon 1 even, and you came into the room and you stubbed your
toe and you had to go to the hospital. You stubbed it so bad that it broke.
I mean, was that really embarrassing? Like, I was just, I just stubbed my toe. I was just,
like, walking somewhere and I stubbed my toe. Yeah, how embarrassing that you have such a frail,
weak body. That I wasn't, that I wasn't even doing anything. Um, I mean, how, how is it,
I'm just, I guess I'm trying to think of like, what is embarrassing about being injured?
Like is, if it's your fault that it happens, I guess, then it's embarrassing.
I guess, okay, I'm thinking like, okay, you're thinking like, like the injury itself is embarrassing.
I'm thinking like, what was I doing something that is, would be embarrassing anyway,
that result, that resulted in injury. I, I see where you're coming from though.
Um, I have never embarrassed myself, so I can't answer this question.
I can't think of a thing that would be embarrassing to be called, and then also get an injury doing it.
Like if the injury is not part of the embarrassment, there's nothing,
you can't be embarrassing, it's impossible.
Uh, what's the, what's the, what's the most severe injury you've ever had?
Mine was, breaking my toe is actually like the most, I'd never, that was the first time
I'd ever broken a bone, and I've actually broken that bone like several times now. I've broken that toe.
Yeah. Uh, I think, you know, the, the, I've never broken a bone. I've been very cautious in my life.
I'm, I'm squeaky clean. I've only ever had like illnesses.
Nice.
So I guess the most embarrassing one is, uh, diarrhea.
Gross.
Because there's shit everywhere.
Oh, the work.
Yeah.
Yeah. Just sitting around, minding your own business, and then it's like,
and you got to, you got to get out of the hair. You got to go real quick.
It's time to escape.
All of a, all of a sudden I'm like, I'm all, I'm super sweaty. I feel weird. I feel really hungry.
I really want to eat, and like I did, I ate some like pickles and I drank some like coffee and
almond milk. I shouldn't be hungry, but I'm like, gotta get, gotta get those soft drinks.
What is going on? You met a morphosizing, you.
Oh no, please.
Is it a full moon?
Change is bad. Change is bad. Uh, I hope not.
Ugh, please. Oh, please don't let me be.
Should we end the podcast before you die?
No, she's don't want you to have the Karungi virus.
I would be really funny.
You're not coughing.
You know, the most, the most embarrassing way, everything is the Karungi virus.
Everything is the iKarumba virus.
I went outside and I went into a pizza place and I hand sanitized.
I was with, I was with Kazi and Munchie.
We went to a pizza place because they were getting pizza.
I sanitized my hands because I touched the door.
The guy behind the counter was wearing his mask wrong.
He had his fucking nose out.
I wanted to kill him.
I wanted to kill him, but he was ethnic, so I couldn't because it would be a hate crime.
But if he was white, if he would, this is why you know white privilege is fake,
because if, if he was white, I would have killed him.
Damn.
I'm convinced.
Or, you know, Jew, or Jew, Jewish white passing, you know, whichever.
I'm sorry.
I end, I end all the podcasts on weird racial notes now because I don't know.
I fucked up.
It's, it's just the Karungi virus, guys.
It's, it's, it's, it does, it does bad things to all of us.
It's, it's, you mean, you mean the Kung flu.
Oh, yeah, that.
Oh, cringe.
Are we, are we ready?
Are we done?
I think we're done.
Send your voicemails to speakpike.com slash pcp voicemail.
P.C.P. voicemail, subscribe, go to Twitter.
Hit the.
At the.
Follow.
Patreon, funny bonus episodes.
We make a new bonus episode soon.
It'll be cool.
Yes.
I guess we better fucking get on making that fucking bonus episode, which if we do it,
it'll be available at patreon.com slash the procrastinators for only $5 for a
host of cool quality legacy PCP content.
And, um, hey, by the way, since I did have a work spree last night,
and I have almost done with slime and punishment,
next thing I do after that, after I drop the finale to that,
is I'm going to be releasing a sonichu lecture too.
So I don't know what's going on with Munchie's lecture or Digi's lecture,
or is there another one that we're waiting for?
No, just those.
Your second one, and then the two.
Yeah, sonichu, sonichu lecture number two is, uh, is going to be,
is going to be coming out pretty soon, actually.
So I'm excited for that.
I need to, I need to reupload the brisk lecture because I have it still.
I just, I don't, well, we, it's going to come back maybe.
Bad.
It might, I was thinking, yeah, we, I've been thinking like, okay, well,
you know, we shouldn't reupload because it would be really shit if like,
the Animorphs lecture came back with zero views instead of the like 200,000 that it had.
Um, I would just, I would just be sad about that.
You and me both.
But then I was like, but then I was like, wait a minute,
I had this like, this like late night, like anxiety thought.
I was like, what if, what if they do actually get around to doing it,
but they bring them back, but like the, all the views are the comments and stuff are lost.
And like, it's as, it's as if we had just reuploaded them anyway.
I don't know whether that happens.
Uh, I mean, I don't have to go to YouTube HQ and riot.
Like, why would that specifically YouTube HQ, why would the,
why would specifically that amount of the data of the YouTube page be lost?
I don't know.
Why are they gone in the first place?
None of this makes sense.
Yeah.
And not, yeah, none of it makes sense.
Like who's, who's to say?
We don't even really know, understand the details of what they did.
So who's to say?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't do it.
I don't know if that will happen, but I don't know that it won't happen either.
But they, I'm just saying, Hey, wouldn't that suck?
Wouldn't that be shit?
Pretty bad.
Well, let's, let's, let's see, I guess.
Uh, yeah.
All right.
End of the podcast.
I guess so.
The end.
See you.
Thanks for, thanks for listening for another week of pro procrastinators.
Goodness.
Welcome to, welcome to the end of the show.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Dude.