Hello, Ashen One, and welcome to the latest Pro Crastinators Podcast. On this episode we'll
be talking about Dark Souls 3. There will be massive spoilers for the entire game. If
you give a shit about bullshit like that, don't watch this video. I mean, really, you
won't understand half of what we're saying if you haven't played the game. And it's
a really fucking good game. We all thought it was a 10 out of 10. So just play it, and
enjoy the podcast.
Hello everybody, and welcome to the Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am your host, Digibro, to talk about
Dark Souls 3. I've got with me Jesse Endless Jess. Say hello, Jesse. Hello. How's it going?
And I've got the best guy ever as well. Hey guys, what's going on? Ready to get
swole in the dark? We decided we're trying to make this podcast
Let me cut and break in for a sec, because there's a lot of talking over people going
on. We want to avoid that as much as possible from here on out. So maybe less people might
be better. By the way, happy Mother's Day to all the
MILFs in our audience. I know there's a lot of you. Happy Mother's Day that we're recording
this and this podcast won't come out for a week and a half. That's true. If there's
one thing I want to do more of in all my online pursuits, it's attract real women into having
real sex with me. So now's my quick plug for that. So MILFs, shout out to you today.
You're the only one here who hasn't done it. You fucking jump.
Had sex via... that's not due to online stuff. That's true. One day. You could be the first
ladies, get in line.
Alright, so we're talking about Dark Souls 3 today. I think we all really like this game
a lot.
Sure do. And that's why we're doing this. It's like the coolest game ever. It's fucking
rad.
I haven't played since Dark Souls 1 probably.
But it's still a 10 out of 10.
Jesse, I'm curious about your issues with it because you have been the most crazy of
this game from the beginning. I've never heard you complain about it really. So what is your...
I guess my main complaint, none of my complaints are huge complaints.
But I like the fact that in Dark Souls 1 and 2, as soon as you start the game, there's
like 3 or 4 different directions you can go. And this game doesn't branch off until...
Well let me refute that right off, because in Dark Souls 2 that's not the case. That's
only true in Dark Souls 1.
What the fuck are you talking about you stupid idiot? Yes it is.
No it's not. You can't go down the well. You can go one way.
You don't know anything about Dark Souls 2. You Gebronies always run your mouths about
Dark Souls 2. I'm already mad. It's been 5 minutes. You always run your mouths about
Dark Souls 2.
There are two ways.
You don't know a goddamn thing about it. You're not a fucking Dark Souls 2 master like me.
That's true.
So shut your damn mouth and know your damn role.
Okay well maybe that's true. I can definitely agree with you with one. Dark Souls 3 is the
most linear of them all. That is true. I looked at a big map that shows like a flowchart
of the ways you can go. There aren't that many optional areas, though there weren't
really that many of the others. And the chart goes pretty straightforwardly.
I would definitely say the first time I played through it I was struck by how linear it felt.
It's really not. I mean when you're in the Crucifixion Woods you can go either fight
the Abyss Watchers or go to the Cathedral of the Deep.
That's right.
There's always spoilers for everything in this podcast.
Oh yeah.
Gonna spoil it all.
No real sense in making podcasts.
That's good because the lore is great and there are some great, I bet there's some stuff
you guys don't even know. If you haven't done all the threads, all the quest threads and
I can't wait to talk about them because they're awesome.
I would say that like when I started up my New Game Plus the very first thing I did was
in the first area go kill the old lady who gives you the cup and then it makes you fight
the dancer as soon as you kill her. So then I fought the dancer and I went up through
the castle and did the castle stuff before anything else in the game.
So that was definitely cool because it made it so, I couldn't imagine trying to do that
on a brand new game unless you were like extremely pro tier and you really wanted the challenge.
Yeah, it's preventative in the sense that you're severely underleveled doing it on
a non-New Game Plus and it doesn't want you to do it really but you can do it if you're
good enough.
But it was cool to do on New Game Plus because it was right away, whereas the whole game
I would say this game is kind of easy compared to the other Dark Souls games especially on
New Game Plus where you were like, I don't know, I was super overpowered for like all
of this game and when I started up New Game Plus I immediately went and fought like all
the hardest bosses at the beginning. You know, like I fought the dancer, I fought the dragon,
the blind dragon Osiros, I fought the living armor and you know, killed all of them.
Well you said you did it right at the beginning but you can't even get there until like most
of the way through the game.
Like Osiros is like buried way down and fucking, I don't know, somewhere, I don't know, it's
going to take you like five, six hours to get there even if you're making a fucking
B-line.
What do you mean? I'll talk about from New Game Plus.
Yeah, you can't just walk straight there, you gotta fucking unlock the paths and shit.
But the only thing you have to do is you start off in the castle area on the wall, the high
wall of Lothric, you run in, you kill the old lady and that makes the dancer spawn and
then once you kill the dancer you can just run.
Oh shit, I forgot it was down that path, yeah you're right.
I was wrong.
So you can just run in there and kill Osiros and I even went to the burned out version
of the shrine, a Firelink shrine.
I did all that shit like right at the beginning of New Game Plus, which was cool because those
bosses all drop a fuck ton of souls and when you start New Game Plus your biggest problem
is that it takes a lot of souls to level you so by fighting all the hardest bosses first
I had like a shit ton of souls.
The only thing you can't do is you can't go into the, like you can't get into the grand
archives until you have all of the other bosses killed.
So you can't go fight the brothers and all that shit until you've killed all the bosses.
So it did feel like once I was on New Game Plus I did get to play it in a significantly
different enough way that it was like yeah cool it's not exactly the same but now that
I've done a few more new game runs it really is like man this is a pretty linear game.
Your choices are you either do Cathedral of the Deep or you do the Abyss Watchers first.
But let's set this in the context of the Soulsborne series because before this was Bloodborne,
before that was Dark Souls 2 and before that was Dark Souls 1.
So like most people are playing this game coming off of playing Bloodborne and so that's
kind of the way that I was comparing things and I gotta say I've played Dark Souls 1 and
2 and Bloodborne recently and Dark Souls 3 definitely feels more like Bloodborne just
in the sense of the quickness of your movements and the way your character moves and all of
that is really good.
It is different so I could see someone not liking it.
It feels a little bit less deliberate but I definitely like it and it's kind of got
the faster pace of Bloodborne with the vast weapon variety of the Dark Souls series and
they've incorporated this new ability with the L2 what are they called like Focus Attacks
which add a whole bunch of extra shit.
Man I just got this sword.
I didn't even know this was the thing this is how great this game is.
I just beat the game again on New Game Plus.
I walk up to Ludelith who can like fuse souls and like it just so happened I didn't even
know this was a thing.
You have the option of fusing if you've made both of the Princess Swords from the Princess
and the Castle he'll fuse them into one super sword that can do both of their special attacks
with the L2 commands.
I did not know that there was a guy who can fuse swords I've never heard of it.
That's the thing he can only do it with this one weapon and I just happened to stumble upon
it.
Wait who does this?
Who fuses the swords?
Ludelith like the guy who fuses and who turns souls into weapons he just fuses it was the
coolest thing ever.
I'm just saying like there's all this shit there's it's it's got the touch still you
know it's got it all.
I don't I anyway like I just wanted to ask you guys how you felt about like the controls
in comparison to you know the other games because I really like the way it's moving
even though this is like probably the last souls they're making for a long time which
makes me very sad.
Makes me angry they should be a new souls game every year for the rest of my game.
I would have absolutely no problem with them churning out a game of this nature every single
year I want that these are great there's no problem and yet they decide to end it.
Well they said that they're ending the souls franchise that they're working on a new IP
I mean that could be another bloodborne for all we know like another game that's yeah
the same kind of mechanics but different you know I wouldn't mind getting like like personally
I'm okay with like souls itself being over because I felt like this game was the ultimate
one you know like if they wanted to because like what was cool about bloodborne was that
it was the same kind of game but it had such different mechanics to it that it was like
you know you could play it for different reasons like I think with with the previous games
each one was kind of similar enough that you would just play whichever one was your favorite
you know but where like bloodborne is different enough that you might play that one for just
because you want a different experience and I think it would be cool if we got some more
games like that maybe something even more in the direction of like a platinum game style
thing with like more action and like fast-paced stuff or maybe something even more fucking
deep and complex you know but I definitely think that like from soft is moving in the
way of maybe just understanding controls better like I don't I wonder how much the like demons
souls was clunky because that made it easier to make a deep combat system you know yeah
I mean there's there's always trade-offs with stuff like that like like the weapon or no
is it like the item weight limits that was in demon souls one like nobody likes that
but like it does add an additional layer of depth to things yeah it's just you know I'll
say that I think so if I were to summarize what I think like Dark Souls 3 did overall
like compared to the other games it's that it really streamlines everything and yeah but
while I think like bloodborne streamlined it but then also was like really different where
it was more of this like fast-paced you know aggressive type of game but with Dark Souls 3
it's like they made the the fact that there's bonfires like everywhere you never have to
like run all the way back to a boss they took out exceedingly generous with the bonfires a
little bit more than I thought was appropriate or necessary right but I really felt like this
game was meant for the long term because like I think with with demon souls that game was
super fucking memorable like everything about it was the most memorable thing ever because you
would go through it a hundred fucking times like if you died you had to play the whole level again
yeah even you know even if you died to the boss you had to play all the way back to the
boss every single time and every level was so distinct that that it kind of got away with
that because it was like such a you know engrossing game but I think that once Dark Souls 1 came out
and you had the shortcuts and it was easier to get back to bosses and it felt more like well
I mean there were shortcuts and demon souls too right but I mean like yeah I mean that's
definitely true but I think with Dark Souls it was just generally you didn't have to run
back quite as much that's true that's true and I think that Dark Souls also with the flask system
like with demon souls if you died a whole bunch of times to the same boss you had to then go fucking
spend a year grinding grass again you know yeah so they introduced this flask system so that no
matter how many times you died you always started off on the same foot you know you never had to
like completely restart the flask system is genius it's the it's the best it's the best so I think
that was already sort of an effort to streamline it but even in Dark Souls there's a lot of moments
where there's there's not a bonfire for a long time they had hidden bonfires like really
dickishly hidden bonfires you know like the one in the fucking forest like if you didn't hit that
illusory wall yeah find that bonfire I beat the game twice before I figured out how to get to the
bottom of the forest yeah right it took me a long time to figure that you know the one in the right
before the area where the the giant is throwing bombs in the top of the snake fortress sends
fortress there's one way up top there and if you don't find that one you have to go through the
whole fucking trap filled fortress yeah it's just it's fun but I always would I would always see
like items down there oh yeah yeah like I fucking went through the game twice going like how the
fuck where is it how do I get there and finally where exactly are you talking about the uh the
bottom layer of the uh of the forest place that you have to get through like where the hydra is
you have to like go through like a secret tree wall or some shit I don't remember like uh near
the gateway to uh I don't know where there's like a where there's the living tree I think I know what
he's talking about yeah anyways it's a pile of shit it's the worst game ever they're all yeah
yeah that's right but yeah like that's the thing like that game it had stuff like that and I think
that was great I think it made it a really memorable and cool game that you had this like harsh experience
but you never get that again when you play it again you know you once you've beaten dark souls
and once you know all the secrets you know them forever and then all those things that are kind
of a pain in the ass become a real pain in the ass because like you know the first time you're
playing everything's equally hard and it's it's never like a matter of well I had to run back a
thousand times here I just raped I'm playing it right now and I just raped the dancer she's fucking
dead she was no match for my magic for my dark powers of sorcery from the another world the
boba duke spook I kill her with the wizard safe take her yeah by the way I meant to mention this
earlier but you should be following endless jessie's channel the blue glow where he's been playing
dark souls 3 and my channel digi bros where we've been playing dark souls 3 uh I would say jessie's
is more memorable though because his characters are quite a sight they're rich and yeah well that
leaves me as deep as real dark souls character yeah the uh the uh the blue glow lore is becoming
quite masterful the time is convoluted on uh the endless that's true that's very true that leads me
to my other much larger complaint that I didn't even realize was wait wait wait can I finish the
point I was making real quick because I actually forgot to wrap it up just that that like so you
know when I for me when I played through dark souls one because I played through all these
pretty recently the hardest part for me the most frustrating was an Orlando because there's that huge
run back to the bot like from whichever bonfire you pick like you always have to run this massive
distance and I thought it was such a pain in the ass to have to do that and so like with dark souls
3 I really think they were thinking about it in like long term like it's not as memorable the first
time through like in dark souls where you really struggled and you really had to run all the way
back because they put bonfires everywhere but I think that in repeated playthroughs this game
will be the least frustrating and the easiest to come back to and I think that might be what they
were going for because at this point it's like we already have the old games you know if you
you've already had that experience of the the epic frustrating intense game and anyone who
anyone who doesn't hasn't played the old ones isn't going to be that like like if they make a new
game and it's more accessible than like any of the people who couldn't make it through dark souls
one this is the one they're gonna play anyway okay I mean I guess you could maybe interpret it that
way but then I see bonfires like like when you kill the uh the what is it like the dragon slayer
armor and then you run up the hill and there's another bonfire right there it's just like that's
just stupid why did you put that well it's stupid but at the same time the dragon slayer
bonfire is the one that's the fastest way back to the brothers once you open up that shortcut
so no that's fine I mean you leave the dragon slayer one and you just don't put that other
one there in front of that building you you yeah I mean they can they can handle the extra two
second walk just I don't know I definitely think it looked goofy and like really at that moment
you know um yeah but I I think I think honestly they could have just moved that dragon slayer
bonfire to the other end of the bridge and that would have been like because it's as it stands
it's only so much more convenient because you still have to run across the whole fucking bridge
to get to the elevator that goes to the brothers so like no matter what you've got a fairly long run
so I was like why did you even put these two bonfires so close together if uh if it wasn't
going to be that much more convenient that's very true I suggest what was your next complaint you
wanted to bring oh yeah okay I didn't even realize that I had this complaint because it's like a
class specific complaint and I'm not the only one people are flipping out about this like Dark Souls
fans is it about the magic no it's uh because the first time you know I made my guy I usually go
for like a dex kind of build I had my fucking dancer swords it was cool as shit I was like all
right then the next one I did my fucking boba duke spook and I'm like yeah I did a little play
field like look at me I'm so cool I'm the fucking evil guy that's gonna suck my dick and that was
cool so then I'm so then I made a third character and I'm like okay who will be my next wacky dark
souls character to enter the blue glow and change people's lives for the better so I decided to make
a tank character and I'm gonna make him I'm gonna make him like the most defensive uh yes like high
vitality impossible to knock down fucking tank guy big fat fucking fat armor I named him tank
mcspank he's the coolest character ever and I wanted to unleash him upon the world but then I started
playing and I started realizing there's no fucking poise in this game poise doesn't do a goddamn thing
in this game and then I started looking it up and I realized it's not I'm not making it up it's not in
my head it's true they fucking they totally nerfed poise so like would you just describe what that
means in case they don't know yeah okay so poise is the stat like in dark souls one if you if you
get hit your character gets knocked back it'll like interrupt your attacks and shit but if you have
like high enough poise then nothing can like stop you so if you're in the the middle of an attack
getting hit by a sword won't stop you you can like walk through enemies like hits and like
just brush it off and keep walking that's what the poise is for and uh dark souls three it has a poise
stat but the poise stat does nothing it to the point where like it has to be a mistake it has to be
like a glitch people are assuming but because now I've been told that the poise also wasn't a thing
in dark souls two I can't verify that because I don't remember making a strength build in that
game okay but it doesn't matter if it were people wouldn't just be complaining about it now well
that's the thing because I I brought this up to my brother shade who's like an expert on all the
games and he was like oh yeah poise wasn't a thing in dark souls two and I was like oh well I don't
know if Jesse knows that because I've only heard it from you but I don't really read souls communities
or yeah well like I never would have noticed it except until like for the first time I made like
a tank kind of character right well that's shit like it like it just it just seems like a mistake
because they have stuff like the wolf ring which increases poise yeah it literally does nothing
because the poise stat is worthless and people discovered it'll get patched yeah a lot of people
there's people who like discovered like they went into the code of it and they like change
something around and they were able to activate poise by going into the code of the game but
then they got like soft banned from from software as though like they don't want people to have
poise well those people probably played online with that poise that you know they were probably
because if if other people don't have it then it's unfair but it just seems like weird and fishy like
you'd think by now there'd be like a statement on it where they'd say either like yeah we took it
off because of these reasons or yeah we made a mistake and we'll fix it I mean I assume it's
the same in the Japanese version which has been out for what six months you know four or three
months something it's a while well that's shit I also complain about magic because I haven't actually
done this myself because I I don't play as a pussy ass magic user but I hear magic is just
totally totally garbage I you know I haven't I haven't done much pvp but I just heard that
it's totally unviable I'll put you into 69 of torment
yeah yeah I don't know oh by the way though I was just messing around for the first time
just a few minutes ago using the spell what was it uh what is it it's the one where you turn into
like the background fucking camouflage or whatever it is it is the most fun I've ever had in a video
game I just I follow behind an enemy I'm in Irithyll right behind the giant like sword dancer ladies
I follow like an inch behind them as a statue and then when they turn around I just stop moving
and they bump into me and move around and I do this for like 10 minutes it's the most fun I've
ever had in a video game they don't know what the fuck's going on it's great stupid ass hollows
that's what I'm saying it is a spell oh yeah well there's also like the item the the white the white
branches do that too oh really oh I didn't know that that's cool yeah um yeah man I I got it so to
talk about builds because my my experience with this game was kind of funny because like you know
I've got my my friend Donsan who played this into Japanese version and he breezed through it played
it three times but by the time the English version came out and uh he was saying that he thought it
was kind of easy and then me and my brother Shade played it and we both beat it in 18 hours of
peace and we both thought it was really easy compared to the other games and like I talked about this
on Twitter and then people were like what are you talking about this game is no easier than the
others it's just as hard and I was like look if I replayed Bloodborne I would have a harder time
than I did playing this game for the first time okay well first of all I'm not sure you should
compare it on a direct thing with Bloodborne because that is a different sort of game but I
think right we just played Dark Souls 1 not too long ago and I find it a very similar experience
the the pace is a little bit faster in this but I don't I don't know that seems like this
this felt like the the shortest and easiest of the games to me where I there's nothing that
there was nothing that gave I never died more than three times on the same thing until like the final
bosses like the the brothers and Osiris were like the only things that killed me more than three times
and uh and in each one was like five so it was just like but I don't know I don't know how much of
that was my build because once I was talking about it online everyone was telling me like
they had a much harder time with it or they took a lot longer than I did well did you did you get
all the secrets and stuff and I was like yeah I got there's like a venture I the 18 hours was
before I did all the secret levels once I did them all like I went back and did them it was like
closer to 21 hours but I still felt like I just kind of steamrolled most of the game you know and
then I figured out did you go into the the catacombs of the fucking underground lava place because
that was that once fucking nightmare that's gonna be like five hours to clear out well maybe not
that long but a while after I was already pretty strong I mean we just did it on digi bros and on
like a new game and we we like went there right in the catacombs we just went straight to that level
and Victor cleared it in the span of three episodes you know so I don't know I but then again the thing
is that all of us we later realized played our first run of the game with strength builds we
all played putting everything into vigor and strength and and like a little bit of endurance
and and like vitality I mean that's that's easy mode that's easy mode for sure right well that's
the thing like I don't know like to what extent that is like literally easy mode but you know we
all played like naked do all the roles and just have a giant sword and that's your like your method
you know like giant sword plus 10 kill everything in one hit run through you know and it definitely
felt easier that way and then once I did try to play like a different type of character that
wasn't all strength then I immediately was like a lot more frustrated like okay this is a lot harder
playing anything other than strength so I do think that maybe the build is like because I think in
every Dark Souls game every Souls game like you can there is built in like difficulty settings
you know like the way you play changes the difficulty of the game and I think that might
be more true in this game than it's ever been before where strength build really is like an easier
difficulty setting of the game than I mean but why would that be there's there's just the one answer
that like I mean the more the tougher you are like a big health bar what it translates to is
you're able to make more mistakes and that's pretty much it because like if you're a ranger it like I've
heard a lot of people have actually played like with a bow in this game that like using the short bow
is is totally a viable way to play and like you can just cheese almost every boss just by staying
far away and just backing up continuously and firing arrows so like I don't know there's uh
there's lots of ways to cheese things and buffing your health as far as it'll go rate making yourself
strong and then just giving yourself the ability to you know make mistakes I guess it's just that it's
so easy to do in this game because in the other games I always grind it at the start like in Dark
Souls uh or rather in uh in Bloodborne because that was the first one I played all the way through
I spent like five hours just grinding souls and and vials so that I would never run out of vials
like right at the start of the game before I made any progress and then like in all the other games
I would always have parts where I had to grind for souls or grind for tight tight night and
shit and then in this game like by the time because you start off with a boss fight like right at
the beginning and by the time you get to Firelink Shrine you can immediately level up five or six
times and then in the second level you find a guy who gives you five free level ups you know
and so but at a dark cost yeah but that dark cost doesn't have any really negative effects
oh it can't use your worst effect it makes you ugly that's yeah yeah yeah but it doesn't have
any like it's a lore effect mostly like in in in the previous games like like take Demon Souls
like if you were well me in this game you know you can ember yourself and it gives you a longer
life bar but like in Demon Souls the only way you could become human was to kill a boss you know
so you more likely spent the entire game as as a hollow with half a health bar you know well like
three quarters because you'll use the cling ring probably right but yeah you still are always going
to have a reduced health bar because it's such a huge risk to be human because if you die as a human
then your world tendency gets darker and the whole game gets harder yeah so like for me I would beat
a boss and then I would immediately kill myself in the nexus so that I wouldn't um you know darken
my world tendency uh because I didn't want the game to get that much harder so like I don't feel
like there's any real trade-off for hollowing in this game like you you gain five level ups and
there's really nothing to stop you all right I mean that is true the the effects of the hollowing
are are purely aesthetic and like ending relative that just fucks with like the the path you can
take but I don't know I the game's like trading the normal hollow it's doing it's it's doing a new
direction hollows are out embering is in lords of cinders are what the cool kids are doing now
and I think it's cool and I just did the uh the the dark ending the usur your usurpation of the fire
ending and I thought it was fucking tight some of the coolest shit happens along that line I have
not seen that ending yet you haven't seen oh dude it's the coolest I think was angry I've been I've
been saving it for baba duke spook because it seems like something he would do and I haven't
thought his storyline was over yeah well his let's play storyline is over but
me playing the game is never over dude you gotta gotta get him his betrothed you know that was just
the end of his seventh life who knows how many he has yeah I don't know he's like the doctor he
regenerates but he's always the same guy I want to shout out real quick um my favorite boss my
favorite thing in all the dark souls games thus far has been um maiden astrea that boss fight is
the coolest thing that ever happened and it really is the best thing in any of the things but uh
there's one in this game that comes close it's not as good but I love it dearly and it affected me
greatly in my in my playthrough so uh I played the entire my entire new game plus cosplaying as an
undead legion member and I was I was making the gesture at everyone I met I was fucking wearing the
armor the whole time I used uh the the the wolf greatsword the undead legion is the coolest thing
that's ever happened uh since maiden astrea and I'll tell you why it's because these motherfuckers
like the when I heard the fucking I forget who said um that that guy me at the beginning
who's like the uh the crestfallen warrior of this game is a is a uh what's the word uh
deserter of the undead legion he's wearing the armor and shit and he he tells you like it's a
it's a bunch of dudes they're all really strong they have this they've consumed wolf blood to allow
them to to to do these inhuman fighting techniques that a normal person can't do with these giant
greatswords and they don't use shields because those are for pussies and um they he in his own
words they will bury a fucking kingdom at the first sign of the abyss spreading into it is that
not the coolest thing these people have no tolerance for your fucking darkness and they
will do whatever it takes to crush it and then when you you go go into the boss fight and all
these motherfuckers are going absolutely berserk they're fucking murdering each other they just keep
picking themselves back up because they're undead they go kill each other and then they fall down
I don't know why they're doing that I I think they were like fucked up by uh Aldrich or something
but but it was the coolest thing I've ever seen in my life it was the best boss fight
since main Australia they are the cutest I love them I want to be one they're my best friends
undead legion for life I love them so much I definitely thought the moment when they started
fighting each other I was like holy fucking shit it was the most creative thing I've seen in forever
I was a little disappointed when I found out that that some of them are specifically on your side
like the ones that have red eyes are fighting with you and the other ones are fighting against
now hang on I I looked into that that is not true because I many a time fighting those guys
die antagonize them and every single one including the red eyes will gang up on you they uh the red
eyes are that's what I I had thought that they were just fighting each other but that they would
turn on you I mean uh my brother told me otherwise maybe it's a new game plus thing because I'll
tell you those red eyes attacked me many times so that's that is not that's cool because that's
what I wanted it to be was just that they were like they were fighting each other but just out of
fucking like those guys are just going crazy in there they're just going fucking berserk it's
the coolest thing ever god that's the best I don't know like uh and and the uh the nameless king
shout out shout out that guy as the most spectacular boss I haven't seen the nameless
king yet actually oh he's he's a toughy he's a toughy yeah because on my on my uh first game
is like I because I did the thing where in this game it lets you if you beat the game you can go
you can still keep playing so I went back and I wanted to bring that up because actually just
now just a few minutes ago I I got my ending and I did that and the first time I instantly
reset because I fucked up I didn't want to but I did so this time uh I want to talk about the
lore implications or if this is just non-diagetic gameplay or something because I did that I I did
the usurpation of the fire thing so I think you like steal it or something and I walked back just
to see what's going on and the uh the the kill of the first flame like the the sword the the
bonfire there like there's no fire there it's like gone out and so I go back to fire link uh and I
see that Ludlith is dead he was alive before now he's dead and nothing else has changed so it's
making me wonder if this is like canon or or what happens if you do a different ending Ludlith is
Ludlith is always dead if you go back after okay so just because he died when when they activated
did you do a new you know continue after you uh if with a different ending you know what I'm
saying did you guys do that I haven't done a second I have not done a second continuation after
I don't know what the fuck I like it feels if I don't I I want to I want to bring this up because
this feels like something that is actually like wrong like this shouldn't be happening but they're
doing it just to let you play around in the world and like I like that I always liked how harsh that
the other games were like if you go fight the final boss you better be ready for new game plus
like it was well that's a thing though I said there was never there was never a warning for it
yeah and I think that like I I understand like doing it that way because you know thematically it
makes sense it's a brutal game you know but like I do think that there was something to be said for
like like for instance I I still haven't played the DLC in Dark Souls one because I straight up forgot
like I went to the final boss beat him and then remembered like during the final cut scene that
I had not done the DLC and I was like fuck I completely fucked up and there's no way I could
just like you know I'd have to play through the whole fucking game because you have to get all
the way to Duke's archives to even get into the DLC you know um and then Bloodborne kind of does
the same thing if you if you beat the final boss then you got to play all the way back through so
like for instance when uh Game Grumps were were doing the DLC like they came back to the game
they had to play all the way up to that point in new game plus just to be able to to do it on the
show it's like I I like that I can just have one character who I can just leave there if I want to
you know like that I can go back and do everything possible before I go to new game plus and have
all the items I want and be like completely prepared and you know have done everything and
and if I wanted to have like let's say you just wanted to have a character who you leave in that
state like so that you can just dick around in the end game you know like just have a guy who's
always perpetually at the end of the game no no don't like it I don't want it don't want it
because what that they're just they're catering it to uh to to the casual audience and I don't
like it I think you should have to play I don't think that caters the casual audiences
they're sacrificing narrative coherence for for you know convenience and I don't think that's
the trade-off I want well I don't think I have to suspend my disbelief at all to understand that I am
already done with the game and this is like a standard feature in most video games but Dark Souls
isn't a standard game it's better than a standard game and it should be held to that standard
like I said this earlier that I think that the goal of this game and I think this is true of a
lot of things in this game that I think the goal of it is to be playable long term in a way that
the other games aren't as much where I really think that with the other souls games they put a
lot of value on the first experience and a lot of value on like you know the learning experience
you'd have with it and like that like that's why there's so many traps and things like that but
none of that stuff matters as much on your second and third and fifth and eighth playthrough
because once you know it you can just easily avoid all the traps okay but here's the thing here's the
thing if you just if you just look into it ahead of time you'll know that fighting the final boss
triggers the end so you shouldn't be looking into it ahead of time if you're on but you should just
play the game experience what happens and then you'll know it's a game that's meant to be played
multiple times I think it's a reasonable trade-off I rather it's not one you shouldn't do that you
should make it I think I would much like I don't know that I would have gone well okay like because
I am so into this game I would have done it but like it would have been so much more disheartening
to find out about the Nameless King after I had already reset my game and I probably wouldn't have
run back and done it immediately but you see the thing you're protesting against is the very thing
that makes the game unique it's unwillingness but I don't bend before the whims of the masses
who want convenience overall with the other games and we don't need it again that's that's
that's stupid this game isn't just those games but why why does every why does every single one
have to be equally a pain in the ass why do they have to be equally narratively coherent because
they're stories because they're fucking art I don't want them to just I don't I don't I think
the trade-off is worth it I don't think okay I mean what you're talking about is a trade-off
and if you think it's worth it then fair but I don't I don't there are some who would argue that
Dark Souls has never been narratively coherent how do you love them apples okay let me tell you
right now why is it that when you kill an enemy you get their soul and when you die to them
why don't they get your soul in its game over forever why is that does anyone know who gives a
fuck that's a real question I'm just I'm helping your point god damn it but you're a I don't know
you're uh because you're a special guy you're not special though you're not special at all
everyone else who dies you get their soul instantly like when you kill the crestfallen warrior
you get his soul how come he doesn't get your soul when he kills you but how do you know he doesn't
get your soul that's what I mean start playing immediately never been narratively coherent
because if they're all in dead they should all be coming back like you but instead you get their
souls for some reason that's always been a concession for gameplay sake that doesn't make sense
in terms of the story so it's not like there's no well if that that thing seems so glaring to me
that I think that there's something I'm missing and there's a reason why I just don't understand
why that's happening you can't just say it's so perfect that if it doesn't make sense the problem
must be with me I'm not I'm not saying that it must be with me I'm saying I'm suspicious that it is
with me but I agree it makes me uh yeah okay it's not perfect it's not perfect I still don't
completely understand the complaint and I have no idea dude just just think about it when you
kill the crestfallen you're saying that yeah being able to play after you beat it you're talking about
npc god damn it there's only three of us you shouldn't be interrupting me I won't stand for
this go on go on I was just having the realization of what you were saying I wasn't cutting you off I
was just saying oh you mean npcs not enemies I thought you meant enemies yeah I'm gonna I mean
like when you just if you just attack the crestfallen warrior before he goes hollow
when he dies you get his souls and he doesn't come back why is that he isn't undead he should
be coming back right because he's gone full hollow well that's what I mean is that you just attack
him okay I've always been a precedent for these narrative concessions in for the gameplay
now wait I want to be super clear did you that that is not correct he was not fully hollow
he was just some dude hanging out well like when you attack him right there or forget him
they're like law trek or any other npc you meet like the blacksmith he's got a purpose when you
kill him he doesn't come back you know I just kind of always thought the implication was that everyone's
kind of at the end of their rope in the souls games because if you don't kill them they will
eventually die of their own accord and if you do kill them it's like you fucking ended it but
it's also possible that because time is convoluted in Lordran that that you're really just ending
I've always hated that fucking excuse that you can you can literally throw that at any problem in
the game and it'll just go away yeah well that's probably why they wrote it in there it's a really
convenient it probably is it was the only way to make sense of the idea that warriors are constantly
showing up in in your game and and disappearing you know okay but like Logan right Logan's on
a quest you meet Logan and then you kill him why doesn't he come back why is he's an undead
why did that happen he's got a purpose doesn't make sense doesn't make sense I guess you could
call it a narrative concession well let's think about the we've acknowledged that this is the worst
game ever okay go on let's talk about the real problem with this game is yeah um it's been out
for like a month now where the fuck are all my lore videos what are those guys doing they're
coming a little bit they're coming I want to understand what I've seen I want to understand it
I think I've got a pretty good idea of what's happened in the game uh there's this guy the
pontiff he found Aldrich Aldrich was an asshole who liked to eat people he he made him into a god
he built a church around that guy something something lords of cinder something something
guys in the castle princes they were gay or something for each other it caused all kinds of
problems for people they had to they had to get the fuck out of there and that caused the end of
the world so I gotta I gotta ask you guys about something that I think a lot of people have had
as like they're possibly biggest complaint with this game okay that uh that I don't think I consider
a complaint personally but I'm curious about your thoughts is the like the sheer amount of stuff
that's taken from the first game ah that's um okay I mean I can see why you might think that
that could be a problem and honestly sometimes you know maybe maybe a little bit thick maybe laid
on a little bit thick but overall I do not hate the idea that this is like it's like a grand return
you know it feels earned the things that were like the visit to anor Londo it's like it's not like
anyone who says like oh they just copy paste at anor Londo that is so fucking lazy like no there
was there was serious craft put into this like reimagining of anor Londo and it's great and like
like when you when you see the giant blacksmith and you bring and you see him dead and you grab
his soul and you bring it to Andre and Andre is like oh I'm so sad that guy that was my brother
that was the most feels moment in the whole fucking game dude that was intense feels it was great it was
great because like you played you know they've got to respect for each other man it's that yeah see
that's the kind of like there's there's love in this shit it's not it's not lazy at all so you
know I'm uh sometimes a little thick overall definitely in favor of it I think it works
wait what's going on I spaced out for like 20 god damn it Jesse how do you feel about the
how do you feel about the references to Dark Souls one in this game I love it needs to be more of
them there I love everything I love fan service I want it in my face all the time yeah so like you
know I was rewatching um Matthew Matosis's video on Dark Souls two from way back because uh I don't
think he hates that game enough he doesn't hate it as much as I do the pure the pure unadulterated
hatred that I have but uh you know he he complained a little bit about the references to Dark Souls
one in that game and I thought it was interesting because I think that the reason that the references
to Dark Souls one can be annoying in that game is because they feel like they're there just to
make references to Dark Souls one even though the story of Dark Souls two feels like it could have
been a totally unrelated yeah the issue is that they tell you it has been so long and everything
has been forgotten from an age oh by the way would you like to join the Sunbroke covenant
like it's like come on guys come on and the Lords of Cinder or the or the souls of the four bosses
of the first game or in the bosses of the second game or something like that yeah it doesn't it
just doesn't seem like there was a reason to do that that's right with Dark Souls three this game
like everything about the story is a sequel to Dark Souls one like it's everything is relevant
because the whole point of it is that it's like a bunch of twins like you're fighting like it's
basically just raising the stakes to the next level in the first game you had to fight all these
bosses just to get to one Lord of Cinder now you got to fight fucking five of them you know like
and and you're no longer just in undead so from Vadi's latest video he kind of implied that like
something that Miyazaki said implied that you the the ashen warriors that you are in this game
are like basically comprised of ashes of people who failed to link the fire in before like so
basically rather than being a chosen undead you're like the remnants of chosen undead who
failed well if you if you think about it literally everyone who is an undead who did not link the
flame which is most people would fall under that description so that is accurate right I just to me
I always had the impression that that you're you like everything in this game is more powerful
than Dark Souls one you're not just an undead you're this next level type of undead this like
right this one who who who can ember himself and become even more powerful like you said uh yeah
like you're dealing with you know many Lords of Cinder instead of one and I feel that the you know
your power is sort of reflective of that you're an elevated individual and I had this because
if you've seen my video about like the it is confusing though it is confusing that is true
it's definitely confusing and like when the game was first coming out I thought for sure the main
character was going to be someone who had linked the fire before like you also were a Lord of
Cinder because it would call back to the fact that you've probably beaten the first game you know
but um but you know I think that in each game the the idea of your character kind of matches the
mechanics and Bloodborne you're a hunter and therefore you're very aggressive and you're
rewarded for attacking enemies head on and you're you're meant to feel more powerful whereas in
Dark Souls one you're more clunky and slow because you're just another fuck off undead like everybody
else yeah and in this game you feel a little faster you feel a little stronger because you're
not just any undead you're in you're this new thing the unkindled you're like a different
type of guy and you're you're a little stronger and better and the kind of person who could take
down five fucking Lords of Cinder you know I guess I mean you fight fucking giant scaleless
seeth the god of dragons in the last and I mean you do okay and you're just some undead
I don't know I guess I see your point though yeah it's well I mean I'm not saying that you're
you're like super weak like the point is that you rise up above all the other undead but like the
mechanics of that game are that you have like when you start off you're pretty normal and weak
you don't really have like the speed and prowess that you have in Bloodborne where you can fucking
sidestep and juke and shit like you're you know you're doing fat heavy rolls and falling all over
yourself unless you're naked so and like in this game it's more like the armor is more like Bloodborne
people call it fashion souls where yep the you know the stats of the armor don't really matter all
that matter is that you wear it yeah that's right yeah um I don't know I think it's somewhere in that
middle middle ground I think that's communicated well in who you are and just the idea that you
have to go kill five people who are all on the level of Gwyn is really cool to me you know though
I mean just just to play devil's advocate wasn't Gwyn like kind of fucked up and like not at full
power because he had linked the fire so isn't he like weaker than he should have been I mean you
know I mean technically all these guys would be I guess because they've all linked the fire but
yeah I don't know I mean I don't know the guy the crestfallen warrior guy implies that you're not
fit to lick the boots of these people they are as gods they are the best guys yeah but I always
kind of thought that was because like I mean when you play through the games the way that you get
stronger is like they perform a ritual on you using souls that you collect and that like just feeds
into you and like your power level rises basically and you know that's that's what I always got out
of it that is like your job is to go out there collect souls use them to get strong and that's
like when you are at the end like if if somebody killed you and like stuck took your soul at the
end it would be worth like a billion souls because like you fucking right you know yeah that's an
interesting thought um video games I like them yeah they're pretty cool but yeah yeah I like all
the references to dark souls one I like how the references to dark souls two are kind of subtle
and hidden there's that giant tree outside which I like yeah there's there's that there's like the
the old lady who sells you stuff might be a reference to the old ladies from dark souls two
yeah but I love that I love that the way that that and I'll talk about this in a video if I finally
fucking do it but at the end of that hallway you see Andre and like immediately if you're if you've
played dark souls one you're like oh my fucking god it's Andre and it's literally him it's him yeah
and then the dark souls two ladies kind of tucked off to the side where you can't see her at first
and I I really think that's intentional I really think you feel that in the game you feel a little
bit of like the okay we can't like get rid of it completely but let's let's focus on the money
maker here you'll find like you'll find characters from dark souls two like you'll find some of their
armor sets and some of their bodies laying around you guys are so goddamn stupid like there's this
like like dark souls two was such a great shame that there's a conspiracy to erase it in dark
well I didn't say that they put your own ass on this you can think about it like this Jesse
me jacking yourselves off for your stupid illogical Jesse I never said anything like that I never
said for it just I never said they were trying to hide it I just said that it's not prominent
but it's all well of course the the nostalgia for the first game is going to be more prominent
it's the first fucking game and I can consider this though I'm being supposedly terrible and
unworthy dark souls two is look dark souls two is the worst game ever made and I'd rather kill
fucking idiot and I'd rather kill you I will shut my penis off and stab myself through my ear
into my brain and die just so I don't have to play dark souls you can you can think about it Jesse
as Miyazaki just didn't direct dark souls two so he's only interested in continuing his word
Ray is too good in the force why was Iron Man so mean when I feel like it's all the same
complaint it's all the same stupid shit Jesse you're you're you're like Aldrich eater of complaints
and you eat all the wines that people make and you use them to fuel you yeah dark souls two is a
terrible game you're an idiot liking it is the problem making the world worse Jesse you're
actually ruining all right all right without being an idiot why it's terrible I dare you
mind the controls suck the animation the level is every dark you're what the fuck I can't even
keep up with how much wrong you're spewing at me right now feel a little bit floaty uh they don't
feel as as as okay okay none of the animation is fucking garbage you're just saying stuff that's
fucking wrong you realize that you have to realize that you're just saying shit that isn't even true
how are you Jesse I can prove it onto you and I will once I start putting out those yeah once
I see you die a hundred times on the first level and blame the game for it like Aaron
fucking Hanson I'm sure you'll prove it to me how bad it is yeah I don't I don't hate it for the
fact that I die all the time I hate it because every mechanic is bad and the game they're the exact
fucking same as every other game in the series they're not they're nothing like that I don't
I don't really see where you're getting that uh there's like some some tuning differences that's
for sure I don't know whatever it's entirely different nothing is the same all of it does
nothing makes sense it's all retarded they changed everything for the worst and it's a broken shitty
game you're just saying these like grand like statements that don't have any specifics in them
you're just making you want me to spend this entire podcast talking about dark souls
dark souls are so much better than in dark souls one I enjoyed the controls are better let's see that
was fun dual wielding is how can you the fucking jumping is so much better jumping is such bullshit
in dark souls you jump like a you jump like one inch in dark souls by the way I want to drink
it possible this is people need to hear about this because in dark souls three is a big fucking
problem because the way you jump is you click the left stick and when you're ready improvement that
no it's not a problem it's an improvement it is a problem because when I'm using the left stick
to click I have to move it and I fucking move up my fucking movement every time I'm doing it fun fact
what fun fact I learned from victor in both the ps3 and pc versions you can change that very easily
in the menu I I know but I don't want to use a I tried it with a couple other buttons it wasn't
working out fucking I said it not on the first I'm baffled that you can prefer the circle jumping
over the clicking jump in I like the circle jumping is better it's true the first time it's
horrible it's impossible fucking roll by accident it's so easy to do it's no you just do it right
and you don't have a problem first time I tried when I started up dark souls three and I was trying
to get that first item that you have to jump for in the very tutorial level yeah I had to I took
10 tries on that I was gonna say it took me about because of the fucking stick jump and then as soon
as I changed it to circle jump I made it on the first try it was the easiest thing in the world
well like there you go all you got to do is be dashing and then hit the circle button yeah it's
totally fucked up and you fucking roll half the time it's never happened all right all right what
is blowing you guys's mind about just fucking clicking the thumbstick it's like that's my because
it changes the direction that you're moving the direction doesn't it's way easier and way more
accurate it's fucking every time I tried to make that jump because you have to break slightly to
the left to make that jump right and every single time when I clicked the stick my guy would change
direction a little and I just missed it's a very precise jump you're trying to make and even that
little bit of fucking up guys just suck at video games because you're totally wrong on this one
the clicking the thumbstick is a massive improvement that dark souls two made over dark souls one
and you don't want to admit it because you're just clinging to anything you can find to make dark
souls two a good game dark souls two is a fucking great game all right there's only there's look
there's a few changes from dark souls two that I think were great ideas that they did keep in dark
souls three uh fast climbing up ladders oh yeah that's a good one and fast falling down ladders
which is much better in this game because in dark souls two you could fucking hurt yourself from
fast falling which is law retarded um looking about if you fast fall down a ladder like two
two distance I don't fucking believe that at all I don't believe you I don't believe you I've never
seen that shit I've seen it before if you fall if you fast fall down a long enough ladder it
hurts you here we've got we've got jesse defending every little point and did you just make and
shit up to shit on no it's this this is fucking go look it up man like this is something I'm
complaining about day one that I don't fucking fall off ladders and shit like that's like a dark
souls bags of sand comment what does that mean it's fucking true though what does that fucking
hurt yourself by falling down ladders you're saying dumb shit fucking the okay fucking
lucatile is the best NPC ever lucatile is boring and I don't give a shit about her come on dude
she's come on I tried so hard to care about her like I cared about solar I tried and I got very
far but in the end it didn't fucking matter because she's boring and I don't she's she's
every NPC in dark enough about fucking dark souls two for no all right all right I will never have
enough of dark souls before I want to talk about NPCs cool sky of all time fucking oh yeah he was
cool vendric was cool I like vendric the fucking emerald herald is the hottest girl in all the games
no I mean she's boring as fuck dude I mean she's pretty hot okay what is her deal is she a dragon
or not what is what's even going on with that no one knows she's a fucking I know she's but she
she's fucking she's rey she's reyanami she is to the dragon all she does is stand there and say
exposition that's all she does oh yeah the other ones are so much fucking different right dude dude
the the fucking the the dog made in the fire the firekeeper in dark souls three will fucking laugh
when you make gestures at her she'll curtsy for you she'll bow with you she'll dance with you
she's my fucking wife she's also ugly ass albino with a so good you're ugly you have no fucking
sense I'm not I'm not gonna defend the firekeeper from three I'm not the biggest fan of her I just
thought she was fucking she kind of reminded me of the emerald herald she kind of just stands there
and like she's fucking real she's as good as the goddamn doll she's like your best friend in the
world yeah so nice oh you fucking be anyway okay I was herald is a fucking sexy ass Irish lass
fucking red hair a green ass god I want to just I want to marry him somehow I knew that this all
all this came down to just that she's a redhead you know she's just a rehash of the maiden black
she fucking she's the maiden black too they just tried to make her again only they put a green
cloak on her and I like the green cloak I actually I do I like the maiden green overall
but she's confused with the lore I don't even know what the fuck she is anyway enough about
Dark Souls 2 forget about I want to talk about Dark Souls 3 and the final boss because we were
talking about bosses before Dark Souls 3 sucks I disowned Dark Souls 3 I'm all about Dark Souls
2 now listen to me talk about Dark Souls 3 all right so the great that we were talking before
about references to Dark Souls 1 and all Dark Souls and that's why he's such a great boss I can wear
that fucking smelter demon armor and look like a member of Guar you can't do that shit and
demon sucks ass all right armor does not suck ass the armor is the most fucking armor in the
entire series I got my fucking you're literally showing off your fucking stomach because you
want to get fucked by all the boys in town all right let's move on I do I want to say no I do I
want King Vendor to come a fucking river in my abs that's what I want I want it all night
all right okay all right let's settle down because the what is he called the the Lord of
Cinder after it what's his name it's like the the the the soul of of cinder right that's it yes
okay the soul of cinder is the coolest final boss and the best final boss in any of the soul born
games in my humble opinion and that's cool for several reasons you should that's a fucking laugh
all right shut up jessie shut the fuck up you're not allowed to talk about dark souls 2 anymore
all right I don't even know how many of these opinions jessie has
is being just great nishonor there's no way he really thinks nishonor is better than the fucking
I'm getting me I'm getting fucking me yes all right it's just a prank bro
all right the soul of cinder is he's a two phase boss and the first phase
all right I'll just tell you what he is he's he is every person who's ever linked the fire before
as an amalgam so what that translates to and you see this in his moveset is he is every player
character up to this point of the game and he's Gwyn on top of it and when that when you get to
halfway through the fight and the Gwyn's the motif of Gwyn's theme comes in on top of the theme
that's already playing and he fucking lights a sword on fire and starts doing Gwyn moves
it's just it's the perfect it's the perfect fucking thing it's okay it's the it's the coolest thing
that I've ever seen or you've ever seen I know that for a fucking fact because you're
jessie bought a fucking figurine of this boss by the way you do where's your nishonor bobblehead
I don't fucking see one on your show they don't make one because the world is full of idiots like
you who don't appreciate Dark Souls 2 and all of its majesty and artistry that's why they don't
make one I'd buy a hundred nishondras I'd buy 50 000 nishondra toys if they made them but they
don't because they're all dummies and fuckboys all right anyway he's he's a great final boss he's
one of these like uh it's like fighting one of you sort of only he's like super player it's like
a rival fight sort of yeah that's right and those are always the best way to end uh a big fucking
because like they challenge the mechanics they they use the mechanics you've been fucking learning
to deal with he's the best it's awesome okay I definitely felt that like in terms of because
the first time I went to that boss fight like because I didn't quite comprehend what I was seeing
at first oh yeah so I went in there and I was just like oh it looks beautiful the red flowers and
shit oh it's the right well the the arena is awesome but my first thought was just kind of like who
the fuck is this guy right because like I would say up until this point Garmin has been the best
boss in the Soulsborne games because he's someone who you you knew who he was bloodborne sucks it's
a fucking three out of ten okay but Garmin Garmin was someone you saw through the whole game yeah
he's always in like a wheelchair he's just this old guy you know and then you get to the final battle
and he fucking gets up and he's the strongest fucking guy ever you know it's awesome and it's like
you know there's been hunter battles throughout the whole game but he's like the ultimate hardest
most fucking like destroys you and his arena is amazing like it's the coolest fucking arena ever
I definitely think it's the best arena yeah even then I yeah it's a it's a tough competition
because the imagery of the fucking house burning in the background is so fucking cool I mean it's
just the flowers man you can't beat and like they try to put the flowers for Soul Cinder and I mean
it's nice it's nice but yeah that's why when I first went into Soul Cinder I was like all right
this arena looks just like Garmin's arena yeah and I don't know who the fuck this guy is because
it's not an established character like it was in that but then once I did realize that oh my god
he's every player character he's everyone who's leaked the fire then I was like oh this fucking
red like Garmin is a guy that you've gotten to know over the course of Bloodborne but this guy
shut up Jesse I'm saying a fucking profound point broke the cycle with this magical crown which is
the best guy I was thinking about what I was gonna say and I'm gonna fucking say it shut up
but Dark Souls 2 guy was a chick wasn't it wasn't N'Shawn? yeah she's the queen whatever all right I
was going to say that Dark Souls 2 guy wasn't N'Shawn I'm talking about the player character
if you do the DLC you get the magic crowns you break the cycle you don't have to link the fire
I'm gonna fucking kill you Jesse shut the fuck up I'm trying to say something okay all right
because my big old dick my big old butt Garmin's someone that you got to know
listen buddy you got to know Jesse I'm gonna fucking kill you
Garmin's someone you get to know over the course of Bloodborne but the Soul of Cinder
it's the player that you've gotten to know over the course of the entire series since Demon Souls
and for that reason once you make that connection it is it is it is a transcendent moment it's the
best fucking thing it's the coolest and that's what I was trying to say I gotta say that great point
yeah it was a great point I love that there's references to Demon Souls in this as well
although I will say that the biggest one I'm kind of torn about because the biggest Demon
Souls reference is that you get the storm ruler to fight the giant oh man that was the coolest
thing okay but go I want to yeah go on well I'll say that there's a way to make that the coolest
fight in the game yeah there is yeah there is do the whole if you do the whole uh Zygward Zygward
is by far the best character in this game he is my bro I love him intensely god he's the coolest
guy ever but go on Jesse do you know about the ending of the Zygward uh uh run like a storyline
no you oh my god it's the best fucking thing ever he he will fight yorm the giant with you
because he has the other storm ruler because him and dude let me set the stage for this a little
bit all right because let me let me just back up a little bit because I beat the game for the first
time and when you go into the arena cool internet guys fighting yorm for me okay well that that's
cool but this is also a cool thing about it well I when I beat that when I fought yorm for the first
time on his on his throne he's got a uh what's it called the the storm king the fucking storm
ruler the storm ruler sword yeah and you pick it up and you figure out to use it and you fight him
with it and it makes him pretty easy which is a little unfortunate but it's still a really fun
fight uh but in the description of that item it says like yorm uh kept one of these weapons with him
and gave one to a trusted companion eons ago before he linked the flame or whatever and then
like as I'm playing through the second time and I'm getting every NPC storyline uh Zygmire uh like
you just right zygward I've always fucked that up zygward is just like you just do his
shit and he's talking about like a friend he made a promise to and then you know you go along
you help him with the stuff and then you finally see at the end when you get to yorm's fucking
cutscene if you've done everything with zygward and you walk it he walks in holding the storm ruler
so all these he made a promise to his brother to fucking murder his ass if he ever turned
traitor on everybody so he's here to fulfill like this sad promise with his best friend from a million
fucking years ago using this legendary sword and it's like the coolest thing that ever happened
and I don't know if you guys know what happens to him afterward but I'm pretty sure he immediately
like dies slash goes hollow afterward because he's fulfilled his purpose it's the saddest most and
because all along zygward was the best bro he gives you fucking booze he gives you booze and
he toasts with it and you just hang out and he fucking will take naps just for fun in the middle
of wherever oh my god I love zygward so much he's the coolest guy in the world I definitely think
that that's like if you do all that then that boss fight is fucking awesome it's insane but for me
it was just like I went in there and I tried to fight him like twice without noticing the thing on his
throat oh really he takes a million billion like he takes no damage yeah I'm a strength guy I have
like I'm barely chipping away at his health and at first I thought it's kind of cool because I could
like this is just a big epic protracted struggle that you're like fighting this guy forever and it's
such a you know such a huge hassle but then he also can kill you in like two hits so it's
like yeah well I'd have to be able to survive fucking 15 minutes of fighting to do this and
then I noticed the item and I pick it up and I'm like oh my fucking god it's the storm ruler right
coolest fucking boss fight when you have zygward walk in there and he fucking says like my old friend
I've come to fulfill my promise to you have at thee it was it was the best part of the whole game
by far by far without that it's a little disappointing when you go in with the storm
ruler and you just destroy it takes five flights to kill him five yeah and he will not hit you
because he staggers so hard after you use it that you could just like fucking you just click the button
a few times and he's dead yeah yeah it went from like the most epic protracted struggle in the game
to the easiest fuckboy ever I wish they had made him a little bit harder that's just an
issue of like tweaking if you take like some kind of defense measure against you when you've got
that sword like you he can't do shit to you it's like yeah embarrassing and it just sucks because
the storm ruler in because like my defense of all the the references to dark souls one is that I
think that they are equally cool in this game like if you played this game not knowing if you
played this game not knowing anything about dark souls one then like sigmar sigward coming up the
elevator would still be like whoa an npc was on that elevator you know that's awesome and and and
then he goes into battle with you like whoa he went into battle with me and like all and going to
anor lando would still be like whoa this thing was up here you know this epic looking castle but I
think with that particular one then the storm ruler and demon souls was like the the whole idea
of it was you were fighting this giant fucking manor ray in the sky and it was insanity and then
in this game it's like a piss easy boss fight and so I just thought that that was the one
reference that didn't live up to what the original was you know I wouldn't be that harsh but I do
think it could have been improved with some some hb tweaking or something but then if you have
zygmire with you then it's fucking cool zygmire zygmire yeah oh i love fucking zygmire so much
he's my favorite i love him the undead legion zygward and uh darkmoon captain yorshka are my
best but that's my wife my best friend and my my bro team that's me playing dark souls jesse do you
have some more uh stuff you love about this game you want to talk about since how about those oh no
he hates this game how about those dark areas and dark souls too you had to use the torch and
fucking you had to light your way those oh yeah oh yeah i love this is the one useful mechanic
jesse this is the one dark souls three podcast we're gonna do are you sure you want to spend the whole
time leaving about dark souls too like jesse do we know you love this game to talk about all the
things you love about this game and how cool it ain't no other pony troll it down like jesse jesse
jesse tell tell me about tell me about the purple phantoms jesse tell me about the purple
phantoms oh yeah the mad phantoms yeah those are pretty cool yeah why are they cool jesse
why are they cool i guess if you actually want to hear jesse talk about this game you'll just
have to go watch the blue glow um i'm just clearly not interested in discussing it here
he'll he'll come around no wait let's talk about the fucking all the cool bosses in dark souls three
they're so okay yeah fucking okay never mind uh who's who's a cool boss i like dancer is the
hottest babe of all time i want to look at her but i want to touch her butt i want to get up in that
butt the dancer has by far the best but in all of dark souls in all of the series without a doubt
it's interfacing the entire time it's amazing i can't even like i don't know who would i consider
the they're all fucking rad there's so many good bosses well the two brothers were super awesome
that was a great fight yeah uh the fucking the two gay boys yeah they're awesome i i i think that
fight is like like the coolest thing but that fight pissed me off so bad because it was the only
one i had like a real like a trouble on like i found that one pretty easy actually for whatever
reason the teleporting it's that that guy's literally tips fedora teleports behind you uh
fucking i don't know whatever oh nothing personal like once they fuse together and the kid would
fucking throw all the magic at you and then teleport away oh there's the best i loved it
bitch but i think aldrich like in terms of the attacks and like how fucking rad the arena is and
everything like aldrich you know i i actually want to that's actually the one boss that i found a
little bit disappointed because uh disappointed in i mean it's like okay they had a choice when
they were designing aldrich like okay we've got a giant like consuming evil monster thing what are
we are we gonna like go the route of like having you fight a giant sludge monster thing or are we
gonna have it like you know use the powers of the people you know because like it's puppeting
gwyndolin which is really cool and it's cool for gwyndolin even though like god did you read the
description of that soul because it's like he's been like being consumed for like thousands of
years still alive in eternal torment yeah it's fucking horrific but like it's a i found it a
little bit disappointing because like you don't really get to see and experience aldrich there
should have been a cutscene for that for that fight what's that yeah there was a there i think
there should have been a cutscene dude there really should have been a part two where you've
defeated like the puppet and then he like rises out from the deep this giant fucking mass that's
like aldrich anything but a a blob that puppeteers well i mean because like all the other cutscenes
you see him come out of that cutscenes but yeah when you just when you go to fight aldrich you
just go in there and there should have been like a look at me i ate this guy and now this guy is
my guy he's a wooden little wooden puppet boy i i don't really mind that there isn't an intro
i was just a little bit disappointed by aldrich's presentation because he is like he is like the
dude yeah yeah i agree with i agree with both of you because of the fact that when i fought that
battle i didn't actually realize it was the same guy like i did not realize you didn't know it was
gwendolyn or aldrich um either like i didn't process like it says aldrich but i didn't process
that it was the blob guy because like the whole game i was like when i'm gonna fight the blob guy
you know right um because there was so much hype like he's got the church built around him and the
pontiff like based a whole religion on him he's like the thing and then it's gwendolyn like okay
well i didn't have to catch that it was gwendolyn at first i just thought it was like i don't know i
didn't even realize that it was like a blob taken over someone i just thought it was a crazy snake
queen you know like i really just thought it was that so i was like oh i guess i'm fighting the queen
of anor lando yeah uh i mean the name is aldrich i mean all right that's on you for not getting
gwendolyn that everyone fucking knows that was gwendolyn that's on you but i didn't catch that at all
but then like once it was explained to me i understood the evil snake queen totally different
just like my favorite boss of all mitha the baneful queen from dark souls too when you oh i love
getting poisoned all the time that's you dumb idiot you're supposed to burn the windmill with
that there's no indication that you can burn that no wonder you hate it i knew it was just because
you suck at the game you don't know nothing literally no way to know that was a trick i learned
you into a trap to prove that you don't know nothing why does it catch on fire and you prove
that you don't know nothing i win i've been playing chess for years and you walked right into it who
who'd have thought that i would have had the worst fucking time imaginable on this podcast
when i was gonna talk about one of my favorite games you know who would have thought who'd have
but here we are i know i knew i ever since i announced like ever since i proposed this idea
i knew that me and jessie were gonna argue about dark souls too like i knew it was coming
because even though sometimes jessie will accept that dark souls two is a flawed game now it's not
one of those times well it's just if you say it too many times that eventually it flips that switch
where he goes into defensive mode about it because he still ultimately likes the game whereas i
hate it yeah i have i have a i have a whiny criticism threshold and if you fucking cross it
well that that happens but i don't i don't consider my dark souls two complaints i don't
consider whiny because for me this is a deep passionate hatred this is not like someone who
watches a movie and come home in the first day that after the movie's out they write a fucking
bitchy pedantic review about it no this has been festering and stewing in me it's it's a part of
my life in my being get it there's nothing fucking wrong with it there there's some things wrong
with it there's some things wrong but okay let's move on to more dark souls cancer that has eaten
away at me for years you know what's really cool you're like you're like garfield with the mailman
i don't understand why you fucking want torturing every day i don't get what you get out of it
hey you know what's cool the deacons of the deep boss fight i like that boss fight i enjoyed it i
thought i i love the concept of that boss i think it's way too easy it's a little easy um because
the thing is that the the idea of it is that you only hurt the boss if you kill one of them who has
the the red shit well and you can just hit him but yeah well no it just hitting him doesn't hurt
the the boss meter it's only when you kill it that it that it that it deals damage that's so which is
which is a great idea because that would mean that if you can't kill them fast enough because
they'll transfer before you finish hurting them i have never had that problem i think every single
time i hit one of them that's the issue killed him like yeah like because i you know when i played
the first time you know or every time i've played strength and like i would kill them in two hits
but there was like one time that i hit one and then i missed what the second hit and then i didn't
get my like my endurance was out and then he transferred guys and so now his health bar was
released like you know it didn't do any damage to the boss itself so i had to go fight the next guy
so if they had made it so each one had more health so that it was like a real like you really
had to time your attacks to make sure you killed them or else you didn't do any damage i think that
would have made it a really challenging fun if you were like a mage trying to do long range
shit that would be a fucking nightmare to like hit the right one i think it was just a balancing
issue like yeah i think it was a matter of like they couldn't find a way to make it work for everyone
so they just kind of made it easy you know and i think that that that took some of the
but some of the quality from it thematically the boss fight is awesome it's the coolest it's
just it's just all these fucking eldritch guys working in the church they're just under the
pontiff they're just all like they're just there they're like oh here's the dude guess we better
deal with this now i don't know if that like like the pope guy there is like a special one
i guess he is but i will say though that regardless of that boss cathedral of the deep was that and
iris are the two coolest fucking levels ever like that was the moment because when i was playing
this game it was like at first the first couple levels i was just kind of like yeah all right this
is you know it's souls it's cool i'm killing guys this is fun like i like how in the first level
on the on the wall like you can just avoid a lot of the big enemies like the really tough ones you
can kind of solid snake around them or you can fight them if you want like the challenge you know
but like you know you get to the undead settlement and i i think that's probably like
my least favorite area the first time but now that i'm starting to like see all the lore that's there
i'm really interested in it like i want to know why they all are all like tree people because like
you gradually realize like everyone has like tree parts on them and stuff something to do with the
world just going to shit turn people into trees who knows then there's the giant tree boss who like
if you kill him then you can't join the mound makers so yeah it's clearly like i think everyone in
that town is part of this like tree covenant or something but uh yeah i don't know it's really
interesting but i i don't know much about it but you know you these lore videos guys yeah i need
him to but you were saying uh sorry i was just going to say that uh before you said that like
irithyll uh and and cathedral of the deep were like the moments you really liked it i think that
um that that moment where i forget when you beat the pontiff no not the pontiff whatever when you
beat someone and you walk out on that ledge and you see irithyll for the first time yeah that's
the equivalent of like the anor londo reveal from uh from dark souls one it's the and if you
want an example of seeing this go watch the blue glow i forget which episode it is but see see
endless jess marvel at the majesty of dark souls three after the best part about that is he was so
pissed off at the boss and he's literally going this is the worst fucking game ever then he comes
out and sees that he goes like like i'm crying that old bait switch right but um yeah for me it
was like you know i got to the crucifixion but it's harder to be sean my favorite song of all time
when i got to the crucifixion woods that was when i was first like all right i'm into it because
like the way that the water looks there and everything is just fucking beautiful i love the
swamp i love the entire swamp and then like because i i did the swamp first i beat the abyss
watchers i beat the catacombs and then i got to i saw irithyll and i was like that looks fucking
incredible but i couldn't get in because i didn't have the doll yeah so i go back to the cathedral
of the deep like i find it and i'm like what the fuck this the fucking graveyard with all the
skeleton people who just keep responding forever yeah and you're just like oh man this is fucking
cool it's like the spooky scary skeletons place and like i i love this is like this is the thing
that makes this game compete with bloodborne for being my favorite of the series because like
on the one hand dude i'm really into gothic horror and like and or gothic architecture
and stuff and like and lovecraftian stuff like those are my that's like my aesthetic man like
bloodborne feels like it was made for me but my biggest problem with that game is that almost
all of it's at night and so every level just feels like the same dark oppressive atmosphere
and it doesn't like it takes so long before you get to a level that like really feels different
and really pops out that is true that is true you know like like like i would say nightmare
frontier because that's like the first level that's like totally daylight and looks really
different and you're like oh all right and then in this game almost all of it's during the daytime
like the only really dark areas are like the catacombs and uh and the place the the jail and
the place below the jail you know where you fight your the the prison the fucking yeah the dungeon
thing whatever yeah yeah like even irithel even though it's set at night it's so beautiful and
like shining out in out of the darkness it's it's amazing it's it's a marvel it's a marvel of level
yeah i don't actually think it's like the most brilliantly designed level in in a like a flow
progression the level design it looks amazing i think the level design is obviously based on
andorlondo where it's supposed to be this huge skill check all like it's all big enemies now
they're all a lot harder you're fighting them in like smaller like it's just like you you fight a
bunch of groups of big enemies and like but they're even cooler because like in andorlondo it's
just like giant knight statues that you had to fight a lot of and this is like these these
fucking crazy dancer people you get the sense that there's like a culture to irithel yeah you're
getting like because all the all the the fucking boreal guys with their icy swords and their fucking
spin moves all the time it's it's really there's a real when you meet one of those guys you know
it's one of these dudes it's great yeah i really feel like there's a culture here that i i'm not
really sure i've seen in another like civilization uh before you know for this and the way that when
you're walking through town every there's like the ghosts like people who i don't even know what the
fuck those are but i love them they're the coolest thing ever uh everything about irithel makes my
dick rock hard and then when you go down into like the when you just go under it like you go down
into the the sewer like area and you're just in this huge open lake and it's like because the whole
level up to that point is fairly linear it's like guiding you through a bunch of like tough and
counters but then you go down and you're like exploring this whole other side of these disgusting
fucking hideous mosquito monsters down there jesus christ and then you emerge back into the thing
and who's who's sitting there with some hot estus stew waiting for you seagward seagward is my
fucking nigga jesus christ is the coolest guy ever did you did you know that every time in that
game that you find a pot of estus stew or whatever z word made it i did not know you can thank him for
that shit yep god he's the coolest guy in the world i love him by the way another awesome thing
i love about this game that i've appreciating more on like my uh as i play it again is the way that
the whole world like the way that you play through the game mo most of the time like there's this even
one area called the path of sacrifice like the whole world is structured in sort of a funnel
where people and you see this in like the the undead settlement like the whole world is sort of
built in this operation of like funneling food and funneling like good like stuff for
eldritch to consume all the way back to anor landa when i realized that nice notice like the guys in
cages like that's what they're doing like the the missionaries they're recruiting people like
those big fat bitches what they're doing is they're out recruiting people to come be uh eldritch
worshipers it's all fucking awesome it's the coolest thing ever man i love it i'm taking now
that i've played like all these games i'm taking much more notice of the lore like of the things
i'm doing as i'm playing through the games which up to this point i hadn't really invested in blood
warren i started to do that dark souls 3 with yeah the constant like hope of like looking out for
like lore stuff like totally i hope i see something cool and i can connect the dots but i'm too dumb
for that i need some more fucking lore videos to do it for me i'm a busy man i agree that like i
thought i was keeping up with it more so than the other like i definitely understood more than
i've understood before but then like once people started making lore videos and i was like well
i didn't get any of that so i want to know everything there is to know about like why is the undead
legion fighting itself something went wrong somewhere is it eldritch i want to know i want to
know real bad i need people to tell me i yeah i i got to say here's some some pedantic complaints
i have okay all right one uh why do npcs teleport to the the place after you like save them
like because there's that moment when you homeward bone i'm gonna say well there's that moment when
you save gray rat from a cell yeah and you like talk to him and then he's like i'm gonna join your
team and then he just like poosh away and i'm like well if he could do that why was he sitting in a
cell okay i'm i'm gonna tell you right now what it is there because there seem to be some implication
that like there's there's some magic going on when you take people into your service as an
unkindled there's something magical going on with that i'm just i'm completely gonna go crazy here
because it sounds like there's some weird connection between you and the uh the fire
fuck firekeeper lady or whatever i'm gonna say there's magic going on there because like uh
the that dude who you meet on the bridge who's like oh i've been looking for someone to serve
i've been looking for like a master a lord to send or whatever it's it's amazing to be in your
presence i'm just gonna say magic magic's involved you're a lord ascended i'm willing to accept
literally any explanation yeah it's just that like in demon souls people came back to the nexus but
it was always like you just kind of left it in all the games they just left the characters behind
you know and then eventually they made it there and then this game they like actively right in
front of your face teleport and i'm like what's the deal with that you know that's true yeah i've
been wondering about that too and then uh but then my other one i this one's a little less pedantic
i think it was just like an issue with the pacing of the game for me is that when you assuming that
you haven't killed the dancer early in the game then like when you kill the last of the guys you
need to kill it just teleports you into oh my god i cannot tell you how annoying that was and i'll
tell you exactly why because uh you you usually end up killing um the the yorm the giant as the
last one that's just how the game usually flows and if you've done uh z words storyline then like
if you he says a couple words to you and then you get teleported away but i wanted to see what he
fucking does after that fight because i've heard that like he does like he he like dies and i want
to know if that's true yeah but i don't know and so like i have to play through the whole game again
and go out of my way to not kill him last because of that issue like i i get it you get summoned by
the bitch but it's still annoying and also you have to constantly recollect your souls from that
previous boss like you know if you die to the dancer you have to make it back there and get
those souls back and if you do die to the dancer on your first try you go back to the bonfire of the
boss you killed you don't go back to the you know like you have to teleport you you'll you'll die to
the dancer then you'll end up back in yorm the giant's fucking chamber and then you got to teleport
to the fucking king play you know the kingdom yeah so that you can go fight the dancer again
i'll be honest i feel like this is one of those things they did to like really force you to get
it to like know what to do now like they didn't like they could have just put a message annoying
i do i do too because the thing is like i was it was so jarring because i would never have thought
that i was at the end of the path through the game you know like you kill yorm and there's like
you've if you if if he is the last one you kill then you've you've explored the whole game
and i never had that sense because i'm thinking well there's still one more guy left you know
so yeah where am i gonna go to fight that guy and i'm thinking that i'm gonna continue on the path
that i've been going on and then it's just like no you're back in the castle uh and then like it
would be one thing if it teleported you there and there was a bonfire immediately and you really
felt like okay i'm in the right place but instead it teleports you into a fight that if you lose
you end up back in yorm's chamber and it's so weird and jarring to like have that epic moment
of whoa i have to fight two bosses in a row and then like oh now i have to fucking teleport all
the way up to the the other guys bonfire because it just deposited me back in a nonsensical location
i i hear you on on all that stuff that's true i don't i don't quite agree uh that i that i dislike
that you're sort of uh sent back to uh to the castle to continue because it's very much like
boletaria which is really the last thing you do and you went back there in that right i wish that
it gave you the the agency to do that yourself i that'd be it was because in in demon souls it
told you how many levels there were in each place so like you you already knew that you were going
to go back to boletaria eventually after you'd beaten everything else but like in this game when i
beat yorm i didn't realize he was the last guy like because again i hadn't realized that eldritch
was the blob thing and i think i was just doing the math wrong because like there's one guy because
like ludlith is there and there's four others and am i one no okay and there's the prince is that two
guys yeah it's right and and i'm thinking the i'm thinking that and the undead legion is one
all right i was expecting all of them right there i was expecting the prince to be the final boss
you know yeah like he's the one who's been built up the whole game so like i just kind of had this
weird jarring feeling of when i was teleported back and i didn't like because i didn't know
that it was just after you kill whoever's the last guy yeah i thought it was just i killed yorm
and it teleported me back so when jessie was trying to jessie was trying to ask me how to get to uh
the the last like where to go because he killed yorm before eldritch because he didn't know how
to get to eldritch right so you know he's like where do i go now and i'm like oh did you fight
the dancer and he's like what and like he said i can't even ask where to go without getting spoiled
you know yeah that's the that's the yeah i'm with you on all that stuff for sure that that really
annoyed me let's talk about uh piece of shit which is those fucking guys in the in the dragon
place is the coolest fucking place ever it's yeah it's definitely red those fucking guys with the
chain axes that go through walls hundreds of miles away what who the hell coded that part
i want to find him and i want to kill his family that's like the greatest that is the greatest
mar on an otherwise great game it's a fucking blight on the entire series those fucking found
that place a little uh a little trying with my patience due to those guys that's that's oh i hate
those fucking guys and there's like 50 of them in one spot yeah yeah i you know what i know what
spot you're you're talking about because there's that one part where you try to go out to that
roost on the end yeah of the place and there's like fucking 15 dudes there and yeah i could not
fight my way through that like because there's no way to not aggro a bunch of them and their
chains like if you go into that little building they'll just hit you from everywhere so like the
only way i could get there is just to fucking run past them haul ass as best i could get that item and
run back you know not only are they so long have such long range but that they go through walls
like everybody prides the dark souls series i'm like it's hard but it always feels fair
the enemies can't do anything that you can't do you know but i can't fucking go through a wall
so well yeah i mean that it's it's a it's a moment of weakness in the story i would agree
the whole game is bad it's because of that i will say that i i i love that eventually i found harder
rooms because like one of the things i really loved in in all the other games is that there would be
these these certain rooms that are like so amazingly hard but they're completely out of the way so
like there's no reason really like uh in in dark souls one in the demon ruins when you like fall
down that that area and there's like all the toxic and all the fucking things that eat you and
shit and that's where like zeigmeyer's story ends like oh yeah right right yeah like that room
is insanely hard there's no reason to go over there if you know about it unless you wanted
whatever items were down there or you just wanted that challenge you know and i i think every game
has moments like that like in the bloodborne dlc when you fucking run into that cave where there's
the guy with the machine gun oh yeah like as a fucking nightmare there's like a fucking blood
starf beast down there like a million other guys and it's like what the fuck like there's just
certain rooms in each game there's a beast in there what the i must have spent yeah two hours
in trying to defeat that cave that one cave that yeah and i love that there's those those little
offshoot moments in each game yeah when i first played through dark souls 3 i didn't find any of
those but then like once i made it to the nameless king place and like that area with all those guys
is definitely one of them i'd say that one's a little too much of a pain in the ass because i
just couldn't even figure out how to go about it but there's a there's one room where there's
like an illusory wall where you can fight two of like the crocodile monster from the bridge
like or something like that two two really big down in the uh yeah i know what you're talking
about yeah to get it to get a certain item or weapon or whatever there's there's also yeah and
then the one where you're like before you're in the giant where uh there's three of the hand monsters
the fucking oh my god those fucking guys they're the worst they're like these horrific hand hippos
oh my god no those things are the most disgusting fucked up monsters in any game and they flail
around like they're fucking high on i don't know whatever yeah they're the worst fucked up they're
the most annoying enemies in the game aside from the axe through wall there's only there's only four
of them and like one you fight by itself and then there's three in that room down there three in the
one room yeah yeah finding out about though that though is like really cool because i was like okay
this game still has those optional big challenges i just i love that area that area forced me to
figure out that the fastest way to get through slow roll like slow roll like mud and stuff is
you equip a dagger you two hand it and you do the uh focus which is that dash and that it like
forces you to come up with new strats and do shit it's great i love it i hate all the fucking mud
pits they shouldn't be in the game they're just a completely unnecessary arbitrary fucking time
waster oh it pisses me off so much i hate going in the mud it makes you just do do my shit equip
a dagger two hand it use the focus move you'll just you'll just sound like too much work it's
it's mad just thinking i don't know i it's funny because i i really loved the swamp area but like
then when a like vadi kept putting out videos and he kept being like oh if you had to go through
that fucking swamp and i'm like eh i i didn't i wasn't that bothered by it like the only parts
you really have to go through the mud is if you want to get like a certain item the party yeah the
area right before you gotta get the items how could you not get the items i gotta get them well i did
get them all but like i don't know i never had a huge problem with it i mean you know that one
spot where there's three of those giant like tree druid the other fuckers around a bunch of items
that was like that was challenging but i did get through it right before the swamp where you're
with the crabs and it's sort of it looks like it's like directly out of the fellowship of the
ring at the end where Boramir dies it's like that it's literally that place that place is awesome
but then it goes into the fucking swamp and you gotta walk through that slow ass muddy water you
gotta fight those fucking werewolves who jump on your fucking head from 50 feet away you can't
fucking die i hate those motherfuckers you gotta oh man those guys yeah it's like 50 000 basilists
all coming around you at once gang rape and you turn into a stone there's those fucking tree guys
there's so tall i want to take that part out of the game and i want to package you help and i want
to put poop in that package and send that package back to me azaki and say this is my poop on your
level which is also i think uh i think i possibly like the swamp because it was purple and i just
think purple areas are the coolest purple um and i i do like how like there's a lot of there's a
ton of big enemies in this game that you have no reason to fight like the crabs unless you want
their rings like there's just a ton of big enemies who just drop some really cool ring and like you
know you could completely for like you don't have to fight a single crab in this game but if you
almost all of them will drop something special they get agroed so you know you get you get into
some yeah but you can easily escape like they're usually out of the way i have to fight them because
i hate them yeah hey crabs are cool dog i'm a cancer i don't respect like crabs to live
dude did you guys know have you guys seen this there was uh some shit on on v of uh you know those
giant skeleton balls in like the dungeon that roll up and down those staircases uh the the lower one
when it when you kill like the the hat guy that like if you kill a skeleton with a hat like they
no longer survive hitting against walls for some reason did you say just now that crabs are a
cancer that was a funny joke that's that's hilarious okay so when you do that nate said that he was
a i'm i'm against well then it was my joke then i made a point all right good good job anyway the
bottom ball when you do that when it smashes open uh there's a crab in there there's just a crab in
that ball there's a crab in that yeah and like people were trying to undead bone shard in there
but i did not know there's there's an undead bone shard in like the first ball but in the second
ball there's just a live crab just hanging out and uh there were there were some people uh on on v
doing threads about trying to guide that that uh crab back to like his his people in that like a fire
dungeon you know you know like all the crabs in that like fireplace but for so like he gets stuck
on the um on the on the entrance to the undead legion which leads out to like the swamp where the
other crabs are there's a threshold that he will not cross so tragically little crabby man was never
able to get home he couldn't do it it was they couldn't bring him down to the demon uh ruins
they tried they tried that too yeah let's talk about all those super cool like sad last in the
trilogy moments where like you'd find like the dead spider babe from the first game or you find
like the dead armor guy from the in uh in in lando the fucking dead giant giant oh man that was so
cool dude fucking because of you jesse because of the blue glow when me and victor went back to
andro lando in our playthrough like the first thing i did was go i'm coming home yes i'm coming home
and like uh this the moment when you see the the giant and then you just made your character fall to
his knees and i was like oh man that was beautiful taking that like we said this already but taking
the ashes to andre of the giant was like the most cry porn moment ever like i was devastated that
that was that was a that was a like an irreplaceable gaming moment how often how often do characters
like not only acknowledge one another but in a positive way in these games you know and that
yeah dude that is a great argument against spoilers can you fucking imagine if somebody
had spoiled that fucking part for me i would have lost all faith in humanity i would have died
an unhappy so i would have gone hollow if someone had spoiled that i'm just reliving that moment
andre it's beautiful man it is beautiful and i'll say this i think that's um like another thing
that would egg this game above possibly above bloodborne for me is the fact that bloodborne's
npcs were totally weak and this game's npcs were fucking awesome i liked that one girl the uh the
hunter killer girl in the crows outfit yeah i mean even she you know she's not that great
she's cool it's just yeah like the because most of the npcs like there's two types there's either
the hunters that you find around which are more like the adventurers from the other games yeah
and those are those are kind of cool but then most of them are just like civilians who have
nothing to do with what you're doing they're not like you they're just like people who are there
and the only way you ever really interact with them is if you go back to odin chapel which
you don't really do because it's you're you're constantly teleporting back to your fucking
the dream you know why would you go back to odin chapel i went to a lot just to check in with those
folks but that's just the way i most of them don't really do anything that interesting except for
like uh most of them are the whore and the priest and their interaction yeah yeah um but like the
old guy and the old lady don't really do anything interesting you know so it's kind of like it just
felt like it was just more people going crazy and like everyone else was already going crazy
like i love the part with the little girl and how uh she'll go looking for her parents and she's
fucking gets eaten by a pig monster and it's horrific but i think uh i think what's cool
about this game is that like in dark souls one everyone kind of had a mission but like all of
them failed like you know yeah unless unless you're able to say that logan succeeded too hardcore
right but like most of them actually you know who the coolest npc is in bloodborne is the guy with
the fucking wheel legarious because he oh my god you are so right dude that is part of the best
scene in that game of euphoria as he has smashed her to fucking pieces i was like yeah dude yeah
he's the best character definitely that's by far the coolest npc quest line in that game but in this
game i remember walking into that room it was fucking freaky because he puts yeah that's where
that pyramid head fucking helmet out of nowhere he didn't wear that up till now i think that was
on purpose holy shit that was spooky but okay go on but yeah in this game there's like a ton of
characters who all have like very clear missions and some of them succeed like seaguard if you
finish his quest line yeah he like does what he set out to do it's the best because that was the
whole tragedy of seagmeyer was that he just like wanted to adventure but he was always getting
you know stuck because he wasn't very good and then you know he goes crazy because he's so worthless
when you see seagland over his dead body oh my god right and then in this game you've got
fucking seagward and like not only does he fight like an early boss with you but then he'll fight
a fucking major boss with you and then like finish his quest and he's like i've done what
i set out to do that you fucking you know and then and there's a from what i understand the lady and
i have no idea how to do her like quest line but the lady in white who meets you in uh oh dude i
can tell you about her quest line because it's fucking awesome doesn't she fight the final boss
with you if you like wait are you talking about the lady in white or the lady in black the lady in
white doesn't fight the final boss dude let me tell you what happens with her one of her whole
deal uh yeah the lady in black does i'll tell you about that but the lady in white her whole deal
is i forget her name but she um is she was attempting to become a firekeeper which i guess
is a thing that you can do uh but she wasn't good enough or something but wait are you talking about
the the the blind one yeah the blind one i thought you meant i'm not talking about her
i'm talking about the lady who just shows up in the shrine and like she's a member of like
urea yeah wait no not urea she's in black that that's like a lady to kill me because i
accidentally joined the wrong dude okay her name is serious her name is serious yeah okay
her deal is just that uh she she's just a dark moon covenant dude uh trying to kill a certain dude
and as you go along you'll find out that it's her grandfather who is that you know you know
the guy who uh lets you into the mound makers covenants that creepy guy that's him and he's
that's her granddad and uh like eventually if you you get summoned by her a bunch of times to
like kill random dudes and the last one is that guy and when you kill him she's like all right
i i i fulfilled my promise to you granddad so like there's some implications that he like much earlier
in the game yeah but you know you want to give her some credit i don't know he invades you in in uh
in there he invades you as a mad face well invading isn't like killing the real one you know
like in this you like get summoned into his world or something and kill him there so uh
and then like she and then after that she shows back up in fire link and is like oh man thank you
dude uh i want to be your knight and she just swears loyal to you to you and then you can summon her
for shit so does yuria fight the final boss with you yuria does fight the final boss with you if you
do the like marriage quest line fully i don't know if you guys have done that but that's also
fucking awesome i could i could tell you about it but i have not done it but i mean i don't care
okay all right so i don't know if jesse uh wants to know jesse have you done that part yet i haven't
beaten it i i mean babadook spook killed anri and it was very sad because she's the best girl ever
you killed her in the ceremony yeah he stabbed her in the face oh yeah okay the ceremony is like
the most important part of the whole thing after that you it's basically you just are getting the
ending like you fulfilled the criteria you just got to get to the end there but okay since you
already know i'll just tell the people so like there's this girl uh well when you meet um yol yol
this guy who will give you those five free levels he gives you this like new like super dark sign
or whatever that's like a pit of blackness that's like in addition to the normal dark sign on an
undead that never goes away and yeah the babadook spooks got that shit and so like you don't have
like enough of them so uh andri she has you do like this wedding ceremony so she like kidnaps andri
does this creepy ritual where you stab her in the face and you like get three additional of these
like dark emblems from them and then uh at the end you just have the ability to steal the fire from
the uh from the fucking i can't remember what i was fucking saying you steal yeah you take the fire
from the kill the first flame and you get like this ending where you've like stolen the power
of the first flame or something i don't know some it's it's good you should go do it everybody
your mind is falling apart trying to talk to me it's completely whatever just go play the game
it's fun all right go do all the quest lines my full name is yule but hey since we're talking
about this anyway and i was gonna say the fact that that blind lady was a failed uh fire keeper
and if you buy all the spells from her if you like fulfill her purpose she then like i don't know how
but she somehow like becomes a full-fledged fire keeper and can perform level ups on you
like a fire keeper wait what dude yeah that's right that she becomes oh my god it's the coolest
thing that ever happened she fulfills her fucking dream it's the greatest but only only if you buy
all the good spells and don't give her any of the dark tomes and buy any of the dark spells you
can't do that shit or she has like a tragic evil ending yeah she just becomes a fire keeper it's so
cool it's like i never knew that that's amazing it's it's so right she's like in one of the dark
towers hanging out with all the like corpses dude she she she's in the tower with all the dead
uh fire keepers behind like the locked door and uh like she took down her hood and she she's all
pretty now that she took off her stupid ass nun hood and she's just she can fucking level you
up and she's just like i am so happy that i can fucking do this shit now oh man it's so endearing
i love i i hate it fucking but until that game is on fleek in this no fucking doubt dude like
you got yoria who's like lining you up with hot bitches to fuck you got this bitch who like
loves you more than anything you got the fire keeper of course oh man it's it's over and you got the
dark one of one of the cutest girl in the game the emerald herald who comes out at the end of the
game to say hey funnily enough i was about to say i'll never love one as much as the doll but
this game has a lot more the doll i got yeah i gotta say the uh the doll definitely uh for you
you know the doll's fucking accent makes my dick rock hard like introducing the idea of reacting
to your emotes with the doll has made her just transcended waifu you know there's never going
to be a waifu like her probably for me it's just the the fucking accent dude and and the hair and
just the fact that she's a doll and she has dark circles under her eyes are you cold she's my
fetish good hunter are you cold i think she might be related to the fact that she and the fact that
yeah probably you wake you become a squid and then she's like your mom she's like she doesn't
mom she's so really she's like she's gonna be there for you dude even in fucking squid form
what a what a great woman what a good woman and that's what and that's why bloodborne is the
prequel to octodad you're a good girl you would be did you i gotta tell you i've been singing that
song from the sea hey speaking of squid men going back to the sea all that shit with aldrich
had like they had a premonition that like the sea is going to be like the new age after the age of
fire feels very bloodborne inspired cool stuff yeah there's there's i i thought it was interesting
that like this game because it has references to demon souls but then like in terms of bloodborne
it's like almost exclusively mechanic mechanical references like there's no overt
other than the fact that aldrich's name is basic like if you read it aldrich's name in japanese
it's it's spelled exactly like eldritch oh really ha may as well yeah he's pretty clearly a like
in eldritch or he's a mode but i mean the arena the arena of the soul of cinder i feel like it's
definitely an homage of sorts to gherman's arena or possibly they're just like okay that worked
let's just do that again you know i think it could easily just be that yeah i would say i don't i
don't think that having an eldritch thing is like a reference to bloodborne though because all the
games were lovecraftian from the beginning you fought fucking cthulhu's in the first game you
sure did well they're i mean they're mind flayers which are a dnd thing but i mean yeah same shit
well i mean it's just very like call of cthulhu esk like the way i always thought it was like
somewhere between dnd and call of cthulhu was like the idea of of uh of demon souls have i
mentioned how dope latria is in demon souls just going up up up getting carried like you fight the
those fucking the clones that aren't real and then you get to the old monk and he's this creepy-ass
dude with the robe and it just becomes some dude's hat oh my god it was fucking insane demon
souls is one of the coolest games ever it is no doubt demon souls demon souls i like demon souls
that's how it goes right but yeah i think overall though like when i played through dark souls 3 it
was like that there was that first initial moment of like all right well that was kind of short
and a little easy and i don't know if it was as memorable as like you know where demon souls every
level was so distinct and different and dark souls felt so new and fresh and like even when you play
it today you can appreciate how new it felt at the time and how how big and open that world felt
and and dark souls 3 definitely feels less open it definitely feels less unique and new but yeah
it's again i think the replayability of it is so much stronger than any of the other games that like
this is the one i'll keep playing forever you know this is the one that i mean i never in none of
the other games that i pick it up like immediately and start playing again and then this one i was
just like i don't want to leave i don't want to be done it's so satisfying to play like
it's just so much fun and everything's cool and every location is there's there's no bad part
like i would say in in dark souls like when you're replaying it and you get past and or lando and
then you have to do like the fucking god damn uh what's it called the fireplace it's just like uh
do i have to do it again all right everybody everybody all right maybe you guys can explain
this to me i don't think you can everybody says that the game gets like drops off after an or lando
i don't fucking buy that shit i love every part of that game i love the fireplace
i mean i don't love the boss at the end it's not like the best boss ever but it's fun i enjoyed it
all like every single part the problem with the part was awesome the problem with the whole uh
with that what the fuck is it called what is the up to the demon ruins what's it called i can't
easelith lost easelith lost islet yeah um like the problem with that area is that if you played
that game when it first came out yeah then all those uh butts had like a dragon butts had like a
giant aggro range and it was like the hardest level in the whole game because you were just
constantly fighting these giant butts and it was like it was like yeah but that's the thing the way
that they compensated for that was to give them no aggro range and make it just a fucking place you
run through you know like it to me it just seems like it was really like like the time constraints
killed it or something like they had an idea they built this level and then they didn't actually
think up good enemy placements so they just threw a bunch of fucking dinosaur i don't know it's just
the way that people say like oh the game just fucking tanks after an or lando i don't buy it i
don't like by any stretch i just i think lost islet is a weaker level i think that maybe that
that what's is the boss there is a pain in the ass um i love duke's archives i think that place
yeah fucking really and design wise is amazing um the the tomb of the giants i'm not a big fan of
but i have i know people who really like it oh i like the two of the giants and then there's the
new lando which i just two of the giants is worth it just for when you finally get that lantern it's
like oh my god thank you jesus it feels great it's punishment i had it before going in there
i thought how'd you get it before i mean it's i don't know i had i had you can get like light
spells and shit in other ways but like the game like gives you a definitely i had a land skull
lantern went to there i don't know whatever maybe you did i don't fucking know um i don't know could
because i did that i think i did it last i think that was the last place i went to so i might have
got one but i mean well i don't know like the lantern that the game i mean i just think that
there's there's definitely in that game there's a few moments that i'm like when i have to go back
there i'm like oh god i have to do this level you know or i would think people would think that
about like sen's fortress or something because it's such a ball buster yeah but that's like mandatory
you know sen's fortress is a lot easier once you know what to do though like if you don't fall for
the traps you can haul ass through that place but like i think uh i think even uh bloodborne like
none of the levels were like a pain in the ass in that game but there was places that were like
that just weren't that memorable that are like i don't really feel like like if i was playing
through the game again i just want to rush through that area nothing felt like that in this game to me
like every single place was so distinct maybe the catacombs but then once i figured out that
you could skip like half the catacombs just by dropping down that first ledge when you walk in
then it's not even that big of a pain you know i don't know what you're talking about but i believe
you yeah well because you don't have to run like when the roly ball is there oh that yeah okay i
know what you're talking about i know the exact right when you walk into the catacombs you could
just drop down and skip that whole other part dude because those fucking skelemangs with their
fucking tip fedora shuriken throwing teleporting around geez christ those are fucking annoying
but yeah once i like once i knew that and i went through it like the easier way i was like okay this
place isn't like that much of a pain and demon ruins as well like the first time i went to demon
ruins it felt like a fucking labyrinth and i was like where the hell am i i love the demon ruins i
thought that was so much fun because like i man that was actually one of my favorite moments in the
game because i'm just going along you know that uh the the ballista is like shooting bolts at you
and i'm just i didn't even know that existed i'm just walking along the ground
one hits near me it breaks the ground and i fall into the demon ruins and i'm like holy
shit i what the fuck yeah i just haven't seen that like i know that that happens to a lot of people
but i've never seen it just happened to me and it was so awesome oh man it was rad what happened
you went through the floor do yeah if if you're running around in the lake like there's a there's
one spot where if the ballista shoots the ground there the ground just falls out from under you
and you fall into the demon ruin i had like i knew about the lake but i had no idea that was there
it was it blew my mind and then like down there there's so much cool shit like the the spider
lady's down there and stuff oh it ruled what a fucking cool game 10 out of 10 yeah 10 out of 10
10 out of 10 10 out of 10 possibly possibly my favorite game of all time it's it's in the running
my top my top four are you know bloodborne dark souls three dark souls and demon souls so it's
in the running with those you know with that top four you know hey maybe we should wrap up but before
we do let's just say our our favorite build weapons i'm an undead legion boy for life with my broad
sword and my shield of want it's the best i haven't fucked around with the weapons a whole lot yet
but the one that i've been using ever since finishing the game was the uh the the the uh the one
that the fucking i'll know is it the icey sword uses the no the lightning axe the giant stone axe
that dragon slayer axe or whatever yeah yeah that's the one i've been using that's a pussy fucker it's
it's slightly it's slightly weaker than the weapon like the great i just had a great axe for most of
the game and then like on new game plus i started using that one it's ever so slightly weaker but
it does lightning damage which a lot of enemies are surprisingly weak too so like especially that
made the osiris fight fucking awesome yeah dragon so i'm like oh yeah so i go in there and start
spamming my weapon art on him and i was like fuck yeah fuck you osiris what the fuck is that guy's
deal he's like gotta dude that is the do you realize that he you know that he is the king right
he is king lothric he's he's king lothric what because if you there's certain item descriptions
that say that king lothric at some point went insane and started trying to become a dragon oh
he was studying ceaths like uh like all of his knowledge i missed all of that yeah that's that's
why the brothers are in charge now the princes because the king fucking went down and went insane
and somehow i have no idea how transformed into a dragon i have no idea what the fuck osilot is
yeah that's why he's a baby or like you can hear a cry so like it's maybe real what i don't know
that is the most out of all the lore i want to know please anyone who makes lore videos please
fucking explain osiris and osiris that is by far the most curious i am about anything in this game
i want to know everything about him he's so fucking cool his voice is all the voice acting in this
game is top notch he should he should have been king osiris should have been like you're pretty good
right the guy who fucking good the guy who gives you the uh uh uh crap the guy who gives you the
five level ups sounds like fucking jafar he's got the coolest fucking voice i love all the voices
are amazing it is your your your cowards don't even smoke crackers my legal name
jesse what is your uh what do you what weapon do you like well let's saw my award-winning
let's play series i saw several i saw several you know for for most of the game i was the hot maiden
endless jazz beautiful herald babe from the other side of fucking funville and i was fucking i i was
hot i was a christian slayer yeah that's right i was i was this hot fiery redhead from the emerald
aisles a christian slayer taking it back for st patty i was driving the fucking snakes out of
drive the snakes out of this bitch yeah yeah i was wearing that i was wearing that black
gown from urea because i killed her oh yeah because she tried to make me ugly so i had to
fucking fix that that wasn't the play through i do not remember that in the uh yeah that wasn't
recorded but yeah that happened um and then i was wearing that and i was wearing my fucking cool ass
crown from that i got from the fucking skelly man king and as i recall you had an icy sword but
were too hot to use it that's true and uh yeah i had an icy sword and a fire katana but i was
pissed off because my fire katana did not look like a fire katana and so it did not match my
icy sword so i was mad you just you gotta use some fucking uh some of that uh what is it you know uh
paper paper but eventually i killed more bosses i got stronger i leveled up i became a true babe
hero and i fucking a true champion i was i was walking around in my fucking artorias armor
with my fucking dancer helmet with the fucking scarf that flows behind you it looks so cool
and it does fucking dancer swords so i had i finally had a fucking a fucking icy sword and a fire
sword a magic sword and a fire sword but i was fucking spinning around i was killing everyone
and that's that's it that's all i got by the way one one quick thing about lore just people need
to figure this shit out am i is the dancer like a princess of lothric that was like captured and
turned by the pontiff into like a horrible abomination i heard that somewhere anyone know
anything about this no i've never heard about this okay never mind we'll make a lore video about
somebody i want to know about the dancer okay we need it all we need it all i think there was a
great noble wizard who was so in love with his his favorite burlesque dancer yes he said you need
to be a giant woman all he wanted to see what i wanted to see it so this is she she dance she
danced too hot so he said chill all right everybody that's it that's it this this dark souls 3 podcast
i hope you enjoyed uh everybody say goodbye good bye
dark souls 2 is the worst game ever
dark souls 2 is the best game ever don't think you can think about this fucking
of all i've never stopped talking this podcast i'll never grand i'll keep talking forever
because i'll never let him get the last word in dark souls 2 is a good game i'm editing this
and fuck you i'm taking out all of your lines i like salt and sanctuary well now i have to leave
all that