Welcome everybody to the PCP!
Guys, it's time we addressed the elephant in the room.
Which one?
Dumbo.
Get out of here, Dumbo.
Your film was racist.
That's the best guy I ever joined.
They won't pay me back the $20 I lent you to go to fucking five guys.
You messed up my order.
This is the last time I'm trusting your Dumbo.
Go back to Anthrocon Dumbo, you piece of shit.
Joining us today is the best guy I ever.
Hello.
That's me.
We've got Tommy Oliver.
Yo.
We've got The Hippocrit.
Snort.
Ben Sain.
Um, I am Pickle Rick.
And Munchy.
Watashi wa Munchy, seksu no tegesu.
It's a fucking full house.
It's six whole motherfuckers here to talk about PCPHQ.
The myth, the mythical legend that people have been like, like strung along hearing about for years.
And they're just like wondering when the fuck it's coming.
It's spoken about in hushed language around the campfire in the wee hours of the morn.
Wondering what is it?
When is it coming?
Is it even real?
Well, folks, today we're going to reveal all.
I've been really excited to talk about this topic for a while.
Like it's no secret that the PCP has been like a cagey mess recently.
And I really want to try and be open as possible.
Like that's my leader agenda.
That's my unique unit.
The no bullshitter.
Plus 15 combat strength.
We're not being a little bitch.
That's me.
No, no, guys, this is all great.
But we have to say, first of all, this episode is coming out in the context of when this comes out.
We are two weeks into our current Radcom 3 Arena Kickstarter.
Everybody, please, this is the most important thing.
If you're a patron, you know, and you only got so much money, allocate those funds to the Kickstarter because we need that thing to go.
Oh, man.
They have a Red Cross like a mini prototype of everything we're going to discuss here.
Indeed.
That's right.
All y'all need to say is if you pledge $50, you get a t-shirt.
It's a good t-shirt.
That was enough to get.
It's going to be a dope t-shirt.
Don't pledge too many, though, because then I have to make all of them by hand.
Oh, no.
I'm a weak-willed little boy.
He's weaving.
But they'll be handcrafted with love each and every one of them.
Put Tom to work, everybody.
And they will all be a randomized, like, still from the gift that is the logo of Armour Tree.
But you see, this is a beautiful thing to make.
That's great.
The first Radcon had, like, a static logo.
And then Radcon 2, we had everybody make logos because we couldn't decide on one.
And now we have kind of encapsulated our one logo is many logos.
It's self-contained.
It is actually pretty cool that all the, you know, you don't know which one of the colors
you're going to get.
But the way you said it is, like, the t-shirt will have a randomized gift on it.
It just sounded so terrible.
It's got an LCD screen.
Well, we're all going to have one, right?
Absolutely.
So if you want to match the cool kids and fit in with their click, you know, like, if you're
one of those kids who, when you're at school, you see all the skater kids and so you just
start dressing like a skater kid so they'll talk to you, like, you know, just saying,
wear a Radcon shirt around us.
There's a good chance you're going to start a conversation.
You know, when you walk into the high school lunch room and you see all those dark emo
kids sitting alone in their own table and you think, what are they fucking conjuring
over there?
They must be up to something special.
That's what you're going to look like if you wear these t-shirts.
You may have come to Anthrocon alone and friendless every year up to this point in your life,
but if you strut in there wearing a Radcon 3 t-shirt, let me just say your life's going
to change.
That's all I'm going to say.
For those who don't know, Radcon is a gathering of us.
If you didn't understand, we didn't mention that at all.
Everybody, please click the link to the Kickstarter.
There's a link in the description to the Kickstarter.
Read everything.
It's big.
It's going to be exciting.
We've done Radcon 1 and 2, of course.
It's great.
This is extremely linked to HQ.
And everybody on this episode right now is going to be there.
I love our advertising method of, like, pretending we're extremely desperate but in, like, a
skeevy.
Like, we're all trying to, like, jokingly manipulate people into buying the shirts.
That's the advertising strategy.
Isn't that how advertising works in general?
It's all about manipulation.
But we're showing them our cards.
We're showing them the method.
You hit them in the brain and you hit them in the heart.
You play all fronts.
That's what a PZPR is like so far.
It's just a skeevy monster mix.
That's all that we are in it.
Talking about.
It's the worst parts of real-life advertising and internet advertising combined into an amorphous
beast.
Hey, can we talk about the actual fucking reason we're doing this episode today?
Can we actually talk about the actual...
What are you doing?
The Urban Dictionary definition of PCPHQ.
I'm doing it right now.
It's loading.
I did actually find that already.
A place that seems to get further and further away as human scientific knowledge improves.
About 100 years ago, PCPHQ was right above our heads.
Humans started flying airplanes.
It wasn't there.
So it moved right above the atmosphere.
Finally, we send people in the outer space into the moon.
It wasn't there either.
So now PCPHQ is past Pluto somewhere.
What is this?
Where did you get that?
We gotta get there.
Yeah, we gotta get there.
That's what fucking Radcon's about.
We gotta send space probes there to get PCPHQ.
I also looked up, just for other people out there, alternate definitions.
First of all, here's the definition of PCP.
Oh, oh boy.
Human as angel dust, probably the scariest of all drugs, was used as a horse tranquilizer.
Makes the user hallucinate because it's extremely violent and not feel anything.
Which is what the PCP does.
I gotta say that it's a little ironic that we would name our show after what initially
started as a horse tranquilizer.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Holy shit.
How has this connection ever been?
It ended in that GIF.
Now listen to this.
People have known, have been known to do horrible things to the Selms while under the influence
of PCP.
Do not use PCP.
Do not.
It will ruin your life.
Head over to the Kickstarter to fund Radcon.
Things like not go to college.
Here's another PCPHQ definition.
A fiery place as overcrowded with jihadists and terrorists besides the traditional politicians,
tax fugitives, bankers, traders, lawyers, and CEOs.
That's Radcon.
Three years before.
Real talk.
How unlikely do you think it is for a PCP fan to get a college degree?
What do you think they beat over under?
I know.
I know they're out there doing their studies.
I feel like we encourage people to drop out on this show.
We do.
If someone asked me about college, I would absolutely tell them not to go unless they're
going into a certain specific field.
Yeah.
I would never tell anyone to not go to college.
I'm very consistent on this point.
Have a plan.
Whatever you want to do.
I know, man.
If you need to go to college, then do it.
The numbers prove that it's increasingly a waste of time and money.
Well, then do the not.
I've been real hard on college a lot in my life.
Recently, I've started to rethink that.
I think I've wasted my entire life doing this instead of actually going to college and
getting a degree.
I've been keeping myself every single night for that for the past two months.
We're forgetting the real reason we don't want anybody who watches the PCP to go to
college.
What is that money instead to fund PCPHQ?
PCPHQ.
That's right.
Now, I got one last thing here, guys.
Listen to the definition of just the word headquarters from Urban Dictionary, aka HQ.
One, a central place for a group or organization.
That's number one.
And number two, slang for PC shop where people play World of Warcraft, Dota, and other gay
ass games.
Dude.
That's what it says.
I can't wait.
That's exactly it.
That was the plan all along.
That's what we're going to do.
Your definitions are what we want the PCPHQ to be and what it's inevitably going to devolve
into.
All right, guys.
Let's get into it.
Let's talk about the basic broad concepts.
What is the PCPHQ?
Let's start there.
For all the uninitiated people who don't even know what's going on.
The PCPHQ, just to go over the bear facts, is you should check out our Patreon page.
We talk a little bit about it on there, but what it is is it is the magical dream realm
place that we all imagine of the members of the PCP being able to live in proximity and
then come to the HQ to work together, to make our collaborative projects similar to what
happens with the ride con stuff.
Of course, that's a different animal because we all gather and kind of live together.
Well, the ultimate goal is basically to make the red letter media set up because those
guys are a bunch of like 35 year old filmmaker buddies who have a similar sense of humor and
style so they all moved into the same place and rented out a studio and that allowed them
to make much higher quality products than what's typical on YouTube.
And since we all like to be quality over quantity type of guys as much as we can, YouTube kind
of necessitates you to fucking just churn shit out, but like, you know, red letter media
has got like a real fucking successful Patreon and real healthy view counts off of like putting
out a video once every couple of weeks, you know, because they can really go all in on
making the quality maximized and we think we are people with like strong enough personalities
and chemistry to carry a show.
Obviously we can do this show, but like this shows growth potential is nothing compared
to what could be if we could raise our production quality and really attract people to this
this motley underground niche crew, you know, so again, in layman's terms, PCP HQ is all
of the PCP members living in proximity, like in the same city and having some sort of space
where they can record, you know, studio type stuff and do new content that couldn't do
over the internet.
Real quick, I don't even want to give people the impression that like, because whatever
we say that red letter media stuff, I feel like people imagine it's just going to be
the plebe in the weave or like other half in the bag, you know, rip off or like a fucking
best of the worst rip off shows.
But I also think of it as like, all right, you know, like when Seth Rogen and James Franco
and they've got like all their friends and they all just live in Hollywood, so they make
movies together just because they all live in the same place and they're all comedians,
like that's also what I see PCP HQ as is like any random funny idea that we just can't do
by ourselves and we need like one other funny guy to be nearby, like it's real convenient
to have some stuff like that for say, if you've seen the collabs that me and Nate did when
I went to your house, I'll talk to a workout training, it's just like, it's like a little
four minute comedy video, but like the way it's filmed and the idea of it, like it couldn't
have been done without both of us being there and like this specific combination of senses
of humor, even body type, you know, like is all plays into the joke of that video, you
know, so it's like something that couldn't have happened with either of us alone.
One of the big strengths of having the HQ is going to be able to like increase the ability
to make spontaneous spontaneous content, because like if we have an idea, we can just do it
as opposed to me like, well, I want to do this idea with Digi, I got to track him down,
we got to plan our time, we actually do something together and blah, blah, blah, like it's just
like, you want to do it, man? Yeah, we'll come on over and then that's it.
You serves don't understand how much the fourth dimension adds to content, like like the ability
to be in the same room as something, someone automatically alters how the content flows.
I, even though like, like I don't think I act any differently online than I do offline,
it's inevitable that just, that just is the case. It just is the case. I don't know how
to stop it, it just is the case. And I think, you know, in all the degradation types, you
know, digital links and like, you're in all the sort of stuff like there, I think, I think
I, I think I have a certain flow in my, you know, natural unscripted live action sort of
stuff that I just can't replicate online because that's, you know, it's just hard. I'm not
in front of people. I can't gauge things. So just being live action will really benefit
like all of us and I mean, just look at the reaction of people to the lectures, the PCP
lectures, which are a shining example. That's the biggest proof, I think that it's there.
I, I, that it's worthwhile. Like, look at the thing about those. They're huge.
That they were obviously got a huge response and imagine if we could do those anytime we
wanted. Imagine a PCP world without the fucking Sanchu lecture or the fucking
declination lecture or the Kingdom Hearts lecture. Like those are two fucking or three
insanely influential pieces of fucking work. They are, they are integral to the PCP lore
and they're all like, you couldn't fucking have a lecture of declination. It would not
be the same. If I wasn't there pacing back and forth for two hours and people falling out of
their fucking chairs thinking about Jace, that would not be the same. You could only have that
sort of stuff in person. I think there could be no debate that there's a lot of content that we
can only make in that situation. And here's my main pitch to people. People don't always think
about this, but if you want to make your, if you want to find yourself in a place where you're
making like interesting or unique content, you have to set yourself up in a position where you
can succeed doing it. So like we could, you know, continue to like slave away on like projects,
just doing exactly what we're doing forever. You know, we could always do that. But like
the amazing thing to me is I like to think back to a moment in the Kingdom Hearts lecture that I
never, ever could have planned. I never would have thought to write this joke, but the way it
just emerged from this, you know, emergent gameplay of the lecture of playing off the people in the
audience was amazing. And it was when, when Jeff asked the question, and I was talking about like
Nominee and Rokus and Sora, how like they're all the same person. And he just said like, Nate, so
okay, or Mr. Best Guy. So if they were to fuck, like what percentage of masturbation would that be?
And then just, you know, I immediately respond, for me, 100%. And it got a gigantic, like it was
the funniest moment in the whole thing. It's amazing. I watch it back all the time. And I never
could have written that joke. And it works in the context of that setting. So well.
You watch back the moment that you really nailed it over and over again, just like reliving the
glory of the times. You're literally, you're masturbating to your masturbation.
It's his, it's his ringtone now.
I feel you hard. I feel you hardcore. The new lecture was completely unscripted. And I had no
idea what I was going to do when I fucking got up there. And I just thought, well, might as well
just go as hard as I fucking can. And there's that catchphrase, that catchphrase, that legendary
phrase was fucking born out of the ashes. That nigger has not gotten up off the ground.
He's still there. He's slam. He's part of the fucking soil at this point. He's decomposed.
I mean, I don't, I don't know what else there is to say. Like just the fact that, like, because none
of that, all this was like an 18 minutes into the podcast date. I don't know what else there is to
say. Well, I'm on this front. I just mean, because I think that really sums it up just in terms of
like the tangible benefits right there. Well, no, I think there's another, another tangible benefit
is because we're talking about like all this extra content we can do. But I think another good thing
to point out is that even the base PCP will increase dramatically in quality because so much of like
conversation and like interaction is nonverbal. So being in the same room, if we all recorded
in person, there'd be a whole other dimension to the conversation that'll just like subconsciously
one of my favorite podcast is the sleepy cast and they record in the same room. The audio isn't
great. But like the energy in that room of them just fucking around and talking about bullshit
is just so it's like it leads to so much more funny moments. The fucking energy, man. It's the
energy. When you're on the computer, it's too easy to like, Oh, look to the side. What's that bag of
pretzels doing there? Look to the side. Oh, there's that glass of milk that I haven't taken downstairs
now to house mold all over the top of it. Well, you're in person. You can't do that. You have to
keep focused on the person you're talking to. And it creates a, you know, a more natural dynamic
conversation. It's like, it's like when we did tbap, like, like all the energy in tbap was because
we were doing it live. And I remember like when we didn't live in the same place, like we didn't
want to keep doing tbap because it wouldn't be the same to record it. Yeah, literally call or whatever.
Literally remember tbap, like, like, not as you don't think about it for like a second.
Hey, speaking of which, you pledged $9,000 and $1,000 to the Kickstarter,
hashtag maxrevive tbap. Those stretch goals suck. I mean, we had a moment just now where
six people tried to talk at once. And that's the exact reason that this should be done live.
You know, like, that doesn't happen when you're all live, because you can all see each other
gearing up to speak, you know, when someone's getting ready. Here we've got a delay so we
can't even tell until after someone has decided to start speaking that they have begun speaking,
you know, it's a lot harder to manage flow in a conversation, especially on like a laggy
discord server with six people on different parts of the fucking continent, you know.
So yeah, think about all that and also think about the fact that the rain reason we don't do
face cam is that sinking six fucking face cam videos would be a pain in the ass getting everybody's
quality consistent, you know, and like also it's kind of sucks to be held accountable for two hours
to not like play with your dick, you know. So, but when you're surrounded by everybody else,
then you can't touch your dick. You can touch each other's dick. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
First like. Yeah. Okay. Okay. So that appeal for real. The appeal of having great
higher g content that that's all good and well, and I know all of our fans would love that. You
guys just listen to the rad con stuff, all that impossible to do online. So that's all squared
away. That's all, you know, obvious that that's all incredible. But here's the thing that also
like, like, you know, the PCP is about content, right? Well, the other flip side of the PCB is
that we're all friends. And we never see each other ever. None of us ever like fucking like like
culture shock, intellectual alarm clock blasting your fucking ears listener, the PCP don't talk
to each other and they don't hang out ever. And PCP you will hopefully fix that. I hope please.
I definitely want to hang out with everyone more. Yeah. Do like, like, you know, let's plays,
but not like for a video. Just just having a place to go and be like, Yeah, what are you
working on? I'm working on my video over here. Exactly. I imagine it being like a combination
of red letter media with the big room where we film things. And then maybe some small I have no
idea what we're like, what we could afford. Like, super fucking cool. If like, for example,
we're all in the same place. And maybe like hippo, you're just like, Hey, I'm working on the next
hypocrite video. Like, look at what I got so far. What do you think? Yeah, things like that. We can
all influence our content as it's being developed. Because there's one thing that I've had like
ideas and I've been told by like Digi, at least, that I could send like my scripts to people to
see what they think. But it's it's, I don't know, it never really feels right to send a script that
I'm working on even when I'm stuck to anybody. But when I'm like, I'm because it's like, it's more
in the delivery and stuff. It would be so so dude, it is 1000 times. Let me tell you, this is
something I've gotten personally, because I've been living with with my fiance now, because she
left her job to work for me. And like, reading a script out loud to somebody else, like, you
could just ask them, like, is that the right word? Like, is that the word I wanted? You know, or like,
is that funny? And then they can go, Oh, yeah, that was funny. Or like, you watch them, you can see
them laugh. And you're like, Okay, that's funny. I'm leaving that in the video. Like, I have definitely
been using we both have like, whenever we make something, we just look at the other person,
like, which parts of this are good, you know, and I think with PCP, with all of us having like,
you know, pretty similar senses of humor and holding each other to a pretty high standard,
having critical eye, you know, I think, if maybe I could watch one of, you know, Nate or hippos
videos over their shoulder, right before they publish it, I could be like, that joke is real
funny. That one I would cut, you know, and then you can look at my video and be like,
This is fucking boring. You should make it funny. And I'll be like, Okay,
let's do that.
Let me paint a picture for the viewers here. So imagine all of the PCP are like nice castles
on a hexagon grid in the in the middle in the middle of all these kingdoms is a barren desert
wasteland. That is our discord chat room. And all communication must go through this desert
wasteland. This is like fucking Sahara, you have to put on your turban and you will have to get
your fucking slaves. You have to venture across this barren wasteland, get to the other empire
to fucking talk to the other king there. That's what that's what talking online is like. If you
fucking help us get PCB HQ, we can just walk over to each other's houses and we won't have to
fucking toil endlessly under the hot blistering discord sun. Now I do just want to put in here.
I don't want to feel I don't want to like make it sound like just give us money and this will
happen like real fast. I want to add just a little bit of a damper to this whole fun conversation
just to say this is a long term goal that we're all working on and obviously if we're talking about
the lives of like at least six people here that have to be like you know financially economically
you know housing situation has to be resolved and all that stuff takes like a lot of money
and a lot of effort. So in no way are we saying this like just get us to like right now on the
PCP Patreon we say like give us five grand I think it's like per episode that we release
and like we will start to make PCB HQ happen. That is start it will not like officially be fully
realized at that point. We're definitely not going because like we're doing a Kickstarter for
the Radcon 3 and that's like a temporary like oh we want to meet up we want to jump together and
just do some stuff and like make more content to like impress you all but like the actual getting
over and everybody getting situated and you know ordering a studio that would never be like that
won't be crowdfunded it will just be like when we all have enough money in order to support ourselves
when we have income that we can rely on that's when it will happen we just need you know to bolster
our own and and the PCP and all that. It makes perfect sense it takes five thousand dollars to
fund PC for to fund Radcon and that's for a week so if we release a video every week and it's five
thousand a video then that means it's a Radcon every week. Oh my god. You know what I'm saying?
Basically check it out. You're blowing your fucking minds. Just keep in mind that this entire podcast
is speculative and not at all like a promise. You're hearing the first real murmurings of this
nationalist ethno-state movement live on air. Yeah. Well one of the main reasons we decided
even to do this episode is like we've been talking because we haven't had set down and had a super
constructive conversation about this anyways. We've tried. So it's just as much for us. It's too far
out. It's too far out. Well hold on. I think okay you guys are bothering me with this. It's too far
out. It's no reality. Look I'm moving to Boston in June that's happening so PCPHQ starts June 1st
when I moved to Boston. PCPHQ is real until two PCP guys live in the same place. Whoever shows up
after me that's it's officially HQ. The second that there's two people that Tom's already there
so me and Tom can already have PCPHQ. If it takes a month for the rest of you to show up Tom's
going to be living in my garage by that point by the by. So you know the PCPHQ will be me and Tom
and Pantsu party over here fucking making vlogs until everybody else shows up. Whoa what the fuck
does Pantsu party have to do with PCPHQ dude. Let's put a stamper right now on that shit.
Just saying that's what it'll be until the rest of you guys show up. What the fuck is everybody.
That's all good well and put up in there. We should come back to that but that's nitty gritty
shit and we should probably keep this abroad still because I still want to. My point is everybody
stop trying to make it less hype by making it sound like it's too far away because then the
audience isn't going to give us all their money because they're going to be like I don't care
about like you know when they release those like teaser trailers for a movie that comes out in like
a fucking year and you're like I literally will not remember that this movie is supposed to come
out like I don't care enough about any movie. Well on the other hand you don't want to be a final
fantasy 15 and promise something and then take 10 years to deliver something that's way shittier
than it was initially promised. You don't want to be Kingdom Hearts 3 and buy like two consoles for
a game that. No we don't want to be any of that stuff we want to be a game that announces it's
going to be released six months beforehand and then comes out and everyone loves it that's what
we want to do so let's just let's just tell everybody it's happening in six months and then
do it in six months. But the complexity involved like am I going to be ready to literally quit
my job in six months. Make it that way. Make it so it's that way. Well I think I mean I think what
it is is that like PCP HQ like like the ultimate like the ultimate hypothetical form of it where
like all of us live together is like maybe far out and it's complicated but like it doesn't have to
be it's not black and white like that like PCP HQ can start to form like yes that's what I'm saying
it's it's it's on a spectrum like I've always expected exactly I've always expected that me
and Nate are probably going to be the first ones to meet up because I'm I'm definitely moving
Nate's probably going to be ready to move before too long if we are all if we're all going to
wherever Tom already is then he'll be there so I'm thinking like you know there's we don't have to
wait for everybody else to show up before we start making videos you know like whoever's available
is going to be the initial crew of making like the live action content and everybody else is
going to still probably be in the audio only version you know and like I expect that to basically
exist until everybody shows up you know and it'll be like all right we don't need that to exist anymore
you know but like whoever's there will make content and you guys already know me and Nate
make shit together I went to your house and we made like 20 fucking videos so like you know as
soon as two of us are in the same place it's PCPHQ and then what that is can grow and evolve as
more people turn up and contribute to it there's one general broad thing that I would like to brush
up upon that's like that may not seem immediately relevant but I think it is extremely relevant
to HQ as a whole what is the PCP to everyone else maybe uh here I'll I'll I'll I'll say I'll say
what I perceive the PC to be to be to me it's sort of like a weekly world war like with each member
being like a mighty empire like each rich in culture in their own right banding together to duke it
out intellectually and physically each sunday to appease our suzerain 15 000 fold no one's main
identity should be like should be appearing on these podcasts like the PCP is like supplementary
material to all of our individual content that's how to say the PCP kind of isn't important all right
I'm gonna I'm gonna go ahead and make a promise right now when PCPHQ happens if there is a live
action version of the PCP in any form physical fighting will be a part of it
it has to it has to end with blood physical violence will definitely be be a sponsored content
of the PCP you know another tangible benefit he'll throw me I mean it's kind of it's kind of part of
this whole situation but like right now Gibb does in fact live in another country and if PCPHQ
can form and become like a stable actual sort of business model then we could get visas for Gibb
to come work and live as a employee yeah I think that's the biggest financial goal like the the
reason that PCPHQ needs like the reason we need a kicker the reason we need a patreon for it you
know like why does it have to be a patreon goal with me and Nate could just move into the same
place anyways it's because we can't do that with someone like hippo who's you know not even from
this country like we need to have a real stable foundation for someone like him to come over right
yeah it's not because I looked into it a lot of times and checked and stuff and there's like two
main ways I could get into the US well three if I'm if I'm illegal but like two is like one is
like marrying someone from this country and the other one is being hired by an by a company
and if the PCP can become like a literal like LLC company thing I think that would be an avenue
that I could like like you can hire me in I could be on shows and be like haha and then I can have a
house and what if we kickstarted Gibb what if we kickstart Gibb and munchies wedding you know
they're mad down dude I keep telling you it's not a fucking joke I will gay marry you to get you into
America this is a full like my legs are spread just whenever you're ready it's so weird I can't
tell my parents that I'm getting gay married to a big fat Mexican lad that's like 16 real question
remember that movie now I now pronounce you Chuck and Larry or whatever it was about like two guys
like okay why what was the problem exactly why can't you just marry like is there do you have to
like prove you like love them or something like why doesn't that just work that was the conceit of
the movie I don't know if that's true in reality yeah I'm real curious I've never heard of like
because people get shotgun married all the time so yeah yeah or maybe they I think it was because
they had to be married specifically for some kind of grant that they were trying to get or some
ride I don't fucking know who cares well whatever I have no idea about it I I mean if it comes down
to that I just won't tell anybody in my family that I'm technically married to a man I will just
you're not married to a man you're married to a god
like we'll just we'll it'll just be munchy and the detail there will be no further details
yeah I'll just say I found God and they're like oh
became a christian and much is every gender at once so fuck respond to what I said by the way
what was that what what is the pcp to everyone I can answer that oh right yeah the pcp is basically
a virus or no no no more more accurate would be to say a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a paramecia
or a single celled organism with many nuclei and these nuclei inside control the main body
and stretch it and squish it however they see fit with the goal of expanding and and assimilating
more and more into the entity as a whole like we're all working independently but we're all
working to the shared goal of getting our big fucking blob body as big as it can get yeah
I'm all about my blob body getting bigger. We're just a big old blob. We're absolutely filled with goop
We're laden with it. Does anyone else share my adjustics my justice league interpretation of the PCP?
I forget the world war. I don't remember. I don't get it parry it to the justice league at all
Or like yeah, but the United Nations. Yeah, what I see it as is what is has always been
Like sans podcast is just a group of internet creators who are like intellectually cool and fun
And I don't hate them and they like me as well. So that's good and we can all make each other
Grow
Our penis is big because we like each other so much, you know, this has changed over time
But I certainly still think of the PCP when you know
I had the idea to start doing the podcast and the reason for it was because I just wanted to talk to you guys
And if not for the podcast that simply would not happen. Yeah, and you know it had and now it's actually making some money
Which is very nice and all these other things about wanting to move in together. It's helping facilitate that goal
so to me it's an excuse to continue talking to my friends continue collaborating with the very few content creators online or some of
them that I respect and
Yeah, it's just it's just a dream of like you you are the guys that I want to work with and I do and I hope to continue to do so in
New ways in the future and this is a unifying element
I do not put a I mean I love just talking at length as as obviously because I just like love doing the PCP in general
So for me, it's just a great way to just dump a bunch of bullshit every week on in a podcast and shit
But other than that, it's a great unifying element with people who I respect and want to work with
Yeah, that's what it is for me
The PCP is like a combination of both a collaborative and competitive effort
Because like we come together and we're all friends. We hang out we talk shit
And we just make a collaborative product, which is great
And it's an excuse to talk with all you guys
But at the same time the PCP is an enterprise is also a way for me to like keep tabs on what everybody is doing and
It kind of keeps me motivated because like I've talked before about how I feel like I have to earn my place here
So I definitely feel like there's like a bar that needs to be bet and that kind of helps keep me working harder than I might
Buy myself. I might like lose motivation. Can I just put out this thought on that? Okay, go ahead
Go ahead. Yeah, I've definitely felt like other groups of friends or people are not
They I don't it's it. They're not like hard on me enough like they don't they just say
Yeah, that's great and like the Brody's like the Brody's it's it's it this group is like one part everything
I said before but then another part
It is yeah, it is competitive
It's like we're always trying to one-up each other and we get annoyed when one of us is like the the most popular digi
And we
But the rest of us are like vying for
We're also jealous of digi we all made a snow idol of him and murdered him
Like it's like it's it's good to have competition. It's like a friendly rivalry like like like it's like an anime like everyone
It's funny give that you mentioned the the the hard talk and stuff because I remember at one point like this time last year
I felt very isolated from the group and I approached you specifically about it and you straight up told me like your shit
Just hasn't been interesting and none of us have felt it's worth talking about and that like kicked my ass and from that point on
I was like I need to bust my ass harder. Yeah, but then they basically started making money and you cozyed up real
Above above all else as much as I like being a content creator. I like being a Jew so much
It's not bad and by the way, here's your dose of hashtag re-utilitarianism for the day
I literally believe unconditional love is immoral and I will never subscribe to it at any point
It has everything to do with this because if we were just friends who didn't criticize each other and we're just like supportive in everything
That we did there would be stagnation and at least within our relationship. I want to bring him my move. I see a PCP
Okay
There's something wrong
I've broken my brain, but uh, no, I I think
How I see the PCP is that everyone in this group is an artist who given the opportunity
Would attempt to make the greatest piece of art they possibly could and then attempt to one up at every time they made something new
Given the opportunity now right now
Everyone's in a position where they're trying to become financially stable through art in order to give them the leeway to do that
All of us are young as fuck. Nobody's even 30 yet. Most artists don't even really become big until their 30s, you know
Hello, I see us as a
I see us as a group of people with an insane amount of potential because everyone in here is so creative and has been doing it for
Such a long time that they've kind of proven themselves
No one in here is like a flake. None of us were one success and then we quit YouTube
You know, we all tried to build multiple careers here and are still trying to grow and are still like hungry and I think
You know Nate is obviously somebody who wants to make really highly produced and epic videos
He might not ever put the like the like stupid amount of effort he put into some of them again, but like incorrect
It's stupid
But if you didn't have to make we Agua you would just focus on making those right
But but I do have to make we I want to succeed on YouTube. So I do
I only just recently got to a point where I'm able to take more of a step back
And even then I still try to I still try to put out shit constantly just because
There's some people who just want to hear my voice all day and I want to appease those people as well
And I have fun doing it. It's a good way to just constantly like throw every
Well, yeah, because we say one of those people is me is that we said yeah, oh, yeah
Well, I mean like you know something like Nate doing we Agua a lot of these are video ideas
And we all have this this all this happens to everyone in this group that we have way more ideas than we can actually fucking make
Like the worst Nate there's no way Nate could ever in his lifetime make fully edited videos out of every idea
That's on we Agua. So there is a reason for that show to exist
And I'm sure you wouldn't just kill like that lower effort content entirely just because you were able to make higher effort stuff
But like you probably would be like hey, there's not gonna be a weekly show instead
I'm gonna make fucking movies that are gonna like you are never gonna want to stop watching this video, you know indeed indeed
And I think that's what everybody I think it's everybody in here would try to do if like they had the unlimited
Resources and and time, you know, I don't think anyone in here is somebody who if we had all the money in the world would be like
I'm never doing art again. We'd just be like
Masterpiece, you know, yeah, you know, I feel guilty even saying this but you know looking back on it
I got to say my respect for Aaron Hansen is
Coming back around as just a businessman and as a practical guy who was like this is what I got to do to succeed
Make game around great just grow it
I you know the more time that passes the more I recognize just what a mature and that dude could do anything
He wants now like if he wants to make an animation
He fucking I mean you I was just like first you get rich then you can just do anything
So like first get rich everybody just do it. Just do the day. I was looking at fucking kitty cat gaming
his wife's channel and like
He animated a full intro for that like just for his wife's channel
Just cuz he felt like it like he knew there would be no profit for him in doing that other than like
Hey, my wife will have a neat little intro animation, but like that. It's like a fully flat. Oh, yeah
But like, you know, I'm just looking at that
I'm like, this is what you this is a freedom you have when like you don't have to interrupt your schedule of like
I have to have an animation about a popular game done every month, you know
Like most people have to see what he just announced on game grumps or whatever like when they were doing game grumps touring
There was no production company that could handle like what they were asking for as youtubers
So they just built their own and now they're like looking for people and I was like goddamn
I want to sign up to this shit. I want to tour maybe I can work with the game grumps and do this shit
God, I'm so impressed by these people
Fucking they made a visual novel, you know, like these are the kind of things that if we I think at our group
If we all lived in one area and we didn't have the monetary concern of like I need constant videos
That's the kind of shit we would come up with I mean
Just made a visual
I'm assuming we all have like a big project like it's somewhere in our minds that given no constraints we would do
I know I do yeah, of course
I've got a lot like I can't diss a but right now
I just got myself up to a point where I'm allowed to make like one video a month on the main channel
And that's enough for me to make something pretty big
But I've never been able to like oh I had to disappear for six months to make this piece of art
So, you know like in we all know, you know, our buddy the endless one did that
I don't know how well that worked out for him financially
But like that's how we got horseshoe finale is dude had to disappear for six months and make that thing because that's that's why
That's why it's a masterpiece is that it had that much time and some
Kind of focus, right? There's a concept called deep work, which it's a concept. I've been reading up about
Deep web. Yeah, the deep the deep web but like deep work
It's it's when because it was interesting was reading this book and was talking about how like social media is destroying people's attention spans
And it's actually like making making it more difficult for creators to do what's called deep work
Which is when you just spend like three four five six hours at a row without any inter interactions or interruptions just working on something
That's how I make all my videos. That's where the majority of like good work comes. That's like um, oh, there's there's a talk by um
Oh god, one of the one of the Monty Python guys
Who's the big one please? Yeah, John Cleese John. Yeah, there's a talk by John Cleese about like the
Like creative mode and like and how like you need like time to like let your mind enter the creative mode or something
sounds similar and
They're talking about how like with multitasking and stuff like when you like no one can actually multitask like your brain can't do it
You just do tasks switching and the interesting thing was like your brain when you switch tasks
You don't immediately just stop doing the other thing. It's still kind of lingering in your mind
So it takes a little while for your brain to completely switch off from one thing and focus on another
So if you're constantly going and checking social media or whatever else or like doing smaller things in the middle of your work
You never fully commit to it a hundred percent. Yeah, so it's like it's just a really interesting like how like the brain works
Oh, I'd love to be able to if you're someone who has problems with that fucking get like the stay focused app
You know that shit just blocks you from all social media for like a day or it gives you it gives you ten minutes
Of time every day, and then it'll just block the page
So you got ten minutes of Twitter today, and you better fucking use it spare you better use it right, you know
Or if you waste it all in the morning
It's like well
I guess you're grinding on your writing all night because you ain't open in that fucking way that better if you get out of the way
And sometimes I've been in cycles where I was doing like I would just do it all at the beginning and then not have it all
Day sometimes I want like I need that little spice of like breaking away from what I'm writing for like just a minute
You know to look at Twitter and but I try to spread that out all night
You know I'm only allowed to look for 30 seconds because it's gonna cut into my 10 minutes
So like that's another way to kind of keep yourself on track
Yeah, yeah, man
Excellent, I feel I feel like
Like like coming back to to you know like like a piece of HQ and have and how that will affect us and how we'll be able to
Be better people because of this even even if you disregard any of
the you know business
Content-wise things again, just being together will in like like like you know
I just said you know remove content
But even just being better friends and just talking to other will you know influence our content and make it better
I know that like like being together will like fucking like pacify all of our dark mental urges and fucking like you know
Moderate our suicidal and and homicidal tendencies and try and make us into more productive
Moral people with a fucking backbone for once and so just being friendly with one other and being able to actually see another person
Every you know once every week or so instead of the zero time we all get to see that will be great
And that will be able to make us you know more functional fucking people and therefore better content
Let me make break out one of my favorite comparisons like fucking in the fighting game community like people who get big as like
Fighting game players they have to play against other big players like you can't get good playing against like your local guys
Like even if they're really great like if you're not playing against a pro
They just know so much more that like just playing against them teaches you way more about the game
You know that's that's preparing you for an entirely different meta
Exactly and so like us living together is it or even working together all this time has always been that way like we've had
Everyone in the PC piece had a very massive influence on each other. I think that's pretty fucking obvious
Which is why why we all share a fan base because people generally you know can see the threads of each other's work in
and everything we do but like
You know living together just to kind of increases that it's I
One of the things about like that the reasons people recommend going to college is like they say you'll get experience just by like
Seeing things that you wouldn't have seen at home. You know and with the piece with with working with you guys
I've had times were like just watching someone edit you might like learn a whole new way to edit
You know or watching someone's workflow or just being around when someone's being creative gives you ideas about how to approach creativity
You know, I might have different brainstorming methods from Nate
But like maybe if I copy the way he takes notes, it'll let me make a different kind of video or something like my famous note taking
Yeah, I mean
I've been exploring all this because I'm helping my fiancee launch her channel and like we've been just watching YouTube videos fucking
Constantly and like taking notes on what everybody does, you know
So I've been in this constant state of like man being around youtubers is powerful
like being around people who do the same work you do like will really
Just like kind of reconfigure your mind to think of things in a different way and I've learned a lot from even just seeing like hippos
Writing style like how he writes the jokes into his fucking scripts, which I don't do at all
Like hippo like writes notes about how to deliver jokes in the scripts themselves
A lot of people might not have even thought about that and some people will probably just learn something just by me explaining that on this podcast
You know so like the more we learn from each other the more we can tell the world because like I might take for granted the way
I write but then one of you guys looks at it and goes oh fuck guys
Did you know you could write like this and now everybody knows, you know, you know
I just don't want to I don't want to get anybody to whipped up in a frenzy
But I just want to say like keep your eyes on what's going here if you if you like what we do
I don't want to make anybody give like us money or whatever to support a dream
That doesn't have a tangible benefit for them, but I think that we can offer that I mean, I mean there's no like there's no like
Yeah, there's no like fun for this, right?
Yeah, just the main PCP patreon, you know does include language saying like if we hit 5,000 goals
PCP HQ will become real now like we'll start to make it when we have the money personally to do it
We will do it
And it depends on whether we individually get big or the PCP allows us like we get an income from that right right
But it's not gonna be like yeah, we're not gonna fund it directly
Speaking of that Nate about specific things that we don't people get all riled up about
Let's talk about specific things that will rile people up
I think we've all talked about the general broad stuff. I think it's time to get the nitty gritty like what exactly we plan to do
Like can I give you my vision here? Yeah. Yeah, sure
Let me let me give you my general vision of what I see when PCP HQ becomes real in my mind
I see and this is just me other people might disagree and this will all be figured out in time when this sure starts to become real
But in my world there is a core unifying show perhaps weekly
That is something akin to a half-in-the-bag style show like live-action people sitting down talking about thing
They want to talk about with probably I don't know
I imagined some sort of we Agua style editing it'll depend on like who the editor is and what the workflow becomes for that sort of thing
Um and so and that's like the main core content on the channel and then aside from that
Probably just like relative or content that's currently relevant to whatever's going on
So for example something like the podcast me and digi did about
Like the era manga sensei like I imagined things along those lines appearing on there as well
Maybe live-action maybe not and I I do get inspired by a lot of what red-letter media does in terms of they'll just make like random videos
Like science man explains like transformer genesis or you terminate like whatever it is all that kind of shit like that
That's the hand boy winter war sort of thing well
That's the kind of stuff that it helps to have the studio set up for because like exactly they created
Oh, it's a different type of video
But like all they really had to do is swap out a few assets and like they already have the lighting
They already have the big cameras like everything is ready to go just swap out the basic props of like the set and
For us even just working individually
I'm sure this is true for all of you because we all fucking work in our bedrooms
They have to set up your whole fucking setup every time you want to record anything
You know see that honestly when I dream of PCB HQ the number one thing I dream of considering
I literally have to like construct my set every time I set up having a studio room where I just go
Flip some switches and I'm ready to record. That is my dream. That is my dream
I that was what we tried to do at the at rad con and with the set that was in my my old house
But like I never quite got the lighting good because it's hard to justify spending a lot
To make a proper set you're gonna have to drop a lot of money
But like if everyone was there and we were all using it it would be justified, you know
Like if we wanted to get real professional shit, you know, I think all of us
Understand that that's the next layer to go to but it's like there's not enough
There's not enough evidence that that will profit us to do it for just our own videos, you know
But like if everyone's working together, it's like okay
Well having a dedicated setup will mean we can like just churn shit out like you know pencil in what whatever
You're doing that day and let's fucking film the schedule, you know, yeah, yeah for sure
That's one thing I dream of in the meantime. I'll probably construct like some sort of home studio
I don't I feel like I'm gonna move pretty soon probably before PCB HQ becomes real and the most important thing is to get a room
Where I can just set up my shit, and I don't maybe get another computer just all that kind of stuff, man
I dream it every fucking day. God. I fucking hate sitting on my goddamn camera
I'm really glad that we're talking about like specific things
We're going to do because one of my main concerns with PCB HQ, you know before this a while ago was a
Well, we had like, you know, of course the obvious benefit of like oh, we'll be able to do things together
There will be new shows available
That's kind of where the conversation ended and there was no like fit like actual show like yeah
Sure, there would be a show if we were all together
But when we're talking about moving and putting people's lives on the line
It's better to have an actual show
Planned instead of just saying there will be a show eventually
The reason it's sort of vague when we initially came up with it was it's just it will be us talking about media like we do
Well, but there's like two of us instead of one or maybe just one like the reason
Like I I mean, I don't do we agile with style things
But I could but I'm just like not that good on camera generally and I have a really bad place to record but like um I
Doing like edited review things only really works with me when it's something that I already have a history with and I can sort of
explain and
And and do all that sort of like big editing long-form stuff
And if I wanted to do that for like my channel to get you know talk about new games and and get like new
Viewers and whatever like it would be way easier if I could just have somebody there and we say yeah
We played this game. This is what we think about it and that would be the show, but it would be great because it's like
It's it's just t-bap, but with a video game
Yeah
I
I've I've turned my nose up a bit at red letter media before but I've been watching it a bunch lately and
Thinking about it in terms of like like what if like what if the PCP had like a similar setup
And I don't know it's just really great. It's really exciting, right, right?
There you go. I mean just like you know this they have these props and they just do these fucking
Shit things
Up to succeed it would just yeah, they did and it would just be it's so much better than it would be if it was audio-only
Mm-hmm
Like if they couldn't do they couldn't do like any of the shit
They do if they didn't have like a studio at the very least their meme potential like two
They're big memes on TV just posting red letter media, you know like gifts and images and stuff like they are
They're kind of a cultural phenomenon in their own small way
Oh, they have a pretty big cult fan base, you know, like indeed like one of them a grown-up version of uh of what we got, you know
um
But I think the reason that it's been so nonspecific is that for me
I usually base the projects I do on what is at my disposal
So like the way I see it again, if it was only gonna be me and Nate for a few months
I would just invent a show that is for me and Nate and is meant to last a few months
You know until we get the next guy or like if it or designed to go on until it needs to be replaced
Or unless it's super successful in which case we just keep doing that show even after pcph
So like
Basically for me, it's just like all right. Who do I have? What equipment do we have right now?
What space do we have, you know?
If if me and Nate both move to the same place and we can't yet afford or justify the expense of a studio space
We might just do something in a home studio, but with both of us, you know, but there's a lot of potential there
So
Yeah, I think that's why it's been so nonspecific
But I just want to have the ability to
If there is an idea to do it like again with the otaku workout training video
And I realized that a lot of the stuff that I tend to cite as like what I want to be able to do more of is not necessarily
Like the most popular videos we do like
Obviously, I think all of us have been are most successful when we're critiquing popular media more so than like just trying to carry something on the strength of like
our personas, you know
I think that
There's a lot more room to explore what we can do with that
Whenever we do make a weird video like that like a comedy video
There's a crowd of people who's like this is my favorite thing you've ever made and I'm like I agree with that crowd
The passionate fans are the ones who will throw their money at you. They're the ones
They're the ones we should be worried about
I got a show idea
But I don't worry about I mean we should we should care about their opinion and not the and not the fair weather people who are just interested in
The popular thing we might be talking about
I I I got a show idea
All right, because like we've got all these like vague things like just uh
personalities put them together and talk about something
That's that's that's all good. We can make a billion different types of those sort of shows
But here's here's a specific one
It'll be we go. I don't know where the Walmart sells like a brick a giant bricks of limestone
But we go and get the
And then we bring them into a room and we get some hammers and chisels and we just learn how to sculpt
I'm definitely down let's sculpt let's sculpt
Let's sculpt me and native had a long long time plan to do some kind of show about learning Japanese
Uh, you spilled the beans, but it's true guys. We've had that plan for like a fucking solid year
And we like it obviously would get done way easier if we live, you know, what is it?
Okay, now that you've said it, let me just give everyone my dream
This is a project I came up with and I think it is literally the best idea of all time
It is a podcast
I mean it'd probably be live action if we if we get this shit together
But it is a a a like regular maybe weekly style show where we are learning Japanese beginning with the fundamentals
And like every week we'll make a new lesson learning more stuff
And the point of this is that one day when many episodes are made
This will simply be a fun youtube playlist podcast where you can just watch and if you like practice and do the lessons along the way
You will just learn Japanese as well. Is that not the greatest idea?
It's like our people for Japanese culture
There will and there will also be a competitive element to it and like lots of lots of dunking on each other
Like that's gonna be integral. You know, I love that idea. Get dunked on bro
Make a lot of money. We'll be playing the entire time
I'm gonna get on a train of thought and ben. I think I think you'll be interested in this
So please chime in whenever you feel necessary. Okay. I am not a video person
I do not create videos as my main thing. Of course, you know
The main thing I do now, you know, like like that people see not behind the curtain is videos
But you know, I don't perceive myself to be that I am a draw person first and foremost and in my heart
And so it like, you know, if I were to go to psphq, well, of course, I would benefit from studios and stuff such as that
That's not the main thing that I would be doing is, you know, creating new types of the main
I have I have types of videos that I would like to do. I would like to do a cooking show
I'd like to do literal fighting. I want I want to literally record fights. That's not a joke or a meme
I want to do that. I'm intensely interested in that. I like wrestling
Uh, and there's stuff that I could do and I want to do but I think even like even the, you know
Most individualistic sort of stuff like, you know dry and stuff just being around like, you know
This goes back to what we were talking about earlier being influenced if I was around ben or if I were around, you know
Any of the other draw boys hippo tom here, that would be great. That would be that would be a huge influence
That would be a huge rush. I I totally
Imagine being in the same room as one of those people and just like we are both just drawing together
Like we're not like being like, oh fair. Check out this draw. Check out this panel. How do you think about that?
We could do that, but I'm just saying, you know, in fucking silence in our in our cave. Uh, I got it
Let me pitch a show to you for when pcbhq happens that you and the draw boys all get together draw erotic comics
And whoever achieves the biggest boner for the audience is the winner. What do you think?
I like it
I'm gonna punch you. Let me tell you
I got a I got a notebook full of real creative fun drawings that ben st
Drew while me and devu pretended we knew how to draw next to him and it was it was a great time
You know, I remember those they're all like colored and shit
Yeah, you were just like fucking around with your markers and drawing like masterpieces while me and devu were just like
Like attempting to even make what we were doing like like visibly readable
I remember it was a great time. I'm totally I'm bored with you
Munchie because like I think just being around because there's I I live in a vacuum
All right, I have no friends. I have nobody who's creatively inclined around me ever at all
So I just do my shit and that's it
But like if I was like
In the proximity of someone who is doing shit that I want to do and doing it better
I'd be like I love you, but I want to fucking kill you and it would definitely make me more
More productive and better and I I I suppose the the piece of me podcast would probably still exist by the way
We'd probably just keep doing this shit. I forgot to mention that it would get better for sure
That's why I was saying having it be in person would have a whole new dimension to it
Because we'd have that like personal like real life interactive element to it by the way
So when you say something stupid, I can go over and punch you in the face
All about drawing said here here fucking fastball like like hit you in the fucking skull before you could even react
Tom hippo, let's have like a three musketeers live action show or you know something to that effect where we're all art people who hate ourselves
Yeah, that's good. That's the main that's the main theme here. That's the main theme
We should all just have a show where we just like shit on everybody else who does like reviews and commentary because it's gay
Yes
Okay, fucking tentative plans for for a bunchy patreon
The highest goal is I will never talk about another piece of media in my life
I will never comment or even think about other art in my entire life
You're wasting your time just create your own shit. The best commentary on media is to make better media yourself
Yeah, true very true
I have in my my brain this this imagery of like
The video like all of us drawing on the on the bottom of the screen
Like you can see the backs of our monitors and are like pasty white faces
Illuminated by the screens and then above of us is like like a recording of what we're drawing
And it's just like 10 hours of like complete silence of us drawing
And then above those as there's a there's a gauge for how self-conscious the artist is betraying
And with the more self-conscious they get the lower a noose from the ceiling
So
Yes, wonderful
And just to just to get just to get really real just to get really really really dark and real
You know, please tommy holla first going to be living in a car soon
And his main source of income is the pcp. So if you pay enough to the pcp tom might live
Yeah
You might I didn't I didn't want to go there. I don't want to put any pressure on anybody, but uh, yeah
That seems to be what's in the cards. Yeah
Get a fucking job if you if you want us
I do have a job
If you want us to be able to afford to just put tom up in a house somewhere
And like have him just like nominally participate in pcp content while he works on like his grand vision of 3d art
Support the pcp
That's can't wait. I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm my my my long-term goal
And I was gonna talk about this my favorite my favorite
I think about about the pcp being a big thing is not even so much the the collaborative stuff because that's gonna be great
I love that because I love doing
Shit with you guys
I can't wait to do stuff with munchie and hippo and art things and like all that stuff
But my number one thing is the the the time the ability that like oh, I don't have to
Squall and squander my day away doing all this bullshit that I don't actually want to do because my number one big
Goal is because I started sources loss and it got immediately in rewrite hell and I figured out
Just a few months ago like okay
I know what the story is going to be and now that I know 3d my long-term goal
And I'm going to announce it and I'm trying to hold myself to it. I'm going to learn all this year
Okay, please
Please tom take it from me. Don't announce your comics before they're done. Please don't yeah, I
I fucking beg you tom. Don't make this mistake
Is gonna be good
All right munch, I'll I'll I'll I'll be a I'll be a safe boy for you
Yeah, I'm fucking crying. Speaking of which, how's your comic going munch?
It's going great
I still I still want to see your sketches, man. I'm still waiting
I'll show you everything I have. I'll give you everything
I'll give you everything I have
I'm going to eat batteries for you tom. I'll eat batteries
I mean if you want, I wasn't I wasn't
Anticipating that but hey picture of the investor grader, which is like a great that's against much of space that he's like
Dining against daily, you know
It's just investigable Nate sunglasses on it's like that scenario before but instead of a noose
It's just a cheese grader on
It's like a grindstone that he's just slowly being pushed forward towards and he's desperately trying to draw
Yes
Beautiful god. I mean what else is there to say anyone got any other
specific ideas that want to share anything?
This is good. We covered a lot of ground here. I
PCP olympics. We'll try it. We'll do the long jump. We'll do
We'll do the the monkey bars. Well guys, you know
Here's here's a literal thing that I would like to make part of canon to like force me to do it
It's always been my dream since I played final fantasy eight and zeal like level one zeal
Did a thing in final fantasy eight where he did 100 pull-ups before the game even started
It has always been my dream to do 100 pull-ups just like zeal and final fantasy eight and also to run up
I think it's like 64 flights of stairs just like cloud and sheenra hq at the beginning of final fantasy seven
Those are my true fitness goals for my life if I can achieve those
You just need to find a tall building to do that second one. I'll get tired though. It takes a lot of energy though
No, no, no one on the cold opens of the live action pcp
We'll just do we'll be you doing 100 pull-ups and then you're just the show like you're just like getting like
All right, that would be the pcp podcast for a bunch of internet creators here today
I will do that 100 pull-ups is not even unattainable. Your average person can do it if they just work out and
That's that's how you know you succeed innate if you can do 100 pull-ups before the show and then immediately start and not be winded
Or anything that's well, I'll be winded but yeah
You got it. You got to get better, dude. And so you got to be not be winded
So I'll just put that out there my record right now in high school was 50. What is this?
How does the pcp hq help you with this at all?
Oh, well because I want to set this fitness goal and I kind of have some idea of like a fitness show in some way
I mean, I don't know exactly. I plan to be a hashtag fit boy by the time of
Of hq. So so we can do a fitness show together. Okay. There you go. That's what I'm getting to
I'm so excited to be the only fat pcp member. I can finally be the token fat pcp member
I can finally achieve my my ultimate goal. I can't wait. I can't wait
By the way, uh, this is not a new show
But I want to fully illustrate that stealing your dad's food was easy would be way better if it was in person
It would be like a show imagine filming it in a car
Like imagine filming it with a dashboard cam
Oh, yeah
By the way, by the way, digi, uh, I plan to do p, uh, stealing your dad live, uh at radcon 3 and I have a costume
Oh
Like like, uh, the the the the the the munchie that you see depicted on uh on the the like, you know
The thumbnail is an outfit that I have in real life. Now. I've attained it. I will be wearing it
I will wear a costume as well. All right. Yeah. So so yeah, just imagine
There's no echo and you can see us eating the food
Instantly triple is good instantly. Mm-hmm. It would be incredibly would be great
Yeah, like even if we just made the same content, it would just be better
Like it would just be better done live
And uh, and uh, and then like
In addition to that like the fact that it opens up more opportunities for new things
Uh
Okay, two things here. First of all, ben, I remember you and not unreasonably here
But I remember you being very poo poo of the pcphq idea
Has anything changed for you?
Um, if I was poo poo about it, it was probably well
I mean because like me and me and digi and divu all live together
When we were kind of calling it, uh, pcphq for a while, but we didn't really do anything because like
I don't know. It wasn't
Everyone's doing their own shit, you know, you have to really plan something. Yeah, we were doing our own thing and like
I don't know
So I just I don't think that was what it was going to be
Like that that we called it hq sometimes at the time, but in hindsight that was not pcphq like the the idea of what it actually is
I think is still cool. And um
If I was poo poo about it, it was probably just because I didn't think it was going to happen
Um, but if it did, um, hey
Uh, mom's the word
Excellent, okay, okay. Let's continue talking about, you know, exactly what shows we're planning to do
But also as well, I would like to talk about
Uh, where this thing will be held where we think like like if there is even a time frame like we talked about this digi
Digi spoiled this conversation topic. But yeah, let's let okay for a while as hardcore pcp fans will know
We were thinking that atlanta georgia would be pcphq
But uh, but uh, that may have changed
After after a meet-up that all the pcb guys did in boston famously documented on twitter where I
wore a basket on my head
My jacket is a scarf and and a home stuck t-shirt only in a freezing boston weather gift by the way my god
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's the place where we did a basket. I thought it was like an actual hat. No, that was that was a basket
I thought you had a fez
Please see twitter to compare the physiques of andrew hussey and munch shit. Please, please
Uh, yeah
All right, so so so yeah, uh, I
I I guess I'll describe it the way I I like like my
the way I interpreted pcphq and the change from atlanta to boston I
From the very inception of the idea pcphq was like I'm ready to fling myself wherever this may be
Whenever it may be 100% like like instantly when pcphq is settled
I will I will migrate there like fucking moths to a flame and then uh, you know
It it was shaping up to be atlanta for various reasons
And so I uh, you know, like, you know, I want to see where I will be living
I want to see where it's like
I want to go to atlanta and then I went to atlanta to see ben and which was a great trip
And from when I saw atlanta, it was awful. It was the worst thing I've ever seen my entire life. It was dirty
It was mucky. It was fucking disgusting. I mean every level it was repulsive
I would no wonder bend lids there
Um, I hated it. It was real
shit and uh, all right
And and and then for other reasons I found myself, uh, uh, like like a month or two later in
Or actually previous to this
In boston and boston was a fucking like it was
As close to nirvana as I could get after kurt cobain's death god rest his soul
It was fucking it was pristine. There were very little homeless people
You could actually walk places which which to a west coaster is very strange
We know it actually walked to a location to location. You fucking east coaster ticket for granted. That is pretty sweet
It it was great. And so I
In this boston meetup that happened during christmas
I launched because because I knew that uh, nat and digi were the high profile targets
I had to assassinate jfk style in order to get my whim of a pcphq in boston
So I set out I I I divided and conquered and I started to to convert digi to to my hellish religion
And I went on a three day hard sell to try and get him to move to boston
I was curious about this story because it just seemed one day digi was all of a sudden really into boston
And I knew there was some involvement here, but yeah, go on. I want to know the details here
Digi, how well did this work? I mean it was pretty simple because
Munchie has like well catalogued what I like about cities and we basically have the same
We're both like huge architecture nerds
We're both huge fans of density in cities like of being able to just like go shop to shop
And it's just like an endless series of things to do, you know
And so munchie not only like told me that that was what it was like the night before we went out on the town
But like we then went out and like he took me to the most dense place imaginable, you know
So as soon as I saw that place, I was like, this is the coolest fucking thing I've ever seen. So I'm curious
Place we were all the fucking market place. Okay
Like it's just an it's like literally like 200 stalls of random
Food and other crap in like the span of one block. It's fucking insanity
And uh, I was I was real hyped for that and we we just walked around
The city a lot like we just went to lots of different stores and shit and I was like this place is cool
It's really easy to get around it feels really safe and people there are beautiful for some reason
Everyone looks like
Stock of DNA quality up there, you know, you know
so, uh, yeah, I was just really excited about the city in general and uh, and then like
You know munchie fucking like really sold me on it
And then may was like I've always wanted to live in Boston and I was like, why didn't you never say that before like
Fucking this place is cool. You know, so we both got real hype about it. And um, yeah, it's just there you go
It seems like a cool place to live
Well, that's your convenient for me. That was always my particular
favorite place since my family lives like an hour away
So I think I was always resistant to checking out Boston because you guys had suggested it
but I had always kind of thought that a everyone was just suggesting it for convenience and uh,
b
That I didn't realize it was it's as big a city as it was like I didn't realize Boston's like huge
You didn't realize Boston was amazing. It's like well relatively speaking. It's no
I didn't realize it's like as big as Atlanta though
Like it's as it's as big as it's like one of the biggest fucking cities in the
Second or third city that your city is named after when you settle as America in civilization five. It's amazing
Well, I think in my head boss, I like my vision of Boston is like a tea party like
My vision of Boston was like a very flat place where everything's a tea shop
Everything's a tea shop Jesus fucking Christ
All this stuff Ben described to me about like living in Boston. He's like, oh, I take the train all the time
And I go to hipster coffee shops and like that's
You know the Boston tea party wasn't actually a tea party. We like said, fuck you British people in your tea dumped it all into the water
We're like we're gonna catch you up on the floor. We could be more anti-tea if we tried
I'm aware, but
I just
My whole picture of Boston. I could just imagine you just you hear Boston tea party
It's just a bunch of people in triangle hats sipping on tea
And you're like, that's what it must be now
dude
It just so happens I saw a tv show about a guy who goes on trains around the world
And he was going around in on like the Boston trains and drinking tea and having oysters. There you go. There you go
It looks cool though. It's apparently tinder dating explained it
Was he tinder dating too? This is my vision of Ben going around Boston. It's just like
In his fifties, he's an old man with a weird jacket and he's like, oh, yes. I like
Incidentally, Boston is the 22nd largest city in the United States with a population of 673,000
Yeah, at least it's not the thousand smallest dick Nate like you. Well, you got me there
You just barely made the list
For the record though, I uh, don't even care, uh, if we end up in Boston or not
I will go anywhere because I have I have dedicated my entire being to becoming financially independent
So I can do whatever is necessary to achieve my goals in life. So I will do whatever I have to do
I catch my cold. I will go anywhere. I I just would prefer it to be Boston because Atlanta was gross
Sure. I yeah, I haven't been to like Austin, Texas the best I think because I kind of I'm still holding a dream
A candle for a dream because I want to work with side live with side forever
But also besides that like the anime like voice acting industry is there and I've always had a little bit of a dream
You know ever since I was a kid to maybe get into that voice carry bro
Oh, yes
In the disney bros anime adaptation
And you know what people keep telling me that I'm just like my voice is great and everyone keeps complimenting and I'm like, you know what
People have convinced me. Maybe I am okay at this. Maybe I can do it. You just got to take the root of become famous
And you can become a voice actor
Well, and I mean he's a great voice actor
I mean fucking like Ethan and ila got to do voice acting and fucking some what was it payday too?
Like if you become famous, you could just fucking flex up just express interest in doing it and people
Fucking total biscuit has like a like a starcraft 2 voice pack or like some shit like that. Yeah, that's yeah
All that shit's great. Yeah, that's the dream. All right. Do we want to move on to questions?
I picked out this time like five or a total dawn
Anyone how?
Conclusive statements. I've heard I've heard that boston is quite an english
Styled city because it was like one of the first ones. Yep. Yep. Yeah, and they made it. It is not very well
Yeah, which is why I would like it. It would be like, oh, there's I remember this sort of thing
I remember being lost and confused. This is just like home
It is the epitome of
Yeah, east coast cities tend to be like a labyrinth much in the way that london is but like
Yeah, it's definitely a cluster punk of cities
What's so impressive about boston is that in spite of it being like sprawling and weirdly laid out and stuff like the trains
Take you fucking everywhere. Anyways, like yeah, they somehow have snake them all around to make them work. Yeah
All I'm saying is I would prefer a labyrinth than something like new york, which scares me
It makes me feel like I'm on like chicago literally freaks like flying out of chicago freaks me out
Because it looks like a giant grid for as far as the eye can see and it's fucking disgusting
All I'm saying is there should be from softs next next game should be
Patriot souls where you play in boston and you go around the town and you kill colonial people
And you slay the redcoats and yeah, you use tea to restore your hp
You drop tea to restore it if you drop it
Find an ocean to hurl a box of tea into that restores
Okay, all right day one purchase for me
Just settle out of here. Uh, what is the time frame? Do we think I think did you say you're gonna be moving in may?
I my lease goes up at the end of may so june 1st. I got to be out of here. So uh,
Yeah, and boston's real convenient because it's a six hour drive as opposed to the
18 hour drive that it would take to get to atlanta. It's closer to people
Closer to families. So, you know, it's it's it's also convenient for me
That's cool. I will I will say and I don't I don't want to like shut on anybody's prey
But I will say the only the only negative thing about boston that we'll probably have to like consider is that if we do the bonus
Yeah, I mean
Depending on depending on who we can get there at the right time the right place by scheming it could be a good thing
But um, no if we do like a legitimate business with a pcp
I know that business taxes in the state are very high
You know, I I specifically talked to my dad about this and I mean my dad's not like a genius
He doesn't know business stuff across the world
But he was saying that the the taxes there are relatively similar to neighboring states at least. I don't know whatever
I mean, all these things will have to be accounted for the northeast is a relatively expensive area to live in in general
I think compared to the south, but it's you pay for like you pay for what you get
It's quality. Yeah, it's a good place to live, you know, so it's like worth it
Um, all right. Well, anyway, all right, we're burnt out. I think I think I think the closing thing to say is just like like
This is our dream. This is what we want with all of our fucking heart. This is what we're at least for me
This is what I'm working towards. This is the goal in my life
These are what like pcp is what all of my actions and and and and you know inspiration is leading towards
This is my motivation is getting pcp hq off the ground and meeting up with you guys and being real life friends in real life
To like so I can improve my artistic and personal, uh, you know life
That's what I want with all my fucking heart
I have as you guys know and no one outside knows because I rarely talk about it in public
I spend so much time devoted to pcp issues and trying to work out problems and organize everything
For the sake of making this come true and keeping everyone in contact
Really like the the whole point of making the pcp was so that I could stay in contact with you guys
So I could coldly and calculately use your artistic merits to you know, make my life better
I mean that's that's exactly like at the end of the day. There's a great utilitarian reason for us all to hang out that like
I want to make the best art possible and I want it to be not only the best but like I want it to be profitable and
I see these as
These people I'm speaking to as creative voices who like are not only capable of putting out
Not better things than I can in some ways, you know, like you guys all have skills
I don't have some of you are funnier than me. Some of you are better editors
Some of you have more creative ideas, you know, or some of you can just draw and I can't even do that
So like having you all around like obviously fills in gaps in what I'm capable of and so
Like let's say I want to make a video that the strength is in the charisma of the host
Maybe I'm gonna go straight a script for Nate. I don't know, you know
There's a lot of possibilities in the future
Maybe half the pcp fades into the background
The other half becomes the popular people and we just go straight for you guys, you know
Like whoever's got the prettiest face and becomes famous like I'm down to make this happen
However, it's gonna happen, you know, imagine the munchie and nate pretty boy show. Yeah
Oh, oh, yeah, the two most conventionally attractive pcp members there are. Hey, man
All I'm saying is it's big boy season lazy
Ladies get you one get you one
I'm just saying that like when you look at the when you look at the game grumps or red letter media
Like they've got guys on the payroll who aren't in all the videos, you know, they like red letter media's got josh
He's always behind the camera and those other videos, you know, he's always there, but like I would give occasionally
I would give anything to look at red letter media's like financial breakdown. How they operate behind the scenes
God and the game grumps too. I want to study these things
I'm honestly considering like taking business courses to like understand this shit more
Dude, just get like a how to fucking get a business for dummies book and read it. You you read textbooks
That's what yeah, yeah, I really should just like google and stuff
But yeah, man, I want to cultivate all this
So I'm capable of making my dreams real because I accept responsibility for making these things happen in my life
No one's going to give it to me. I gotta I gotta make it happen
Listen to go talk to Jeff for like hours. Yeah, he just had a chill properly. It's true. We need to know
Uh, I'm I'm so glad I've started this journey with all of you
And I can't wait to see how it ends up when we're all fucking dead in addition Africa
And that's the bad situation we go from that's that's that's the the good end at the end of all this
You don't even want to know what the bad end of this is
All right, all right enough enough faffing around. Let's get to the fucking comment the questions
Uh, I've got I've collected five that aren't shit. It was not easy. You guys need to ask better questions. Told you please always
Uh, first one's from banksinator
He asks do you think there's enough time left in your life to achieve all of your goals slash try everything you want to do
I'm gonna add on to this. Let's let's let's say without the singularity
Like without the singularity, let's say none of us gets to put our brains in computers
Do we have enough time left in our life to achieve all our goals? I I'm 17 years old
Well, I don't know how big your goals are. I mean, maybe you wanted to be like a Mozart and it might already be too late for that
I mean, he's still alive. Could he still be alive? Okay. I'm sorry. Go on. He's trapped inside my 64
I I think definitely like there's no reason I can't continue to be making art at 60
Yeah, I don't I don't have any I don't have any goals that are like time sensitive
Like my goals are just like spend my life making my stuff
And that's it
Honestly, some of my biggest heroes in life. This is gonna sound weird right now
Our guys like Aaron Hansen and like jenke yuger in terms of how they just like created something like huge and just like
You know, they just fucking built an empire and I kind of hope to do something similar to that the pcp is certainly
First thing I want to do
Or my first approach to doing so and I definitely think I can do it
I definitely think I will let me be the first to say no
I don't think I have enough time left in my life to achieve all of my goals and try everything I want to do
I do think that as I get older
I will have fewer like some of those are gonna fall off like some of the shit that I've always wanted to do
I'm just gonna be like, I don't care anymore, you know, or it's definitely too late
um
Too late to become a porn actor
You know
I'm engaged now
And uh, and I'm in my late 20s. So I don't know about that. I can never let you be
Just gotta sit down and have a very serious conversation
I can never be any kind of athlete not that I particularly want to but I I don't know
Yeah, that's that's the thing though. Do you like there's loads of things like I like uh, like, no
Wouldn't it be cool if I had done that all my life, but I don't actually give this there's definitely a part of me like
Like I I like tennis as a sport like as one to play and I've always wanted to learn to play it just to do it casually
Just to have a sport I play and like I've tried to get it off the ground a couple times
It hasn't really hasn't really worked out. I'm really stuck, you know
And I'm kind of feeling like if I don't get into tennis in the next couple years
I'm probably just gonna shelf that, you know, so like that's the kind of the way I look at it
You could be a tp hq tennis court. That's a stretch if you have if if you have a kid
You could you could be a tennis dad and just beat them because I uh, I I'd be doing my my hero scooby 1961
A disservice if I didn't say you can get fit at any age at least up to 60. Oh, no, no
I'm not saying I can't get fit. I'm just saying I don't do I don't like actually want to go play tennis
Like yeah, okay. I I enjoy the idea of it, but then I go out and do it and I'm like, well
That was I guess that was the thing and we're gonna do this tomorrow
Like how long is appropriate between tennis sessions like how
How after how many days do you say? Oh, this isn't a thing. I'm really doing actively anymore
Like do you have to do it once a week in order to say like oh, I play tennis sometimes in my spare time or like is once a month enough
You know, is it like bowling you do it once a year and then you're like, oh, I don't bowl
Well, it's a spectrum and and you can say it at any point on the spectrum
But everyone above it who does it more than you will laugh at you
Yeah, but you'll be legit to anyone lower than any that's true in any uh
Did I did you I was gonna ask you, uh, how was the um
porn manga going dude
It's it's not not really going we've been busy with youtube instead of drawing and we haven't been listening to the stupid
Fucking two-hour podcasts at all
Um, yeah
Turns out they're kind of mind-numbing
Because it's like two hours of random topics and they work really well as digi daily videos
But they do not work as well as like just listening to two hours of me just talk about random fucking shit
Like did you I have never lost more respect or like like like like I've never like thought
Like like I've never thought that someone's IQ has dropped as much as I thought when I heard you say
We're going to listen to podcasts of me
For two hours every day and and if we aren't good at art
But after one month, then we are going to quit and we will realize that it's not what we want to do anymore
I never thought of like a worse or ill-conceived notion than that
Fantastic
I'm glad you recognize it better than I did
I just
Well ben messaged me like oh, I watched your fucking uh one video your mokoto shinkai video
It's an hour and a half long like five times while drawing and I was like, oh that sounds like
I could do that because I listened back to my own shit, you know
But that's that's you you you've like you've put the cart before the horse. I think
Yeah, he's kind of right. Yeah, you confused you confuse the the causal order in which those things occur
Because one listens to digi videos one develops
You channel the skill
When you equip weapons you gain skill points and then once you've equipped that weapon for long enough you've unlocked that skill
That's what digi's podcasts are like just listen to them and you'll be unlocking skills at no time
That's what you think
Like a japanese shrine and he like channels spirits whenever it turns on a new digi video and the flavor of the video is how good he is at art
Okay, oh
Okay, someone is good at math confirmed for me like okay, wait, wait, wait, wait
Never mind. Hold on
It'd be 100 120 hours, right? Like if if it was two hours every day for 30 days
It's 120 hours of drawing practice
I think that would be enough to tell if you wanted to keep doing it or not, you know
Yeah, that's 62 hours a day. Oh, what the fuck ever it's 60 hours
Uh
Point being 60 hours is longer than I would ever play of a video game
It's longer than I would ever do most things, you know, like drawing is a skill that you have to invest thousands of hours in
No, I know but the problem is just to figure out if you like it enough to do to get good like sure
Okay, when you are someone like me who you only really draw like once every six months
You draw one time like you have no real way of gauging your skill or like how fast you could evolve, you know
Anytime I've ever sat down and like consistently drawn for five or six days
The pictures get better because you develop like the most basic skills just by like drawing at all you like realize
Oh, if I want to convey this I just need to put a line here
Like you didn't know that before you tried to draw that pose, you know
So I think if you're trying to draw shit, and I mean two hours is enough time
You're gonna complete multiple drawings
So you're drawing multiple things a day every day you're trying out different poses and I drew some some pretty
Daftly decent porn. I can't post anywhere because it's too fucking extreme. It's like a lolly getting like I've got like a gigantic drill
Just like pulverizing some lolly's cunt and it's
I've got a bunch of shit
All right, we're going down
I don't know where to put it
Like depending on anatomy
Like expression like poses all these things have to have mastery over to make even semi like
Decent porn he's just gonna start with that immediately
Drill in the cut and then work backwards
That's my I mean most of the way I draw is just like I just envision something and I try to recreate it in in art
You know, and I got sure I
I study a lot like I
When I look at pictures I like try to study how they did it, you know, like I'm someone who thinks about art
I just have not practiced it, you know, I haven't tried to do it and like
Because it's frustrating to be bad at something like it's frustrating to draw and suck and like but if you see progress
That it alleviates some of that frustration
You think like oh well the stuff I made at the end of the month the stuff better than the stuff
I made at the beginning
Does that make me feel good enough to keep going or do I feel like
I don't actually enjoy this enough to make it worth making this slow progress because I'm gonna have to do this for years
If I want to be good
I think our art boys here would say you got to stick to the fundamentals. Did you stick to the fundamentals?
I mean, I'm kind of that good at art
But it just the the the you know drawing a stupid piece of shit drawing of like a stick figure is fun
Enough for me to continue drawing occasionally. Oh, yeah, and I mean, I think I've been doing like, you know
I did stick figure comics my whole childhood. I've done I've took every kind of design class like I know all the
I know the art basics. It's just a yeah discord digiprody. That didn't involve any art at all
You know
But yeah, I mean
I think that the main the place I'm at right now is the place where you need to practice a lot to have anything
Competent come out, you know, and so to me it made sense
I don't know why I'm trying to justify this so hard. Let's just move on to the next fucking question
Okay, so the point is did you suck start? He'll never be good and let me also just throw out
That I always wanted to be a scientist and one who uncovers the truths of the world to get back to the actual question here
About things that we'll never end up doing I in my heart of hearts will always hate myself
for like being a guy who's like
Kind of like commenting on stuff instead of actually just making the tangible stuff and maybe one day that'll change
I hope that'll change one day. It's time for a question that only you and maybe I can actually answer
From horse power asks, how do I become more disciplined?
Oh
Okay, that is an interesting whip yourself from the back
Here okay. Here's literally what I did like like things like me and mafava and uh, like weagua
Require discipline to get done as well as like fitness stuff. Here's what you do
Except look at yourself study your behavior patterns. This is what I did recognize your massive personality flaws
And how you have failed at everything you've ever tried to do just recognize
What's going wrong and then just structure your life in such a way that you cannot
Not do the thing like so you completely go around these weaknesses like for me whenever there's like I've got a long deadline
And I've got like a month to do it. I just won't do it
I will fail and I always have my whole life
So instead the fix was that to this was to recognize the times when I did manage to get things done
And the answer was extremely clear
Deadlines deadlines would allowed me to make tbap happen. I mean, you know, ben was involved. I just mean like it helped me
Set yeah, well, it's true. It was true for both of us
Be creative with your deadlines by the way because like my for instance
I have a let's say
The two weeks review a podcast I do for my patrons which comes out every Tuesday on well
It's two alternating podcasts, but they come out on Tuesday right at the start of the day like midnight Tuesday
So I haven't written on my schedule like Tuesday do this podcast
But it's supposed to come out at 12
You know, so really the deadline should be the week before
It should be like do next week's podcast by this Tuesday
PCP is recorded a week in advance for instance, you know, like the deadline for PCP to be recorded is Saturday
And then the release is is eight days later
So like I just think that's really important to achieving discipline is to make sure your deadlines are as
immediate as possible like and if you think you can do with project in three days
Set your deadline for three days and then try to get it done in those three days. Yeah, I I've had a problem with this
because I
Did like a month last year of a video every day and posting the video was the deadline
Like I had to get it up before the end or like if it was like an hour like 10 minutes later, then that's fine. I'll just put it up
um
I've tried to do that again, but like
Understanding that doing one video per day will kill me at the rate at the the the like
Quality level I was doing him
So I say all right two days
But then then you start to slip even just even just two days
Like spreads out into a week like sort of like it accelerates the amount of time you think you have
To fuck around and I don't know how to well. How do I like give a deadline for two days instead of one day?
It's okay to like make it to like try stuff like that and then fail
But you got to recalibrate like for example you give you do heavy editing on like all your videos and stuff
There it's just it's an unsustainable business model to say like okay in one day
Like I'll get one of these Kirby videos done
So like you just have to and here's the other really important thing
Make your deadlines like either publicly available so that if you fail people will give you shit
And you will feel bad and face financial and social repercussions if you fail you have to put stakes
You have to do it. I yeah, I mean I could do that. It's just
The the videos like I want them to come out weekly and I want to make them faster than one per week
Which is unfortunate if I it doesn't work like that like if nobody sees that I finished it
It doesn't feel like I have a deadline. I think uh,
Unfortunately like the the reality of being disciplined is you just have to hold yourself to a high standard because like if you are letting
It be the social standing and everything like you just said Nate like the problem is you have to care enough about that
Like I have a lot of daily shows that come out late all the time
Like you know or like weekly or none of my shows ever come out on time
It's what I'm getting at everything's fucking late and it's because people just expect it from me at this point
So like I've just got a low standard of like
Being me like I don't I don't hold myself to a high enough standard to have discipline is basically what I'm saying
But you you there is a social clout to doing that like people have more or less respect for you for it or trust in you and like
You know that's the thing that's the thing you have to have something to lose if you don't do it
I mean whatever that is for you like right now with we Agua we Agua has been kind of slipping later and later
And like I just kind of like missed a week recently when it was just like I was just too
But like I couldn't do it and I didn't even bother to announce it. I was just like whatever
I'll just like get it out when it comes out
Um and you know like this is me sinking into a bad pattern that I want to avoid
And really the way to fix it is what I've been trying to do to like limit
How much work I actually have to get done and you know like make the video shorter because they're way too long
They used to be like the most popular we Agua by far has like 150,000 views or something
And like it was like the easiest one to make
I only talked for like five minutes about the actual topic and now I'm doing like half an hour
Just like on the base top before I even do the other shit like what am I even doing?
You got to recognize these things and calibrate yourself. You've got to take responsibility
I also think people need to look out for the pitfall of the I missed one and now I don't care anymore
Such as like if this is a big thing for the gym you miss a gym day and you'll be like, oh well
I already missed the day so
The whole schedule my whole schedule shot, you know, and then it's just you never go back to the gym
And like then every two weeks you're like resetting like okay time to go back and then every time you miss a day
It's like you just got to make sure you're in there every day
Like you just got to make sure you got to plan your life around getting in there every day and forcing yourself in there
That's what discipline is, you know
It's it's easy to it's easy to lose lose perspective on something
Like if you're trying to make something into a schedule and like you fuck it up
Like you haven't really fucked yourself because you missed one like you just missed the one thing
Right, like it doesn't have to ruin your schedule, but it's easy to let it do that for me right now on things
I'm really trying to me. I'm working out pretty regularly
But for me, I'm trying to fix my diet and like I'm doing calorie counting every day and like when I miss a date with that
It's so easy to just like get out of the swing of it
But yeah, I mean this whole thing is yeah, I couldn't agree more
You got to you got to keep the momentum going keep the ball rolling
And I think it's also about like understanding who you are and like setting realistic expectation
Because like if you shoot for the moon right out of the gate going from like zero to a hundred
You're never gonna let yourself down everything begins by understanding who you are and what you need in order to succeed
You have to start one of the things that I that I just changed recently
It's like I had a schedule for the last couple months where like I had like
Monday I do something Tuesday do something else because I have a bunch of things
I want to get done and I just I can't switch tasks like that
Like I'm super unit task
Like I have to just get one thing done
Because if I don't if I if I because I had like oh, okay
I'll do a drawing on Monday and that'll do 3d Tuesday and Wednesday and then I'll do a video on Thursday
I'm like none of those things would get done in those one days
I'd start something the next day start something else and so the next day I'd still be thinking about the task
I didn't finish the day before so my attention just got divided and nothing got done
So like this month I'm just like fuck it like I'm just doing one thing until it's done like yeah, even if
Ideally like I'd get the exact same amount of stuff done, but just because I'm
Not worried about something else now and I'm just focusing on the one thing
Like it has a better chance of being and here's and a very good point
And here's the thing that a lot of people miss about this whole process
Be trying to do this be trying to stick to a schedule and then after sometime a month a couple months six months a year
Look back at what you accomplished doing things the way you've been doing
And really think about if it's getting you where you want to go you have to reassess
And decide like that's exactly what I did before me in math
I recognize this is not getting me where I want to go
I have to change things and it's been a great success. So I recommend it's hard
It's hard to change
It's hard to change even if you want to but you just gotta put your priorities in order and decide like what's the most important thing for you
You know like doing things the way you've been doing them or or something else that you need to change something in order to get to
Tom on something similar to what you just said
Let me explain to you guys the enemy of alligators. Like this is this is the reason gators taking so long
It's what I like to call morally convenient procrastination. Oh boy
Go on. Yeah, I rest in peace to boo
Oh no
Um, I will be writing investigator and then and then you know, just just so like like just so happens
I'll get a message from someone like hey, like I want to commission you're like, oh, hey
Can you design my t-shirts or like? Oh, hey, can you can you make a thing for my Kickstarter? And I'll be like, yes, of course
I would love to do that
I would love that with all of my heart and then I can be like, well, okay
I'm not working on investigator right now, but I'm doing this really cool epic thing for the walls my friends
And so I can justify it to myself like oh, I'm not getting this work done. I'm getting other work done
But that's how most of my vlogs come to be actually
Yeah, all everything that's not investigator is worthless. It's much. Yeah. I'm so sorry
This you know, this is a great point and it's like god. I don't know
Oh, fuck wait keep going. I lost track of my thought
All right. Well, I was gonna give another motivation advice. Um, or what the fuck can we talk about discipline?
One of the ways I disciplined myself and this is probably the most effective trick I've used on myself
I'm obsessed with having a clean desktop
Like I don't want to have more than one row of or one column rather of icons on my desktop
So I just keep all of my project files on the desktop so that I have to do them to clean the fucking desktop
Good idea. Like it drives me so insane if there's more than one row that I will literally like
I'll sit down and I'll just get frustrated and edit like all the stuff I have there just to get rid of it
You know, all right guys, listen, I remember what I was going to say
This is where
Objectivism comes into the picture and where okay when you look back on your life on your deathbed
Only you will give a shit about how successful your life was how much you accomplished
Everyone else isn't going to give a fuck about you
Only you have the power to make your dreams come true and only you will have to live with yourself
And what you accomplished when you're on your deathbed
Do you want to look back on your life and say I fucking did it. I was a fucking pimp. I slayed queen
I was the yas boy
I did everything I wanted to do and I worked so fucking hard and I achieved great things in my life
Because people will just placate you and lie to you and tell you that you're doing everything great
And I don't care if you're a fucking 50 year old man
You got like four kids if you want to be I don't know a fucking anime voice actor anything like yeah
You could just say well, I gotta take care of my fucking kids. What am I gonna do man?
I don't have time to make my dreams come true
Only you will look back at yourself on your deathbed and say god damn it. I had all these kids
That's cool and all but I never achieved my fucking dream
No one else is going to give a shit
You have to care about yourself put your priorities first people. I don't say to ignore responsibilities
I'm saying literally sacrifice all sleep until your dream comes true
If that's what you have to do
Whatever it fucking takes because only you only have one fucking chance to make it real one shot the love of god
Make it happen people to seize everything. It's 10 luck 20 skill 50 percent concentrated power
Oh
100% reason to remember the name
Oh, that's beautiful and inspirational. Let's ask you to answer an equally
Great question. Jayhawk DX asks a favorite flavored milk strawberry
Oh, hey, it's it's famous sex havers strawberry milk on the show everybody
Strawberry milk that was hit with a uh an accent twig
Dude is an accent twig a.k.a. some dank weed
Oh, yeah, I like I like skim milk. I like skim milk. That's all I let up slavered milk. You fucking asshole
It's flavored like milk. That's me. It's everyone everyone shits on skim milk. Everyone says. Oh, it tastes like water
I don't care, you know, like I don't mind that at all
It's refreshing. I grew up on skim milk and it and then I switched to
Vitamin D milk because I had a vitamin D deficiency that made me break my foot. So then you'll bend over. I'll give you a
I literally
I never thought this would be the case, but I literally can't go back like I can't go back to skim milk
It's not it's not drinking whole milk as a skim milk boy
Drinking a glass of whole milk is like drinking a glass of fucking whipped cream. I can't it's too much
It's too much. I don't want that. I don't want my favorite flavored milk is benzane
And and and all of you on the inside will know what that means. Yeah. Yeah the the benzane likes the you know
You all know that's what it is
Last question that I have from the patron discord if you didn't know that's where they come from
We get our questions from people give us money and we answer their questions if they're not retarded
Which is rare cygrus asks
Realistically for how much money would you have gay sex with the celebrity of your choice on camera?
Your oh on camera. Wow. There's a lot of factors here. This question. It does. Here's the thing for me
Uh, how I would answer this is like
I mean, I would not choose to have gay sex with the celebrity just because it's for money
Like like I don't think it's like
Unappealing enough to me if I was desperate for cash, I'd be like I'd do it for like a couple grand
You know like why not you need the money, but like I don't need the money
I won't even like fucking run ads from anime companies because I don't need the money enough to fucking do it
you know like so so
You gotta give me a lot of money
It's got to be like six figures for it to be like worth
Breaking away from what I would normally do with my life just to like for just for money, you know
Sure. Sure. That's that's fair point. I'll do it for pennies on the dime
Pick your poison everybody. Um
Yeah, fuck. I don't know. I mean, oh, is the right way to answer this to pick like the most effeminate guy
You can think of is that like the right way to go
He would ask what guy, but if you want to answer you go right ahead
Oh, he just said how much money would you have gay sex the celebrity of your choice on yeah?
I mean, that's the thing. I'm already financially solvent. So it's really not much of a motive
I mean, I'd be sure maybe for like a billion dollars. I'd fucking like why not I guess I'll do it
But who's who's the guy who played call drogo?
Oh, dude, that guy will tear you apart, dude. I don't know if you want to go
That guy, what is it? Are you pitching or catching in this scenario? That's an important question
You know
Fucking hippos like five feet tall and like 70 pounds like the bunch of fucking raping cal drogo
Oh boy, aren't right now. Please
Oh guys here would make for great tv
That that question gave me a riddlin injection and now I can't think I straight
So here I'm gonna ask you guys an even better question a legendary question
You will pray to this question day and day out at night
How can our viewers support this show and the dream of achieving pcphq?
How can they do that? Well, let me tell you what the number one way to do is right now head over on to kickstarter people
Radcon three arena link in the description click on that shit the radcons are our demos
They are the future a proto exactly the right way to prototype demos and you know how well that turned out
Damn, right. Damn, right. Uh, it was incredible. Uh, I I we will literally make undertale two
Sign up right now. That's a fact now. We have to make a video called undertale two
A whole show of like downplaying it be like I don't want to make any promises like
I promise we will make the most financially successful video game that has ever been made
$9,002 toby fox comes to radcon three
Guys, we should make some sort of undertale skit where I play torio. That's a fantastic idea
And then you fuck everyone because that's what that's what she does in my in my head
Okay, but seriously the link in the description people the Kickstarter, please fund it as of recording
We are 50% like 51 or 52 funded
We need money if you want to see the pcp grow and go to the future stuff
Of course go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators
But for the meantime at this moment the best thing you can do to support the show in our future endeavors together
Is go to our Kickstarter and fund radcon three. You will
If you got inspired by any of the stuff we talked about today
Is your duty to support this because this is because support radcon is the only way this will get done
Because radcons are what this is all built right? It's all a prototype to see what it's like to be in person
This this is the light blood. This is what it's good. This is the spark that will ignite the fucking uh fire that is uh
pcphq, this is the only way to fucking do it
Or it's all hype and you'll be disappointed in us for the rest of your life
Oh, no, but hey, you know what you know what there was actually a question on the patreon discord that said at noise bandit
Who whose question was if radcon three fails?
What will you guys do which I think is a great question. It's the kickstarter fails
Well, there's a bunch of ways if the kickstarter fails, we will be very embarrassed
But we will soldier on as always we'll keep doing what we're doing if we fund it
We're just gonna blame we're just we'll just blame the fans because it's the fans who didn't give us money
So it's their fault
Blame arm retrieval uh con the go fummy for siphoning all the hardcore fans away. Very true. Very true. Um
The the point is it could fail and if so you guys have the ability to hold us accountable by immediately
Unplugging, you know, I I want you to hold us accountable to what if it fails. Nobody pays anything
Well, I mean if it's funded and then we just like make a bunch of bullshit like everyone's mad or whatever like we
We totally don't I mean that won't happen
But if it did you guys still have power over us, which I think is a great thing
I want you guys to be in control. I mean, that's that's that's the case all the time
Like I would expect if we started putting out like consistently shitty episodes. We'd lose all of our
Patrons like that's how it works. Very true. Very true. That's the dream
The axe is constantly over our heads ready to drop and we have to dance for you guys
Effectively every week
The pressure is on this is the rare chance for you the viewers
For you serfs to become the sultan
If we do not create quality content, we will be sent to jail kickstart or jail
We'll be sent to the the high security prison
Also, we'll be fucking sniped literally
Bedtrap and we'll be shot every time we respond in our bed
Let's just say obama didn't shut down guantanamo bay and it was a big conspiracy
But he knew there were a couple of boys that just had a spot to serve for them, you know
He had to prepare for all contingencies
And uh, let me let me read one last question here from xylevich. This is a personal one
I'm I'm I'm just hijacking the pcp. Is this from the twitter or from uh, this is from the twitter. This is from the
Oh, Hannah's xylevich. How do they twitter? How do they twitter question us? Oh, uh, you hashtag ask pcp everybody
Uh, and here here we go. Uh, and of course we record on saturday pity question. Here we go. It's nat
I'm a philadelphia sports boy. You're a patriot scum
What do you think of the chances that the eagles win their first super bowl over new england?
This is assuming you watch sports. I am up to date. Uh, this is the worst question
Okay, that's why I said this my buddy john will not be listening to this
But if you ever hear this john, who is okay, this has been a big thing. He's an eagles fan always has been
I'm a patron's boy. I've been lording over him for decades
Oh god, we were just talking about losing patrons now. We're talking about sports. We've just alienated our entire fan base
We're accessing a whole new demographic right now. We're pulling them in. Yeah, okay.
Listen, john at the very end of our piece, the patriots have a zero percent chance of losing this fucking game
It's not going to happen. We will destroy the eagles for all time. There will be no recovery
There will be no more eagles after this fucking super bowl, but then who's gonna play hotel california?
I want to hear my hotel california
Oh god, thank you
I'm so sorry
You're so kind