Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Is this the new duo, Sickly and Hammered?
I think it might be the North Korean one is the Sickly and Hammer, and also the Brush.
If Tom shows up, he can be brrrrbrushed.
He can be brushing us off, because he's not on TV.
He responded when I said earlier that I was going to be late. I assumed he would be back, but I guess it's only been a little while.
The reason I'm on Kazzy's account is because I am at their house, Kazzy's and Munchy's house.
I was going to go back to my house to record, but I have a whole situation.
I feel like I should wait until we actually start the PCP proper to explain it.
Yeah, get your recording going.
Let's sync, I guess.
On the count of three, one, two, three, sync.
One, two, three, sync.
Yeah, no, I started my audacity, and it's still going, so that's convenient.
Okay, I guess this is probably several minutes into the episode now, but welcome to another episode of the Pro Crastinators podcast.
It's me, Ben St, and Gibbon Take, and Tom might show up.
We're starting early, fuck it.
We won't penalize them.
We won't penalize them for us starting early.
If I early, I mean late, because I said I wouldn't.
Okay, as I was saying, so the reason why I'm late and I'm on Kazzy's account is because I have a whole moving out roommate situation, right?
I'm moving out of my place and into the semi-permanent place that I have for a year in two days.
My roommate, my temporary roommate has already moved out.
That guy left so much trash just all over the kitchen and all over the floor.
He was just like, I'm leaving, fuck it.
So he just did.
And like, okay, I guess I'm just, I'll just live in a trash house for a while.
That's fine.
But he also took, and I guess I can't really fault him for this, he took the, his Wi-Fi router with him.
So I have no Wi-Fi at my house.
So if I were to go home and record there, I would have to use my phone as a hotspot, which would cost me a lot in data.
So I'm just doing it here at the Munch House.
Munch House, Baron Munch, Munchhousen.
So you're currently, well, you would be in the new apartment, but there's no Wi-Fi?
No, the old apartment.
Or like the one month temp apartment.
Yes, yes.
The interim one month apartment is the place where...
So the other guy took his, okay.
Yeah, he left early.
He left like a week early and he took his Wi-Fi with him.
So I'm stuck.
I got none.
Oh, wow.
This computer has recording space for 228 hours on it.
That's luxurious.
You think of the podcasts that could be recorded.
We should, we should just record the rest of the year's worth of episodes right now and just make a, make a buffer.
Well, we'll make a prediction.
Okay. What's the news?
Not that we were ever news centric before, but we'll just predict news from the future.
December, December 20th, 2021.
North Korea dissolved by the, by unanimously dissolved by the UN invaded by NATO.
I thought you meant dissolved like they got a big bunch of acid and they poured it all over it.
Yeah. Well, that too.
Well, that, that also.
No, it'll be, it'll be broken up into little tiny pieces and the pieces will be given as gifts to whoever lives in there.
I assume South Korea is next to his neighbors.
Do you think King Jong-un would like dissolve if you poured salt, salt all over him?
Well, because are you implying he's a snail?
He's a slug.
That's fighting commentary.
Yeah.
Well, you know, actually I'm apologized to like slug fans out there.
Apologize to all the North Koreans listening.
I'm just thinking of that dissolve made me think of that scene in the bugs life movie where the snail, the snail was served something with salt on it and his mouth starts dissolving.
He's like, hey, I said no salt and he's dying and just cuts away.
He starts like bubbling.
That was very scary.
He starts like, he starts like bubbling out of his mouth. Yeah.
Hey, I said no salt.
And because of that, well, I didn't find it scary the first time because I'm a movie, whatever.
I didn't know.
But then as a stupid kid, I was like, oh, it's a slug.
What if I put salt on it?
It was, it was devastating.
I felt so bad.
So that's siren, by the way.
A little bit.
Okay.
So you wait, did you try putting salt on the slide?
I put salt on a real slug and it sort of, it was a guest grotesque.
I'm trying to remember exactly what it was like, but it sort of like ballooned out and then burst a little bit.
It's like, oh God, what have I done?
This isn't just fucking around in the fucking yard anymore.
This isn't just kicking over an hills.
This is serious.
This isn't like pouring like molten mercury into a fucking molten mercury wouldn't even be hot.
Molten lead into like an ant hill and like casting a mold.
This is serious sin territory we ventured into.
This is spitting in right in God's eye.
Bug fighters.
Slugs aren't even bugs when you get, when you get right down to it.
Anything small as a bug.
I saw, I saw an enormous, well, it was, I mean, it was a praying mantis, which is a pretty big bug.
I saw a praying mantis last night we were walking around at night going to like 7-Eleven and a big old praying mantis.
Like, I think it jumped off like a telephone pole and it like fluttered under the, under like the wheel of a car.
And then I'm like, I thought it was a bird at first because it's like wings were so big it almost like look bird size in the, in the darkness.
And I was like, well, what was that? I think it was a huge bug.
And I went and I looked at the wheel and it like crawled out from under the wheel well and like crawled up the side of the car and we were like, wow, bug.
That do be feeling when you get the bug big.
If only this were Animal Crossing, I could have made like several thousand bells from this discovery, but alas, it was worthless.
Oh, you know what I did yesterday? I did something cool. I did something I've never done before.
I'm saying it's your mother. I hope not distracting you from the broadcast zone.
You gotta clean up your toys and sit in the living room.
Who's this? Who's that?
You're talking truck and you're fishing price. It's your mother. You gotta go to church tomorrow.
We'll be talking right here.
That was, uh, no one.
Oh, it sounded like someone.
No, no, it wasn't who you're thinking it is.
Of course it wasn't. Yes, it was.
We're playing.
Write that down. Munchies on this episode of the progress. They put in the title. Everyone will come back.
Eleazar, you better put a little munchie on the, you better put a little munchie on the, on the tombstone there and have it blink a little bit. You better do it.
Oh yeah, right, so the reason I'm here I was out of the houses because I did the big, I did like a convention.
Yesterday I tabled at a convention.
Good. Yeah, I did the, which I've never done before.
It wasn't like a real, that was pretty much a real thing. It was um, they have like every year, they used to do.
for the m-m-m-m-m-.. Wait, Massachusetts Institute of Something or Other.
No, Massachusetts Independent Comics Expo. I went two years ago and like I met, I met
Abbey Howard and then I lost my phone so I lost the picture that I got together with
Abbey Howard so that's depressing. Abbey Howard was not there. There weren't as many,
it wasn't like as big an event.
I saw it on Twitter, the Chuck and Smirk went, you know, that guy, that cool guy with the
the comics that are funny.
I saw him tweet that he was like a tweet that implied he was going to go, but I mean, I'm
not a I don't know what he I don't know what he looks like.
So I might have like not even noticed.
Well, he draws himself all the time.
He's got the light little horns.
Oh, yeah, I didn't see anyone with little horns.
So unfortunately, um, yeah, so he might have been there and I just, I don't know.
I don't I don't think he was tabling.
I looked over the attendee list and I didn't see anyone named Beanie Tuesday.
Um, shit, maybe he was there, but he was like listed under his real name and I just
didn't know it's possible.
Maybe he was like the weirdo next to me.
Uh, I was, uh, uh, yeah, so I did the it was so this year they did mini mice.
They called it.
And it was like an outdoor thing.
And it happened to be in what was essentially a parking lot, but it was like a parking lot
that it had these like temporary like walls sort of built around it.
Um, so it was kind of, it was kind of nice and enclosed.
It was, it was literally like right in front of the, the mural from problem sleuth, the
ethnic cheer mural that he has in his office on Twitter that that's, that's a real thing.
Yeah.
And I, I was there.
Um, did you get a picture of you next to it?
Yes.
We took a group photo, me and, uh, me and, uh, and, uh, Kazi and Munchie and, and crack,
uh, and some other unimportant people, uh, uh, Jones was there, uh, if you know, Jones,
um, uh, yes, as can, um, so, so yeah, we got, we got a picture in front of the, of the
mural, uh, and I did, I did the, I sold, I sold comics and I sold RFC K pins and I
got to, I had to do, I sat there for four hours and I had to like pitch my shit over
and over again.
I was, I was amazed that like, like I actually sold stuff.
People actually came up to my booth having never like heard of me and just were like,
what's this?
And I was like, this is the vapors.
It's a story.
It's a comic that I made law and here's my, uh, here's, here's, and then I had to explain,
I had to explain what endless war is.
Like when, as I'm explaining the, the, the, my, my pitch for the vapors was it's a comic
that I made along with some guest artists.
It's a series of vignettes about awkward college kids embarrassing themselves.
That's what I said and it would usually get a little chuckle.
So I think that was, that worked.
And then, uh, the RFC K stuff, I was like, this is based on a game that me and some of
these guys make cause, cause Munchy and Crack just happened to both be there.
And they're like, this is based on a game that we made.
It's an end, it's a text-based MMORPG.
It's, it's, uh, in the, in the game you play as a juvenile delinquent who must join a gang
who in a, in a city of slime, you got to join a gang and you got to get slime.
Uh, people really liked that.
A lot of people were like, what, tell me more about this endless war thing.
Like you made a game in discord.
Wait, are you saying an entirely free tech space MMORPG playable entirely in a discord
server?
And I said, yes.
Wow.
Yes.
I am.
And here's a button of red man's face from the game.
I had to, sometimes it was a kid and I had to tastefully avoid like saying what the gangs,
the gang names are one.
Okay.
One, a little girl came up to with, with her mom, I think, I think it was her mom, a little
girl came up and like picked up the slime corp logo and was like, is this the Illuminati?
And it was like, kind of, and she bought it.
She bought a slime, she bought slime corp.
Uh, what, I sold, I sold a, I sold a bunch of nega slime, the Lord of ghosts and the
nega slime, that one, like, that one in pizza Chan, actually, were the ones that I sold
the most of, I sold a cup, I think I sold one or two, I think I sold one rowdy pin,
rowdy fuckers pin, uh, uh, oh, two, these two kids, these boys, like, ran up and like,
they picked up slime coin and they were like, oh, I want this, oh, I want that.
And the dad was like, okay, and he just bought kids to slime coin, like, yeah, the big like
medallion thing, that's cool, I mean, it looks great.
It does look great.
I think they were the only ones to get one of those, but, uh, yeah, I actually, I made,
and I sold them, I didn't think I was going to sell like anything, um, because I mean,
you know, it's just some like, it's just some local fucking con, just for nerds, basically,
and no one's like, heard of me, uh, but no, like, I brought a dozen, I brought a dozen
copies each of Vapors One and Vapors Two, and I didn't sell out, but I like, I almost,
I like mostly sold all of them.
I think I made, I made like $350, just like, just selling, it was $10 for, I sold the Vapors
for $10 a piece, I offered a bin, this was crack suggestion, that I offered a bargain
bundle, $15 for both, and most people that I offered that to were like, yes, sure, why
not, and I sold the pins and the patches for $5 and the coins were $10.
Yeah, I made like $350, which was, I was expecting to make like 20.
You know, I had, I had, um, I think I had, there were, there were a few names there that
were like kind of big, what was the one, there was a guy like a cross for me, his name started
with an, his name started with an E.
He was, he was kind of legit, he probably, I didn't really look at his stuff, but most
of the other tables that I saw were small, they were small timers, and they mostly had
like zines, like most of their comics were not as, were not like, you know, perfect bound
and like a, you know, printed by like a real printer like mine was.
So I think I had like fairly upscaled merchandise for the venue.
So I didn't feel like other places were charging like $5 or less for their comics, but they
were mostly like much smaller and like not as like professional looking.
So I feel like, I feel like $10 was like a fair asking price.
People seem like, people seem like impressed to like the comics were like as, as big as
they were.
I don't know.
Everyone else and dog shit.
Everyone else bullshit.
I was, I was king.
I mean, what's the printing cursed of like the Vapra's one, um, uh, it was like, I think
because I got like a bulk order of 500, I think it cost maybe like 250 to print a piece
and then it was some more to ship.
So it probably came out to maybe like 350 to get them made.
So you know, yeah.
So like that's upfront costs, but it was paid for by Kickstarter.
I guess if, if you, if you don't have like a Kickstarter campaign and you're just like
investing money into your comic, you don't want to go too high.
Yeah.
Just, just, just like printing them and getting them shipped to me.
I think was like 1800 or something.
So, you know, and then it was, and then like crazy.
Yeah.
And then it was like envelopes and, but you know, doing the 500, the print of the
run of 500 saved money per copy.
So it, uh, it raised my, uh, what do you call it?
My, my profit margins, you know, assuming you, assuming you move product in bulk, I'm
like almost, I'm almost out of Vapors one.
I literally have like 10 copies of it left, like period.
So if I, if I were going to do another con or something, I would actually have to
like get more printed because I'm out.
I just don't have any more.
Um, actually sneakily, I had some, I had some Vapors one copy because I, we did,
when I did the Kickstarter, I did the, the, the stretch goal to like get the card
stock cover.
I had a few printed that didn't have the card stock cover and I didn't give those
to people that bought online because I said I was going to have the card stock
cover, but at the, at the con, I brought the ones that didn't have the card stock
cover because I don't feel bad about selling those there because the person
is like, actually, like if they're seeing it and they're seeing exactly what
they're getting.
So I didn't feel bad about selling those, even though they didn't quite match the
Vapors two, because the Vapors two had the card stock cover and Vapors one didn't,
but nobody, nobody seemed to mind.
Uh, yeah.
So it was pretty good.
It flew by.
I thought it was, I thought it was going to be boring and I thought I was going
to be sitting like by myself with no one, like looking at the tape.
I thought there was going to be long stretches where I just be sitting like,
like twiddling my thumbs.
But no, people like were coming up to me like constantly.
People were coming up to my table.
They, you know, there was just like a flow of people just circling around the
whole place and they would just stop at every table and hear like the
pitch.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm thinking, like imagining, like if it's a mini convention, a
single person could probably see everything.
Right.
If it's just like a parking lot size.
Yeah.
They were probably like instead of like a gigantic convention where your
position may determine whether people ever see you.
Yeah.
That, um, at the old mice, the one that was inside of, um, I think it was one of
like some Tufts campus.
It was something like a university building near importer square.
Um, there was, it was like two floors and there would be like the, the, the
ground floor level and you would walk around and there were tables and then
you would go down and you would go down hallways and in the rooms, in the
hallways, there would be like a big room full of tables and then you would go
downstairs to like a basement floor.
And then that was just one, one big like room with like tables all around.
So yeah, there were definitely a lot more, uh, uh, vendors at the old one.
I guess that, I guess that's why they called it mini mice.
But, um, yeah, I didn't have to pay anything to table.
I literally just sent them an email.
They were like, we're open for applications.
And I just sent them an email and they had, they said, like attach your
comics to the email and I did.
And they were like, okay, you have a table and congratulations.
I would like to do such a thing.
It was fun.
It was more, it was better than I expected.
I thought it was going to be kind of a nightmare.
I thought it would probably be a hassle and I wouldn't sell anything, but no.
All it was, it was good.
I was glad that like Kazzy and Munchy and Crack Hall came and hung out, although
I was honestly like so busy, like giving my pitch over and over again.
Like I didn't even like get to talk to them that much, but like it was okay.
They, uh, they, uh, they were, uh, I think, I think they had a good time.
Oh, I have a funny story.
There was, there was the, the lady next to me, lady next to me was like,
we were, we were setting up and this, this, she, she asked, um, the person,
not me, but the person on her other side, she was like, hi, I'm Liz.
What's your name?
And the person said the name and they were like, okay, what are your pronouns?
So they just, they just, they just, they just, they just, they just, they just,
it was like, she, her, and he's like, okay, I'm any, all, any, all for me.
And then she turned to me and she said, what are your pronouns?
And I laughed and I hope it didn't, I laughed because she asked me my pronouns
before she asked me my name and I didn't mean to, I hope I didn't, but when I
say it out loud, I hope I didn't come off as like a, ha, ha, you asked me my
pronouns, you idiot.
I just thought it was funny that that was the order, but she didn't seem
offended, so that's good.
Uh, uh, they gave me stickers.
They gave me pronoun stickers too.
I put it on my badge and it was very helpful.
If only Beanie Tuesday had been there.
He's, he's the, he's a heterosexual icon.
He would have, he would have had all the he, him stickers made us all proud.
Uh, yeah.
Now, if Beanie Tuesday was there and I didn't see him, I'm going to be so,
I'll be upset.
I want to, I want to, I want to pat him on the back.
Maybe he, maybe he was, maybe he was that person next to me and I didn't even
know how would I even know?
Now I'm so, now I'm curious, does anyone, does anyone know what he looks like?
If Beanie Tuesday was there like tabling, you would have been able to see, did
you get a chance to go check out other people's stuff?
Only a little bit.
No, I didn't really like go around and like look at everyone's other
booths cause I was just, I was busy at mine.
Uh, so he, it is conceivable that maybe there was some table that he was at.
And I just didn't look at it.
Wait a shit.
Now I, now I'm like, oh wait, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Now I gotta go to Twitter, and I gotta go to BeanieTuesday.
BeanieTuesday, chalk and smirk.
Let's see, did he post anything about that?
No.
Didn't he?
In fact, he has a picture of you, and he's like, ah, look at this idiot.
No.
He says, yeah, yeah, this is what I saw.
He posted that this is how I'm showing up at MassMice tomorrow.
Pro cod player walks into GameStop, expects to get notice, and no one cares.
So that definitely implies he was there to table, but he didn't expect much of anything.
It's done in response.
I think it could mean that he was just going to visit.
I don't think it necessarily implies that he was tabling.
Oh, no, he said he got a reply.
Oh, actually, this is another guy.
This is funny.
I see this reply from SnacksYumski.
He says, I didn't know you were tabling at mice, and Chalkin says, I'm not.
So no, he was just going to look or whatever.
Okay, he was just an attendee.
So I might have talked to him and not even know.
That's depressing.
It just so happens that this guy SnacksYumski, I met this guy SnacksYumski.
Munchy shouted at him on the way to meet me at the place because he was wearing a shirt that Munchy liked.
He was like, hey, you, I like your complicated shirt.
And he was like, okay, cool.
And then we met again at the place.
I mean, because he had these cards, he had these business cards that had a little green pyramid with an eye on it and looked like Endless War.
He did some kind of like a radio drama that had this little Illuminati symbol as its logo.
And we were like, oh, we have a green triangle with an eye on it too.
So I just happened to know who this guy is who made the reply that Chalkin, Smirk replied to and said, I'm not tabling.
So that's funny.
And then just by coincidence, that guy left.
This is just weird.
That guy left and then we stayed for a while longer.
And then when it was over, we packed our stuff up and we were leaving and we got on the bus and we were going back to this house.
And like when we were almost here, we just saw that guy again just sitting on through the bus window.
We just passed him sitting on a bench.
We were like, oh my God, it's that same guy.
What the fuck?
There's only one person other than you and Munchy and Kazi and the others.
There's just one guy going around buying everything.
Listen, I don't think it's just because it was in a completely different place.
It was just like, it wasn't like he was just was still outside.
He had left the venue and gone somewhere entirely other.
And there he was.
Oh my God.
I mean, it's the same city.
How far away was it?
It's a big city, Gib.
It's likely, I'm talking about when we saw that guy on the bench.
Kazi's making a face at me.
I can't hear them.
Max.
It didn't finish the sentence.
It's a big city, Gib.
It's not, you don't just, it's not some couple.
You don't just escalation point go to and it instantly travels.
And there's like only two other people in the district with you and you're all fishing together.
No, it's a big city.
It's not some hamlet where everybody knows each other.
This isn't Cheers, whatever.
Wacky stuff.
Well, that's my whole week.
That's all I did this week.
I've got nothing else to say.
That's pretty cool though. It's more than I did.
I did, I made $350.
I'm amazed.
I'm blown away.
I literally thought I was going to sell like two copies.
I was going to sell two pity copies.
But yeah, I guess I had a bit of a moment this week or I had a continual moment that started.
It's an ending moment of bad feelings.
I don't want to talk about the bad feelings too much.
I do want to talk about that one moment I had where I felt okay for a little bit and it was cool.
I went outside and I went for a walk because the sun was setting and I felt like I had wasted my entire day being inside.
It was like, ah, that was a lovely day.
I just watched leave.
I just watched it go and I was like, no, even if it's cold, even if it gets dark really soon, I got to do something.
Otherwise, I'm just going to jump off a bridge.
So I got to go out there and it went out and I didn't bring my phone.
And I couldn't take pictures of all the cool nice things I was looking at.
So I had to just look at them instead.
That was way better, I realize.
The process of getting your phone out when you see like, oh, it's a baby duck.
Get your phone out.
Try and get a good shot of the baby duck and you fail to get a good shot because it's kind of dark.
Well, whatever.
The moment is soured because of the failure to get a picture, but if you don't even have a phone, you can just appreciate the little baby duck that you saw.
And that's how I was feeling.
I was walking around.
I saw a baby duck.
I saw the sky was blue and then it was turning the colors, you know, how sunsets work.
And it was twilight hour.
It was like that exact time of day.
Everybody was sort of leaving the park.
My little pony.
Yeah, from my little pony.
I've heard about this.
And it was, I stood in a big old field and I heard the wind rustle through the trees.
And it was hardly anyone around.
It was getting dark and it just sort of felt great.
Well, you know what?
It felt great in retrospect.
I think I was so depressed at the time I could barely feel anything.
It was just sort of like, you know, when you're like sad and you're like, okay, I got to do something to cheer myself up and you do something.
Or like you just sort of exist.
You stare into nothingness and you're like, well, I don't feel bad or I don't feel good.
I don't feel much of anything.
But I'm sure I'm going to stand here for at least 40 minutes and I did.
Okay.
So, and then did you feel better afterwards?
I don't know.
It was weird.
I appreciated existing in the moment, I guess.
I like the memory.
Sure.
But yeah, the rest of the month or week or whatever has just been a lot of existential thoughts.
More specifically, I don't think there's any reason to do anything.
I can't logically argue for doing anything, nor can I emotionally argue for it.
And I've been trying to think of ways to kickstart myself into thinking that I should probably do anything.
But it's like, nah, I don't know.
I saw your post, your Patreon post about the like, why do anything, Money Spenders podcast, but I haven't listened to it yet.
It's only a little, it's not a Money Spenders podcast.
It's an into the void, like thought dump that I do occasionally, which are sort of unedited off the cuff thoughts.
But maybe it would be interesting, but usually I was just sort of like, I wanted to write like a video essay about why do anything?
Because I was watching video essays and I'm like, that's cool how they can like take a thing and explain it.
And I can hear it.
And I wanted that.
But I guess I had to make it and then I had to think, how do I do that?
And then I realized that the question is kind of flawed.
I don't know.
It's hard to explain because I failed to figure out how to explain it.
And so I'm just like, ah, you know what?
This idea of trying to do stuff is itself impossible.
I don't know if I follow that.
I don't really know what I'm talking about either.
The crux of the thing is there's a voice in my head that's saying, yeah, but why would you do that?
Why would you even do anything?
And I can't like beat that guy in a debate.
That person constantly is coming up whenever I'm thinking, maybe I could just do, maybe I should or maybe I could do something.
And then they're like, give a why though.
You don't even know why you should do anything.
You can't even answer that question.
And I'm like, damn.
Well, I've had that thought and I've had that same feeling of like, I could do something.
But why?
So I know what you're talking about the.
I think, okay, I don't know.
I don't know if this is like, I don't know.
I don't know if this is like healthy or good.
But in the past, when I have, when I have done things, it has been, it has been because I feel like I, it's not like, okay, I'm going to decide.
I don't feel like, hmm, I think, what if I did this?
Okay, maybe I'll just, I'll just try and do it and just see what happens.
It's, I feel like I must do it.
I have to do it.
They have, I have no choice.
This is how I feel.
Oh, the other, I guess the other thing I was doing this week is I have really, I have really been getting a lot done on the phantoms revenge.
And I, I, I had hoped maybe to have it done this month, but that's definitely not happening.
But it's getting, it's getting pretty close to done.
And when I work on that, I feel like, I feel like, oh, oh, there's so much work to do.
Oh, I've worked so hard on this and I have so much more work ahead of me.
And it's so, it's so demanding.
And it's so, it's such a tall order.
It's such a, such an amount that is being asked of me.
But then I'm just like, well, it doesn't matter.
I know I just have to do it.
I have no choice.
I feel, I feel a compulsion that will not let me be satisfied until it is done.
So no matter how long it takes, it must be done.
So I might as well do it.
I don't know how to get that.
I feel like, I mean, I don't always feel that like that, but just project in particular makes me feel like that.
But like sometimes I have that as well.
Like, oh, I've got to get this thing done.
But I think the things I'm attribute, like the, the, I've been streaming recently, just video games.
And I've been sort of, it's been kind of fun.
And I think that is where I've latched on to, I've got to do this because I said I would instead of the far more difficult time consuming, creatively draining,
but also like way more fulfilling stuff of like creating comics and working on the, you know, stuff relating to all that.
And I've, I keep thinking, yeah, but what if, like, there's, there's layers to this, this evil demon that says why, the why demon.
He asks why and I'm like, well, it doesn't matter why I'm just going to do it.
Like if I punch through that hole, he's like, well, you could fuck up.
And it would be really embarrassing and terrible if you, you know, and think of all the reasons that you suck.
And I'm like, oh no, this ammunition used against me.
It's very powerful.
It's super effective, you might say, just like Pokemon.
Now I understand.
So like, I'm taking damage from that.
And I'm like, a lot of the time, like the, the way to like, just stop feeling bad is to get something done.
And I know that.
But instead, I, I got something insubstantial, unsubstantial, unimportant.
I got something unimportant on like a Super Mario stream.
I played Super Mario one and, and that was fun until I got stuck and I was tired and I couldn't beat world eight.
And I'm going to, oh, I was like, I'll do another stream to finish it later.
And I was saying during the stream, oh, you know what, wouldn't it wouldn't be fun if I like beat every Mario game one after the other.
That'd be cool.
But like a bunch of streams and like making big promises about streams I would do, even though not like a very small amount of people care about those.
And I don't even care about them because I, I'm not like entertaining enough, I feel, to be like a good streamer.
Even though people find value in it, it's like, I feel like I'm using that as like a, like to let the pressure out of the valve.
That's building up when I'm not doing anything.
And then other than that, when I realized that that's what I'm doing, I'm like, oh God, I'm focusing on doing these streams instead of focusing on doing the stuff that's good or better, at least.
Then I, then I feel really bad.
And that's when I go all catatonic and I get all, I don't know, like hollow and like static dark noise music plays in my head that doesn't exist.
You know what I mean?
Like the sort of like doomer anthem that I've never heard before, but I know what it sounds like, which is just like a low rumble and like crackling and like screaming banshees in the distance.
I just feel that vibe.
And then I lie on the floor and that's it.
It sucks.
I can't even cry.
I wish I was like emotional, but it's not even that.
That sounds like, that sounds like depression.
That is depression.
I mean, I'm not one to self diagnose, but it certainly sucks.
Well, I have, I have, I have felt that way before.
So insecure.
That's true.
No, I, I'm mostly not understand.
I don't, I don't know if I have the, the, the doomer anthem banshee wailing experience.
Well, that was just sort of like a way.
The metaphor.
I feel like one of my imagination goes, I'm like, God, I just, there's like so.
There's like so, such a large like, like a screaming, but I'm not screaming, you know?
Like I could imagine the sound my mind would make if it were a song that other people could listen to.
But my face is totally blank.
I'm completely motionless.
It's a, it's like that woe jack with like the black scribbles all over it.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I know, I know that one.
So like a, and then occasionally, very occasionally I will draw like a little sketch, sad skeleton comic and post that on Twitter.
Oh, the one where he's looking into the puddle.
Yeah.
The little puddle one, the please validate my existence studios, little guy.
Yes.
And things relating to that.
That's bent stuff.
And that sometimes gets me out of it actually.
Maybe I should do more of that.
Maybe you should do more of that.
Sometimes when I come up with like a doomer like vent comic that is like, it's, it's sort of the absurd and like stupid in a way that I actually makes me laugh and makes me feel better.
So I should probably do that.
There's so many things I feel like I must be doing with my time.
Yeah.
Every time I'm not doing them, it's, it's, it's the worst feeling, which is no feeling.
People feels bad and then I end up feeling nothing.
People keep asking me to do other things.
People keep asking me like Ben, please make more Winnie the Pooh videos.
Ben, please make Sonichu 103.
Ben, please make another Nuzlocke.
Please make champion chapter two.
Please make, please make papers.
Ben, please stop peddling your toddler leftist beliefs.
Your toddler leftist beliefs.
Yeah, that's a big one.
People ask me that a lot.
And I have to, and I have to, but it's, it's kind of a relief.
It's kind of a relief that I have Phantoms Revenge.
Phantoms Revenge is my rock in these, in these hard times because they don't know.
They don't know what they want.
I am the artist.
I, my job is to anticipate what they want, the people before they want it and then get, and give it to them and surprise and amaze them with their own delight at having received such a thing.
And Phantoms Revenge is that thing.
And I know that they don't want me to do those things.
What they really want is for me to finish Phantoms Revenge and blow all their minds with the masterpiece that it will be.
So when they, when they, when people tell me, Ben, you should do this, I don't even have to think.
I don't even have to think about respecting their opinion because I know I have faith in my, in my self and in my heart that I, what I am doing is right.
Like, even if it spits in the face of what they, of what they want and what they wish.
Who gives a fuck?
That's pretty good.
I have, I have, I just want to bring it up because the way, in terms of like things I should be doing, it's, it's very clarifying.
It cuts me through the bullshit.
At any given time, I know what I should be doing is finishing Phantoms Revenge.
It's the only thing that matters.
If I'm not doing that, well, I know I'm fucking up, but at least I know exactly how I can fix the situation, which is to get back to working on Phantoms Revenge.
Yeah, I wish I had like a rock like that, or at least I wish I had like people asking things of me because I don't really have that.
I think the most people ask is like the occasional old hypocrite fan, but that's stopped for a while.
I don't think people really ask for those to come back.
The sentiment's still there, I guess, but like, oh, and the podcast, that's the thing people are asking.
I'm like, that's a joint effort and me and Nate both have to get together to do that.
And I guess neither of us want to.
I feel like whatever.
But like, when it comes to my own projects, nobody's like asking me, oh, can you do more of this or that?
I'm like, I'm left to completely my choice.
There's no nowhere that's been like, I don't know, tugged at.
Nobody's clamoring for me to like finish Clarissa Gunsmoke, even though I know people did like it when they saw it.
And I know it's good.
I just need to do it.
But like, nobody seems to care about these issues.
Now I feel bad because I meant, I still haven't read it because I said I'll read it when it's finished and it hasn't been finished.
No, but like, that's fine.
I'm not like trying to impugn people for like not nagging me for stuff.
It needs to happen naturally.
I guess I just don't have enough, what do you call it?
Like, I'm not a high priority in people's minds of like, I got to see the next give and take comic of this or that.
They'll just be happy when it happens and I'll be happy to make it.
Well, I mean, all right, let's let's let's let's let's interrogate that thought for a second.
I mean, no, no, no comic, even like the most famous comic artist or whatever isn't like a high priority in anyone's mind.
Like no, like nobody is like waking up and being like, oh, man, I wish the next issue of Brian Leo Malley's snot girl was out now and like I need to go and like the first order of businesses go and like ask him when it's coming out.
Right.
I don't mean like priority as in like some individual person's most important thing.
But like, I don't feel like I'm enough of or at least my work is not of enough of a priority higher up on high up on anyone, anyone's priority list for them to like decide to ask me about my comics.
Well, I mean,
Well, speak, I mean, speaking of your comics, me and me and Cassie were talking about the Lord of Ghosts yesterday and Cassie told me that they have.
I was I was a bash because Cassie said they've started working on theirs and I have not I have not started on mine.
But I guess I guess I had a I guess I have to get that get that going soon.
I probably I probably don't have enough time to get it done before the move.
So maybe I will maybe I will have to take a break.
I don't want to take a break from phantom's revenge, but maybe I will take like a.
You'd probably get it drawn in like two days or so if I really if I really bust my hump.
Let's take it.
Maybe I can do that first thing after I after I get all settled in to my new apartment.
So I guess I I mean, the thing you're doing now, I mean, I guess I assumed you were you were focused on, you know, Lord of Ghosts fulfillment stuff, getting the zine made and so on and so forth.
Yes.
I've put off certain things that I really could have got done.
I could have printed the red man comics by now.
Yeah.
I made the little test print and I did.
I just haven't got around to like fixing the PDF because I need to like download.
I need to pirate a new PDF editing thing is the thing I had like exploded Adobe caught me.
Mm hmm.
So I have to do that bullshit again.
I just hadn't felt like it.
And then the Lord of Ghost plush samplers here.
I could order the rest.
I guess part of me has been like, oh, what if somebody wants a plush and they haven't mentioned it and they they're willing to pay for it later?
You mean you mean you're thinking like, oh, what if what if I need more?
What if I need to order a few extra?
That's basically the sort of thing.
I mean, I could I could have done that.
Like I could have like figured out if anybody wanted any by asking or if anybody had changed their mind.
I don't know.
I could have done like graphs and management for the Lord of Ghosts.
I mean, start a backer reward to your stuff.
I just haven't.
If I if I were you, this is just my practical two senses.
I would I would plan to have some extra because like probably there will be people in the future who would be like, do you still have any more of those plushes?
Can I can I get one?
Or, you know, if you if you ever do if you ever do like table at a con or something, that's that's merch.
That's merch to move at something like that.
I did my Kickstarter is all I, you know, I ordered in bulk so I could get a price cut at the price breakpoint and then I would have extra stock to sell later on.
I'm always planning.
I'm always planning for the future.
Yeah, I guess I just just buy a few extra.
I did make a little over the what I needed in the Kickstarter.
Yeah.
Right.
So yeah, I mean, those are going to take a while to get made anyway.
So I should order them as soon as possible.
Yeah.
In terms of the the Lord of Ghost comic itself, I need to wait for the artists to get their things finished so I can put them all in and make that PDF finished and then get that printed.
And I have the pins already, which is good.
And then after that, it's a it's a simple making a hundred billion like signatures and and doodling on some of the copies and then getting all the packaging and logistics and sending them out.
Oh, man, speaking about speaking about the Lord of Ghost, I just want to about like, OK, yesterday, so I was tabling and I was talking about the pins.
I was explaining Endless War and sometimes people would be like, Oh, what's this?
What's this?
They would pick up a pin and be like, what's this?
And like, yeah, we sold.
I sold all three of I just brought like a couple of each pin because I assumed like no one was going to be buying like a ton of any one thing.
And I was right.
But I sold all I sold all three of the Lord of Ghost nega slime pins that I brought and people asked like, oh, this is cute.
What is this?
And I had to be like, I had to explain the lore of like, why did the Lord of Ghost summon the nega slime?
What was the nega pause?
And did you really need to do that?
Yeah, several times.
I got I had asked and like the old this is the only way I can explain it.
I have to take like a whole but but it was but like telling telling the story.
I think I think twice I had to go through the whole like, yeah.
So the leader of the cop killers and the leader of the rowdy fuckers, they were running, they had a mayor election.
But the Lord of Ghost, who is a stay dead, which by the way is someone who decides not to revive when they get killed in gang violence.
The Lord of Ghost, he ran as a spoiler candidate and he won the pity vote.
So he actually got elected and he used it and it was basically that scene from Ghostbusters 2.
And both times I explain it like the people that were asking like, they were like laughing and stuff.
They were like, chuckling as they were having a good reaction to hearing like the whole narrative like condensed just how fucking absurd it was.
And I was just like, I don't know.
It's like, man, that sure was a that sure was a weird time in history.
It still makes a good story, I guess.
Yeah, people really like that smear that smear pin that and one like one like old guy, he came up and he just like picked up Levy Jevy.
And he was just like, I don't think he even wanted to know what it was.
But I think he asked me like, what's the and I explained what a stay dead was and he was like, hell yeah.
Oh, God.
Clean up your toys.
Your hot wheels are all over the living room floor.
You're right.
Clean them up or you're grounded.
You're right, dad.
I stepped on your hot wheel.
It hurt my footy.
That's funny, dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm feeling like toeing out Benjamin because of your hot wheels.
He's recording one of his podcasts.
What are you in there?
I don't care.
He's got to do his part in the household.
Stop fighting, mom and dad.
Stop fighting.
This is why I'm here with Jeremy.
Jeremy, I see you.
He's got to do his part in this household.
He's got to get a job.
I don't care if he's five years old.
No.
He's got to put his foot in the hot wheel.
He's got to have money.
He's not making shit.
It's not making shit.
It's not true.
I'm straight edge, mom and dad.
I'm a pro gamer.
Thanks.
Don't get divorced, please.
They're getting divorced.
Mom and dad.
Sure are our characters.
Man, they're not even my real mom and dad.
They don't have to listen to them.
What are we talking about?
Lord of ghosts.
Oh, yeah.
Pins.
Levy Jevy.
That one guy.
Oh, yeah.
I think that guy, I explained that a state editor is someone who's just like giving up on shit.
And he was just like, yeah, cool.
I want it.
Nice.
Oh, man.
It was really, it was really weird.
I said this before, but it was just so weird having like a little kid be like, what's slime
core?
Like what's a cop killer?
I was like, uh, well, let me try to explain without using any F words.
What a delight.
What a treat.
They're in the server.
Well, actually I don't.
Oh, this was my beat.
Like, okay.
If eventually I quickly realized like, I need to not have to explain this over and over.
So I wrote, I wrote like a little sign that was like endless war, a free text based MMORPG
playable on discord.
And then I wrote like the discord link down.
So anyone that wanted to, to like check it out, I could just point to that and be like,
that's, that's the link.
If you want, I had stickers.
I had a bunch of stickers that the ones that smear had had designed that had the discord
link on them.
And like anyone that bought a pin, I was like, here, take, take the sticker.
It's, if you want to check the game out, it's got the, it's got the link on it there.
So for all I know, some of them did go and like showing the server after and be like, yeah,
I bought this, I bought this pin that's like a pink screaming face and a clown hat.
And like, I don't know what, I don't know what it is, but it gave me this sticker and
it had this discord on it.
So what's going on in here?
I haven't, I wonder.
I used to go around and stick those stickers just on, on like walls and on like posts and
stuff.
And I think one or two people did just like join the server just based on seeing like
stickers around, which is pretty funny.
It's, I really like the meme of it just being an actual URL, but printed in like, you know,
it's not a, it's not a special URL where it's actually a name like a company or a brand.
It's just like a discord URL with random numbers and letters.
Yeah.
MTS, MTSRX, like ZK or MK.
It's, you can say it phonetically.
You can say it's, it's like Mount, Mount Sergic or something is the, is the random URL for
the server.
Yeah.
I like, it doesn't explain itself.
It doesn't have a name.
It's just a random like a like QR code or, or, or URL that you can just, if you're curious,
you can just type it in and you will arrive at this mad magical land of gang violence and
slime.
I'm thinking imagine, like imagining, you know, those little rubber arm bands that you can
get like mass produced.
Yeah.
Kind of uncomfortable.
With the swastika on it.
Imagine having the, yeah, imagine having a discord logo and not, no, no, the discord
URL on one of those bands.
Oh, like the, like the Livestrong like bracelet.
Yeah, those things.
Yeah.
I made a shirt that is just the, the, the QR code.
I don't think anyone bought it.
Cause like, I mean, why would you want to wear a shirt that's just a QR code?
But it would be funny if anyone did.
If anyone wore it and they were, someone was just like, whoa, let me scan your shirt for
a second.
Whoa.
Slime.
Uh,
It just makes their phone green.
It's like, it's like, um, yeah, it's just like the green just like extends down their
hand and like covers their, like, like in one of those, like in a gushers commercial
where like you eat the gusher and like it turns your whole body a certain color and
then your head turns into a fruit.
It's, it's like that, but it turns you green and your head turns into endless war.
And you, and then it just pops like a grape and slime just goes everywhere.
Hell.
Yeah.
Do you ever see those old gushers commercials where their heads turn into fruit?
I don't know.
I think I understand the, the, what it looks like though.
There's probably something similar.
Now those, now those would make, if those were color graded correctly, that would make
some pretty good endless war propaganda.
Gushers are very RFC K core.
I would say they're pretty slimy.
Um, right.
So the lord of ghosts.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, gotta, gotta get my fucking, gotta get my fucking comic done.
Soon, soon when I'm, when I'm, when I'm moved, being in like a temporary apartment
has been really stressful and it was, it took me a while for a while.
I was like feeling too like insecure about like my, my place in life to like get a lot
of done.
And then like halfway through the month I was like, no, Ben, just get, get a fucking
grip on yourself.
And then I've been, I've been really cranking out work since then.
Uh, moving into the new place where I'm like, yes, I'm settled.
I'm here.
I don't have to move for another year.
I'm good.
That'll be like few and hopefully the people there won't just fucking leave garbage in
the sink and all over the kitchen and like get fucking clouds of fruit flies fucking
everywhere.
Uh, one, one hopes.
Terrible, just terrible.
I fucking hate this guy.
Oh, but he's gone now.
He's gone.
He can't hurt me.
Oh yeah.
Speaking of moving, I have to move out of my cool apartment that I've been in for the
last bunch of months, which is pretty upsetting.
Yeah.
You told me that that was, that arrangement was, was over.
It was only going to, at the beginning they said it would maybe last till July.
So I guess I'm lucky that it lasted longer.
Yeah.
Um, but the, the cool deal that I had, uh, is I now have, if I had to, if I were to
stay here, I would have to pay very big money that I don't have.
So I have to, I guess I'm just going to move back with my parents for a while.
I'm trying to look for another place.
I've no, I, I don't know.
It's, it's a, when I've got all this load of ghost stuff to do, I don't really want
to be moving around.
I want to get all that finished at least first.
Yeah.
Oh, side note, but I have the, the, the Road to Radcon books are printed.
I just have to go pick them up from the printer, but I guess I won't do that until
they're not open the weekend.
So I can't get them now.
I can't get them on Monday, but I'll probably just wait until Wednesday when I, uh, I'm,
I'm not going to have to move anymore.
I don't want an extra box to have to carry around.
Um, yeah.
How, okay.
So your apartment, how, how was, I don't know, how was the experience of like living
in your own place?
How did you feel about it?
Aside from feeling sick quite often, uh, it was great.
I like the, uh, I like the.
The cooking ability.
Hmm.
Cause it's always been possible to cook at home, but like dad always cooks.
Yeah.
A lot.
He's like, got the fridge filled with like future ingredients.
It's like difficult to like plan around him.
Hmm.
I'm going to try anyway.
Cause like I've learned a lot of, of cooking things.
I've tried to learn lots of different recipes.
Um, and I feel like I, I, I can do it now.
I can cook things.
I can, I can have a bunch of stuff in the fridge, ingredients and be like, okay, I can
put something together and I can actually make it work without really needing a recipe,
which is pretty cool.
Um, cause I know like, I know some basics.
I know how, how to cook an onion until it's soft.
I'm like, that's that.
Then I, I finished the onions done.
Now I put something else on it.
What?
You put a can of tomatoes on it.
Spread some peanut butter on it.
No.
Okay.
Why would you do that?
Who knows?
You experiment.
You cook an onion until it's soft.
You know, you know what?
I laugh, but I've seen that, that, that the Townsend video of him, they did used to, they used
to just bake onion.
You could just bake an onion in the oven and then eat it and apparently it's good.
I mean, it's the thing you eat.
So at some point it'll be good.
I mean, I mean, I've never eaten just an onion.
Apparently you can do it, but that's not even like, that's not even what I mean is like,
like for basics.
Cause like before I know how to cook, you follow a recipe in the numbers.
They're like, Oh, you do it for 10 minutes and you do this for two minutes and you turn
it over after four minutes and I don't really have a sense of like when something is about
to be burnt or whether it's good or whether it's undercooked.
I just follow the numbers.
But now I kind of get an intuition.
I intuitively understand when something is like, that's done.
I think I can, I can see a lot of things when they're done.
Not so much in the oven cause I didn't have an oven.
It was mostly frying and boiling and stuff.
This whatever I can cook now.
If my, if my new kitchen, I would be very upset if my new kitchen doesn't have an oven because
how else can I cook my delicious frozen fried chicken wings that I buy in bulk from Costco?
That's my new, that's my new dietary staple.
I love that shit.
Yeah.
The cooking has been good.
The independence.
Well, it's not so much just the independence, but the ability to like dress how I want.
I've been trying on some, some more feminine clothing and it's not embarrassing because
I don't have to worry about people seeing me.
And I've sort of built up some courage to go outside and a bit more feminine clothing.
Haven't gone out in a skirt yet.
Not really ready for that, but I have gone out in leggings and stuff.
Do you, would you, I mean, I guess at your parents place or where you're at now,
are you near like a city, like a, like a center of, do you like walk to like the store?
Do you like walk down the street and like go buy some?
I walk down the street to the high street to get food and groceries.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
I was, I was just wondering, I was wondering if like you're in like a place where you're like going out
and walking around people.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, when I go to get groceries, it's quite a busy street.
And the only other time I really go out is, is to like walk in the nearby park.
And there's always a bunch of people there.
So it's like, yeah, it's a nice park.
I probably, I don't go on enough walks.
Walks are based.
Yeah.
I used to justify walks like, oh, I need to walk more, but I don't want to, but I could play Pokemon Go.
And as soon as Pokemon Go stopped being interesting, I stopped going on walks.
So that was a stupid idea.
Yeah.
But it did, it did make me realize that the walks could be fun.
So I have been going on more just to experience like fresh air on my face.
It was nice.
I used, I used to go, I used to go on Pokemon Go walks and now my phone is so old and shitty.
Like I basically can't do it anymore.
So I don't go on walks.
You know, it helped, it helped.
Going on walks helped me lose weight like before, like when I, when I lost all the Radcon 2 weight,
or Radcon 3 weight rather.
So I should, yeah, I should probably walk again because I need to, I've got, I'm fat again.
Although I think I have lost a little bit of weight since moving because I've been very,
I've been very strict about keto this month.
And I think it's, I think it's, it's going, although it's not going as fast as I would like.
Oh, but so I guess, because I haven't, I haven't been walking and because I have,
I have not been lifting this month because I had to disassemble the rack.
I had to disassemble the exercise rack and it's sitting in pieces now.
And I'm not, I get, after I move again, I can reassemble it and then I can use it again.
I was on such a roll too.
I was on such a roll.
My squat was actually really good and now it's shit again.
I lost all my progress.
God.
You just gotta find heavy things and pick them up and put them down.
No, you have to do the one way.
You only do the one thing.
You put the bar on your back and like a crumbly old building.
You pick up a brick and put it down again over and over.
Pick it up and you throw it across the courtyard and you go find it and you catch it and you wind up
and you throw it the other way and you just go back and forth until the brick breaks
and that's how you know that you're strong enough.
You just gotta find.
You, you, you pick up a brick and with two hands, like pull it apart.
And once you can pull it apart, then you're ready.
You're for, you're for whatever it is.
You just, you just gotta find a calf.
You gotta find a newborn baby calf and carry it on your shoulders and go for a jog.
And then as the calf grows and becomes a mature cow,
you will get stronger and stronger until you're eventually just running around with an entire cow on your shoulders
and you're the strongest guy.
And then you can occasionally suck on the teeth for energy.
Absolutely.
It's mid-run.
Yeah.
A female calf is recommended.
When she gets heavy enough, you're going to need, you're going to need that milk.
When she's getting to the milk producing age, you're going to need that, the lactose in that milk.
Let me tell you, that's an essential part of the, of the strategy.
Oh God.
Delicious.
A man in his cow.
It's just getting ripped.
You carry the calf from birth.
Every so often you have to put it down in a field so it can eat, so it doesn't starve to death.
And you just walk across the entire earth slowly that the cow grows and it gets used to jumping on your back.
It never.
You have to keep getting stronger.
It's the only way it gets around is because you need to exercise.
That's like a story.
I think, I don't think it's Hercules, but it's some Greek hero.
That's like the story of how he got fucking super, super strong is because he did that with a cow.
I don't.
It's the origin story.
I want to.
I want to read that.
It's a superhero origin story.
Wait a minute.
I can.
Hold on.
Hercules.
No.
Berkulosis.
Greek.
Carry.
Poseidon.
Strong.
Perseidon.
Posturer's name.
He was just a real resurrecteds.
Winning 32 wrestling competitions in the ancient Greek Olympics.
According to legend Milo trained by carrying a calf whining from its birth until it became
a full sized ox.
Milo of Croton.
Just a real dude who really did it.
It really happened.
He really ran around with a full size ox on his shoulders.
That's his history.
Dang.
The past really do be better than us.
You know, I said, I'm not going to phrase it as, if this were, if that happened today,
this would happen.
Because for all I know, something like it did happen.
But imagine if he was like, like he gets famous from winning all these wrestling competitions
in the ancient Greek Olympics, and it's like, man, everyone knows my love, Chris.
So imagine he like, I can imagine that he like, sold fucking like scrolls.
He's I imagine he sold some kind of like self-help table like like the Milo method.
Like, no, like, like he has it like print.
I guess they didn't have movable printed type.
So I don't know what like, I don't know what like the most economical way of like disseminating
some sort of like written material would have been an ancient Greek, but there must have
been some way to do it.
And I wouldn't be surprised if this guy literally like sold pamphlets.
It's like the Milo method for getting fucking ripped because like, what else do you do?
What else do you do with when you're a world famous athlete who's run 32 wrestling competitions
in the ancient Greek Olympics?
Like what what is the point of that?
If not to somehow monetize it?
I mean, I don't know much about ancient Greece, but were they a capitalist system?
Did they work like that?
I mean, they had they had money.
They did commerce.
It's not like they wouldn't have understood the concept of like farmhand on most of the
time.
And then for fun, they'll get together and see who's the strongest.
Do you do you think that there was just no money to be made?
Like it was all just for no, they must they must have been so I mean, I don't I'm saying
I don't know.
So maybe but like my gut reaction is that they they weren't so cynical back then.
Maybe they would have been.
I think I think that the the almighty dollar, right, the value of money is not a new, you
know, they understood the money.
They had money.
They did commerce.
Like if he didn't, I mean, maybe people just didn't have like strategies for capitalizing
on fame.
I guess I guess my thought process is like, I don't think he would have done it for money.
I think he may have done it for fame and glory.
Like I am the strongest and you will all be my pupils and they're like, oh, Pog.
Okay, I could I could believe maybe that like he's, you know, he's getting into he's getting
into all this wrestling competitions and he's like, he's really good at it.
He's the best wrestler and everyone's like, dude, you should do the Olympics.
And he's like, yeah, I should do the Olympics and he does the Olympics and he's so good
that he wins 32 competitions over however many years.
But, you know, you can't do that forever, right?
You're not a you're not a world-class athlete your whole life.
So at some point he's like, damn, I'm too old for this shit.
I'm like, you know, I'm 30 now, you know, my body is failing.
I'm decrepit.
I'm ancient.
It's time to retire.
Now what do I do?
Well, I'm I'm world famous athlete Milo of Proton.
So you guys.
Olives.
No.
So you got to do.
Make olive oil.
You got to do something with that.
I refuse to believe this is like a modern like late capitalist invention.
You must have.
I mean, they had schools.
I bet he like I bet like the school of Athens or whatever like I bet he was like a guest
lecture.
I bet they had him like give speeches and like give I bet he like taught something like
what do you do?
Speaking engagements been like a trainer for like younger athletes or like soldiers or
something like when you're when you're famous when you're a famous guy, you like you got
it.
You do something.
Society just demands that like you society rewards you and you when you just lean into
that and you get and you go and you're like, I'm going to do I'm going to do something
with this thing that I'm famous for.
Like was it was it Greece or Rome that had like the wax tablets that they draw on and
you can wipe them off?
I am not.
I am not sure.
I'm not sure.
There's like a thing I remember learning at school where it's like, oh, they didn't have
books and paper to learn.
They went to school with their wax tablets and they would carve things into the wax and
that would be their way of jotting notes down.
And I'm like, wow, that sounds really bad.
Wait, so you could just like wipe the wax and like smooth it out again.
You could squish it down and then it would be gone.
I don't know what the purpose maybe I'm misremembering.
I would assume.
Let me type that in.
I would assume that you scratch the things into the wax and then maybe later you like
copy them onto like a more permanent thing.
Oh, yeah. Wax tablets is a Roman thing.
No, I didn't know about Romans use wax tablets.
Tablets, pieces of wood tied together so they would open and shut like a little book.
Each piece of wood had a shallow recess that was filled with wax and formed the writing
surface.
So it's like really thick pieces of paper in a in a book and a tablet and stylus.
It was just like real life.
It's like a modern day.
History is just like it's almost like these.
This is really happened.
It's like, yeah.
So, so they just like used writing, making lists, leaving instructions.
But why did they not have paper?
I thought they would have.
They had.
I think, yeah, I think they had it.
But it probably would have been expensive.
I guess the fact that it was a reusable writing implement like, oh, I just got to remember
something. Let me write that down.
Honestly, honestly, kind of convenient.
Sounds kind of good.
Like it's you don't have to waste paper.
Like, I mean, paper is like cost nothing now.
But like maybe it wasn't always so, so plentiful or so hard, easy to come by.
I'm just, I'm just trying to imagine like what it looks like.
What it looks like to like scratch it into and then do you just take a cloth and like
wipe the wax and it like smooths it out again?
Like an etch a sketch?
Wouldn't you eventually run out of wax?
Wouldn't you eventually like wear it down?
So it's, yeah, I guess.
But you could fill it with more wax or is it just like, huh?
Wow.
Look at that.
Would you, would you fucking look at?
Yeah.
And I guess you just kind of smush it.
Yeah, that's awesome.
That's so cool.
I love that.
I want one.
Imagine that you're going around and you're like, you're a young Roman.
You're going to a fucking school.
You're going to go to gym class with Milo of Croton from ancient Greece.
Oh, yeah, yeah, true.
And then you're just like, you, you, oh, and some of your friends like, hey, check this out.
And he's like, I drew.
I drew as a penis.
I scratched, I scratched a, I just, I scratched a little picture of, of, of Mr.
Mr. Mr. of Croton, like taking a dump.
Haha.
He, he's so smelly.
Don't let him see this.
Check it out.
He's like, damn, that's damn.
You, you got to, you got to, you got to rub that out of that wax, dude, before you see it.
Like, no, I'm, I'm showing everyone.
I don't know.
That's fucking wild.
The more I think about it, the more cool it is.
Cause like, oh, the other things, every other writing implement,
wears down a pencil or a piece of chalk, like a, you know, a quill with ink.
Yeah.
And this is like, it's just the illusion of a line, which is the same with everything else.
But the illusion is made by squishing something.
I assume, I assume you did have to like, like, wouldn't the wax like get dirty?
I feel like, like the wax would get dirty and either you would have to, you would have to like, replace it all the time.
Or how maybe it just gets dirty.
Maybe it just gets brown and you're like, whatever, I'm just writing in it.
I don't care.
Hmm.
This is, this is, this is, this is exciting.
This is an exciting thing to see.
I love, I love to like, you know, when you, when you find out something from history that's like this, it's, it's, it's fun to think about like, it's, it seems weird.
But like imagine, imagine just like real, like modern day people using it and like envision like, what would it look like?
Cause like, cause like people back then were not so different.
They were basically the same.
They just had different like stuff around to use.
So it's no different than if like a modern, modern kids were like carrying around these fucking books of wax.
It's like, it could happen.
Maybe there's an alternate history where people were using wax tablets up in like, you know, early America or whatever.
I don't know.
It's funny.
It's cool.
History is neat sometimes.
Yeah.
Well.
How do we get on that?
Milo getting strong.
Oh, I was complaining that I haven't been able to work out because my rack is disassembled.
Nice rack.
It's a nice rack.
I've got a nice rack, you might say, but not at the moment.
Well, we're an hour and a half in.
We could go to voicemails.
Yeah.
Okay.
I think I'm all waxed, tablet it out.
We've, we've waxed.
We've been waxing philosophical about all this stuff for a while now.
Dude, maybe that's where that comes from.
God, it might.
If you're in a philosophy class and you, and you got your wax tablet.
And you're like, hey, quit.
Just teach it to a slap study or quit waxing philosophical or quit, or quit waxing something
other than whatever I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Quit waxing others to it.
You should be waxing philosophical right now.
No.
I want to draw, I want to draw lewd caricatures of people I don't like.
Okay.
Let's.
What's the ancient, the most ancient lewd?
That's the, that's a video.
Well.
It's a video idea.
I feel, I feel like there's no way that like cave paintings don't have like naked ladies
in them.
Naked ladies and perhaps depict the act of, of coitus.
Maybe.
I feel, I feel.
I haven't heard of one.
So.
Although.
Maybe, well, maybe all the, the archaeologists are embarrassed.
Although, I mean, I feel like, not that I know a lot of cave about cave paintings, but
I feel like they mostly depict people naked anyway.
So maybe like they wouldn't have bothered drawing people naked because like they wouldn't
even care because like everyone's just naked.
Yeah.
Everyone's naked.
Everyone fucks.
It's not really a weird thing.
Yeah.
It's not really like a, ooh, but I feel like sex.
I like it.
The, the, um, what are those, those fertility statues?
Yeah.
Little clay figures.
That, that Venus of whatever.
The, the thick little, little bitches.
There's that.
Yeah.
There's that one, the ancient work of ancient pornography.
The like fertility goddess statue.
Yeah.
I know that one.
Oh, I'm well aware.
Uh, but that was not like cave.
That was not like cave painting.
That was, that was from like a civilization.
Sure.
They lived, they lived in a society.
But I guess, I guess like the, the idea of a fertility statue may not have been like
an erotic like, oh, oh, oh, oh, sort of thing.
It may have just been like a normal like part of like a statue that you would make about
anything.
I think.
What?
I don't know.
My impression was that, was that people, was that people whacked off to it.
But I, but I don't know for sure.
All right.
The first voicemail is called Bob is building an army.
Three, two, one, go.
Can't fucking sleep doing this now.
All right.
So the PCP community is terrible.
Tommy not be able to participate in the episode.
So we must kill the voicemail.
And here's how you do it for the next week.
Anytime you have to fart.
I believe so.
Cored a fart voicemail and give it an innocuous title.
So Ben doesn't know what it is.
Speak pipe works on mobile.
Okay.
Hold your phone right up against your.
So spam the voicemails and make them so, so bad.
We'll have to listen to each and every one.
Make them so bad that we have to kill the bit.
And eventually.
That's a great idea.
Someone else had this idea.
The pig person.
Yeah.
I mean, gaspan.
The pig.
The pig was kind of a similar idea.
Okay.
That was great.
Loved it.
Next one is called.
It's a it's a fast.
It's a different file.
It's called voicemail roulette.
You got it?
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It's one of these ones.
I don't understand why some people submit a link to a
different.
Site where they upload their audio.
I don't like why not?
Why not just use speak pipe or whatever.
It's fine.
You ready?
Maybe they don't realize they can upload edited audio or
something.
I don't know.
I mean, I actually don't know how submitting on speak pipe
works.
So maybe it's something like that.
Okay.
You ready?
Yeah.
Voicemail roulette.
Three, two, one, go.
I've come up with rules for a game you might find interesting.
It's called the voicemail roulette.
Should you agree to play this game, you will be obligated to
kill one voicemail per episode.
Voicemailers that are killed must abstain from sending in
voicemails for a month.
This will incentivize creation of few high quality voicemails
as opposed to lots of low quality ones.
It will also provide an element of risk to every episode.
Increasing viewer engagement.
This game requires active participation on the side of
voicemailers.
I like the idea, but we can't enforce it.
No.
And also the name roulette is like a, it's a gamble.
You don't know.
But this is also, this is like saying good voicemails won't
get shot.
No, I think, I think the idea is that we pick completely
randomly.
So a good voicemail might get shot.
But the idea is that like, you want to make, you want to
make as few voicemails as possible.
Oh, few voicemails.
Just to lower your chances of being killed.
I mean, what if just one person makes a voicemail?
Do they automatically die or is it just?
I think so.
Yes.
I think that would be the logical conclusion of this rule
set.
Okay.
So now it's a game of chicken.
Yeah.
Yeah, basically.
Everybody will, everybody will be like, they don't know how
many voicemails are put in.
And if they put one in, they may be the only one.
Yeah.
It's, and it's like the, the act, making any voicemail
inherently carries some risk of like, is this one going to
get me picked and get me, and get me killed?
Yeah.
But there's no, there's, we can't enforce it at all.
We would, we would have to just expect you to voicemailers
to play along, which I'm sure most of them would.
It's a fun, it's a funny idea, but I don't know if, if, how
practical it is.
Next voicemail is called a guy clearly wearing Kringus
Bingus' skin as a suit.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh yeah, I would do it.
I'll never suspect it.
Hey everybody, Kringus Bingus here.
Sorry I haven't made a voicemail in a while.
Anyway, the thing that I've been doing, fuck you, it's a
Kring.
Just roll with it.
The thing that I think the most recently was moving into a
house.
It is fucking awful.
Cause first thing you have to do is get rid of the old
occupant, and then you have to move in your stuff and you
have to get rid of the blood.
It is a mess.
And the thing that I think the most recently was odd
taxi.
I think that Ben St. would really like to do it.
Anyways, Kringus Bingus signing out.
Yeah, Kringus Bingus.
I appreciate the voicemail.
And you're absolutely right.
Moving is a nightmare.
I'm lucky.
Especially the body.
Luckily I'm going to have a little more help with the
second move.
And I mostly have everything from the first move just like
still in boxes ready to go.
So my second move won't be as bad.
The body.
I mean, I don't have to deal with that.
Fortunately I don't have to deal with any bodies or anything.
But you know, it's still, it's still, it's a real, it's a
real hassle.
So my, my, my deepest sympathies.
Next voicemail is called Question to Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
Did you hate Trixie before she left the PCP?
I was getting there for a while.
Not like all, not like the whole time I knew her or anything,
but like by the time, by the time she rage quit, I was like,
I had been souring on her for a long time.
Well, for a while, let's say.
I mean,
Well, how long?
It wasn't like post retcon four.
It was post, it was post retcon.
I mean, Trixie wasn't, was annoying in some ways at like red,
about retcon four, but it wasn't like so bad.
I mean, she was kind of annoying about retcon three, two,
but it wasn't like so bad that I was like,
I don't like this person anymore.
No, I think the turning point was, it was the time when I went
on May's stream and that one person read that like George
Floyd was just as bad as, as Michael Chauvin, uh,
just read and I, and I got, got angry about it.
And I, and May kicked me off the stream and then Trixie DM'd
me to be like, why are you mad at my wife?
You're just jealous.
Cause you don't get pussy like me.
Oh yeah.
Why don't you, why don't you just get,
why don't you just get some pussy, Ben?
And then you won't be mad about this kind of thing anymore.
Leave like, like you fucking idiot.
So I think, I think that was when I was like,
I don't think I like this person anymore.
Um, yeah, probably.
That was probably the biggest thing.
Um, the next, do you want, do you want to answer or what?
Oh me?
I mean, I guess I never disliked her until she rage quit
and then all of that stuff.
Um, I didn't really have a lot of rapport with her though.
Yeah.
It was sort of like a, a Gib and Digi or Trixie,
uh, like project wouldn't really work.
You, you, you guys never had a,
you guys never had a spotlight episode.
Spotlight episode.
You know how like in My Little Pony or something,
there were some, sometimes an episode would be like
these two characters.
Yeah, that was one time.
What if Rainbow Dash and Pinkie Pie play pranks together?
There was that one time we did like a My Little Pony
review collab thing, but it was like,
we didn't really work together.
We just sort of had an idea to make the video with both of us in it.
Right, right.
So Trixie wrote her thing and then I sort of responded to it
and then like they read my script of that.
You mean this was back in the Pony days?
Yeah, like Pony review thing.
That was a long, long SM go.
I was like, uh, admired their work and their work ethic.
Yeah.
But yeah, I never really,
never really felt particularly strongly about them as a person
until they started like being terrible.
Oh, on a, on a somewhat related note,
I put, uh, yeah, terrible.
Just, just, just, just terrible behavior,
just absolutely reprehensible behavior.
Let me, let me be clear about that.
Trixie's behavior is totally unacceptable.
And I won't, I'm glad.
I'm glad I will never have to deal with it again.
Um, it wasn't, it wasn't, yeah, it wasn't always as bad.
Trixie has got, Trixie got much worse,
like at a certain point.
I think, I think May was a really bad influence on Trixie,
who was very, who was very, who was very,
Trixie is very, Trixie is not very smart and is very susceptible
to it being influenced.
Um, because she thinks, because she thinks she's too smart for it.
And that makes her like more vulnerable to just like believing
dumb things because somebody told her so.
Um, but on a somewhat related note,
I've been, I've been doing, working on the game and I put some,
you know, since, since the game about Phantom Horn,
I couldn't help but put a few, uh, references to some,
to some Pony people that I had,
had quote unquote, admire in the, uh, in the game.
So there, there might, there are some Easter eggs in there.
I won't say, I won't say who, I won't say who's in there.
But, uh, if you're familiar with that scene,
you might recognize some people.
Uh, that's, I cackled to myself.
I cackled as I, as I, as I implemented them.
Um, next voicemail is called small, small turtle house.
Three, two, one, go.
What's your opinion on tow-hell?
I don't even know what it is.
Uh, it's a, from what I understand, it's a series of,
uh, obscure indie, uh, like bullet hell games with anime characters.
You know what? Um, I don't, oh, you know, it's not that obscure,
but it's, it's the, it's started very small and it was like
an internet thing, I think.
I, I looked into it one time and I played like the first one
and the first one is like really weird and hard to play
and it's not really a bullet hell.
It's kind of different.
I think the, the first one is like a lot different
than what the series ended up becoming,
but I played that one on my own years ago.
And then when I lived at Trixie's, I think it was at like
Radcon 2 or something.
I think Trixie got me to play one of the, of the Toho games on stream.
And I think it was like fun.
I'm not, bullet hells aren't like my favorite genre or anything,
but I thought it was fine and cool, I suppose.
Uh, so.
And I know there's like fan music.
I enjoy some of the.
And there's a lot of music that people like from it.
The music sounds pretty cool.
There's a lot of music.
I remember like lots of YouTube poop music video fads of Toho music,
or at least one.
Like you and Owen was her, like everybody did it,
like a YouTube poop of that.
And there's a lot of porn, I think, of those characters.
That's pretty cool.
I haven't seen, you know what, I might not,
I probably wouldn't even recognize most Toho characters
if I saw them.
So.
You might recognize Reimu.
People, I know that one because people want her for Smash.
I know that name.
I might, I might recognize that one if I saw her.
She's got the red dress and she's like the ghost,
like Japanese ghost, which attire with the funny thing.
With a stick with like the paper diamonds coming off of it.
Yeah.
Uh, so yeah, that's all.
That's all I really had to think about Toho.
Um, I don't think about you at all.
Uh, next voicemail is called the return dot dot dot.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, everybody.
It's me, Cringy Spingus.
I just want to say, I'm glad to be back after a long hiatus.
And thank you to the guy who made that pink Floyd about me.
That was really good.
Who made a pink Floyd about?
Let's just get right into it.
What I, what I did recently is that I, my family had to watch
a family friend's dog.
And that dog was really crazy and, uh, just annoying.
And I didn't, he was, he was sweet, but he was real rambunctious.
And there was a lot to him.
Yeah.
Sounds like, sounds annoying.
What I've been thinking recently is, uh, the, the, the critically
acclaimed, um, live-action drama, suspense, comedy show, Breaking Bad.
And it's really good.
And I do say comedy because Breaking Bad's really funny, actually.
It's, it's, you know, it's suspenseful.
Sometimes it is.
Serious and it's intense, but also it can be really funny.
It's an interesting drama about a bunch of different characters
and how, and how they, they interact with each other.
True.
So yeah, that's, that's what I cring and bang lately.
I'll do some more of these soon and goodbye cringis fingers.
Goodbye cringis fingers forever.
Yeah.
Yeah. Breaking Bad's pretty good.
I, you know, I never, I don't think I ever watched the last season
of Better Call Saul.
I think I meant, I watched a bunch of it and then I never finished it.
I think it went on hiatus for a while and then it came back
and I never got around to watching it, but I liked it.
And I call Saul was pretty good.
Damn.
What about that other guy?
What about that other cringis fingers?
What's, what's the,
That was the guy clearly wearing a cringis finger skin as a suit.
Sure.
So what's, what's the story?
Who do I shoot?
I gotta kill somebody.
Gotta kill somebody.
Oh, right.
The Pink Floyd, somebody made the song, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Does anybody remember cringis fingers?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
We should make that, we should make that the opening song.
It's just, it's just the song of the, it's the theme song now.
Oh, next one.
Oh boy.
We've got one of these fucking things we've got.
It's a, it's a comic.
It's a comic.
I guess I'll post it in the, in the general.
Oh, it's a whole fucking thing.
Phantom Horn, then doing his little virgin walk.
Hey, Phantom, hey Phantom Horn.
Want some cookies?
No thing.
That's, that's mage there.
It's definitely mage.
Don't be shy.
We can always make more with my magic.
Yeah.
Well, bye.
Later.
Horn sells at me topics as unicorns live on easy mode.
This hornoid bitch walked out to me today.
Screech.
I was worthless for having no magic.
I lost it and called her what she was a worthless.
I don't know what that something had.
I don't know what's, hmm.
I don't know what that, that term being blanked out is there.
I told that bitch.
I hate hornoids.
So goddamn much.
This is, this is how.
No.
Is this like an old, um, like mage at the time comic?
Because it feels like it might be.
I feel like I may have seen this, but.
What do you mean by mage at the time?
No, no, no, mage at the time, the comic.
There's no way.
Like this is majoring the Phantom Horn pony days.
Cause this is, this is that guy who's been doing the, the voicemail drawings.
Is it the same guy?
It looks very different.
I think it's the same guy, but I don't know for sure.
Um, the, the, the Phantom Horn is like dark blue.
They, they must have used like some people draw Phantom like really dark blue.
And then, and it's, it's funny.
Um, that is, okay.
I think, is this a reference to a shelf, shelf deprecation?
Do you remember that?
I don't.
Me and, me and mage were doing a like collab comic where we would like each draw a page.
We would do, like I would draw a page and then she would draw a page and then I would
get it back and I would draw the next page.
Yeah, we were, for a while we were doing a.
Was that like a, like a primordial comics jam?
It kind of, yeah, in a way.
I think it was after.
I think it was after we did the comics jams.
Um, yeah, but this was back in the pony days.
We were, we were doing a comic and she dropped it.
By the way, she dropped the ball on it.
I, I never, I never fail at anything.
Um, but the story was about, it was about Phantom Horn, uh, getting.
It was, fuck.
It's like, I think he's like stealing keg's cookies off the shelf or something.
Uh, and then, yeah, there was going to be a whole thing about like, mage using her magic
to get the cookies, but it just causes magical, wacky hijinks.
Um, Phantom would not.
Phantom is, um, Phantom wouldn't make a scre, an anti-Hornoid screed.
Oh my God.
I can't even tell who's one eye through the door.
Crack is staring at me.
Phantom wouldn't make a, a, an anti-unicorn screed because he's, he's pro unicorn.
Right.
So he's, um, I don't know.
This is, he must have been having a bad day for him to have this.
He must have been having a bad day for this.
This is not, this is not as typical.
His typical reaction would be like, I'm like that too.
It might be, this is why I'm thinking it might be an older thing because like Phantom
would used to kind of be like a little racist against unicorns because he was jealous of
the horn.
What, was he?
I don't remember.
Well, not like, like overtly, but like sort of, um, actually kind of, like I'm trying
to remember.
Well, I don't know.
This is certainly an interpretation.
Okay.
There might have been, yeah.
In the early Phantom horn days, there might have been some, he might not have been completely
consistent about it.
Uh, he, he might have, he might have had a grudge against certain unicorns.
Maybe.
You know what?
He might, he might have, he might have begrudged certain unicorns for flaunting their, their
magic privilege or something.
I feel like that was something he would do.
It wouldn't call them hornoids though.
No.
Uh, okay.
Next.
Anyway, I enjoy this is a, this meme is, it's usually like a, I think the original meme
is like white guy meets black guy and black guy is just like, says something normal.
And then white guy goes on forum and is like, oh, I saw some fucking N word today and he
was so fucking bad.
Uh, yeah.
I think this, this particular is, is more like in parallel to like, like incels, like
a normal woman just is normal.
Yeah.
Like God, what that, that bitch.
And then it's like completely delusional.
Um, yeah.
You know what?
Honestly, I mean, heck, that version I just described might not even be the original version.
Maybe it was an incels thing first.
I don't know.
Uh, I like it.
I'm having a, I'm looking at this and I'm thinking, ha ha.
Uh, thumbs, thumbs up.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called nominal consideration.
Three, two, one, go.
Aliases.
Talk about them.
What do you think makes a good online name?
I would say it requires a balance of brevity, distinctness and aesthetic quality.
Notch is the one of the best out there in my opinion, though it sucks that notches the
one who got it.
Digibro is my personal favorite alias historically tied to the PCP, though most members or
frequent guests have pretty good ones too.
I'm I'll die.
And I think while mine is a little clunky phonetically, it succeeds especially well thanks
to how good it looks when written all lowercase with no apostrophe.
What are your favorite online aliases?
What do you value in them?
Do you agree with my appraisals?
What aliases of PCP members, PCP adjacent folk or commenters and fans over the past
year stand out to you as especially good or bad?
That's too many questions.
I agree.
I mean, the criteria you lay out.
What is it like?
Distinctness, aesthetic, I mean, aesthetic quality is obviously important, but that's
like very, that's subjective.
Distinct, distinctness is good.
If it's a name that like nobody else has or no one has, like it's like, oh, you get
confused with somebody else's name.
That's important.
Brevity.
Yeah, brevity is important just because you don't want to be brevity.
I think as with any name, beyond a certain threshold of like a household name or a famery,
it doesn't matter what the name is.
If people know what you are, they'll associate that name with you.
Like dream, for example, is so big and it's just a dictionary word.
It's kind of a shitty name to have, but because he's so big, it works.
Yeah, you know what, about notch and dream, yeah, it works because they're big.
I don't know if I think that dream or notch is like a great name on its own.
Like if they were never, if you'd never heard of them, the name notch wouldn't stick with you.
So I don't know if I agree about that one.
I've always said that a name becomes associated with whatever it's referencing.
So people just get used to it no matter how stupid it is.
But there is a certain amount of like marketable qualities that a name needs to have.
Yeah, like you can't copyright the name dream.
Yeah, and if it's hard to Google or if it's like a reference to something or a pun,
like my name's like puns, gib and take.
But Gibbs, pretty good.
It works most of the time.
Hippocrates was a lot worse of a name because it's a way that people actually misspell the word sometimes.
I guess so.
And it doesn't really communicate what it's about, although that's not always that important.
I always complain.
I thought that Kantent was a bad name because it is just because it's so...
Okay, people disagreed with me.
I think that it's kind of bad because it doesn't communicate what the show is.
And I think the show needed a name that would communicate what it is.
But worse than that, it's un-Googleable, but like for the different reasons.
It's a common word, but because nobody knows how to spell it and nobody ever spells it right.
Yes, it is not spelled phonetically and it has like two H's that are silent and it's not a real word.
It's spelled in a way that is like deliberately confusing and that's really bad.
Yes, I always had a problem with that as well.
When it comes to like...
It's really bad for discoverability.
I feel like it tells you more about what it's about than half in the bag does.
I...
As a name.
I guess they both communicate basically nothing.
So yeah, I don't know.
That one's not as important.
Because you're right.
Like if you have a show, you can call it whatever you want.
And once people know it, they're like, oh yeah, that's the name of the show.
I know.
Yeah.
I mean, this is colloquially referred to as the PCP and we don't talk about that drug.
No, we're Dewey.
That's in the bonus episodes.
We're on PCP in every bonus episode.
That's what we pay for.
I didn't put the bonus episodes up.
Maybe I'll do it this week.
Maybe I'll do it, but maybe I won't.
Maybe I won't.
I don't know.
Who knows?
Next voicemail is another image.
Put it right there.
Oh God.
Oh, hang on.
It's a...
What's the actor's name?
Is it one of the Phoenixes?
It's not one.
Is it Joaquin Phoenix?
And Crazy Frog.
It's Joaquin Phoenix as Joker and Crazy Frog.
Happy about Crazy Frog's pregnancy.
You're going to have a whole bunch of clown tadpoles.
Dude, this is just a homesick image if you think about it.
Yeah.
We go to Subjugilator and...
And a Frog.
And a Universe Frog.
Mmm.
You know what?
Based.
Next voicemail is from at Mauricio Gamedev.
I assume that's a Twitter handle.
Three, two, one, go.
A few episodes ago, when Ben made a tier list of all the PCP Electors,
a topic was brought up that they still fly Kingdom Hearts, One Piece,
and Final Fantasy wearing really good topics to make a lecture on.
For me, those lectures are a good way to catch up on what was actually happening on those stories,
since there is a lot of stuff to catch up on.
Best example of this is Guilty Gear that I have been playing since I was a kid
and had no idea what was going on.
Final thing.
Tom is great at doing lectures, and I think he should capitalize more on that for his own stuff.
Right.
I don't think I said the Kingdom Hearts one was not a good one.
That one's a great topic.
He pointed that out as the subject matter works, because it's hard to parse otherwise.
Guilty Gear is the same.
Guilty Gear is similar, because it's something that most people don't know the lore,
and the lore is hard to get your head around and understand.
One Piece and Final Fantasy, I don't think they have a greatness,
because the games just have a story, and it's basically just relating the story of the game.
I guess if you want something to just catch you up and give you a Cliff Notes version,
I guess, sure, it's good for that.
I would say it's better to just read it.
I would say the One Piece one is, if we're talking about just those two,
I feel like the Final Fantasy one is the weakest, because the individual Final Fantasy games
have no relation to each other, and so they don't need to be in the same video.
You know what I mean?
Oh, thanks, Dad.
My bacon's here.
Your mother and I had a talk.
I was too hard on you about your hot wheels.
Thank you.
I'll pick them up for you.
You better.
Just try to remember to pick up your hot wheels next time.
I might, maybe.
Sorry, I brought you some bacon.
Acceptable.
But however, your mother and I are getting a divorce.
Okay.
Well, you can't win them all, Dad.
Good luck on your podcast, Benjamin.
Thanks, Dad.
I am winning.
It's not dead.
It's daddy.
Okay, daddy.
Thank you.
You're welcome, son.
I love it.
Ew.
Okay.
I got bacon now.
Sorry to love you.
No.
Yeah, they're my dad.
Dad's gonna do that.
What is your dad?
What is your dad not love you?
Fucking idiot.
What was I talking about?
Oh yeah, lectures.
Tom's lectures are good.
Okay.
I feel like we've answered this one.
Wait.
This mouse is so sensitive.
I don't like it.
Benjamin, I'm sorry about you and my father.
Oh my God.
I hate my parents so much.
Why?
I'm trying to record a podcast, Mom!
If you need something to talk about me and your father getting a divorce, Benjamin,
then you can talk to them.
No!
I'm sick of it.
I'm sick of all this bullshit.
I'm cleaning out your father, Benjamin.
I'm taking him to a family court.
I can never remember fucking anything.
I'm gonna do the amnesia.
I'm gonna deal with lawsuit so fucking fast that we'll never be able to see you again.
Okay.
I need you to say to the federal court that he abused you and he molested you.
I need you to say that so I can get a nice quick victory.
Sure, Mom.
Fine.
Whatever it takes.
Okay.
I'll give you a lego settlement.
You just have to make sure that you wake your father through the day.
Two lego sets.
Yeah!
You have to pretend that your father molested you in family court so you can keep the system
rigged against broken fathers.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
You've got it.
I was gonna do that anyway.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so sorry about all this bullshit.
Next voicemail is called Peek PCP.
Three, two, one, go.
It's Japanese niggas, Japanese niggas, Japanese niggas, Japanese niggas, Japanese niggas.
They just keep selling.
This is the whole video.
I think so.
Or it's a minute, 30 of it.
It's catchy.
Yeah, I remember it being pretty funny.
Genius.
Japanese niggas, Japanese niggas, Japanese niggas, Japanese niggas.
You all have to simple hook, a simple concept where it really works.
Yeah, they just kept going because of you
OK, it finally it's finally over.
Well, I have fun.
Yeah, I'm.
You know, you know, it is what it is.
It's fine, it's cool.
Uh, what a, what a, what a delight. Okay. Next one is called art parlor. Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben Shane. I DM'd you on Twitter, but you didn't respond. I was asking if you wanted to be
on my drawing show. It's being just a couple of grandmothers and we do funny drawing challenges.
And then I edit the fuck out of the recording and make a fire video and give if you want to come
on or Tom. That'll be cool. All you guys are invited to the grandma drawing show. I don't remember
getting DM'd by a grandma. Grandma drawing show. Maybe. Maybe sometime if I catch me in the right
mood. Maybe. Maybe. Next one is called hydration. Three, two, one, go.
Give and take.
You say that I need hydration, but there is no water anywhere around here.
Have you tried pissing?
100% hot spring macaque water. That is what I need.
Hey, sorry, I'm back. Did I miss anything?
They're thirsty. They need hot spring macaque water.
Who doesn't?
You could also, if you can't piss for liquid, you could cut your veins open and drink that blood.
The body is a wonderland. You're full of delicious liquids. And then you could just cry
about how dry it is and you could make tears and you could get those. And all you need is two
buckets worth. You get two buckets worth of water and then you can make an infinite source of
water. In Minecraft? Yeah. Hell yeah. What do you like? Put one water source block next to another
one? And then it's infinite. Does it create two more in the square? Yeah, in the other corners.
Hmm. I didn't know that. That's a trick I could use, actually.
Next voicemail is called Tommy J Sucks. Three, two, one, go.
I dread to even speak his name, but please stop playing the Tommy J voicemails.
They're so horrible. You guys shouldn't have to go through them and we shouldn't have to go through
them. They're just pain. They suck. And Tommy J, you suck. Please stop calling in.
I think he just made the one call this week, so maybe it's a solved issue.
They are not labeled in a way that we can identify who put them in before.
Yeah, we just have to recognize the voice.
Next voicemail is called Some Commenters Suck. Three, two, one, go.
Also, commenters, stop leaving comments like, I don't like the podcast now. Bad podcast. You
guys should do a different podcast. I think this is bad and should be something different.
I think you should stop leaving that comment. It's been like a year and you haven't changed
their minds yet. Stop saying the exact same thing over and over and over and over. Please,
just stop watching or just accept that a thing is a thing, that a thing has changed,
and that maybe you don't like it anymore. And maybe you can move on. Please.
Yeah, I got in a fight. I got in an argument on the last episode in the comments because somebody
left that comment that was like, the podcast is stagged. Why don't you make the podcast something
that would have more, what do they say? Why don't you make the podcast something that would have
more, could actually grow? Why don't you make the podcast something that could grow? Why not
do something else with your creative ambitions? Yeah, okay. First of all, I negatively commented
on that comment and then someone else came in and was arguing at me that I was dumb to not like
that comment. And it's like, okay, the podcast, first of all, I don't even know what they're asking
because the podcast already is about our creative endeavor. We already talk about all the shit we're
doing. So what do you want? And second of all, why not make the podcast something that can grow,
make the podcast something that'll be more successful? Like what? I don't know. Do they
want us to do the drawcasts again? If you just like the drawcast, then just say you just make
more drawcasts. But I don't understand the mindset that you're like, hmm, the PCP formula
isn't working. So it should be something else. When it has always been, it has always been the
same thing. It has always been, we get together and we just talk about shit once a week. There's
nothing else. I mean, there have been minor changes like the introduction of voicemails and
we don't do that specific chosen topic anymore. But those were changed for a reason.
They recognize that they can't just say, have the other members back. I liked the podcast more
when it was like that. There were more views. If you're a Natehead or a Trixiehead and you just
want to hear Nate or Trixie, I mean, fair enough, you're just not going to get that here anymore.
Then I think they're misunderstanding the reason that the podcast used to get more views and it's
because the people who are on it had bigger channels than me and Ben. Yeah. I mean, the
viewership is not, it is somewhat lower than it is, but it's not like it's completely falling
off the cliff. I mean, the old episodes have more views largely just because they're older
and they've been accumulating views for a while. True. I can't remember exactly, but there was a
time when it was like hotter shit and the episodes were getting like maybe 10K views on a good day
and that was a fun time. I guess that's true. But that definitely does have to do with the
people who happen to have large audiences being on the show. Trixie just had a bigger audience.
It's not entirely to do with the quality of the show itself because people who were just there
for Nate or just there for Trixie are gone mostly. Yeah. It's true. Or Jesse or whoever.
Yeah. There's really no getting around that.
Yeah. I guess I agree with this voicemail is the takeaway. Next one is called Nathaniel.
Three, two, one, go. Also, also, I don't know if this was intentional,
but you guys were talking about Nate as a role model and Gib just totally dunked on Nate. It
was like, yeah, sometimes when you're little, you don't realize that videos aren't good.
I don't even remember that. I just thought it was really funny that you essentially said like,
yeah, you know, some people just don't realize that all of Nate's stuff is bad.
It's not bad. I didn't mean that. That was an accident, I guess. I don't remember exactly what
you said, but I mean, I like Nate's videos. At least, you know, I've like I've like I enjoyed
me a mouth of her and we Aga was occasionally. Yeah. Yeah, that's true. I never I never watched
a we Aga. I don't think I like I don't think I liked we Aga that much. There was there was a
few that were like, the subject matter was interesting to me, or at least I remember the
what was it when he talked about the guy from One Piece and I can't even remember his name.
Oh, the the the Taffy guy or the the big man pirates, the Mochi guy Mochi guy. Yes. I haven't seen
like I said, I've like never watched it. I think the only me a mouth of that I have what no not
me about I think the only we Aga I ever watched all the way through was because people were
complaining about it in my discord. And it's because it's the one where he it's the one where
he like walks back and clarifies that like, no, his Galco Chan video is not a body positivity
video. He does not support fat women. That was kind of cringe. I didn't know that one's awful.
That one's I didn't watch it until someone told me it's like, and I was like, there's no way he
says that. And I went back and he watched, he's like, no, that's exactly what he says. He's like,
he's just like, no, this is not the message of that video. This is not in support of like,
as a body positive thing. And I want to clarify, I want to clarify. No, it is not. Yes, that's
literally it. That's literally the point of that we Agua. There's there's. Yeah, although it's hard
to find because it's not labeled. Then there are a bunch of we Agos that have like, that I'm that
mentioned the Galco Chan video in them, I think. So sometimes I try to find it and I'll accidentally
find another one where he isn't talking about it. There's one, though, where he says that one
sucks. I don't like the Tifa, the Tifa boobs one is shitty, too. People complain about that one.
And I watch it. I'm like, yeah, it sucks. That's annoying. Anyway, my comment about like, when
you're young, you don't know what videos are good or not. And I think I was mostly talking about
myself. Because like, you're young, you don't know, you don't know shit. I was into thunder for a while.
Like a while. Yeah, like, he's he has merits in his science stuff. But yeah, he's a shithead. And
I didn't realize that quite so much. I didn't really I only heard about Thunderfoot through
people like criticizing his politics. I didn't I didn't realize that he does like other, like
science stuff, which I'm sure is probably fine. It's his better stuff. He does like, he does like
debunks of bullshit. He hates Elon Musk, and he thinks he's like a con man. And so that's
kind of based true like his his his like, obsession with Anita Sarkeesian.
I mean, he wasn't he's not the only one. He's not the only one. And it yeah, but like,
it's kind of cringe. Like, I didn't really notice it when I was subscribed, because just a video
comes out every so often. But then you look at the playlists, and it's like, I don't know 100
videos about why Anita Sarkeesian and feminism is stupid. Right. And it's like, uh, yeah, that's
not very good. True. Yeah. Okay, next one is called I'm so hurt by never pain. Three, two, one, go.
Oh, yeah. Fuck you.
Yeah.
No, false, false.
Pain her anime has a weight loss problem in yours.
No, I'm sorry.
You know, I know what you're talking about. I mean, maybe meeting a first land
makes sort of. Like, I know I can really effectively you're this like a
gobbledig monster.
I think this is like a golem like talking to himself kind of thing.
I don't know, really honestly, I saw Cocoa's was better than the PCP at the end.
Although that wasn't a showscore, I think.
I mean, no.
Major cope, major cope energy.
Mae was always bad.
I wanted to like Mae.
Her videos were sort of okay, I guess.
I'll be honest, I didn't watch the anime has a weight loss problem video.
It was an OK idea.
I guess some sort of body positive, something or other.
The hero we need, Nate refused to be the hero that fat girls need.
So may had to do it.
Yes. Yes.
Get owned, get owned, never paint.
Next one is called Ben, this is your doctor.
Geez, three, two, one, go.
So there's been a lot of talks on bringing back certain old members
of the peace of mind, considering the certain shambles of the peace of mind
right now.
I love it. Ouch.
Like a popular one is saying, you should come back.
How we talk about fucking
Trixie Doodle, but.
You'll forget one very important person, one very important piece
of the puzzle that could come back and bring the PCP to its former fucking glory.
And that is my boy, Cy live.
Bring Cy live to the PCP and see the bitch's rise or or don't go off.
OK, those are your two options.
I'm giving Dr. Wolf or Cy live.
Cy, is Cy live?
Cy pillow, blue pill.
Is who is that?
Cy like S.Y.Y.
I can only assume.
I don't know. I talked about this.
I asked him, I asked him if he wanted to be on and he just said no.
He just was like, no, I don't want to come on the PCP.
He's like, oh, OK, I don't know what his problem is.
But he he just was like, no, no, no, like reason given.
You know, it would never happen.
We would have to like trick Dr.
Wolf, but I kind of want to interview him about like,
what the fuck is up with the everything you're doing, including TF2 analysis anarchy?
Well, TF2 analysis, it's it's TF2 analysis.
Anarchy is like the funniest thing that has ever existed.
Yes, but there's a lecture in that, but I don't want to watch any of my God.
You're so right.
You're a genius.
Give your own fucking genius.
That would be so good.
But it's like I've only watched the first one and I was in it.
And then the other ones were like, oh, God, this is unbearable.
I can't I can't imagine doing the research that would make
an amazing, amazing lecture.
I love that.
But Dr.
Wolf, from what I can tell, he's mostly just doing like, you know,
pretty normal like YouTube stuff.
He'll upload like a two minute video where he like reacts to like a new bit
of information that was just revealed about like the Gen 5 MLP.
Hold on, Dr. Wolf 01.
Let me let me see what's what's he doing?
Duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh.
Hip pedals, mixing royalty and social media is hitched.
The next Fluttershy season five trailer reaction, sunset shimmer, audition announcement.
OK, he's doing something.
He needs auditions or voice actors for something.
Yeah, he's he's he's doing he's doing a lot of like little mini like videos
where he like just notices something about the new MLP.
He's priming his audience.
He's priming his audience for a big comeback with with with with Gen 5.
Oh, and he's still he's still hanging out with Josh Scorcher and Lightning Bliss.
You know, the cool the cool kid's crowd.
Oh, who's who it who I'm sorry.
Who is this pony right here?
I want to I want to meet that pony and the bottom left with the red with the red
and black hair. Now, that's an O.C.
If I've ever seen I don't know that's and I'm excited.
I mean, give me give me like alarm bells ring in red and black.
You know what they say, red and black.
I attack sexually.
Yes, yes, good.
Next voicemail, I think.
It's called so I can just have Ben say anything here, huh?
Three, two, one, go.
So a lot of people are talking about how the PCP needs some new blood
and I agree.
But at the same time, the names getting thrown around don't really meet
the proper guidelines.
I don't think let's go over what makes a good PCP member.
Number one, content creator.
Yeah, and most of them are that.
So I'll give them a point for that.
But as we go on number two, trans most of them aren't trans.
So, you know, right there.
Number three, Christ conscious level of four or higher.
None of them have that.
So I mean, that won't resonate.
I bet literally that will not resonate.
I can't see them like saving the world with the love battleship number
four killed and eight a man's heart.
Maybe some of them have done this.
It's possible, but they're not talking about it.
That's missed content.
Like we want that if they're not, if they're not the reason people are
dying and I don't even want to hear uncircumcised none of them.
Like you may as well just say, hey, yeah, the PCB should die.
Put these people on and let it die.
Pathetic.
I like a man with standards.
You know what?
This guy, this guy, he's just being pragmatic.
Look, he's looking at it the way it really is.
No, no, no sugarcoating next voicemail is called cope dot mp3
three, two, one, go.
What if what if like Nate is just like waiting, you know, to
be on the podcast?
What if he's got a big, big plan, you know, he's got a big comeback
reveal, you know, what's all the rad content is out?
You know, what's all the rad content things?
Would it like he's got something planned, you know, like, oh,
yeah, dude, like, oh, my God.
Oh, my God, dude, it's going to be like a big horseshoe finale,
like big reveal, like it was all part of my plan kind of thing.
The views jumped to 1200.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, we're, we're, we're back, baby.
Oh, the next one is an Imjur link.
So let's take a look here.
Why do I look like that?
Now that you're moving apartments, you'll be more responsible
with your money, right?
Big boy, let the good times.
Why am I with horses?
What are these parties doing?
Are they hooking us?
They're your escorts, escorts.
Yeah.
I mean, you're at a casino.
Why is my hair like golden?
Like, man.
It's a lot to like about this.
I made it.
I'm at the top of the food chain on top of the pole.
I got my Citibank custom cash card.
I'm never, I'm untouchable.
So it's time to just roll the dice on Bitcoin.
Actually, I did, I did, I did upset selling my Bitcoin
because I was like, I don't know.
I was like too scared.
I was too scared of it dropping.
So I basically broke even now.
I pretty much broke even broke even.
Yeah.
It went up for a bit and then it kind of like went back to
around where it was.
And I was seeing in the, it was, it was slowing down
and it's still kind of hovering, but like it's not really going up.
I was seeing people.
I was seeing the word exhaustion thrown around a lot
and I was like, people were saying like Bitcoin.
Oh, wait, it jumped.
Oh, it actually jumped up.
Oh, it's not, it's not that big of a jump or is it?
Don't trick yourself, Ben.
Oh, it actually think of the larger scale.
It actually went, it actually went up a bit today.
So that's, I mean, it's still, yeah, it still hasn't gone back up to,
oh, damn it.
It's having a good day today, but it hasn't gone back up to 50K
or it almost, wait, why doesn't it say that it hit 50K?
It did briefly hit 50K.
Why does it, why does it say it didn't?
What is this?
What is wrong with this chart?
Oh, that was back.
Oh, wait, that was longer ago than I thought.
It's coming.
It's climbing again.
It's climbing again, but people were saying it's getting exhausted.
I hate it.
I fucking hate it.
No matter what, even if I own Bitcoin or I don't own Bitcoin,
I'm always losing all the time.
There's no escape.
I can't, like, no, no, no more.
Yeah, you gotta, you gotta let it go.
Probably.
You gotta jump in when it's really far down.
This is what, okay, but if it was going to go up, it would still be worth buying
even if it's high, if it was going to go even higher, it would still be worth it.
I think that, well, the thing I think is that the precedent has been set
that it will probably not be as high as it is right now because it's quite fucking high.
So it's likely it's going to go down before it goes up again.
It was, I mean, it was and it still is possible that like the first big spike
this year was only the beginning and it will spike even higher.
Like, and like that was just like the first possible.
But it is so hard to predict that it's like not worth trying to.
My, my, my thought was like, my thought was like, if I don't own any Bitcoin
and it goes to the moon, then I've, then I've lost a ton of money, basically.
So it's like, well, I better have some just in case.
Oh, people are saying it's or it's people were saying it was bullish.
Now people are saying, it looks like it's losing steam.
It might be bearish and like, who fucking knows?
I mean, nobody knows, but everybody, everybody together thinks they know.
Yeah.
And so what they say kind of does influence the market.
Because it influences other people who think, oh, yeah, these people know
what they're talking about and now I know what they're talking about.
And now we all know what we're talking about.
And it's like they've tricked each other into believing that it's not going up.
So it just doesn't actually go up.
Yeah.
I mean, you're right.
I'm just, I'm just looking at this image again.
I guess that's Applejack.
Is that yes.
Applejack and Twilight.
Is it?
I guess it's Twilight.
That's definitely Applejack.
And I'm just having a, I'm having a ball.
You know, I wish, I wish this were me.
It's so determined.
Like, yeah, here we go.
You're super large head makes the hand look like a baby hand.
What, like, what picture, what video is this image of me from?
I don't recognize.
It's all like warped and distorted.
And I don't know why.
Why would you do?
Why would you stretch out on five?
Why?
I don't know what the point was.
Oh, it looks, I look like a freak.
This is great.
The next, next voicemail is also an image.
So let's see.
Oh God.
Ew, I don't know what this is.
It's a, it looks like a, a fake monkey head robot on wheels.
I don't, and it says the PCP in current time.
I, I feel like this is a reference that I don't get.
Like, I don't know what this thing is.
I guess it's a reference or it could just be a bizarro meme.
Like, it's just weird.
And that's the point.
Hmm.
I can't because I don't think I can glean any like.
Meaning out of this image.
No, I'm not, I'm not getting anything from it.
I'm sorry.
Big cheese shimolinsky at pinkypie.com who sent this next
one is called Sigma.
It's the Greek letter Sigma.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you think the collapse of human civilization will happen
during the 21st century?
No, no, people thought things are going to collapse.
I mean, global warming is pretty big, but the,
yeah, but it's only going to start at the end of the century.
It's like, it's a terrible, if it continues the way it is,
you know, it's, it's not going to.
Right.
I mean, global warming is bad and we'll have catastrophic
consequences, but it isn't going to like end civilization.
I mean, unless it will just get really, really full of death
for a while and then have less humans.
Yes, that's right.
So it's fine, actually.
No, it's not life will grow and kill us all.
Things are not, things are not that precarious.
Like it's not, we're not under an existential threat of like
there will be no more civilization.
Like the infrastructure that exists will mostly continue
to exist.
Yeah.
People, people do like to imagine that they are at the
end times because that makes them more important.
Like I'm the last person who will see like stuff.
Yeah.
But no, probably not.
Probably not.
No, it's things are pretty dire in a lot of ways, but it's
not like, it's not end times bad.
Next, I wouldn't rest on your laurels, but I also wouldn't
like doomerize.
Like there's no hope because they're clearly that's what
that's what they want.
That's what like oil companies stuff want people to be like,
well, global warming happened.
We fucked it up.
There's nothing we can do.
Nothing we can do.
Well, better just say fuck it.
We're already facing the about that's what they want you
to think.
Because then because then you don't have to fucking do
anything about that.
Next one is called Rx like the prescription 321 go.
Hey, PCP.
So a couple of weeks ago, someone suggested the name
Nate mates instead of Nate heads.
So I just wanted to suggest the name Ben pals instead of
Ben heads.
Oh, you send me the great work.
Ben pals is pretty good.
Yeah, it's in Ben pals.
That works really well actually like a pen pal.
But for me.
It's like a pen pal.
But when that meme where you put a B instead of a P with a
B emoji.
Yeah, beater beater Griffin.
Then I don't I don't know the meme actually.
I mean, I can imagine it.
What is it?
It's called if I Google B for P meme.
Yeah, I don't really know if has a name be emoji meme.
It's just the letter B.
Oh, that emoji.
Yeah, the red regional indicator red letter B.
Oh, I was imagining like the bug.
No, no, I see.
I see.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, I've seen people do that.
But the bug Venus put my Venus in the whatever bet this
bet bet yes, that's it.
That one low volume to asshole again three two one go.
Hey guys, it's that low volume to asshole again.
True.
In light of recent events and the shitstorm surrounding Ben
and pretty much every single TV farmer ever.
I'm just wondering.
You know, has there ever been a point of your life where you
hated Twitter so much that you just simply just want to
straight up delete your account for something because
no shit cannot be good for your psyche in the long run.
You know, it isn't it's not really sad when some people
just don't want to fucking downward spiral.
You know, say what you will about Will Whedon at least he
realized how much of an asshole he was on Twitter and
needed his account.
No, it's just I fucking hate life.
Now, are you saying that I'm on a downward spiral because
of Twitter?
Maybe maybe a little bit.
I don't think it happens to everyone.
If you if you if you stay there too long, it's a very bad
place to be.
Yeah, I've you know, I think I'm cutting back.
I'm happier when I'm I'm happier when I'm not using Twitter.
So, you know, I was on a bunch for that for the whole Chris
thing, but like in times when I don't have anything to be
posting about.
Yeah, I'm probably going to be a little more a little less
on Twitter.
You know, unless like I there's something that I feel like
I need to be posting about.
Next one is called silly question for give three to one
go.
Whatever happened to Gibbon finale?
Whatever happened?
Oh, I give him finale.
I'm sort of taken aback.
Someone even knows what that is.
I don't even remember mentioning it.
Um, but I guess in the vein of horseshoe finale, I wanted to
have like.
Uh, Gibbon, the character, the pony.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, I sort of set a few things in motion when I ended the
Gibbon take a review show on the on, you know, with the
pony character.
Yeah, yeah.
And I was thinking, what if all of the instances of Gibbon
take were like part of like this big grand adventure plot
that all culminated in a big fucking thing and I had so
many fucking ideas and I was going to have like hippo was
going to be there and action giraffe and phantom horn and
teabap and, you know, it was going to be a big thing with
everybody and it was going to be like home stock.
It was going to be so fucking sick.
Yes.
And of course I realized at some point I was like, wait, I
should just do that.
But it like an original comic idea.
I don't need to fucking make it about my fucking pony review
show.
Kind of.
Yeah, that's kind of true.
Because I was I put so much effort into like that and I never
showed anyone the plans I had.
It was so fucking ridiculous.
Well, did you did you like reincorporated into something
else?
Hmm.
Oh, who knows?
Hmm, I'll never tell.
Well, I'm okay.
Well, now I wait.
What is it?
What does it mean?
I want to know what like where did it what did it end up as?
Okay, if you'd spoilers or something, then I guess then I
guess we'll just move on.
So there's the answer.
I thought I thought that give was killed in a pirate ship
explosion.
Yes.
Well, you know, all right, here's some lore that I'm never
going to use anywhere.
So I may as well explain.
So give and take the pony wasn't me.
I was a separate person and we were like, yeah, he he was the
pony or I guess he was your own seat.
Oh, is she?
Well, you know what?
I don't know.
It's completely it's up to I they were always like gender
non-specific.
Yeah, look in anyway.
Yeah, I guess I guess they wait shit.
I was going to say they're your oh, they're your OC from
Dimension C one nine seven.
So you know when the merge happens, you'll meet.
I think and the end and they'll kill you if they don't like
how you've treated them as a character.
Oh, no, I didn't kind of abuse them or I made fun of them.
In the first in the first thing dying the marriage video.
I used the give and take pony OC.
It was like at the end of one of my like compilations.
I was like, hmm, maybe I should do my little pony reviews,
but I'll need no C and then a little character comes up and
says, what about me?
And I'm like, no.
And he says, okay, but then I end up using it from then on
they speak through me the pony review stuff and then I get
bored of that and I stop but I have like a ending where give
and take the pony goes off on a pirate ship to the ocean and
then they get attacked by a pirate ship.
Another one that has like a Kim possible discord sort of sale
that nobody noticed as it was other brony analysis pirate evil.
They killed him.
He's dead except he didn't die because he turned up in crown
princes animated version of a moment with Dr.
Wolf starring me and Dr.
Wolf and then I showed up in that Kim possible.
Like let's go and meet the bronies animated segment.
Yeah, I think.
And it was also there.
He was also there.
Give was I mean, give was also in a TBAP resurrection.
Yes, TBAP resurrection and well, TBAP resurrection is that
version of of Gibb is with a starboard starboard bow Jesse's
pony and because I had been lost at sea or the given the pony
had been lost at sea presumed dead actually joined a pirate
crew with starboard bow started reviewing ponies on the pony
cursed crew.
Yeah.
Wasn't there a video though where like you like put up some
binoculars and you like see like oh oh his ship exploded.
Oh, he's dead.
No, the ship sank.
It was off.
It was binoculars and it was like oh shit.
There's the ship and it got hit by a cannonball and it sank,
but you didn't see anyone die.
Hmm.
Okay.
So the so what happened is the Gibbon takes swam away and
you know, got rescued had a whole piratey adventure.
Eventually was on the pony cast with starboard bow and then
that ship crashed and then they ended up in a TBAP resurrection.
So presumably they'd been on adventures hunting and then treasure
some such and then suddenly something happened and then
they're in the Lord ghosts.
Yeah, in the Lord ghosts.
Wait, are they in the Lord ghosts?
They're right at the end.
I don't remember.
Dog the dog the dog grasped them from like the clutches of
like a shadow beast Netherrealm because dog just can go places
like Pluto from Kingdom Hearts.
And and and and he's just brought them here and they're like
talking to flower head and flower heads like what the fuck
who are you and was like we're ponies.
So what the fuck's going on?
Are you doing in my review?
What?
Yeah.
What are you doing in my comic basically?
Mm hmm.
And then now they're in my now.
Now they're in my Canon comic universe, which is kind of
wrong.
RFCK and everything's all connected.
I gotta go that flower head plan I had, but it's it was
kind of fun just put them in there.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
Well, now I know.
I'm sure he's I'm sure he's thriving.
Next voicemail is called Ben's slave from the future.
Three, two, one, go.
We do eat things for customers.
It is a sir.
And I can't be bad news.
Great leader Ben said has recently spent all our country
money on 50,000 Bitcoin.
This was a lot of Bitcoin financial decision.
And now none of our people are eating.
So I come to the past to tell the young man said not to
spend all this money on you know, if I had that much
Bitcoin, I could just sell it.
And also Ben seems to get seeds in the future.
So don't remember the location.
Okay.
Thanks.
I won't.
Oh, damn.
I wish I had 50,000 Bitcoin.
Look, the future is looking up.
So that's like 50,000 squared.
So that's how many like like a billion, like 20 billion
dollars.
I don't know.
Uh, next one is called death and no piss.
Three, two, one, go.
Damn it.
I fucked up.
I recorded a voicemail and then I actually refreshed the
page and lost it.
But I was asking like, do you all think about when you
die, how much content there will be left that has your
voices?
Yeah, I think about that all the time.
So like if you have kids or if, uh, like Nate has kids
I got bit.
They'll always have recordings of your voices to hear.
Yeah.
It's not good, but they'll have it.
But also I was pissing during it.
So it's kind of funny.
I was going to call it death and piss.
Death and no piss.
I see.
I, uh, yeah, I think about that.
Like, man, if like if I ever had kids there, they could
just be like, man, my dad was on a podcast.
I could just go and like listen to like what he was
talking about in like 2000 and 18.
I don't know whether they'd give a shit.
Like they'd see it there.
Yeah.
I mean, it would probably be hard to, it's hard to know
because, you know, stuff like that of my own parents is
does not exist.
And so I can't know whether I'd be curious.
I to like listen to podcasts.
My dad and honestly.
If, if, if my dad had like had a podcast, I probably would
be curious and I probably would go back and listen to like
what was my dad's podcast about when he was like 30?
Yeah.
I would, I would check it out.
So yeah.
And then like having a parasocial relationship with
your own parent and then, and then to imagine.
Yeah.
I'm like, after you're dead, there will just be your voice.
Oh, I was going to say probably the thing that would
like if your parents like dying and you were like, wow,
I missed the sad that they died.
Like I, I should, I'm going to go back and listen to my dad's
old podcast and be like, so this is.
I'm hearing him from beyond the grave.
Sad.
That'd be really sad.
Yeah.
Ah, geez.
Be really sad.
Cheese.
Well, now I'm depressed.
Next.
In terms of like just general, like your voice being out
there recorded for all time.
I mean, I don't expect like YouTube to be around for all
time, but like certain recordings will probably exist
for a long time.
I think that just the sheer amount of stuff kind of precludes
the, I don't think that's the right word.
I don't know how to use that word.
Um, you'll be lost in, in the, the sea of people uploading
stuff that nobody's ever going to find that unless you're
super famous at one point, you're like a note in history.
Like, oh, then this podcast was the very important podcast
that caused this to happen.
Yes.
Like nobody will find it.
So it's basically secret.
It's basically like, like we never recorded it anyway.
After we die, the PCP will, the PCP is like only irrelevant
because like we are alive and people know us and people are
like, let's hear them.
After we die, the PCP will no longer be relevant because we
will be irrelevant because we won't even exist.
So what would maybe some people might be like nostalgic for
it and might go back and listen to an old episode now and
then, but like in the future, future, nobody's going to unless
one, unless we have some sort of something happens and we have
like an outsize influence on history and we become like someone
of historical importance and then it's like, oh, wow, that,
that guy had a podcast.
I'm going to go back and listen to his podcast.
Imagine if ancient Romans had podcasts.
They imagine if Milo of, of, of a croton or whatever.
Fucking wax podcasts.
Wax podcasts.
Yeah.
They'd get the, the gramophone or dig it into the wax.
The wax cylinders.
Yeah.
The wax cylinder is the, you would crank it on like the, in
like a piano or something, right?
Like a player on the wax.
Yeah.
So, you know, it's not that crazy.
That's basically, they had that in ancient Rome.
They did probably did have podcasts, but they, they, they
scrubbed the wax cylinders clean.
I think that in my opinion, Beethoven's ninth symphony is
my favorite podcast.
He didn't, he couldn't record his voice.
So he, he did the next best thing and just like wrote a bunch
of notes down and was like, yeah, listen to that.
That's my podcast.
Death sure is sad.
Lamal.
Next voice.
That's funny.
Actually.
Oh shit.
You're right.
Actually.
Next voicemail is called Berserk or Homestuck follow-up.
Three, two, one, go.
So I finally decided between Berserk and Homestuck.
You don't have to choose.
I just wanted to do a follow-up for the last.
Weeks voicemails about Berserk and like, yeah.
Uh, I'm reading Bleach.
Great.
I mean, Bleach isn't that bad.
It sort of falls off at some point, but this is some good
stuff in there.
I've never read it.
So I don't know.
I'm, I'm pretty sure it's not as good.
I'm pretty sure like visually like, uh, like, oh, cinematic
with panel layouts and like, oh, cool drawings, bro.
Oh, the story is pretty normal.
That's pretty cool.
I guess, uh, yeah, no, no experience of Bleach at all.
Last voicemail is an image.
So let's fucking take a look at that shit.
I really don't get this meme.
We've got you surrounded.
Come enjoy this meme.
No.
I mean, I mean, you know what?
You forced it on me.
I have no choice but to like it now.
But why, why are you smiling?
You don't get the meme.
I don't know.
You have an AK.
I, I don't understand.
I don't understand anything.
This is the week.
It's the new iteration of the same irrelevant meme.
Honestly, um, I'll be, to be honest though, this, this drawing
of me is like the most accurate one I've ever seen.
This one, this actually looks like me.
This is how I see myself in the mirror.
And I go, oh, don't show me that table with an AK.
47 and devilish grin, a big, a, you know, a big, a big round
head, sparsely covered with a huge forehead sticking out
and, uh, and the little, yeah, the sniveling little glass.
Although I don't have a beard at the moment.
I should though and just stop picking at my beard.
So I can get the, I got a haircut.
Oh, I got a haircut.
And now I have short hair again.
I had long hair for a long time.
Now it's short and I need to grow the beard so I can look
like, uh, brony con Ben again from those pictures.
You're, you posted those, those, those pictures of us on stage
or brony con the ones that that's, that's the look I need
to go back to.
That was peak then.
Uh, yeah.
So that's my hair situation.
And that's the end of the podcast.
Slaw.
Well, it's over.
Wait, let me refresh and make sure there's no last minute
voicemail.
Nope.
It's over.
Thank God.
Nice.
We did it.
Um, a patron, a patron.
Dot com slash the procrastinators speak, have that
com slash PCB voicemail.
If you want to leave a voicemail, don't leave any shitty
comments and be like, don't like the podcast anymore.
We know.
We know you hate the podcast.
We don't only do it to spite you.
Uh, anything else on the voicemail roulette or click.
Oh, we shot Tommy J.
Oh, Tommy J is dead.
Oh, darn.
Oh, dear Tommy J.
You can't, you can't put a voicemail.
So sad for a month or a week.
He said a month.
The voice that month.
Let's see if you can, you can play along.
That was the rules.
I don't, I don't make the rules.
It's just how it's just how it goes.
Uh, okay.
Good, good, good.
Bye.
Goodbye.
I love you.
Just like my parents.
Okay.
Later.