Hello everyone, welcome to the inaugural podcast from The Pro Crastinators.
I'm here with my internet friends. Everyone introduce yourselves.
I'm Digibro, and I, uh, spoke a lot of weed and promote Black stereotypes.
Yep, uh, who else?
I'm Hippocrit, I'm an African animal from the Africa, and I review video games.
I'm Ben Saint. I do a comic called The Vapors. Go read it.
Nice, and I guess I'll be Guy from Best Guy Ever. Go watch my YouTube anime videos, they're the coolest thing.
I'm so unsure of yourself.
Well, you know, it's one of those, I don't know. Anyway, so this is a new thing we're going to do.
We're doing podcasts on some general sort of theme that hasn't been decided yet,
but today we've got a topic, and our topic today is what constitutes a best game ever.
There was recently a poll on game facts, as there is like every five years or something for the best game of all time.
And so the first one to win in like 2005 or something was Final Fantasy 7,
and then the next one was Ocarina of Time, which are some of the two most beloved games ever.
And this year, to the surprise of all, Undertale, the new, that new meme game, Undertale, has taken the crown.
After being out for what, like three months or so?
Yeah.
And so, you know, it's quite an interesting situation. Possibly it was just rigged, but nonetheless raises some interesting questions.
Depends what you mean by rigged.
That's true. There's lots of ways to rig or not rig.
It was, it got won because of like rallying from Tumblr and other places.
Well, I mean, it really is.
Someone could have made a bot, but probably not.
I mean, it isn't.
I guess.
There's a conspiracy going on.
Speaking as the only person in this group who actually votes in every game FAQs poll and has done so for fucking eight years.
I know that two days ago, there was a poll called, did the best game ever contest convince you to try Undertale?
Oh, cool.
The answers went, the first answer was it might have, but I already owned it before the contest started, which had 21% of the votes.
Yes, I picked it up after it was featured in the contest battles, had 3% of the votes, 3.8.
Some, somewhat, I might have to at least try out the demo now was 20.32%.
Not really, it's not my style of game, not something I'd ever get, it was 29.61%.
And no, and I refuse to ever buy it purely out of spite, got 24.71%.
So you're telling me that less than 50% of those people said they had played it or wanted to play it at all?
Yes.
That's, okay, that's extremely interesting.
You know what, it's the kind of game that lots of people wouldn't play anyway, so I don't think it's going to make any difference.
Well, I mean, okay.
For old Toby Fox.
I know, the whole popular opinion thing is just interesting, but really it's not the focus of what we're going to talk about here.
So, you know, to make a comparison between like the other two, like the games that had previously won the polls, Final Fantasy VII and Ocarina of Time,
are both like complete game changers at the time they were released, which was around the same time anyway.
Undertale could be real influential, but like time, we have to wait and see.
That's the thing.
Final Fantasy VII and Ocarina of Time were both like technical marvels, absolutely blew away anything else that had come out at the time in their own ways.
Undertale is like not at all that way technically, but you could certainly make a case that it is that way in terms of like narrative and storytelling and like game immersion, that sort of stuff.
That's all really vague shit you just said.
I know, I know it is.
It's totally vague and subjective, but that's, you know.
The thing about Undertale is that Undertale does a lot of things that are all very interesting, but I think it only actually does like one thing that's totally new, which is...
Does it do anything?
I don't know if it does anything that's totally new.
I think the only thing it does that's very new is offering the meta commentary on save scumming.
That I don't think there's ever been a game that weaves your save scumming into the narrative in a way that you are changing the story by resetting your save.
You know, spoiler alert for anyone who didn't know that about Undertale, but for fuck's sake, it's already won a best game ever, Poland.
It's a six hour game.
Fucking play it if you're interested at all.
Now, that's a very interesting point, and it certainly has a unique twist on it.
However, there have been games that incorporate the death mechanic into the gameplay, which is a very interesting way to go.
Yeah, but just incorporating death is like step one.
Incorporating the act of save scumming is like a next level beyond that.
Even if we talked about a game like Dark Souls where they have written death into the story, that if you give up playing, then it means you hollowed.
If you keep going, it means that you're continuing to be reincarnated.
But Dark Souls handles this by saving constantly.
There is no save scumming in Dark Souls.
It's always saving for you.
Whereas, I don't think I've ever heard of an RPG where you can restart and you can redo things, but the game is keeping track of it.
I think there might be other games that do keep track of that kind of thing, but not for the reasons that Undertale does.
Not for narrative reasons.
I don't think it's hugely important whether or not it was the first game to do it or not.
I think it's important.
Well, I would make the argument that it's much more about the sum of its parts and how it works.
No, if it did something before anyone else did it, that's important.
Okay, it deserves credit, but like long term, I don't really think that's...
I know it's important.
I just think that Undertale is much more than just any one of those mechanics.
Okay, well you're moving the goalpost, so I'm not saying it's whatever.
This is not an adversarial thing, Ben.
We're all friends here.
We're all friends, I'm telling you.
Fine, fine.
Okay, but I kind of don't want to go into too much specifics here,
because I'm currently making a video called Best Game Ever Undertale, so go watch it when it's up.
This was your podcast idea.
I know, I know.
And you don't have to release this before Best Game Ever Undertale if you don't want to.
Maybe I'll save it till afterward.
You know what? Okay, I'm gonna go with that.
I'm going full out with this.
The whole save scumming thing, and the way that the characters respond to it,
is definitely the most special thing about the game.
And the way that it...
Is it totally subjective?
Well, alright. Okay, I'm gonna...
Warning, these are just my opinions.
They are not facts.
I cannot validate them objectively.
Alright.
Why, Ben? Do you think there's something else that's more important?
Well, just because you said definitely.
Yeah, I don't...
Well, definitely to me.
Yeah, just because it innovates in that way,
doesn't mean it's the thing that recommends the game.
I wouldn't recommend that game to someone on the basis that it's meta about its save states.
I would recommend it on the basis that it's a good story,
and it's really hype, and it innovates in a number of ways, that being one of them.
Well, I would. I just wouldn't use those terms.
I'd say it's really good.
I mean, that's what I like about it.
I mean, in discussing why it's good, that would definitely come up.
Well, yeah, but I wouldn't really want to describe that to someone before they play it.
Okay, you know what? We're getting on to our topic here.
The focus here is to discuss what it means to be a best game of all time.
And what was the motivations people had for voting for it?
So, let's just talk about that now.
So, I mean, just comparing the winners of this poll,
there's the technical innovations,
and then there's the classics,
and then there's this one game that's been out for a couple months that is completely taken over.
Was it reasonable to vote Undertale as a best game ever?
I mean, obviously it was a popular...
Some people's favorite game of all time.
Okay, okay, that's true.
But will we look back on it in...
It's been like 20 years since Thomas VII and Ocarina of Time came out.
And that's the conversation that I've been having with the DeVue,
and I think you have as well.
Yeah, we probably should have just brought him in this, but...
Sorry, DeVue.
He can be on some other time.
That, like, yeah, it is the best game ever right now.
And it might not be six months from now.
Well, right now is when we're voting.
Right, exactly.
That's true, that's true.
That's the issue, that, like, this poll...
Because this poll only happens once every five years,
and I guarantee you that if Undertale had come out one year ago,
it would not have won this poll.
Yeah.
This poll happened at a time when this game was at maximum hype,
when the highest number of people possible care about it,
because it's had three months to build up, you know,
where, like, the initial fan base exploded,
more and more people care, more and more people are creating things,
and a lot of that, all the ideas that have been had by the Undertale fandom
have sort of been realized by now,
or they will be within the next few months,
and six months from now, it will not be hype like this.
There will probably be something else
that a lot of the people who were super into Undertale have gravitated towards,
you know, maybe a new season of Steven Universe or something,
or the next bomb from that, you know,
and people will be talking about something else,
and the specific circumstance of a best game ever poll happening
and then someone campaigning really hard to make that game win
would not have happened.
And, you know, when you look at the voting,
like the way it was going,
because I turned you guys on to the fact that it was in the running early on,
and it had narrowly beaten Mass Effect 3 at the beginning,
and I remember that my impression was like,
huh, Undertale won, but I had marked it as winning
just because no one likes Mass Effect 3.
It's a game that's widely disliked
by even fans of the franchise.
So Undertale winning against Mass Effect 3 was kind of reasonable,
but every single round, its margin got bigger,
and it was beating games that are more and more considered classics
that more and more people love by wider and wider margins.
Suddenly, it's beating Fallout 3, which is a game everyone loves,
and suddenly it's crushing Ocarina of Time in the last round.
The numbers were crazy by then.
And the fact that it so barely even beat Mass Effect 3
says to me that the game FAQs for people who would have voted for this
would not have voted for Undertale.
And no question, there was a surge of outside influence
for the normal voting.
And I think it speaks to the influence of Undertale's popularity right now
that no other game got.
Because obviously there was tons of people who were mad about it.
There was a huge counter move against Undertale,
but it didn't work against Undertale.
Love Trump's Hate, Hillary, 2016.
No one was building up a counter force of people voting for Ocarina of Time.
Right, certainly not in the numbers of the influence.
Because if Ocarina of Time was relevant enough right now
that it could have beat Undertale, then it would have beat Undertale,
because there would have been enough people going,
no, Ocarina of Time is still the greatest game ever,
and after fighting it.
Well, you gotta ask yourself,
you gotta look at who's voting in the poll
and what percentage of them are making a legitimate vote based on favorite game,
and who's just coming in specifically.
Oh, someone told me to vote for Undertale to mess this thing up.
So it doesn't necessarily say anything about Ocarina.
I kind of agree.
Yeah, Ocarina could have been, if popular enough,
that that might have happened,
and the fact that it doesn't say that Ocarina maybe isn't that relevant,
or whatever, compared to Undertale.
You know, there was that post one of you guys linked,
of the guy who said that, like,
he said something to the effect that he voted for Undertale
just because he didn't want the same old games to be winning again and again.
Yeah, right, right.
And just it feels that way too.
And all I could think was, you know, noble goal,
why didn't you vote for Dark Souls, the actual best game ever?
Yeah, I think that Dark Souls,
and this gets to the heart of kind of what I want to talk about,
you know, what exactly makes a best game ever.
And I really think that something like Dark Souls,
I absolutely love Undertale, I'm crazy about it right now,
though the fan base, I find a bit obnoxious these days,
but Dark Souls has not only completely changed the game of making games,
it's had a huge influence, and nobody expected it.
And there's just, there's like a post and pre Dark Souls World,
and it's one of those milestone games,
like Final Fantasy VII, like Ocarina of Time.
Maybe we'll be saying the same thing about Undertale in a year.
Right, that's true, we might.
And you know, this is only my opinion, but we don't know.
It seems to me too early to say.
I don't think I could honestly make a case that I think it's the best game ever.
I can't help the feeling for me personally,
that like, if Undertale is bringing in a new revolutionary idea,
then it's not the game that's gonna have done it the best.
You know, like, I think if there's a game that takes the ideas of Undertale,
and then does it in the full package,
where it's not like an 8-bit indie game,
and it's not like 6 hours long,
and you know, and really, like, while the...
I don't know that I agree with you.
Hang on, here's where I'm going to completely 100% disagree,
because in no way do I think a game has to be anything more than the presentation Undertale has.
I think a game could look exactly like Dwarf Fortress,
and be the best game of all time, if it was built in such a way.
I just don't agree with the whole idea of a best game.
Like, I either want to play it, or I don't.
That's how I see it.
Like, it's good because I remember the fun times I had playing it,
and or I want to play it again right now.
Having like a best is just sort of pointless.
It's entirely masturbatory, that's true.
It's also as pointless as having scores.
They're kind of a little bit more helpful, but it all still boils down to
do I want to play it, yes or no?
Yeah, like, look at the poll.
Final Fantasy 7 one, then Ocarina one.
Like, they'd both been out the whole time.
Only thing to change was people's opinions,
and that's just how it's going to be forever.
Well, for me, I love having a best,
and I like having a most favorite thing, because...
It's very fun to...
I can look at it, and I can say, like, this explains my taste.
You know, like, this explains what I want.
This is what I want games to be.
Like, for me, I consider Dark Souls to be the best game ever,
because, like, it represents everything I value in video games.
It has, you know, it's a game that, at the same time,
has a deep and involving narrative,
but one that you can engage with on your own terms.
It has, it incorporates the way that you play the game
into the narrative and style of the game,
where, you know, if you die, that's part of the narrative.
If you give up playing, that's part of the narrative, you know?
There's nothing that you can do in the game
that would break your immersion with the game,
other than, like, glitches and stuff, you know?
Which that's super important.
I think that's what really makes Dark Souls a greatest game contender.
Like, that's what I really value in games.
Well, you know, I just want to throw out there.
That's fine, but I'm 13,
and my favorite game is Call of Duty Black Ops 2,
because it's the game I play every single day for six hours after school,
and I get more enjoyment out of that than anything else in the world.
But, I mean, and yeah, that's fair.
Yeah.
And, again, I think if we're judging,
if we're saying best game ever is anything other than personal opinion,
that just means it's consensus, right?
And that's the answer to our whole,
that we just answered the question of this whole discussion here.
It's consensus, there is no objective...
Well, podcast over.
Go on, Digi.
Yeah, well, you know, I think, yeah,
the reason Undertale wins in this contest is that, right now,
there's enough people who care about it,
but that's the funny thing.
And those people are able to galvanize votes,
because I bet a lot of those people, you know.
But that's the funny thing about it, though,
is that, like, six months later, if you ran this poll again,
it won't be Undertale.
And you have to wonder, like...
I think what that does is it puts into perspective
how, like, how subject to change the idea of the best is,
because, like, I think on-game FAQs,
as someone who's been on there for a long time,
like, the Legend of Zelda franchise and anything by Square Enix
are extremely overpowered for these contests.
They are franchises which people have set in their mind long ago
that they are the best thing ever,
and they will continue to vote that they are the best thing ever.
You know, like, the fact that fucking The Legend of Zelda,
a link to the past, beat Dark Souls in this whole,
you know, this game that is, what, God,
nearly 30 years old?
No, it can't be 30.
20 years, around 20 something years old.
And it's a game that literally every Zelda since
has iterated on and improved on, you know.
Every 2D Zelda has tweaked the controls to be a little better,
has tweaked the way the world building is a little better.
Every 3D Zelda game has used the same formula,
has used the same, you know, structure.
Well, you could say it's attachment to the original,
the, you know, originator of the formula.
You could, but like, I just think that,
that that game is like, it makes it that far,
mostly because people think it's a link to the past,
it's the classic, it's the original,
it's, you know, automatically great,
but not because they would actually play it today
and it would be their favorite game, you know.
Sure, yeah.
I think people voted up because it's the OG
and not because they legitimately think
that it's a better game than Dark Souls, you know.
Well, that makes me, that reminds me,
I want to go back to your point that in the future,
games may iterate on Undertale's ideas and do them better.
Because I don't think that's necessarily the case
because the thing, because like, like Guy was saying before,
the things that Undertale did better than anything else
were not technical things, they were creative things.
And they were, and anything technical that was going on there
was done in service of its particular narrative.
And so I'm not sure that's the kind of thing
that can actually be improved upon in like, any measurable way.
And only in an artistic way, which is entirely subjective, yeah.
I could see that, I guess for me,
because out of anyone in this call,
I am the least impressed with what Undertale is.
Because for me, like my biggest problems with this game were like,
I appreciate like the graphics and everything,
but to me they felt like a limitation.
It didn't feel like this was the ideal presentation.
No, absolutely not.
You're completely a limitation.
Look, the great things about Undertale were like,
like the resetting and the keeping in memory of the things you've done
and the way that it closes itself when you like lose to Flowey later on.
And the way the game, you know, permanently fucks up everything
if you do the genocide route and then try to do it again.
None of those are particularly impressive feats of programming
or game development, but to apply the ideas
in those kinds of meaningful ways shows just the creativity of Toby and all that good stuff.
Some of the art in the game is bad,
and that's because it was done by Toby before he got kickstarted
and had the money to pay artists.
That I think is a limitation, but like the fact that it's 2D pixel graphics
and you know, like white enemies in the Blackfield,
I don't think those are limitations.
I think even with all the money in the world, it would have still had that aesthetic.
I have no problem with 2D pixel art,
but if you went and played like a old, like let's say Super Nintendo game,
like Super Metroid or even, well, I guess Mario RPG wouldn't really be 2D pixel art per se,
but like they're really nice looking games that hold up really well.
The game that always comes to mind for me is like a Valkyrie profile for the PS1.
That game has like these luscious environments, gorgeous pixel art,
or if you were going modern, Muramasa or like Skullgirls or something,
like do you think that Undertale would not be better if it had the art budget to be a beautiful 2D game?
That's fair, and you can improve the art of anything?
I don't really think it would be any better.
Well, that's exactly what I was going to say.
What I really care about is the ideas,
you've got a sprite that conveys the idea that this is Heath's Flamesman.
Do not forget his name.
What if you had the exact same game?
All the ideas are the same, but the graphics are better.
I'll give it to you.
That would be better, I guess.
I guess that'd be better.
Would you say Hippo?
I don't like good graphics.
Yeah, I agree.
I mean, the best looking place in the game is the core.
The core has all these really fancy cloud effects and lighting effects
and everything looks really nice and crisp and shiny,
and I don't like it any more than the ruins,
which is like 2D, piece of crap drawn by a totally isn't an artist.
See, I feel the opposite.
I thought the ruins looked like shit,
and I didn't feel invested in the game yet because it looked like shit.
They do look like shit, but in a way that I'm totally fine with.
The thing that bothered me the most in Undertale design-wise
is that the whole game to me felt like a very long horizontal hallway,
because you always see, especially in the ruins,
you continually see a black border,
like you are walking through a tunnel that exists in a void.
In my mind, I'm picturing, like, designing this map
on the backdrop of nothingness,
because you're drawing a tunnel through,
like you're just drawing a tunnel and putting a game in it.
I agree, and let me add to that
probably the worst thing for that,
and it's so bad that even I was slightly bothered by it,
is that in the very final area,
in the walk up to the last boss,
you're walking along this gray platform,
and around you is just blackness
with a couple of really shitty-looking stone buildings
copy-pasted in a perfect grid on either side of you,
and I think what it's supposed to be suggesting
is that you're walking through and or over a city,
but it really just looks like these rectangular things,
like stuck on a black background.
It really is terrible.
I think if this game didn't feel...
because the moments that it really sinks in
are when you backtrack or you go back and forth,
and you really feel this sense of,
like, this is just a left-to-right motion.
There's no... you never really go far, up and down.
You never really go much in opposite direction.
And I mean, that could be on some level symbolic
that this whole game is one long trip to the right, you know?
But, like, I just felt like if this world felt more integrated
and less like a hallway and more like a, you know,
maybe like a Zelda-type thing,
which even Zelda, you know, feels like a fucking square,
so, like, once you really explore the map.
Now, see, I'm glad we're talking about this
because none of this had the slightest bit
of detrimental effect to me in my experience.
I don't think...
Like, what Undertale is does not need to be an open world.
Like, the story Undertale is trying to tell
is successfully told via a hallway.
I don't think it needs to be open world,
but I think that the...
I think that by having...
if that black space off to the side was drawn in
and, like, you could tell that there's a world right outside
this hallway you're in,
then that would sell me on it more.
So, I've always been a big fan.
There are places where the art could have sold things a little better.
Here's a video game.
Here's an RPG conceit that always bothers me, right?
That the Final Fantasy games do this much better
than any other JRPGs, in my opinion.
I hate it when I show up in a town in an RPG
and there's five houses.
And, like, those five houses are the only relevant,
like, you know, people live there
and they sell items or whatever,
but I'm meant to believe that in this world,
there are towns that literally consist of five buildings
and five people, you know?
Even a game like Skyrim,
like, there's towns in that game where you'll show up
and it's, like, a handful of houses and that's it.
And because, you know, the limitations
of building a game with that system.
But if you look at a Final Fantasy game,
there's always a huge amount of city
that you're just not exploring.
Like, Final Fantasy IX especially, you know,
like, the actual gameplay takes place
within, like, three or four streets in that city.
But you can see this huge, sweeping city,
so you feel like it's a real living, breathing place
in this world, you know, that would make sense
whether it was a video game city or not.
And, like, I think Undertale could have had some of that
and I think it would have been better for it.
Well, Snowden was a pretty big town.
Yes, Snowden felt pretty good.
I like some of the areas where you do see more background,
you know?
Obviously, like Ben said, the grey area towards the end
could have looked better, but it did at least suggest
that there was this city you were walking over
and, like, that you were in a place,
that you were walking through a place, you know,
as opposed to, like, the part where you're in the caves
where you turn on the lights and everything
and it's just, like, suspended hallways in a black void,
you know, like, where is this? What is this?
Now, this isn't really an excuse for the game design,
but there is at least the idea that things were sort of
deliberately constructed in a, it's a lampshade hang, I guess,
that monsters love puzzles and, like, winding dungeons and things.
Yeah, the puzzles are definitely an element of that
and, like, the ruins are definitely designed
in a way that is like that
and is a single hallway full of puzzles
and the game, like, points that out for sure.
The caves, though, I don't think there's really any defense.
Well, you know, are the caves...
I don't know. I don't know, maybe.
I don't know if that excuse covers the caves and everything,
but, yes.
There's a lot of things about this game that are minimal
in a really good way that I don't think would have been better otherwise.
This game would not be better with voice acting.
Oh, certainly not. I don't think those games would.
The sound design is perfect because they used sound effects
that sound like the fonts that they're showing, you know?
The sound design is perfect.
The sound design is like...
I think the sound design might be the one thing about this game
that's, like, completely beyond reproach.
Yeah, I think the moment that...
Because, like, when I think about this game,
the dramatic moment in the game that sticks out the most to me
is when it says...
It's a dramatic moment where it says you are filled with determination,
but it spells it out one letter at a time with spaces between it.
You are filled with determination, and I was like...
I just remember feeling like, oh, fuck, yeah, you know what, I saw that,
and you could not have done that with voice acting or without text.
Along with the musical beat that plays at that moment.
It's like that...
Man, that fucking fight, dude.
I don't think the music could have been any better
Dude, these beats are banging, bro. These beats are off the charts.
They're radical.
I'm just saying that I think it is possible
for Undertale to have been a better game
just by having little things that it could have done,
like having more graphical budget
or a more imaginative layout of its world,
or just being able to spend maybe a little more time
with the characters and in the story
to really feel like you knew them and what they were about.
Here's another point that we've previously discussed,
which is, I mean, I would call Undertale a 10 out of 10 game for me.
And you convinced me previously that that doesn't mean
that it has to be perfect.
It's just one of those legendary games that you really love
and that you'd play again, and super good.
And so on that basis, and that applies to best game ever.
It could still be the best game ever, theoretically,
despite not being perfect.
It just can be topped.
If another game comes out that's even better,
then that has to be the best game ever.
That's absolutely possible, and that will always be possible.
I might be totally out of whack here.
I might be the only person in the world,
but I think maybe there are some technical things
that could have been improved on the graphics and the layouts.
I think the one thing that I actually would have preferred
to be a little different would be the writing.
Not in every way, but in certain parts,
where certain parts tried a little hard
through their writing to sell the emotional thing.
What's an example of that?
Mostly towards the end.
Just the sheer number of lines that Asgore gets as he's dying,
trying to sell him as the nicest guy.
And the sheer number of times that Azrael has to say,
like, why do I feel this way?
Why are you being so nice to me?
What's happening to my heart?
Here's a series of questions that were raised for me throughout the game.
When I'm going through the caves,
why does it just so happen that there's a bunch of text scrolls
on all the walls that just happen to be in order
and tell me the story of this world?
Oh, come on. That's totally understandable
that they record their history.
I don't have an answer for you.
Why do they record it that way, though?
It's a bunch of text scrolls in order just because you're passing through this area.
Or when you're on your way to Asgore
and you keep running into monsters
and each one is picking up the story where the last monster left off
and telling you what happened in the past,
which isn't even in character for these monsters,
for them to be telling you this part of the story
and speaking normally, you know?
Those little things took me out of it in a way
where I was like, this is a way too convenient way to do exposition,
to have it, you know, dimed out just right at the right pace,
but it's not in a way that makes sense in the context of what's actually happening.
I think that both of those things that you mentioned are like deliberately...
Okay, whether they're successful or not, I don't know,
but I think that those are both like deliberate immersion breaks.
That's possible.
With deliberate gamey moments.
With a scene like that, you're making a trade-off
of keeping the world feel 100% intact
to, in the case of the monsters delivering the lines,
which is one of my favorite parts in the whole game,
you're making a trade for an emotional payoff.
And in my personal opinion, I think it was totally worth it.
I like how this podcast has just become a review of Undertale.
Yeah, that's fine.
It's all to getting to the core of the matter here.
Well, I mean, at least we're still talking about what makes a good game.
Right.
Here's what I want to know, actually.
What I really want to ask each of you is that
if you got to choose the winner of Best Game Ever, what would you have picked?
Final Fantasy VII.
Like, and I can pick any game at all.
Yeah, you can pick any game. What would you pick as the winner of Best Game Ever?
That's a good question.
Hippo, do you have an answer?
Probably Dark Souls.
Cool.
Because I could play that over and over again forever.
Ben?
I mean, Dark Souls is a pretty strong contender.
Oh, God.
I came into this podcast about the Best Game Ever
without having prepared an answer to this question.
You know, now that I'm thinking about it,
I think right now I might fucking pick Undertale.
Yeah.
Even though I fucking railed against it
and was like, this is fucking bullshit.
It could never beat Final Fantasy VII.
It can't beat Ocarina of Time.
I think I might, right now I'm kind of feeling like
Undertale is like my favorite game ever.
You know, I'm kind of with you.
I think it needs some time to sit and like, you know,
we need the benefit of hindsight to really know if it's the best game ever.
But its pedigree is impressive
and its list of accomplishments is long.
I have always held like the idea that my favorite game
is whatever I can think of when somebody asks me that question.
Because I'm never thinking of it at any other point.
So it's just because something I...
I might have to, I might fit Binding of Isaac.
That's cool.
So that's your Call of Duty.
I fucking love Binding.
Yeah, it is.
But better.
That's fine.
I fucking love Binding of Isaac.
I think it's like a brilliantly designed game.
Well, let me...
It appeals to me in like every way that a game can.
I'm with you.
I love the shit out of it
to the point that I might even call it the best game ever.
My...
You know, I was thinking about this
and I talk about this in the review.
One of my...
Probably my favorite thing in a game
is that feeling of like slow progression
up to an ultimate SuperDuper awesome best ending ever.
And so like in that sense, like Chrono Trigger
is one that does that.
You can get like good endings along the way in various ways.
But if you really work at it
and really do the extra mile in the game,
you are rewarded with like the ultimate SuperDuper
best ending everything works out.
Another game like that is Radiant Historia.
And I really like it when they fake you out.
You get like a good ending, but it's not perfect.
And then you go investigate.
And you actually...
Both those games happen to be time travel games
like Undertale is.
It's a good formula for that, I guess.
And so you put in the work
and you get your best ending ever.
You don't have time to travel at Undertale.
Well, sure you do.
When you reset the game,
you're going back in time.
Oh, okay, sure.
But Undertale...
Man, Undertale does that too.
But like Undertale does that
to get the true pacifism ending.
The ending where you meet Azrael.
Like, that's where Chrono Trigger
or Radiant Historia ends.
They end with the Azrael fight.
But Undertale, in my opinion,
continues after that with a whole new thing
with the genocide ending.
And in playing that,
there's all this other shit
that comes out of the woodwork
that really puts it like way over the top
in its own category
in a way that no game I've ever played
has done before.
So it's like...
It gave me every single thing I wanted
and then just a fuckload more.
So, you know, there's nothing like it for me.
It was by far the most big life experience
out of probably any game I've ever played.
Yeah.
You know,
I kind of just want to go over all the reasons
that I don't love Undertale as much.
Sure.
What's your favorite game?
I think Undertale is great.
Oh, I already said it was Dark Souls.
Oh, yeah, right.
But it's funny because Dark Souls,
my reason is opposite of Gibbons
because, or Hippos, rather,
because Hippo said that
Dark Souls is a game he feels he can always...
I'm back. I'm back. I'm back.
Okay, good.
I didn't even know you were gone.
Yeah, no one knew.
Alright.
God damn it.
Hippo was saying how Dark Souls is a game
he can pick up and play anytime.
He can play it over and over again
and keep playing it.
I actually don't really like playing Dark Souls.
You still haven't beaten it, right?
Yeah, I've never beaten it.
I've played up through Ornstein and Smo.
But I like it more because
I like watching it and I like thinking about it,
and I find it so...
Which is so you. It's so you.
I find it so naturally pleasing
because I love the way the controls are,
the way that the game feels,
that it's a game about running up to an enemy
and timing your attacks right
and dodging, and that even though it's an RPG,
it completely plays like an action game.
It's sort of the best of both worlds.
I love that every environment is so different,
and yet it all feels right together.
Dark Souls is a game where there's a lava level
and there's an ice cave type place.
There's this and that.
Highly original level designs.
Right. They're all these different stuff
that you usually see in games,
but they all flow together so logically
that you don't really question it that much,
even though it would be weird
for some of those things to exist in the same place.
It doesn't even make sense, like,
Ash Lake where is that, but it's not important.
But that's what's even cool.
Ash Lake is my favorite.
Yeah, it's the best.
Ash Lake for me is like...
I've always said it's like the keystone
for what I appreciate about Dark Souls,
which is that...
And the fact that it's hidden behind two invisible walls.
Yeah, the fact that you would never see it
unless you were really into it.
Either you heard about it from someone
or you were just exploring this game
down to the fucking teeth.
And it's this magical, ethereal, strange world
that seems to be underneath the world.
It's a lake that's underneath the entire world somehow.
And you go down there and there's two fucking hydras,
and then this ancient dragon king who doesn't say anything
and he just gives you a dragon head
and now you can breathe fire.
It's insanity.
But that's the most magical feeling place in the game.
Totally.
I don't think...
For me, the coolest things about games,
these are the things I value the absolute most,
are the cathartic feeling of movement.
Just feeling good controlling your character
and having a world that I'm interested in.
Pretty much world building and catharsis.
Those are the two biggest things.
So I'm a huge fan of Ocarina of Time.
It's actually my second favorite game
because in comparison to all of the other Zelda games,
I feel like this is something that no one talks about enough
when they talk about Zelda.
They all have totally different controls.
Even though they're all the same basic controls,
the way Link moves changes a lot.
If you play, say, Twilight Princess or the Wind Waker,
Link kind of controls a motorcycle where you hold forward
and you steer him left and right
and he moves in a weird circular fashion.
Whereas in Ocarina of Time, he moves more like a 2D character.
He moves exactly as much as you press the control stick.
When you let go, he stops.
When you touch to the side, he turns to the side.
You just have a more direct control.
I could see thinking it feels a little stiff, maybe,
but I don't know.
I always feel like every step has weight to it.
Everything Link does in that game has a certain weight to it.
The way controlling him feels is so good
that there was a point when I was playing that game
and I was taking song requests
and people were telling me songs to sing.
I was doing side flips and back flips
in Kakariko Village for 45 minutes.
I was doing back flips and side flips.
Was it a good time?
Yeah, it was great.
You can just flip off of everything.
You can start flipping off of ledges
and watching how he reacts to different elevation changes
and stuff.
It feels so good to watch him flip around in that game.
The Wind Waker has almost the same feel,
but the Wind Waker is also...
You have to get in a boat.
You're on this little island and you can roll around a little bit,
but then you get in a boat and you sail somewhere.
Being in the boat is cool as an idea,
but it doesn't feel as good.
In Ocarina of Time,
I could just literally side flip across the whole world
if I wanted to.
That's what all the speedruns are,
because side flipping is the fastest way to travel.
If you watch a speedrun,
they'll just side flip through the whole fucking game.
It looks crazy.
The world is very dense and intricate,
and everyone in it has their own story
that they're living out that has nothing to do with you
unless you make yourself a part of it,
which is a great thing about Dark Souls.
All the NPCs have their own game they're playing.
Each of them is the main character of their own story,
and each of them is basically, if you failed,
this is what you would become.
They're all other heroes from other timelines.
As Sunbro points out,
time is fucked up in Lordran,
and everyone here is from their own game,
but they all fuck up.
They all die, except Sunbro,
if you keep him alive through the whole game.
I like that.
I like it when the world sort of exists without you,
and Undertale does a pretty good job of that,
where it has the characters show up in the bar,
and they continue to have their own dialogue together
and their own things that they're up to,
even though the game is so short
that they can't really get up to a lot.
You don't see a lot of things going on in the world,
but it's nice that they have those things.
In that sense,
I definitely think that
all the characters of the game exist
to make you like them.
Like you said, it might not have been as much time as would be ideal,
but their function...
Are you back to talking about Undertale now?
Briefly, yes.
It's just that the characters, to me,
I like them all,
but they really are simply a tool
to attach you to the world
to put you through the exercise
of playing Undertale
and making the decisions
that you make when you play that game
based on those feelings,
and it really is most effective
if you really care about the characters.
And for me, I was totally on board.
I like every single character there a ton,
except for Alphas, who's kind of an asshole,
but she's okay.
But you know what? I want to talk for a second,
just to finish up what you were saying before.
The way you were describing all those things
and the way each of us have talked about
our favorite games,
I really think shows the kind of person we are
and as a result, why we like
the kind of games we like.
You're describing all these...
your appreciation for the construction of the world
and the way it all feels,
even though you don't really play
a ton of games, like Dark Souls, if you've never played it,
it's your favorite game,
but you like to step back and appreciate it
as a big piece of art altogether.
And then Ben, like Binding of Isaac,
is his favorite game,
and Ben likes to just sit down for hours
and just play a game and just get into it,
like master it.
He played...
Orbezatben, you played that?
Oh, a fucking Dungeon Crawlstone soup.
Yeah, yeah.
It took me a year and a half to beat it.
Congratulations.
And then Gib, I don't know,
Gib seems like he's looking for light-hearted,
fun most of the time when he's playing games.
He plays fucking Dark Souls.
It was his favorite game.
To kind of goof around.
Is that wrong?
I don't think that is right.
I think he's doing the same thing I'm doing
and just getting immersed in a day-old game.
You don't talk about it that much.
Yeah, there you go.
I want to kill things in Dark Souls.
And then there's me,
who, more than anything,
likes to play games where
a hero goes on a journey and achieves self-actualization,
clearly a projection
of my deep personal insecurities
and a desire to fulfill them.
You know, all of these things
are what make each of our favorite games
and it's completely a projection
of our values
and the kind of person we are.
I would feel a little guilty
picking Binding of Isaac as a game of all time
because it's so deficient
in the story category.
And I do like game stories,
but I don't, yeah,
I guess I just don't feel like there
what I really play games for.
Because I, like,
with Dark Souls, I can kind of
rest assured that I do think
it's a cool story,
but I don't really value
the actual narrative that much.
I like that it's so,
that there's so much going on
and that it sort of feels like it exists without me,
but the actual specifics
of who the characters are
and what they mean,
the lore has never really grabbed me that much.
And because of that, it's fun.
There's no way that you'd love
a game like Undertale as much as someone like me.
Just because our priorities are so different
in that sense.
Or like Jesse, I guess.
My little brother Shade, who's a big fan of both Dark Souls
and Undertale, he gets deep into
lore and deep into knowing
the background info.
I like the lore a lot in Dark Souls, that's probably my favorite thing.
He really only started getting into
Undertale once he started
learning all the crazy
background stuff.
Did he get into it after playing it or to
start to play?
He played through it.
He did the pacifist run, he was doing the genocide run.
But then he just started coming up to me
every day with all these new facts
he'd learned about the game.
And telling me all this stuff that he'd heard.
Because I didn't watch anything
of the game after beating it.
I just kind of played through and was done.
But then I kept hearing new things about it from other people.
And all of it is very cool
to know that it's all there.
That kind of stuff doesn't make me
love the game more.
I'm just like, oh, that's really neat.
It's cool that it's there.
It itself is not like anything mind-blowing.
The only thing about the Dark Souls
story that I think really stands out to me
is great is the whole fire metaphor.
And everything
that they try to do with that.
Yeah, that was very effective.
Like, Ocarina of Time, I could not give a
single fuck about the narrative of that game.
Even though when I was a kid it was the
greatest narrative I'd ever seen before
in my life.
When I was a kid, growing up...
You don't think that now just have not explored?
Growing up, Ocarina of Time was my
favorite game purely from having
watched my cousin play it and having never
seen a game with a story before.
And I literally never
heard of a game having a story.
What, like 1998?
It was probably 99 or 2000
when I watched him play through it.
You got to play more Final Fantasy past Digi.
My dad was an N64. I'd never
seen any other console.
Uh, Conker's Bad Fur Day. Greatest story ever told.
Yeah, and I found out about that one later
and I always wanted to know the story
because the story seemed really interesting.
I'm making that up. I've never even played it.
Oh, it's got a phenomenal...
I don't know about the story, but the
dialogue and the voice acting
is fucking incredible in that game.
Unfortunately, I don't like playing the game at all.
I think it's boring and shitty, but
the dialogue is great.
Like Banjo?
Is it a collectathon like Banjo?
It is exactly like Banjo because
it's not, though, because Banjo-Kazooie
is more of a platformer
that's more skill-based.
It has platforming challenges.
Conker feels, to me,
more like an adventure game.
It's sort of like Psychonauts
where every level is just something
different and I think that's the biggest
problem, is that it constantly...
every single place you go has a new mechanic
for you to learn, but none of them are like
fun, you know?
Oh, and speaking of best game ever, Psychonauts
too, guys, go give your money to Tim Schaefer,
the whole fucking hack himself,
3 million, and it'll make Psychonauts
too. Fuck you, Tim Schaefer.
I think Psychonauts is super overrated.
It's like that weird underrated, overrated sort of game.
Well, the story and story loves it so much.
But the actually playing
the game is just frustrating as fuck,
especially the last level is the worst thing
I've ever played before.
And remember that time in that game where you're
like talking with the girl and you're like,
oh, we gotta come up with a plan. And she's like,
yeah, we gotta do something. Oh, we gotta go save everyone.
We should make out.
That was probably the funniest thing
in any game I've ever played.
My favorite part is when you find the two
like quiet kids sitting up on the roof.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
It's not in the story. It's not a cutscene.
It's just at some point you're walking around.
You can go up on a roof and like the two
like nice, quiet, like I think maybe
they're implied to be religious kids.
The boy and the girl, they're sitting up there.
And if you listen to them, they're just like,
look at all the people down there.
They look like tiny little ants.
And the other one's like, they are ants.
Worthless little ants.
And if you hit them,
they like respond to it,
but in a real like, they try to be nice
about it. You can tell they're really hurt
emotionally.
By the way, like you use this way,
you do a psychic punch on them and one of them's like,
hey, look who's still punching.
And then your character's like,
and your character's like, oh God,
what have I done?
You know, I told that kissing story once
when me and my friends were in line for lunch
in college somewhere.
And like as I got to the end and just yelled at like,
we should make out this guy behind me in line.
You're just like, dude, you do that too?
Like, yeah, I just,
if you go up to, if you're in a party
and you go up to enough girls and you say that,
what I was gonna make out with you?
Yeah, that guy was alpha as fuck.
My role model.
It led you to some important life lessons.
Some important game.
Anyways, you know, there's
there's only ever for me been one
game that like I legitimately
care about the story and that's
the Mass Effect.
Mass Effect 1 and 2.
Is that just because it did so much
to give the characters and make them
like fleshed out people? Yeah, it's the only game
I've played where like, I just
honest to God found it
really interesting.
Like the characters in the world
are so fleshed out
and just like
it's a game that
has like any
story I could name that like
like any like HBO drama or anything
like that that's considered to be like a great
narrative or something.
It's as good as that.
Like the story is legitimately as good
as any story I've ever heard before.
Yeah, Commander Shepherd, I'm
the Asari lady. Nice to meet you.
I'm super attracted to you.
I love you more than anyone I've ever known
in my entire life. You've completely
opened me up and let's
immediately have sex right now.
10 out of 10 writing, dude. Sounds like a
10 out of 10 writing. I will say
that not
not everything in Mass Effect is
equally interesting.
My favorite in the trilogy is the second
game and there are some of the characters
you meet like late into the game
are just kind of whatever who cares.
Yeah. But like
you know, I think Garrus is a
fantastic character. His whole arc is great.
Tali's pretty
is a really fun character. I have a deep affection
for the quarry and papal.
Rex is great, you know, throughout
all the games and like the entire
everything that has to do
with the Genophage
and the fucking
what are they called?
Not a sorry.
The other guys. Rex's race.
The Krogans. Everything that has to do with
the Krogans and the Genophage
and Mordyn Solis is like
the most interesting shit ever.
Mordyn especially is my favorite character
in like any game because
he's in the second game. You'll meet him
pretty early on and he's a doctor
who he literally
created the Genophage and committed the
genocide of killing all of the Krogans
and he joins your team
and that's going to cause some
tension. The thing about it is though
that he did it because
he was trying to save the galaxy.
Just like when we nuked Hiroshima
and Nagasaki. To him it was like
deciding to choose
the needs of the many over the needs of the few
but then the long term consequences
of it make it questionable
whether it really was better
or worse.
He sort of has to grapple with
deciding whether or not he
still feels that way and then has
a fantastic payoff in the third game.
It's by far the best thing about the third game
is the end of Mordyn and
the Krogans story.
I've heard.
It's just legit fascinating and the game
just has so much information about everything
because not only
do you go to planets and you can like read
little, you'll find text logs in places
and learn little details here and there
but then the game has like
an insanely huge codec
that you can read through and it's like
a lot of it's voiced so you'll have like
a narrator telling you like audio books
about the world.
Another game that has a massive
log like that
is Final Fantasy 13
and all the seasons.
Why is it that it's so much more enjoyable
to read through the codecs of Mass Effect
than Final Fantasy 13?
Probably because the...
I haven't played 13 but I am playing
Lightning Returns and I have been
reading all the codecs in that
and having a great time with it.
Well that blows me away that you actually read through them all
because man I hated reading them
that Lightning Returns
is batshit insane.
Like the story is the craziest
thing that I've ever heard of
because it takes place in a world
where everyone has become immortal
and no one new has been born in
500 years and everyone who is still alive
has been alive for 500 years
and Lightning has become...
great. That sounds like a fucking
crazy fantasy world to me.
I would love to live in that world.
It's fucking insane and Lightning is now
like an angel working for God
trying to save everyone's souls
because the rapture is about to happen
and reset the world.
I wish that was an original game and did not
involve Lightning.
Did you the way you're describing
Final Fantasy 13.2 Lightning Returns to me
sounds awesome.
It's the third one, not the second one.
The thing is, the thing about Lightning Returns
I mean the characters themselves
are like planks of wood.
Like they're not
interesting characters but the world
is just so insane
that I'm like fascinated
with it and I keep learning new things
and there's like there's so many like gods
and random bits of
like lore that
have nothing to do with anything and I'm like
what the fuck is this like I'm not
necessarily saying that it's like a great story
but it's just fascinating that a game
is like this and to me it's sort of
like how every RPG kind of
ends with you like killing God
and it feels like this game is what happens
like if you had already killed God
and then the world got really weird afterwards.
Kind of like the end of God of War 3
I guess. Yeah a little bit.
I always thought that was interesting and they just don't describe
like the world is fucked but
they just that's the end. Yeah he just kind of ruins
everything and like yeah and
you know most of these RPGs
they don't really usually have much
of a day-new-mon. They don't really show you
what happened after you
changed the entire nature
of reality and like this
kind of... You just get
all your party members, stand them on the bow
of their airship and have them all look up
at the sky as like the
rubble of their past world
and then have the main character jump off and disappear
and not be heard of again. Well nobody cares
about like how
lock, marry cellies
and settles down to like become
you know and it started venturing
like mercenary business. Nobody
gives a shit. We just know that they won
and then they can just do whatever. You can just fill it in.
It's really hilarious because
on the one hand I feel like
the reason they can get away with
doing this story in Lightning Returns
is that it's a sequel to a popular
game so people will buy it.
But I think it's
a terrible sequel because
it takes place 500 years later and everyone's
totally different now because they've aged
500 years. Not to mention
the fact that 13.2 ends on a huge
cliffhanger and to wait
like 500 years is just the worst
fucking thing you could possibly do.
I'm still mad. If it wasn't
like 50 hours long
I'd be tempted to play
Final Fantasy 13 and the sequels
just to see because sometimes
I end up liking things that nobody else like
and I would be curious if I could find anything
to love about it. Here's the thing, Lightning Returns
is a lot more well-liked
by critics in the first two.
I don't know about if fans like it
but critics in general were like
this game is actually kind of fun to play
and it's... I'm not
far into it but it seems
like it's very short
but it also seems like you can
fuck up so badly so early on
that you will need to play it twice. This is a game
you can fail. It takes place
over the course of 13 days
and you basically have to
save enough souls by the end of 13 days
by doing like... you have to get through
all the main missions and then you can do a certain
number of side missions if you want to get like a perfect
run but if you
fuck up and you don't do the missions in time
then you just lose and you get a game over
but you're allowed to do like
a new game plus and like even if you
fail and sort of keep all your weapons
so I don't feel too bad about the idea
that I'm probably gonna fail because I fucked up
so bad on day one that I feel like
I'm already set back forever
and it's a little bit confusing because the game
like as if
in response to the previous games is like
totally open like you just go
wherever you want and do whatever you want
to an extent and so
like I got lost. This is obviously a reaction
to the whole...
I kind of got lost trying to find my way around
and like figure out where everything is
and I felt like oh shit I don't really like
I actually I kind of don't like the
mechanic of the time thing because I feel like I really
wanted to get engrossed in this world
and instead I'm running around like crazy
you know it's a
it's a lot like Dead Rising where you
it's so strict about
being on time that you
like it's almost at odds with what you actually want
to do in Dead Rising which is to just go
fucking kill zombies with weird
you know weapons and shit. Yeah I've heard
mixed things about the Dead Rising
I think Dead Rising is a
fantastic game after watching them play it
on Game Grumps and being reminded of it
I think it's fucking awesome.
If I if I might bring this conversation
back to the topic of the best
sure sure let let me
I'll just I'll just start a whole new thing
Okay. My pet peeve
is people who think
that a best game
and a favorite game should be two
different things. Those people deserve to be firebombed.
I think they should all be consigned to the flames.
I think they can be two different things.
No you're different
from your own face are you recording Jesse?
I am recording.
What the fuck? Jesse's here?
I showed up. Okay.
The count of three say Misty. One, two, three
Misty. Misty. Misty.
Okay good.
No okay Jesse defend your position.
Why is it okay to separate them?
Well okay.
I wouldn't call Crazy Taxi the best game ever made.
Well that's just objectively wrong.
Okay. But I would totally call it my favorite
game ever made.
Why isn't it the best? Isn't the game's function
to give you enjoyment? Wait I have a question Jesse.
Yeah. Would you say it's exclusively
your favorite game?
No. I have like five
favorite games ever made.
Is one of those your also your pick for their
best game?
I guess. I don't fucking know.
Is it Lion King? Yes.
Lion King for Sega Genesis
is the best game ever made
objectively. No.
And that's the end of the conversation.
The monkeys cost at all
of its points.
But it's got the hippos.
Right? Hippocrates.
It's your favorite game.
I'm with you Ben.
I hate when people try to like
to make...
I hate any best game ever list
that goes by impact
and then has like games that aren't even
good anymore on the list.
Like oh this year
I played
down well for five hundred hours
and fucking loved every second of it.
On the other hand
I thought Undertale was a pretentious piece of shit
but you know everyone likes Undertale
and it made such a good thing
for the indie scene that I'm going to name it
the best game of the year. Fuck that.
I'm glad you guys are talking about this now
because I sort of mentioned before
I'm going to sound like a hypocrite now
but I really do take
impact on the world
into my examination
of what I think is the best game ever.
Well that's wrong. That's wrong of you.
What I value in a game is
the influence it's going to have
not only on just me but on everyone.
Bullshit. Like I really love Undertale
but I think that it has
more implications. I like Undertale
because I see it. That doesn't make it a better game.
Undertale is a quiz
that I want everyone to take to learn about themselves.
That doesn't make the game any better than it is.
It does. What?
Do you think that Undertale is
the best game ever
because of its impact
or because of your value
of its impact?
Definitely because of my value.
If you didn't give a fuck about Undertale
but it had a huge amount of impact
would you still call it the best game ever?
Definitely not. I would certainly say that.
So it is ultimately
just you saying that it's the game you like the most
and therefore it's the favorite.
The reason it's the game you like the most
is because it has impact.
I guess that just happens to be my
what I value.
What I've been talking a lot is that I feel
so weakly about this whole subject.
I just don't care.
Get out of my podcast!
It is kind of totally stupid and pointless.
Well, we're fair enough.
Okay, yes.
Games are fun. I like them.
I agree.
I said Binding of Isaac before.
I'm not super committed to that choice.
I really wouldn't say that I have a strong pick
for a best game ever.
Hey guys, go make a Procrastinator's Wiki
because this is Binding of Isaac.
It's official.
Whatever.
If I'm picking one,
I honestly don't see how you can defend
any other position than mine
because there's no objective standard
for how good something is.
Therefore, the only metric
of how good it is is how much you like it.
Therefore, your favorite and the best
should be synonymous.
I agree.
I think that the best game of 2015
was Dengeki Bunko Fighting Climax.
Fine.
Is Mage here?
Yes, Mage is in the call.
Are you recording? Are you recording your audio?
Mage, we can barely hear you.
Wait, you are recording your audio, right?
Well, you gotta record your audio.
It's gonna be all fucked up.
Don't speak until you're recording your audio.
It sounds like you're talking into a headset
that's on the opposite end of the room.
Guys, it's gonna be blank sounds.
Somebody say something.
What's...
Well, I don't know what the hippo was trying to say earlier.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
What do you say something?
Was I...
You got mad at me for cutting you off.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Oh, I forgot.
Okay.
You're recording, right?
You're recording?
Ah, you got it. You're recording right now.
You're recording? Okay, let's sync up.
Okay. On the count of three, say,
Misty's my favorite Pokemon trainer.
I like red, blue, the best is the best game.
Okay, ready? One, two, three.
Misty's my favorite Pokemon trainer.
Fuck you, man, you piece of shit.
Okay, go on, Gib.
Hippo.
I have no idea.
What I'm doing here...
Mage, what is your opinion on the best game ever?
Yeah, what's your favorite game?
Undertale?
Yeah, yeah, what do you think is the best game ever?
And is it the same as your favorite game?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I don't
particularly believe in the best game ever,
what I'm calling, but
my favorite game is definitely Undertale.
And I...
Really? Yes.
Shock. Would you say of all time?
Fair enough. Yeah, of all time.
Of all time, would you say?
At this moment in time, yes.
Okay, okay.
I think I have one favorite game of all time,
because it's going to change.
Yeah, but you know, all of these
questions are in the context of the time.
The phrase of all time is a weird
phrase, because it's
never of all time.
That's the thing.
I mean, it means up to now.
It means right now.
That's the phrase we should adopt.
Instead of saying my favorite of all time,
we should be saying my favorite now, currently.
That doesn't sound as impressive.
That's the whole point.
Because I feel like of all time...
Well, I feel like of all time implies
and I think this is how people think
of it and this is why people sometimes
vote for those older games that they don't care about anymore
is that they think of it in terms of
what game they liked the longest.
Which is a perfectly valid way
to like a game. To be honest,
that's why I'm picking Isaac. I haven't played
the new Isaac, but I loved
it so much and I played it for so long
and I still think it's a great
and amazing game.
Like right now I care way more about
Undertale than about Binding of Isaac
and yet I'm not comfortable picking Undertale
just because it's so new.
I'm glad you brought this up. I wanted to talk about this too.
And it seems like...
I think this shows kind of maybe
the context of the gaming industry
or maybe just us as consumers of it
with like YouTube and Let's Plays and all the stuff now.
So like the previous winners of the poll
were Final Fantasy 7 and Ocarina of Time,
which are really old games that have
their like legends.
I was here talking about the game path, I think.
Yeah, the concept of a best game ever and what it means.
So those games won.
That's kind of what inspired the discussion.
Those games won kind of based on their
legacy status
and I think that maybe it had something to do
with the way that games were coming out
and the way people appreciate games.
But these days, like what are the most
popular games in the world? Like League of Legends?
Stuff that's like
quickly consumable
and can be like
completed rapidly
and is like mass consumable.
And I wonder if it
doesn't say that as a culture of people
playing games, we have more
interest in something like Undertale
that's super new and might
not even last very long.
But our focus is
attuned to these sort of
you know like spurts of popularity
less so than it is to the big
context of all the games we've
ever played. Our focus is shifting
I'm wondering.
It's an interesting point.
I think
a big part, now that you've made me think
about it, I think a big part of the reason
that we're going to see a shift away from
Zelda and Final Fantasy winning everything
forever is that
right now
it's happening and in five years
it will be the case that
gamers are not mostly
in their late 20s anymore.
That's true. Because the thing is
there's a very clear bias
towards the year 1997
here.
A time
period when
the majority of
I've seen enough GameFAQs polls to
know the general age of
the site because they'll ask you how old you are
and things like that. Right, around our age
it's like the median
age of the website.
And it's a lot of people
who are in their late 20s
who played these games and they were young
and the reason that I know that has to be the case
because on the one hand I do think
that Ocarina of Time and Final Fantasy 7
hold up extremely well
and that both of them are games that can compete
with all the modern games right now
and the sort of
oldest games that still
get to the top of the list are
Super Nintendo games.
Super Metroid
and Chrono Trigger
and Mario RPG and A Link to the Past
but they're all games from the 90s
and like you never see
NES games getting in here
and if you were trying to make the
the like
if you were trying to say that these games were legacy games
that it was just because of how influential it was
we would have
NES games, we would have those old
games and there's people from that era
who still legitimately feel
as strongly towards those games as we do
towards Ocarina of Time
like how come Mario 1 isn't on the pole
but don't you think
that it's gonna
nobody says
that the best movie ever made
is like anything made in the last decade
everyone always says you know Citizen Kane
that really depends on who you ask though
okay okay
but I'm talking majority, I'm talking cultural consensus
on the best movie ever
is definitely old movies
there's this great article
that I'd love to dig up
or something for this but like
there's a huge
identity crisis when it comes to video games
where people don't look back
people don't play
this article
it was written by a guy who was teaching a game design
class and he asked
everyone in the class to raise their hand
if they're a fan of the Elder Scrolls series
and like
a majority of the class raises their hands
right and then he asks them
like how many have played Skyrim
and like most of them have their hands up
and then he asks like how many of you have played Oblivion
and like more than half of them lower their hands
and then he asks how many have played Morrowind
and he gets down to like two people
and he asks how many of you have played
Daggerfall and it's nobody
and like what a fucking hipster
well that's just a shameful degradation of the time
right I'm so glad you brought this up Digi
cause it really reminds me of
the whole conceit behind
the remake of Final Fantasy 7
and the question is
why is it being made from an artistic perspective
there is no reason
the game is fine because it'll sell
and people don't want to look back at the old one
there is absolutely nothing preventing
anyone from playing that game
they just want to you know make it again
so they can sell it again
and you know
I think the reason that some of the
like a link to the past and Ocarina of Time
specifically are the
like the older Zelda's that always succeed
but like personally
you know I've played all the old Zelda's
just two years ago
and I liked the first game
more than a link to the past
I thought it had like more
interesting ideas it had more interesting mechanics
and I think there's a huge contingent
of people who just think
it's old and they don't
want to play it cause it's old
I'll be honest that's why I haven't played it yet
right people look at the first game
and they think well isn't a link to the past
pretty much the exact same thing except
better and the answer is no
it doesn't play anything alike
I think the first game has better controls
because a link to the past is really
floaty it has a bad knockback
when enemies hit you it's really frustrating
sometimes whereas the first game
is like whatever you input is exactly
what happens on screen you know
exactly how your character moves stuff like that
the game is completely open-ended
it never tells you where to go
it's all about like just exploring this
world and sort of getting lost in it
whereas a link to the past is very
streamlined it tells you exactly
where to go next you know
and you know you use this item
on this specific dungeon whereas
in the first game like the items are useful forever
you always use everything forever
and like
it's just it's a different game
but people don't look at Zelda 1
they look at the games that they've
heard of that you know Ocarina of Time
and a link to the past were so influential that people
like the people just ignore them
but like if the people voting in game FAQs
polls were born
like 10 years earlier
like if there were more people
from like for instance
the game grump Danny Sex-Bang
he's like in his late 30s
and all the games he likes are NES games
like every game that he considers
like a classic that he knows how to play
that he's amazing at you know he loves
Zelda 1 he likes Zelda 2
you know and he's
he loves the link to the past as well
but like when you see him play the newer games
you can tell he doesn't feel as strongly about them
and it's like if more people
his age were voting we'd get stuff from the 80s
when people our age are voting we get stuff from
the 90s and I think we're entering a period
now where there's a lot of kids
who are voting in game FAQs
polls who were like my brother
Shade who is 18 now
he is a legal adult
he was born in 1997
he was born the year Final Fantasy 7
came out so there was
never a world for him where Final Fantasy 7
wasn't an old ass game
you know or Ocarina of Time
you know the first Zelda he would have seen
would have been Twilight Princess
oh my god I cannot believe that
I guess the idea
I mean I guess the idea with games is that because
there's like there was technological
improvement happening for a while there
new entries in the series
are basically just
improvements on the previous ones
even though everyone loves
Morrowind and everyone hates Oblivion
you say improvements
but like
I made that video about Final Fantasy 7 and the remake
like the remake is just
it's not going to have so many
of the things that I love about
Final Fantasy 7 like the janky weird animations
that are only done
because they couldn't express things the way that
I'm sure they wanted to but that as a result
are like one of my favorite things about that game
there's no way to
incorporate that sort of thing into the remake
it's just going to be replaced by
is really awkward, stilted
anime dialogue
I know dude I know
that's why I fucking hate voice acting
I hate voice acting in every sense
in games it should not be there let me
read the text because my imagination
is so much better than the best
voice actor you could possibly find
quick quick note on that
I understand why everyone
reads Papyrus' lines
like snidely whiplash but to me
in my head he never sounded like that
and it's really weird
like I get it I get it he goes
sounds like an evil laugh
he's tall and thin so he has
a reedy voice I get it but he never
sounded like that in my head
he's clearly Skeletor
no man that's
that's just not how he sounds to me
if you watch
like Skeletor
literally goes
he literally does that
inform Papyrus' character
those ne'ers were purposely put in there
I understand
the logic behind that
when I watch an undertale
fan like thing on youtube
and they're doing any kind of voice
for him that's not Skeletor I get pissed off
well I get pissed off but they do do
Skeletor
my life is suffering
he's objectively Skeletor and I'll fight
I'll fight anyone
here's here's head canon
Skeletor burned off the rest of his skin
and became Papyrus exactly now we know
there you go
I forgot the fuck I was gonna say
I'm talking about Final Fantasy 7 and Legacy
oh yeah you know the thing Ben
that you mentioned about like film
that people like old films
but there actually is a sort of
cutoff people like films from like the
fifties onwards because
it is the same with
technology advanced people don't go back
like you don't see a lot of
unless it's a real film you don't see
a lot of silent movies on this you might see
like Metropolis or something
like if the person is really
it like you know or that one about going
to the moon yeah like how come Pong
never comes up on like best game ever when it
did it all baby it started
you know Digi Digi you
make a good point I guess there is like a cutoff
in technology whereas like before that
no one like really considers them watchable
but then if but that's the funny
thing though is that it's it those
movies aren't worse
like because if you do know film bus like
go watch you know every frame of painting
talk about Buster Keaton's films and like
all the the technicality of those that
like hasn't even been topped today
you know and and yet you don't see them
on anyone's favorites list you know people
don't talk about them as much they talk about
Casablanca and Citizen Kane because
everyone knows about them and you know
they're they're famous
you know people don't talk as much about
the older movies I mean some critics
do I mean if you get like Roger Ebert
he's going to talk about all those old ass
fucking movies that make a great you know
he is dead but like he his great
movies reviews would span the whole
history of film because he knew the
medium and he knew that even
silent movies could do things that
movies now can't do you know
I actually watched a bunch
of metropolis although I was
playing a coheedy camera music
over it and
I was really interested in like
the makeup effects and stuff that are totally
different from what they would be now because
like to look right on film they would like
take on tons of like dark makeup
under their eyes and stuff and it looks
really cool and I was like man this
movie has a look that I would love
to see emulated in modern
technology but like I don't think it has
been and
you know so like even those ancient fucking
movies still have things that are interesting
that can teach you about film and inspire
new things and
games can do the same you know I've
going back and playing a game like
Zelda 1 really made me think about like
man I would love to see the Zelda
franchise kind of like get back
to this and then like they released
the what's it called
the fucking A Link Between Worlds
which is interesting
because it plays more like
it's a sequel to A Link to the Past
and they were playing it up like oh you can
choose whichever order you want to do the dungeons
and it's like A Link to the Past had that
in Dark World but this game
does it much more similarly to the first
game where it was like you just kind
of find things on your own and pick up
whatever weapons you want and use them here
and there you know it's sort of a hybrid of
Zelda 1 and A Link to the Past
like taking the best elements of each
and sort of hybridizing them and
it's like cool I don't think a lot
of people would have even known
that because they haven't played Zelda 1
you know but yeah
I think looking back can be interesting
and I think that's why so many indie games
that look back and have like
you know retro feel but they take
like retro ideas and put new spins
on them are so big right now
because
you know a lot of people think it's like oh it's nostalgia
but it's like Shovel Knight's not popular
because everyone who played Shovel Knight
had also played Mega Man in Castlevania
it's popular because it took those
ideas and did something interesting
with them you know
I want to disagree I think that is part of the reason
why it's popular is because it harkens
back to those games from the day
well okay okay but I think that has
a lot to do with the context of games
coming out today in the way like
all these big games are these big like
3D
Unreal Engine
like action adventure shooter games
that's like when you want to make a game to sell
like that's what you go to
if you want to make a big AAA game
and people are getting kind of bored with it
and so when someone makes a game that appeals
to some other aspect
what's happening with AAA games
is that they're all homogenizing because
they have to sell them
they have to sell so many fucking copies
that they can't afford not to sell them to literally everyone
so the game has to appeal to literally
everyone and then the indie games
don't have to appeal to basically anybody
except for like 10 people
except the one making it basically
okay let me
I found a blog the other day
actually I was looking at Davoo's Twitter
and Davoo follows these guys
called the Indie Game Advisors
oh yeah it's like a troll
and one of their tweets was like
there's only one place for your game
Zero Feedback
and it was a link and it linked to a
blog called Zero Feedback
that is a blog that collects and reviews
games that have been made
and posted online
and three months or more after being
posted have gotten zero comments
from anyone
gone completely unnoticed
amazing
wait what were we just saying that got me on this topic
that games cost a million dollars to make
and that they're all appealing to the same
don't have to appeal to anybody
I was scrolling through the list and some of them were really interesting
but one of them started was like
games are made for different audience
some games are made to be
a meta commentary on gaming in general
some games aren't meant to be played at all
and
the game is like a birthday present
like the dev just made the game
it's an interactive cake blower
like candle blower out some matter
made for his friend as a birthday
and there's two versions
like made on two different years and like
the second one is like this weird like
like lion puzzle
but the one that was like
Jesse beating up um
who was it, what critic was it that you beat up Jesse
oh I don't even remember
Razor Fist I don't know
it was that um
every time you hit them their sub count
was subtracted and put into your sub count
oh yeah
wait Davoo made a game
Davoo's made a bunch of games
I know he's made games but I haven't seen any of them
he's made a few RPGs that he said
actually have a lot of the ideas that
Undertale did and he realized it later
that's interesting
it was the cinemasins people
yeah it was cinemasins he made a game where Jesse
Jesse said he wanted to beat up cinemasins
and then Davoo made a game where Jesse
beats up cinemasins and takes their subscribers
that reminds me of
my idea about a youtuber
gambling ring where you can gamble your subscribers
and if you lose
your subscribers go to the winner
what a great idea
I know right
but anyway
if only there was some way to transfer subscribers
it would totally work
I'll agree with you on the idea that
I'm sure Shovel Knight was like
initial success is based on
nostalgia but like both of my little brothers
played that game and neither one of them has played
fuck all old games
they have not played a single NES or Super Nintendo game
in their fucking lives
Victor's never played a Super Nintendo game
Victor is like super against
going back to old games
he finds it so hard
to play a game that doesn't look pretty
that it's like
kills him
I have done God's work
by way of Nintendo
and gotten him Final Fantasy 7
and he's starting it up now
if he likes pretty games
forget the Legos
those pre-rendered backgrounds man
they're gorgeous
get the fuck out of here whoever said that
I'm just saying I think by most people's
definition of what a pretty game is
most people are literally retarded
I'm a really big fan of
static pre-rendered
backgrounds
best environments
fuck anyone who says the graphics are bad
they don't know what the hell they're talking about
when you're fucking walking and shit's going on in the background
and there's fucking like cannons
flying and like the weapon is coming towards you
remember how when you walk outside of Eris's church
and it's like tiny and it looks like
so out of proportion it's so adorable
and I love it and it's the best
the best
when it zooms out in the intro
it shows the logo on the screen
and then it zooms right back into the train
and then directly to gameplay
seamlessly
how did they do that with the camera
they can't even do that
nowadays I've never seen that in any game ever
since then before then
the best game ever made and we finally
solved the problem it is objectively
look at red13's dad
look at his character model
it's a piece of shit
you gotta admit though
that it would have been
look at the fucking aliased jagged edges
sometimes when the camera is moving
and how fucking janky it is
fucking complete a total biscuit
about your anti-aliasing
I wish
I will say this
I wish that if they were gonna do a Final Fantasy 7 remake
then you know
you said that the scene where the train stops
and it seamlessly transitions to gameplay
you can tell
the moment where the train stops
being a 3D model and starts being
part of the background
you can see that moment
that's the kind of thing
that if they were gonna do a remake of Final Fantasy 7
just fix that
just make it look like the train is the same train
that's such a small thing
that would just enhance the immersion
it wouldn't change anything
it doesn't change the artistic nature of the game
it's just now the train is the same train
I'm gonna be that guy
and just say that changing anything about the original
will make it worse
I don't care if it's improvement
I don't care if you fix any bugs
I love every bug
every glitch, every bit of shitty anti-aliasing
only because it's tied to that experience
so any change will be
it'll feel wrong
Jesse's motto, you're supposed to love the flaws
in someone you love
I keep referencing
in my videos because I love them so much
the real Silent Hill experience guys
Twin Perfect
I love the HD remake
they say it all
I was gonna say it's like Silent Hill
changing anything
even changing the things that suck about it
they make that point
that every flaw, every mistake
whatever is a mistake to you
who's redoing it
but it was put there, they made a choice to leave it there
and all that was the context for making the game
and to change it is just disrespectful to the original
you know a game that I should play
are you talking about Silent Hill Shattered Memories
because I love that game
the HD versions of
2 and 3
they're garbage
I haven't played the original
so Jesse I know you have
I don't know about the other guys
but I wanna know your opinion on Resident Evil 1
versus the GameCube version
the GameCube version
is the exception that proves the rule
because it's superior in every way
because when I was watching Nate's video
and I was like
on the one hand I agree
conceptually that changing things is a bad idea
but the GameCube version of Resident Evil
is a fucking masterpiece
yeah well okay
what was the situation for that game being made though
I'd really like to know because I don't know
it's the exact same game except they
made the controls not tank controls
and they made the
the pre-rendered backgrounds just
utterly beautiful
they were still tank controls on the GameCube
I think they took that out
in the HD version
they didn't remove the fantastic
cutscenes or anything did
they made new cutscenes
they put like whole new
stories of them
they did change the dialogue
to make it less corny
do you like it better that way
cause a lot of people love the corny ones
I was gonna say there's things about the original
still that you can't duplicate
the corny dialogue is pretty
fucking cool in the original
he does not say you were almost a Jill
sandwich this time
are you the master of unlocking
yeah he doesn't say that
but like
I definitely don't see the remake as
being something that could replace the original
I think that's good
that's what matters
mmhmm
but I think
I think
would you say that if someone
told you that they've only played
the remake of Resident Evil
and that they're not interested in playing the first one
do you think you would say
you would be like okay with that
I'd think less of them but I'd be okay with it
I guess
sadly I think I do want to play that game
I will probably play the remake
but I don't want it to
I would rather have been in a situation where there was only one
to play so that I could get the experience
just by playing the game
the thing is Resident Evil on the GameCube
is like the
most gorgeous fucking game ever
like it is
the most beautiful game
I've ever seen
and I think it does a lot
for the game that it looks that way
where like
there's parts in that game where you walk
into a room and just the
level of detail and the way the lighting
is fucking terrifying
just the way the room looks
you walk into a room and
you'll be like facing the camera
and your character model looks
really realistic and the lighting looks
realistic and it just puts you in this weird
frame of mind where you're like oh god
I'm really here and things are really
killing me
because it looks so hyper real and they got away with it
because it's all pre-rendered
so they could draw as much detail
into the backgrounds as they wanted
they didn't have to worry about lighting
that's the joy of pre-rendering dude
why doesn't anyone do pre-rendering anymore
god it's a shame
I think you can
that's what's so cool about like
nobody big does it
what's so cool about 2D games like Muramasa
is that they can do shit like that
every single background be like
the most opulent thing you've ever seen
but I think it fell out with
3D games because people bitch about the cameras
people don't want to have the camera
constantly changing modes
that's why tank controls are
important
in the HD version
it doesn't have tank controls
but I never found it confusing
like I was just
I thought it worked perfectly fine
even in Final Fantasy 7
it can get confusing sometimes walking between screens
and it doesn't have tank controls
and I remember several times
I'll walk back through a place
just because the camera changes completely
the worst in Final Fantasy 7
is that tunnel
in the beginning where
it's really confusing to tell
if you're supposed to go forward or backwards
I know exactly what you're talking about underground
I've actually heard that
referred to as the noob tunnel
where people have gotten so lost
in that tunnel that they quit playing the game
because they couldn't figure out what to do
is that the long tunnel that just goes
really far in both directions
it's like when you're waiting
to Shinra HQ
and you're trying to get there
and you go through all these subway tunnels
I kinda like that
I mean it's a cool place
but it is confusing
that's true
I'm changing my vote
my favorite game of all time is frog fractions
I like number munch
math plaster
have you guys played frog fractions
no I've never heard of it
I have played it on your suggestion
and it was great
I must have made you play frog fractions
you guys should play frog fractions
another frog game that goes crazy
am I thinking of this
there's a dragon
oh yeah I have played that
I remember that game
where it turns into like a million different games
yeah that's right
so I'm looking at this article
and apparently frog fractions too
is coming out
but it's coming out
by way of some insanely
convoluted alternate reality game
that involves like
weird
real life performance art pieces
guys let's all play frog fractions
that sounds fucking awesome
I'm reading about it right now
holy shit I'd forgotten about frog fractions
but god damn
you know what you're right I'm changing my vote
frog fractions is objectively the best game ever
I'm so glad we were able to come to consensus
this is a progressive
not even that this convoluted release method
means that frog fractions too is the best game ever
and it doesn't even exist
certainly the best franchise
that is a phenomenal game
that honestly probably would make my list of
like top 5 games ever
my game of the year
for 2015 is
dengeki bunko fighting climax
technically it came out last year in Japan
but it came out this year in the US
and it's
possibly my favorite fighting game
that's not called super smash brothers
I play as kozaka kirino
from ore no we motoga
nani kawai wake ganai
or my little sister can't possibly be this cute
and she's
I kick everybody's ass with her
and she has
really fun moveset
and she's like the most satisfying character
to play in a video game
I've ever played
I'm going to give you guys a spoiler
for future best guy ever
episode
kirino
the worst creation
in the history of mankind
she is an abomination
she is an utterly
reprehensible
piece of human garbage
and it is my mission in life
to obliterate her memory
from the face of the earth
I'm going to fucking recreate Hiroshima
if it means one more person
will not
fuck kirino
I'm surprised you haven't bought
dengeki bunko fighting climax
just so you can beat her up
I'll go pirate it
I can't give money to the people
who created kirino
but I will get it
you're misrepresenting
the problem guy
the problem is not that she's a terrible person
the problem is that
the show is a terrible show
that wants you to like her
the biggest problem
are the people around
kirino who enable her
but if we eliminate her
and who the show then goes on to celebrate
as having done the right thing
I feel like if we kill her
that's at least one scourge
of
badness
I want to fight you
with kirino
I will be kirino
you be kirino
we will have the ultimate fucking battle
see the problem is that
kirito sucks
and kirino is like the god tier character
I'll do whatever it takes
I've got determination man
oh he's bringing it back undertale
yes we did talk about
that's why I wanted to bring up
my favorite game is dengeki bunko fighting climax
it's not undertale
even of this year
I also like axiom verge more than undertale
but I don't know
axiom verge is a game
I don't like undertale made me think
more
axiom verge did not make me think
a lot but it's a game
that I definitely see myself playing again
in a year or two
undertale I don't think I will ever play again
I find the
gameplay to be extremely
frustrating and I hate it
I'm going to play undertale the way I play
final fantasy 7 I think
which is just every couple of years
just take the journey and just do it
just to re-immers
yeah I know
I don't really see myself playing it again
I think I've gotten
all there is to get out of the
I think I'll play it again
I already played it a third time and didn't even intend to
was that mage?
I want to say I play undertale again but I feel bad
you don't have to do
genocide or anything
oh right but if you reset
me and Shade were going to do
a let's play
because we were drinking and he was big
into undertale so he was like why don't you just start
up another undertale run and then I turned on the
game and Flowey showed up
and started talking to me and literally asking me
not to do it and I was like
well if I'm not supposed to do it in the context
of the narrative then I won't do it
oh that's so great
that's why I love undertale
you all this time
have been saying
you guys keep saying oh you didn't do a genocide run
you weren't here
you have been heckling me for a week
telling me I have to kill everyone
you piece of shit
you are definitely a better person if you do not play
genocide but you do not
get the game you just don't
you don't know everything
that's stupid you're accepting
the game's logic uncritically
playing a genocide run does not
make you a worse person no matter how much the game tries
to tell you it does
you killed all your friends
even Toby said why would you do a genocide run
he put it there
I don't think that it makes you a worse person
it's a temptation you're supposed to resist
I think that it means
the game's putting one over on you
and it refuse
to play by its rules
all of those things
you are constructed as temptations that you are supposed to resist
you can do what you want
I don't even think it's tempting
I did not reach the end of the game
I sure want to kill all these guys
that would be interesting
that's why I did it
I wanted to know
it's that there's additional content
and it's honestly really good content
that's why it's such an effective tool
I think the reason
the reason that there's
like a divide of people
that don't want to do it
don't even think that it would be a fun time
not like it would be fun
but like they don't want to do it
not just because it's nasty
but because they just don't care
and I think it's like
the game
undertale
if you end up wanting
to not do the genocide run
it's like it's affected you in that way
it just speaks more to
like the character
writing
if you don't feel a desire
to do the genocide run
I think the game has kind of failed
in what it was trying to do
I think it's trying to incentivize you to do it
I think, no, you know what
I'm gonna say it like this
I think there are
two equally valid endings
to undertale
one where you keep going and you do genocide
and one where you don't
and I think that
you could say that the genocide run
has a lot of the interesting content in the game
but I think it's equally interesting
to play a game and then for that game
to actually convince you
you don't want to play it again
I totally agree with you
that is legitimate
I think every single ending
is totally fine
my whole thing is
I love that the genocide run exists
and I respect what it does
as a work of art
the fact that it gives you that choice
and tries to tempt you is like the coolest
most unique artistic thing that
in many years, however
me personally
Toby Fox is not smarter than me
I'm not going to fall for his shit
I'm not going to let him browbeat me
and talk down to me for doing something
that he tried to get me to do
so he can suck a dick
I'll never play the genocide run
he'll never fucking trick me
and I'll never fall for his metal bullshit
because I'm better than him
the problem is you know everything already
so you don't have any desire to play
like Toby
it's weird for the game
to look down on you
when he programmed this
into the game
he's the bad guy
he made the genocide run
a choice into the game
so of course there had to be a negative choice
it's up to you to do what you want
let me just explain to me the logic
he's like God
judging me for masturbating when he gave me a dick in the first place
that's right
when I played through the game
on my first run
even though I was going for pacifist
I ended up killing some people
and resetting
I killed Toriel and then I reset to do it again
and got the happy ending
I killed Undyne because I couldn't figure out what to do with her
and I saw her fucking death
which is awesome by the way
if you haven't seen her neutral death
it's fucking heartbreaking
it's wicked cool
sad as well
okay spoilers
you know how in
Jesse don't listen if you don't want to spoil
you know how in genocide
when you kill her she starts melting
but she's like no everyone's counting on me
I've gotta defeat you
it is the best moment in the game
and then she wills herself back to life through determination
and becomes the ultimate champion
in a neutral run
she tries to do that
but because you're not the ultimate monster
she can't summon the determination to do it
and she's like no I won't die
I can't die I won't die
that's genius
brilliant I love it
she's like no
I can't and then she just melts away
I would suck that dog's dick any day
no it's wicked good
so I saw that and I loved it
but I was sad so I
reset and undid it and saved the game
saved her
and then I got to the end
and
and if Toriel dies
she has a good scene too
so I really wanted to see the ultimate content
so I was like of course I'm gonna do the genocide
because
I want to see
and that is exactly the point
that's sort of the point the game's making
the funny thing is I hate games
having multiple paths
I never do multiple paths in a game
like if it's a game that has
three endings I'll take the ending I got
I don't give a fuck
I think
there's a lot of people who they get to the end
and they're like you have to get
the true ending the perfect ending
you have to get the one where you did everything right
and you saved everybody and I'm like
I'm just gonna take whatever ending I get
if I played in a way
where I fucked up then this is the ending
that my story has
I'm one of those people who always
does whatever it takes to get the true ending
on the first playthrough
I don't know if I'm going to be able
to put in the time
to do it again
and I never risk that I'll
get about and have to play through another game
I feel like the world we live in
you can't restart anything
right you go through
you're totally right
I get why for video games
it's an escape from the real world
it's a world where you can do everything again
you can make everything perfect
and have your Groundhog's Day loop
you saved everybody and the end is great
but like
for me I just kind of like to take
what comes and be like
I mean mostly out of impatience
I don't want to fucking play through the whole game
twice or redo things
I never save scum in any game
unless it's fucking Fire Emblem
cause I'm not going to let any of my characters die
I also do it out of impatience
it's exactly the same as Fire Emblem for me
I cannot let any character
die in Fire Emblem ever
it's an impossibility for me
we'll never do it and I cannot
to me it seems like if you let a character die
you lost the game
that's right
you could win any battle
if you just do enough soldiers at it
that's my obsession with getting the true best ending
I totally understand
obviously because in Fire Emblem
all the characters are characters and individuals
you don't want any of them to die
because it would feel really terrible
and not only that
but at least just try again
so there's no excuse for letting them die
and so I'm totally with you
on why you would want to redo it
however in games like that
I think it really ups the stakes
and makes it a lot more engaging
and ultimately fun
if you decide ahead of time
I will not reset to save anyone
if I fuck up and die
I have a thought about that
but I suck at Fire Emblem
so like if I tried to play that way
I'm fucked
it would obviously
make things a lot harder
it'd be like Nuzlocking
doing a Nuzlocke run
of a Fire Emblem
I love Nuzlocke runs
and I love the idea of Nuzlocke runs
but the game is so not balanced for it
and it takes so much grinding that I don't think I'll ever do another one
you don't have to restart your game
when you lose your Pokemon
you just pick up a new Pokemon
and just play with that one
if your Pokemon dies
you have to pick up one of your other ones
I think that is a lot more
convenient than trying to do Fire Emblem
without a character
you're a fool
because it's the opposite of convenient
everything about a Nuzlocke run
will destroy you forever
if you lose a character in Fire Emblem
and you go to the next level
and you save your game
then you are fucked forever
because you can never get that character back
if you keep losing characters
you're just going to have to restart the whole game
with Nuzlocke
you will have to grind excessively
but you will never have to actually just reset the game
you know
in Fire Emblem
they give you way more characters than you can ever use
in one match
I've never gotten far enough
in Fire Emblem that I had the huge stock of characters
you can lose Pokemon
you can lose enough Pokemon
you can easily lose enough Pokemon
in a Nuzlocke run that you're completely fucked
you can also lose Pokemon
or just not gain Pokemon in the first place
through bad luck
so as to not have Pokemon on your team
so there's a rule that you can only use
each type of Pokemon once
oh you're talking about Nuzlocke now
no you can
you just catch the first
every area you come to you can catch the first one
so if you end up with
and if you fail to catch it
then you just don't have one
and if you start gold in Nuzlocke
I got to the Dragon Trainer
and I had
well I mean there's a whole terrible story
I had an Ice Pokemon
Brunswick the Mammoth Swine
he died tragically in a horrible Wabafit accident
disgusting piece of shit Wabafit worst Pokemon ever
but then because I went
and because of that
I was completely fucked against Claire the Dragon Trainer
got my shit wrecked
didn't actually game over
pretty much the next climactic encounter
where was I going?
we are way off the topic of what the best game ever is
well what's your point are you making a point with that?
well no but I will now
and I'll say
I think that it's highly
recommends Pokemon as a game
for best game ever
or some title like it
the way that it's systems are broad enough
that you can play it in multiple different ways
interesting though
how much of this like what do they call it
expanded gameplay
emergent gameplay
how much of that can be factored into
all of it
absolutely all of it
there are games
if you played God of War
you cannot do anything differently
from what the game is
there's no where to go
there's no other abilities you have
you just play through
I'm not criticizing God of War
if you play Dark Souls
you can play it in so many hundreds of different ways
that completely change it
where you can play a run where you only use the whip
and you're Simon Belmont
and it's Castlevania
I've watched people beat the game like that
I've watched a guy beat the game with a guitar hero controller
I've watched a guy
beat Dark Souls with voice commands
he was saying left, right, jump, dodge
left like that
I've watched him beat Ormstein and Smough
fucking voice commands
I've watched a guy
one of my friends beat the game at level one
he beat the game using only
shields, only two shields
for weapons
I've watched him
there's just so many ways
that you can beat the game
there's different ways that you can speedrun it
where you can do a natural speedrun
where you go all the way through or do a glitch speedrun
where you skip half the bosses
by jumping through the first flame
or whatever
what's the big one called
the giant bonfire
whatever, you know what I'm talking about
the Lord Vessel
there's a glitch you can do where you just go through that door
and completely bypass the whole
second half of the game
which is how the early speedruns were done
there's just a million
ways to play Dark Souls
and it makes it endlessly replayable
and super awesome
you're never done with the game until you decide
you're never done with the game
and even the nature of the story
supports that until you go hollow
the game is still going
and the cyclical nature of it
especially, I mean
I'd say that if there's one flaw
with Dark Souls that's not like a technical flaw
it's that the dark ending
doesn't seg you well into New Game Plus
because...
I like saying seg you, okay
seg way, god damn it
this podcast is over
I like saying seg you
anyway, but that's not the word
I just like saying it, it's my version
of the word
people give me shit about this all the time
but I like the word
the dark ending
does not seg way
and people won't stop giving me shit about it
what's going on?
the dark ending does not seg way well
into New Game Plus
whereas the light ending makes sense
as the cycle continues and you are the new
guy or whatever
I guess it doesn't make perfect sense because it's still Gwyn
at the end and it's not like your player character
or whatever, but like
it makes more sense
it feels more natural
I'm not sure the light ending particularly segways very well
into it
it would be like a cycle much later
segways well into what
into New Game Plus
Gwyn is back
and he shouldn't be back
I don't think that the New Game Plus
is part of the story
I don't think it's meant to be
people have argued this over which ending is better
for seguing into New Play Plus
I think the dark ending
both of them, all the bosses come back
and it doesn't make any sense
it's as much of a different world
does not make any sense
it's as much of a different world as someone else
who you summon, they come from their version of Lord
but if it wasn't
for that you could
isn't it supposed to be like an alternate dimension
that's right
because time is convoluted
you're a different guy who is on the same quest
so I think it's fine
whatever
I'd say that
but the game is pretty much
only over when you say it's over
and you can keep doing so many
new things with it
I feel like
I've watched my friends do upwards
of 40 runs of Dark Souls
and doing it
in so many different ways
there's a lot of ways to chug through the early part
first, there's a cool video
that I saw early into
when I was learning about all the different ways to play Dark Souls
that was everything you can do before the Gargoyles
and this dude just like
plows
he does like pretty much everything
aside from Sen's Fortress and Anor Londo
can be done before
and everything that comes after those
can be done before the Gargoyles
and
it's like mesmerizing to watch
people do shit like that
that's really cool but to bring it back
to the topic at hand
all that stuff is like
you really enjoy how the game
is open
to doing whatever you want
all these ways you can explore it
whereas in my opinion
I sort of am more focused on the story
and the
sort of the point of the game
like the specific story
it's just different ways of looking at it
and that's kind of the consensus here
everyone's got their own way of looking at shit
you want to know where best game ever debate becomes
really really interesting
is when you involve mods
and you have to argue for whether or not
you think that a game
is qualified to be compared
or to be like you know
celebrated when it has mods
on that basis like Skyrim
would probably be a lot of people's best game ever
just because it's got so much shit
I think that it is totally fair
I do too
you just have to specify
what you're talking about
for instance Super Bunny Hop
when he made his video on Fallout 4
he was saying on twitter
and in the video he kept saying
it's advisable to play this game 6 months from now
when it's been modded to the point
that it fixes all the issues
and I was like
what I want you to do Super Bunny Hop
and I said this on twitter I was like
6 months from now about the new game
because it is a new game at that point
it's a totally different game
now that it's got all these mods
and I think it's worth
celebrating
if you can mod a game
and make it the best game ever
then that's worth celebrating
and with Dark Souls the PC version
was definitely better than the PS3
because they made it so you could play it in 1080p
you could play it
but when it came out
they had it locked at 30 frames per second
they had it locked at
I don't think it was locked at 720
but like
the thing is there was a fix for it
the day the game launched
and Steam put
a link to that patch
on the front page of Steam
if you bought the game
it literally told you
the patch is right here
to fix it and so from day one
Dark Souls PC
even though like if you were writing a consumer review of it
people would be like
oh well the game has these locked frame rate issues
and it's a big problem and like
people want to punish the company
for not releasing it right
but from the very beginning
you could mod it in 5 seconds
and have it look beautiful
now see I have no problem with including that
as like a general review of the game
but the only thing and this is an aside
is I don't want the company to get that credit
it doesn't deserve the credit for
yeah but I think games should transcend
who created them
ultimately yes but just as a matter of like
economics it's you know
saying that mods don't
count in terms of determining
how good a game is or whether it's the best game ever
or whatever really smacks of like
I'm not saying that though
really I know you're not but
someone that did it really smacks of like objective
like you know best versus
favorite bullshit
well I think the problem with it
is that it turns
calling a game great
into just like an award
for the people who made it
as opposed to an award for the game
like you know we're trying to figure out
what is the best game
for us
we're not trying to find the best game ever
so that we can give a fucking trophy
to the people who made it
we're doing it to say like
according to us
is the most fun game to play
if mods make a game the best game ever
then it's the best game ever
regardless of you know
just credit the guy who made the fucking mod
if you're giving the trophy
to everybody just give it to the mod guy too
it's the best game ever
can you imagine like them ever share
like the Skyrim devs ever like sharing credit
with like the modding community
did you not hear about like this huge
controversial thing that happened where they tried to
make a like
they tried to monetize mods
yeah build a community of like
like oh we're gonna support the mods
and people have to pay for them
and it completely bombed and fell apart
that was just another way to like capitalize
on other people's work by the company
it didn't work out well
it was not a good idea
it'll be back though it'll be back
give it a couple years
in some form it might return
well
we've been going for two hours now
feel like we've covered a pretty good
of shit how do you guys feel
anybody got anything else to say
I can't believe I'm awake
I want to go back and retroactively
change what I said about Crazy Taxi
it is objectively the best game ever made
not just my favorite I'm on Ben's side now
it's both the same
good all right
good hippo man
what do you got to say
Undyne is the best girl
and I want to kiss her
fishy
vagina
why does Undyne have more hair
when she's on the date
because she's more attractive that way
she is to me
she was wearing it in a ponytail
but if you look at her head even from the back
the top of her head is blue
no she is obviously more attractive
that way but I'm saying why
in universe what is the explanation
for the fact that she has more hair
she grows the hair from the back
to the front
that is possible
it could just be resting not growing
she's got the
she's got the Prince Zuko top
thing going on
and Zuko looked like he had long hair
when it was down right
I don't know
he did Zuko looked
like he was bald everywhere but
when it was down
her little
battle sprite looks like
Undyne's
out of battle sprite looks almost completely bald
that's true it's just got the little tough
but you know what the fan art
looks a million billion times better with a
really tight ponytail
and if one thing's canon
it's fan art
there's also the scene later where she pulls her hair
for whatever
everyone thanks for joining
this was the first
possibly not even going up version
of the
oh I forgot you were here
mage
what do you got to say mage go on
let's hear it
well memed my friend
thanks for listening everybody
we'll leave your feedback
if you like this just tell us
and we'll maybe do another one of these
some time soon
thanks for watching guys
goodbye