Hey everybody, welcome to episode 3 of the PCP Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best guy ever guy here once again to talk about stuff that interests us.
Everybody, let's say who you are, and I'm going to organize this so that we go along smoothly. Jesse, who are you?
Haha! I'm me. There you go, Tom.
I'm Tommy Oliver and I make videos about art stuff and I'll do a comic or something someday.
Yes, Gibbon. I mean Hippocrit.
I am... I am the...
You said it, Ben.
SaintComics.com, Patreon.com slash Ben Saint.
Always getting that patron plug. That's my boy.
And together we are the procrastinators. We're here to save the day.
Together we are... We'll always do it anyway. That's why the people of this world donate to our YouTube fund.
They give us money there. We're crustal friends. We suck a lot of dick. It never ends.
And if you haven't guessed by now, the subject of today's episode is Steven Universe.
And we're going to talk about a whole bunch of stuff regarding it, all our favorite things, things we don't like if there is any.
And I'm interested in talking about the way the show is produced as well.
I'm going to write off the bat and let everyone know that even though Steven Universe is great and the way the steam bomb was great,
I don't care because I'm in a shitty mood. I'm going to complain about it. I'm going to tell you all how much it sucks.
It's the worst show ever. And how you're all gay for liking it.
Fucking SJWs. SJWs all of you.
Yeah, it's true.
I'm glad at least someone is here to object to us because all of us love the show. We're all super into it.
I don't think many of us have much bad to say about it in general.
Who doesn't love the show?
I know. You have to be a Dumbo.
Is there some grinch up on Mount Crumpet somewhere just like sneering down at the rest of us?
I mean, it is true. The show has progressive values in general. If you're looking for them, you'll find them.
And if you just hate those, then sure, the show probably won't do it for you.
You don't matter and go away.
Because the way the show does it is super acceptable. It's never beaten you over the head.
It made me, I'll just tell you right now, my favorite thing about the show has to do with gem culture and garnet and fusion and all that stuff related to that.
And the way that the show presented it in real life made me more accepting of people who have weird life choices or different from normal.
And it's the strength of the storytelling of the show that I think it evoked that out of me.
Well, there you go, guy. You've just admitted to having been indoctrinated by its SJW agenda.
It's true. I'm hanging up my Gamergate hat. You're no longer objective. Your opinion is no longer valid.
That's true. Who's saying something, Gib? Was that you?
Now that you've seen all the gems, you're willing to accept real people?
What are your stance on the Jews?
Not the biggest fan of the Jews, but I am down with the trans.
Nothing's changed.
Jews are not gems. I don't have to like them.
That's true. It's only applies to gem people.
Aren't the Jews the gem people? No, that's the gypsies who are the gem people, right?
Those were those headbands with gems in them. They're IRL gems.
They do adorn themselves with gems.
Me thinks you all protest too much to the Jews. Me thinks that maybe you don't hate the Jews quite as much as you pretend to.
That's not correct. I'll never admit it.
We are the Crystal Jews. Ben's certainly a Crystal Jew wrapping his patron every episode.
That's true. We're trying to fund his cluster building operation.
Let me just say, I just got cut up with Steven Universe a couple weeks ago, and then this Steven Bomb happened to happen right then.
That short period of waiting was already agonizing. It was horrible.
Get ready for a whole lot more of it.
I know. Steven Universe has so much continuity, more than any show I've ever seen, maybe.
I don't know, maybe Breaking Bad or something, but the way it does it is beautiful.
That was already extremely painful. Now, after this fucking Steven Bomb, it's going to be like what?
Six months? Four months?
It's going to be months. You're measuring your weight.
Brutal. It's brutal. They put these five episodes right back to back in one week.
That's the nature of the Steven Bomb.
I guess let's just talk about that. What do you guys think about it? Because I hate it.
I hate it. I detest it.
It's great. You love it? Really?
It's the best thing. I would rather wait a couple months in one go than have to wait a week between every single episode.
That's interesting.
I hate that shit. I hate space-bound content. It's artificial and stupid and dumb and it doesn't work and it's bad and it diminishes the viewing experience.
I'm really glad that they've gone in this direction with it. I think more shows should do it.
Oh no. I know you. We both read one piece in general, but you definitely do this with one piece.
You wait a year and then just catch up on all of it.
It's way better. Reading Homestuck was way better when I had a million updates to go through.
Once it started coming out every couple days, it was bad. It was way, way worse and it's the same with everything.
Maybe you're right, but I think there's a difference between a couple pages of Homestuck versus an episode of Steven Universe or a chapter of One Piece.
I just want to say that I think this would be different. In the case of Homestuck, I kind of agree, maybe, but definitely don't with One Piece or Steven Universe.
What do you guys think? Jesse, I know you have strong feelings.
I'm kind of in the middle, I guess, just kind of bringing another perspective is that I think Steven Bombs can be really good if they're kind of, the episodes are designed to be viewed one day after another.
Because the first Steven Bombs I thought was really disjointed because it was clearly just like we have some episodes put them out and they really had nothing to do with each other.
But the last couple ones and even this one clearly like each episode kind of built upon the last one.
There was that two-parter in there, but even aside from that, yeah, it was like Paradot the Bomb.
This was the Paradot Redemption Arc.
Yeah, so they're clearly designing the show to be viewed like this now.
It did succeed in, you know, doing that Paradot Redemption Arc. I think it did. A lot of people were, you know, kind of upset about the plot not moving along that far.
Who was upset about that?
Well, maybe I'm exaggerating how many people this was, but in like the Steven Universe Generals, there's like two camps.
I know, there's generally two camps of like lore fags and character progression fags and the lore fags were upset.
Even though we got to meet Yellow Diamond, which was...
What the fuck? We had the bet.
There was a ton of fucking lore in this Bomb.
I don't know, maybe I'm exaggerating about how many.
The first episode was so fucking dense.
It was like the biggest lore episode ever.
Oh, with the answer, right?
You know what? I shouldn't get too mad because honestly, Guy, probably you're just explaining it badly.
Probably the reality of the situation is fine and you're just filtering it through a lens designed to make me angry and I'm not gonna fall for it.
I do try to do that as much as possible.
Well, I have heard just about all that I can take. I have never disagreed with Ben more strongly in my life.
He's wrong. The Steven Bomb is a disaster. It's garbage. You are wrong and you are garbage and you belong in a zoo, my friend.
You belong in a zoo with smelly apes who've played with their own shit.
The Steven Bomb negatively affects my viewing of the episodes because while I'm watching the episodes during the Steven Bomb,
all that I can think about in the back of my mind is the days of the week ticking by and I know that eventually it's gonna be over.
It negatively peppers my perception of everything I'm watching.
Is that really so different from like a weekly format?
That's how I feel about it.
Because with a weekly format, if you release the episodes once a week like a normal fucking show, you would have very little cause to go on hiatus.
It wouldn't happen as much.
Every week is a little hiatus.
Yeah, but it's a hiatus that you can digest and get used to as opposed to this wonky up and down bullshit.
It is more manageable.
Bullshit definitely gives you a routine and it's more expected.
Like right now we have no idea when the next Steven's gonna be.
I just went on a huge rant about this.
Just this morning on my award-winning show Serialize, the greatest show of all time.
It was a good point.
When you're watching...
On Manchild Incorporated.
When I was watching the last episode of the Steven Bomb, which was a great episode.
It's an episode about Peridot and Garnet fucking around.
Just fucking around and it was great.
But because of the nature of the way the Steven Bomb is set up, all I could think of was, well this isn't a very good way.
It forces you to view it as a season finale as opposed to just a regular episode.
That is kind of true.
It's unfair to the episode.
It was not written to be a season finale.
You shouldn't have to...
You know what?
I totally feel you when I agree on many of those points.
But really, just after Tom and Ben talked about it more as like its own little compartmentalized section that this was like the Peridot Bomb,
I kind of like it more.
I'm kind of willing to forgive it.
Honestly, the way I see it is, it's kind of like how I used to view YouTube channels.
Yeah.
Because like say someone like Egoraptor when he used to be an animator,
you would come up with a thing and it was cool and you would go watch it and then it would take, I don't know,
how many months, like eight months for a new thing.
Yeah.
People used to go onto his comment section and his description and his YouTube page and they say,
why the fuck's the new thing?
Yeah.
I'm unsubscribing because you haven't made content in a long time.
And I saw them and I'm just like, that doesn't make much sense because all you need to do is just go about your life normally
and then eventually it'll just pop up and it'll be like, oh, that's a nice surprise.
Why would you unsubscribe?
Okay, but the difference is that Steven is so dependent on continuity
and there's the risk of not giving a shit when it comes back, which is something I've suffered many times.
I wish they would go even further in this direction.
I wish they would just, I wish they would just bite the bullet and release five new episodes in one day
instead of spacing them out over a week.
That would be way better.
Well, you know, I was going to, it brings up an interesting point because I wanted to mention that like,
the Steven bombs to me, I feel like they're just movies.
Like you're just watching a movie over the course of a week.
Uh-huh.
You know, because like you don't, you don't usually complain about the hiatus between films.
Like, you know, the new Star Wars just came out.
And I'll be like, oh, fuck, I have to wait two years for another Star Wars.
You know, I'm just like, you want, you kind of accept that because the medium is like kind of,
well, you know what, I feel that way.
Yeah.
Exactly what I said in the theater when the movie ended.
Steven Universe.
I stood up.
Ah, fuck, I have to wait two years.
Uh, with, with Star Wars, that definitely felt like one, actually, I don't know, I kind of,
I have my issues with Star Wars, but it felt generally like one condensed adventure.
But when you release them in these little bundles, like, like, I like how normal shows really do it.
Like, like how MLP does it.
You got one episode a week.
You got your season.
It's there.
It's not going anywhere.
There's no speculation.
Like the story is being told and you know exactly when it's going to hit.
Even knowing that, I think is, is better than, you know, being up in the air.
Not sure when, when you're going to get the answers you crave.
I don't actually mind when, like, if I don't know when the next thing's coming.
I'm not constantly, like, sitting in my chair, like, waiting for something to be announced
and then, then I'll get all hyped for it.
I just, when something arrives, it's just like, oh, that's a nice surprise.
Cool.
I guess the best thing that means you're not, you don't like Steven Universe as much as the rest of the world.
Yeah.
We found the treasure.
That's true.
The phone.
Fuck.
That the reason I don't like it is not enough waifu material.
What?
Paradise Ultimate Waifu.
I can't, I'm not into any of them.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, sir.
You know what?
I'm going to agree.
I'm not, I'm not attracted to any of them.
I'm attracted to Pearl.
I think Pearl is really cool.
It's not even about attractiveness.
It's just about pure fucking wind.
Parodot was fucking awesome this week.
Dude, when Parodot pulled those boxes over her ass, that was pretty great.
That was pretty awesome.
Sexually.
They're awesome characters, but they're not waifu material.
As far as I'm concerned.
Hey, that's in the eye of the beholder, man.
I know, I know.
Yeah, well, I know what you mean, I guess.
But you know what?
Maybe you guys should stop fucking objectifying women
and treat them as actual individuals, you know?
Man, they're not even after poisons.
Funny you should say that because they literally are objects.
They're fucking rocks.
No, you're projecting your hatred of women.
No, they're projecting a hard light,
projection barrier of themselves out of their fucking rock body.
They are pure projection.
Can you guys imagine the hot, sloppy, disgusting amethyst sex?
Yeah.
Just nasty, sweaty, filthy.
She's gonna make a shit halfway through.
Jesse, you make a strong case.
Yeah, she's gonna do that Castanza shit of melding food and sex.
It's gonna be, you know, yeah.
Wait, what happens to amethyst when she eats something and then shape shifts?
I think it...
Does it go somewhere?
Probably just shifts.
Her stomach probably just shifts around.
I'm sure she's got some kind of crepes inside of her somewhere.
I don't know, but she definitely poops.
That was confirmed that it comes out the other end, so...
She was way into pooping.
Probably pooping is great.
Combined with sex.
Why are Gems even capable of digesting?
Do you think it just comes out the other side completely undigested?
Yes, I do, pretty much.
Oh, that's horrible.
No way, they have to poop.
We're asking the important questions now.
That's true.
They have to poop because otherwise Pearl would not find it so distasteful.
Alright, here's my prediction.
I think...
Okay.
Normally, Gems probably don't have digestive systems, but you can probably adapt their
form to do it, because Rose obviously adapted her body to be able to bear it.
To have that vagoo.
That's true.
I think amethyst just makes some guts and then makes it work.
On that topic, I want to get deep into this.
So did Greg fuck Rose?
Did she shapeshift a vagina and his sperm combined with her somehow to make...
Yes, as fucking yes.
How is that even a question?
If anyone tries to tell me that anyone didn't have sex, I'll throw a fucking tantrum, the
likes of which have never been seen.
Yeah, there was some definite fucking going on.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, Greg was all over Rose.
That's true.
They even said he had like a fat girl fetish.
He has a tall eight foot tall woman fetish, which is awesome.
It's all about it.
It's Stephen does as well, as it turns out.
Really?
Well, you know, he sang a whole song about wanting to see a giant woman.
Oh, that's your head cannons.
He probably does.
I don't accept them.
Get them out of here.
It's fucking true.
No, he just...
He only has eyes for Connie.
He's going to be the first boy.
Let's talk about that for a second, the music, because Giant Woman was by far the best thing
in the series until the return or whatever jailbreak happened.
Man, fucking...
I'm such a great episode.
It took me a while for the music to grow on me.
Yeah, me too.
It's quirky.
But what I really like about it now is that it's so...
I like the simplicity when before is really turned off by it, because I felt like they
weren't trying.
Yeah, yeah.
And maybe that's because the MLP music that I came from was so overproduced.
No, man.
It's really good because the music is being performed in-universe by a kid with a ukulele.
Exactly.
That's what I didn't understand until a while later.
So it's so good.
And now it's so much fucking cool.
In-universe?
Yeah.
Oh, like how we sang Giant Woman or whatever?
Was that Canon?
I guess it was.
Yeah, he himself is singing the song.
And he's like playing the...
It's happening.
A kid is playing a ukulele and singing along with it, so the song should be simple.
That's what's so cool about it.
It's like real.
It's not like...
It is.
A big production.
That's not always true.
No, it's not always true.
Yeah.
Like Pearl songs, I don't think are diagetic really.
But like half of the time.
Oh, don't...
Yeah.
Di...
Dilute this conversation with diagetic bullshit.
I agree.
Just hearing you say that word made me wretch a little bit.
Let's...
I want to talk about...
Unnecessary memories.
Because this is my favorite thing about the show.
Everything having to do with gem culture and the social implications.
And to just talk about...
I want to talk about the things I love about it.
And why it's so great and why the answer was such a fantastic episode.
Snore.
And the diamonds.
Let's go through every episode one at a time in the new Steven Baum and give it a ranking
out of ten.
Well, we could do that.
Well, I don't know.
Let's just talk about the answer and the lore that came with it.
Because man, that was the tightest fucking shit.
And even like...
Okay, how about blue pearl, right?
And now yellow pearl?
So cool.
There was a blue...
Oh, right.
Blue...
Yeah, yeah.
The hair over her eyes.
So good.
Now, she was probably the best waifu in terms of physique in the show.
I don't fucking know what you're talking about.
She looked exactly like Pearl with a different haircut.
Hair...
If you watch anime bad, hair is all that makes the difference.
It's all about that hair.
Yeah.
It's like Japanese shit.
Oh, man.
I want to say that...
I can't wait for Pearl to simultaneously beat the shit out of blue and yellow pearl.
They confuse together.
She'll still kick the crap out of them, thereby symbolizing her development and growth as
an individual human being kicking the crap.
And you know what she'll say as she delivers the killing blow?
They'll be like, oh, you can't beat us.
You'll be like, shut up.
You're just a pearl.
That's what she'll say.
Dude.
Because she's not just a pearl.
Pearl is the real pearl.
Pearl would never say you're just a pearl to another pearl.
That kind of defeats her arc of overcoming.
No, no.
The way I see it, that illustrates her arc.
Get out of here.
What do you mean get out of here?
Arcs are the most important part of the thing.
No, no, no.
It's not an arc.
I'm saying guys over here are being like, oh, that would totally destroy her arc.
Fuck you.
Her arc is not about overcoming the social stigma against her.
That's all in the past.
It's overcoming genetics, which she already did before the series started.
No, yeah.
That's all in the past.
It's not her arc.
Have you heard the theories that Pearl, the one, the renegade pearl, is like white diamond's
pearl?
I think she would be pink diamond's pearl, would she?
Yeah.
Well, the idea is like if pink diamond is Rose or like Rose is like a high ranking someone,
like renegade pearl would like go from white diamonds with Rose, like I don't know.
That would save her from the white diamond's grasp or something like that.
It's possible.
It's a cool idea.
I was going to assume she was pink's pearl, but yeah, sure.
Well, let's flush that out a little bit, what you said there in case people haven't heard
this, because I think it's really interesting.
I want to talk about this theory about pink diamond and all.
By now, everybody knows that the diamond authority or whatever the official name is, is yellow
diamond, blue diamond, white diamond, and they're in charge of everybody.
If you look at the old architecture in places like the battlefield where pearl trained Connie
and swordsmanship, you'll see a diamond shape which has yellow, blue, white, and there's
also a pink one.
The theory basically is, if you look at newer structures like in the battlefield where that
big tomb was, where they got the big white diamond from, emblazoned on that thing is
a symbol that only has a blue, yellow, and white diamond with the pink one suspiciously
gone.
The theory is that a row is possibly is pink diamond or maybe a fusion involving pink diamond
somehow.
She's not a fusion.
She only has one gem.
All right.
But she's a quartz, so it could be something going on with there.
It's also kind of interesting.
But anyway, the point is she was pink diamond, she left, and that's so her faction was excommunicated.
Maybe quartz is like a title for a fallen diamond or something.
Well, but there's a real quartz with amethyst.
Well, that's not what she's called either, I guess.
My personal theory is the diamond is a title that you get by being a hierarchy gem.
Yeah, so I'm saying maybe quartz is a title too.
I guess.
If you've noticed the...
Maybe she was rose diamond before.
God damn architecture.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Go on.
Like all the, on the moon episode, whatever it was called.
They had the yellow, blue, and white, and the white diamond has her diamond on her forehead.
Yellow and blue have their diamonds under their neck, and rose has it on her stomach.
Yeah.
So it's sort of like a hierarchy there.
The white diamond's the big bad.
Possibly.
I think that's how it's going to go, because we've met the yellow diamond already.
If you look at the symbol with the four diamonds, they're in the identical locations.
The white diamond's on top, the pink diamond's on the bottom, and then the blue and yellow
diamonds are on the side.
So like their gem locations are identical to where they are located on the symbols.
So people are saying that's like a hierarchy.
So that's interesting.
Yeah, yeah.
Pink diamond would be the lowest rank.
Pink diamond was the bottom pyramid in the pyramid of them.
Why would there be one top rank, two middle rank, and then one bottom rank?
Because it makes a bigger diamond, and because of graphic design.
I don't fucking know.
Yeah, because of graphic design.
But that doesn't make any sense from like an administrative perspective.
We need to consult a geologist, only he can deliver the final verdict.
We need to find Bill Nye.
We're getting off track a little bit.
Let's talk about the gem culture and what we've learned recently, because the answer
was the coolest episode ever, and went into all about that shit.
I'm really stoked about the fact that we now know that if multiple kinds of the same gem
fuse, they just become a bigger version of themselves.
That's really interesting, and kind of raises deep concerns within me, because everything
in the show has been about how you're more than your gem.
That's what Pearl's all about.
And then when Ruby fused with the other rubies, this was thousands of years ago, but still,
she still just felt like herself, but bigger.
But then in that very episode, goes on to lead, take a whole divergent path from the
other rubies.
Well, it's gotta be that all of the rubies had such similar life experiences.
At that point in history, they were basically the same person, there was nothing distinguishing
them.
Well, I feel like it's kind of like all rubies are cut from the same big ruby or something,
and then that's why they feel all connected.
It could be something like that.
Obviously, they're very related.
I don't even know if it's an actual connection thing.
I didn't think it was like literal, like, oh, I just felt like the same thing.
I think it's just like cultural conditioning, because Ruby makes that statement that when
Savart's like, you were going to be shattered, it's like, who cares?
There's a bunch of me.
Man, I love how little care Ruby cares about herself compared to Savart.
Even today, even she still got this thing about like, man, fuck me, Sapphire is the
one that's important.
Exactly.
We gotta like help her.
Man, it's the best.
Ruby and Sapphire, and therefore Garnet, best character in the series, bar, none, the
best.
Nate, Nate, Nate, how much did you fucking flip your shit with that ending song, and
then they bring back the fucking progression from stronger than you?
Oh, dude, I lost my shit.
Did you buy?
Oh my god.
Wait, wait, wait.
I fucking lost it.
And then Sapphire and Ruby sing to each other, you know, that like, oh, I did you whenever.
In that song, as they begin to dance, a little thing comes in, it's like, which is the stronger
than you, like Melody.
Shit, I missed it.
They brought that into the song.
And holy shit.
But you know, I fucking...
And then that was genius, Tom.
But you know, I didn't like stronger than you as much as everyone else did.
You're a goofball dog.
That is by far the high point of the entire series up to this point.
Dude, that was such a hype fucking moment.
It was insane.
Maybe if I rewatched it, I'd appreciate it more.
I've watched that episode a bunch of times.
It's, yeah, it's good stuff.
I mean, I liked the moment.
I liked the moment.
Except for yesterday, so I haven't gone around to rewatch it yet.
I liked that scene a lot.
I just didn't care for the song itself.
Well, whatever.
That's fine.
So I guess I just want to extrapolate you guys who are listening.
You guys, you guys get it about Garnet, how Ruby's, it was okay to fuse, but when she
fused with Sapphire, everyone was like, oh gross.
That's not allowed.
That's gay dog.
And clearly it's a combination.
It looks like Garnet's whole existence, like being a shameless display, just being fused
all the time as Jasper put it, is seems like a parallel to being either gay or trans.
That's the vibes I get from it.
Well, I mean, you gotta shoehorn your goddamn liberal agenda into my car too.
I'm saying I get out of here.
No, no, I'm just saying.
That's what it looks like to me.
Okay, you could definitely draw that parallel.
Yeah.
But it's not explicitly that.
No, I know.
What it is, now maybe this is a headcanon,
but I think it's pretty solid.
Yeah.
What it is, is I think we can safely say
that a fusion between two different gem classes
represents basically like a perversion
of the social hierarchy that gem society is based on.
It's based on Uptown Girl by Billy Joel.
That's pretty much what Steven Eurebs is all about.
When Blue Diamond flips her shit at Ruby,
it's not like you fuse with a sapphire.
It's like you fuse with a member of my court.
Right, that's true.
That's true.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, so I think in universe,
it's a class social power dynamic.
But I mean, from a thematic standpoint,
Garnet clearly represents social deviancy.
Absolutely.
Things are unaccepted in culture.
Well, I think on another level,
it's just a culture that generally looks down
on individualism.
Oh, definitely.
That's definitely.
Why would they deliberately,
because I mean, they deliberately group Rubies together
to fuse because their personalities
aren't gonna change, they're just fucking guys.
It's just utilitarian.
And they're not naturally lacking in individualism clearly,
as we've seen from the characters.
It's something that is clearly imposed upon gems
by the Rubies class.
And that's why.
They grow gems in like big factory things.
Right, right.
And it was, sorry, I was just gonna say,
it's so great to have Peridot here
as the reflection of gem society
and like to see the way she interprets Garnet and her,
I mean, and it's the best in that her arc
is her like coming to terms with it,
trying to understand Garnet
and like getting over her hangups,
or the stuff that had, you know,
made her weirded out by Garnet.
That arc is super endearing
and she happens to be super cute.
And it's just couldn't be happier with it.
Here's a question I have.
Yeah.
Okay.
I wonder if fusion between similar gems
is always acceptable,
or if like Rubies are expected to do it
because they're grunt soldiers and they're just whatever.
But I wonder if it's a thing
that higher class gems don't engage with at all,
even among their own class.
There's a lot of information about that.
Like how Garnet said, it's something that,
sorry, how Jasper said,
it's just something weak gems do to be strong.
And she was looked on down for that reason.
Yeah, that's a good point.
And then there was also, you know,
all these things Peridot have said,
I was like, you're not even doing anything.
And in the last episode, when they fused into Opal,
she's like, okay, see, that makes sense to me.
They're doing it for a purpose.
You're just fused for no reason.
Get the fuck out of here with that shit.
Do you think that the reason
that there's only one of each of the diamonds
and also the reason they're so big
is because say all the blue diamonds
are combined into one blue diamond?
That, you know, was a thought that I'd had.
I personally don't think so.
I think they're just one big ass super gem.
That's just, you know.
They're just a fucking diamond, you know?
Diamonds are fucking legit.
Pretty cool.
I see no reason to assume that they're a fusion,
but, you know, that might turn out to be the case.
I see no reason to not assume it.
I mean, it could go either way.
I feel like, I feel like if they did that,
there'd be like a hypocrisy to their whole like,
that's true.
Cultural structure.
Well, there'd be a utility
to fusing into like your supreme overlord.
Like he's got a job to do pretty much all the time.
I mean, maybe, but at the same time,
would Jasper be shitting on fusion?
If like, the person you're serving is a fucking ooper.
Well, Peridot's the same way
and Peridot's not retarded.
Like she loves-
It's a combination of things, you know?
She loved the yellow diamond,
but hated the concept of fusion.
If you're like, person you're serving is a massive fusion,
like would you be?
Yeah.
I don't know.
It just feels like it's a little contradictory,
but it'd be an interesting kind of twist.
Well, no, but if the diamonds are-
It could be something that only is allowed
for the top fuses.
Diamond is a fusion of all of a single sort of diamond gem.
Then it wouldn't be weird because that sort of thing
is okay under certain conditions in gem society.
I don't know.
I don't like it.
I feel like it would weaken.
Here's a thought.
They are some sort of fusion thing
and have made a social stigma against it slash outlawed it
in an attempt to keep power
so that no one can shout at them.
I just gotta say, I really don't believe that theory
because they only have one gem on them.
Well, we only saw one.
It could be, you know.
Oh, that's true.
I guess their whole body is.
Maybe under their dresses,
they just got gems everywhere for nipples and gems.
Yeah, maybe.
Okay, well, you know what?
I forget that.
Let's talk about yellow diamond
and how shit her design is.
Can we address that?
Yeah, no problem.
Her neck was three times the length it should have been.
And her shoulders were dumb.
Yellow diamond.
It should have been though.
I didn't remember what she was supposedly-
Right, we're all basing this on that one image
in the extended opening.
So when I saw her face and neck, I was like,
oh, cool, she's like a weirdo.
But she looks, I just,
when I think back to how she looked at first,
I'm just like, why?
Yellow diamond looks ridiculous.
She looks laughable.
The thing that threw me off about it
was just the saturation of the yellow to such a degree.
Yes.
Because she looks cool and still a wedge.
And it's all one color.
She's got a great shape to her.
But then you see her,
and it's like someone just urinated
inside her fucking mouth.
Yeah.
And it took over her skin tone.
Her design is boring.
Yep.
Silly drab.
It's all the same color.
It's like her shapes.
Her shapes are so dumb.
She's just got this stupid breastplate torso
with these stupid big giant shoulder jangles
jabbing out of the sides
with these two little stick arms coming out.
I'm so angry, I'm so angry that they disappointed me.
It is drab.
It is droll and I find it rather pedantic.
It's the proportions are bad.
The proportions are what's bad.
I disagree with anything except the neck.
I think the neck's cool.
Yeah, that's because you love those long necks.
The neck should be longer.
She should be called yellow giraffe.
Yeah, you nailed it dog.
But you know, I thought Blue Diamond looked fucking sick.
She was awesome.
Yeah, Blue Diamond looks fucking sick.
Why?
She was a cloth.
Yeah, but cloths are cool, you know?
She's got that whole, I don't know.
But you don't know exactly what a neck or face looks like.
When I see that neck,
I'm gonna be getting out my ruler.
Maybe they all have long necks.
I'm just saying, I've seen so much great fan art
of Yellow Diamond, and then the real one
was just like a million times worse.
Rose Quartz was ostracized from the long neck guild
for having a normal neck of fat, short neck.
She was like, what's with these fucking necks?
I've got a fucking head cannon.
In the one where Stephen stretches himself out,
Amethyst is like, Stephen, your neck, you have one.
So clearly neck length in Gem Society
is a strong status indicator.
Kind of like height and invader zoom.
Yes, exactly the same.
We've done it.
Definitely it's the same.
Well, this is great news.
Amethyst is like, whoa, Stephen, you've got a neck.
You're the champion now.
She was about to bow down to that neck.
Dude, remember that time?
You're the new gardener.
Remember that one episode where Amethyst
is falling apart and her head gets stretched
like a million feet from her body
and that big, noodley neck?
She was so OP right then.
She would have been like king.
All right, anyway.
Let's move on.
Let's talk about the best episode of the Stephen Bong,
which was Stephen's birthday.
It was the most beautiful thing that I've ever.
What do you mean?
You're saying you're being all dismissive.
It was beautiful, buddy.
The problem was which one was Stephen's birthday?
It was the one where you find out
that he's not eating good.
It's the one where they rehash the whole aging
out of his control thing.
Whoa, whoa, rehash.
You are too hung up on things rehashing
and being similar to other things.
Who cares if it's similar?
It was done better, in my opinion.
In fact, forget the original old guy episode.
Throw that one in the garbage,
throw it in the trash compactor.
I liked that episode because it made me real sad
because Connie really liked it when he was tall.
And in the end, he's just not.
Do when she's bare in her face, it was chess.
So that's just not a thing that's gonna happen.
I mean, eventually maybe he'll get taller.
I'm sure it'll happen someday.
The thing that I love about it is that
it starts out with this revelation about Stephen
that's really interesting,
but also kind of concerning and scary.
That makes it 14.
He looks eight.
And those are kind of the best little things to,
shock people.
He's like, wow, that's cool, but also what?
He's gonna be a baby for that.
But then, when he turns into a baby,
you have Stephen and Connie's relationship
throughout the whole series.
And it's just like, yeah, whatever, they're friends.
They like each other.
They're probably gonna grow up
and blow each other or some shit.
But then it gets taken all the way to the next level
because Stephen becomes a baby.
What are they gonna do?
He's gonna be a baby for every now.
What do we do?
But Connie, her love and devotion,
her true love for Stephen, it comes through
and that's what allows him to get his mojo back.
And it's just...
That's true.
It's beautiful.
That was a good moment.
It warms my heart.
Yeah, Connie's a good character.
I like her a lot.
She's really endearing.
I think Stephen, I don't know.
Her relationship in this episode was great.
I thought this was probably the weakest episode of the bomb,
but I thought...
I agree.
The relationship was great.
The moment when Connie gets super thirsty
with tall Stephen was fucking awesome.
I love the line where he's just like...
In Stephen's mind, they're already gonna get married
because he's like, I'm gonna be the first boy
when she's president because I'm never gonna get older.
Yeah, that was so cute.
I think the romance between Stephen and Connie
is the best romance in any current cartoon by far.
No, you're forgetting about Flash Sentry
and Twilight Sparkle.
Get the fuck away!
No, it's good.
Now listen, I'm gonna say,
and now this isn't necessarily a criticism of the show,
but I'm not that impressed with Connie's devotion to Stephen.
It doesn't stand out to me as something
that's very noble.
I kind of agree with that, actually.
Because I mean, yeah, she's friends with this guy
who has this great magical destiny.
Through her involvement with him,
she's come into contact with these three fucking gods,
these living gods who decide the fate of the universe.
She's become entangled in a web of causality
that is way farther, way beyond anything
she could have hoped for as a mere human.
Yep, yep.
So of course she's gonna fucking stick by Stephen.
She has gotten so much out of her relationship with Stephen.
Look at what she's gotten out of him.
Well, Ben, I guess if you're just a complete cynic
and a pessimist, you can break down people's motivations
and find the selfishness behind what everyone does
all the time.
But yeah, no, see, that's why it was good in that episode.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
To see why Connie was still, you know,
she didn't get frustrated. I don't care if it's right,
it's poopy.
Hey, speaking of poopy,
remember when Stephen pooped on Amethyst's face
as a car seat?
I mentioned that in my video.
He took a big shit right on her face and she loved it.
She wasn't face at all.
She probably ate it, dude.
She probably ate it and thought it was fantastic.
That's what she does.
I had no idea that that was Amethyst
until she talked.
Well, yeah, please not.
Well, it wasn't supposed to.
You weren't supposed to.
Do you think that Amethyst was?
I thought I just missed it and I loved it a lot.
No, that was a joke.
I didn't, I did not like that scene
when it suddenly reveals it to be Amethyst.
I was like, what?
Why?
Okay, they didn't have,
the devil's advocate,
they didn't have a car seat if they needed one.
They didn't have a car seat.
And if they didn't have a car seat,
why would they have diapers?
So do you think Amethyst was also the diaper?
Oh, yes, definitely.
That was her mouth around his ass
just consuming whatever came out.
I mean, she does like pooping.
The most important headcanon of all time.
Amethyst is Stephen's diaper and she got pooped in.
So Stephen is gonna live forever
and Connie's gonna die someday, right?
That's gonna happen.
It wasn't set in state views.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if Stephen and Connie fuse
and they stay fused forever?
That was my thought.
Okay, it's time to reveal my theory.
Here's my theory.
This is what I think.
I've got one too, but okay, you go.
Are you ready?
This is my theory of how this is all gonna fucking go down.
It's gonna tie in what we're talking about.
I wonder if it's the same as mine, but yeah, let's hear it.
Rose Quartz is Pink Diamond.
Okay, I'm with you.
And she...
What?
Shut up, Ben.
I'm getting it.
Rose Quartz is Pink Diamond.
And that was the reason the whole kind of revolt happened.
She was like a big part of the culture
and she's like, you fuck your shit
and that caused a hole to do and that happened.
But that means that now Stephen is Pink Diamond.
Yeah, yep, yep, yep.
Well, sure.
Okay.
It's the same gem.
He's like the big fucking head honcho
without even realizing it.
So what's gonna fucking happen?
Because what's the big conflict going on right now
that they keep referring to?
The fact that fusion is utilitarian on Homeworld
versus fusion with the crystal gems
is something emotional to do with love
and relationships and all that stuff.
And that's something that's what really binds
Garnet's kind of character and conflict.
It's something that all the crystal gems
have kind of come to understand
and they've learned that and reinforced that
because Rose and Greg's relationship
and how relationships kind of like a big thing in this show.
Yeah, sure, sure.
So that's something that like the Homeworld gems
need to figure out
because they're still like collectivists in mentality.
So what's gonna happen?
Fucking Stephen and Connie are gonna fuse into Stavati
and fucking be the new Pink Diamond
and they're gonna fucking teach the Homeworld
that fusion is good.
Garnet's gonna be like, you did good kid
and then they're gonna fucking blow everyone's minds
on Homeworld and rule as the new fucking leader
and like Connie's gonna be president of the fucking galaxy.
No, that's crazy.
You know, call me old fashion.
It'll be a permafusion.
Yeah, we'll go to fascism
which is the logical progression of all society.
Call me old fashion, but I would much prefer
rather than being a permafusion of Stavati
that they just fuck like animals
like normal teenage human babies
the way that God intended.
What I want to happen.
Would their babies be a quarter gem?
How would that work?
There's no, who knows, man, who knows?
I think their babies would just be human.
I agree, I guess.
I don't fucking know.
But here's- Maybe with like some very minor-
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
What if when Connie and Steven go at it,
Steven then disappears and then there's another baby
and then- Oh, God.
And it starts all over again.
That's kind of what I thought might happen.
It's the worst, the worst.
All right, here's a thought.
Steven can fuse with Connie, right?
That means he can fuse with humans
and maybe gems too.
One day, why doesn't Steven just fuse
with every single human being on the planet
and go full God mode?
And then just kill animals.
What I was about to say is-
Why doesn't every gem just fuse?
I don't know, I don't know.
Steven can be the ark floating in space,
preserving humanity's memory for all time,
like Ava Unit 1.
The way I was imagining-
Just be giant ball arms?
Yes.
The way I was imagining a way it could end really cool
or there'd be a big climax is like all the diamonds
aside from, you know, Pink Diamond,
they fuse together into this giant thing.
And then Steven fuses with the cluster or something
and becomes a giant robot space gem.
Ew, the cluster's gross though.
No, but think about, I mean, it could be a cluster.
It could be just some other thing.
I don't know.
Just like a huge giant space battle with gem people
punching each other, throwing planets.
It's gonna go full ground login, hopefully.
So you want the end of ground login?
Yeah, if that happens with Steven Universe,
that'd be something.
It'll be the best cartoon.
I think what's really gonna happen
is that Steven's gonna change gem society
in some major way.
They'll all just be friends.
I wanna blow shit up, I wanna throw-
Let me change-
He's gonna do it by blowing shit up first.
Yeah, all right.
Let me change gears for a second.
In, I forget which episode,
the one where they go to the moon.
There's that terminal and it shows the map of the earth,
right?
Which was an awesome episode with all that more.
Everyone's really bent out of shape
about the big hole in Russia.
And that is a big deal.
But that's not the only difference.
And in the center of it was a gem construct of some kind.
Yeah, yeah, but there's more than that.
Like, Africa is like cut in half
and South America has a big chunk on.
And I think Australia is like kind of messed up too.
It's like half gone, yeah.
Yeah, so there's all kinds of weird stuff.
It was just that those could have been explained
by a shitty map version,
whereas the Russia one seemed a little more overt.
No, no, no, no, no, I disagree.
They were definitely their intention.
I mean, the Russia one was the most obvious.
That's right.
What are you fucking saying?
What are you talking about?
What about Russia?
People are bitching about the countries
being deformed on the map.
Is that a thing?
Yeah, yeah.
Are people that fucking retarded?
Oh, I hate to tell you the entire fucking planet's dead.
Well, Tom, what are you talking about?
The planet's fine.
It was gonna be dead later, but it didn't, you know.
I have to say that Ben completely lost me.
What about Russia?
Who gives a shit life?
Okay, this, all right, you're gonna have to go look it up.
But if you look at the map that Peridot
brings up on the moon terminal,
the map has a few changes from our world and their world
and the most noticeable is that Russia
has like a huge hole blown in it.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait.
And there's a gem construct located right
at the center of the crater.
Yep.
Yeah, whatever.
I know, it's blinking, you missed it.
Like it goes by in a second, but it's definitely there.
Yep.
And so I guess, so I'm thinking what it must mean
is probably that their world is our world
except that, you know, however many thousands of years
ago, some cataclysm happened where the gems showed up
and it changed the world
and it's like an alternate timeline of our world.
Yeah, I pretty much agree.
It's what our world would be if the gem.
Does that really even need to be clarified?
I mean, it's a cartoon, I already assume that it's not real.
Yeah, like why are people giving a fuck?
Well, whatever, he's just saying, it makes sense.
Fuck you guys, I'm giving a fuck because it's interesting.
Oh, no, no, okay, I assumed from what you were saying
that people were like offended that Russia was fucked up.
Oh, no, I don't think so.
No, it's fucking awesome.
Okay, okay, I thought you were implying that like
people were like, what the fuck?
No, truly, that is the brightest possible timeline
in which Russia was blown the fuck out.
No, because it's not just Russia.
Africa is Africa and Australia and South America are all different.
I'm just kidding, Russia, I love you guys.
You make cool things.
Yeah, that was a lot of lore in there.
Hey, do you guys think that in that,
what people call the tomb of white diamond,
that thing in the, where they got trapped,
that they all just split up,
that gem that Steven pulls out of that thing,
it's in that field with all the strawberries,
the battlefield with the big war happened.
Was that white diamond?
Do you think she's dead and that's her
powering that entire thing?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It was too long ago.
Well, whatever, never mind.
No, fucking explain.
I'm just gonna say yes.
In that, you know that one episode
where they go to the strawberry battlefield
and they go into that upside down pyramid
where they get trapped and like it turns out
the place is rotating, you know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
At the end of that, they break through the floor
and go down and Steven, out of like the central core,
he pulls out a big white diamond looking shape.
Does he take it with him?
Yeah, they bubble it, they bubble it.
But the thing is, the whole place was built from that gem
and disappears afterward.
And a lot of people are thinking that it's supposed
to be the tomb of white diamond
and that she was killed during the battle for Earth
and this is her, you know, I don't know.
Maybe, well maybe my question is that.
White diamond ever evolved in the world before?
We don't know, we don't know, no idea.
Well the whole thing is like gems don't die.
Like if you die, you just like get reformed later.
Like wouldn't the gem have to be destroyed completely?
Well, that's the thing, it was trapped in this thing
like in a construct, you know.
Yeah, well they did bubble it.
So maybe, yeah, maybe now that it's been removed,
it could reform into white diamond.
Wouldn't that be something?
I mean, possibly?
I don't know.
But you'd think they would recognize.
Yeah, like they've been there,
they fought that battle, right?
I feel like they should've known themselves.
I mean, they just like saw yellow diamond on communicator
and all like piss themselves.
Yeah, you know what else was interesting though
and I wanna talk about this a little bit.
In the answer, okay, so it's been confirmed
that Rose led at least some kind of big army
against the forces of the homeworld gems, right?
She definitely had an army, that's been said.
And yet in the answer, like she and Pearl show up
by themselves to do a mission,
which doesn't necessarily mean a lot.
But what it does mean is that every single other gem
that fought on her side was killed in that fight,
except for like five of them.
That's pretty crazy.
Isn't that, I'm wondering, I'm afraid it's gonna turn out.
No, it doesn't necessarily mean that.
We don't know, the rest of them could've been taken prisoner
or like been granted a pardon after the battle
for whatever reason and gone home.
But no, it's said that Rose won the war, right?
I mean, is it winning if like all of your forces
are captured, why don't they just?
Winning would be the earth not being destroyed.
And that's kind of why Peridot was like,
well, you didn't fucking really win anything
if the cluster's still gonna fuck it up.
You know, that was kind of her point.
Who's to say for sure that she did have a big army,
maybe it was.
She says many times that she had an army,
but did she mean her and like her four friends?
Was that her fucking army?
Well, that's the whole thing,
because like, you know, fucking like,
it's just Rose and Pearl in the answer.
And like, on the one hand, maybe it's just kind of like
a representation, because like all the background characters
weren't even like fully drawn,
so maybe it was just kind of taking
some artistic liberties there.
But on the other hand, like we don't know
any of the other ones, like they did mention
in like one of the earlier episodes
that like all the monsters that they were bubbling
used to be gems, and I'm assuming those are probably
like maybe gems, like their comrades
that they've been connected or something.
Yeah, possibly, possibly.
Like that's kind of what it seems like it was implying.
And like on the battlefield, where that, you know,
they say the Tomb of White Diamond was,
which wasn't necessarily that, like that's full of swords
and like weapons, that was clearly a huge battlefield.
They say it was a gem war was fought there.
It couldn't have been fought by just five fucking dudes.
Unless like it was just them versus everybody
and they're just fucking OP Neo.
Okay, Pearl is super OP.
She beat like a triple fusion by herself.
She is super duper strong.
That's true.
True, but that took a lot out of her.
It did, she only barely did it.
But at the same time, when you think about it,
like, you know, we saw the rubies
and they're all kind of like crap.
Yeah, like they're ass beaten and like Pearl
didn't even break a sweat.
And that was like, I'm assuming probably early rebellion Pearl.
Because like Garnet hadn't even showed up yet.
So I don't know how OP are they, we really don't know.
Well, that's the thing.
If they're not super OP,
then how the fuck did they fight this whole war on their own?
It wouldn't make sense.
So they must have had forces.
Because they had swords, man.
They, other guys had swords.
Yeah, but they had swords and they know how to use them.
Hey, you know what would be cool speaking to using swords
if Steven fused with Connie
and they use the sword and shield together.
They definitely do, because that's what Rose added.
Oh, it just made me come.
I know it's gonna happen.
That's what I'm saying.
They're gonna fuse together.
They're gonna be the new pink diamond.
They're gonna fucking retrain at the end of the series.
And they're gonna ride lion through space.
And it's gonna be glorious.
It's gonna be glorious.
That's for sure.
I'm so ready.
Yeah, that's how it's looking.
Boy.
I love cartoons.
I do.
Me too.
Let's talk about how Steven Universe
is clearly better than other cartoons in many ways.
That's dumb.
No, it's true though.
It's true.
Wow.
The continuity is just my trigger.
It makes me feel good all over my body.
Well, that's dumb.
That's dumb not every cartoon needs to be like that.
It's not only that.
The way it's built its world,
like gem culture is so cool.
And the way it's set up with all these other social problems
that we can't exactly relate to,
but understand what it would mean if it was in our society.
And how Gem Fusion is a taboo that we,
and how Fusion itself is something that we can get
on a referential level,
but can't specifically experience,
but still understand how cool it is.
Oh, I love it.
Oh, very impressive.
It's great.
But, you really glue me away
with your description of the show right there.
You know what?
Get the fuck out of here with that sarcasm.
I don't even need it.
I know, right?
I'm just saying, like, so what?
It's all of these things you like.
Big fucking deal.
I don't know.
We're doing a podcast about things that we like.
No, no.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm being an asshole.
Honestly, no, like, for real though,
like what show, at least like what Western animation
right now is anywhere near as good.
I mean, I think the closest is probably Gravity Falls,
but Gravity Falls isn't nearly as complex.
No, okay, okay.
It's true.
Steven is my favorite show.
There you go.
All right.
But it still sucks.
Yeah, that's true.
Not as much as your opinion sucks.
Oh, fine.
He's got you beat there.
So guys, let's, I guess, I don't know, feels like.
But I'm just saying, not every show needs to be
what Steven is, which is, you know,
like a dramatic, you know, heavily continuity based,
you know, action comedy, like mishmash genre,
fucking feel-
It's just a cool thing that we like because we're cool.
I just, I agree with what Jesse said in his video though,
that there's not a bad episode of Steven Universe.
Like, that's pretty, pretty much true.
You run the gamut of good.
Wait, are we sure about that?
Some of the episodes involving the citizens of Beach City,
I really do not give much of a shit about,
but they're generally okay.
Honestly, I'm tempted to call the one with the yellow diamond
a bad episode because of how fucking angry it makes me.
Are you kidding me?
You are a moron.
You are such a fool if you let her design blind you
to all the amazing shit that happened in that episode.
I think it was in orbit with that episode.
Yeah.
It's so important and it's so,
and they botched it so bad.
They botched one tiny aspect of it.
It's not even that big a deal.
You are blinded.
Dude, when Peridot yelled at her and overcame her, you know.
Can we talk about Peridot and how she's fucking perfect?
Yes, yes, she is perfect.
Yeah, let's talk about it.
Let me criticize that because I thought that her change,
I thought that her change at the end was a rush
and I didn't call her rush.
It wasn't even rush, it's not like she changed then.
That was the, that was the,
when she expressed the new feelings
that had been developing over the season.
The very, the previous episode,
she showed absolutely no remorse or misgivings at all
at the thought of the entire planet
and everyone on it being destroyed.
The very next episode,
she fucking goes against everything she believes in
to, you know, prevent that from happening.
That is not true.
She clearly is forming a connection with the earth.
Even if she herself doesn't immediately realize it,
people can have contradictions in their own mind.
Dude, the whole thing, Ben,
her interpretation of how best to use the earth
was just different, but they explain it to her.
And she's like, okay, I love the earth.
Let's, you know, monopolize it for resources.
That'd be cool.
And then they're like, no, that's not how we do things here.
We like life.
We want it to stay alive.
And she's like, oh, I hadn't really thought about it that way.
I guess a planet can be useful in that way too.
She's growing as a character.
She's learning new experiences about the world.
And that's what makes it so cool.
Yeah.
Dude, it's even, it's more than that
because Peridot, it's not like she goes into this,
like saying like, I'm going to call Yellow Diamond.
I'm going to like say sorry
and have her come down and fucking wreck this planet.
No, what happened was that
she had realized that the earth was valuable.
But she'd also realized like in that conversation
in the truck with Steven,
that like she thinks that Yellow Diamond is the fucking best.
Like she believes that the diamonds
are inherently superior to everybody.
And she also knows from the map and the shit
and like how the cluster, like the gems,
the crystal gems haven't really accomplished
what they set out to do.
Because like they're still kind of on like a crash course
with like fucking everything up.
That like they can't fucking solve it.
But she believes that Yellow Diamond could.
And she says, the reason she idolizes Yellow Diamond
is so much is because she's logical.
That's what she loves about her so much,
which makes sense because Peridot tries to be logical,
but she's shown throughout this entire time at the barn
that she's quick tempered.
Like she blows her top over everything.
So she's like, I need to go contact Yellow Diamond
and plead my case because she'll listen to me.
I have this new perspective that none of us have
that I've been taught by these people
that I'm going to explain to her and she'll listen to me.
That's exactly right.
She goes to do that and when she does,
she finds out that her idea of what Yellow Diamond was
was a complete crock of shit.
Because Yellow Diamond is fucking pissed
that Rose tried to defend that planet.
And that emotional bias is why she wants
to fucking blow the place up.
And when Peridot realizes that Yellow Diamond
isn't an actuality how she thought she was,
that's when she lets her temper again,
get the better of her and blows her stack.
And that's what causes her to reverse like that.
That's right.
So it's fucking natural, it's completely logical,
it's fucking amazing.
Peridot, wife, who tier, awesome.
She reached out to Yellow Diamond,
thinking that Yellow Diamond would be able
to solve the problem.
Everyone's like, no, don't call her.
But she's like, I'm just gonna fix shit.
But wait, there's something, I think you lost me there.
Maybe I missed it.
But where along the line did, okay, two things.
When did Peridot decide that, oh yeah,
maybe life on Earth is precious
and we should save it.
And more damningly, why would she think
that the logical thing for Yellow Diamond to do
would be to agree with her?
I think that in that moment, confronted with the reality
of ultimate destruction of all life on Earth,
she had a minor change of heart in that moment.
No, I disagree, I don't think it really.
I can believe that, I can believe that.
But what specifically was it that convinced her
that she was wrong about Yellow Diamond
and that she wasn't?
Okay, well, probably also the fact
that Yellow Diamond was that moment.
Was talking down to her and insulting her
and she is a hothead.
Well, that's the thing,
Peridot had come to understand.
And she realized that there was that lack of logic
that what she thought she idolized in her.
But I think, you're right.
What lack of logic?
Because she was trying to present a case
and Yellow Diamond wouldn't even listen to it
because she was so emotionally blinded by her hatred
for what the Earth represented that she wanted it destroyed
and wouldn't even listen to an alternate perspective.
Well, okay.
So what you're saying is that Peridot decided
that Yellow Diamond must not be perfectly logical
because she disagreed with her?
Yeah, pretty much.
Because Peridot knows that the Earth is valuable.
That's pretty darn illogical.
God, not even close.
She just changed.
People change, Ben.
People can change.
It's real, it's really, really simple.
It's fine because I know, as we've said before,
she isn't as logical as she thinks she is
because she's hot-tempered.
I don't even think it's that.
She blew up, Ben.
So she didn't just say like,
okay, well, now I'm not listening to you.
She got frustrated because this person that she idolized
wasn't reacting in the way that she had
internally convinced herself that she would.
Okay, I guess what it comes down to is that
I don't remember any moment before the phone call
where I was like, oh, now Peridot has come around
to the idea that life on Earth has value.
I don't remember that happening.
That's the point of the next episode
is when you see her entire progression
during that three month period
where she learns about fusion,
where she almost fuses with Garnet.
Right, during that phone call,
during that phone call, we are clearly set up
to expect her to like betray us,
but when she actually makes a case for the Earth.
Because we've seen that episode that came after first,
we would know she was no way in hell,
she was gonna fucking do it.
It was intended to be a surprise
that she was on Earth's side.
By keeping us in the dark, we were able to like
be more caught up in the drama of that moment.
Right, exactly.
It was awesome.
It was awesome, it was great.
I can kind of buy that, okay.
But if she'd had this ongoing thing
where she was learning to love Garnet and whatever,
then why, when she saw on the terminal
the image of the entire Earth destroyed,
was she like, heck yeah, that would've been great, right guys?
I mean, that was a big moment when she learned that,
you know, because she still thought
that using the Earth for resources
was a good way to use it.
She didn't really make a connection.
Despite her growth, she was still in that moment.
A tad naive and had different values instilled in her.
I think she was just caught up
in like her admiration for the diamond.
She was like fapping downstairs
about how great they were.
Even during that episode with Garnet,
even then she isn't able to fuse with Earth.
It's not like she's completed her transition
into becoming a crystal gem.
It's like all part of it, you know.
She's shown to be trying to understand this perspective,
but she doesn't get it yet.
Yeah.
It's gonna see how she grows and continues to grow.
And I think her conversation with Yellow Diamond
is the moment the catalyst that makes her finally get it.
She's been trying to get it.
Agreed.
She doesn't quite get it.
But then when she sees Yellow Diamond up,
Yellow Diamond is just being a snobbish,
a snooty cunt.
She's like, you know what?
She's a snooty cunt.
And that's what she says.
She says, you, Yellow Diamond, are a cunt.
And that's how it ended.
I agree that that's the moment when,
I agree that's the moment when she decides
that she can't stick with the diamond authority.
You guys have made a pretty respectable case.
All right.
So that's fine.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you were able to help you.
We saved every, we saved the world.
We did.
We changed Ben's mind about something.
Ben, you've known it out.
Ben, like Parodot, has been introduced to a new opinion.
Oh, he's an arch.
What an arch he's had.
Amazing.
Yeah, what an arch.
What a day.
Oh, look at him.
He's easy.
He's being all sundry now.
Like, oh, yeah, I've learned a lot, guys.
It's not like I like Stephen or anything.
Well, it's been an hour.
I guess that's a pretty good thorough discussion.
Oh, man, I feel like we have any,
I feel like we could go all day on this bullshit.
Yeah, we could talk about specifics, but I don't know.
We could have another Stephen podcast later.
Yeah, we could maybe do that.
I don't know.
Maybe after that bomb.
Leave in the comments if you want more of this, I guess,
you know, or whatever.
See what people have to say about it.
All right, well, thanks for watching, guys.
It's been a good conversation.
Glad we had it.
We'll see you guys in the next one next week.
Everybody say bye.
Bye.
See ya.