Hello everyone, and welcome to this week's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We are delighted to have you back once again with all my best friends, except for Ben,
because he's fucking farting up a storm over there.
Gay.
What do you have to say for yourself, Ben?
I think that money is gay, and I hate you.
Understand.
Digi is here.
Yeah.
As is Geoff.
Yeah, that's me.
In his mom's courthouse.
Geoff returning for the first time in like months.
Oh man, true.
That's right, actually.
I've been busy.
What a cloud has been cast over this lovely podcast of ours.
What's the last time influences?
Uh...
Geez, really?
Maybe.
That was a long time ago.
That was his first one, so that would mean he was only on one.
No, no.
I've been on a couple.
I think the last one I was on was Selling Out, which is perfect for this.
And our friend, Endless Jazz, is here.
That's right.
Now I want to give a big shout out, a big thank you to me for that brilliant job I did
putting together The Plebe and the Weeb, the greatest two guys talking about shows
and drinking beer show in the history of YouTube.
The definitive one, the only one that's ever existed.
I invented it.
I made it.
And I made it so goddamn good that I'm now a millionaire.
So thank you.
And that's what we're here to talk about today.
Thank you, Endless Jazz.
Thank you, and you're welcome.
And you're welcome to Endless Jazz.
Yes.
Thank you.
We all are thankful.
And the topic of today's podcast is crowdfunding.
And by the way, there just so happens to be an urban dictionary definition of crowdfunding
that I pulled up ahead of time.
All right, so here we go.
Crowdfunding.
The number one definition.
I love that this show is urban.
I love that we keep it straight in this podcast.
Yeah, we really do.
Yes.
All right, so our definition that we'll be using and not deviating from the slightest
is crowdfunding.
Hipster slash tech speak translated to quote, begging for money over the internet.
And that's exactly what it is.
That's what I would have said.
Hashtag soliciting, hashtag begging.
A noble calling only for the bravest of champions.
And we've got a few of them.
In fact, every single one of us.
Every single person on this podcast is a crowdfunding millionaire.
In fact, one person on this podcast is a crowdfunding website, patreon.com slash bensane.
That's right.
I invented the market and then cornered it.
Turning every dream into a plan and then fulfilling it.
So I mean, everyone listening, everyone listening probably already knows what crowdfunding is.
And if not, there's an easy way for you to learn is to go to patreon.com slash your best
guy ever.
Or patreon.com slash a million dollars.
And it's already disgusting.
This is already a disgusting podcast.
I agree.
The people love it.
All right.
This is what money does to people.
And that's why you can't be implicit in the system.
You got to rage.
Rage against the garbage.
This is coming from the wall.
I want to hear that from you, Ben.
From patreon.com slash bensane.
You ruined Corona's life with all that hot Nuzlocke money.
You ruined his life.
You made him a wreck of a man.
He's depressed.
He won't come out of the toilet.
I think it's a transitional phase he's in.
I think he's going to come out of it stronger.
Oh, I hope so.
I mean, I hope so too.
Did you, you were saying something of substance, I think?
Yeah.
Please continue.
This isn't the podcast for that.
Get the fuck out of here.
I want the biggest, greenest arrow with the biggest implying in all caps right next to
that statement.
Yeah.
But, yeah, no, Ben, patreon.com slash bensane here, who's just coming off the heels of a
very successful Indiegogo campaign.
It was GoFundMe, but yeah, same thing.
To fund a computer that you built and as well as a 3DS with a capture card so that you
could do a Nuzlocke.
But yeah, Ben's computer is almost done.
His squat racks finally finished unrelated.
That was a crowdfung.
Yeah, so I should just say about the GoFundMe that, like, I mean, I saw Monkey had done
a GoFundMe for a capture card and I was kind of inspired by him and I went and I did mine
for my computer that I really needed a new one, but I couldn't afford one.
I feel a little bit like Monkey has become the new drowning in footwear and that he's
the guy that everyone's like, oh, remember what that guy did?
He's so awesome.
He's so cool.
I want to do things like that guy.
Well, no, maybe.
I guess.
I agree.
Monkey is an inspiration.
I love you, though, Monkey.
A scholar.
Well, yeah.
So we're also coming on, this is literally, we're at the very end of day one of a 30-day
Kickstarter that I've launched with Mr. Endless Jess in order to fund-
He says launched with me, but I had no idea this was happening.
Yeah.
No.
I just woke up a millionaire.
That's the end of the story.
You know, kids, if you follow your dreams, someday you'll wake up and one of your friends
will have made you a millionaire.
You knew before you went to bed that this was going to- that a Kickstarter was in the
worst.
Yeah.
Well, like, we had been talking about it.
Yeah, we should do a Kickstarter and all this.
And I'm like, yeah, okay, sure, whatever.
Because like, my general philosophy with all things in life is that eventually someone
will do it for me.
And once again, I was proven right because I was like, yeah, sure, it's Kickstarter,
whatever, sounds great.
So then I wake up today.
I wake up in my bed surrounded by all my women.
I've got all these women here.
You know, it's like in the Feel Good, Inc. video when Murdoch wakes up and he's got
all those babes around him, all those, all those fine sluts.
You've got Asuka, you've got fucking-
Yeah.
And I go over-
I was so turned on by that highly problematic scene.
And I go over and I look out the window and off in the clouds I see Digi on a windmill
playing guitar with a fucking kickstarter behind him bringing all this money into my castle.
Wait, no, this metaphor doesn't end well, that's when the windmill gets shot down.
And then I just picture off on the side, Colt Corona just walking and singing, Patreon,
Patreon, Patreon, kickstarter for me.
I can, whatever, things, things related to that song.
Yeah.
That's as creative as Colt Corona could probably have been about that.
Yes, I was in character.
I'm sure there's some line in there about his giant dong or some shit.
He tends to shoehorn that in wherever he can.
He really does.
But don't be fooled, people.
There's still such a void in Jesse's empty soul that could only be filled by more money.
It's true.
Don't give up.
And if you toss in even more money, you'll be able to see even more cool people in videos
with Digi.
Yes, you'll get to see Hippo and Nate, cool people.
And also, Jeff might show up.
Maybe.
I'm not a cool person.
I'm just advocating for the rest of them.
Do we have a, is there a numerical goal for that tier?
Yeah, it's a 5,000 for you and Hippo and then another 400 for Jeff.
All right, there you go, folks.
So yeah.
And after that, all the money will just go into Jesse's pocket, essentially, because
he's adding this thing and it's mostly his work.
And I can assure everyone it'll be spent wisely.
And we're talking about 26 episodes at this point, right?
That's correct.
20 episodes.
They're not going to be all filmed at once.
It's going to be like, you know, we're going to do season one and then like six months
later we'll just fly Jesse down again with the remainder of the money.
Because like, Jesse doesn't, I'm sure, does not want to have to edit 20 fucking episodes
of this at once.
Yeah.
Or for his wife.
Even three nearly killed the man.
Yeah.
I don't think he wants his life to be filmed.
You know what this reminds me of, actually?
I was watching the DVD commentary of Seinfeld of the early episodes, at least I think with
the DVD commentary.
It might have been an interview.
But they were talking about the process through which Larry David had to write the scripts
for the show and he was talking about at first there was a pilot and he immediately wanted
to kill himself, that he had to write a pilot.
It was already done.
But then the show got picked up and he had to make like a four episode season, season
like zero, season one.
And he also at that point he knew there was no, there was no saving him.
He had to die, but he somehow got it done.
And then it came time to write like a 26 episode season and at that point every shred of the
man had been eroded away.
There was only a husk where love and trust had once been.
And that's how we get the Larry David of today.
And that's how we get the movie.
And I just imagine the same thing happening to Jesse.
Yeah, that's right.
Jerry, Jerry by the way, was fine.
Jerry, he didn't really write as much as Larry, so let's see his personality that just let
things roll.
Anyway, who cares about fucking Seinfeld?
I don't know.
I care about Seinfeld.
He's a bee.
Yeah, fuck him.
Yeah, fuck that guy.
Nice, he's cool.
He is a bee after all.
So, so in addition to these Kickstarter and other campaigns thing, we all, every single
one of us has a Patreon that run in slightly different ways, but in general they are sources
of funding that allow us to do the stuff we're doing.
And by the way, the rest of us all can entirely subsist off of our Patreon.
That's exactly what I was going to say.
And add money.
That's true.
Right, yeah.
Oh, look at these guys with their add money.
Well, actually, I mean, I make like, I'm making a substantial amount of cash this month
from just shelling for various companies.
Oh, right.
That's true.
Which is something we should all get into in a good way.
Not crowdfunding.
Yeah, that's true.
That is not crowdfunding, it's not part of the conversation.
When I get my ad revenue checked from YouTube every six months or in the mail for a fucking
like $10, it feels like I got the golden ticket.
It's such a rare occurrence.
It's like when they had the jury in Clerk's The Animated Series and it's like, well, they
gave us $5 for breakfast today.
I hope this trial never ends.
That's how I feel when I get my fucking yearly $2 of ad revenue.
It gets lower every time I mention it.
Yeah.
If we ever get paid for T-Batben, I don't know if we did.
We got like, I want to say $130 at one point.
Yeah, we got like slightly over $100 for like well over a million views.
We got well over a million views, like $100 and that was it.
So thanks, YouTube.
You're the best.
Yeah, no, ad revenue is so unreliable that like, I don't check it at all.
I never look at what I'm making, like maybe once a month, I'll take a glance just to see
if I'm like, you know, doing better or worse than the previous month, but I plan all of
my finances just around Patreon so that every time YouTube money does show up, it's a huge
surprise.
And it's like, oh my God, I'm rich.
I have all the sex money.
Let's talk about like the $10,000 or so that YouTube owes me for my fucking Bats video
that they siphoned all the aggregate wall that got like 10 billion views and I've never
seen a penny from it.
Inexplicably.
Well, yeah, yeah, that's that's that shit Craig.
But you know, I was going to say, it's really interesting to me that shit Craig got.
That just about sums it up, guys.
It's really interesting to me.
You know how this thing happened recently where like videos were getting demonetized
and everyone was freaking out because like, oh, all the YouTube guys are going to go under.
But like, it's interesting that pretty much all of us are talking like our primary source
of income, at least for you, Digi, of the primary source of income is Patreon.
So like, you're not even really depending on the ad revenue that is sort of being pulled
from some people, whereas other creators are like freaking out because it is.
Patreon has definitely changed the model.
It's changed the game.
And for two reasons, and this will get into some of the deeper stuff, like on the one
hand, it's just that ad revenue is so, so unreliable.
And also, I think a business model that's dying.
I think it's going out because ads on it, I've seen, you know, a bunch of studies basically
saying that ads on the internet aren't actually making anybody money.
Like everyone's assuming they should be making money.
Everyone thinks that it's like, you know, it sounds like a good idea on paper, but it's
not like, it's not nearly making back what it's being, what's being spent on it, you
know, like the, the, the paying for ad space is not having enough returns for the advertisers
in the first place.
So eventually advertising has to either transform or die, you know, it's, it's going in that
direction where people just have to really consider what they're actually trying to advertise
on YouTube, make sure it's super relevant to what people are, you know, watching.
And then, you know, some of the paid endorsements are a better way of doing that, which is why
those are getting popular and why guys like Jeff are, you know, doing some of the endorsement
deals, but, um, but beyond that, I mean, the thing is like paid endorsements, they're
fun, they're fun for everybody.
If you do them right, if you do them wrong, it's like, oh, hey, Rob Schneider's on Game
Grumps.
What? Yeah.
Was he, was that a, I mean, I don't think that was paid.
I don't think that was paid, but it like feels weird and uncomfortable.
It was a shitty episode.
I watched it and I don't really watch Game Grumps, did not enjoy it.
Yeah.
But like the point that I'm making is like, when you have, when you have fun with doing
a paid endorsement, it's like, it connects better with the audience because it's the
type of content that they're actually there for as opposed to something completely different
that's being tossed on.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, the reason I'm comfortable doing crunchy roll ads is because I legitimately
use crunchy roll.
I watched most of my anime on there because it's fucking convenient, you know, for me
because I, you know, live in the United States and don't have half the shows blocked.
But like, you know, I'm endorsing something I actually believe in.
And even then half of the time I do it as like a fake mock, you know, ad, like I'm usually
shitting on whatever show.
And then I'm like, oh, by the way, it's on crunchy roll.
If for some reason you want cancer, you know, and that works.
People really respond well to that.
And that's going to get me into why I believe so strongly in crowdfunding because I really
think it's the most respectable way to get money.
And like it's it's funny because I feel like most people feel the opposite.
And I did too.
When I first started, like I really didn't want to ask people for money.
I wanted it to be all through, you know, through ad revenue, because I was like,
that's so corporate and, you know, disconnected.
And it's like, you know, I'm just I'm just doing a job.
I'm just getting paid by the machine.
You know, that's how money should flow.
It should all be structured and stuff.
But like that is actually the opposite of how it should be.
It should be organic.
It should be people choosing exactly where their dollar goes and why it's going there,
you know, and I have to earn every single fucking dollar that I make.
It has to like for me to get paid, I have to impress people.
My work has to be something people want to see.
It can't be something advertisers want.
It can't be something that the mainstream media did just died.
No, he died and he took my Kickstarter money with him.
That's now that's a tragedy right there.
I was just giving an impassioned speech about fuck the fuck the advertisers.
But like, you know, it's just that, yeah, every single time someone pledges to me,
it's because they personally felt a connection to my content and wanted to support it,
you know, and like, and that's how I spend a lot of my money as well.
Is like, I I spend my money to vote with the dollar.
I don't really buy art for the sake of owning it.
I buy it for the sake of giving money to the people so that they know,
hey, someone out there appreciated your work enough to think that you should be
able to live off of it, you know.
Yeah. Yeah. And you know, it's interesting, you know,
however your personal feelings are about, you know,
like people having a patron or not, like even some artists do,
like Gibba was telling us the other day that what's his name?
Happy Harry cartoons, like the guy who makes that, he hates Patreon.
He like makes fun of people with patrons or something.
He hates Patreon. It makes fun.
Demolition D. There you go.
But why is it more?
Well, that's the thing. You have to think about trash, idiots, scum.
Well, all right, that's that's the thing, though.
Like you have to consider what are the alternatives and like what are the
what are the reasons for your belief and what are the alternatives?
If you don't like crowdfunding, then like theoretically,
you would think that their motivation is probably that they think that it's in
some way taking advantage of the fans' goodwill or something along those lines.
But I mean, does that argument really hold up because no one's forcing them to do it?
And I think a lot of it is a matter of there's so many people who have
and I'm just going to call it pretentiousness about like what deserves
to be paid for and what deserves to be considered art, you know?
Like there's there's there's still even among lots of critics and stuff,
there's still this mentality that anything that's derivative of another work
is lesser and not deserving of, you know, making money.
Like I hold that belief.
I hold that belief personally.
I mean, do you think that like that someone who draws like the shittiest
comic in the world should be getting paid more on Patreon than me?
Do you have a new personally advocated for
I mean, I mean, I mean, did you qualify with the shittiest
comment in the world and no, did you did you?
We already we already know that Ben thinks he should be paid more than you.
Well, that's true. That's true. I do believe.
But hey, wait a minute, Jeff, you fucker.
Jeff, the full implications of what you've said have sunk in
and I'm prepared to kill you for that.
That was a slow burn.
That was nice. That's that was a five alarm.
That's all right.
Samurai walks.
That's when the samurai slashes walks five steps.
Oh, yeah. She's the sword.
The blood. That was that was Thor.
That was Thor taking his eight steps or whatever
after he was bit by the by the Mjolnir serpents.
And yes, that's the five finger death punch.
But by the way, people,
if you want to see me be killed live on camera by Ben St.
Right.
Then you should get money to the plea of the lead Kickstarter.
Absolutely true.
Shilling Kickstarter that we are.
I my superpower is shilling literally just like
true. Get me to record myself for 20 minutes.
That can be a starter video.
I knew there was something special about you.
I knew there was that X factor that made you a winner.
I feel like you've done that.
To get back to what I was saying, like, right, you know,
I think there are some people who like really think that
if it's if it's original, regardless of the quality of it,
if it's original, it's more deserving.
Like Demolition D, you know, makes high quality YouTube videos
that some would say.
Some would. I used to make high quality YouTube videos.
He used to make videos at all.
But he used to make videos that that, you know, would be deserving
of, you know, making money from them, but he doesn't see it that way.
Meanwhile, he has this novella that he has on Amazon and he's selling it,
you know, because he sees it as this novella is my original work
that is worthy of being paid for, whereas my videos are not
because they're derivative, even though, you know, I mean,
I haven't read the novella, so I'm not going to say it's shittier than the videos.
But, you know, I think that's the mindset a lot of people have.
But that's not what the market is.
The market is people pay for what they want.
They want, you know, if people want derivative work, then it's, you know,
you might consider it unfortunate if that's not to your taste or whatever.
But again, I think that's pretentious.
The value of art lies solely with the people who place value in it.
And if people decide that something is worth their money,
then there's no fucking argument.
It is with their money because they decided to give their money.
And if you're going to sit there, you have to be you have to be a seriously
like arrogant egotistical twat to think that you're the sole arbiter
who gets to decide that something that someone made is not worth being paid for.
You know, you know, it's interesting because I think you guys are all
basically in agreement on that.
But I kind of I actually disagree with the part of that argument
because I've really racked my brain about what the usefulness
or like what the point of art is.
And the only answer that I was able to find was that it has like
that if a piece of art has a real world practical implications
about making the world a better place, that's the only way at the end of the day
that it has any value at all because art has a value in let's say
I get home from work and I want to kill myself.
And then I watch an episode of anime and now I don't want to kill myself.
That's that. Well, then that means that anime has done the world a disservice.
Let's be real. Yeah, that's true.
If you that was like, oh, man, another seven.
Jeff is all Jesus Christ.
That's what I'm here for.
Apparently, I bought today.
Oh, God.
Oh, brain dump is so good, though.
I was I was just going to say that I completely lost my point
after that savage blow from Jesus Christ.
It's all I've been I've been working.
I've been working at a shill video for the last like 30 hours straight
and and reediting and reediting is built up in your veins.
All that's going on in Jeff's brain is like, money, money, burns, money, burns,
burned the money.
I was something crossfire.
All the money's gone.
Right. I think I was going to say something along the lines of if you can do
sort of like, I mean, to expand from my point, if you can do like a social
experiment and determine whether or not there are like the the market forces
or just like the the the the social forces of like a given piece of art,
if they are trending towards a positive thing, like, you know, more people
are, I don't know, helping humanity in whatever factor that you can calculate.
Then it's a good thing if it is like making more people kill themselves
and making people unhappy.
That is how I would quantify a bad piece of art because it is causing bad things.
People kill themselves as opposed to there's got to be some amount of the
like unfathomable quantity that of people who like message everyone
who makes art and tells them, you saved me from depression.
You saved my life.
Wow. Your art has helped me to, you know, come to grips with the torturous
reality that is living, you know, that's the kind of messages I get all the time.
You know, that's great.
I mean, if if art does that, then that's obviously a positive influence.
But I'm just saying that this is my criteria.
This podcast has changed career trajectories for many fans who've written
in who have completely changed the way that they, you know, organize their lives
because of the advice we didn't go.
I had just today I read a letter from someone who was like trying to become
a scientist and then like she realized that, you know, my whole rant about
like how there's a difference between enjoying, you know, the idea of the thing
versus actually doing the thing.
And she's like, I realize I fucking hate doing science.
So, uh, oh, yeah, the world is descending into nothing but artists.
No one's going to do anything anymore because I want other people to do the science for me.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, no, no.
OK, OK. So it's slightly unfortunate that it happened to be a scientist doing
doing what you like. That only applies to us. OK.
That only applies to the people that are broadcasting this podcast.
Everybody else fucking make my sandwiches for me.
Please. Yeah, I would definitely rather have the science be done by people
who fucking love science than the people who, you know, are miserable
and just want to fucking get their damn paycheck and go home.
Let's let's get all the all the intellectuals on the Reddit board.
I fucking love science to do all our science for us. Perfect.
Is that a Reddit board? I thought that's a.
That's a real it's probably Facebook or whatever.
I don't keep up with the hip things going on with the kids with the Facebooks
and the tweet bots and the pictograms.
So I want to talk a little bit about how we've all had such fucking
successful crowdfunding campaigns, because I think there's there's sort
of a unifying factor with all of us, especially.
And like it's it's not that any of us have tried to like be
the the personality that gets this to work.
But like if you read all the advice given by Kickstarter and Patreon about
like what to do, it just happens to fit what we already are like,
which is to just be extremely honest and open about what like what you're
doing, what you're trying to do, what the money is for and like, you know,
how you feel about it.
And I think that honesty goes so far with people because like it's kind of
this whole model is kind of, you know, rejecting what I was just describing
of like the corporate ad culture where everything is so fake that
you literally know that, you know, that like everyone knows that ads are
a fake dolled up, gussied up version of just on Friday, by the way.
I mean, since I'm in the corporate world myself still, the like just on Friday,
we were having a meeting me and some of my coworkers and they were saying
that like no names, but like they had just nothing to do for the whole week.
And they were still getting a paycheck, but like that's the exact sort of
thing that would not be tolerated in a crowdfunding thing, you know, not delivering
your fans would fucking revolt on you as has happened plenty of times.
You know, and like that and just the the idea of ads.
There was a great super bunny hop just did a video about this, how like,
you know, in games nowadays, like there's they're trying to debate the legality
of whether like showing a blatant gameplay trailer, but styling it like
bullshots, legal bullshots, and like it's currently being considered legal
just because all advertising is like that.
So it's like what makes this we're used to being lied to.
So there's no crime here.
That's actually what the judge said.
Like people are used to being lied to.
So no reasonable consumer would assume that this was real.
You know, that means that you have to raise your children and teach them
you are going to be lied to all the time in life.
Like there's no avoiding it.
You have to do it according to the system.
And it's so when people see someone who's just like blatantly being honest,
then it's like it's such a refreshing thing to just be like, yeah,
I'm I'm giving my money to that guy.
And like, I think for for for us, especially, and I know this is certainly
true of me and Jesse, like, I think a lot of it also has to do with how loose
we are, that we never make like promises we can't keep.
We never try to make it sound better than it is, you know, like me or Jesse
will put out an update that's like, hey, I'm going to charge you guys for a
vlog. I need money, you know, and like, yeah, yeah, because like, I don't ever
want anyone to expect something other than what's the best I like, honestly
think I can give, you know, I don't want anyone to think I don't go out there
and I'm like, oh, man, if you guys give this much money, it's going to be so
much better than ever before.
That's why like all the reward tiers on the Kickstarter for pleave and the
weave were like goofy shit, you know, it was like, we'll buy more posters and
t-shirts because you're not going to make a better product than what we
already planned, you know, like that's not going to happen by throwing more
money at it. So just be completely real with people like, hey, here's how much
money it takes to just fly Jesse down here. We're going to make the show.
It's going to be just like the pilot, but with better visuals and audio because
we have the equipment working now. And if you give us more money, we're going
to spend it on, you know, shit to put in the show.
And I saw in the comments, people were like, they really were positive about
like, it is so great Digi that you were just like, if we're get over this
money, we're just going to buy t-shirts, posters and booze.
So, you know, give it your own risk.
So that was great.
I mean, really responded that.
That's a good thing to keep in mind for crowdfunding, right?
Like, I mean, everybody's biggest concern when they go into crowdfunding is,
oh, what if we don't make our funding goal, but drastically
outseeding your fund or exceeding your funding goal, outseeding.
What the fuck am I talking about drastically exceeding your funding goal
can be like a huge detriment to your thing.
I used to be a game journalist.
So I looked at a lot of crowdfunding campaigns, you know, I'm a writer.
Yeah, exactly. And you look at you look at mighty number nine.
You look at broken age and you see examples of people who got too much
money and they didn't know what to do with it.
I don't want to raise the money that could live up to Jeff.
Let's not put the idea in people's heads that it's bad for me to make too much
money. The thing is, that's why I I know all those things.
And that's why I styled the Kickstarter this way, because the one I saw
where like I learned all this from because we're from the My Little Pony
community was the Brony documentary that fucking what's the greatest community
of John DeLancey, John DeLancey put together.
So with the Brony documentary, they asked for like a pretty small amount of money
and they ended up making six times what they asked, but they kept like
like all the extended tiers were like, you know, oh, we'll add in this many
interviews, we'll go to this convention and stuff.
And what the thing is that they didn't account for like reshoots or having to
pay audio people to do all like, like having to move the whole crew between
each location, you know, they were just thinking like, yeah, we'll go,
we'll add more, you know, but then it ended up being you have to add way more
because every like every little thing you add is so much more.
It's kind of like how, um, as any of us can tell you, because we all edit
video, like if you make a five minute video versus a 10 minute video,
it's literally twice the work.
And for the audience, it's barely a difference.
You know, they just see it as like, yeah, the video is like five to 10 minutes
long, but you, you really do have to edit five whole more minutes.
And that means that all of the work that the first half took, you have to do twice.
So if you're adding twice as much on, you're doubling the work.
And so like, I mean, there's count for that, you know, there's, there's ways to
cheat, like for instance, if you just play CS go nonstop and talk over it.
Oh, well, that's true.
But the videos are easy to make in the first place with those.
Yeah.
But I, there are actually like ways to cheat with thinking video.
Like the more live action footage you can put into a video where you're talking
about anime, the less you have to think about what I'm not going to put in this
part.
There's ways around it.
And I'm, I'm also, I used to do a lot of that where I used to like, you know,
throw game footage in for a couple of minutes.
If like, I didn't know what to show there and I didn't want to edit that whole
section, the best example being your sword art online rant, which is literally
just an hour and a half of you playing terror online.
Well, that was cause I, I didn't think I'd be able to get past copyright
if I tried to edit the show.
And I didn't want it to look at the show for the time it would take to edit
a fucking hour of whatever happened to that old brony community.
Those swell guys, whatever.
They're embroiled in turmoil about how one of them may or may not have been
slightly mean to the others.
It's tearing them apart.
I, yeah.
I think the best Kickstarter that I've ever seen actually is from Internet
Comment Etiquette, which I don't know if you guys watch that channel.
But I, I suck his dick like every day.
I've almost watched it many times.
He's, he's really seen a bunch of them, but not recently.
So he did an episode about commenting on crowdfunding campaigns.
And then at the end of that, he made a Kickstarter called Eric drinks wine
and gets a haircut, which is to fund the documentary about him drinking
wine and getting a haircut.
And then he, because he is who he is, he decided to make a joke out of
taking for fucking ever to get a haircut and drink wine.
How much money did he raise out of curiosity on that?
Um, God, like 10,000 dollars.
It was something ridiculous.
Let me, let me, let me look at the people of the problem.
The people of the potato salad thing all over.
Yeah.
It's, it, it wasn't quite the potato salad thing, but the potato salad one
though is so indicative of how to do a Kickstarter right because only raised $4,000.
It's all about making your audience feel like they're a part of something
exactly they're contributing to something that's, that's fun.
You know, like the potato salad thing is like, you can give one dollar to this
thing and be able to, to be like, you know, forever be like, huh, I gave a
dollar to a fucking potato salad thing.
You know, from the, from the end of the potato salad guys, it's ridiculous
that they made so much money.
It was my favorite, the user experience is simple.
You just gave a dollar to be a part of my favorite Kickstarter of all time to
this day was one made by our own Ben St.
That was Ben St.
makes a page, a Kickstarter campaign.
No, no, it was.
It was a Patreon.
It was a Patreon, right?
Actually, my, my, what, what is currently my Ben St.
Patreon was originally a joke, a joke Patreon that I converted to a legit one.
Oh, I didn't know.
Yeah.
The original one was Ben St.
It was great.
It was better then.
Please go back.
Yeah.
It was Ben St.
is creating a Patreon and the joke of the Patreon was that the Patreon itself
was my Magnum Opus that I would be like continually building on and like nobody
I even bought a space for it a little bit.
Like I thought I thought it was funny.
Like I thought people might see it and pledge like a dollar just to be like,
yeah, I pledged to this joke patron, but nobody have had there been any pledges
already there.
Yeah.
That's some of us pledged a little on your request, didn't we?
That's another important thing with it didn't.
It didn't catch the way I was hoping it was.
Oh, sorry.
Did you brought up something that's that's another important thing with a
successful Patreon because like I or Kickstarter for that matter.
But like being honest is important and allowing the audience to interact is
important, but the other thing is creating a perception of value.
So like one of the biggest things that you can do to have a successful
Kickstarter or Patreon is have a like make a bunch of your friends agree to put
in a couple of dollars for the first month or so.
Just just so that it looks like it's not dead, you know,
yeah, so make sure it doesn't sound too because like if you if you phrase it
that way, it can sound kind of like shady.
Like we're trying to make it look bigger than it is.
But it's just like if someone says zero, they think I can't save this.
Yeah, yeah.
It's it's it's the full tip jar effect.
Right.
Like if you see a tip jar that has no money in it, you're not going to put
money in it.
But if you see a tip jar that's got like five, 10 bucks in singles in it,
you're going to be like, Oh, I could put a dollar.
Yeah.
And like, do you call the better business bureau over that shit?
Like, no, it's it's not it's not a big deal.
Yeah.
And I mean, I think we've we've also we're also in a fortunate position
that we have an audience that's willing to be like
to immediately give us money so that we don't have to do the full tip jar thing.
But yeah, I think a huge part of why this Kickstarter has taken off
like so fast in such a big way to me, the one being Jesse you're doing
is because I offered a limit to reward that if you paid a hundred dollars,
you get to pick one of the shows.
And those two went instantaneously.
Of course, like even if this show, even if only like 20 people had cared about it,
two of those people immediately cared enough to give a hundred dollars.
And what I would like to see right now, wow, this Kickstarter is on the track
to success. You know, I want to see.
I want to see one of those guys make a Kickstarter campaign to choose which show
he gets to pick for Digi Bros. Believe in the Weeb.
I hope it just keeps going forever.
You know, and by the way, I just wanted to say again, how much I agree with
what I want that I just like, I want that Kickstarter to be like,
like the main goal is like one show, but then every stretch goal is a different show.
Like, oh, no.
A more controversial show.
So the more money he makes the more controversial the show is.
You've got to do tactical pledges and unpledges in various.
You can't do shit right.
I was just going to say that I really was I was thinking about this
as your as your thing was going off.
And I would just think like, let's say that this Patreon campaign had been
like a like a fifty thousand dollar project, just just for argument's sake.
And like if that happened and it met that and then even exceeded that,
that would be getting into some seriously like ridiculous money, you know,
being exchanged. And at that point, it just it worries me
when like guys like just like little people like us doing stuff like this.
And if it could damage the personal relationships between people,
this is something that I've been thinking about for a while, how like having
having a corporate wall in between like where money goes,
sometimes sometimes can be a really helpful thing for preventing
like accountability of where money goes.
And this is just because I am the most I don't know anyone in the world
who cares about money more than me.
I care. I think about it all the time.
Everything I do is motivated by making sure I have enough at the end of the day
to get the things I want to get.
And it's it's it's fucked me over in many ways,
but it's made me extremely keen to any issues involving like shadiness
or like other people trying to pull one over on me.
And also makes me want to pull things over on other people all the time.
And I will if I can ever do it.
So don't trust me, people.
I mean, I make me accountable.
It's funny because I I always fear that I'm going to fuck that up
because yeah, everything I do has been very loose.
Like the money situations that we deal with are exceedingly loose.
Like me and Jesse both.
And that can be dangerous.
Well, like because me and Jesse have done a lot of collaborations
in like, for instance, The Plebe and the Weeb.
Each episode, Jesse marked on Patreon, which is fine,
because he edited all of them.
So he definitely, you know, but I I didn't because I didn't see it as
like my mainline content.
You know, I didn't see it as like each one of these should be Patreon by me.
And Jesse did most of the work anyway.
So like, you know, who am I to to make twice what he would have made off of it?
You know, just because it's on my channel.
But like, but like, I kind of see it as this exchange
because we never know collaboration I've done with anybody.
Have we agreed beforehand?
Like how much money would be paid out?
It's all been like, hey, I think you deserve to have money from this.
Or I think we should do another collab.
You know, like every time Jesse patrons, something that me and him worked on together,
I just think, well, that's another video that I'm going to get Jesse to do with me later,
you know, or, you know, I'm about to do a show with with Jeff in the near future
about Re Zero on his channel because I got I got him to do one on a race on my channel.
You know, I probably made like a hundred bucks off that video.
So if Jeff can make a hundred bucks off of me being on his show, then, you know,
it's even made twice as much money as we would have made if I just split the bill.
You know, yeah.
So like I do think that, you know, it's something you have to kind of tread carefully with
because I think everyone who's been working with me on these shows
understands that I am making a profit from this, you know, whether I offer them money or not.
I think if you go into it and like you don't say anything about wanting money
and then, you know, you come knocking later like, hey, where's the money?
Like I don't remember offering it to you, you know,
but I think I would probably give them something if they, you know, if they begged like, man,
this is this is a dangerous topic.
I just see pitfalls everywhere.
You know, I think I think that the fact that we're all friends
and the fact that we're all again, generally honest people has kept this fairly safe, you know,
and like, you know, that's true.
But I always just everything so far has been 100 percent great.
But yeah, I always think that somewhere down the line,
if we get involved financially with each other, that would be the one thing
that could cause theoretical problems.
And you know, I think about that for every business relationship of everyone in the world.
Like even if you room with someone, like that can get messy.
I've had difficulties with friends over the years, but that's why I live with them.
That's why you're like important to Analyst Inc, Nate,
because you're you're like you you're not a scumbag, but you think like a scumbag.
And that's what you think you piece of shit.
Yeah, but that means you can be our scumbag watchdog.
Yeah, that's true.
That is true.
My thought process though is just to be extremely cutthroat about it.
If any of you fucks me, I will never speak to you again.
Yeah, yeah, what if I fuck you just a little bit?
If you what if I give you a little reach around?
What if I give you a little reach around, you know?
That sounds like a positive thing.
You know, while I'm fucking you, what if I fuck you?
But I give you a little reach around.
Maybe that's just the courteous thing to do.
Luckily, I don't have the patience to fuck any of you.
I might have the desire.
I might have the desire to steal from you and betray you in the most
heinous ways possible, but I just don't care.
Oh, but see, but see, this is exactly why crowdfunding is so
such like an interesting topic socially, because like even just
bringing it up at all has made us get into this thing about like,
can we trust each other?
Like, where do our boundaries lie?
Like, what's the responsibility of us to like manage each other?
That's kind of what all money and interaction is.
Like, it's all a system of trust.
It's all based on the idea that if I give you something,
you will give me something in return, you know, and that's entirely
a trust based thing.
And that's why, again, I think that's part of why we all
feel so lied to when every day I go to some fucking fast food
place and I buy something and they half cook it and they
sloppily throw it together.
And I'm like, why can't I just fucking get an honest transaction
that I get my money's worth out of what I fucking bought.
And so when you can actually make the same argument with the ads
that you should know by now that fast food is going to be shit.
So it's your own fault.
Yeah.
And and and so again, when like when people, you know, donate to
my channel and they actually see videos that they, you know,
care about, then they're like, finally, a transaction that I feel
good about in my life, you know, and I'm sure there's some people
who don't feel good about every single one.
And I'm always telling, like, you know, my patrons, there's no
guilt if you leave, you know, like, if you don't like what I'm doing
not to pay for, like, you know, you can set a cap for the month.
Or, you know, that's the great thing about it's really on you
as a as a payer, what you want to pay for and what you don't want
to pay. Exactly.
They're both all the all the crowdfunding sites are very like
you know, in favor of the buyer and that's I also that's why I
favor Kickstarter over like Indiegogo or GoFundMe because in
Kickstarter, you have to make the full amount before you get
paid, you know, if it if on the other sites, if you don't make
the full amount, you can still just pocket all the money they
gave you, whether you can even afford to do the thing or not,
you know, it's more of like a donation charity kind of thing,
which I mean, I'm not opposed to it, but Indiegogo is where
scummy kick starters that couldn't make it on Kickstarter go for a
second run.
Yeah, to be fair, or perhaps something like, you know, like
like a pity party like guys, I'm being abused by myself. I need
to move out of my house where my Tulpa lives. I need to leave
him behind, you know, you know, so like my you make, you know,
half the money you're looking for that's still helpful. Maybe
something like that would be appropriate. I don't know. I'm
just thinking about when it could be a good idea.
I want to I want to get into now the topic of kick starters, I
have a problem with and I'm not talking about the obviously
bad ones, the ones that everyone thinks are like a scam or
something like that. But I am talking about the ones that
turn out bad. And I feel like we we should have known and to to
that come to mind and I was thinking about doing a vlog
about this anyways, why I'm gonna get into this rant here is
mighty number nine. And while it remains to be seen if it will
be good, that Castlevania one what's a bloodstained lords
bloodstained bloodstained will be good. I don't know man. I've
I've seen I've seen some of the like footage of the game. It
doesn't. Okay, what bothers me about it is that it doesn't look
as good as Castlevania. You know, like it doesn't look as good as
Symphony of the Night, which is everyone's paying for it
because they want it to be another Symphony of the Night. But
it doesn't look as good as Symphony of the Night. What's
the point?
It doesn't look as good. Are you talking visually or
mechanically?
Visually, mostly. Okay, because I mean, we're close. Because I
mean, the thing is that it looks 3d now. So it's it looks
substantially better than anything that they could have
done at the time of Symphony of the Night. But the thing is
that Symphony of the Night, you're thinking about in terms
of PS one aesthetics. And yeah, Symphony of the Night was
impressive for a PS one.
No, I'm thinking of it in terms of if you look at both right
now, Symphony of the Night looks fucking great. And that game
looks like shit. Because that game has this goofy fucking 2.5d
shitty graphics, where the characters look floaty as fuck.
And there's no like, there's not enough frames to the animation
to have that satisfying line.
Hang on. That's, that's, it's, it's kind of irrelevant how, how
pretty the game looks because you just won't fund it. But what's
important about the situation is whether or not what they're
doing is deceptive or is like
not that it's deceptive, but you know, here's what bothers me
about both of these cases, specifically with why I think
they got funded, right? Because it's, it's nostalgia. It's one
is a guy who's saying who's saying I created Castlevania
Symphony of the Night, you guys all love that game. They won't
let me make another one. So help me make another one. And then
this other guy, KG Nefune, like I made Mega Man, you all love
Mega Man, they won't let me make another one, help me make
another one. But like, why are they not able to make another
one?
The profound. Okay, so there's a difference.
Capcom's a piece of shit.
Capcom's a piece of shit. Konami is an enormous piece of
shit. Konami is the biggest piece of shit in the world. And
they will literally do stuff not to make money, just despite
the people who work for them. But the difference, the difference
between KG Nefune and Koji Igarashi, Ega, Ega. Yeah, that's
right, Egarashi. Koji Igarashi is that Inafune is a producer,
whereas Igarashi is actually a game designer. And that's what I
think the key difference between those campaigns is because
what I'm getting is staying with Mighty Number nine was, I have
a game idea, I'm going to take your money and hire another
company to make it for me, which is basically like the grown up
million dollar version of that guy in game design chat rooms who
says he's the ideas guy.
My favorite guy.
Here's what I'm getting at, though.
That guy's got it all figured out, man.
Castlevania Symphony of the Night. That game is is legendary.
But Igarashi then made like eight more games that were the
exact same fucking thing.
And they're great.
I love every single one of them.
Dawn of Sorrow.
I already have so many fucking good best, best one.
Dawn of Sorrow's best Castlevania.
How do you guys all play the last DS game?
Did you make it that far?
Was that Order of Ecclesia?
Because that was a great game.
Yeah, that was a great game.
I played every single one since Castlevania of the Night.
Was Ecclesia the one with the paintings?
Because the paintings one was fucking cool.
No, that was that was Portrait of Ruin.
Portrait of Ruin, right?
That was so good.
I'm telling you, dude, they were all good up to Order of Ecclesia.
Well, how about Mega Man?
Do you know anybody who played every Mega Man game?
Because that's the thing.
They made a ton in both of these cases.
Both of these are franchises that they were not performing as well
by the end of their life.
You know, these are games that were selling less and less
that were getting lower and lower metacritic scores, you know.
And like so when when the creators come back and are like,
hey, remember me?
I made Symphony of the Night.
I'm thinking, yeah, but you also made all those other games
that you're not mentioning that no one cares about as much as Symphony of the Night.
Or, hey, I made Mega Man.
And I'm like, yeah, but they made 10 Mega Mans.
And by Mega Man 10, no one was buying it anymore.
You know, that's why they're not making Mega Man.
I didn't speak to market forces about Castlevania,
but I will say that Ecclesia was a great game.
And if they just made the more in that spirit,
then we would have some great games.
I think that Konami just chose not to for whatever reason.
Konami chooses like Konami just straight up is a shitty company.
Like this is this is this is like a cannon fact.
They have no idea what they are.
Yeah, they have no idea what the market wants, right?
They like they are there's there's a lot of writing out there about how shit.
Konami, they they are their their solution to continuing
Metal Gear Solid without without
Hideo Kojima involved.
Yeah, why am I having so much trouble remembering Japanese names today?
Anyway, their solution to continuing MGS without Kojima involved
is fucking Call of Duty Zombies, like not even anything above that.
It's just Call of Duty Zombies in in a parallel universe to Metal Gear to present
to present like a good and bad side of this.
And like why I think it's working,
but also why I think a lot of people are getting disappointed
is because I think that what's great about Kickstarter
is it allows those people who do still care to give like more money
than they could have given to just buying the game.
You know, like most people think of it in terms of I bought this game.
It was twenty five dollars.
But even if I love it more than every other game I've ever bought,
it's still you know, it's it's a game.
It's twenty five dollars.
But if you're someone who actually feels that strongly about it
and like what's great about Kickstarter and Patreon is you can just throw
as much money as it as you feel, you know.
And I think that's something that's very powerful
and it's becoming more and more apparent that people can do that when like
one of my favorite Vati video videos is where he just shows that he's bought
Dark Souls like six times, like every time he just feels a swell of emotion
about how much he loves Dark Souls, he buys it again, you know.
And I'm like, that's awesome because if if these games are being made
for just that niche audience and that niche audience felt so strongly about it
that they're willing to just give whatever it takes, then like cool.
But I think that once these games escape
because of the fact that, you know, a big deal is made about it
because it's a Kickstarter and all that and and everyone's like, yeah,
I remember Symphony of the Night and then they play the game
and they're going to be like, oh, this isn't, you know,
this isn't the best game ever made like I thought it was going to be
because you raised so much money for a Kickstarter and I thought of Symphony of the Night.
And it's like, yeah, but you should have been expecting
like Order of Ecclesia or like the later games are the ones that, you know,
the people who still care about this one, you know, the amount of money
that they raised for the amount of money that they raised for a Kickstarter
is a fraction of the budget of like a triple A video game.
Like even even the biggest kick starters out there are still like.
They're they're huge budgets for.
Didn't Shenmue three like break every record
and that was only like a tenth of the total cost or something that it needed
to be like Shenmue three could only exist on Kickstarter
because Sony was like, OK, we will pony up ten times as much money
as what people are putting into this Kickstarter because the Kickstarter shows
a market willingness to engage with the product.
But like the thing with bloodstained that I think is good compared to.
Mighty number nine, there were never not Mega Man like games on the market.
You know, like like Shovel Knight is a much better Mega Man game.
Then then Mighty number nine is there are tons of people
making Mega Man like games.
There are tons of people making Metroidvania games, too,
but nothing that is like Castlevania.
Watch out, we got some people who are going to get triggered by that word.
Well, all right, I mean, I'll go to that.
But I think but I think so much of what's integral
to what makes those Castlevania games fun, the Egavania games
was the production values, the spirits are so great.
And the the the the hit sparks and flashes as as a Egoraptor put it, you know,
when he was he was talking about how the Egavania games
don't have the same like depth of control and absolutely godly animation.
The I mean, not the animation, but the fucking character art
that was fucking shat on for Dawn of Sorrow and Portrait of Ruin.
I'm still mad about it.
But at least they fix it for at least yeah.
Oh, yeah, they are there was shit.
But but like I just think that people aren't realizing that
like you cannot fund them just making you your favorite game again.
You know, no, you're not going to be that way.
You're never going to you when you buy Metal Gear Solid 5,
the money gets evenly split between Konami's like slot machine division
and the game division. They don't give a shit. No.
You're never going to just crowd fund
like the same best game you played before unless it's, you know, it like if.
OK, if if Toby Fox came out with a Kickstarter,
like we could expect that it might be a game that's as good as Undertale
because Undertale was a Kickstarter game.
It was always for $10,000. Right.
But but but Toby Fox doesn't know.
No, but Toby Fox doesn't have to kickstart
Undertale to probably not because well, not anymore.
Not any more. Toby Fox is actually a millionaire now.
Right. Well, I mean, OK.
And that's something to keep in mind.
Like, like I put I put some money in.
But that's from sales of a fantastic.
Yes, exactly. He deserves it.
And I deserve some money because that's original content.
And original content is what deserves money.
Not. Yeah. Shut the fuck up.
I agree. I agree, Jeff.
I couldn't agree more. You've been debunked here by the memebusters.
Once again, Digi.
Anyway, I put money into that game indivisible.
Right. Because of the fact that it's the same people who did Skullgirls.
I'm so I'm so I'm so lacking in things to say this episode.
I got a chip in and say the indivisible
Kickstarter looked like fucking garbage.
Oh, I was so pretty.
I'm not necessarily convinced that it's going to play the demo.
It fucking sucked.
It wasn't great. The demo was not good, but it also was a prototype.
It was a prototype. It was a process.
I was a big naysayer, too. I don't know.
It happened. And now I'm saying whatever.
Like, it's not a huge difference.
But they released it as a fucking teaser for this is what our game
is going to be like. And it was at least as like a product prototype.
Like what you would do if you were like, you know, when you have a building,
you're going to build and you build a little scale model of it to show people
this is what the building will look like. That's what a prototype is.
That's why they called it that.
Yeah. And it wasn't a demo.
And it is. It's it's like you're in Zoolander right now, Ben.
Like like with the with the music, you know, the school for ants.
You're like, this is how are they going to play this game?
How do you judge this game? It's not even finished yet.
It's got it's only a beta. No, no, no.
It's accurately judge what it's.
No, no, Ben, Ben want to kind of let just just a sec, Ben.
Prototype is not a beta.
A prototype is not an alpha.
A prototype. I don't care.
Where did you use? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm showcasing what it was.
No, it is not.
Ben, it's it's a. No, it is not a prototype.
Ben, Ben, Ben, can we please clarify exactly
what your complaint is about the game that it wasn't fun and it was bad just it
just a sec okay just a sec Ben yeah right a prototype is not any of the code
that will go into the final game at all it is are you telling me that the yes I
am telling you type that I played there's no resemblance at all to the game
that I don't answer that that's a trap the prototype that you played is a
testing bed for things that they will use in the final code the thing is when
you make a video game nothing that you fucking put into the prototype goes into
the final game except for maybe art assets in the same way as if you drew a
bunch of shitty concept art that was just like napkin concept art for a comic
that you want to work on and then you did the comic later and somebody saw that
napkin and was like well this comic looks like fucking garbage I'm not gonna
read it that's what you're doing look Jeff don't that's what you're doing me for
one thing and for second thing the fact that they included this prototype with
their Kickstarter means that they deemed it representative of their product and
it was bad I took the prototype to be that they were saying hey this is
generally what our game is going to play and look and feel like if that's your
thing and donate you know not that it's going to literally be this that it's you
know here's what the mechanics are like so because it's kind of hard to describe
on paper just by saying yeah it's super Metroid I didn't alchemy profile I didn't
like them yeah I didn't like them again can we at least agree can we at least
agree that it is reasonable for Ben to come to a negative impression of the
game based on the prototype and not be interested I don't think that's
unreasonable I just think that it would be unreasonable to think that the final
product will be reflective of okay but the case then what is even really the
use of it if it like if you can just with this argument then what's the point
prototype is the same point as the or is the same purpose as concept art on a
Kickstarter again it's we this is the idea that we're trying to go for this is
the sort of thing that we will be doing but we will have the game I have
to have to raise this point now exactly what what all right but what is the
difference at this point between a criticism of bull shots and a criticism
of a game that may play because they called it a prototype exactly they call it
unfinished they call it unfinished gameplay footage in their advertisements
when they do you know yeah but this wasn't an advertisement for the game it's a
prototype similar if it wasn't an advertisement what the fuck was it it's
a fucking prototype it's a proof it's something to show to investors you're
paying for a kickstarter you're an investor the whole if the information is
useless why included the information accurate it's fair to be judged either
way you lose and I know Nate it's simple it's fucking simple okay all right it's
a prototype it is not an advertisement for the game but they are putting it out
there as part of their Kickstarter campaign to show that they are being
open with their contributors in the same way that they would be open with
investors which is a good strategy for a Kickstarter okay but if I'm so well it
was a bad strategy for me because I played it all right there you go fair
enough Ben but if I play it and I just if I was wrong that it got funded and I
hate it all right hang on if I play it and I really like it and I give money
and then I get the game of the end and it has lost the qualities that I liked
initially I mean who's who's gonna take responsibility for that that seems like
a reasonable I think the fact that they literally said this is a prototype that
in no way resembles the final how does that put it on the donor to literally
say to the donor this is not what you're getting so please don't why this is what
you're not what you're getting then what is the use of showing it is to a
certain extent what you're getting it's a matter of degrees it's a matter of
degrees I think I think there's a lot you want to answer if do you think that
it would have been better if all the Kickstarter said was okay here's how it
works basically the the triangle button makes this character attack and the
square button makes this character attack you'll totally get it once you
know once the game's out you'll totally get what we're talking about but just
trust us it makes sense you know so so yeah so just put money in or would it be
better to just say look okay here's like the controls you know look at it here it
is here's like you know jump around a little bit you like the feel of that
okay that's basically what this is gonna be that's what a prototype I see what
you're saying and I agree that I don't hate the idea of a prototype to introduce
people to the gameplay but when you kind of when you have this concern of like
this is prototype footage or this is a prototype gameplay you can't expect this
to necessarily be the end result then I just wonder like there's going to be some
disconnect between people who liked what was there initially and the things that
they end up with in the end and I just think that that's kind of causing a
potential problem that's that's all and I think it's a nuance I think it's a
nuanced issue you know caveat mentor buyer beware if you can't figure out from
the fact that they said it's a prototype that it might not be the same game then
you might be literally retarded and a human idiot well you know I just think
that it's it takes you're right you know you have to think about it that's
true money if you aren't certain you like I gave money to it because of the
fact that I like skull girls and skull girls was a Kickstarter project I and
the ideas behind it are promising I love the character designers work it's the
kind of thing she's the best I it's a guy I it's a girl we're talking about
there's a guy what there's not drawn by the guy who did the art for you and I
talked about this there I was familiar with the girl who was like the lead
animator yeah but I think that's a distinct person from the character
designer yeah yeah I want to go on a date I'm available but the designer is
Alex who's a guy I met him he signed a copy of his art book for me so well
tell him to let me meet his girlfriend anyways you know I just I see it as
this is a project that is of a scale that makes sense on Kickstarter and like I
know I kind of feel like I know what I'm getting whereas with something like a
like a ukulele for instance where like I know that everyone really hopes that
hey it's the old Rareware boys these are the people who gave us Banjo-Kazooie but
Banjo-Kazooie was a triple-a game and I don't think it's good like even if it is
a good game it's not gonna be as good as Banjo-Kazooie it's just that's
I think it's distinctly possible that it could be again I think it's
distinctly possible that it could be because the thing about the thing about
Banjo-Kazooie is that that game as much as the aesthetics are important in a
Rareware game the most important thing in a Rareware game is juice and I guess
okay so juices juices a slang term for game feel right if you get if you get
the juice right watch Mark Brown game makers toolkit he talks about that in a
video I got a brown for I don't see any reason why it couldn't be as good as
Banjo-Kazooie yeah it could be if it's a different like if there's something
different about it but if it's literally just trying to be Banjo-Kazooie then
even if it was like mechanically identical it won't have as much polish in
the graphics or the animations no no but it's not no way it'll be as good it's
not gonna be mechanically identical their whole idea like their whole thing
that they're selling it as like Banjo-Kazooie is that it's a a open-world
character platformer where you have two characters who work in concert to do
different moves instead of one and you know what sucks about this whole thing
I'm sorry your finisher thought and yeah they're yeah well I mean that was
basically it I was just gonna say that like like a got a bat on the head of a
chameleon yeah is a very different mechanically carer character that is a
very different mechanical character from a bear with a bird in the backpack I
think well let me see it might be exactly the same intentionally you know
maybe the beta that they put out or the alpha or whatever stage they're at right
now does show like a lot of different moves and the moves the moveset for the
character is very very different like there's a lot of gliding and I mean it's
possible if it is if it is a more unique game whereas opposed to like how you
know like the Castlevania thing and the the mighty number nine thing are like
just basically exactly the same but mighty number nine had dashing you idiot
so did Mega Man X not change the game actually Mega Man X as shown in your
Raptors sequel it is dashing changed everything in Mega Man X so so it's the
same you know if you're just gonna make but that X was good so like yeah well
I'm just saying like you know mighty number nine and that Castlevania game by
virtue of trying to be the exact same thing and this is a you know I'm making
assumptions here I mean not about mine right now and everyone knows that was it
but like about the you know the the Castlevania game if if it tries to be the
exact same thing as Symphony of the Night then just by the fact that they
don't have you know the same amounts of or quality of people working on it means
it will not be as good a Symphony of the Night you know even if it is good and
well if you could lately is like mechanically different enough and
inventive enough it could be better and hell even if they just modernize the
fucking live system I'll probably beat it and I couldn't I could not beat
Banjo-Kazooie because the live system pissed me off so badly and you know what
that brings me to the to the biggest meme that needs to die by the way every
episode of the PCP is a continuing extension of the meme that needs to die
it's like we're in Star Trek the next generation where the test never ended for
humanity from episode one but what the biggest problem is capitalism it's the
fact that we have to do things to make money to live and you can't just make
art for its own sake you have to make art profitable you have to do things so
that you can live when are we gonna fucking get our shit together and
invent whatever the fuck things it is that make not communism no I ain't no
fucking pinko don't you look at me with that pink eye you piece of shit just say
you're talking about the automatic star Trek we need those things that make
everything you need we need to no longer worry about having to survive by if we
have those if it if we that's exactly right if we have those if once like my
little pony but once once we live close scarcity we are gonna be in a
communist world or something where I know I'm not a socialist yeah socialist
world honestly we'll need a new we'll need a new paradigm where what isn't a
whole different but is viewed but but like the yeah the thing is yeah that's
right that's right cuz capitalism only functions as long as the supply of food
is lower than the demand for labor and at like we don't even need to have food
synthesizers to get past that point we're at the point where we can automate
all farming we're at the point where we can automate all fucking food delivery
and we're close to the point where we can automate building shelter which is
the three necessities that people need at this point the only forgot smashing
puss my dog no that's that's that's what I'm getting to the puss smashing the
thing is the thing is the thing is at the point when we reach that the there's
gonna be four necessary sectors one of which we shouldn't be we shouldn't be
part of capitalism in the first place which is medicine medicine should just
be right right everybody one of which is pornography smash and puss one of
which okay sure is art and one of which is managing money and if we can just
figure out a way to get the people who fuck good and the people who make art
good to do that for the public good cuz they enjoy it and just give them food
to be happy then we could get rid of the fuckers whose only job is moving money
around for other people yeah we can get rid of fucking money and then we're
done be that would be great and but by the way while we're talking about
Star Trek there's oh there's only one issue with this and it's that there's
this one great episode of the next generation where some some guys like
from like the 21st century or like a 22nd or whatever where capitalism still
existed wake up and like Picard has a talk with one of them and there was this
one guy who was a rich man and he's like Picard I would like to see my accounts
from my various banking institutions and know how my finances have been doing in
the 300 years I've been asleep or whatever and Picard's like well buddy
things don't work that way anymore money doesn't exist so you have no more
influence over the world than anybody else around you and this guy is very
disturbed to hear that not because he's worried about his personal safety or
getting all the food you want those things are available to everyone just as
a right of being alive in the Federation but what he's concerned about is that he
no longer has power and control over his destiny in the way that he once had and
you know it's it's just a fascinating thing to think that even when you can
eliminate all the bare essentials we still theoretically in Star Trek they
kind of figured this out but we might theoretically still have this urge to
just rule over each other and kill and kill and rape our own butts I mean I mean
if we want to get pretentious you know it's the will to power you know I read
that buddy is that actually in Zeno saga I don't know yeah no all of the Zeno
like Zeno saga and Zeno gears all of those are loosely based on it's so
fucking weird yeah anyway the will to power is like a separate part of like
human consciousness and that is yeah but that's like something we can move past
if we just agree to not be fucking asshole yeah you know that that's the
thing to in Picard's you know world like in the 24th century with Picard like
they had pretty much all gotten over that most most humans had whereas this guy
was a relic from the past which is why he was still kind of driven by this urge
that had been weeded out of society so I don't like even in Star Trek they had
fixed you know if you've seen Star Trek beyond no I have not so start Star Trek
beyond is great it was written by Simon Pegg who actually gets Star Trek so it's
not like the previous two Star Trek movies where it's that's what I've heard
that's what I've heard and the villain is a guy who this is kind of a spoiler
let's just say everybody the core the core conflict of Star Trek beyond is
about the Federation ideals versus warlike pre-Federation ideals that's the
most interesting kind of conflict and the the idea that the like the Federation
I mean if we if we want to talk about truly great visionaries we can talk
about how Matt Pat from Game Theory did that theory about how the Federation is
fascist which is very incorrect that's not true at all but there is a
restriction of freedom when you don't have a capitalist system that's that's
just yeah like this of course there's going to be compromises no matter what
system you put in place even capitalism has I mean there's the basic you know
rules you your your right to extend your fist ends at my nose you know all that
all that kind of shit and and yeah I mean like capitalism has like like we
don't have pure capitalism we have rules against monopolies because it's super
obvious that monopolies make capitalism stop by the way what is to those who
aren't aware what is the most successful and popular program in American
history Medicare which is a socialist program so it's not like yeah you know
we got other shit and you want to know what else people really fucking like a
lot fired apartments police not true sometimes we've got we got it what are
we doing the crowdfunding yeah crowdfunding is a let's bring this back
crowdfunding is a stopgap between capitalism and the socialist utopia that
our Lord and Savior Bernie Sanders will eventually bring us into and Gene
Roddenberry theorized about all that good stuff yeah all right I can't hear
anybody anymore well I'm old I'm spent like a lover on a hot summer's Eve all
right I guess that's it we end on that note all right thanks for listening
everybody thanks soon buddy Jesse give us a singer go on the Zinger Jesse what
give me money everybody give me more money idiots were talking about for the
last hour they were all screaming at each other I mentally checked out like
45 minutes ago I've been arguing with some guy in a comment section this whole
time I'm not even a I hate all these guys I would rather argue with people in
comment sections then whatever asinine conversation just happened for the last
six hours but anyways wound me money I'm sorry that was too far you know what I
went too far yeah you did I wounded you and I apologize thank you and also go
to patreon.com slash best guy ever to give your money to the only place where
it'll count so I can leave my job and be an internet hero like the rest of these
assholes I'm the only one who really needs it people forget them they're
already living the dream no go to patreon.com slash mother's basement I'm
right now $1 away from a corporate shell people he's the worst capitalist of
them all don't trust him but you're $1 away from what I'm $1 away from having
$1,700 and it's driving my OCD crazy $1,700 all right fuck you all right we're
done thanks for this everybody we'll see you next time
I am an asshole I am a stupid I've got a deadline don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong with me I'm supposed to be
making money I'm supposed to be creating funny
think that the people gladly will pay for artistic genius that's what they came
for instead I'm tweeting hashtag repeating that's why there's no
yeah it's quite the burden it's a hard knock life being a genius