Hello everyone and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Hello, this is us. We have a special
guest today, Gamers Tavern. Here he is. Hello. Gamers Tavern is a reviewer of video games and
does Let's Plays, which is the topic of today's podcast. And with me, Hippocrit, we have other
members of the show who are usually here. You're an expert at this. I really am good, aren't I?
He knows what he's doing. Where'd you get that green fucking trash, Ben?
Yes. And here we have Munchy Jones. Welcome to the only podcast on the internet where one
six of its hosts consistently has severe, mold-induced respiratory issues. I cannot breathe
right now. There's too much mold in my room. Oh no. We have Tom Oliver. Hello. I have risen from
the grave to bring you more fantastic ramblings. We have Best Guy Ever. It's about that time,
everybody. And we have Ben Sainte. Discord, I'm hallowed at the moon. In the middle of the summer
afternoon. Discord, remember whatever we do. Take my pain away. All right. Now, I guess I should have
left Gamers Tavern at the end. I was going to reintroduce him. Gamers Tavern is here.
Hey. There he is. Yeah. Yeah, we're happy to have you. I'd just like to say right off the bat
that I and a bunch of us here are longtime fans of Gamers Tavern, a tragically underappreciated
channel who back in the day was putting out some really great, some really enjoyable Let's Play
content. There can be no doubt. Link in the description to his channel. I'm very flattered
to hear that. We, I think at the very least, I think Jesse originally was the guy who found
your content first. Is that accurate, Kim? Was it? I think it was me or Jesse who found his content
and we shared it amongst ourselves and we said, this guy has got the best dry comedy. I think
that's why you call it dry comedy. Like Let's Plays of just the, it was so funny. We were
laughing the whole time. It was great. We loved your videos so much and we subscribed and we watched
your podcasts and we love Gamers Tavern, we say it. I would like to throw out that I,
unequivocally, wish to preemptively crown Gamers Tavern the king of Let's Plays. I have not seen
one that's better. It is, you guys, you have to watch, please go watch some of his videos,
like his Sonic Let's Plays or any of them, the Rocket Knight Adventures. We got Rocket Knight,
Kirby, Sonic. There's more. I'm blanking. There's a whole bunch. Listeners, just look inside your
heart and think, do you want unscripted podcasts like a banter between two unqualified, unprofessional
internet hacks long since their prime, like the Digi Pros or the Game Grumps? Or do you want
masterfully paced, beautifully executed, pure art Let's Plays such as the Gamers Tavern offers?
The puns are off the charts and so is the quality. Mr. Tavern, I'm curious. How would you describe?
That's his official name and title. Please be respectful, everyone. Mr. Tavern,
how would you describe your Let's Plays style?
I don't really know. I just think up of things that are funny and I just try to do them.
I've been dying to ask you for years at years at this point.
I think I know what you're going to ask, because I was just about to ask the same thing.
Were you going to ask him whether he...
Whether he does them right as he's doing it or if he goes back over and dubs over them.
Or is it dubbed in after? Because it's so tight, your lines, the stuff you say is so tight,
one after another, and it's really funny. I feel like it has to be scripted.
It has to be scripted. It has to be put in afterwards.
Well, you're correct on both of those accounts. It's post commentary, so it's done after I record
the gameplay footage, and it is scripted. Okay. Fantastic.
And as we've established in the pre-show, by the way, Ben St. D value is all scripted content.
Any rehearsed media is invalid and worthless artistically, so that's the major problems here.
I mean, it's less. It's made less. It's a good thing that the champion,
heralded comic, never had a script at all. The champion was all improv.
You know, my whole life is just a big improv. That's true. That's true. A tanking improv session
one day at a time. If I could be that funny without a script, I certainly would.
Of course. I just want to share. I don't know if you remember Mr. T for short.
But there was one occasion where I hooked up at the old house I lived in with a bunch of friends.
I hooked up a projector, and we projected your Let's Plays onto the wall, and we all hung out
for the evening and just relaxed to the sounds of Gamer's Tavern. It was really great. And I
tweeted a picture of it. Yeah, actually, I remember seeing that. I saw that on Twitter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That was me. That was pretty cool. That's awesome. Thanks.
You know what's great about your content? Okay, so guys, in case we haven't made it clear,
the whole shtick that Gamer's Tavern does is he's got his Let's Play footage that he's playing
games, and he just mercilessly, unyieldingly, one after another after another, just lumbasts you
with puns, unceasing, unpityless, or pitpityless, merciless puns. Well, I mean, it's not all puns,
but there are quite a few. It's not all puns, but some of it is just commentary on the game,
which is also cool. Sometimes. What I love about it is that it's not like completely,
like there's no, there is like comedic timing and pauses in between the jokes that is just long
enough for it to feel like a realistic pause, which is why people, like why we were wondering
whether you do it off the cuff, because there's like, you know, you're playing the game and there's
a pause that is like, it's not so long that it's like nothing is happening, but it's long enough
to make it everything really funny and just like, and not like you just, you know, you just sit back
and you just let it all wash over you. It's almost sort of anti-humor in the sense that like, the
pauses are just long enough to give you room to breathe in between the puns, at least for my
favorite of your videos, I always think of like the sonic ones, when you're on like the ice levels,
ice to meet you. Oh, it's snow, snow problem.
But it's like, it's like an Andy Warhol, if I, is that, wait, is that the right, who's the guy
who, uh, who's the guy who Jim Carrey played? Uh, uh, Jim Carrey. Andy Kaufman. Andy Kaufman,
that's the one. It's almost Andy Kaufman style of like anti-humor, because the puns are super,
you know, they're just incredibly obvious, but it's the way that they're done just over and over
and over again, just builds up this like, it doesn't start, it's a slow build until eventually you
just hit this peak, like this combo of just hilarity after one after another. It's such an
experience. I don't know what it is, sometimes with your delivery, it sounds almost like,
like you'll make a pun, and then like the one I remember is, I think I remember you made a bunch
of cloud puns about when, um, when Kirby is walking around in the clouds, like you'll make a
cloud pun, and then there'll be a pause, and then you'll kind of, you'll come back in with your dry
delivery, and you'll make some more, and it's like, it's, it's like, it's almost like a self-aware kind
of like, well, I made one, I have to make some more, I'm just gonna do it again.
Uh, do you feel that kind of compulsion to just keep going with the theme as long as possible?
Is there, yeah, what's your, what's your thought process as you're coming up with these?
Is it just really just, I'm going to keep doing this as long as it's on screen. I'll just keep
making the joke about clouds or ice or whatever it might be. Uh, yeah, it's something like that.
I mean, uh, to me, I feel like, uh, what's the point of watching it? Let's play anymore if the
commentary isn't funny or interesting. Damn right. Absolutely. So, um, I work really hard to always
have something to say about whatever's on screen or maybe, uh, you know, just jokes or puns or
whatever. So, um, I have to find inspiration somewhere, so I kind of look at what's on screen,
and I try to make puns about it. And then when it's not on screen anymore, I make puns about
whatever else ends up being on screen later. Yeah, and it's, and then sometimes I'll make jokes.
I love the distinction between puns and jokes. Yes. I feel like I'm getting played right now.
I feel like you're on a higher level and you're meming me at this very moment. Like I'm just not,
I don't know, like you're, you're some sort of ancient Egyptian alien pharaoh who understands
things in a higher plane than I do. We've only read about this game of Tavern on pyramid walls
in ancient hieroglyphs, and now we've done the summoning circle. We have him here today. We
can already believe it. It's anonic. Well, uh, I guess ancient manuscripts describes me well,
because, uh, I, uh, I started my website in, in 2002. Whoa. Yeah, we should talk about that.
We should talk about that. That, that's pretty impressive. And I'm actually looking here. Um,
you haven't updated, I think a lot of your Let's Plays in, in a little while, but I'm looking
at your review updates and you put out your Golden Axe Warrior one, uh, what, like three,
four days ago or something, and then like a two weeks or so before that Axe Battler two weeks
before that, um, Golden Axe the Dual. So you, you really churn these things out on your website.
I haven't really read too many of them myself, but, uh, is this more of your passion or this more
of your interest kind of doing the reviews as opposed to the Let's Plays? Well, uh, that's
where I started, you know, I started writing reviews back in 2003. I started a website in 2002
by the first review I published in 2003, which, uh, that's also when I first named the website, uh,
Gamer's Tower. Because before that, I didn't really have a name or design it. Before that,
I was basically like, uh, those all GeoCity sites from the late 90s. That's how it looked like.
Just full of anime gifts, no doubt, I'm sure. Well, actually it was even less than that. It was
basically a black background with red text to make your eyes. Oh, perfect. Yes. The most delicious.
No, I had an old website just like that. So we would have been brothers in arms back in the day.
Gaia online. So I just didn't have the good sense to stop. I kept it going over 15 years.
I'm curious what your professional background is. Do you have any like programming or any,
is your field of work related to this in any kind of capacity?
Yeah, I guess you could say that. I know a little bit of programming. Obviously, I know
web, HTML stuff, CSS and things of that nature. That's cool. That's cool. Well, I mean, okay,
I mean, we've gone pretty in-depth with your content, which obviously we all love. Maybe we
should open up the floor a little bit and just see what we feel about. I mean, I don't know about you
guys, but I kind of want to talk about things like other popular let's plays in comparison to
Gamer's Tavern and why he is vastly superior by every metric. There's a few ways to make a let's
play and true. A bunch of us, I mean, a bunch of us have done it. So we've got we've got insights.
The legendary T-Bat plays cannot be questioned as the pinnacle of all let's plays. It's just that
they've retired. I think I've told this before, but at the peak of all of that, my involvement
with the horseshoe crew and my, you know, my whole deal with those bastards, I tried watching
T-Bat plays and I couldn't get past one episode and I quit halfway through because it was the
worst video I've ever seen in my life and I was so bewildered and disappointed that I couldn't
even stand looking at my computer anymore and I had to go for a walk. I couldn't believe what I had
witnessed heroes had let you down. Yeah. Yeah. Literally exactly. I couldn't believe that Phantom
Orcheg did this. Like what happened? Like, like, do they have a ghostwriter for the normal videos?
Like, what is happening? Yes. Geez. I mean, I didn't think it was bad. Hey, remember the first
fighting game? Remember the one we did the fighting game? Like the very first episode we did that was
on our main channel that eventually we poured it over as like the first episode of T-Bat plays.
Yeah. That was that. That was that sick like fighting is magic or whatever. And that when I
put a bunch of like edits in and was pretty sick. Yeah. That one was good. That was a quality,
quality thing. I mean, maybe I'm crazy, but I enjoyed T-Bat plays Equestria Bound. Yeah.
Over a hundred episodes. Over a hundred. We were having more time. I mean, yeah.
I guess that's one way to phrase it. No, that's like, it's kind of weird that there is so much
content that I have not consumed because I'm normally the content minor. I mined as much
content as I produced Bitcoin on my computer. But I don't like, was there anything worth listening to?
Let me see that's the thing. The Let's Play is coming a few camps and T-Bat plays is probably,
is easily the champion of the terrible Let's Play camp. It is not good. It is like we simply
describe the things happening on screen and like talk about, you know, it's boring. I think that
the true nadir of T-Bat plays was T-Bat plays super lesbian horse RPG because no, no, I liked that.
I thought it was terrible because the game was really text heavy and a lot of what we did was
just reading text on the screen. At least we did voices. We did some voices, but like how long
do those stay interesting really? How long will a funny voice buoy a piece of content? I will tell
you this though. I'll tell you this though, Ben. The only video I ever go back to watch from T-Bat
plays is the finale of horseshoe whatever. Super lesbian horse RPG. When the Anamanaguchi song
drops at the end and it's us reacting to it, that was good. Do you actually go back and revisit that?
That one moment, yes I do. I have several times. I have not, but that's interesting.
Maybe I will. Maybe I will just for old time sake. It's always funny to see what kind of weird,
like not important, not grandiose videos that we all secretly have in infinity before and go back
and listen to from our past. Like that episode, I'm sure does not rake in the view. I'm sure it's
not that popular or that like remembered or celebrated. There's just something about that
will just stick out in your mind forever. I have a lot of views like that from the past that don't
like like Measurement Man. I fucking love Measurement Man. Measurement Man is my
shit. I love that video. I forget which episode it's from, but the moment, I mean,
I put this in one of my videos because I loved it so much, but it's when,
fuck, it's the dude, what the freak? Like that one moment of duties is so great.
Well, okay. What do you guys think of the Game Grumps? Game Grumps. You get to say something
first. Well, I'll talk about Game Grumps. The Game Grumps introduced me to the idea that Let's
Plays were not terrible. Because before that, I had only heard of the idea of like Let's Plays.
I'd seen things on the side of YouTube. We all used to try some quite a bit. Let's play this.
Why would I want to watch someone else play a game? And Game Grumps, they were just really funny
from day one. I saw the video from Egoraptor linking to it, and I clicked on it, and it was great.
And to this day, I think there hasn't been like a daily upload Let's Play show that is good.
Aaron! We got a certain nation just for the white race, Aaron!
Oh my gosh. That's John for you. Yeah, I guess so.
Gamestaven, do you have any experience watching other Let's Plays?
Loads. I've been watching them since 2008 or 2007 or something like that.
But I kind of lost interest in watching them because once the novelty wore off,
kind of found them boring. But there is one guy in particular I like still,
one Let's Spare. And if you like my stuff, you'll probably like his stuff a lot as well.
His name is Karma Jolt. I don't know if you've heard of him. Probably not,
because he only has like 500 subscribers. He's really funny and he does the same scripted style
of commentary that I do. How do you spell that? He's been doing it before. Karma Jolt is just,
you know, the word karma and Jolt. Oh, Karma Jolt, okay. Oh god, his last video one month ago
is channel update moving on. Oh no, we caught him at the tail end. Rest in peace. He's not quitting,
he's just on a break. Oh, okay, cool. Glad to hear it. He kind of updates infrequently,
kind of like me. Actually, it's more accurate to say that I'm kind of like him because he came
before I did. Oh, he must be old school. I mean, I'm seeing like 30 videos uploaded over the course
of a month. Yeah, okay. Well, recently he's been updating more frequently. He sure has.
And his recent videos aren't scripted. Okay. Oh, so Ben would like them is what you're saying.
Yeah, they'd be vastly superior. Just in principle. I would just like to mention for the crowd,
so I can be, I can be vaunted and approved of in the comment section. I will wear on my badge,
much like call cost victims wore the Golden Juden star on their shirt proudly. I will wear the badge
of being one of the few people who found Gingrumps through John first and I clicked on
his link from his channel. Talk about GamerCred. Talk about GamerCred. I know. I was talking to John
before and I was like, John knows Egoraptor? Egoraptor like has friends and is like a person
that like exists in the physical material world. I'm losing my shit and I couldn't believe that
my rinky dink god, god king, John Tron knew Egoraptor. It obliterated my perception of reality.
It was incredible. How big was John at that time? Was he like a 500,000 kind of guy or something?
No, no. It was like, yeah, 10,000, 50,000 sort of. Geez. When he made Gingrumps, he was that size?
He was not big. He got big from Reddit and it was like, you know, a big front page post and he got
like a couple thousand subscribers from, well not a couple, like maybe 10,000, 20,000 subscribers.
And Gingrumps is what like five years old now or something? Yep. Damn. What do you know?
The thing with like, let's plays, I feel like there's certain types and they usually fall
into two main categories. One is about the game and the other is about the personalities.
And you can sort of like mix and match like a slider. Like are you talking about the game more
and or are you just playing a game and not even talking? You're just talking and it's got
gameplay in the background. T-Bap, I feel like was talking about the game, which is why I didn't
find it that interesting because I would rather listen to you talk about cool things. And then
things like Digi's Let's Plays were mostly not about the game at all. Victor would be playing
something. Digi's were way better. And he was just talking about stuff and he even called it a podcast.
Yeah. And like Gingrumps was about the personalities. But after a certain point,
they run out of stuff to say. They just... Well, a few life things change for those boys and they
had to change. Like for Digi Bros, they had to like, you know, it wasn't just they ran out of
things to say. Oh, no, no, not Digi. I was thinking about Gingrumps. But yeah. Oh, okay. Yeah.
Were you talking about like the Jontron leaving stuff? No, I'm talking about, well, I mean,
at the end of the Jontron era, that it was sort of winding down as well. And then Dan era, as you
call it, it was also sort of like, occasionally, I'll click on a Game Grumps. But most it used
to be I would watch every single episode because they were always really funny bits. But now I
spread out. I started watching Grumps like pretty like a little bit after John left. And I got into
Dan and I listened to a lot of like the early Dan stuff and I really liked it. But yeah, eventually
it came to be like, I feel like we're now like revisiting old topics or we're just talking about
nothing, you know? Yeah. Well, it's just it's been every day for like years at this point. Like,
like human experiences and lives are like a physical, what's the word, like fossil fuel
mine. Like eventually it will all be used up all of your experiences. You all of the reminiscing
you do is like a plus one Bitcoin you are mining and you will eventually run out of life experiences.
That graphics card is going to wear out. Exactly. Exactly. So you're not going to be able to, you
know, fucking survive on that for that long and they've just been talking nonstop every
fucking day for years. Of course, it's just going to become nothing. Makes sense. So like this way
is for like the personality driven Let's Plays to get old because the personality is overexposed
to like the internet, like people just see them over and over and then they run out of,
they run out of like, yeah, you've been hanging around my house for too long, go away, you know,
that sort of feeling. You know, that's why. But then the opposite is when the like it's usually
things like Gamer's Tavern or maybe even like some of Spoonie's early Let's Plays where it's
either like a hybrid or like entirely scripted and talking about the stuff on the screen to the
point where it can't really get old because as long as it's funny, you know, as long as you
find a way to continue to make it funny, you can keep doing this forever.
Yeah, it's kind of like, I know the Game Grumps at certain points and maybe still we're taking
like comedy classes, like professional actual, you know, like acting classes and that kind of
stuff. So like it seems like they're, by doing that, they're kind of preparing themselves for
like a long term, actually delivering like a show and working on like, what's the running for,
Extemporaneous Comedy or whatever it is. Yeah, Improv. Improv, exactly. Improv. And then like
in the same way, like Gamer's Tavern for here, for example, like the way he like, you know,
writes scripts and stuff, and I suppose it's a little bit different than just like live Let's Plays
or anything. But he's also, he's like generating content with which he, you know, will stick in
his episodes versus when you, as much was saying, if you just talk about your life, you will definitely
at some point just run out of interesting things to say, which I think is a lot of people have
experienced that with Game Grumps. If you do that for long enough, and if you do Let's Plays,
you know, a lot of the time, like a Game Grumps does, then your life becomes telling stories
about your life. So once you tell your eventual life story, and then you get to the part where
you start Let's Play, where you're gonna say like, oh, remember the story that I told? Wasn't it funny
how I told that? Remember that one time we played a game on the show? Wasn't that crazy? That will
be your story. Yeah. Yeah. And then it just gets less and less like interesting because it's less
and less like fresh new information for people. So I think you really got to do something to like,
maybe you just like take a break, I don't know, maybe even for a year, and then just like go live
a life and have experiences. Then I mean, you'll have built up some experiences that you can bring
back and just like dump onto the table again. So that's maybe that's the cycle. Is it maybe it's
inevitable that happened? I feel like that's like a good idea to like make good content is like,
oh, take a break, experience two things from a regular perspective. The problem is like,
you just basically torpedo your entire business during that because like, if you stop for a week,
YouTube will fucking kill you. So like, you have to be on their dick 24 seven or the algorithm
will murder you. Well, what about this is a theoretical business model, like a Game Grumps
style channel, where you have like hosts, maybe kind of cycling in and out of the channel. So
the channel is always putting out content, but the individual contributors have time to go off and
kind of mind Bitcoin. And then you can remove the game entirely and just have it be the people
talking. And then you can, you know, you can cycle through the members. Yeah, yeah, it's kind of
like it's too fancy to actually join. So it'll just be consistent group people is normally
bother show fucking up. Yeah, you know, eventually the hosts just start procrastinating. You know,
it's fucking it's a it's a disaster. It's a disaster. Well, I get it. I would like to bring
up moment depending on depending on how many tomatoes are thrown my way. I'd like to bring up
the shitty juvenile embarrassing that I would even talk about this topic of Game Grumps drama.
Just what happened? I'm the kind of guy I will not be, I will not be, you know,
I won't be shy about this fact. I am the kind of guy who when John, you know, left, I was the kind
of guy was like typing like, like haunted Game Grumps ARG explain explain to me this content
mansion story. This is a good opportunity for me to reveal the truth because John is me and I have
told myself the truth. And here's what happened. John and Aaron, they started Game Grumps and then
he hit Susie didn't he? Huh? He hit Susie. Yeah, he beat Susie to shit. Yeah, she's a zombie now.
John and Aaron started the Game Grumps and they didn't know it was going to be a big thing.
And then it was and then they had to start a they made a joint bank account to have funds go from
that so they could both think. But there's like hints here and there that John, I mean, you know,
Freudian slips, but like he thought of it as his show. So what I think happened, this is all like
out of my brain, is that John wanted to stop Game Grumps because he wanted to work more on
John Tron. He also wanted to go to New York because the continued guys were there and a girl he was
talking to was over there and he wanted to go live with her. And so what John said is like her name.
I love Kim Possible. And then what he did is he said, OK, I want to quit the Game Grumps.
But he didn't just say that he wanted Game Grumps to end. And Aaron was like, well, wait, why can't
we just continue without you? And he's like, well, I don't know. I don't I and it's like there's a
big argument because the John wanted it to be ended. And Aaron wanted to continue without John.
And John was like, fuck you. And he left. And that's why they were angry at each other.
And then Danny was brought in to replace him. And nobody really wanted to talk about it.
Aaron didn't want to make John look like an evil piece of shit. And John didn't want to make Aaron
look like a piece of shit. So they just both kept quiet and it became really awkward. And that's
what I think happened. And then, of course, eventually things eventually warmed up and they,
you know, are talking. And, you know, they were on the Star Wars thing together. So things,
obviously, if Danny was smaller, I could brush my teeth with them.
Well, I was just going to say, he's just like you. That's a good little summary of the whole
thing. I think we now at this point, we pretty much all know prove all the details that I mean,
I still think, you know, Susie, you know, talking sexy time. But no.
Why? Yeah, on top of all that, John was fucking Susie the whole time.
She was always there. But that didn't have anything to do with it.
There's the hot goss I came here for. Indeed. Well, cool. All right. So I mean,
are there any other Let's Players? What about the Yahtzee? Who talked about, people were big
fans of Yahtzee, right? Yahtzee and the, God, there was the Ego.
The insufferable game social media crapcast, right? No. Hang on. God, what was the name of Yahtzee's
Let's Play show that he did with that fuckface Gabe? Oh, was it? I think it was called Let's Drown
Out. That's the one. I'm also a fan of Yahtzee's reviews. Of course, me too. Yeah, I love Yahtzee.
He's great. And I really like Let's Drown Out. And I don't even mind his co-host, Gabe, most of
the time. It's just sometimes I just get the feeling that he's the biggest douchebag and I hate him.
In what way? Is this Gabe with Penny Arcade fame? They'll argue a bunch. Wait,
is that Gabe from Penny Arcade? Is that who that is? No, no, it's an Australian guy.
They'll argue a bunch and Yahtzee will accuse Gabe of waffling. Like, Gabe will say something and
Yahtzee will be like, well, I don't think that's true. And Gabe will be like, well, neither do I,
but da, da, da, da. And Gabe will be like, you're waffling. Like, just out with it,
you're waffling. Gabe will be like, fuck you. I'm not waffling. I'm just saying what I think.
And I always agree with Yahtzee. Gabe is a total waffler. Just like fucking John Kerry. And he'll
just get killed. And he'll talk about how he's studying to be a teacher. It's really important
and relevant to anything that's going on and it never is. I can't fucking stand it.
Did he ever become that teacher? Did he do it? Not to the best of my knowledge.
By the way, I'm looking at the channel right now. The last Let's Drown Out I Can See was
uploaded over a year ago. Oh, wait, wait, no. One, oh wait, yep, a year ago. Yep. Looks like
they stopped. Looks like they stopped. I guess they stopped because Yahtzee moved to America,
I think. He did. That's news to me. He's on our soil. We can track him down. Yahtzee once.
If we're just listing off the people who we watched or do watch currently, I'm in the
class, you know, electrical beast, billion seat, you know, Lyme Pop School, my personal
giants of the industry. Please. You know, I wouldn't be where I am today without watching
Billiam C's incredible spine-cracking Mario Let's Plays. I'm sorry, are you saying Billiam C?
Yeah, you don't know who Billiam C is? I don't think so.
Billiam like William, but with a B? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, okay. Here, here,
Gamerstab, you know who Billiam C is, don't you? Yeah, I do. Yeah, yeah, what do you think about him?
I think he's great, but he doesn't appear to be aware of it.
Yeah. What does that mean? Strapolate on that a little bit?
I know what you mean. I know what you mean, Gamerstab.
You gotta watch Red Supri to find out. Yeah, I was just about to say I watch Red Supri all the
time. I kind of stopped since they started doing like weird Kickstarter videos. It wasn't too into
those, but I love Red Supri. I know about all, you know, shit through there. Red Supri, to my
knowledge, correct me if I'm wrong, Gamerstab, but Red Supri is sort of a, it's a commentary channel
where they take Let's Plays and then they commentate over the Let's Plays, and these
Let's Plays are of dubious quality at best. Are we talking about like the greatest Let's
Play of all time, Dark Side Fill with his How Not to Play, kind of like those? I suppose so. No,
those are commentated. These are, this is like, they're like a Mystery Science Theater 3000-ing
these Let's Plays. Yes. Well, that's kind of, okay, fair enough, fair enough. And the thing
that's interesting about it is I'm fairly certain that one of the co-hosts is the guy who like
invented Let's Play. Yeah, his name is Slow Beef, or I think it was either Slow Beef or
Diabetes that did the first Let's Play. I think it's Slow Beef, I think it's Slow Beef. Yeah,
it was Slow Beef. Well, and so it's interesting to see like this guy who like created this like
weird like cultural worldwide phenomenon looking at like the worst of the worst of his spawn and
ridiculing them extensively. You know, that is a fantastic angle. Is he popular with this series?
Retsu Prey is pretty big. Yeah, yeah, they're pretty big. Okay. I've seen, they don't do actual
Retsu Prey's that much anymore. I'm not sure why. I just realized that Retsu Prey is a joke on Let's
Play. Yeah, that's what it is. Fantastic. I would highly recommend a lot of old ones. My favorite one
is... The Billy MC ones are good. Yeah, Billy MC ones are great. My favorite one is when you're here,
your family. I fucking love that one. These all sound fantastic. I want to watch all of them.
But I think it's time that we crack open the nut I referenced earlier and talk about the
unequivocally greatest Let's Player in the World, with of course the exception of Gamer's Tavern
and the King of Hate and the original Fighting Game Master. And it's Darkseid Phil. Darkseid
fucking Phil. He is the only V-approved YouTuber, the only one. He is incredible. He is a god. Gamer
Staphen, what is your take on Darkseid Phil, if you're familiar with his work? I've heard of him,
but I'm honestly not very familiar with the guy, unfortunately. Okay, fair enough. I mean,
you've been spared a little bit. I'd just like to throw out... Actually, you know what? I won't
say that. Okay, I will say it since I brought it up, but someone just linked me this very morning
saying that for the second time, give. Your creaky haunted house needs to shut up for recording
her podcast. They say Darkseid Phil was caught masturbating on stream for the second time ever.
Okay, that is not real, I don't think, because it was just audio. He could have just
been yawning loudly. So, frankly, I think people are exaggerating with that, but he definitely
did one time. I am not familiar with this phenomenon. How does one even make such a
fault? There's something wrong with your yawns. That's how I yawn. That's how I yawn.
I mean, you know, when you stream like all day, every day, you know, sometimes you make a slip
Yeah, you leave your camera on and you just, you know, just the other day, just the other day,
I had just finished a live stream and, you know, me and The Misses were getting up to some activities
and, you know, I was kind of petrified. I had continued to stream by, you know, but luckily,
I had not, but it's just as easy as forgetting to click one button sometime and there you go.
This is why no one should ever live stream. It's the worst idea in history.
I thought you were going to say no one should associate with women. Concentration camps now,
that's all I'm saying. You know, that's a safe thing too, but...
Darkseid Phil is a legend and it's kind of amazing to watch him. He's gone through so many
ups and downs over his career. He really is a, he's like a slightly, well, okay,
he's honestly significantly more together version of like Christian Weston Chandler,
but like he has his own massive weaknesses as a man. Like he's terrible with money,
he like is not, when he started to get big, like doing Let's Plays and stuff, he just like bought
a big old house and like a new car or something and moved out. I don't know, like to Seattle or
something and just like, and now he's paying for it. Like his girlfriend left him a little while ago.
I don't know exactly what, I don't want to speculate on his life too much. I just want to state the
facts here. The fact are that he overextended himself and continues to bring up how like he
is one of the, he is one of the guys who started like Let's Plays and before it got big and,
you know, continued it getting well. I don't know if he was, it sounds like this Retsu Prey guy is
actually the first, but he was certainly one of the formative people on YouTube doing Let's Plays.
And just to watch his life and to watch him be such a terrible, just like guy kind of in general,
I actually am in no way with like these assholes, the sons of Kojima who are like that whole crowd
that like go, they find like every reason to shit on the guy that I think is just like way beyond
the pale and like not actually fair to him whatsoever. Like I hate when people take it too far,
but the tangible things he has done of just being such an asshole and he tells the story one time
of like what an inconvenience his like girlfriend was for like something like having like a mental
breakdown at work and like making him go like take care of her and stuff. Like it's entirely possible
that she was very inconsiderate at some point in that story, but the way that he told it certainly
did not paint him with any degree of sympathy. And he sounds like a big asshole. So, but just
he's such a character. I really want to dive in and I've been thinking of doing a PCB lecture on
him specifically. So let me know people if that's something that interests you. People really want
that. They've been asking for that. I think they do want it one day. I can't guarantee it for
Radcon through anything, but one day I will have to do it. I did see the down the rabbit hole about
Darkseid Phil. Yes. And my only real exposure to him before that was through the let's have the
how not to play with Dark Souls. And I mean, I don't know how much I don't know how much you can
infer about a guy based on like what he says while he's fucking playing Dark Souls or whatever,
but he was a huge asshole and just the most obnoxious dude. Like especially the way he would
like just he would blame the game. Like his blaming the game is the biggest meme. It is the biggest
meme about Darkseid Phil. It's and the wow, really? You know, when the are you saying that it's not
true? I am. No, no, I'm completely agreeing with you. He blames the game for like the vast majority
of everything that goes wrong when he's playing. See the thing with that is that I like I do it too.
I mean, I blame the game like verbally, but like when I calm down later, I'm like, well, that was
just me fucking up. See, not him, not him. He does not. It's his worldview that like the games
cheat. My only exposure to Darkseid Phil was like knowing vaguely that he is not good at video games
and then watching several Street Fighter Street Fighter Terminancy was in where he kicked ass.
Darkseid Phil has been riding on this wave of being like a super sick, nasty Street Fighter
player like for his entire career and like refuses to play anyone in it. It's it's exactly like
the episode of Seinfeld where Jerry is like gonna race the guys and he like he chooses not to play.
He chooses not to play. So he doesn't lose his title. It's just like that. It's just like and
you know, I honestly, I honestly do not have that much hatred for the guy. He just seems like kind
of a jerk. I actually respect him in a lot of ways. In other ways, I don't, you know, just because he
seems kind of like a jerk. But like, I mean, hey, man, he was out there. He was one of the pioneers
of the Let's Players. He is this guy who realized why don't I just set up my fucking camera behind
me, film the TV that I'm playing games on and upload these full Let's Plays. You know, I
it's that's that's creativity. I don't ironically love camcorder LPs. Like when you can actually
see the screen, it's super comfy and it's super fucking aesthetic. And really honestly grossed
to me. I fucking love camcorder LPs when they're when you and of course, you can actually see
the screen and it's not blinding light. I gotta look up how many Let's Plays Darkseid Phil has
uploaded on his channel. Okay, DSP Gaming has, okay, no, sorry, that's the number of subs. Okay,
I can't check right now, but I think he has like hundreds of thousands of uploads or like the most
out of like anyone in all of YouTube, something like that. It's been doing multiple times a day
for like, since like YouTube was young. Yeah. And we're talking like 10 a day or something like
that for, because he splits up his Let's Plays into so many small individual parts. Let me just
see what he's done today or possibly yesterday. You gotta get those ad dollars, man. You gotta run
an ad on every video. Let me tell you how many videos were uploaded 11 hours ago. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14 videos were uploaded 11 hours ago. And how
about 16 hours ago, you might ask, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11,
12, 13, and then 17 hours ago, 14, 15, 16, hang on, 17, 18, 19, 20. He's uploading. He's uploading.
34 videos yesterday, 34 videos. He's uploading over one video an hour, like one and a half videos
an hour. That's insane. They're all like 10 minutes, you know, snippets of this Let's Play. Just,
wow. Unbelievable. That's like the brute force as sense method right there.
Damn right it is. Is this the like most optimal way to do this? Because all these videos have like
150 views or so. No, it is definitely not. Nobody has the time for that. Even if they're only 10
minutes long each. Yeah. It just feels overwhelming to just click on the next one every so. That's
around the views I get. Yeah, exactly. And I mean, he does put out again so many videos. So like,
I suppose all the views add up to some degree. But like, I'm looking at his videos from like a
while ago, they get like 500 views a piece. So even if you upload 30 views or 30 videos of this
thing, if they each get around 500 videos or 500 views, that's a total of 15,000 views in one day.
And that's not terrible, I guess. But for a guy who's trying to make it is so living,
I mean, that's not, that's not sustainable. I mean, you know what, I'm not here to critique
his business model, really. I'm just here to point out that he is a man of legend, you know,
and I wish him well. I hope he keeps it up. Is that what this is about about wishing him well?
Well, sort of. I don't hate the guy. I don't hate the guy. I want to talk about like,
the whole like, cutting episodes up into 10 minute chunks. I have, I used to do Let's Plays,
and part of the fun, for some reason, was like having my big recording and then splitting it up
into 10 minute chunks, and, and, and like uploading like 10, and like spreading them out to release
scheduled over like one per day. And I don't know, it's just that that was a cool thing. But like,
those videos, if you ever look at my Let's Plays on Gibbon Gaming, the very first ones are like,
I'm the meekest you could ever imagine. Even meeker than, than currently. And it's like,
over the course of the Let's Plays, and then into streams. You, you, like, you can see me grow
into a real person. Yeah, I sound like, I sound like a mouse in the Rayman 2 Let's Plays.
You're like a chiapet, only far less entertaining.
Yeah, yeah, they're not even good. They're never, they've never been good. I kind, I kind of like gave
up the, the, even though I liked splitting episodes up into 10 minute chunks, and, and seeing the
uploads, like, oh yeah, look at all these uploads, because Digi used to say, yeah, I've made like
100 videos this month, and most of them are Let's Plays. I'm like, yeah, I like numbers.
Yeah, no kidding. I, I like numbers too. I like saying I can make, I can upload a bunch of videos,
but nobody cared. And, and the live streams, the live streams are so much less editing intensive,
so much more fun, and there are some incredible moments in those, like the Minecraft times with,
with Munchie here. That's right. Me, I was there. If there's, if there's anything that I can say
video games have impacted my life in such a way, it would be that now, unequivocally, because of
video games, I love seeing numbers go up. That's what I live for. When I wake up, I, I'm like,
what if I see a six turn into an eight today? I would lose my fucking mind. I love seeing numbers
go up. I am, I am, you, you guys know very well that I have grown into watching analytics and
compiling spreadsheets as in a fetishistic style fixation. And I, it's great and I love it. And
I definitely think video games, like I think of it as a video game in the way that, like,
my stats are rising. I'm going to unlock the ultimate weapon at some point.
Nate is totally stoked this month to play taxes 20, 2018. It's going to be a great time.
I have been prepping. I've been, I've been grinding out my skills, preparing all my
documentation. Basically, I've been basically specking into taxation mode for the last,
like six months or so. And it's time to read my rewards.
I want to comment. This is kind of like a weird tangent, but I think it's interesting.
Okay. Nate. So like, Darkseid Phil is like one of the, like one of the founding fathers of the,
of the let's play ethno stay. Right. Without question. Without question. Yes.
And, but, but he's averaging like shit views. That's true. This just reminds me, like, like a
month or so ago, I was just, you know, searching for homesick music because that's just the kind
of guy I am. And I found a video called a doctor explained by George Bunziaki and, and you know,
linking the comments or something. And it's, it's, it's the guy who made doctor,
like the Homestuck track doctor, John's land. Okay. And it has like 5,000 views. He has like
less than 300 subscribers. And it's really think like the guy who made Dr. Like, like
probably the most popular, like well received favorite of the homesick entire like OTST
doctor, like is a fucking nobody. Like he's dead in addition, fucking Africa now. No one remembers
him. Like no one gives a single shit about this guy, even though he made like the most successful
fucking track in Homestuck. See that, that's the thing right there. And it's the fact it, it strikes
me as a little bit unjust. Like it's not, it's so unjust. Illegal or anything. But it's, it's so weird
to me that all these people are honestly like significantly successful. Have their little
communities based on I should get that guy to work for me. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Maybe he would,
you know, I mean, obviously he's got skills, but like these guys who just like, for example,
with dark side fill, he gets pretty shit views. But people just, you know, like mock him and
take his content and like retool it in a mocking way and get just so many more views than he gets
and obviously more ad revenue and everything that comes with it. And like that's fine. That's not
criminal. It is relatively transformative. It just strikes me as like, I wish dark side fill
was in some way capitalizing on this too, because he's just languishing and just, it's sound, it's
seeing, it's my, you know, my, my, my faint hints of socialism buried deep down in my sake. You make
me think, God damn it. I wish he was getting a share of this too. Hashtag bash the fash.
I wanted to mention earlier that like going from let's place to live streams is what I did.
And, and a lot of other people have done that. Some successfully, some not.
One of my favorite, who's not really considered, yeah, it was German and, and star to maybe bring
up Demolition D a little bit. He's a little different, but still. Yeah. Well, what they did
was they used to make videos about, you know, they, they played a game and then they would
heavily edit it. So it's like, right. It's a let's play, but without the, the boring parts.
And, and it was really funny. And they were really funny. And they would often
collab with each other. And both of them have migrated over to Twitch, which is much more
critical. But in very different ways, in, in very, very different ways. And it's clear that,
that star is shit now. He sucks. He's real bad. He's got like, he's got really cool.
A new cool like intro graphic. He's way more successful. Like, like, okay, okay. Like, he,
he, he sucks. Like I would never watch a star stream. That would be poison. But like he, he,
he's way more successful. He, he's like, okay, okay. Well, just to explain. Star and German are
both like Team Fortress 2 players who basically did almost exclusively Team Fortress 2 content.
And then Overwatch came out and, and, and, and, and German just kind of, you know, stopped doing
TF2, but not like, you know, gotten to Overwatch a little bit, but that wasn't just his main thing.
But Star got super in Overwatch. And now he's like a, like a serious Overwatch streamer,
commentator guy. And he goes like Overwatch events. He's like a real esports boy and does that whole
scene. And it's just dreadful. It's just the most, the entire world. Like he was never that funny,
but it was sort of like the understated like, yeah, I'm just playing a game and he does something
really cool. And he's like, yeah, yeah, you're dead, you know, whatever. But now he's like screaming.
He's screaming constantly in his Overwatch, let's please. Is that good or bad? It sounds bad.
The screaming is, he's not good at it. And he's like, screams are never funny.
So these guys are like bros though, right? Are they like a team?
Well, I mean, they're their friends. I don't know what the situation is, but they haven't
like, collabed or done anything together in a long time. I just noticed they have a channel
called stir slash germa stream archive. That's someone else like a third party just uploads them.
Germa has, has, has changed from, he's streaming and he's doing like any game,
like any game that could be funny. And he just makes it like, he tries really hard to make like
funny comedy videos. And he's really good. And he's my favorite boy.
We know this is a very interesting topic. The idea of maybe there's like a cultural shift
happening now from let's plays to streaming. I mean, I'm certainly, I'm streaming.
It's way more profitable, dude. Yeah.
I mean, you got your super chats, you got your stream labs, you got your Twitch,
you know, money stuff. And obviously that's going to drive people to do it.
Like I've been thinking about, I've really only tried on YouTube so far,
but at some point I'll probably try to switch out and, or Twitch out and like the stream lab
stuff and whatnot. But like what I'm, what I'm thinking about is just like, I had been doubting
myself like for a long time again, we'd all doubted like let's plays. And again, I don't think
they're obviously like going to stand the test of time as well as, I don't know, for example,
a Plinkett review. I want to get into that later.
But no need to get into that. But like the other day, I saw something that really rocked my
fucking world and it was, it was just like a snippet of, are you guys familiar with Dr. Disrespect?
You know that guy? No.
So he's like an extremely popular YouTuber, a Twitch streamer who recently had just gotten
into, he had like a little scandal or whatever. I don't care. But like he had, I think this is
as after he had come back and I just saw someone who uploaded a thing and here's what happened.
He's just like, he was like hanging out and like someone donated like five grand or something
all at once. He's like, wow, holy shit. And so he's just, you know, he's like playing the game
and he's, you know, he's got the face cam on him obviously. He's green screened a little bit
and he's like, wow, holy shit, hang on guys. We just got like a big donation. Hold up. And so
he presses a button like on his thing and like the visual changes and the visual is now we're
looking at like a big like night sky skyscraper field with like, like there's a big building
with like Twitch HQ, like on the top of the building. And I had never seen this before because
I haven't actually watched any of his actual streams. And it's all of a sudden, like on his
stream, we're now looking at a big image of like this, this nightline skyscape or whatever. And
we see Twitch HQ in the distance. All of a sudden, like on the bottom left of the screen onto this
like animation, Dr. Disrespect himself walks out into the animation. So, and then he points
up at Twitch HQ and he's like, there it is guys, Twitch HQ. I'm taking it for my own today or like
and I'm like, what is happening? How is he doing this? And so, so clearly, like at home,
he's got like a setup going on where he's got like a green screen somewhere and he can press a button
to like switch the viewer to like go to that and he's got it set up so that he can like suddenly
be in this cityscape, like looking up at Twitch HQ with like his green screen and like camera
set up at like any time he wants to. He's got this ready to go. So he can just like, he can be in
like this weird cyberpunk Twitch future looking up at the fucking Twitch HQ. I was like, this is
the most creative use of streaming I've ever seen in my entire goddamn life. And I'm starting to get
why this might be where things are going in the future. That sounds incredible. That sounds
indescribable. It was so, I was, I was rocked to my core. I could not believe someone had done
this, but it was like the coolest thing I've ever seen. By far the coolest thing I've ever seen
anyone do on Twitch or like while streaming, it was nuts. Like he must have had another camera,
a green screen setup, everything's ready to go. He must do this all the time, but just unbelievable,
incredible. I loved it. That's sort of like, like real broadcasting sort of, you must have a team of
people setting that up so you could click, click, click, change camera, everything. I mean, I was,
I was just thinking to myself like how I could do it and Xsplit, which is what I use, has like a
function where you can just like basically click to switch like views and it automatically does
just like changes the inputs. And if you set everything up, you can have it at like the push
of a button. If you set up everything ahead of time to just like have that ready to go while
you're streaming, but still like to put that whole production together is like, even the idea, the idea
just like, this is what I'm going to set up. This is what I'm going to do. Like that's just,
this guy just is like, he made this animation or something. He's just like, I'm just going to go
now, stand for a while, look up at this fictional Twitch HQ that I've invented in my own little
narrative on my stream. Like, holy shit, that's like the best idea I've ever heard. Just, I mean,
if he gets like a regular huge donations of like five grand, then I guess it's easy to pay for that.
They call him, yeah, he's doing very, very well. But like any of us could do this too if we just
had like a second camera running and a green screen. And all you do is like put the image up
or something. First video, first video of Radcon 3 checking the Kickstarter. Wow, guys, we got a
big donation coming, like cuts cuts to a recording of us. There it is guys, PCPHQ, we're going to
take it for ourselves. All I'm saying is, if we have PCPHQ and we have like a live stream room or
some sort of like talking room, we could definitely set something like this up. And I very much want
to. I would love that. I'm actually super into streaming. I love streaming. I think it's really
nice. I used to stream a lot, but I've fallen off the wagon now, but I really like it. I think
it's the way of the fucking future. I'm curious though. Mr. Tavern, what do you think of streaming?
Do you see it as possibly the way the future is going? Or do you think it's going to be
equal or just kind of parallel to let's playing stuff? Or what are your thoughts on the matter?
Well, I have no idea really. I've never been much for the wave of the future kind of thing,
if you know what I mean. Sure, fair enough. I usually review old games and play older games.
But on a personal level, it's really hard for me to watch streams because they usually
happen at very specific times. And I prefer YouTube videos because I can just watch them
whenever I want. I do like that. That's kind of the main advantage, isn't it? That's probably
one of the reasons why I've never gotten into watching streams. I do stream sometimes and I
like doing them a lot, but I've never gotten into watching them. I guess.
It's fun to stream just because there's no extra editing work you have to do. You just do it and
once it's done, it's up somewhere. That's great. It's a very relieving feeling to just know you're
done at the end. It's a different feeling from making a product because the whole thing with
let's plays is that if it's a personality driven let's play, you're basically hanging out with
the people on the let's play. Exactly. And a stream is just more directly adding to that so
that you can chat to the person in real time. The reason I like streaming is also one of the
reasons I don't like streaming. It's a two headed thing. It's a Hydra. I like the fact that I get
instant input and satisfaction from my trials and tribulations within the virtual world.
But then I also feel like it's kind of sometimes too fan oriented where it just
especially if you're watching stream archives and there is no streamer hasn't put up a
visual of the chat, who's just responding to things in chat and you'll have no idea what the
fuck is going on. So it's super archaic and hard to get into from an archive's point of view,
but I guess that's not the way streams are meant to be played. I'm wondering if maybe it makes the
most sense. I was thinking exactly that. If the point of streaming is to get the engagement,
from an audience perspective, you get to feel like you're part of the action as it's going on,
which I think a lot of kids will really enjoy because kids have no sense of self and they want
to attach themselves to a powerful figure in their eyes, et cetera, et cetera. But maybe stream
archives are fun and all, but you totally lose that sense. That's why maybe stream highlights
are the thing to go for. That's what German does. I don't want to say I found a solution,
but if you archive something on Twitch and you go back and you rewatch it,
it archives the chat as well. That feature is amazing. That's so good. Your archive is on
Twitch. The chat will go in real time with the replay. That is why, unfortunately, all my racist
slurs I post in the Twitch chats every day are forever more be seen by everyone watching.
I was going to be, I guess, the sole contrarian just be like, I hate live streaming. I hate doing
it a lot because I don't know. I feel really stressed out when I do it. I think the reason
is that I either live stream me doing artwork or I live stream playing video games. The reason
I do work is to get work done and I want to stay focused. When I'm sure, and I have to not be focused,
I got to keep tabs on the chat and stuff and make sure I'm not just because if I'm just sitting there
doing work, I must just do work. Why split my time? Well, I'm curious. I mean,
we've been talking about the idea of possibly streaming the PCP recordings. Haven't you been
kind of advocating for that? Is that a different situation? Yes, I think that is different. The
reason I hate streaming solo is because if I'm doing work, I want to stay focused. Dealing with
the chat is just like, I'm not good at multitasking. They'll be like, half an hour blocks me just
sitting there working and then I'll check the chat and I'm like, oh, hey. Half the people aren't
talking anymore because no one's paying attention. When I stream playing video games, I play video
games to relax. And so I can't relax because I have to like try and keep a persona up and be
entertaining. Yeah. So both scenarios suck. But streaming the PCP would be fine because I'm just
talking. And that's true. That's true. You know, like we'd all be able to keep tabs in the chat
if we had a chat going. So I wouldn't be my sole responsibility. Like there's been huge lulls in
the conversation for me. While you guys are going off about dark side folks, I don't know shit about
them. I could be in the chat just fucking bomb and shit out or whatever. So like, I feel like
that would make more sense just for my comfort in terms of like being able to do it. But when I
just stream solo, I hate it. Like I'm trying to get better because like, I think there is going
to be a big market for that. And I think a lot of people are into it. But I just, I'm not naturally
attuned to that medium at all. And this is uphill battle for me. I like, I genuinely like the fact
that I have a small stream audience that I get like maybe 20 viewers, like, like, you know,
after it goes on for a long time, like 10 people like that. You know, that statement,
Munchy is like the equivalent of that old line Ben used to say about how he loved
average looking girls. He liked, he like normal looking girls. You know, I don't want those tens.
I don't want those actually attractive girls. I just want to really say that.
King of five. That's not the same at all. Everybody knows what I'm talking about. Everybody
knows about like, you know, the like the blonde tan look is not for everybody. You know, the
classic 10 out of 10 is not for everybody. Ben likes attainable girls, everybody. That's not
even true. And if I said that one time, it was ironic. The reason I like it is because then I
can just play the game. And the chat is not always going, I don't have to always look at my phone and
you know, see the chat open and respond to it. It can be a slow, you know, drip of a fan interaction
so I can pace myself. I can respond to the game. It's like a let's play. But occasionally I can
have fan input. And this is the second thing I'm about to say here goes into my weird two-headed
double think about streaming is whenever I like put a joke in a Twitch chat and the streamer is
like, haha, like I see that like, like, like very funny, munchy, W tiny hats. I'm like, I've been
validated. My life is worth living. I can go to sleep a happy man. If I were to, if I were to die
today, I would die fulfilled a happy life. But then when I'm in a chat or I'm in a stream
archive, I'm just like watching. And then like, like, I see, I see the fucking face cam. I see
the streamer with his dopey fucking expression. Look and like lean forward at the monitor, like,
like looking and like reading chat. And I see him go, that's a funny one Excalibur 2007. I get
flying to find to an uncontrollable rage that this interaction in the place of my of my timeless
media is getting the place of my timeless content. And it's ruining the fucking experience. And I
and I fly off the handle and I cannot accept it as valid artistically. I fucking I hate it when
it's not happening to me. I definitely feel like there's a place for both like, let's plays as like
rewatchable things that aren't like in the moment stuff. And then also streams, I feel like you
can do you can be a streamer who also does let's plays. I don't know if anyone actually does that.
But like, I mean, the the Spoonie experiment let's plays, where he's just he does like
Fantasmagoria and this this Ripper game, they're like old Windows PC pointing click games with
like full motion video sequences. And he he riffs on the game. He's just he's playing it. And he's
occasionally he explains something to the audience. But most of the time he's just,
you know, doing like that guy with the glasses reactions to things. But he's not like on camera
or anything. It's just like a let's play show of, you know, him playing through the game and
reacting to things as they come. And you know, it's kind of like a hybrid of like, it recorded at
the time and also scripted stuff. And the scripted stuff, the aspect of that that's like scripted
and cutting out like really boring parts is what makes it so rewatchable. I think I've rewatched
him play Fantasmagoria to like eight times, and it's like a six hour let's play.
Like they're just like, they're so so rewatchable. So like, I try to rewatch Digi Bros. But because
because it's all about like stuff that's currently happening to Digi and Victor,
it's hard to like get into it again, because it's so long in the past. And it's not even that
particularly interesting. It's just sort of anywhere in an episode. You have to start from
the beginning of each series. Yeah. And it's like the things like the what Gamers Teven does and
what was the guy you recommended? Darkseid Phil? No, no. The one he recommended.
Retsu Prey? Yeah, Retsu Prey.
Was that your frame to Hippo? No, no, the the other one.
Are you talking about who I recommended? Yeah.
Cormor Jolt. That's the one. I'm gonna I'm gonna look at him because like I feel like if if there
anything like yours, they're gonna look at this early early stuff. Yeah, they're gonna be like
things that you can just rewatch and put on at any time to just like, oh man, remember this,
like you I could come back like 10 years later and watch a Gamers Teven let's play because
they're just like funny things. They are basically timeless. They are basically timeless.
You just filed for your second mortgage and your wife has left you and you're stuck with two rotten
kids who don't respect you or love you in any way. You can look back on the old times and just
play a playlist of Gamers Teven videos while you put the fucking pistol in your mouth ready to meet
your fucking maker. Oh, looking a little cloudy outside, gets hit by a cloudy with a chance of
pain balls. Got him. Classic Gamers Teven quotes. You're fucking gray matters.
Well, hell guys, we've got quite a journey here. Maybe are we done here? Should we get to the
questions at this point? I'm feeling pretty pretty good. What about me? What about me and my legendary
let's play pieces such as nobody going to bring up the elephant in the room? Oh, of course,
the Nuzlocke's. You know, I wasn't thinking the most let's play in the room. I was thinking of
this like more like Nuzlocke's to me are like a subcategory of let's plays, I suppose, that are
just infinitely better in every way. Well, yeah, the Ben St. Nuzlocke's are of that sort of same
like rewatchable quality, although I have not gone and rewatch them. I probably should. I just,
since we're on the subject, I want to say about that whole thing that I was really going for,
I was really going to like take an extemporaneous improvised format like a let's play and turn
it into, not a scripted, but turn it into like a narrative experience. Of course not. You can't
discredit your own statements from earlier. It can't be scripted. Well, yeah, yeah, no, it was
totally unscripted. It was totally raw. Ben put like the basic plot points in order, like he's,
you know, a weird dictator murdering Pokemon and whatnot. Delete from the watch later right now.
That came up kind of off the cuff. Like I wasn't planning that when I started it.
Right. With your first one, that's true. That's true. More for the second one. Yeah,
like that was all kind of. And it was just like, oh, anything that comes up, anything that gets
brought up as like a joke will continue to be relevant and will become lore, you know, was the
goal there. And yeah, you're right. It's, I don't know if I would even really call it a let's play.
I mean, it is, but it's really its own animal. It's really just its own piece. You know, it's
something greater. It's something greater than anything. It's greater than let's play. It's
more artistic than your commonplace peasant let's play. The Ben St. let's play is truly, you know,
a breed its own. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I would certainly recommend Ben's Nuzlocke's. If you
have the slightest interest in Pokemon or Nuzlocke's, I would say a genocide is better than
conquest. Um, oh yeah, which one do you like more? Uh, yeah, it's tough. I would probably have to go
with genocide. Um, but they both got their, they both got their, their charms. They've both got
bananas. Which is the one with bananas? Which is the one with bananas? That's genocide.
Then genocide's better. Yeah. Yeah. Bananas is a pretty legendary moment.
Also, which is the one with, uh, uh, the radicate, uh, whipstitch? That is all. Yeah,
that's also genocide. Yep. Genocide wins. Genocide wins. Whenever we bring him up, I have,
I have to mention how I famously ripped off whipstitch with a lowland radicate and named him
which whipstache and use Ben's own tactic against him. I have to bring that up every
sometimes. Did you beat Ben using that? Yeah, I did. I'm so proud of myself. I, I, that, that's
what I think about when I go to sleep. I, I, I, I sue the pain and all the, all the dead souls
looming in my ear by just thinking about how, how I pull that off expertly. Fantastic. Well done.
Congratulations. That, that did happen. It was canon. Uh, former vice president, Joe Biden did
do all of the things Munchy just described. Oh, that's right. That's right. I, I, I, I actually
want to extend this a little bit here. Nate, if that's all right. I've been brushed up upon
something that I would like to mention, uh, how the, I'd not, not, not, he did not actually mean
this. It was me, me saying this, but, uh, how some like, like the, the let's plays that are two
dudes talking and let's plays that are, you know, two or, you know, people talking about the game.
There's various types of let's plays of varying quality. And I would like to get to the hard
matter here. Are let's plays like, like good, are, are, are they good? Does just playing a
game and coming to a constant being good content and you know, it's, it's a fuzzy area, but it's,
it's lofty and retarded. But I, I think like the two different types of let's plays, personality
or like a presentation or like a show, like an edited show. Uh, it just depends on a, like if
it's a personality thing that you don't do it too much, I guess. Well, actually, no, that's not
really a question. The question is, are they good in general? They can be good. Are they art? Are
they art? Are we using the super narrow definition of art? No, what I think it is, is that my, my
opinion is that let's plays playing a video game in and of itself is not art. Uh, there's nothing
artistic about it. And if you're making a let's play, just because you're like, I want to play
video games and get paid for that's the dream. You're going about it wrong. A let's play is a
foundation on what's, which to build art on top of playing the game has to facilitate some sort of
creativity or some sort of, well, you know, entertainment value, whether it's presentation
or personality, or it's a, it's a, it's a platform to showcase something beyond just playing the
game itself. I feel like this is sort of wrapped up in the fair use question where it's kind of
unclear whether or not, uh, like a let's play is a transformative work, legally speaking. Um,
but like, just as like, I think there's things that like long plays are probably the least, um,
aren't it, which is just showing especially when there's no commentary commentary. I love watching
long plays. So I have to actually play the game. Yeah, that's what they do. But, but there's other
things that don't really require a personality or like, um, an edited show, which is speedruns,
which is basically like, it's the same as a long play. It's just less long.
In a way, in a way that's true. Um, um, there's a lot going on in a, in a speedrun, but Ben, go
ahead. Speedruns are really great when it's a game that you know really well, you know, because
like these people are, they're showcasing their mastery of the game and really breaking the mechanics
to like optimize, you know, completion time and whatnot, which is in and of itself sort of,
you know, like changing the game. I mean, it's not actually changing. It's all within the
parameters, what the game allows, but it's, I think, I think it's a documentations. Things
like speedruns are like, like just a document. They're kind of like a technical manual of a
thing. I guess if somebody makes, if somebody makes a documentary about people's speedrunning,
then it's, uh, but before that it's just like, here's like footage of me trying my best.
Is a, here's a question. Is a comedy routine art that like a comedian does on stage, is that art,
or does it become art? If you film it, are either of those art?
Both are clearly inherently.
Both are. Okay. So we can all agree at the very least that what Gamer's Tavern does, for sure,
is art.
Absolutely.
Oh, yes.
When I say art, I know that obviously.
Thank you very much.
It's a vague term, but what I mean is, does it hold the same like cultural, like culture per
turn output, or like societal, you know, pressure, like, like, like, you know, the Holy Titans,
like 3D anime, or like Super Hals?
Here's a good example, though. Like, uh, Egoraptor did, of course, his famous sequelitis on Mega Man X,
but then he also did a long solo Let's Play. I think he most, either completely or mostly finished
Mega Man X. Is one of those art, and the other isn't? If so, why? Because they basically do the
same thing.
Wait, so I've never seen the second video you're talking about.
It was a single Let's Play on Game Grumps where Dan was sick or away or something.
Was he just talking about the game?
Yeah.
He was playing it and talking about it. I mean, you've got to just ask the question,
is somebody talking art?
That's exactly what I was about to say. Are two people playing a game,
commenting on it, constitute art? Well, are six people talking about Let's Play's art?
Is this art right now?
Well, see, that's the thing. That's the thing.
No.
We have to completely put aside the question of quality.
Quality is completely irrelevant to whether or not it's art or not.
If quality is irrelevant, I would say that yes, it is art.
Yeah.
It's a sort of performance art.
Because, yeah, it's kind of performance. It's recorded.
It could be edited, you know.
I guess it depends on the presentation or the intention, I guess.
Because I wouldn't say if you go to college, you sit down in a big fucking auditorium
and someone presents you biology. I wouldn't call that presentation art.
But what if the man makes a single joke within the context of this lecture?
Then the joke is art.
But not the whole thing, just the joke.
I don't think so.
I just think that this whole idea, it's silly.
If it's a recorded product put somewhere for people, if it's made for an audience.
The definition of art is really unduable and at the end of the day, rather irrelevant.
It's all gray. It's an unspoken truth that we all have fuzzy artwork legitimacy hierarchies.
Oh, for sure.
Like subtlety, it'll change for each genre or medium, which we consider more art,
regardless of how retarded that is or how conceited that is.
Like how I famously set fire to the petrol black, oil doused wooden altar of porn and books.
Their artistic credibility ruined literature and porn forever and no one could view them
as anything that have our artistic quality to them.
But at the end of the day, all art is art and there's nothing but pretension and segregation,
but we all do it.
You're asking for an authority here and luckily for you, I have the authority right here.
It's name is UrbanDictionary.com and we've got the definition of art,
allowing me to provide it to you so we can settle this debate for all time.
Here we go, art.
Art is used as the shorter version of the common British greeting all right.
It means that you are okay with something and accept.
Jim wants to go to Walmart.
Quinn, hell yeah.
Jim, I'll pick you up in 10.
Quinn, art, the end.
That's it.
Wow.
If, Sue, we're going to have to saw you apart.
No, no, right.
That's wrong.
That's incorrect.
It's right.
We don't say the A bit.
We don't.
We just say right.
That's how we say all right over here.
Okay, fair enough.
So you can't make that.
Well, now we know how they say all right in the UK.
Exactly, that was what we really achieved our goal here.
I just want to say one thing.
If say Munchie was not any internet guy, I just, I saw him on the street and he was
saying a speech.
He was just talking funny and I was like, yeah, that's funny.
If I was just doing arm retrieval alone behind the fucking dominoes, yeah.
Walking down the streets doing an arm retrieval and I was like, huh, that's a funny talker.
I like that wordsmith right there.
Would that, would me watching him or listening to him just in person as a human being,
would that be considered art?
Yes.
I have something to say about this.
Okay, okay, okay.
Imagine you're in a quirky, comedic or otherwise interesting scenario,
like Kimbo just mentioned, waiting explicit.
Like it doesn't matter what you just, you know,
you're something in your life is unfolding and entertaining and provoking way.
And it's something that you would, you know, present to others, to the unwashed message.
First of all, is the experience of this scenario are inherent or, and secondly, what would be,
this is what I want to, what would be more artistic?
You telling your story to someone or you recording the scenario?
Let me break here.
Okay, here's definition two is the answer to this question.
I think this is actually a very good definition from Urban Dictionary on what art is.
Once when asked, or art, once when asked what Trans-Siberian Orchestra was about,
Paul O'Neill replied, it's about creating great art.
When asked to define what great art was, Paul said,
the purpose of art is to create an emotional response in the person that is exposed to that art.
And there are three categories of art, bad art, good art and great art.
Bad art will elicit no emotional response in the person that is exposed to it.
Good art will make you feel an emotion as you have felt before.
You say blah, blah, blah.
And great art will make you feel an emotion that you have never felt before, et cetera, et cetera,
that's the rest.
I think that's, I like his first statement before delineating between them.
If you feel an emotion, that's it.
You're, it's art.
And, and I mean this podcast and any and all Let's Plays by that definition are do qualify.
So, so, so if I, if I touch a burning stove and I go, ouch, does that mean that's art?
That experience was art.
The experience is art.
Your decision, your decision to touch the, the, the stove was.
There's always going to be arbitrary lines.
I don't know if, but yeah, like some gatekeeper.
The reason it's so like everybody always argues about what art is and like the parameters of
what you can define as art and like, oh, but what about this?
And then everyone's like, oh, fuck, what about.
And it's like, the reason is, is that art is, if it like applies in that way,
which I probably would agree with, it becomes mostly useless and you just have to use it
colloquially.
Like if you see a painting, people generally accept that a painting is art.
You see it on the wall and you're like, yeah, that's a good piece of art.
And even if something else would qualify, most people like, like somebody just talking on the
street really in a funny accent, you're like, whoa, that's cool.
I feel an emotion.
Nobody would say that's art.
They just say, I saw this real cool guy today and that's what they would say.
Give us right.
Ethnic minorities are art, for sure, for sure.
I would say that art needs to be created.
So, so this means in your scenario, if I had wrote a script for Armoryville and then was
reciting that script while banging trash cans and pushing over homeless people,
walking down the street, then that would be art.
But if it was, well, that would rule out improv, I guess.
I don't know.
It's never going to be something that anyone can define.
But except for what the wider consciousness of the world of people generally think of as art is
like media and things that are like things that we like.
Yeah, that's art.
Even if other things qualify, we'll just say, here's a cool thing.
It's here's a cool art.
I think I have it.
It has to be a creation for an audience.
So, so if I were to like touch a stove and get my hand burned, that would not be art.
But if I was like, hey, check out this.
Watch me touch the stove.
Yeah, exactly.
And I was like, ow.
And then I did like a like a cartoonish like suck my my my dick afterward.
Get that nice and wet.
Okay, but what if, okay, here's a thought though.
What if like a lightning hits a beach one day and forms like this beautiful like circle of
glass somehow?
Okay, let's say maybe that's not even art right then and there.
Not art.
But what if a guy discovers this is like, wow, this is beautiful.
Comes by like puts a frame around it and starts selling tickets to come see this artwork,
this natural artwork.
At what point did it become art, if any?
It's not art.
It's a product at that point.
No, that is totally art in the same way that photography is art.
Because you can take a picture of something that naturally exists.
And it becomes art because you've curated it.
Because you've excluded, you've chosen what to include and exclude for show.
But he hasn't done that to just put a frame around something.
But that's what you did choose.
That framing is delineating what is and isn't part of the artwork.
You can say if they put the frame in a specific way to frame like that natural formation and
the background and you were only supposed to view it from this specific angle, then fine.
But if you're someone who's just like, hey, check out this thing on the beach.
Here's, give me $5 to look at it.
That wouldn't be art.
Well, he had to choose the frame.
This comes to what I was asking earlier, where what is more artistic?
Like telling the story of a scenario or recording the scenario?
Because recording is like the obvious like, oh, you have the video file.
There's a difference in scale.
I definitely think so.
I think that the story is more artistic.
Because you're using words in specific ways and telling because, you know, when you're
telling a story, it's not going to be completely factual.
You're going to make work.
You're going to use different words that will have a different meaning in everyone's
else's heads.
Like one word will be different for different people.
But if it's like a recording, it will just be like, you know, a recording.
All I know is that this week can go back and forth on what's artistic, what isn't all I want.
But this entire conversation is definitely autistic.
And I'm done with this.
Well, I was going to bring it back around.
The best way to solve this is art is whatever you want it to be.
Yeah, it really is.
That's pretty much what it comes down to.
And that's why Game of Seven is the best Let's Player of the World.
Is the European Union art?
Oh, definitely.
Because they had to curate it.
Because it was created for an audience and that audience is God.
Indeed.
All right, guys, I think we've hit the wall here.
I think we've done all we can do.
Please God end us.
We just have to let the audience sort out our science that we have witnessed before them.
Our patantic bullshit arguments that mean nothing.
But nevertheless, we care intensely about.
Of course.
Well, that being said, everybody, I should have said this at the very beginning,
by the way, but I just want to make an announcement.
RadCon3 Arena is 100% funded and is 100% happening now.
The five members here, plus Digi, March 14th or so, it's entering the arena.
Hashtag enter the arena.
It's happening.
Get us the next stretch goal so we can get some fucking go pros and I can shoot the shit.
I can fucking strip Abraham Lincoln.
Nate, best guy ever.
You give me the money.
Wouldn't it be John Wilkes Booth?
Well, I guess not.
I guess they're both.
I guess you will be Abraham Lincoln.
You fucking bigoted fuck.
Bear it up.
Me and Nate can 1v1 best guy ever versus worst guy ever in the arena.
It's ultimate battle.
And remember, please, if there's a link in the description, of course,
to the Kickstarter.
If you would just want to give money, thanks.
Well, we can always use that.
Again, fund the stretch goal for the enter the arena, the RadCon3 Arena IRL,
shooting each other with guns and go pros and whatnot.
I really hope that happens.
Real guns.
Hopefully going to.
We're buying Glocks for everyone.
Indeed.
It's going to be great.
And then also, we're going to have to invest in double jump jet boots for everyone as well.
That's going to be pretty pricey, but we'll see what we can do.
We'll make it happen.
I'll keep you guys posted on Twitter.
I'll let you know when I locate the quad damage and the mega health inside the arena.
I'll let you know as we can keep up.
And also, feel free to keep giving money if you want to pledge the $50 thing for the,
for the shirts, the $100 for the shout out during RadCon.
And if you want to get that $1,000, if you want to be in the Royal Rumble,
is there still time?
There is still time, my friends, as well as, you know, $20 for the, for the pin and $10 at
least for the behind the scenes content.
That's something that people might want, you know, at any time behind the scene stuff.
Wait, there is.
I want to shout something out real quick, but I have to find it.
There's a comment that I want to shout out on the Kickstarter or where?
No, on a previous video.
Okay.
Well, while you look for that, Nate, would you like to show us the, the, the pity poor
fuck peasant surf question from the Twitter?
Indeed, I would.
Actually, I want to give a shout out to the Twitter boys, because there was a couple of
questions here that are actually pretty good that I'm, I'm fond of.
So we might do more than one pity question.
Oh my goodness.
Oh my God.
And again, that's on at TPCrasnators as our Twitter and using hashtag asked PCP when we
record on these Saturdays.
That's generally when we're going to see your question.
So keep it as follow us so that you see the notification so you can send your questions
in there.
But here we go from this is, this is one of my favorite questions of all time at
Newer Borno asks, why do bitches have time to hit the club every night, but don't have
time to attend one parent teacher conference?
Because they're too busy hitting the clubs because they didn't have any kids in the
world.
You should never be allowed ever seen.
If there's any failure here, it's my delivery.
That question is awesome and hilarious.
And I want, I'm glad everyone saw it when you, when you, when you were like, finally,
we were going to have a good question on this show.
We found the one good question and we found the needle in the haystack of these shitty
horrible questions.
We finally got, we've started on a strong foot here.
I have found the best question we've ever been asked.
Yeah.
Best guy ever.
Reading from the sacred text that is the Twitter.
I was prepared.
I was pumped up, but you have shoveled me shit.
And I will rue the day you were born.
All right.
Here's one that's actually got substance to it.
Again, from the, from the Twitter at LibRplex, I think.
From LibRcock.
Exactly.
Aside from the things immediately relevant to your career, what other internet slash
IRL communities are you part of?
That's an interesting question, I think.
Communities?
Yeah.
I mean, for example, just as one that I, I'm kind of part of is like the fit board on
4chan.
Like it's in no way really relevant to like any of my content or whatever.
But I sure hang out with those guys and talk about stuff and we talk about fitness and
whatnot.
So that, that, that's one for me.
That's one for me.
Pretty cool, dude.
It's pretty cool.
My, my answer is kind of sad because my 2017.
Our incels, our incels.
Yeah, yeah, they had.
Yeah.
2017 was the year of, of the shrinking circle for me where I, I went from, you
know, not particularly a lot of communities, but over the course of my
involvement with the PCP, my, my, my soul has been sucked and my life has been
drained.
And, and, and I've, I've found myself becoming a part of less and less communities.
Obviously not part of the PCP.
You know, I was not doing that, but I just know coincidence, uh, you know, time frame
reference.
As, as a man focuses on the things important to him in his life, he'll have less time to
deal with the things that are less important.
And you know, I think that's a natural consequence.
So, so, you know, I used to frequent like, you know, like, like V and stuff, you know,
not, not super in depth.
I used to go in tumblers to, you know, do a whole bunch of stuff.
But now, uh, you know, I used to be part of, you know, fandoms and shit, but that was,
you know, that was, that was, that was way further, uh, wave now.
Yeah.
Uh, I used to be in a ton of stuff, but now I, I'm really only, you know, a part of
this circle, which is, you know, you guys are nice and all, but you know.
Look, nobody's forcing you to do shit, Munchie.
No, I'm not.
This is not a pity party.
That's not what I'm saying.
That's not what I'm saying at all.
Okay.
That's not even the point.
You fucking bigoted fucking family.
Okay.
I'm, I'm, I'm just saying that, uh, I, uh, I, I'm not part of any communities and,
and I will make that my goal for 2018 is that I need to be, I want to get back in
the groove of going on different websites and, you know, uh, you know, hanging out with
different people.
I think that's, uh, that's,
I do too.
I feel like I'm, I'm not, I'm not as active around the internet as I used to be outside
of the PCP and that kind of sucks.
It's healthy.
Yeah.
You gotta have more, you know, you gotta, you gotta, you gotta live a life to have the
right to reminisce.
You got, you gotta know more people so you can kill more people.
That's my, that's my golden rule.
Exactly.
I found the comment I was looking for, by the way.
Oh, okay.
It is on the, uh, the radcon three Kickstarter announcement.
Um, it's, it's one of the top, it's one of the most liked comments on there.
Um, and I want to encourage you do not like this comment because Russell posted, Russell
the Gengar posted saying if his comment gets 111 likes, he'll enter the royal rumble and kill me.
And, um.
Oh no.
Please.
He's at, he's at 68 likes so far.
So he's more than halfway there.
And if that were to happen, I would shit my pants on the spot.
We're close.
We're fucking close.
So what do you mean we?
What do you mean we?
Who's side are you on?
Our guy Russell.
I'm just saying guys, you have the fate to put Russell in the royal rumble, it seems.
If you, if you, if you would so desire to see Ben vanquish by his ghostly minions.
If anyone were to imagine how a ghastly would translate onto a humanoid WWE custom character.
He's involved into a Gengar now, right?
He's a Gengar.
He did eventually evolve into a Gengar.
Okay.
He would get those, uh, get those likes up.
Hashtag let Russell wrestle.
It's going to be.
Please everyone, it's time.
It's time to make it happen.
Mr. Tavern, what communities would you consider yourself a part of?
I forgot.
Was the question about online communities or?
It actually said IRL or online.
It's all open.
Well, as far as online goes, nothing really now.
I used to post on a lot of forums in the early 2000s and used to frequent IRC chat rooms and stuff like that.
And I used to have a forum on my own website as well.
Mm-hmm.
But, uh, now I'm not really part of, uh, many online communities.
I'm just, uh, flying solo.
Yeah.
It's like our hero, Jason Derulo.
Same.
Feels bad.
It feels bad.
The only, the only community that I'm involved in that has nothing to do with my work is the gay community.
I'm the best.
Well, I wouldn't say that, Tom.
I see a lot of that projected into your work.
So, you know, you know, you got, you got me there.
You can't completely expunge all your influences.
What can I say?
Gamer, I was a huge forum rat, though not in the early 2000s because I was too young.
But in like 2010, I was a huge, huge forum user.
As, as I've, as I've talked about in my embarrassing role plays,
I'm just a role play episode so I can explain, I can explain my various role play up at a
grease because, because I have numerous.
That's not a bad idea.
It's not a bad idea.
That could be a bonus episode.
Press one, press one if you want to hear about munchy role plays because that is sick.
The question was also about IRL communities.
If you guys like do anything.
Sorry to interject, but I am actually part of one forum right now.
It's called Hardcore Gaming 101.
Oh, shit.
That sounds like a nice place.
Sounds like my kind of place.
Sounds like some place Dark Side Phil would hang out.
It is basically just they do game reviews and they have a forum,
you know, very similar to my website actually.
Yeah, I'm looking at now.
I started first.
They started in 2004.
I started in 2002.
Yeah.
Got them beat.
Show those youngsters what for.
Actually, we haven't said the name of your website.
I think it's just a, is it gamers tavern.com?
Yeah, that's it.
Yep, gamertaverns.com.
There you go, everybody.
Read the reviews.
The longest running, most fantastic website review site ever.
Fuck gamespot.com.
Fuck IGN.com.
You want the fucking great shit?
You go to gamers tavern.
You know, you know that you're at gamers tavern.com.
You're not getting any of that corruption that you get,
that journalistic corruption you get.
At some place like Kotaku.
You know, we're freeable.
You're a journalistic integrity.
Yeah, exactly.
Gamer tavern, the most ethical person known to man.
Exactly.
His scruples count is as high as the fucking hammer units.
I pray when I do a dance.
He may deny it with his dying breath,
but I suspect that gamers tavern
is both the alpha and omega of GamerGate.
He is the source and the end of all of it.
Well, I did write an article about it.
What were your thoughts?
I actually didn't know anything about it.
That's the point of the article about it.
That's the best place to be.
Oh, see, plausible deniability.
You wrote that as a cover.
It's a joke.
It's a joke article.
Oh, okay.
Fantastic.
I did absolutely no research for that one.
That's how you know there's no collusion.
That's exactly how much you should do.
Because he didn't even know what it was.
He didn't even take a side.
Dude, talk about journalistic integrity,
not even willing to be corrupted by the facts of the case.
That's exactly what he just said.
Incredible, incredible.
Exactly.
Beautiful.
Well, hey, I think there was one more question.
I wonder, oh, okay, here's one final question
from the Twitter from atreadordarrel.
And this is incredible.
It's, are you aware that in the same month as Radcon 3,
the Muppet Baby's reboot will also be released?
Both will feature six members,
and both will have members absent
from their previous installments.
And here's the question.
Oh, shit.
Coincidence?
I think not.
I think we definitely are the Muppet Babies.
What do you think, loyal viewer?
We'll leave it up to your interpretation.
Yeah.
Which Muppet Baby are we?
You're definitely animal,
because you're an animal in the sack, as we all know.
Wait, no, he's a baby.
You can't say that.
Oh, no.
That has never stopped me before.
That's why I can't make that lie now.
Yes.
It's true.
Now that those fucking poor people questions are out of the way,
those fucking, you know...
If only the contents of their wallet
match the contents of their brain.
Indeed.
Oh, and by the way,
actually, we said Patreon.com slash The Procrastinators
pledge as little as $1,
and you're into our Patreon Lounge
and then $5 more to get those sweet bonus episodes,
which we just released.
Just a reminder, everybody,
GamerGate versus the 2016 United States presidential election,
the most legendary of all bonus episodes.
So this is from the Patreon Lounge,
from XenoGrade.
Do you think guides slash wikis
ruin the experience of playing the game?
Oh, what a question.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, okay, my response to that is,
have you played Minecraft or Terraria
without having the wiki handy?
You will kill yourself.
You know, Terraria is actually interesting.
Yeah, yeah, maybe that's a guide.
The guide is really nice.
Well, that's true.
I just want to say about Terraria,
since you mentioned it.
I played Terraria blind the first time I did,
and I actually did get a strong sense of satisfaction
in the very start when I played it.
But when I started to look up,
just kind of like the little tasks
that I should be doing,
I got a lot more focus,
and it really made the experience more fun to do it that way.
In my experience, the experience of playing Dwarf Fortress
is mostly reading the wiki.
That's like, is the texture of the game,
is the wiki, because I don't know.
Maybe it's possible to learn it without that,
but if so, that's a better man than I.
Do you feel like games that require looking at a wiki,
do you feel like they're victims of bad design?
Should that be necessary?
I think times have changed a little bit.
I feel like if it can be like an addition,
like you play a game all the way through,
and you're like, well, I didn't really understand
some of these things, and then you look up the wiki.
Like Dark Demon Blood, all those games have the lore.
And the first time you play it,
you're like, I don't know what happened,
but I enjoyed myself.
And then you go look at all the big old theories
and stuff and the explanations of the lore,
and you're like, oh, cool, now I care more.
That can be good.
Dark Souls is good enough on its face.
The one thing that's maybe a little bit worthy of criticism
is it's really hard to get your footing
at the beginning of Dark Souls
and figure out where Andrey is
and how to upgrade weapons.
Like that can take a lot of hours of gameplay
before you understand that stuff.
That's true.
That's the one way I would criticize it.
With the lore, though,
that really is just stuff to explore
once you're already into the game.
So I wouldn't really criticize it on that front too much.
But Ben, remember in the old days
when we would go to Game Facts
and print out sheets of how to do stuff
and Secret of Mana and Mario RPG and stuff.
Yeah, staple them together
and keep them in the box that all our video games were.
I remember that too.
Those were the old days.
But with the modern world being the way it is,
I am much more forgiving of games sort of like Dark Souls,
or right now I'm playing Stardew Valley.
And that game, it's similar to your Dwarf Forges
sort of, or like your Terraria's and whatnot.
Yeah, I played some Stardew Valley.
More like Terraria, yeah.
But like in that game,
there's a lot that you need to either
just like patiently wait to figure out.
But I'm way too like goal oriented to wait for that.
So I'll like look things up on the wiki.
But it's so easy just to Google
and go exactly where I need to go.
Like every game is its own wiki now
with all the information.
It's so easy to like find the question,
the answers to the questions I want to know.
So I'm way more forgiving now.
And I wouldn't really call it necessarily
like a bad game design with something like that.
Because I don't want to read a page after page
of tutorial in a game.
When I can just super easily Google,
Stardew Valley wiki,
how to grow a certain type of fruit
that I need for like the community center or whatever.
I would much rather just do things
at my own pace outside the game and then jump in.
Well, Stardew Valley doesn't have any like time restrictions.
Like a harvest moon.
Not really.
Harvest moon, you had to do everything
in a very tight timeframe.
And to play that game and get a good ending,
you really like needed guidance.
But I feel like Stardew Valley is designed differently.
Whereas it doesn't really matter
whether you're playing optimally or not.
I mean, the worst case scenario
is that like you miss a window
and you have to wait a whole year to like do it again.
Like, and that's gonna be frustrating.
But you will always I think have more time
to do more as it keeps going.
I don't think there's any kind of hard end
to the gameplay.
Though I'm only, you know,
I'm not even through my first year of the game.
So I'm not really sure.
But I do want to make a distinction now.
Oh, go ahead.
There is a hard end and the first harvest moon
for the Super Nintendo.
Okay.
Oh, there is one.
There is one in like 97 or 98.
I'm only familiar with the one for the N64,
which does, I mean, it's got,
it doesn't have a hard ending,
but it's got like a point
where like you need to have completed everything by.
And then, and that's like sort of the ending.
Here's what I want to make a distinction about.
Like if a game, a game should be like,
I don't know, I'm right now,
I just got like the new like Dragon Ball Z,
Dragon Ball Fighter Z game.
And like I don't really like fighting games
in the way I have to like,
in a super like non-natural,
kind of annoying way,
I have to like study to learn
how to do the basic mechanics of the fighting.
Because there's like a lot of,
like that is just not fun for me.
But if a game,
like like a Metroidvania on the other hand,
like builds the game in such a way
that it forces you to like learn
every mechanic as you go.
And so it kind of naturally develop
the skills you need to do the techniques
as you play through it.
And like it becomes a real integral part
of the experience that you can't just skip over.
Now that,
and then so by the,
when you started playing at the beginning of the game
versus at the end,
you have just naturally developed all these skills
as part of the progression of the game.
Now that is something I really enjoy.
That's my favorite way to do stuff like that.
I think when it,
Yeah, me too.
I think when it comes to guides and stuff,
if you can just pick up a game
and turn it on and play it,
and like get the gist of
how the game is supposed to be played
enough that you can start to get into it,
then I think it's fine.
I think,
I think when a game doesn't make sense
or isn't fun unless you use a guide,
that's,
that's the point at which a guide is like,
the game is just badly designed.
The most important part,
I think of any game is that initial curve
to get you like hooked on the game.
Like that is like the most critical moment
and Dark Souls has a pretty steep one
just as one example.
And something like,
like a Metroid, for example,
I think is like way lower,
which is why it's like easier to ease your way
like into a Metroid than like a Dark Souls or something.
Hippo, there are certain games now
where like,
like with Minecraft tutorial
where I just mentioned,
there's like,
there's like sometimes like built in guides.
Like like, you know,
we've tried,
there's the guy where you can go to the materials
and you can,
you know,
see how do I make this?
He'll tell you Minecraft,
there's like a whole like recipe book now.
But with one game particular,
Civ,
civilization,
which I've been playing a lot now
as you can probably tell
the viewers can tell by my dialect nowadays.
But with the,
with the,
there is a
actual like Wikipedia
inside the game called the Civlopedia
where you can just like,
press like escape,
like go to the menu,
then you can just like open that.
And there's like a fully functioning,
like Wiki for Civ
that explain like the details,
the hard stats and percentages,
all that stuff is inside of the game.
So like,
is that part of the game now?
Because it is like legal,
like like right from the start,
it's telling you to search things up on there.
And it's like,
you know,
it's encouraged to do that.
Is that part of the game now?
I think,
I think it's,
it's kind of the same as like,
well,
I don't know about Civ
because I haven't played it,
but like,
things like Final Fantasy 13
is like notorious for,
if you don't read the data logs
of information on the things,
nothing in the story
will make sense at all.
Basically.
Which is,
Yeah, I remember that.
And it's like,
reading things is boring in a game,
most of the time,
unless you're already invested
and you want to know more,
if you have to read
like loads of data logs,
it's just sort of annoying.
So I don't know how it is in Civ.
I assume it's fine.
Yeah,
it's,
yeah,
you don't need to do it ever.
But it's just like,
you know,
like,
it's nice because you can just like,
press like,
oh, like,
oh, what is,
what's this guy unique ability again?
Just like,
you know,
press escape,
like,
look it up.
But it feels like,
it feels almost like it's,
whatever I do play a game,
and I'm like,
I don't want to figure out
how to do this.
Just show me the,
you know,
just wiki,
wiki please.
I always feel like I'm
snidely whiplash,
like I'm a cartoon villain
on the run from the fucking FBI,
and they're going to track me down
and shoot me right where I stand.
But with Civ,
the Civlopedia,
it just feels like
this is just part of the game.
This is just what you're supposed to do.
They are giving me this option.
And it feels way different.
It feels like I'm not a criminal
on the run pedophile.
It feels like I'm not Dan Snyder.
Yeah.
One of my favorite memories growing up though,
this is where I didn't feel like snidely whiplash,
and I felt like a fucking god,
is when me and my friend were playing
Pokemon XD Galvanarctis.
Incredible.
Love that game.
Fucking great.
We were playing that.
And we, you know,
we just like Google search,
like Pokemon XD Galvanarctis,
like tips and tricks.
And then we found this like
really, really shitty game facts guide,
which like,
was like incomplete,
I guess it just showed you
what like shadow Pokemon
were in each area,
but not like who had them.
And like, you know, who,
yeah, you know,
and that gave me specific people
who had specific Pokemon.
You had to fight those people
to get those Pokemon.
So we just knew that they were
somewhere in the level.
So whenever we were at a new level,
I would like check the fucking,
you know, guys,
you see like which Pokemon are where.
And I'd be like,
dude, you're not gonna believe this.
There's a fucking Ampros at this level.
And you would just be like,
what?
And then we would search,
we would battle every single
conceivable person.
We found that fucking Ampros.
And then the moment someone
threw out their Ampros,
and then that animation player
where the guy like unloads glasses
and he fucking like zooms in,
like, you know, like tactical lens,
we would fucking scream
at the top of our lungs.
We finally found the fucking Ampros
that we needed.
And we throw,
we throw as many balls as we could.
And it was the greatest experience
of my life.
And I loved it.
So that's,
it's a time that guides,
guides hide in the experience tin fold.
Well, excellent.
All right.
There's another question wrapped.
Hey, but before we read,
like another one or two questions,
there was one thing that I forgot
that we did want to address here.
So, okay,
slightly serious topic, everybody,
but just want to,
I'm sure you don't want to do this
at the end,
just in the middle of questions.
Well, I suppose if you want to,
I mean, do we have other questions lined up?
There's only one more that I would like to do.
Okay.
Okay, go for it.
It's from Mozilla Finneken.
Which games have you played 100% completion?
Is getting 100% a gratifying experience
or a complete waste of time?
And where is the line stand in between those two?
I am a 100% guy.
That's like what I do.
I'm the kind of guy where if I like a game,
I will do it to 100%.
Famously, I think that-
Well, you know,
I was kind of of that opinion
until actually fairly recently.
Two games have made me really rethink
this whole 100% thing.
And I think that it really just depends on the game.
And those games are Breath of the Wild,
also Metal Gear Solid 5,
and then also Mario Odyssey.
Oh, God, Metal Gear.
Those games, all three of those,
are a total weight.
You know, also actually Kingdom Hearts 2,
like my favorite game of all time,
is 100% not worth completing
because you've got to do all that
gummy ship stuff that sucks dick
and is not fun and is not cool or interesting.
If I don't 100% a game,
I feel like I haven't really beaten it.
Well, no, I feel exactly the same way.
No, there are some games that just-
Can you imagine 100% in Metal Gear Solid 5
taking photos of every single thing of wildlife?
Bunny Hop's video is legendary on that front,
and it looks terrible.
You have not done all the game has to offer.
Okay, but literally not all of the game
is that fun or worth your time to do.
I think it comes down to games that are built
to have a certain amount of content
and that games that are built to end satisfyingly at 70%
and then 30% of it is just monotonous boring stuff
padded out in usually an open world game
where you just have to go around and over an entire cycle.
That's how I felt about Reciteer,
like after the main story,
and even a little bit before,
like toward the end of the main story and definitely past it,
because there's bonus content,
like there's extra characters to unlock,
but it was like, oh my god,
you have to do these fucking dungeons like a thousand times.
The grind, I'm just not up for grinding that.
I'm totally up for 100% a game
where like all 100% of the content is engaging.
Like I did 100% of Fallout 3
because all the content that I found very entertaining,
it was interesting, there's lots of quests and I got the DLC
and it was like fun, but Metal Gear Solid 5,
I could never 100% that game.
And even like when like the main campaign
starts getting really grindy, I get pissed off
because I'm playing Metroid Prime 2
and I'm at the point where like you have to go back
to all the places you've been before
and just scan all these corpses
and like they reveal like a secret part of an item
you need to like unlock the final part of the game.
And like the most annoying part
is I've already scanned all these corpses
because I'm like obsessively like scanning
and trying to like read all the lore.
So I have to, I already know like where they are,
but like I don't know where they are.
So I have to go all the way back
and find all these things all over again
that I've technically already done.
It's infuriating.
To me, okay, we had a,
like what is the actual question we're asking
because I feel we're coming at it
from slightly different perspectives.
Like guys like Munchie and Gibb,
or I don't know, whoever was saying it,
I know Munchie was.
Like if you sold your through
and in fact 100% complete a game,
have you absorbed more of its content?
Are you like more of a master
of all the content that someone has?
I've got a perfect metaphor.
I've got a, I've got a perfect metaphor for this.
Yeah.
It's like a big old plate of food.
You know, you can eat the entire plate of food
even if, you know, you get full at like 80%.
And you can, it feels good to like, you know,
eat all the food and then it's a clean plate.
And you're like, yes, I ate the meal because it's there.
But a lot of the time it's better to stop when you're full
because it'll be better for you in the long run.
You will just feel more satisfied afterwards.
You won't feel bloated.
You won't feel like a tired.
It will just be good.
It's a good metaphor because you can always come back
and have more food later.
You can always go back and finish the game later
if you feel like it.
But I won't because fuck that.
Playing a game, okay, to go with this food analogy,
playing a game is like eating ice cream to me in a cone
where they're like, the main game will be the ice cream.
But then the after game to get one is the cone.
And the cone is delicious.
So of course I'll eat it.
No, it's like, it's like,
have you really eaten the ice cream?
Like you can't just throw the cone away.
Like you can't just throw the,
you can't throw the crust of your pizza away.
Like you got in guys are thinking way too simplistically about this.
The objectively correct answer is it depends.
Okay. I mean, it depends.
It depends on what question we're asking.
Yeah, go ahead.
I guess there were some games where I wouldn't feel like that,
but in general, if a game is like a story game
and has like a campaign.
Okay, let gamers.
Yeah, please.
Personally, for me, I feel like I used to like,
I used to enjoy 100% in games back in the 80s and 90s.
But the newer games, they got way too big
and they take way too long.
And a lot of the extra content isn't fun.
Right.
In my opinion.
See.
So, for example, like in Chrono Trigger.
Ah, yes.
When you get near the end of the game,
there's a bunch of side quests that open up.
They're optional and you can do them and they're all really fun.
They all give you really good rewards.
They all have a lot of good character development
and they add to the story.
And the attention that is given to these side quests
is almost the same attention they give to the main game.
You know, as if the same budget and the same treatment
was given to the side quests.
But in a lot of modern games, it's obvious the main quest
is given a much greater budget, much greater priority
because that's what everyone plays.
And then the side stuff, they figured,
well, nobody plays the side stuff except, you know,
a couple of people.
So they just, you know, put something together
that's usually really repetitive and tedious
and just to artificially inflate the play time.
So that's why I almost never 100% games anymore,
even though I used to 100% everything.
That's a great example.
It definitely depends on the game,
but I'm just saying that, like,
one thing it means you have conquered that game.
There is no bones about it.
You have obliterated completely.
Well, look, I will never accept.
I will never accept that I have not conquered Kingdom Hearts 2
because the Gummy Ship missions are fucking terrible
and I'm not going to waste my time doing them.
Here's the thing about it all of them.
I know that they're not good.
I know the facts that they are not good
and they are a waste of my time.
It does not matter if it's good or not.
They're not even sort of relevant
to the actual game experience that I care about.
Not even kind of.
The question, the feeling Munchie is getting
is just the numbers thing.
It's like seeing 100% is very satisfying.
Exactly.
And I would agree, but I would also say that I get more,
like, I guess I'm just able to go away from a game
that where the number is not 100%
just because I've had a lot of experiences
where going for the 100% is boring
and overall is just like bad.
It's just worse than trying.
I know, we're kind of making different sort
of emotional arguments here.
Like, for example, I'm very busy
so I really don't have time to make 100% game play
on like, you know, fucking Metal Gear Solid 5 or whatever.
So like, I have a reason to want to,
I want to like justify my gamer cred
by saying like, no, I've effectively done everything
even though I have not.
I mean, that game, I think it was kind of close.
I'm not saying it's a moral necessity.
I'm just saying like, objectively,
there is code on that disk you have not unlocked.
I mean, there's always, okay, well, if you mean,
that's your metric.
There's literally going to be like developer code
that you have not experienced no matter what you do.
But you know what I mean.
I understand where Munchie is coming from
because I used to have that kind of like OCD.
I got it 100% out.
Yeah, it is, it is.
It sucks, you know.
Yeah, exactly.
And I was trying to do that a lot during the PS2 era
when games started to get a lot of padding.
And I was constantly at war with myself.
I was like, I really want 100% this game,
but I hate playing it, you know.
I feel, yeah, yeah, I am.
It's such a conundrum.
So that's how I got with Reciteer.
And eventually it beat me.
Yeah.
I played Final Fantasy VII for a GRPGA video that I did.
And I got to the end of the game,
and I beat Sephiroth and the final boss and all that stuff.
I stopped the meteor.
And then there was like post-game content
where you could go fight the big under,
like the, what were they called?
Ruby and Emerald Weapons and stuff.
The weapons.
Yeah, the weapons.
Yeah, of course.
And I was like, I tried fighting Emerald Weapon
and it was too hard.
And I was like, well, it looks like I have to grind.
Well, I beat the game.
I'm done.
And I didn't feel the need to complete it beyond what I did.
And I know a lot of people like,
what?
How could you not do all that?
And it's like the same with Kingdom Hearts I.
I never tried doing like the,
I'd never tried getting to Sephiroth to fight him
in Kingdom Hearts I.
Sorry, it's all right.
One because I heard,
one because I heard that it was like really tough.
And I was like, well, I beat the game.
I'm done.
I'm good with that.
I feel like it's more satisfying to me.
And I don't feel like it invalidates
my completing of the game or like,
oh, well, you didn't play exactly everything.
Therefore, your opinion isn't valid
because I played enough of it.
I played at least the whole game.
I played to the last boss.
I feel like that's enough.
Yeah.
I mean, that's kind of what I think.
The way to look at it is if you enjoy doing the side stuff
and you enjoy 100%, 100%ing it, then you should do it.
But if you don't enjoy it, then just don't do it.
This is kind of where I'm coming from with this.
I feel like my emotional response here
is that it's like Munchy is making an argument
that someone who has like mastered the gummy ship
in addition to like all the base gameplay
of like Kingdom Hearts 2, for example,
would have like moral, more authority over Kingdom Hearts.
I literally have just said that is not a moral necessity.
Oh, I will.
I think I get it.
I think it's like Munchy was saying in the back of your head
you know that you haven't experienced a game entirely.
But the way I see it is that there are so many games
that I haven't gotten around to
and I feel like I should sometimes.
But I've just sort of, it's the same sort of feeling
like I can let that go.
Like maybe I'll never get around to that game.
Maybe I'll never get around to that movie.
I don't need to experience them all
and I don't need to experience everything to 100% completion
as long as I get the gist and I can talk about it with people.
To me, I just feel like it's futile, you know.
Sometimes, yeah.
Futile.
There's just some games that it's almost impossible
to 100% unless you give up your entire life
and just play it.
I mean, here's a question.
Here's a question.
What about a game like Disgaea
where there is literally infinite content?
Like at what point have you 100%?
That's basically what I'm talking about.
Yeah, well.
I tried to 100% that back in the day.
Oh, yeah, it can't be done.
Can't be done.
What I'm saying is just look at what I'm saying.
It's not like controversial or like I'm not saying
that it is good or bad to experience 100% of the game
and I'm not saying that you have to get 100%
to be in a four-hour or talk about it.
I'm just saying the fact that you have not experienced 100%
of the game if you have not completed 100%.
I'm not saying that's a good or bad thing.
I'm saying I want to experience it.
The fact what?
I mean, that is true.
But is there any consequence of this?
Or are you just saying it is?
No, it's just that it doesn't feel right.
Yeah, it doesn't feel right and I really beat in the game.
Okay, here's what I'm willing to concede.
I am definitely not an absolute authority
on the Kingdom Hearts 2 Gummy Ship missions.
I am absolutely not because I have not beaten them.
But I am an absolute authority on Kingdom Hearts 2,
Mainstay, Combat, Story, all that shit.
I will concede that.
But that's it.
This is not a fucking war treaty, Nate.
It is a war treaty.
This is not.
You're going to have to concede authority on the story
and issues.
I just like seeing numbers go up.
That's all I want to do.
I just want to see numbers go up.
Well, fair enough.
You should really enjoy this guy, then.
Yeah, except it has no end to it, unfortunately.
There's so many big numbers in that game.
I could not get into the whole infinite procedural content thing.
The problem with that is that there is no end goal.
You have nothing to shoot for.
Yeah, it really was a problem for me.
And it's weird because I really like a lot of procedurally
generated games, like roguelikes and stuff.
But those, again, those have an end goal.
Those have a win state.
Disgaea basically does not, which is a problem for me.
With Disgaea, it's like, well, I already beat the game,
and now I can just do all this random extra stuff forever.
But to what end?
For me, that is completely unanticipating.
Tactical RPG.
This might surprise and baffle and horrify some people.
And this is in no way a discouragement of the quality of Kirby 64.
But I will, and I do not regret any of the moments I spent with that game at all.
My experience was the pinnacle moment of my life, and it was great.
But I will say, there were certain shards where I just
would fucking rather piss on my cat than play it.
That one fucking level where you have to get the dynamite ability,
and carry it through until the end of the level.
And the dynamite ability fucking sucks, and you cannot hit shit with it.
And to traverse, and then fucking parry, and parkour around Bronto,
Burtz, and Wildies to get to where you need to fucking go.
With this shit ability you cannot use.
I remember that, actually.
Yeah, it was the worst moment of my life.
But when I beat it, I felt so good.
So I feel like the slog and the turmoil that go through for some of the shards
and 100%, it's worth it in my opinion.
If I like the base game, which I love Kirby 64, I love it.
And I'm happy to concede.
I'm happy to concede.
I like to do it.
I'm definitely on your side when it comes to, I don't know,
like I do go for 100% completion on a lot of stuff,
and would absolutely look down on the people who have not done it.
I just want to kind of judge it on a case-by-case basis.
Like for example, getting all the moons in Mario Odyssey is an absolute waste of time.
Do not do it.
You will regret it.
It is not worth doing, because some of them are just not fun.
And it is in no way an exercise of skill.
Or like what you get for doing some of that is like,
just like you have to like go talk to one character wearing a certain outfit.
And like that does not give you anything.
Like yes, you have to buy the outfit,
so you get like a little bit more experience with it.
But like you already get a moon for just like buying every outfit in the game.
Like to me, that's like a goal that makes sense.
It's like this large, big goal.
You should get like some grand prize for doing that.
But the weird way that that game has made the prize
for literally every accomplishment, a moon,
totally cheapens and devalues the moons themselves.
And did you see the Joseph Anderson video about it?
Of course, of course.
Okay, yeah.
I'm with him on a lot of that stuff.
Yeah.
Yeah, he had the same complaints about everything gives you a moon.
I'm never going to play that game.
But I watched that video like three times.
Sunshine is better because Sunshine is the best 3D Mario,
literally objective fact.
Sunshine is the fucking best.
I would like to close this out,
but I think reciting the story that I've said before,
but it's relevant to this and it's incredible.
And I am a god.
Bow fucking down right now.
I was going on like a road trip.
I knew that I'd be in the car and I couldn't do anything else.
So I brought my DS along.
And so I didn't have any games for reasons.
So I went to GameStop and I bought Kirby Superstar Ultra
for the road trip.
And on that road trip, that rat trap going from my location,
which is like seven hours away or something, and coming back,
I completed Kirby 64 or Kirby Ultra 100% three times on all save files.
And then I did that.
I brought it back to the GameStop and I turned it and I got my money back.
In one day, I completed all the files 100%
and I turned it and got my fucking money back.
That was all.
That's incredible.
I used it like a fucking whore and I got my money back.
Okay, that's the thing.
It is important.
Okay, and this is the thing.
Some games absolutely use the 100% completion system
as a way to make sure that the players experience
all the content that is worth doing.
Some of them definitely do it that way.
For example, I would argue that like most Castlevanias
do it that way.
The RPG ones, like for example,
getting all the souls in Aria of Sorrow,
I think is absolutely worth doing.
A lot of them are a grind and are really annoying,
but you get to experience meaningful new aspects of that game
when you push yourself to get like fully...
I think that the actual percentages,
it might be like 210% is what you get
when you actually have done literally everything in that game
or something like that.
When the game does it that way...
For me, I think a positive example for me
is actually Super Mario World.
Sure, sure.
Because there's a lot of hidden levels in that game,
but all the hidden levels are just as good as the main levels.
Exactly.
Sometimes they're even better.
So if you 100% that game, you will truly experience everything.
And like what if...
That's worth it.
What if Super Mario World had a mechanic
where you have to like go collect seeds
and then you come back and you plant them in pots
and then you have to like come back to the level
after like 24 IRL hours have passed.
I think I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, I mean those kind of mechanics are not fun.
Sometimes they can be, sometimes they can be.
But again, I just want to judge it on a case-by-case basis.
Gummy ships, terrible, don't care about them, waste of time.
All this is coming from a guy who has not played
single-player games at all for like legitimately...
Like I've never played a single-player game seriously
in a really fucking long time, like a year.
I don't do the multiplayer games
because fucking multiplayer games master race,
I love those.
Fair enough.
Okay, well, you know what?
I think it's all the questions.
I think yeah.
I'd like to say you're serious gambit here.
Okay, well the thing is this isn't actually
like that serious of a thing.
So I felt uncomfortable saying it before
because it's not actually like a major issue or anything.
I just want to slip it in.
But nonetheless, so here's the thing guys.
So everyone's been commenting on like
when's Jesse coming back?
Where's Jesse?
Et cetera, et cetera, since the whole monkey thing.
And like I hear what you're saying guys.
I understand where you're coming from.
Like why isn't Jesse back?
But here's what you got to understand everybody.
Jesse was under no impetus to actually return
to the show after Monkey Left or anything.
It was just if he then chose to.
It was a separate issue.
So right now Jesse doesn't want to come back on the show.
He's doing his own stuff.
Do not expect him back.
He may come back someday or he may not.
It is up to him and do not count on it.
Do not have expectations.
So everybody commenting, where's Jesse?
This is your answer.
He's not coming back anytime soon.
He has made that explicitly clear.
He is going his own way.
The proud MGTOW that he is.
And didn't go bother him.
We have no bad blood here.
There is literally no bad blood.
We have been having more fun conversations with Jesse
than at any time in the last like six months.
He's still our friend.
He is a friend.
He's in our chat.
We talked to him.
Like there is literally no problem here
other than Jesse just isn't interested in being on the show.
So there's no conspiracy.
You can go ask the guy on Twitter,
but please don't bother him.
Like it's his own, you know, you can add like,
this is just it.
This is just how it is.
He just doesn't want to.
And we bear him no will will as a result.
So, you know, chill out everybody.
You can stop asking all the questions over and over and over
again, because this is the answer.
He's just not interested right now.
To be fair, it is our fault for not calming on earlier,
but the where's Jesse Commons can, can, can please cease.
You can stop them now.
If people keep asking, then just link them this part
right now.
And then, and then that'll be the answer.
This is the official PCP statement.
You just, just so nobody thinks, just so nobody thinks
that he's like not invited for whatever reason.
It's not, it's not like that.
Yeah, we continue to have an open invitation
anytime he wants to come back.
And in no way is this an attempt to like guilt him in any way.
He chooses not to come back.
That's perfectly fine.
Sometimes people are busy who are regulars
and just don't want to be on the episode
because they're doing other stuff.
I consider it like that.
He's just doing his own thing.
There's nothing, nothing to be worried about guys.
Just maybe we'll be back.
I know a lot of people want to see him on,
but unfortunately, you know, it's, it's his decision
and please respect it.
And, and again, you can stop with the questions.
Like we got it.
We got it.
This has been a great episode.
Thank you so much, Mr. Tavern for being on.
It's been a real treat.
I'm, I was delighted to, to be on here.
Thank you.
Oh, great.
It was really good.
I'm so glad we finally got a chance to talk.
We've been kind of admiring your work from afar for a long time.
And man, I hope maybe we can, we can twist your arm
to make some more content on that YouTube sometime.
Cause man, do I miss it?
All I, all I can say is that if there was more, I'd watch it.
That's, that's, you know,
Well, I do, I do intend on making more.
So.
It's a little perfect.
Is there anyone, check out his channel in the description.
Yeah.
If you subscribe to him, he deserves more subs.
He's a great guy.
Gamer's Tavern show.
And last, here's the last question for you.
What would you recommend as your own content
that you think people should watch?
What would be your content of choice?
Oh, you mean me?
Yeah. Like it would you recommend like people watch your rocket night
or your sonic or if people were going to get into your channel,
what do you think it'd be a good place to start?
Well, uh, my opinion, uh, which I might not be the same as people who watch me.
Sure.
Uh, I think my best stuff is the most recent stuff,
the sonic three, uh, and not goes play through.
So start with like part one of that.
I've, let's link that in the description to people.
That's the point when I started to know what I was doing.
Before then I was just kind of, you know,
I don't know, man.
Those rocket night adventures are pretty legendary.
I love them all.
They've all got it.
They've all got a slightly different like tone to them,
but they're all, they're all great.
And I'll just put them on, I'll just put them on, uh, you know,
like the full playlist and just go through the whole series.
And I don't want to underplay fancy when I get the wild hair.
We have really loved your content, especially Jesse Gibb and Ben have been
like your champions out here talking about how great you are.
And loving your stuff.
I can't overstate just how great I think it is.
Just how much I've gotten out of it and how I think the other people would too,
if they knew about it.
If they knew about it.
And, and, and Gibb, I want to prompt you.
I mean, what do you have to say about this man and his catalog of work?
It's, it's, it's just really good.
It's, it's, it's a type of, it's a type of comedy video that just I've never seen.
Like I don't see people making really dry pun laden videos of just, it's,
there's no like ego there.
It's just, here I am talking about this thing and oh, there's, there's funny.
And this is what you do with this boss.
And here's a pun and here's a pun is like, it's, it's, it's very unique.
Like I haven't seen that before and I really, I was really happy when I found it.
It's, it's like if hippos best pun tweets were read by your tax attorney.
Excellent.
Yes.
So, so great.
That's one way to put it.
Well guys, what a lovely episode this has been.
Thanks again, Gamer's Tavern for joining us.
Maybe we'll have, we'll have you back sometime soon again.
I would sure love to talk to you again.
All right.
Thanks for having me.
Anytime, dude.
Anytime.
All right, everybody.
We're going to be trying to be more guests.
So yeah.
Let us know if you like having guests, guys, because we're really,
we're really looking to mix it up and we've got a couple of people in mind.
And I guess, I guess, I guess, but we're fucking free spirits.
We don't need that shit, but if you want, I guess.
Indeed.
That'd be nice.
Yes.
Remember everybody, follow us at tbcrastinator's questions on Saturdays,
hashtag askpcp for those.
Join the discord, patreon.com slash the procrastinators,
one dollar to get into the patron launch,
five dollars for those sweet bonus episodes,
Gamergate versus Drumpf.
You want to get in on that and the whole gang, of course.
And we will see you soon.
Thanks for joining everybody.
Bye-bye.
Salutations.
See you later.