Hello everyone, welcome to an episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Here we are to listen to your every sin, everything you've done, it's time for you to confess.
It's time for a laid back, therapeutic episode of the PCP.
This is ASMR. This is better than-
HELL NO! We're getting rowdy up in this piece!
We have Digi.
Self-explanatory.
We have Nate.
We have Hippo.
Self-explanatory.
We have Ben.
I'm supposed to be sleeping right now.
No, that's Ben. Don't you know that that seems like it's been fucking banished from ever trying this podcast ever again?
You know, our iconic theme song that everyone knows the words Ann Mellie to has been fucking, you know, obliterated.
It's in the fucking new version! It's in it!
It is in it. It is literally in it.
Wait, the one with the stay at home mom and dad?
Yeah, if you listen close, if you open up the baby ears of yours, you'll hear the melody.
If you open up the frequencies, if you open up the waveforms on a dash, you're gonna be able to make up in, you know, distant.
Distant in the background.
It is the instrumental. He is using the instrumental in the opening song. You can hear it.
I can't hear it. Stupid.
Okay, you have not paid attention then. The fault lies with you friend, not with me.
Ben, you're in a grouchy mood today.
I am in a fucking grouchy mood today. I didn't want to...
I stayed up late last night waking up a ghost, okay? I had to summon a ghost and it was really stupid.
It made me very upset.
Oh yeah, what the hell was that? You said you were going to a seance or something?
Yeah, I had a seance.
Because there's a ghost in my house, you guys.
Or maybe not a ghost. Maybe just a spirit.
Could be a low level.
Maybe not a demon, could be an incubus.
Maybe just a phenomena. Maybe just some kind of phenomena.
How does it feel to be a certified scientist with like a master's degree?
As a bachelor's.
Feels great. Feels wonderful.
In a house with ghosts.
Well...
You're still out of your element, Ben. This house doesn't apply to you.
Yeah, I'm weak to ghosts. I'm literally weak to ghosts type.
And you know what? They really took their toll on me. I had to sleep it off.
I had to sleep off.
How late did you spend?
The time is not matter. The time is not matter. Just because my sleep schedule.
The point is I was supposed to be sleeping through that whole period, but instead I wasn't.
It's funny you say this, Ben, because I also have been up all night.
And Tom was too. I'm guessing that he passed out at some point. That's why he's not here.
For like two seconds before the show started.
And then he was like, fuck this. I can't stay away.
He said like two words that were irrelevant. You know, like usual.
Yeah, three slaves, but you know, irrelevant.
You had a seance. We had a blood sacrifice at this house.
Because Tom spent...
What's going on with you guys? I'm the only pure Christian boy left in the museum.
Were you becoming games?
Tom was setting up for our games to become even greater by building a server and streaming PC in the house,
which he spent like 15 hours doing last night because of a comedy of errors.
One of which was the computer slicing his finger open.
And apparently it was like Kill Bill blood spraying all over the place.
There's like dried blood in places where blood shouldn't reach from a finger.
It's intense. Me and Mae were not home when this happened.
So we just come home and Tom's like, yeah.
He's come home and there's blood everywhere.
Wait, wait, so Ben, what are the specifics of this ghost?
Like has a poltergeist invaded and started knocking down family heirlooms and sacred urns in a hilarious comedic fashion?
Oops, my grandmother's ashes are all over the floor.
Listen, because there is a small chance that my housemates could listen to this podcast,
I'm not going to say that I think they're fucking retards for doing any of this.
I will. I'll say it for you.
Your housemates are fucking retards for believing ghosts.
What about the whole story here?
So one guy, he was smoking on the porch one day and he claims...
The devil's lettuce.
Okay, so we had like a broken door, right?
Like the doorknob was extremely loose and would fall off the door.
That's the work of a ghost right there, for sure.
Well, yeah, to start, yeah.
So this doorknob would fall off very easily. It was not held on very well.
He claims that one day he was sitting out there and the doorknob just flew off the door in an arc and like landed kind of by his feet.
And this spooked him really bad.
You know, for days this was all he would talk about.
Jesus Christ.
Is that he witnessed a paranormal event.
I mean, if that was true, it would be spooky.
Yeah, yeah, sure. Sure, whatever.
I get it, I guess.
Did anybody ask him if there was wind that night, by chance?
We're talking about like a metal door.
Look, the thing he describes, if it happened as described, would be very strange and hard to explain for the doorknob to fly off in an arc.
Just the problem is like, how reliable is one sense?
How do you know you didn't just see it at the corner of your eye and that's not really like, you know, how do you know?
Of course.
The human error is a huge factor in these things.
Maybe a squirrel landed on it and then jumped off and it like propelled it off and he saw the squirrel traveling in the arc.
No, Arkham raises that, did you? That's too complicated.
And then saw the Arkham's razor.
I am a chief philosophical mastermind.
If you just strip away all the complexity, it's a ghost.
I mean, there are incidents in like, there's one like South America where like a literal entire village claims to have witnessed some like extremely strange like solar phenomenon.
But it's just like, what's more likely?
God stole the sun for a minute just from this one location?
Or that like there was some sort of mass, I don't know, maybe it was a fucking mass.
Or what's more simpler than that?
A.K. less words and it was a ghost.
That's how we Arkham's razor, it just was a ghost.
Okay, so there's more, so there's more.
So, you know, obviously nobody cared about this, but then naturally this was irrelevant to everything.
But then a couple days, maybe two weeks later, my other housemate, he is a little tipsy or whatever and he hears a bottle cap fall off of a countertop and he looks at the ground.
And he screams as loud as fucking hell.
There's no way that the bottle cap could have fallen that far across the floor just from falling off.
There's just no way.
The counter is a lot of substances involved in these stories.
It went like halfway across the floor, you guys.
It's like almost halfway across the entire kitchen.
Wow.
So, you know, and he didn't even touch it.
Has anyone put a level on the floor of this house yet to see if it's like leaning?
Maybe, not a bad idea.
Or maybe it's a circle and it rolled.
So the point is, so this convinced, let me call these, I don't know, these are, whatever, so these are the ghost bros who are both now convinced.
And then, you know, and then we got me and we got Big John and Little John.
And Little John is like, guys, we should have a seance.
We got to invite people over.
We got to buy a Hasbro brand Ouija board.
And we got to have a seance.
Got to do it.
So that's what we did, you know.
And basically, so the ghost, yeah, it kind of was.
So the ghost boys are totally, totally believing, convinced that there is a presence, there is a spirit, you know.
And the rest of us are just sitting around, just like, you know, intently, intently pretending like this isn't the dumbest thing we've ever seen.
So, yeah.
So, okay, so we started the seance.
We asked the ghost, first question, one of the ghost bros is sitting there.
Two people have their hands on the Ouija board planchette.
One of the ghost bros is one of them.
The other one's this girl who's a friend of the house.
And this guy asks, he's like, first, he's like, is there a presence here?
And the planchette moves immediately to no.
The ghost is immediately denying his involvement in any of this stuff.
So the ghost answered in the negative to his own presence.
Yeah, there was more.
He asked it, he asked it, at one point he asked it, are you fucking with us?
At which point it moves somewhat towards yes.
And then he asked it, do you like to have fun?
And it moves strongly towards yes.
Whatever, whatever.
Oh man, then our downstairs neighbors heard about this and like one of the answers it gave at one point had an eye in it.
And she was like, oh my god, my dad died this last year.
And his name was Irving, I for Irving, I think it was his ghost.
This is legitimately worse than hearing about a dream.
So I literally went outside and threw myself off of the balcony that the ghost removed the original doorknob on.
And then your ghost came back and completed the seance for me.
Yeah, I answered, they asked, you know, how can we help you move on to the next world?
And I answered with a B for Ben and that was proof.
So that's, I'm sorry, was that a boring story?
No, that was fascinating.
I'm fascinated with the story.
You're poking a lot of fun right now, but can you prove that there wasn't a ghost in your house?
I cannot.
Well then there you fucking go.
There you go.
Then shut the hell up and pack it on out of here.
I will.
Anyway, I'm cranky.
I'm cranky and I don't like ghosts.
I ain't afraid of them.
But I don't know why I stayed up.
And from generations from now, apography will be misquoted to all of you.
But famously, I have spoken in many letters that the government is scarier than ghosts.
As I said once in a procrastinators podcast very recently.
And so I don't believe in ghosts, but I do believe in the government, which is way worse.
So it's possible that the NSA in fact planted, you know, an assassination attempt on your friend
and their method of choice was to fling a doorknob at his head as fast as they could.
Not even at his head.
Maybe like towards his knees kind of.
Listen, okay, I'm going to guess that if your guy believes in ghosts,
they probably wouldn't go to the doctors because they would probably be, you know,
some sort of like demon incubi that would rape him in his sleep.
So I'm assuming if his knee was scraped and blood were to come out,
it would probably get a staff infection and he would die.
So the NSA might have better intel on your friend than you do, Ben.
Maybe you're just a fucking idiot. How about that?
I live in a house.
I live in a house with a weird spread, a weird melange of like people from different places on the ideological spectrum.
And there is a certain segment of my house that is like weirdly, apolitically,
like what's it like, neoconservative with like a weirdly spiritual bent.
And I think it's the worst.
That's like dubstep country mashups.
Yeah, these are, we're talking about guys who voted for Trump
just to shake up the establishment and who like regularly talk about going to church
and how much they like going to church, but who don't actually go to church.
I know I'm just the kind of person we're dealing with.
I know I'm about to preach to the choir and say a bunch of shit that's obvious,
but what blows my mind whenever this is the subject of ghosts
is that like you can have people who like by and large don't believe in any weird shit
or superstition or ghosts, but like the second they can't explain something,
it's immediately ghosts.
Okay, so little John, who was the one putting on the seance,
he was telling me that like he would mention the seance to people
because he wanted to invite more people over for it.
And he would get split reactions, like some people would think it was really funny
and others people would be like, oh no, don't do that.
That's a bad idea.
Like people would react negatively to it.
Like it's bad because like, oh no, don't mess with the ghost, dude.
I think, yeah.
Okay, yeah.
Okay.
The thing about...
Not even, like I could almost understand if you were like,
don't mess with your dumb friends like that.
That's really mean.
Yeah.
But I don't care about that.
I mean, sure.
The thing about jumping to ghosts...
Of course I'm going to do it anyway.
...that gets to me is that like ghosts are like made up by people.
Yeah.
It's like you could have...
There's some biblical references to them,
so maybe people are working from that partially.
If I see something like weird and inexplicable...
Maybe I'm wrong.
If I see...
There's like risen dead or something, but okay.
If I see some weird inexplicable shit and I can't explain it,
like why jump immediately to made up shit instead of just like,
oh, there's probably like a rational thing that I just don't understand
or did not observe enough.
Like...
There's an answer for that.
Are you aware?
I forget.
There's like a name for it I think,
but there's a phenomenon that's just like,
after the events of like,
I forget what it is,
but there was like some alien conspiracy
where specifically like the gray alien...
Roswell?
Like Visage became...
Maybe it was Roswell,
but there was like something where in popular culture,
the gray alien depiction became like the zeitgeist,
what people thought aliens looked like.
Like before that, there had been some alien reports that they'd been kidnapped,
but after that like fake thing happened,
it maybe was like whatever that...
Those encounters of the third kind movie?
Yeah, it might have been that.
It might have been that.
And after that,
like all the very different types of reports about alien abduction,
all very coincidentally settled in on the like gray alien depiction
to describe like what their alien kidnappers looked like.
Because it's a way for you to fill in the blanks.
It's like you see a...
Yeah.
But kind of like with UFO sightings,
it's like there's so many things that look like a floating black disc
that you could see,
that as soon as you mentally associate it with one thing,
that's what you're gonna see.
I think that's what you're trying to say.
These people, they just need to watch some Vsauce
and understand the basics of the human mind
and how it's fallible and learn all the funny things about illusions.
It can't be true.
All your problems.
YouTube, videos, UFO.
I'm so fucking upset with all of you right now, Nate.
You're being so ridiculous right now.
So all these people from different walks of life,
all just coincidentally are talking about the exact same type of aliens
and driving the exact same way.
All these different people at different points, intervals of time.
That's so just a complicated, you know, conspiracy theory, Nate.
The simplest Occam's razor way is just say it's real.
It's just real and they're all describing the same thing.
You're right.
You're an idiot.
You haven't even been to poll.
Occam's razor, man.
You're right.
Jesus Christ.
Come on.
Like as we define Occam's razor to mean the thing that takes the fewest words
to explain.
Yeah.
I mean, we could also, let's just Occam's razor it to gestalt psychology then.
Eh?
Yeah, but no one knows what those words mean.
How many, how few, how few letters can we possibly use?
Oh, oh, no, no, no.
Okay, guys.
No, yeah, I've got it.
Yeah.
Real.
R-E-L.
It's real.
Yeah.
There you go.
Wait.
Fake also has four letters though.
It's a coin toss.
It comes down to a coin toss.
It's always split.
Everything boils down to a coin toss between fake and real.
Ben, how many people do you, do you live at your house?
Because it just seems like there's just a clown car just constantly revolving door
of just like 20 or so people who are all insane.
Okay.
Not counting my downstairs neighbors because we live in like a split condo.
Hold on.
I want to say six.
Uh-huh.
Whoa.
Six?
If you do three of those, that's the mark of the beast.
Real.
Big John, Lil John, the ghost bros, the other, the anime recluse.
Nice.
Who's Indian name is Clips Through Walls and me.
Sick.
So I think the six.
Yeah.
I think there's six.
My Indian name is Hacks the Mainframe.
Hacks the Mainframe.
Yeah.
Can you imagine each of them up to a My Little Pony character?
Ooh.
Cool.
I don't really know who they are.
We have no way of knowing if their comparisons are accurate.
Yeah.
Let's not do that.
Okay.
Well, no.
We got, we got.
They're all Queen Chrysalis.
They're just all.
Yeah.
Who's the spike of the group?
There's Serendipity.
That's a band, of course.
That's definitely a band.
Yeah.
All right.
There's Serendipity, Chastity, Grace, Serenity, Firefly.
Action Adventure RPG video game.
There's a pony called Chastity.
Yeah.
God, I hope so.
The biggest slut of the bunch.
So I can fuck her.
You know what I'm saying?
What's it like living with your old roommates after living not with them for so long?
I don't know.
It's good.
I like it.
Why are we interviewing Ben?
This is terrible.
Okay.
Hey, hey, hippo.
How's your life going?
Huh?
Oh yeah.
How's your life?
What have you done today?
Oh yeah.
That's real great, dude.
That's real fucking nice.
Oh wow, hippo.
I'm so impressed.
Hey, wait.
Speaking of which, happy birthday, Munchie.
Yeah.
Happy recent birthday.
Oh my god.
You're a fucking adult, aren't you?
He's 18 at last.
It was yesterday, right?
No.
It was the 14th.
Now we can release all those unreleased videos from Radcon 3.
Now they've become retroactively legal.
You better head over to that link, the Gumroad link below.
Get the backseat pass if you know what I'm saying, ladies and gentlemen.
Heyo.
Now I'll be the second PCB member to have their dick shown on camera.
Who was the first?
You.
My dick's never been on camera.
All right.
What are you talking about?
No one's ever seen my dick.
No one ever.
I don't know if you want to get into it.
Wait, do people think my dick is out there on camera?
I think it was.
Of course not.
Like a brief flash, because you had holes in your undergarments.
Oh, you mean the PCB.
There was that thing.
Ah, yes.
I forgot about that.
You didn't see my whole dick, though, right?
No.
I mean, I suppose not.
Not the whole.
You gotta leave a little, you gotta leave a little mist.
Like my foreskin.
Cut this off.
Cut it off.
That's right.
Destroy this whole piece.
Why?
Well, I don't know.
If you don't care, I don't care.
All right, let's get this phone straight.
Why would I care?
It's not even, it's not available.
Nobody could find it.
I mean, I assume somebody downloaded it.
You know.
And enlarged it and enhanced it.
It was with your podcasting skills.
All right, my podcasting skills.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to another Let's Play.
I'm gonna play Minecraft today.
Have you been sick recently or at school and not been able to release a video?
Yeah, that's what I wanted.
Are you sorry that your voice sounds a little weird because you have a culture?
I'm sorry, guys.
Save me if you would will.
Guys, listen.
When did you first realize that you had wasted your life?
At what point did you realize this?
Today.
Just now, actually, listening to you ask me that question.
You know, I realized I was wasting my life.
It was in college after my girlfriend broke up with me and before I went to Japan.
And then I fixed it and it was pretty good.
Actually, there was actually a second round.
It was after I got back from that and I was before I started doing any YouTube stuff when
I was just going through my shitty school and stuff.
That sucked.
But then it got better.
So that's cool.
Hey, have you guys heard of this Hispanic comedian?
Guzzlin Dispera?
No.
Have you heard of this Hispanic comedian called Munchie Shatsky?
How about Guzzlin Disparity's nuts, bitches?
Wait.
Yeah!
Say that name again?
Guzzlin?
Say it?
Guzzlin Dispera?
Is that it?
That's right, that's right.
Okay, so I'm Guzzling This Pair of Nuts is what I'm...
That's correct.
Yeah, that's what you are doing.
Pretty good.
I like this new meme of names that make people retarded.
Those are good.
I like this new meme of the past time when it's all this desperately trying to cover
up with something to say and then two people talking about it nervously chuckling at one
other.
Other people are just fucking panicking right now.
Just sweating.
Just sweat.
Like bill bullets off their fucking forehead.
Okay, okay.
It's okay.
They're filling up time.
Okay.
Oh, fucking thank, thank, thank.
All right.
That comes courtesy of Big John, who by the way, Big John and Little John are comparably
sized with one another.
Okay.
I just want to put that out there.
Is it a question of personality who fills the room with their charisma?
It's more like Big John is older and was here first.
Pokemon Go.
Here we go.
Pokemon Go topic.
Yeah, let's do it.
I have a thing to say.
Pokemon Go podcast.
PGP, everybody.
Because this is the only thing that I'm constantly doing that isn't just, hey guys, I'm working.
It's like Pokemon Go.
There was a new update where they have allowed for a short period of time, you can send gifts
to friends and stuff.
And sometimes you get like a special, a lowland egg that takes like seven kilometers to open.
And recently they updated it for like a Gen 1 special event where they try to get everybody
to complete their Gen 1 Pokedex by releasing all the Pokemon, all the legendaries are in
raids, and all the Gen 1 Pokemon are all over the place.
But the thing they did that made me really mad and rarer, I'm going to fight, I'm going
to kill, is that they made the Gen 1 region exclusives available in these eggs so that
people don't have to go around the world to catch them anymore.
They can just wait for them to be...
I heard about this on a video by some YouTuber called Gibbentake?
No.
No, you didn't.
This is the first and only place you'll hear about this exclusive news dropped like months
after it stopped being relevant.
But like, it just got me thinking about like how video games are like people feel entitled.
Because I had a lot of people in that comment section of that video by Gibbentake where I
didn't know.
That you didn't make.
That I didn't make.
And they were arguing about like my point that it was bad that this was happening.
And they were saying, oh, but what about the people who can't travel?
What about the people who...
It's good.
It's good because now I can get the thing that I couldn't get before.
Right.
Yeah, their argument basically boiled down to, but I want it.
Why can't I have it?
Yeah.
And it just made me so annoyed.
I don't understand where these people, like, who exists that literally cannot travel ever.
Like, if you're like, I'm 15, I can't travel.
You'll be 18 in three years.
You can get it then.
Like, hold on a second.
To be fair, if you want to get all the region exclusive, you will have to go to, like, if
you have to go to places, you have to go to Japan.
You'll have to go to Europe.
Yeah.
You'll have to, let's say you live in America, so whatever, you're there.
Where else?
Do you have to go like South America?
South America.
This should give you something to strive to, all right?
Yes.
It's expensive to fly to Japan.
Yeah.
That means you should bust your ass and get a job and work really hard and save up your
money so you can get that goddamn far-fetched.
I agree.
In terms of opportunity costs, like, I would argue that, like, the time spent getting a full
Pokedex other than the region exclusives is, like, way bigger.
Yes.
Like, it's a huge commitment.
And especially now with trades, it's not even that you have to go there.
You can just meet someone who's been there.
And how great is that?
You'll be able to meet someone in real life.
You can't trade over online, so you'll meet someone in real life just down the street
or, you know, at your local park or something.
And you'll ask, oh, where'd you get this far-fetched?
Oh, I was in Japan.
I was serving in the standing Japanese army during 1943.
And they're like, wow, you must have done some real nice things.
And he was like, yeah, I did.
And he got the far-fetched.
Wait, was that like a rape of Nan King joke?
Yes, it did.
Okay, good.
I was just checking.
I say it every time about this stuff, but this 100% comes down to just different conceptions
of how the world should be.
Like, if you're, like, a 15-year-old kid, like, obviously you don't have a lot of money right now
and you want to complete your Pokedex, you're going to be, like, bummed out that you don't have enough money
to, like, go to Japan and get far-fetched.
I mean, you're already five years late to start your Pokemon journey.
Okay, fair enough, fair enough.
But, like, so you'll want to do it.
But, like, it'll be hard and it'll be, like, you'll have to find someone online.
And, like, what I'd like this person to do is, like, go online, research, find people in their area
who, like, maybe have been there.
And, like, kind of, I want them to rise to the occasion.
But a lot of people don't want to do that.
They just want to, you know, have things lower down to make it easy for them to do it.
Find someone who's got a phone from that, like, just buy phones from people
who've collected the Pokemon from those regions.
There you go.
I want to know.
I want to know how many of these people, like, how many of these people have a full Pokedex
aside from the region exclusive?
I'm going to bet none.
I'm going to bet, like, zero, zero percent.
I've heard the argument, simply so this is a well-rounded piece of conversation here,
I've heard the argument that the game has been out for so long
that all the people who would have been able to get the regionals would have got them already.
Which I think is the stupidest thing I've ever heard in my entire life.
Like, literally, even if you grow up three years and in three years,
you'll be able to potentially do it.
And, I mean, not that you're limited by being 15 necessarily.
But, like, even if it was literally impossible for you to ever go to Japan
or meet anyone from Japan and get that Lapras, who cares?
Right.
I really come back to that.
Who cares?
Like, guys, there's a problem.
People don't like.
People have a huge problem with the fact that the world is in fact hierarchical.
People hate that, and they think it's unfair.
But, I'm sorry.
It's not even a matter of hierarchy to me so much as just that this is what the conceit of the game is.
Like, it's not that being able to travel makes you a better person,
it's just that this is what the game's purpose is.
It's maybe not meant for people who don't travel.
Like, yeah.
It's almost like it's a social game that's meant for you to travel to different places
to catch different types of Pokemon.
It's almost like that's the goal of the game.
I do sympathize with people who are, like, let's say they're really poor,
but they have a smartphone with Pokemon Go somehow.
Okay, fine.
I'm sure that could happen in some cases.
I do feel for those people, but I just care so much more about preserving, like,
the ability of people to, like, challenge themselves and, like,
accomplish things and, like, obtain greatness by working really hard
and, like, getting exclusive things.
I know this is a silly example of a Pokemon Go game,
but that's so much more important to me
than, like, making sure everyone gets the fucking participation trophy
of a fucking, you know, gimme Pokemon.
And I just need to reiterate, because this is not, like,
like, these are all great points, but this is not an issue of you having to go to Asia anymore.
You literally don't.
Okay, Google search.
Like, the name of your city.
Pokemon Go Discord.
Boom.
You will have, like, 30 fucking people.
You will have, like, thousands of the Pokemon that you want.
Meet up with someone in real life at a nice sunny park,
actually play the game, engage with people socially,
and you'll be able to get the Pokemon you want
for, like, you know, a high amount of stardust.
Who cares?
You don't have to spend literally any money.
I'm sure there's people who are really frustrated by the fact that, like,
there's no online trading, so they can just, like, do it all from home.
But that is not what the game is.
That is not what the game is.
That's not the point of the game is to say you're home.
The point is to go out and walk around.
I'm still, like, completely baffled by spoofers.
Like, the idea of playing the game.
Like, there was this one time when I was, like, there was a raid,
and it was a five-star raid, and I was by myself, and there was no one around.
I was like, well, let's just jump in and see what happens.
I'm not going to win, but, you know, whatever.
I jump in, and then, like, 17, like, level 40 spoofers jump in out of nowhere,
and I'm like, oh, shit, I'm going to get this guy.
And it turns out that these level 40 spoofers just, like, I guess they have,
like, a program that jumps into people to raids that are currently, like,
have people in them to leech off of the, you know, the battle,
because none of them were actually doing anything.
They were just sitting there, hoping that, you know, whatever group had started
the raid would complete it, and then they would catch the Pokemon.
What in the fuck is a spoofer?
It is a person who plays Pokemon Go indoors, like, with a program
that allows them to cheat and go anywhere.
Yeah.
And it's like, the whole idea of Pokemon Go, like, if you strip away the walking
outside and, you know, the experience of being, like, catching Pokemon in real life
and being an explorer and moving and walking and doing all that stuff,
it's not really that good a game that, like, you just tap the screen.
Is there a monetary benefit to doing this?
No.
I mean, technically...
Could sell your account, possibly, maybe?
I guess people might do that.
Because it makes me think about how, like, in World of Warcraft,
like, a lot of botting and shit like that just...
Yeah, for the sake of selling accounts.
Okay, okay.
Niantic has specifically, like, engineered their trading system
in a...
In trying to make it so that, like, World of Warcraft's steam markets can't exist,
which I think personally as a Team Fortress 2 trader is fucking gay as hell
and it's literally the funnest thing about any video game ever
is spending real-life money to buy, like, ones and zeros
that make your character look cooler.
I think that's literally the funnest part of Team Fortress 2,
so I'm fucking upset that there is no underground market for, like...
Well, I mean, sure, but those markets are, like, super illegal and unregulated and, like...
Yeah, it's great! It's fucking cool!
I mean, it's all, like, untaxed purchases going back and forth, so...
Yeah, okay.
I mean, I don't think the gambling side of things there has been much discussion about.
Like, I'm sure that the reason those companies don't want this to happen
is because they don't want the government to start telling them they have to do something to regulate it.
You know?
Of course, of course.
Um, and so they're just like, fuck it, we'll make it so they can't.
Yeah, well, you know...
So, since Hippo brought up the video game I don't give a shit about and know nothing about,
I'm gonna talk about, just to you, Nate,
I started playing Final Fantasy IX and...
Oh, great! Fantastic.
I started playing Final Fantasy VI, so fuck you!
I'm in this conversation too now!
And...
And I ruined it...
I ruined it for myself immediately with fucking Tetra Master.
Oh!
Yeah, that'll, uh...
If I remember correctly, I think Tetra Master was my favorite card game, though it might be the one from 8.
I remember, I played the one from 8 a lot more, but I never actually beat 9, so...
Yeah.
I think the games, like, regularly had card games in them.
They do?
I tried them when I played these when I was a teenager.
Tetra Master...
I guess they don't know anything past, like, 11, so...
Tetra Master's a fucking nightmare.
And...
Yeah.
It was like...
Hell yeah!
So, here's what happened to me.
So, for anyone who doesn't know what this is...
Triple Pride, that's the one for me.
In Final Fantasy IX, there is this card game that you can play with, like, half of the fucking NPCs in the game.
Like, you just walk up to them and press X, and you'll just start up this very bizarre, um, like...
I guess...
Do-da-do-da-do-da-do-da-do-da-do.
Oh wait, that's the 8 one.
I guess how we describe it is, like, go.
Like, the Japanese game go, but with cards.
Kind of.
Right, right.
And the thing is, the game deliberately doesn't tell you any of the fucking rules of the game.
No, it doesn't.
Not a one.
It purposefully keeps it obscure, and at first I thought that was kind of neat, and I was like,
oh, I'll learn the game through playing it.
I mean, while getting all your fucking cards taken by the enemy.
Yeah, so the way this game works is that if you lose, the enemy takes one of your cards, and if you win, you take one of their cards.
But so, if you're just trying to figure out the fucking rules of the game, and almost everyone is stronger than you,
then you can literally lose enough cards that you can never play the game again.
Like, if you have...
You can get cards later, but I mean, yeah, you can fuck yourself up real bad.
So, I didn't really start engaging with the game until I got the Lindblum,
and by that point, the enemies were all too strong, and I didn't understand the game,
so I was just like, man, I feel like I should have collected a shitload of cards at the start of the game
and just hoarded them so that I could have a buffer of stuff I could lose.
So I started the game over, and in the beginning part where you're playing as Vivi,
I got my five cards, and I just started challenging this one dude over and over again,
and just like, just raking him for...
I had like 30 slimes, and all I would use is slimes in every battle.
I was doing this like an hour and a fucking half.
Flans, I mean.
And so, I'm trying to take this guy's whole deck, which I don't think you can actually do,
I'm not sure, but I'm just taking this guy's cards for a long time,
and finally, I start challenging other people and immediately getting my ass kicked,
and I'm just like, what is this game?
So I finally just, I'm like, I'm gonna look up the fucking rules, I'm just gonna read them,
and then I read all the rules and I'm like, oh, it's a nightmare.
It's like, not only is the game extremely complicated,
but like, there's like cards that there's only one of in the game.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
And if you get that card, you're gonna have to use it eventually to get other cards that there's only one of,
and if you were to lose that card in a match, you have to then win it back in the next match,
or else it will just be gone forever.
That's right, that's correct.
And you will never complete your card deck.
Completing the card deck is considered like the most, like, difficult task.
It's prestigious.
Yeah, it's prestigious for sure.
So when I found all that out...
I mean, if you basically imagine, just imagine playing Final Fantasy IX,
not even like, to save the world, or do any of the stuff, it's just,
you're in there to become Setokaiba and have all the blue-eyed white dragons
and destroy the purple one.
That's one of the things I love about the Final Fantasy games,
is the PS1 one.
Well, the thing about, it's really frustrating, because in Final Fantasy,
they always put in something that like, there's like a challenge that would be fun,
except that there's that one thing that's so fucking impossible, that like,
you're just like, there's no way it would remain fun.
Like, as soon as I read the full rules and like, what to expect,
I was like, this will obviously stop being fun at some point,
so I should just stop now before I get disappointed.
I mean, that's fair.
So there is a tournament I think you have to compete in at some point in the game.
Do you have to compete in it? I think you do.
In Final Fantasy X, for example, there's like, if you go back to certain towns,
you have to fight like, insanely powerful versions of the Aeons,
and like, the only way you're gonna have a chance is if you have the ultimate weapons for your characters.
But to get one of the ultimate weapons involves dodging 100 consecutive lightning bolt strikes
in this one place, and predicting them and dodging them is not impossible,
because the controls are not built for this, so like,
and you have to do it 100 times in a row.
Yeah, I did it.
I did it.
You actually did that?
Of course I fucking did it.
How long did it take you?
I mean, the time I did it was like, when it first came out when I first played the game.
I mean, it took me hours. It took me a couple hours to get it done, I think.
Just a couple hours? I spent a couple hours trying to dodge 10 in a row.
Damn. I mean, it gives you some warning with like, the rumble of the thunder or something.
I'm sure dodging 100 lightning bolt sounds really hard to some people,
but we live in a post undertale world.
I spent six hours beating Sans. There's nothing that I can't do.
As a white male in America who beats Sans, there's literally nothing society can stop you from doing.
Did you also beat the jump rope minigame with Vivi in 9?
Oh, there's progressive difficulties. I don't think I ever beat the topmost one.
I beat like the 50 instead of like 200 or whatever the top one is,
but yeah, that one was pretty tough too.
That one I just got fed up with, because like, the reward I looked up and it like, wasn't that great,
so I didn't worry about it that much.
All the rewards are cards.
Cards. Yeah. Okay. There you go. There you go.
It was fun though. I mean, I love that Final Fantasy puts in that kind of stuff,
and you have the freedom to fucking do it or not.
I mean, that's some reason why I love those games so much.
I just wish they made it, I really wish they made it more.
Like, with the Tentrum Master, it's fine, because it's like, it's whole other own world,
but I also wish, because it is actually fun, that like, there was a version of it that wasn't a huge pain in the ass.
I hear that's what Gwent is for Witcher 3 people. Yeah, they just love playing that game so much.
But I would say that Triple Triad from Final Fantasy VIII, I have to say, is the best.
Like, it's fairly simple, and it's the best of any of the Final Fantasy mini-games,
which is why, incidentally, just unrelatedly, I'm real sad that Final Fantasy VII, VIII, X and XII
are all being ported to Switch, but notably VIII is just being ignored and skipped.
What?
Yeah, they're skipping VIII, they're just skipping VIII.
Also, it's coming to like, Xbox and Polypies 4 and something.
I never understood, I never really understood. People shit on VIII.
They sure do.
Like, it's like a, I don't know, would you say it's like a Dark Horse in that like, era?
It's the most oppressed race in all of gaming, Final Fantasy VIII fans.
Somehow, I feel like it's even less popular than X.
X is awesome.
X is beloved, X is beloved.
Is it? I don't know.
I played it recently and I literally plotted out an entire book.
I wanted to write about it.
That's how excited I was about X.
What? Why?
Hey, did I ever tell you?
I didn't like X as much.
I think age is superior to X for me, but whatever.
This reminds me.
I liked it more than XII.
There, I said it.
Oh, alright, fine, fine.
The first brain-embigging panel I ever went to at an anime convention was something called like,
Final Fantasy X and like, Tidus in the role of Ubermensch, or like something like that.
It was just about how Tidus is like, yeah, it was pretty dope.
It was very brain-long.
I will say my analysis does not incorporate such elements.
I don't.
Okay, alright.
Such elements.
Tidus being the, ah!
So yesterday, I went out, ah!
Yesterday, that scene is, that scene makes sense in the game by the way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I agree.
People name that scene so ridiculously hard.
Like deliberately misunderstood.
Jason Arnold, or whatever his name, James Arnold Taylor, the voice actor.
He himself on his own YouTube channel.
Jonathan Taylor Thomas.
Like, a decade later, no, whatever, James Arnold Taylor.
He made a video, like, just clarifying, like, in extensive detail.
And he pulls out the script he was given from Square when he recorded the game.
And it shows an explicit detail, like, all the reasons why he was intended to be forced.
You should be able to tell that immediately by watching the scene.
I know.
People don't, people don't actually know what they're looking at.
It's Spoonie's fault.
Spoonie made fun of it.
It is Spoonie's fault.
He fucking didn't get it because he didn't like the game and he's returning.
Because, I mean, that's, that's Spoonie being very nostalgia critic by just misunderstanding
what that, like, scene is actually.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, you know, Spoonie, you know, Spoonie's dead and nostalgia critic is disgraced.
It looks like those hacks got what was coming to him, just like we all will one day.
Yeah, it's true.
It's coming.
First they came for nostalgia critic and I said nothing.
And I said nothing.
Then they came for Spoonie and I enjoyed it and laughed.
So yesterday I thought, hey, this is just getting better and better.
Yesterday at long last.
I can't wait for the next one.
God damn it, Ben!
Why are you laughing so hard at this?
Yesterday I went out to the local game stores, the local big used game stores finally, which
are amazing out here in Boston land.
Oh, cool.
I went in search of Melee.
You can't find Melee anywhere.
I'll give you Melee for price.
Fucking Mewtwo King bought every copy in the world.
He's hoarding them right now.
Just like Saddlekai, but he's got all the blue eyes, white dragons.
What I did, however, impulse purchase was Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles.
And then six hours later found out that they literally that day announced a port to the
Switch.
Dude, online play for Crystal Chronicles.
Come to the fucking Switch or whatever.
Does it have couch multiplayer?
Does it have what?
You know, I don't know.
Probably, but I mean, the Switch is built for couch multiplayer, but I didn't check.
And I'm very glad that I did not do what I almost did and buy several Game Boy Advance
SP link cables because I didn't think I had enough Game Boys.
Because for those who don't know, Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles has the worst local multiplayer
of all time.
Right.
Where it requires everyone to have a link cable for their GBA to the GameCube so that
you can have a map screen on the GBA screen.
And one of the players has to carry the crystal chalice at all times.
So.
Right.
That's right.
Like basically you have to fight within this little circle that is surrounding this chalice
and one of the players just has to carry the fucking chalice and that's all you get to
do.
But like you can have four players play this game, but one of them is always stuck with
the chalice.
By the way, I'm just looking it up.
Local multiplayer has not been confirmed, but online has.
But here's the hilarious, I was looking this up and I found out that you can play the game
with GameCube controllers as long as you have the Game Boy Advance link cable plugged in when
it loads the level, and then you can swap it out for a GameCube controller and play
it perfectly fine.
So what you're telling me is they really just were doing this to push system sales of GBAs
or something.
Yeah.
I mean big time is for the link cable.
This is also why Four Swords Adventures happened.
These are like around the same time and then they horribly bombed and so they did not
do this again.
Digi, you know what we should do is you and me should do a playthrough of Kirby's Amazing
Mirror is what we should do next time.
I want to play that.
That's my literal favorite Kirby game.
That is the best one.
What do you mean by that?
That's four players.
It's four players, right?
Yeah.
It's four players multiple GBAs.
Oh, I did not know that.
Yeah.
That's sick.
That's a really good one.
I mean I guess if we all meet up in a place and we all have GBAs and link cables, that
can happen.
When are we going to do another Radcom?
Never.
It's banned.
When are we going to do another games?
I want to play video games with my band games.
We should do a Shekels for Hekels and one for Crystal Chronicles when it comes out.
It's a fun one.
It's a game I've never played.
There's like sequel Crystal Chronicles games, but I've never played the original one.
Good.
I've got, well, because I've played, I mean, I bought it again.
I had it when I was younger.
It doesn't play anything like any Final Fantasy game.
It's just an action RPG with like, the level, it kind of just puts you on a level that's
like 20 minutes long and usually you just got to solve a couple puzzles and fight a
bunch of enemies and get to the end and it's just a pleasant little happy time, but it's
got really cool character designs and great music, great art design.
But what about the Chalice?
I thought the Chalice just was terrible.
Well, if you're playing on single player, then you've just got a Mugle that carries
it around for you.
So it's not even a big deal on single player mode.
On multiplayer, it's just a bad game.
Okay, cool.
But on single player, it's perfectly fine.
And then I also bought a Fantasy Star Online, which is the greatest game of all time, Word.
Word.
There's a lot of videos going around right now.
It's like arrows flying over your head in the Indian and Joe's ride Disneyland.
It's just like constantly...
When is my stupid switch owning roommate going to stop being a coward and buy Splatoon
2?
You could buy it.
Yeah, yeah.
I could.
He's got Zelda, he's got Mario Odyssey, but he doesn't have Splatoon 2.
Blown the fuck out by Joseph Anderson, no thanks.
Ben, you know you could just come over here and play it because Tom has a switch.
And that's true.
I'm fairly sure he has Splatoon 2 because he really loves Splatoon.
Maybe I'll do that.
Maybe I'll come over there and be Splatoon 2.
Yeah, it's a good idea.
I recently started playing Metal Gear Solid 1 with my friends and it was totally like
the eye-clap from when I saw it, experience, and willingly and happily, whenever we saw
any sound effect or character, we just went like, I love Solid Snake!
Yeah.
That's the peak experience.
And then when we heard the brand, we just like jumped up from our seats and just clapped,
it's hard as we fucking could, like every single thing that we could, we did.
My friend's mom can testify, we were fucking tearing up the house to see Metal Gear happen.
Every time a new asset appeared on screen.
What happened when you saw my Japanese enemies?
Oh, okay, like me and my friend, Leif, we basically know what was up with Metal Gear
2 to an extent.
My friend Kyle and the Tories Furry, and I've called that many times on the show, bitch,
did not know.
So the entire time, me and Leif were building this the fuck up saying like, Kyle, Kyle,
it's you, you're gonna be on screen soon, it's gonna be you, then I'm gonna start pissing
his pants, and then we jumped up and we started making fun, like Kyle, this is you, you're
a bitch!
Fuck you!
And it was great.
It was, you know, something like...
It was great time.
Fairly owned.
Yeah, we just beat the tank guy, it was a horrible experience.
Vulcan Raven.
The game is scary and awful, and makes up, like, it's like, like, migraines, but visually...
Have you gotten to the part where you have to machine gun down dogs yet?
No, oh, we started to play the first Metal Gear game, and that was a fucking, that was
a trip.
That was a, that was...
Oh, the NES one.
Yeah, I didn't use to emphasize with, you know, prisoners of war and Poland being reduced
to gulags and forced labor, but now I do have to play one video game, and I understand
what it was like for them.
It was a great time.
And too bad the PS3 we were playing on is gone forever, because Kyle moved away, and everyone's
moving away, and this is the part of my life that's in movies, and it's happening right
now.
Oh, they're going to college now, huh?
Yeah, all my friends are gone.
It's like that.
It'll happen again.
This'll happen again when you start to get, like, 50 or 60, only this time they're all
moving to hell.
Munchy, it's literally your favorite Green Day song.
The one that's...
Oh, dude, I want to let you know that literally that night was the last time I saw Kyle, and
for the entire car ride home, we fucking blasted good riddance as loud as we could and screamed
the lyrics.
The lyrics which are as follows.
Tell me why'd you have to go make things so complicated?
See the way, act like somebody else gets me frustrated.
I love that song.
I love the gorillas.
It's crazy.
Everyone's leaving.
I thought it was a joke that people said, like, oh, your friends are going to leave,
and I was like, psh, nah, and then there they are.
They're all going to go off to become boarders managers.
You got to do what I do, Munchy.
Establish an organization that entraps the people that you want to keep nearby with monetary
incentives.
Yeah, financially.
That's the way to do it.
Yeah.
You got to bait the hook.
Keep them around.
Otherwise, they'll be.
Otherwise, what do you want to be lonely?
What do you want to be abandoned?
Yeah.
Exactly.
Watch the fuck out.
It's this or nothing.
I've got a topic that was kind of brought up.
No, you don't.
I do.
It was brought up via, well, I was reminded of it, because a couple of things.
Munchy was talking about Pokemon Go, and Isabel got confirmed for Smash, which is cool.
And there is a connection, and it's that she's a dog, and it's that I got a dog.
I got a dog recently.
What?
I saw, I saw the dog.
I'm keeping it under wraps.
I saw it on Twitter.
I have a dog.
You got a dog.
This is the happiest I've ever become on a PCP episode.
And his name?
His name is Lord Sashomaru.
Is this full name?
No.
Come on.
That's his full name.
Dude, that's crazy.
Your dog is Lord Sashomaru, and my cat is Killala.
Killala.
I thought of that, too.
I fucking can't even believe it.
The Inuyasha permeates the culture.
So what do you say when you're calling the dog?
We call him Sessho.
Call him Sessho.
Come here, Sessho.
Sessho.
You got to call him Sessho.
That was the fan girl nickname for Sashomaru.
Was that true?
Okay, good to know.
Good to know.
Probably mix that one in there, too.
Yeah, he's a great guy.
What kind of dog is he?
Okay, get this.
He looks like a small German Shepherd, or a German Shepherd combined with a Chihuahua.
But in actuality, he is half Beagle, half Welsh Corgi.
I see.
It's very strange.
I'm not saying he's a men pin, but no, he's just a freak.
He is a freak.
He's a weird genetic slurry.
Indeed.
That's him?
Isn't it funny what we've done to dogs as a race?
I just sit back and laugh.
Just mess them right the fuck up.
We got him from the SPCA or whatever, like the shelter, and he had recently, like within
like a couple of weeks, gotten his balls removed, and he still has a dangling empty ball sack.
It is quite horrific.
It's just nightmarish to think about, really.
I feel so bad for him.
Why do they...
Why does he just have the sack and not the balls?
Well, apparently the sack like shrinks into the body or like it goes away to some degree
at some point.
Yeah.
Erasing all traces of sexuality.
Thank God.
My dog has a literal genetic dysfunction where he has a boner 100% of the time.
Is that true?
They're told it's painful.
Yeah.
That sounds real.
You got to help him out, dog.
You got to help him out.
I mean, they say you're supposed to go to the hospital after a mere four hours.
Consider an entire lifetime.
It really gets in the way of new dates.
Yeah.
By the way.
If anyone out there wants to make fan art, I've got a picture in my mind of I am...
You know Rin, the little girl who hangs out with Lord Sashomaru?
That's me.
The dog is Lord Sashomaru and Michelle is that little gremlin jack-in who hangs out
and just dances and does kind of Jewish shanties around to announce Lord Sashomaru's presence.
I demand that you become a basic bitch and send us cute dog photos on a regular basis.
Don't do that.
Do not do that.
If you do that, you better make a fucking containment chat.
Yeah.
Why?
I don't want to see that shit.
What's wrong with dog?
Why?
What's wrong with you guys?
Look, I saw one picture of the dog.
I get it.
I'm not kidding about this.
I have seen none and I get it.
And I didn't even hear it described.
I got up to piss before he started describing it so I wouldn't have to hear it.
I want to see dog photos.
I just thought it was an interesting change in my life because actually I feel a ton of responsibility now
and it's a huge burden in the good way, just something I have to worry about now.
What's it like being able to try and raise a child?
This is the basic training.
So far, so good.
Doesn't hate you yet?
He doesn't hate me yet, but he's building up to it.
I can see it in his eyes.
He's building up to it.
He's waiting to spring that on me at my weakest moment.
But it's good.
So that shows he's a good lad, but I'm waiting.
How old is he?
Oh, he's just under a year.
So he's a year old.
So he's basically full-grown.
He's small.
Yeah, okay.
I wasn't sure if he was a puppy or not.
Is he for leisure or for pleasure?
He's for farm use.
He's not for pleasure.
I don't know.
Maybe you need a guard dog.
I know you live in Cincinnati, which is a nightmare.
That's true.
He's for pleasure.
He's for my pleasure.
Indeed.
Anyway, that's about it.
I would say probably I'll post pictures on Instagram if anywhere else.
So I mean, you can call me there if you care to.
So there you go, people.
Munchie, did you not know that I already have a dog?
No.
And I also post...
Sunny.
Wait, wait, wait.
I didn't know you post images.
On Instagram.
And sometimes Twitter.
Oh, I don't follow any of your Instagram, so they don't use Instagram.
Same.
It's a good place to put dogs and cats.
It's where normie things go.
Normie things go on Instagram.
That's how I think of it.
Hmm.
I don't have any normie things.
The most normie thing I did this week was have a fucking sance in my house.
Yeah.
Fucking...
I went for a walk.
Mm-hmm.
Because it was, you know, late and I forgot to spin my poker stop for the day.
Of course.
Gotta hit that.
And I went out and it was dark.
And Luna, my cat, decided to come with us as she sometimes does.
Walking like...
It's very strange if you've ever had a cat walk with you, like go on a walk with you.
We were going through the park.
Cats like to go where they think you're going.
So she would like wait for a bit and then gallop like as fast as she possibly could.
Like at marked speed.
Like 100 meters in front of us and then turn around and wait for us.
So you can like take your cat out and she'll like follow you around?
Yeah, it's weird.
I think what she does, I think that she saw that we take the dog for a walk.
And like part of her is like, I want to be included in that.
So when she's outside and we go outside, she jumps out from the bushes and says,
I'm coming with you.
Mm-hmm.
And it's very...
That's actually amazing.
I lived with a cat.
I lived with a cat who was the opposite of that, who if the door was ever opened,
she would bolt and just run.
Sounds like a captive prisoner.
Yeah.
Oh.
No comment.
How do we know that this person isn't what, you know, Peter Pettigrew was in Harry Potter.
Which is a, you know, a transmogrified human attempting to seek escape.
Listen, I tried to put a harness and a leash on this cat.
It was the scariest thing that ever happened.
Jesus Christ.
All right.
She went completely ballistic.
Trying to get it off was a nightmare too, because she just ran into a corner traumatized
by the fact that she was wearing a thing.
I tried to walk her into the backyard and it was going okay for like two seconds.
Like for two seconds there was like a solid hope like, oh, maybe she's over it.
Maybe she can like walk around on this little cat harness and a little leash.
Wait, wait, okay.
Until I stepped on a twig, until I stepped on a twig and she went nuts and like flew up
to the end of the leash and was like, bah!
I was like, like spun around on the leash like a tether ball.
Like a taut tether ball on a cord.
Okay, I must have missed something.
Were you attempting to expose your therapy on this cat by trying to get her like acclimatized
to like being outside that she wouldn't run away?
Yeah, I was trying.
Sounds like it, right?
The idea was to try and like get her used to wearing this harness so she could be taken
on catwalk.
Makes sense, you know, relatively.
Yeah.
Well, that was a failure.
Yeah, yeah.
Completely failure.
But hey, I just wanted to say that about this Pokemon Go thing, I just love Pokemon Go
because I'll go walk with Sessho and we'll just walk.
It's a little bit of a longer walk, but I'm kind of glad.
It gets me out and doing stuff all the way down to the Pokestop on the end of the road.
And I hit that and then I walk back and it's a great time and I love doing it.
And I'm happy to have an excuse to go do more things.
So I'm getting over the initial anxiety of getting a new responsibility in this dog
and getting way into just the benefits.
And I'm raking them in.
This dog is paying dividends.
This is just such a perfect breeding grounds for fatherly attributes.
You can test out the dad joke.
Are you a Pokemon Sessho?
Literally every single time you walk here to get the exact perfect cadence
so that you can torment your kids every day of their lives.
That's true.
That's absolutely true.
And I look forward to doing so.
I can't wait for the day when Pokemon Go is an old man thing and I'm still doing it.
Hey, by the way.
All the kids are hip and they don't do it and they think it's gay.
That'll be great.
All the kids are playing Fortnite Go.
They're all walking around with VR headsets or whatever.
I'm shooting each other.
This was absolutely incredible to me.
So when we're actually getting Sessho, it was crazy.
We go to the SPCA or whatever it's called, the dog place.
And we look at all the dogs.
And Sessho is by far the cutest and the strongest dog in the whole place.
And so we're like, okay, he seems like he's got kids going places.
So we get him.
And then we go up to the desk and I'm like, all right, what's the damage?
How much for this fucking piece of shit asshole dog?
And they're just like, with that plus the color and the leash,
that'll come down to, they're like bracing me forth.
They're like $56.
And I'm like, this is like a life we're talking about.
It's only $56.
Okay.
And then they hit me with this bombshell.
They're like, okay, but there's something you need to know.
And I'm like, oh shit, what's it going to be?
You can have this.
There is a 30 day return policy.
And if you are one fucking fraction of a split fucking second late,
you'll be on this 30, 30 day policy.
And you bring this dog back anytime.
We will not take it back without paying the fee.
And I'm like, what's the fee?
$14.
I was just like, guys, relax.
That's like, by the way, you can just leave a dog there for free.
So like, why do you even have to pay anything?
I don't know.
You can leave a dog there for free, but you can't return a dog.
I mean, it's a charity.
Without paying $14.
Just like a man and a dog outside.
And like, they'll, you know, do it.
Oh, okay.
So that's what I'm incentivized to do, to just drop him off, tie him to a fucking post,
pound it into the ground, and then just skid off on my fucking sick electric skateboard.
Like hog time and leave him on the doorstep.
Exactly.
How much time has this taken up?
Stuff an apple in its mouth.
Well, I mean, this was like the week where, oh, do you mean just like getting the dog or since having him?
No, since having him.
Like, like how much maintenance do you have on this guy?
Very little, honestly.
Very little.
It's been, I mean, he honestly has a great attitude.
So like, he has not been up in my shit.
He's been like hanging with me when I was like streaming the other day.
He was in the room and like didn't cause a peep.
He's been real good.
He's sparked like ten times.
How fucking poor are these people like getting dogs from SPCA that they're like having to
brace you for the news that it'll be $56?
Not to be overly condescending, but like honestly, there was a lot of poor people there.
Getting dogs.
So like I could, I could, I got the impression economically.
Absolutely.
Yes.
But like dogs make you happier.
Statistically speaking, maybe not digi here.
I mean, I mean, what do you think?
What do you think it costs like on a weekly basis to maintain a dog?
He doesn't really.
Honestly, not a lot.
I mean, all you really have to pay for is food.
Dog food is all you need pretty much.
And that's like, I don't know, maybe up to 40, maybe $50 a week.
I mean, I have no cons of it.
That's probably way too much.
Feeding your $40 to feed your dog.
That was a retarded guess.
We bought one bag for probably $20.
I don't even eat $40 of food in a week.
Okay.
Honestly, it's probably like $10.
Maybe.
Not even that.
There you go.
All right.
Enough dog talk.
I wasn't trying to bore everybody with the dog talk, but, I like the dog talk.
I wish she was the only dog talk.
We're getting dangerously close to dream.
Sheer.
What's the word?
What's the word for when something doesn't matter?
Sheer.
Irrelevance.
All right.
Yeah.
I'm unbelievably uninteresting.
C.G.P.
Gray has been, I've listened to his latest Hello, Internet episodes and he is going on
a, not a crusade.
He's got a operation Cyclops, which is.
I don't have a way of what this is.
To cut out social media usage, podcasts, Reddit, and just generally internet usage that is
clearly wasting his time and the sort of stuff that he checks without thinking.
Yeah.
Good guy.
I like you.
I'm really into that.
I've been into that for a while, but I've never gone like full force on it because I do
kind of like, you know, it's, well, I mean, you justify it to yourself in a lots of ways.
Yeah.
I was talking about like in that, you know, let's play or something about a similar sort
of thing.
Yeah.
I'm like, I was inspired by M dot strange because I've been like watching a bunch of
his blogs and he has his attitude towards social media is that he has never even bothered
with it.
Like he pretty much identified it as a bunch of horse shit from the beginning and just
like, like out of pocket makes fun of it and is just like, yeah, it's totally worthless.
And I'm like, this is a guy with a career as an internet content creator telling you
that you don't need social media to do that.
So like, why am I tricking myself into thinking I do, you know, good question.
Yeah.
So I was thinking about all that stuff and I'm like, what do I do?
Like I could, I could feel when you're in the paradox of needing to be social media
plugged into a podcast to tell you to get off the internet and stop wasting your time.
I mean, they they talked about that in the hell of internet podcast was like, well, it's
what are you going to say to our listeners then?
Right.
Yeah.
But I think I don't think of a podcast as social media, though.
Well not so.
I mean, CGP Gray was was more about like things that eat up his time that he could do Twitter
obviously and like whatever for me, like podcasts and like long YouTube videos.
Like from the thing, the thing that I should probably unplug from immediately is like, I'll
start up my day and I'll just start my day by like starting up some like some long like
analysis video or something.
I don't know.
Listen to like start up an old like, I don't know, a Matthew Matosis or some yeah, start
up a red letter media to a playlist or something and it'll just go throughout the whole day
and I'll be like, well, just leave it on in the background.
I won't pay attention to it, but like, at some point, at some point I start paying attention
to it and at that point it becomes a waste of time.
That's why ASMR is great because nothing in it is important at all, but just having sound
is helpful.
Just like is this podcast ASMR, nothing in this podcast is helpful at all.
Well, I recommend Ben instead of throwing on interesting analysis videos, just throw
on needle drop videos because I almost apparently uninteresting.
That is deeply uninteresting to me.
So like even more so than you.
That would work.
I mean, probably the best thing, the best thing for me is to put on music.
Like when I put on music, it helps me focus, but I don't care about that.
I can't man, music's too distracting, but whatever it's not just well, I think music
I listen to music that isn't distracting fucking do you like my car, you know, put on
Future Funk and Baby Waves mix, mix-taves.
Yeah, I guess this guy doesn't even know shit about sludge fest.
He's not even listening to raw, slow down, Alvin the Chipmunks, he's not listening to
Country Eye Joe dubstep pre-mixes, he doesn't know what the place is going on.
I was just putting, I was just starting, just starting, Hillary Duff, where'd you come from?
Where'd you go?
Hillary Duff, come rain night four, put on autoplay and just let it go, let it take you
where it may.
Yeah, makes sense.
I've been like to do, to, like I've realized a lot of stuff is just you have your house
and you have your computer and through that you get the internet and everything.
And then like other things in your house are just not there anymore like they used to in
old houses.
Like everybody used to have a piano, everybody used to have like, you know, more like, you
know, you have like the family bike or like a set of tennis racquets or football.
You know, that old slut, they have chained up in the yard, the family bike.
I hear you, I hear you.
Yeah, family bike.
Yeah, rider and all that.
Like, there's just not a lot of stuff in my room and I'm like, like when I don't have
the internet, I have video games, but I don't have like, I'm not a toy guy, I don't play
with toys anymore.
Yeah.
And I threw a lot of them away.
So like, what, what do I get to fill my hours with if not like editing or like, like leisure
hours.
Thinking, yeah.
Yeah.
Literal sitting in the thinker pose for hours on end and you know, yeah, why not?
Why not?
I ask.
I can't think of anything.
Nate, why not?
I don't know.
I'm curious.
Nate, why not?
Would you think with your brain to think about your ideas and who you are?
My ideas.
What's so retarded about that?
My ideas are too dangerous, Munchie.
The world's not ready.
He needs to be distracted from the material goods.
Thinking while that's funny to imagine just sitting down and thinking.
Thinking in the shower is quite good.
I mean, I spend a lot of time just literally sitting and staring at a wall and thinking
about what I'm going to do.
Well, okay.
Literally thinking while doing a manual labor, I find very enjoyable.
Like while doing the dishes can be a very helpful like time to think.
Yeah.
There's only so many dishes.
There's only so many like tools to do.
Yeah.
I'll eat food so I can survive.
I'll drink some water.
Yeah.
Okay.
What I'm trying to get at is that I've started to like right now get more into arts and crafts
in a way that I used to like as a child and a boy.
You mean like macaroni?
No.
I'm crocheting right now.
I'm doing a little crochet and I've realized my brother has like a bunch of like modeling
clay and I'm thinking, yeah, I'm going to get some like tools.
I'm going to model something.
I'm going to make 3D models, but like analog 3D models and like I kind of I kind of want
to get like a wood carving knife.
Oh yeah.
The wristband I made munchy.
I haven't let anything happen to it.
I'm really I appreciate you going down this road hippo.
I feel that I want to start doing something with my hands other than masturbate because
like in Dick Masterson talks about this all the time that like as a man you need to have
like a craft because like it's just something that makes you feel proud of yourself for
like having built something.
And I kind of got a taste of that by putting together Ikea furniture because I built a
bed frame and this fucking mechanical desk I've got and it was just like that sense
of man I took this this looks like it was going to be a pain in the ass and now it's
a thing that I literally use constantly every single day.
Yeah, it's a good feeling.
What if I could just at any time do that like what if I just needed something and I could
just put it together and then have it forever that would feel so badass, you know.
I want it like I think you have to make things like I've always had like like dreams of like
making a fucking real suit of armor with something like chainmail.
It makes sense for me especially because I am so about like customization and like having
everything be just right in my work environment where like I'm always frustrated when I go
out to the store to like buy a shelf and there's no shelf that is the shelf I want.
And so it's like what if I just you know blueprinted out the shelf that I want and then built
that fucking shelf and it would probably be cheaper than trying to buy one.
I mean it's not going to be as pretty but it will be the shelf I want because it doesn't
exist you know.
I have like fantasies of like having an office like Casey Neistat which I consider like Casey
Neistat's office is like his reality marble from Fate Stay Night where it's just like
in there he has infinite power and infinite control over everything that's happening.
Yes.
He should be a Fate Stay Night character and that should be his thing.
I love his office too and it's funny because like when you compare his and MKBHD's like
it's two radically different aesthetic approaches to the same thing.
Both are just very clean, very organized environments but one is like about being uncluttered and
one is about being like immediate.
Casey's is so practical and immediate and we lean towards that one.
I like yeah I definitely lean towards Casey's but like I don't even know if I'd want it
to be so ridiculously organized like he holds on to stuff that he doesn't really need to
like I feel as though he's so attached to having this as much visual noise as possible
and I'm kind of moving away from that because that's how my old room was like I used to
just have anime posters covering every fucking conceivable surface of the room and it was
just like because I wanted it to be like you know the old otaku room pictures you used
to see.
And now I have more appreciation for just like well instead of just covering everything
let's build unique areas like let's think about this wall and what can we make it into
and like not necessarily that it's austere but that there's a theme or an art piece so
that it's like it's not just a chord arrangement that's practical it's like chords arranged
in a to create something like what if you you know spiraled all your chords that are
attached to the wall until like you formed a Pikachu head or something you know.
This image is basically Digi's perfect environment.
His perfect work station.
That's actually pretty great I would not mind that.
Digi no this is a nightmare the whole point of this picture is that it's absolute hell.
I don't know it seems pretty comfy.
This is what like my setup was I mean aside from the fact that it's in a basement this
is like what it kind of was when I was a kid like just a TV on a box and like you got
a fucking you got a husband chair this looks comfy as fuck I mean a husband chair that's
what that's called those are called husbands.
We got to link this one this is a famous meme image of of I literally can't even conceive
of what's wrong with this it looks comfy as long as it's like yeah as long as it doesn't
stink and it's warm does it say rape sucks on the wall and no one knows what that says
I think it says Ray sucks oh yeah it says Ray sucks or is it it might be rare as in
rare abandoned Nintendo to go work with Microsoft I think it's RAYE Ray sucks okay I guess.
All they would need is just like some carpeting like a blanket that would go a long way yeah
well it's like the fucking pliers on the ground and this like shitty towel I mean are these
in the main he probably use the walls and floor aren't good but the actual furnishing
is great I mean I guess it's alright.
Is this is this Jesse's is this the furnace room the furnace room it actually looks worse
than this like this looks more comforting to me than the furnace room how how low how
unfortunate.
I like the two the two the two bottles of water there the two like jugs like once for drinking
and once for peeing in right next to each other and sometimes he makes a little mistake
and grabs the wrong one whoopsie what little oopsie dates.
I mean he's got a great gamer thirst he doesn't have time to stop and check which one he's
grabbing and guzzling currently I'm fairly certain that the VCR is just sitting on top
of a toolbox and the pliers are sitting just outside of the toolbox and I'm thinking he
was probably using them for something with the VCR because every chord you play into
a VCR is like an impossible fucking wait is it I suppose is that is that a portrait of
Iwata yeah it's a torii Iwata okay no way that can't be what that is no it is for Iwata
it is Japan it's a torii Iwata you tell me they love video games he's kind of fucking
oh it's good I mean Iwata is looking real good in this guy it's a real smug I'm I'm
thinking PCPHQ right here I hope we get a set up this good in PCPHQ the love of God let
it happen oh I think okay I studied this picture very closely and I think he's playing
Twilight Princess I think I was wondering what you might be right because if you see those those
like six icons across the top of the screen I think those like the horse whip things you know
how like that could be you hit your horse repeatedly and hands zoom and hands Alexa now
if you want to talk about truly being a poor boy picture if you want it you know this is how
this guy's going to get out of the basement because he has a Gamecube copy of fucking Twilight
Princess and those sell for like a lot he can probably refinance his house on that
Luigi's Mansion is definitely on top of the stack who said gaming doesn't pay I think he's got
fucking fancy star online on the bottom this is a true gamer right here because it looks like the
box all right I mean maybe it's possible I mean it's out like the bottom box is like a color
yeah that white to blue gray it's either like Mario Sunshine visual shit or Sonic Adventure DX
or Fancy Star okay all right well all right does Iwata look a little bit George Costanza-ish
in this picture to anyone I mean I suppose in general oh there's some more pictures of this
well I mean yeah I just found this other one from this definitely confirms that it is Iwata
yeah I mean 100% 100%
oh he's got a hot pocket package like to the left of his TV in the second I think it's like a
chicken pot pie like a frozen pie something like oh wait I do know what I see I see sleeves I see
hot pocket yeah hot on the TV on the milk crate actually it seems like it's more like he's playing
Luigi's looking at this space really is like a tactile experience like I can really feel what
it's like to be there yeah I just I really like the tight and closed spaces because like is like
laying on the ground that's not good oh that is gross yeah like get all just put it on just a towel
on it's a towel on concrete it's literally well let me let me get a dank base I'm gonna go out
on a crazy limb here and say and this this might be racist this is probably an Asian guy
you think so this is just on the basis of my my Asian friends Iwata uh just it's Iwata's
gamer set up he has a picture of himself on the wall walls and floor aside like this is exactly
how my friend Donson would have been playing Gamecube like yeah towel on the ground two water
like two full water jugs like two fucking gallon jugs towel on the ground not towel on the head
and it's because the two water jugs lets me know that this guy does not intend on getting up like
that's true he is not going to stop this sesh although he also has a soda but he probably
just had that for his eating like he clearly ate a plate of something dude the presence of those
water jugs and that like neatly snug fitting box is the most interesting thing here it tells me
this guy is like serious about hardcore gaming incidentally he needs to fuel up what he has
eaten is a banquet pot pie you can see the box for the pot pie I knew it yeah that's right and you
can see the 10 there's also hot pocket things around there's a fucking hidden object game we're
playing yeah playing where's wall though I just feel really comforted by this image in a strange
way it feels like my childhood I I know it's so warmly tinted someone someone please like do a
gif of did you like phasing into this picture like like being absorbed into this world where he's
finally at peace yeah it's like all shitty it's like shitty setups for sat like fantasy novels
like the guy gets sucked into the book it's an isekai this is literally the digi isekai happening
imagine like the opposite of like the getting sucked into the video game where like the
the video game character comes out and then plays the game just sits there and plays the game that
he was trying to do is so easy I think the box that's behind the chair is a glad bag box
like a trash bag trash bags all right guys enough on this fucking picture no I I love this
it's it's it's great I want to I want to go there yeah we all want to be a minute living in this uh
this guy's basement you know what I'm talking about the minish from the minish cap oh yes
living in him from arthur and the invisibles my favorite 3d animated family movie from the 2000s
shout to the guy who made arthur and the invisibles I'm sure he's poor and died yeah
um all right team uh what do we do should we should we go to questions now or anybody else
want to bring up the topic to talk about questions I how long we've been going like an hour and a
half yeah pretty close to an hour and a half did you what's this giant list of topics you've been
talking about have you like what have you written down what are you talking about has he been mentioning
one when did I say anything about a list of topics you said earlier like you've been making an epic
list up all night intending to be on the pcp while making an epic list was the list the list has
nothing to do with the pcp I am just making an epic list and that is why I've been up what what
constitutes an epic list all right here is you want to hear about my list that I'm working on yeah
I'll tell you yeah I do it is called is it a things I want to consume and so number one so okay
you're I think Nate I think you're gonna love this once I've explained it all the way I think
you'll actually be totally down for this idea so what it is is a list of every piece of media
that I want to consume whether it's one that I haven't consumed before or that I want to
re-consume like you know so rewatch replay so far I've gone through anime games books movies and
tv shows so it's just the the the column it's a spreadsheet the columns are as follows format
title time investment in total and time investment in pieces so for instance the first thing on the
list sounds like this sounds this sounds like Oolulili is things I want to do before I die
it's kind of like that except not as autistic just slightly less well that's one man's opinion so
okay like for instance it'll say anime little witch academia time investment total seven hours
time investment in pieces 22 minutes because you can watch 22 minutes at a time um I'm also going
to code it by like categorize it by like casual consumption versus like immediate so you know
something that you could just watch an episode of randomly forever actually way into this idea
already I already love yeah because the idea here and this is this is actually related to what
hippo is talking about um so I have a lot of these moments in my life where I just am not really sure
what to do and I sit around for like an hour trying to think of what to do yep like I just go like
uh do I want to watch a movie do I want to play a game do I want to watch an anime and it's like
I know there's like hundreds of things I want to consume but like how do I fucking pick one like
how do I keep track and then like a big part of it is I don't know uh do I want to like dedicate
myself to a game that's going to take 16 hours you know because like the first game that comes
to mind is some rpg uh so because I have this organized by time investment I can just uh you
know just say all right well I want to spend four hours on a video game so I just literally
go through and find a video game that takes four hours and I go oh I can play this game finally
and then once I beat it it's fucking off the list and so like this making this list has been a really
like I imagine this list is growing a lot faster than it's shrinking um well I mean it's brand new
so it's growing yes it is growing way faster than it's shrinking um however I am being extremely
spartan about this list it's like anything that I don't think I actually want to finish is not
making the list it has to be like stuff that I'm like yeah I really want to finish this like I went
through my mal and cold like shit loads of my on hold and plan to watch list where I was like
because there's a lot of stuff that you tell yourself you're gonna watch because you think it
would be like good to have seen it just to be like more worldly or because like it'll teach you
something about a creator but you don't really care so like this is a list of just stuff that I
like have a personal investment in that I'm like I want to see this thing through and so creating
the list it's simultaneously is a feeling of man I've got a lot of shit I want to consume but on
the other hand it's like this is all of it like I'm going through everything I'm going through
like every recommended chart on you know on every fucking 4chan board like every rec chart every
like list I have of stuff I've consumed and like anything I want to rewatch anything I and there's
a lot of stuff that I'm just like you know what I don't need to rewatch this show like yeah it was
good but I fucking remember it and I'm not going to get anything out of watching it again I don't
care you know so it's not going on the list but so like I'm at 437 items right now and I'm pretty
what is the total hours investment oh it uh make a spreadsheet I mean I spread it is a spreadsheet
spreadsheet oh okay you you might be able to to get a like a little formula to figure that out yeah
I that'd be fun I might I mean it would take fucking forever but well if you if you have a
column that lists things in like the format of just a number and you select the column it should
auto add them if it's in excel then you can see on the right unfortunately I have it written as
like the number and then the word hours and also the number then the word men um because I don't
know why I feel the need to type it out every time but it just makes it more beautiful all right um so
but like yeah it I do organize it that way so that like I can just you know click the column and
then look at all the two hours stuff and be like oh what two hours thing do I want to you know consume
today and and the basic idea was not not just to make it easier to pick out stuff to watch but also
to cut out all the dumb bullshit I do end up filling that time with because usually this is the time
that I'm gonna end up on Twitter and or I'm gonna end up on my discord and just like talk to people
for like an hour about nothing that in none of it matters like you know it's just like literally I
go there to waste time because I couldn't think of what I wanted to do fast enough and this is easier
and that's the main strength I think of this kind of list which is why I love it M dots what really
got me on this was that M dot strange has this video called be your own dope dealer and he just
talks about how like you know all the systems of all the social media is just to make you have dopamine
hits for for everything that you click on and it got me thinking about like what do I go to for
dopamine and it's mostly just the confirmation that people have consumed the thing I made like I
don't really care about likes or views or any of that shit I ever since getting tweet deck which
cuts my Twitter down to like like I have a mentions tab that's available right when I go on the page
and there's nothing else there no likes no retweets no other bullshit it's just the mentions
and since having that that is now the only tab I read I don't actually read Twitter I just look
at my mentions because I get enough of them that I can you know that it that can occupy my time
but it's like why why do I care that people are mentioning me on Twitter other than you know
and eat a little ego rush of like ah people are paying attention to me you know it's the main one
yeah and I get nothing like even when like you can trick yourself by being like well some of my
friends tweet funny stuff or like some of sometimes people draw me fan art and it's like yeah but
that doesn't you're just justifying this you know like that stuff is largely irrelevant you
could spend the same amount of time you saw you spent reading that funny tweet doing something
productive and in my case like consuming media is productive like it is something that will either
give me ideas or enrich my understanding of the things I talk about because my job is media analysis
so like the fact that I spend so much time on stuff that just is utterly inconsequential
I'd like to cut that shit out you know and just focus on things that are that are the very least
fun and enjoyable and like we'll have a lasting impact you know yeah so uh yeah that's my big list
I also have made an epic list kind of recently not the same like not for the same reason
but I just decided one one day to like list every video game I have access to because I own in some
fashion like on Steam or I have the physical thing or it's on one of the consoles I own
and I've made I googled like I made a spreadsheet and then I googled um for like a pick random thing
from a list in excel or google.google sheets or whatever and now I go to that tab and I just
click on the little button and it just pops out a game that I have and can play right then and there
if I really wanted to by the way uh that's cool just if anyone's interested in making a list
like this themselves here's your pro tips for anime my anime list will tell you how many episodes
and the length of each episode I just assumed for most shows 22 minutes but in cases where I know
it's not I listed it differently so you know I just calculated the amount of hours based on 22
minute episodes for games I used how long to beat which is a site that just tells you how long a
game takes to beat there's there's like the main story and then main plus extras and then completion
and it gives you those three times based on you know user submitted times I usually take about as
long as whatever is main um and then for books there's actually a site called how long to read
that tells you how long it takes to read a book based on if you can read 300 words per minute
which I'm pretty sure I read slower than that but I just went with it um and then for movies and tv
shows there's a website called binge binge or like binge time binge something like that that tells
you how long it takes to binge a show so yeah you can find all of the fucking at least a semblance
of the data online um yeah it's pretty sick I mean it'd be helpful I'd like to make one at least for
like I don't know the top 10 things I wanted to consume right now and then just to have that so
I can like ah like last night uh me and uh we watched um what was it um fucking uh we watched
this movie uh Gerald's game do you guys ever see this it's a scary movie it's about it's about the
the lady gets chained to a bed and then her husband dies on top of her and they're all like alone
but a great movie highly recommended um but then after that I wanted to watch something and I was
like I want to watch something what's going on I ended up watching um the purge at like the first
purge it was shit it was garbage uh so I really wish I'd done something else if only I'd thought of
something better or you know sooner than I had that movie instantly god that movie sucked um but
also very funny also another thing about actually making this list sorry budgie is that uh like um
there's a lot of stuff that I am more encouraged now that I know how long it is because like with
with video games in particular people don't usually tell you like the exact length of games
and there's like a lot of games that that like seemed like rpgs to me that go on forever and I
like for instance uh fable is only like 12 hours long that's shocking yeah and like I thought about
it and I was like well that explains how I got so far in it as a kid because I almost beat it as a
kid um but you know this idea of not knowing how long a game is I've wanted to I've I own uh the
last guardian I've really wanted to beat it I just like haven't because I'm like as scared it's going
to take a while but if I know that it's like five hours or something which it probably is
be way more likely to actually play it dude I'm gonna hit you up literally right now it is 12 hours
long okay all right good to know one of the one of the things I did as soon as I've made my gaming
list is like I assumed that to be like the the average time would take to be like every game on
this list is like one week per game if I'm doing other things yeah and then it would take like
actually let me check how many games there are there's like uh 510 games I guess so like 510
weeks that's a lot of years yeah yeah like that's 10 years that's 10 years or so I mean yeah so like
the prospect of buying a new game is like completely gone I didn't have much of a reason to buy into like
to to keep up with modern games or to buy games or to to do things but like there's a lot of these
I don't want to play but it's a lot of them that I do and I think yeah uh I've got I've got plenty
of stuff to keep me occupied I think the biggest shocker on the whole list for me was Mega Man
Legends which I had just because I've only ever played like the first hour or so of it multiple
times over the years and I just had the impression it was an RPG and therefore long it's like a seven
hour game like I could probably beat it in an afternoon in one sitting yeah um that was nice
to know it's empowering yeah I because I will play a game in one sitting you know yeah try to make
a list like this many times in my life like four or five or six times I've tried to but I've just
never I've always wanted to have a mal but for everything I've never just like some media spreadsheet
that was just you know I mean I I spent a lot of time a few years ago my everything list I have
like spreadsheets of everything I've consumed in in each uh each media that I made like a couple
years ago and I've tried to keep updated with but not really well mal is a lot easier obviously but
um but like knowing all the stuff I've completed it doesn't like this how do I put it like with
anime I had like the on hold list and the plan to watch list and like that kind of lets me know
like what's left out there but like eventually I go through the on hold list and I'm like okay half
of the shit doesn't need to be in here like half of this is stuff that I like watched the first
episode and went oh well this wasn't bad so I'm not gonna drop it but then like a year later I'm
like I'm never gonna find time to watch that fucking show like who cares that it wasn't bad
it's not amazing if it didn't make my fucking if it didn't have my balls in a vice in episode one
then it's not good enough to be like on the list of ultimate things I want to consume because
even after cutting all the stuff I don't think I want to get better in the episodes
one thing say one thing doesn't matter I just remember that like I looked into Buffy the vampire
because Jesse is a vampire slayer sorry but like there's like eight seasons of that and every
episode is an hour long right right and it's like some it's just too much like some of the seasons
have like 20 episodes that's just I can't believe I watched three seasons of loss was it good
it's all right all right yeah I was I mean I didn't I didn't see or no was it six seasons
I watched all but once I watched all but once season I didn't watch the last season I am consistently
blown away by the fact that normies watch like entire shows like that they love this watch they love
60 hours of a show in like three days and I'm like how do you even do that like people think I
watched so much anime you know why did you know anime that takes that long outside of like Gintama
you know it's cuz fucking people and this is fine I like this is with me and League of Legends
before it's you they go to work for eight hours they come home they sit their ass down they watch
TV that's what like every person in America does uh and that's you know it's fine but it's you know
also gay so that's yeah I finally instead of just standing at the brink of the bus and just
saying that I will soon I've actually actually taken the plunge and I'm reading books now
shout out to uh Sarah Yowl I hate your voice but your writing is pretty good I'm listening to
unaudible uh my my aunt got me a book about venice that I'm reading right now is I went there before
you remember callback and uh and I'm I'm reading books now that's quite nice I highlight wait
wait but you said you're reading books we're listening to the audiobook right well I I I just
said that I am listening to an audiobook of one but there's okay I was given that I I am reading that
got you physical well that's cool and I like it uh let's go to questions immediately shall we
yes let's do that yes yeah okay what about voicemails do we what oh sorry I meant voicemails
of course oh shit I forgot about those fuck yeah we've got we've got voicemails people yeah
uh ww.com uh slash what is it speak god damn I don't fucking forget what it is there's a link
in the description I don't think it's I don't think it's www.com.net I think it's imgames.fun
oh my god I can't remember what it's called there's a link in the description so click on
that you piece of shit did I just hear it all right here we go it's patreon.com ben slash ben
slang groan at my imgames.fun you know I did I did um what are you gonna do
suck my own dick furiously in front of you all right here we go here's our first voicemail
of the week people it's time to actually give a shit this is uh this is whoa it's kind of perking
yeah this is from crunchy this is from crunchy let's see what he's got
he's
it was a trip listening to that because the techniques he used to manipulate his voice
are like yeah I've done them so specifically that I could exactly recreate it I want okay okay
so I see this is from crunchy yeah my housemates they were asked about after the after the rfck
stream on wednesday twitch.tv slash rowdy frickers cop killies groan um yeah um they were asking
like who's that they were like who's that uh who's that kid you were you were that kid yeah who's that
kid who's that who's that kid you're streaming with uh stumpy boy this is true uh uh they're like uh
stumpy I was like oh munchie stumpy stumpy stumpy stumpy is uh oh my god stumpy is munchie's long
lost twin who lost an arm in the war and has a sick eye patch all right crunchy isn't funny you know
all the different variations of munchie not funny but stumpy is one of the seven dwarfs by the way
there was another one from from crunchy here that I think was better uh let me let me play that here
all right that one was great what are you talking hello PCB I am crunchy and I have a very big
problem with the boy but she is too gay and too fat to continue to exist she must be punished
immediately I have sent a missile from Cuba to his direct location and at last he needs five cheese
burgers and the next 10 seconds I will not
whoa well munchie do you have five cheese
all right that's enough
all right well I like this guy yeah now he's really redemption arc there for crunchy
um he's ambitious he is ambitious you know I I gotta say people uh we want more than just
base basic bitch questions and that's the kind of artistry I want to see and these
with the voice modulating oh you think so
you think it's some faggot like that I can some some killers trying to pull one over on
all munchie here he's definitely doing that stuff in audacity well it's dope whatever it is
I want to know how to do that because that sounds like Daleks from docker to who oh yeah well they
did sound cool um uh I just can't just wonder wonder when that missiles get yeah I mean keep an eye
soon probably as soon as the episodes yeah probably right about then um hey here's another one from
bad wife in parentheses no sexual connotation here whatsoever um okay all right let's see what
she's got for us I denied all the warning signs but deep down I knew I was addicted the pcp is
the drug I cannot live without I tried to bring my husband down with me I'd call honey I'm listening
to the pcp right now it's so addicting was it so wrong to want to share this fleeting joy with
the one I loved he was concerned and for good reason I procrastinated for my duties as a good
wife only enough he claimed that I was not the darling he fell in love with and left my friends
and family forward suit I listen every week I cannot live without it yeah once a week for a few
short hours I can pretend as if I have people who still care about me oh boy the pcp gives me a
reason to exist I could not will as fate upon anybody roll roll my eyes with these hashtag girl
problems pcp it's so addicting well I mean cool glad to get uh intro lady from uh pcp theme
bad wife no sexual interlady a noted lover of pcp guy intro lady oh intro lady and pcp guy
shipped officially now done yeah it's nice that we're able to come together each week and
lark and pretend that women watch our show and that we can come in and pretend you know what
there was some lady shy I wish I could remember her name there was some girl a few hours each week
we can pretend that women watch our show yeah there were there's some girl you see watch our
show machine something like that no no she's she's dead to us um there was there was like some
message during the question I saw this a couple times some female person said like hey pcp here's
my question or you ever go to acknowledge your female fans first of all I was like what a terrible
question that is acknowledge your female what is that this is why yeah let's just let's just rope
like velvet rope a little corner of the pcp to acknowledge our female fans that sounds like a
good use of time and not at all I didn't mean for her to turn into this I did not know it
I didn't make congratulations one of our like one of our like six female fans you've just
alienated so you know well done look I'm just ribbing her if she can't have a little ribbing
then she truly isn't the rib from Adam that I thought she was all right here we go that's true
uh this is another one from uh this is from cart let's see what carts got us
day cart
hey there ladies and gentlemen it's too late
I just got a question for you oh this is awful
yeah let's an efficient human being somebody's been operating on just a normal level of existence
all right this is shabby and what music before you make a call Jesus curls I noticed in a lot of
these voicemails uh there were a bunch of people who uh like left music on in the background
possibly to get us taken down for copyright infringement uh or possibly just for flavor just
retarded yeah I think it was just retired too uh cart uh be productive that was I thought
that was a fuck you that was a shit question I shouldn't have played it I regret that intensely
what quit I didn't even I did not even hear this question was like some shitty phrasing of how to
be an efficient human being I don't know do your goddamn homework uh pick clean your room
whatever stop picking your nose oh god I was just picking my nose oh shit go to church
go to church every sunday yeah that's a good one that's a good one get the pope to pick your
nose instead all right here we go here's one from communist best guy ever um okay hello comrades of
the pcp it is a communist best guy ever also known as most seem as everyone else guy ever
and I come from alternate universe ccp ccp ccp aka pcp red sun and I come to deliver message
okay uh in see in my universe in my alternate universe on his lines I do not post on youtube I
am a government funded version of youtube government run state run version of youtube known as red
you yeah because that is glorious communist god oh wait okay uh with more money on because
it is workers owned we have more resources so I make viagra every day and oh in my viagra
I have talked about video about uh oh good and lagann great japanese animation and all right this
sucks this video I see and it's yeah we're we're done already we get it very funny uh communism
hilarious um die there you go good good yeah red yeah red tube youtube red we get it red scare
god oh you know what uh this message was from one spar uh this was kind of a public he was the
guy who offered the bounty the other day about uh for like the the timestamps of the weird utilitarianism
no it was starfleet it was starfleet that was an entire week ago can you imagine can you believe
that it's hard to it's hard to but that was seven whole days ago that is pretty crazy um uh here here
he's an update so let's just listen to his fucking up to here once bar hey there pcp that once bar
again from the place hey there yeah so uh I will admit wrecked the criticism you know how we're
always complaining about in the last episode saying well deserved hey guys haven't made a video in a
first did you hang on pause yeah um the the reward is credit I'm not oh the bounty he's gonna pay you
an exposure all right thing okay the bounty uh second of all uh getting contact with me uh yeah
don't get me on the uh he's about to show his channel once bar google it you'll figure it out
uh but sorry did you what were you saying what were you saying oh I was deliberately talking over him
but any oh shit I get it the uh I actually don't even remember what I was fucking saying oh just
that like everyone keeps opening with like hey hello pcp it's uh whatever and I'm like just get to the
point yeah get get to it get to it we don't tolerate that from youtube video don't I don't want to hear
voicemail yeah no there's no need for preamble no and keep it we know we are the shortest you
possibly can I'll tell you people if you record one when I see one of these that is longer than a
minute I'm like hmm I don't know about that so there's nothing there's nothing there's nothing in
all of human knowledge that takes more than a minute to pull out the time tested uh a comedic
goal that is hey blank I am blank and then you can proceed to tell your joke and it works every
single time I'll read your name I'll read your name so don't even include that just say the question
or get to the jump like the guy with the robo voice was good he didn't do shit just imagine
just imagine that you're like uh like a drunk guy in the crowd like we're up on stage and you
are heckling us you're just saying whatever comes to mind as loud as you can scream into the microphone
I'd rather you do that I would say that if at all possible try and keep your message under like 15
seconds I think that 99% of the time you can probably say what you want to say in like 15
seconds that's probably true that work on it don't be afraid to do a couple takes I don't give
that that last voicemail could have been hey fuckface all you get is credit dumbass shouldn't
have maybe wasted all your time go to my channel yeah yeah once bar's a good guy but uh that that
true there was some some rambling there so there you go buddy there's some constructive criticism
for you I'm just saying that I made a lot of calls into the biggest problem the universe in the dick
show right and every single time I just sat there and labored over what I was gonna say for minutes
on end to try to make it as funny and concise as possible and I never got played even though I
tried so hard because other people were even better so yeah you know it's a hierarchy uh all right
well let's go to uh we got a fumble the second I fucking actually started talking fair enough uh
ultimatum juniper with another one here what do you what do you got what do you got I'm supposed
to have been working right now okay hang on four years ah okay because of you fuckers
I've lost that time now all I want really is compensation via uh the star fleet brand of
communism you know the one uh so like you guys would be like put in a isolated chamber stop it
where you have to wait stop stop it your time okay doing literally nothing wait no stop just
gonna stop I just stop it gotta try all I want to say is that I ran the numbers I did the math
and I'm pretty sure that if you listen to all of the pcp continuously it would take like eight and a
half days that's a pretty good chunk of that's how much of your life we've stolen yeah there you go
maybe he means like all our independent content too and maybe he like quit his jobs we could be
ready for rad country and watch the whole thing you know I mean I know that my content in total
adds up including pcp adds up to like a month and a half of total time so that's pretty good
it's pretty good digi I recently made I recently made a uh a playlist like that for myself yeah
I got like oh yeah so I got like I got like 450 videos on that it was more than I thought
honestly I have way let oh I think you included everything in tbap and I just didn't go to the
tbap yeah I did include everything in tbap yeah right including including equestria bound which was
like a hundred videos and mine included absolutely everything even if I had like one line in the
background like I put you have to eat your greens in mine like I there were a couple there were a
couple things uh like um oh I I include I think I included analysis anarchy hell yeah
yeah that sounds good I just want to be thorough I even I included that that time that I called into
uh uh jesse's uh pony show oh yeah and he took my that's like the second video on the channel
it's not I thought it would be the first time I was ever on youtube it was not that was actually
slightly after our first our first upload yeah word oh that's dope curious curiously we got any
more voicemails yeah here's one from chillin chocolate uh let's wait wasn't uh what oh sorry
wait but oh well I was curious okay because I want to watch that video again which one did you call
in to jesse and then you interrupted him recording a review or something uh I think it was the daring
do one but I don't not sure it was an early horseshoe reviews though right it's the second
it's the second video on my every video I'm in playlist okay I thought it was like migraine
reviews but what a time capsule or something maybe it was no no it's one of the it's one of the main
line um god what was the series horseshoe reviews horseshoe reviews yeah it's one of the main
line horseshoe reviews that phantom horns really big all right let's uh let's hear from chillin
chocolate let's let's chill and chock here's a song for ben saint I'm sorry that it's out of my vocal
range you've got to eat your fat that's why yeah you've got to eat your fat
it's not bad
you've got you've got to eat your fat pistachios pistachios pistachios are too high car
the tree things you're fat
what best
he's a warblin
this is great some of the old guys don't have that a respect for this guy yeah I like him I like him
only I think we should be are we gonna listen to this whole thing all right all right let's pause
buddy uh appreciate that that was good but that's long so can can can people listen to the full
things of these you know okay only we have access to you know what you know what the it is it is true
the way that we listen to these is they are all up on a sound cloud where I upload all of them to
listen to um now I was planning to like delete them and just use them to hold them there because
like it just works through soundcloud but like this this chilling chocolate is up on soundcloud
and can be listened to there publicly if people have the link let's just see if I can get the
fucking link make sure you get in before we have to start taking them off to make room on our sound
cloud yeah question oh you know it's soundcloud.com slash the dash pro dash crastonators so if you go
there you can listen to that you listen to the whole thing fun fact yeah fun fact I actually
knocked myself out of ketosis this past week oh no and I think the way that I think it was
I did not eat any carbs I think it was that I ate too much protein damn you Ben because damn yeah
because because I went to the supermarket I went to Wegmans and I got like a deal I got like some
like some there's a Wegmans near you yeah it's the closest supermarket well there's a whole foods
and there's a Wegmans the Wegmans is cheaper we're constantly talking about how much we miss Wegmans
because Wegmans is the only thing in Rochester basically and all the grocery stores here suck
compared to it um do you miss uh do you miss food lion no food lion sucks do you miss uh do you
miss Kroger I would have missed Kroger I would have missed Kroger in Rochester if not for the
fact that Wegmans is even better but now I miss all of them do you have Publix in Virginia Beach
no southern grocery stores are stupid and I hate them uh um chat to violence they need that
they need the shout out from the pcp they need that endorsement um um um wait I was gonna say
okay I went to the supermarket I went to Wegmans and there was like a big thing of sausage super
cheap for like like two dollars and change a pound for this Italian sausage but it was like you know
expiring in maybe like three days yeah so I was like so I bought it and I was like I'm just gonna
eat nothing but sausage for three days I did it was delicious ketosis completely destroyed
it's not well I think I just I just ate too much protein and and yeah flew too close to the sun
flew too close to the sun lost lost that ketosis that was good that was good sausage so cheap I
I just realized that we're gonna have to go to questions after this why don't we just make questions
not a thing and have them just all be voicemails and that will weed out the week who are gonna be able
to do it well we we've been doing fewer questions yeah we've been doing less okay my my only thought
on that is like I let's say someone just doesn't own a microphone but they have like a great question
I'd like to give them away you know that's that's way too theoretical it's probably okay it's
unrealistic people have phones better people do have phones now yeah we should um I suppose we should
really like vet these questions and just pick out like you know the good ones yeah we don't vet them
at all I mean I make sure that they're not like completely nightmarish before playing them but
that's about it yeah speaking of which here's one from Ben St publicist let's uh let's see what he's
got for us so what he goes to this website you see it's um seen comics no what's he got and there's
this um there's this uh this story on there oh no called the vape men uh yeah vapor clouds
and I just wanted to give a quick review uh so that you could improve
your feature ads okay I can't there's not enough weed I can't so I noticed in this story
you got a guy and he's kind of seeing uh so that makes it a zero out of ten for me
and uh if you could just like post a revised version all right all right thanks for that buddy um
I think he was onto something you know sad boys you gotta nix them gotta get rid of the sad boys uh
makes sense all right let's do one more how about from um from you are the more bullet sci-fi
what was that nothing okay all right actually do please don't just read me
all right everyone the pcp is hostage at this very moment if you do not get the patreon
up to 1100 yes by the next episode yes I I'm offing one of the members I'm gonna
I'm sorry to say uh you better reach that goal or one of them's gotta go okay well I volunteer to die
he volunteers to die so we don't have to listen to any more voicemails um I volunteer Nate to die
I mean well he said he said it's a random the the the the choices in his hands we can volunteer
someone but it's really up to him at the end of the day okay this is this is not his doing yeah he's
he's he's subject to the whims of this just like the rest of us yeah so uh I mean there you go actually
the the patreon was above 1100 before but it's dipped down after the end of the month which is
understandable but you better start pledging everybody or we'll be dead so uh yeah I mean
your your favorite you know your favorite pcp member might be no more on the other hand your
least your least favorite one might be destroyed so I guess it's a it's a coin you can either give a
little today and keep a lot tomorrow or you can give nothing in a day and lose it all tomorrow
the choice is yours he's worked you've worked hard for this viewer don't all right that's enough
that's enough of these voicemails here let's just grab like a pity question or two and then
wrap this shit up shall we let's see what we got yeah that's a wrap uh how about um oh no what do
no no oh these are all shit no no let me let me uh this guy fucking posted a screen cap of a
question too long to be posted in a uh fucking tweet can you give me can you give me the cliff
the cliff notes is like what are your thoughts on the value of the game reviews that are objectively
incorrect uh and then he goes on to say reviews of k-mart's two final mix you usually describe
it as mindless button measure blah blah blah stop it stop stop it stop uh no that's that's just
i mean i guess i'd say if it's objectively incorrect i'm not a fan oh by the way that was uh
at karasu underscore b i i yeah here's one here's one from blue nimbus uh questions suck
why would anyone ever ask one this seems like we've entered a paradox uh with this question
iraq son says uh will you replace the voicemail segment with questions i maybe but in reverse
wait yeah i think he probably meant to in reverse uh maybe yeah i don't know i don't know yeah i think
bat sling says chibi bakas when oh yeah chibi bakas when soon munchie has an edited editing of one
there is one they're not that hard am i allowed to say um am i allowed to say what uh what
uh what it's about anime work we want to watch well i mean sure but don't get people's hopes
that this you weren't in the last episode no i haven't i haven't been on one yet right yeah
you can talk about what you want yeah yeah sure oh i really want to do one for s cry ed i don't
know what that is to happen i want i i think they will like it and i want it to happen it's great
it's pretty dope it's pretty especially if you're only watching three episodes because the first
three episodes are strong and wait so is this supposed to be like scared but instead of the
the middle it's cry s cry ed square squared it's like s dot c r y dash ed or something weird like
that it's pronounced it's fucked up it's bizarre i think there's a meaning behind it but it's
retarded and it doesn't matter yeah i there's only one question in here that i think is actually
interesting um kajoro bitter thorn asks what's the most you've ever done to pamper yourself
going to hawaiian vacation was a pretty big pampering experience i mean i didn't like go to
like a spa but like i feel like it's like the same sort of thing that's probably the biggest i've
ever done yeah yeah we've actually got a lot of questions in here oh yeah are they good
in the quite are you guys looking at the i was looking at the that's where i pulled that one from
and that was the only one i found that i thought was that could potentially lead to a funny story
from somebody yeah i don't i don't know about pampering i guess i've been to a salon once to
cut my hair because i had too much hair and a barber wouldn't know what to do with it myself i
don't like i don't like it i i want to get a massage so bad everything i get a massage for
like an entire year but then i have to get my dick jacked off at the end and i you know i just don't
have to go into a fancy restaurant with nate was a pretty big pampering of that was great
shout out to uh uh jack ruby's the precinct or something like the precinct yeah i mean like
because i pretty regularly pamper myself by just going to like expensive restaurants which i would
consider to be pampering yourself oh what i'm what is like pampering is pampering buying something
you like that is no pampering is like i've been pampering myself recently when i go and i buy
pampers and i really you know i tuck myself in i pampering is pampering is you lay in a bathtub
full of mud and you rub some green shit on your face and you put cucumbers over your eyes and
you wrap your head in the towel there's no other way to pamper yourself pampering just indulging
in things unnecessarily for your own benefit slash yeah treat yourself that's a good way of putting
and i was trying to get a dictionary definition and it basically is that uh oh urban dictionary uh
it's time it's time to bring it back oh my god oh our pcp pampering what do we got urban dictionary
to pampering all right here we go it is something you guys aren't aware of most gentlemen and older
men know this after a man and a woman are done with sex the man gets up and prepares a warm
to wet washcloth by setting it in the microwave for 30 seconds the man then comes back to where
his partner lay in either passes the washcloth to to her where she wipes herself down pampering
and cleaning herself or he wipes the woman down thereby pampering the woman not only is the sweet
gesture for your partner it also prevents uti and maintains cleanliness that's the definition
of pampering apparently it's a very bizarre urban dictionary definition why would you why would you
warm up the cloth after what i imagine would be like hot like vigorous sex like i want a cool
cloth well i guess it's better for sticky stuff okay here's just a definition of pamper on urban
dictionary the only pamper the a word only ever used by women over the age of 40 meaning to treat
or indulge yourself in beauty there you go all right well i'm done with this question are we done
yeah uh we're done uh let's yeah let's call it right here thanks for listening everybody hold
there's something out my window whoa what there's some sort of a weird but bizarre sort of object
like hurling towards my my my room right now i'm sure it's nothing you didn't eat those burgers
did you well i mean i tried but there's pickles on one of them and like even though if you pick
them off they still have like that pickled juice on them yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you know it makes
sense um well uh patreon.com slash the procrastinators people dollar get in the chat ask questions etc
maybe we'll keep doing them i mean we're still doing for now don't fucking panic people uh
but just go to the speak pipe that's at speakpipe.com slash pcb voicemail i think check the description
of the fucking url uh and five dollars bonus episodes it's like 16 17th one will be coming
soon something like that it's going to be great it's going to be good you're welcome uh all right
we'll see you next week with another hot take goodbye bye
you