Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hi, I guess. Welcome to, I guess, The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I guess this is like another episode or something.
Surely not.
Whatever. No, yeah. Yeah, it's episode 200 in...
The word on the street is that this is the show.
Yeah, that's what I heard. I didn't buy it.
I know, I know. It's terrible. Funny gimmick. No, that's it. That's it. That's the episode. This is really the product you've chosen to listen to.
You've arrived here in 2021 listening to this. I'm so sorry.
You know, I was looking at the thumbnail for the last episode, and it's got two Nostalgia Critic faces and then our logo.
I kind of help but wonder because it's like the titles like Nostalgia Critic and Medical Fraud, PCP.
I just have to wonder if somebody comes across that not knowing what we are. What on earth are they going to be thinking?
I don't like that the title is Nostalgia Critic and Medical Fraud, and there are two images, but they are both Nostalgia Critic.
It's not like we spent the entire episode talking about the Nostalgia Critic.
It was just the beginning. Yeah, I don't know. Eleazar does all those, so send your hate mail to Eleazar.
Send your hate mail to Eleazar. He deserves every bit of it.
Yeah, so what's up gamers?
Well, let's start. Speaking of gamers then, Ben, you have released the Alpha Build of your game. Do you want to talk about it?
Yeah, I'll talk about it a little bit. My secret project that I've been teasing and teasing for months, I announced what it is, and I posted the Alpha Build of it.
I think a lot of people guessed that it was a game. I tried not to give it away, but some people...
I think that the way I talked about it, the fact that I talked about adding stuff and including stuff, I think might have given it away for some people.
That it's a game. I just assumed it was a game based on the fact that if it was just another comic chapter, it wouldn't be, I don't know.
It'd be like, yeah, you already do that.
Oh, I would just say I was doing it. Yeah, I feel like.
Maybe, maybe. Yeah, it is the Slime and Punishment, the true finale.
I made the video last year that was so long ago, S-Rivert, which was like this...
It was sort of the climax, sort of the, what's the word, the S-Cascade, but that wasn't the end.
But Phantom's Revenge is what I'm calling the game, and it will actually be the end of...
Well, it'll be basically the end. There'll be a little bit of comic that comes before it and after it to kind of go with it, but the game is it.
So I put out the Alpha build, which is like, it's not done. It doesn't have any of the story in it.
It's basically just as dummy backgrounds, dummy enemies, but it's playable, and you can play it and beat it.
It's like, I might tweak it a bit, but it's mechanically complete, so it's a playable.
And that's on my Patreon for $5 patrons to play-test it for me.
And having a bunch of people have played it, and I think the number is five people who have actually beaten it, because I made it really hard.
And I think it's... I made it really hard, expecting that people would probably surprise me, and there would probably be ways to beat it that I didn't consider.
No. No. No, it's just really, really hard, and you really have to...
Beating it requires that you have a lot of patience and try it many, many times.
Maybe like a dozen or 20 times, somewhere in that range, and that you just very carefully exhaust...
You think of what could I do differently, and then you exhaust many, many different possibilities trying it until you find the right way to do it.
That's a little... I guess that's a bit of a hint on how to beat it.
Yeah, I don't know. Do you mind? Well, I guess since it's a patron-only game right now, we shouldn't probably talk about all the stuff in it, but I just want to say...
I don't really mind if you talk... I don't mind if you... There's not much to spoil in it, really.
Well, I wouldn't say don't spoil... And this goes for anyone who's maybe a patron of mine talking to other people about it.
I would say don't spoil how to beat it, because there are sort of little things you can think of, and you go, oh, I could try this or something.
Yeah, I can't do that, because I haven't beaten it, because I thought it was too hard.
Wait, I want to shout out everyone who's beaten it, because the list is so short.
Hold on. I'm going to look at my patron channel and search images, because when you beat the game, it shows an image that gives you stats to what...
It shows you some data about how you beat it and what your numbers were at, and this was just for me to obtain information.
But because it is so... The ways it can be beaten are so limited, they're all exactly the same.
Yeah, I figured.
Yeah, it has an image, let's see.
So the people who have beaten it are Munchy, Sean, Sean Don, Sean Garrett, that guy, Shinisaba, Taiyo, and Crack.
Crack was the first to beat it. He currently holds the speedrun world record at 5 minutes and 57 seconds.
Beat that.
Speedrun?
Like as in like from the first... like booting up for the first time, just beat it in 5 minutes, or did he...?
I don't know if he timed it from... wait a minute.
That seems impossible to figure it out so quickly and to do it perfectly.
Well no, not from booting it up and never having played it. I assume it's probably from hitting start.
Or maybe it's from hitting restart?
Because it plays slightly differently if you start from the main menu versus if you do restart in the pause menu.
So... I'm not sure which one.
But I can find out. I can find out.
Because he has an unlisted video.
Okay, it is timed from... I can find it out.
Yes, it is timed from hitting start on the main menu.
Not a restart, because that would be cheating.
Because you gotta wait through the opening quote screen that sets the mood.
Yeah.
I had... I'm gonna say I had fun with it. It was a good game and it was very cute.
Little phantom horn with a sword. His little sprite.
His name... there's a bit of lore. His sword's name is Platinum.
And I want to include something in the game that will let you...
No, it's named Platinum because it's after Princess Platinum, the founder of the Kingdom of Unicornia.
Actually, yeah, that's the lore there.
I think I'm gonna put in a slime command that will basically be like a look command
that will let you sort of scan your enemies and yourself and get a description.
If you read Phantom's description, it will give you...
As if you've done a slime or a look command in Endless War on a character
and it gives you the characters' readout and what they're wearing and stuff.
So I think I'll do that maybe and it'll explain like...
He is wielding Platinum, a katana.
He is a level whatever sword master and so on and so on.
So that'll be fun.
I think we need to add to it before it's done.
The basics of it are... it's like some sort of a fighting RPG turn-based thing.
Phantom horn, a little sprite.
And there's enemies that are at the moment just orbs, like Unicorn Jelly orbs.
I'd assume they're like actual enemies.
No, those are just plate...
Yeah, you just fight colored orbs that are just placeholders.
Those are not the real enemies that are actually going to be in the game when it's done.
Yeah, and it's got like a little text thing with like a...
Your voice going...
Yeah.
You can tell it was my voice.
Oh, completely. It's so obvious.
That's so funny.
Well, I mean, Canonically Phantom's voice is my voice, so I mean...
Yeah.
Okay.
I feel self-indulgent in talking about it, but I'll discuss it a little bit.
He has lines that he like shouts in battle.
I voiced all those, but then for like his text box, yeah, he has the little sands.
But I just made a little sound.
I recorded myself going...
And I just made that little bit-bit-bit-bit-bit sound.
He...
I was...
My favorite part of it, and the part that I think is so funny, and I was like,
I have to make this game with this idea in mind, is...
When he attacks, he yells the...
He yells the...
Like in Kendo.
Just like...
Months and months ago, before I started working on it, I would think about it,
and I'd be like, it would just be so funny.
They have Phantom Horn doing that.
And you know what, I would...
Has he ever expressed interest in Kendo before that, or is it just sort of a...
Well, in...
I mean, in Slime and Punishment, he learns to fight, and he fights with a katana.
So...
Only in that...
I mean, and you know, it's implied that he is trained with a katana in the dojo.
But I just decided like, you know, I used to do kumdo,
and I feel like Phantom Horn is me in a lot of ways.
And so I'll just migrate that element of myself into him.
And I think it makes sense that he would be very like...
He would be very by the book.
Like he would have like bought like a book about like Kendo forms,
and like practice them, and like, you know, he would...
He would say the lines at the appropriate time, like you do in the sport.
Just seems appropriate. Just seems like what he would do.
Yeah.
I was making more sprites.
Yeah, I've been making more sprites since the Alpha launch,
because there's a bunch of things that I kind of just put placeholder animations in
that I want them to look better.
Like when he drinks the fuck energy in the Alpha build now,
there's just one frame of him like holding a can to his mouth.
I would really like to add them.
So like, there's two frames where he's kind of like...
The can is sort of like moving as he kind of like chugs it like...
And then I think I would like to like have him like either like crush it on his forehead
or like slam it on the ground afterwards or something.
I just think it would look cool.
I was adding things like that in.
That's what my mind's at.
The sprite work is really nice.
You know, it's like he's got a little phantom horn with his sword
and he's got this...
Every time he does the sword slashes, when he says the words,
he does a different pose. I think he mentioned that to me.
I was like, oh yes, kendo moves.
When he does...
He does like a side slash across the abdomen
and when he does men, it holds the sword up high
and then when he does kote, it's kind of like middle forward.
He slides forward.
He knows his kata.
He knows his forms.
He's trained.
He's trained in the art of the blade.
While you were having sex, he was studying the blade.
While you were partying.
It worked out for him, I guess.
For the people who could beat the game.
Yeah.
He's got to take his revenge and this is the only way.
This is the only way he can do it.
It's really hard.
I think I will make it...
I like that it is hard.
I think maybe it's a little overboard right now
and I will probably think of ways to maybe relax the difficulty
a bit before the final version.
A little bit.
I still want it to be hard
and I still want you to have to play through it multiple times
and consider like,
what could I do differently that would make me survive?
That's good.
Also, a bunch of people told me...
I'm not going to say what,
but there are things in the game
that a bunch of people tried to play through multiple times
without even finding or noticing
and then when they stopped and were like,
shit, I keep losing,
they went a little bit into the options
and were like, oh, that's there?
Oh, wow. Neat.
Oh, I didn't go into the options menu.
No, no, no, not like the options menu.
I mean, like looking at your...
looking at like the stuff you have.
Oh, right, yeah.
I want to talk about my experiences with it
because like...
RPGs...
Don't spoil, don't spoil.
I won't spoil like what I figured out, but I...
Like the game you go in
and you have to attack
and in RFCK rules,
you spend slime to attack
and slime is also your health.
So you're like dealing damage
to these enemies
and then they're dealing damage to you
and your slime is going down,
you have podrons and you can munch on them
to get some slime back
and you know,
if you don't use your items,
you have a bunch of items you start with,
like a fucking energy drink
for getting your hunger back,
which also depletes when you attack
and you have to use these items properly
and if you use them incorrectly
and as far as I can understand,
if you do a single thing
in any of the turns wrong,
you will fuck yourself for the later battles
where you will either run out of slime
and be unable to attack
or you'll just die.
There is basically zero margin for error
the way it is right now.
It reminds me a little bit
of Robo-Dobot's
Minecraft
car
map.
Remember that?
God, yeah.
Oh, God.
You have to do it completely.
I mean, that one was a little different
because Minecraft has physics
and there's so many different ways you could do
the drive.
Yeah.
It's not painful.
At least it was memorable.
This is the sort of game that I would hate
in every way because it's
trial and error. I know.
It's anti-gib and it's design.
A lot of number munching.
I feel like if I wanted to
truly understand
how to beat it, I would need to
pay attention to when the enemies come in,
how much damage they deal
and then write a spreadsheet of,
okay, I have this much here,
I have this much slime here.
I'm able to get to this point.
Oh, but then something will go wrong.
I'd need to do a lot of
sitting down and writing stuff down.
That's not what I like.
But I did enjoy the process
of learning
because
in a lot of RPGs, you have all these things.
You never use them.
How many times do you actually use
fucking X attack in Pokémon?
There's so many items
that are completely useless. You just attack.
With a strong attack and you win.
And in this, every
single part of the game is
integral to understand and to be used
to its fullest extents
in order to win. You will be used
to fullest extents. Yes, you will.
I think the quote is,
I will you use to fullest
extents.
I thought it was you will be used
to fullest extents. That's why I found it so funny.
It was because it didn't make
any grammatical sense at all.
I will you used
to fullest extents. Wait, you there?
Shit. Oh god,
my headphones died. Oh.
Give me a sec.
Classic bin.
How many times has
the headphone thing been a problem?
Oh my god, no. How many thousands
of times? I'm sorry.
Eleazar, cut this. No, don't cut it.
People need to know about
the headphones.
How could this
happen to me?
Hey, you there?
Okay.
Hey, I hear you. Okay, cool.
Hey, cool.
Okay, yes, fullest extents.
I'm back.
Oh, I wanted to say
about it that like
in terms of the difficulty,
I, yeah, it's very exacting
but the way
it's a menu based, turn based
RPG style battle.
So like you only have limited options.
And so
I want to
when you're playing through it and trying to figure out
how to win, I think you go through a process
where you at first you kind of have to
come to grips with like, okay,
what options do I have
available?
And then you kind of are like, okay, here's the things
I can do. And then, hmm,
so how can I best employ
these things against, you know,
the configurations of enemies
that I'm going against? And then eventually
you figure out like, oh, okay, if I use this
at such and such a time,
then I can get through this section without taking damage.
Yeah.
Genuinely, like a cool, like
unique thing that I hadn't really seen
in a game. I feel like it's,
it's like, you know, being thrown into
a nuzlocke, except I hate those.
But like,
you need to know your shit
and that when there's only
a small amount of shit to know,
like the items you have, the turns
that it takes, the health you have
and the damage the enemy does, once you know
all of the variables, and there aren't that many
variables to memorize, it feels like
it's doable. So it's not annoying
in ways that it would otherwise be
if it was like part of a larger RPG.
When you're, when you're
like learning it, I think there's that
first phase where you're
figuring out what your options are
and how they should be used.
And then once you get that
down, then there's like, you're not
quite done yet, because then there's like,
okay, now I understand
how to use this stuff, but
now it's a matter of like
trying over and over again
or trying a bunch of times
to like, use them in different
ways and just kind of experiment with it
until you find that perfect exact
combination of like moves
that results in victory.
And I think that like the first part
is good difficulty
and the second part is like not as fun
difficulty. So I would kind of like
to maybe increase that first
part
of like the understanding, the complexity
and then decrease
the second part so that like
once you get, okay, these are
my options and these are how to use them,
then that's basically
when you win.
Yeah, because I got to a point
with less sort of
trial and error of like,
okay, did this work? No, did this work?
No, did this work? No, did this work? No.
Okay, that finally got it.
Yeah, that's where I was getting
is like, I got pretty
far. I learned a lot
about the ways to get to a certain
point in the game.
But then I was running up against a wall of like,
I'm not sure on which
turn I made a mistake, but I did
something wrong and I can't
figure out what it could have been
and now I
realize that the next like 40
minutes to an hour is just going to be me
getting to this point again
and then trying one
thing differently and then losing
again and being like, what, what is it?
And I'd be hitting my head against the wall
and that's the trial and error and I
couldn't, I couldn't bear
the idea so I stopped.
Without spoiling too much, I will
tell you that
I know how far you got
you got most of the way through
but there was a little more
and the bit more that there was
that you didn't see yet
I know that you
would have gotten there
and been like, oh, okay
I understand
what I have to do and
you would have been wrong
there would have been even more
and it would have driven you fucking crazy
Yeah
Yeah, it just didn't add up
there's not enough
numbers to, you can't
put them together to create victory
it doesn't make any sense, do I have to click
on a pixel or do I get a secret?
You just can't do it
Yeah, so
I feel like
so I feel like
Mission accomplished
Well, part of me feels like
part of me feels like, okay, I should have
just known
the short
strengths and shortcomings
of how I balanced it
already
but I feel like having had
some people test it out
and get their feedback really confirmed
it confirmed
what I feel like I should have already known
but that I didn't really have that much confidence in
which is like
yeah, that
difficulty curve
information that I just mentioned
It's, I mean it's
playtesting tells you a lot
because you're building it, it's like
it's like when
like an editor
sometimes edits like a video
and they do that thing where they
put the
like an image on every
like word being said
such that it, when it's
played back, it doesn't make any sense
and you can't follow along because the images are too short
and it's really annoying and terrible
and it would be so much better
as a viewing experience if it was
just like a simple image
to go along with the audio
and
from the editor's point of view
nothing is wrong, it totally makes sense
each word is lined up to an image
and through
you know
a viewer's perspective
it feels different, so like you're making the game
you don't know
the learning curve from the perspective of someone
who doesn't know what is in the game
so it's like, it's completely
you need to do playtesting
and those things to figure out what
you're missing because it's always something
yeah, because I
I like had to
figure out the game in reverse
because like
I sort of like
I was like playtesting it
and like this was, I didn't
hadn't decided like any like
numbers at all
and so I had to like kind of
I sort of had to like
assume like the optimal way to play
and then like play it through
like that and then
I put in like
counters to count like
how many attacks do you have to do
how many turns does it take
how many times do you
take this damage from this enemy
how many times do you take damage from that enemy
and I built those in so that I could
look at it and then sort of
tally up the numbers and then be like
okay so if I set your starting slime
to this amount
that gives you just enough if you
if you are
if you play correctly
and then I was nervous though
and the reason why there's so little margin
for error is because if
I wanted to give a little bit of leeway
but if I gave too much leeway
then that would allow
for sub
a wide enough margin
would allow for sub optimal
play to the extent
that you might be able to win without
understanding the like
the like what is the right
what is the right play
and what is the wrong play
which I would consider a failure
like yeah if you
just if you didn't
understand why
you shouldn't
I don't know waste certain resources
at certain times and but you did it
anyway and you won anyway I would be like well my game
failed you didn't learn what you were
supposed to learn
yeah which is why I controlled
it so tightly
it's interesting and I like
if we get into the philosophy of that
because a game
is an interactive experience
but if it's exactly the same
I mean obviously
there's still interactivity because you can
fail and you can do it wrong
but once you know how to do it right
you're doing it exactly
as the author intended
as opposed to most games
where you don't necessarily have to do it exactly
that way there's like
yeah
you know
well it's like
I guess it's like a
mystery when you
when you read a mystery
you know you have the
tension of the story and then you have the
when the mystery is revealed you have the catharsis
of the aha moment
so I guess in a roundabout way
what I was going for
was not so much that like
oh you can
interact with this game
this is a creative experience
that you participate in playing
but I guess it was
I was seeking after that
that moment of revelation where you're like
oh I understand
and it so
and I mean based on
what people said
who played it they did have those moments
where they were like you know first they were like
oh I see what I have to do
and they try and they're like what
it still didn't work what am I missing
what am I missing and they're like oh
there's that works okay I get it
so like you know
I guess mission accomplished
in that regard
I think it's good as much as I sound like
I'm like salty or whatever
I am
a little bit because I wanted to see
what would happen
but I just got too tired
maybe I'll try it again soon
as much as I sound salty
it is a good
well crafted experience
like I enjoyed the detective
the detective stuff involved
hmm
it's not complete it doesn't have
a real ending but I did throw in
a funny little
something
when you win
just a funny little goof
it's not much
but it's something
for anyone who has
the courage to see it through
did you ever
play
and more importantly beat getting over it
with Bennett Fuddy
I played a bunch of it
and I got pretty far
and I was committed
to beating it because like
I am
I'm no offense
but I am the opposite of you
I am a very patient gamer
and I am very
driven
I'm very much like
I don't get bored
I do get frustrated but it doesn't stop me
I just am like
however long it takes
I will beat this fucking thing
I'm very like
that's not a good thing or a bad thing
it's just
I'm very easily hooked
by something that is like
you can't fucking beat this
and I'm like yes I fucking can
so I really wanted to beat Bennett Fuddy
but at some point I kind of fell off
trying and I never got around
to actually beating it much to my
shame so
I played a bunch but I never actually beat it
I did spoil myself
and go and look up and see
people beating it even though they're not supposed to
they're not supposed to show it but somebody did
I did it with like the
cause like seeing the ending is not really
the point is the
the point is having gotten to the ending
and feeling accomplished in doing so yeah
I did it with the understanding
that like one day I will go back and I will beat it
I will attain the technical mastery
but
it's 2021 and I still haven't
so shame on me I guess
I think the thing with that game is that
it's more
than your
game would ever be because of the fact
that it's like physics based and you can
you know
the movements of the mouse
are so
numerous in the way they could
happen that it's like
impossible to have
unless you're a robot
a perfect path that always works
without any other problems
the like the
like the possible
I mean you know
in my game every turn
you could give one of a number of different inputs
so like the number of possible
the number of possible inputs
is like
I don't know how many turns it takes maybe like
turns or something and each time there's
or 4 possible inputs so
that's like 3 to the power of
30 to the power of 4 which is probably
like you know
something like 10 to the
10 to the 35th you know some huge number
but like in
the body it's like every moment
you know your mouse can be
have a different position and it can have a different
velocity and so like
every moment the possible
the possibilities are like multiplying infinitely
and so like it's like
it's like fucking
instead of like aleph null it's like aleph
3 or whatever it's like
it's like
uncountably infinite
instead of like countable infinite
if that makes any sense
I guess it's also like
not a strategic thing
it's because
necessarily like knowing
the right thing to do
is not so much as important
as being able to have the
reflexes to do it or the muscle
memory to move your mouse in that way
yeah there's reflexes
and there's muscle memory but there's also like
I mean you do have to
there are like techniques to learn
like getting up the
the chimney
do you know the chimney part where you have to go up
the really narrow like
vertical tunnel
yeah like getting up that
I mean you can kind of like
fudge your way through it sometimes
but
after you try it a bunch
you figure out that there is like
there are consistent strategies
there are consistent like techniques
that will consistently get you up it
like cooking your hammer on the lights
and stuff
so like yeah there's reflexes
and there's like stuff but there's like
there's sort of puzzles in that
to figure out too where you go oh I can use
that bit
and if I do it just like this then it works
like 99% of the time
there's definitely things you can learn
but like the game is teaching you
as you play it
twitch reflexes and muscle memory
will not help you get better
at phantom horn revenge
phantom's revenge
so it's purely a 100%
intelligence test this only
the only thing is the brain
knowing
and I don't have that you see
knowing how to beat it yeah it takes some
oh you gotta learn
you gotta learn like the room
layouts and you gotta like remember
like when
when enemies are coming
oh I definitely got
used to
to the first
is it a spoiler to say how many
rooms I got through
no that's fine
the first seven rooms
I memorized them pretty well because I couldn't get past
the seventh one
yeah
it's a little bit of a
as I was
deciding like the room layouts
I was like
you know I want the game to be very exacting
and I want you to have to really know it
to beat it
but then I was like okay so I have that one
design goal on the other hand
on the other hand
um
ludonarratively speaking
sorry to use that word but ludonarratively
speaking
I forget what that even means
it's when um oh the gameplay doesn't match the
story that is yeah gameplay and story
ludonarratively speaking and I guess this is
no this isn't a spoiler exactly but this is
about like
you know the final game will have story
elements and it and like the alpha doesn't have
a story yet so
so I guess this is a spoiler
kind of but not really
you know phantom is he is
fighting his way through this place
for the first time
like he is delving into
a
a dungeon essentially
like a game definition of a dungeon
uh you know
to get his revenge he's fighting through it
on his first time he wouldn't know
like what is coming
in the next room he wouldn't know
like oh I have to conserve this for then
or oh like this room will give me an opportunity
to you know do such and such
uh so I was like
is it ludonarrative dissonance
is it is it like a bad thing
if I'm requiring the player to know
stuff that phantom
wouldn't know and I was like
I guess my conclusion was yes it is
but
I don't see a way around that without
just like completely tanking the difficulty
and making the game winnable on your first try
which is like an unacceptable
compromise so I just had to say fuck it
I mean
there's a in universe built
in way for him to try again
you could just like revive with
endless war rules
no no is that not
is endless war not here
it's a bit of a spoiler but no the game does not take
place in lakakam
sucks game sucks
ludonarrative dissonance at
100% so no if he if he dies
in the game he is not
reviving and trying again he actually
dies for good those are the stakes
I mean lots of games like that but
what do you do
we all know that there's an abstraction between
what the character is and the player playing it
unless there's deliberately throw attention to
I guess most games
are like
you generally don't win on your first try
and therefore like
how did the player character know that he
had to
that enemy was waiting for him it's because
the player played this before
and died and tried to second
I guess most games are like that
to the point that it's kind of silly that I even thought
like hmm will this take
the player out of the gaming experience
I mean
there's certain ways
because it's like
in some games like early NES games
where like killing the player
off is like a hold over
from the arcade where
if you kill the player unfairly
they'll spend money to play
again to get extra lives
and then early
video games were like
unfair in ways where you couldn't see
stuff coming and you'd need to die over
and over again in order to figure out exactly
what you should do on the way through
so that you don't fucking kill yourself
and then
that's annoying
but it's a challenging
experience and some games are good like that
but more modern games
like Dark Souls
are like
cool
to me at least in the way
that you can see
everything coming as long as you
the player
are paying attention to
the environment
there's nothing that comes out except in Dark Souls 2
but there's nothing in Dark Souls 1, Demon Souls and stuff
there's nothing that
can surprise you that
it requires you to die a few times
to figure out what to do
you can
theoretically figure out
and defend against everything
you say that
and I know you're right
and yet
it never happens
it's not like anyone ever has the
experience of oh I'm the chosen undead
and oh I could see
everything coming because I'm such an attentive player
and I was able to avoid
all damage
it's not about having a perfect run
it's just for the player's
benefit seeing that
if you die to something
and then you go back there and you're like
if I was cautious here
I would have lived
because I can see the thing coming
I can see the guy around the corner
it's
satisfying or gratifying
that
to know that you the player
were at fault in a death
and then you feel okay
I did that
bad now I must get better
and that's why it's so
because when you play a game
and it's like you couldn't have fucking seen something
coming and it's like that's bullshit
I hate this and you just get frustrated
and I usually leave
but like
yeah
that's what I have to say
I understand
I mean I guess
I guess the old games
right it was a holdover from the arcade
at first but then even after the arcade
even on console
like old games they had
they were difficult
as a way of extending
the game time yeah yeah
which I guess is my goal too
because like I'm not a
AAA gaming industry
you know
that was my gym sterling impression
AAA game
yeah
the
I'm not that I'm just a guy
I'm making a short little game
and yeah making it
hard is a way that like
the player will have to
it won't be over in
5 minutes and 57 seconds
maybe it'll take
an hour or half an hour
or whatever
make it a little more of a substantial
experience which I guess
is cheap in a way
but also it's sort of
a gaming tradition and probably
generally accepted as
fine as long as it doesn't
push into obnoxious territory
and I mean each run
is pretty short so I'm hopefully
like yeah because it's
really bad when it's like oh I couldn't have seen
that coming it's really bad when like
oh you've been playing for half an hour
and it sets you back all that way right
that's why nobody minds that shit kills you all the
time in Meat Boy because you respawn
in like 30 seconds and it's just like do it again
do it again do it again so like a run
of Phantom's Revenge is only a few minutes so
that's all you can be said back if you lose
the only way it would be
bad in Phantom's Revenge if
was if there were
too many variables too many things to try
and like too many things
to memorize at where
to the point where you would have to start writing down
like
every single encounter every single turn
to do and then trial and error
trying everything
but you don't have to do that you can
figure out quite a lot by
just you know
simple logic like what haven't I tried
like oh if
this item if I don't have any of these
items at this point then I'm fucked
so I gotta keep at least one or
you know some something like that
where it's the the solution
to the problem is pretty obvious if you run out of
slime it's because you took too many hits
or it could be because
you attacked too much
you know so you learn
by the way you
lose what you need to
alter in the next play
play through so it's like it's it's doable
I feel like I could do it
there are a few
I don't know
there are um yeah
there there are a few things
that I think are maybe like oh okay
maybe like if you
are someone
that has like a bad memory maybe there are a couple
points where you're like you might write down
like okay in this room
I should do this because
I mean I've probably forgotten all of the things
in the next room yeah but there's not
that many of them and probably you could
just kind of keep them in your head and remember
or or not uh I don't know
yeah uh
yeah I mean so
you know I've learned a lot
I guess I've learned a bunch
I guess it's given me a like
hearing people's input
has given me a bunch to consider
I'm hoping that a few more people
will beat it in the coming
days
before
I would like to say
that I could have the final
version done this month
but
I don't know if I could have the final version
and all of the like the
comic pages that I want to release with it
because I want to release a bunch
of comic pages that lead up to it and sort
of come after it
along with the game itself
so I don't know if I could do all of that
in this month but I want to give
it my best shot oh
and then um
some a couple people asked
this is the thing that
I was waiting for
that I wanted to have done before
um
Sonichu 102 so when
Phantom's Revenge is done
and it comes out along with the
final pages of Slime and Punishment
then I will finally be ready
to be like ok mission accomplished
I can put
I can finally release
Sonichu 102
so that'll be a glorious day
it'll all come together
I love it when a plan comes together
this is my this is my
long game my stupid and
probably pointless long game but I just
really I just had
a vision it's just like
it's just like Phantom's Revenge itself I had
I don't know if it's good or bad
I just have a very specific
vision and I feel compelled
like I must make reality
I must make reality
reflect this
very specific vision that I have
and it will be this way or it will be no way
and that's
that's how it is
it's really
exciting seeing this
little project this game
I'm excited
it's legitimately cool it's like
it's a little
you know obviously not all the graphics
are there yet but it's the stuff
that is there is really good
it's very solid
it feels like more
I don't know
I don't know if well built
is the right term
but like
the first page of the champion
had that little video game
thing
it feels a little
like more advanced from that
and it's
obviously it's a lot more advanced because it's like
actual gameplay
this game actually has
numbers in it
in the champion
it's the point
that she's so powerful that nothing
can touch her but like
still means there's not much like
replay value for that
I feel like in a way
in a certain way
Phantom of Revenge is kind of the sequel to
that game never really had a name
just the champion
page zero
prelog or something
yeah like
because it sort of starts out in the same way because
minor spoiler
the first enemies you encounter
in Phantom's Revenge can't hurt you
just like the enemies can't hurt
Sophia
but then
after a room or two
some enemies arrive that can hurt you
and in the final version
that'll be justified
you'll understand why that's the case
in universe but so
because it sort of starts out in the same
like the main character is invincible
I feel sort of like
that champion game
iterated upon to like
but then let's introduce some enemies
that are an actual threat
haha
that's I don't know
that's a
feeling I have about it
I don't know
I'm very gratified that
some people have complimented my
sprite work and the animations
I put a lot
I put a lot of it work into the sprites
and the
the timing because you have to like
in game maker studio you have to go in
and you have to like
tell the object like
okay
when the menu sends this command
like when the menu says phantom
an attack command it's like okay
pause the menu commands
pause all the other game functions
then the phantom or horn object
begins a timer
and then the timer starts counting
and then the timer counts
it does all these operations on him
to like change his position
and change his sprite
all with very precise timing
and it does certain if l statements to determine
like what attack he does
and then he does the sound effect
and then he does the sprite
and then when he ends his animation
it's like okay where is he
where does he need to go
okay have him move in this path
to get back to his original position
where he'll like sort of like bounce a little bit
to give himself sort of like that bounce back
that like lends a little more weight
to a movement in animation
and
it's just a lot of little bit
and he does the him and
other things they do the
when they move
and they land at their final position
they have a little like sort of dust cloud that kicks up
from their feet where they move to
to sort of give a sense that
they've stopped their movement
yeah I had that same
I did that same thing with the
yeah with the dust cloud in
the champion
game had the same thing
so I put a lot a lot of work into that
and so it's nice that some people appreciated it
and I'm like yes I did it
I did a couple of good things
and
I don't know I want to add more
like the drinking animation
I want to improve and stuff
oh boy
um
I was like I feel like I might have had
one more thing to say about that but
we've talked for like
45 minutes about that
uh
it's a big moment
but yeah it is a big moment
it won't be it's not as big as when the final one
comes out and people can actually play it that'll be the real
that'll be the real poggers moment
I gotta get my secret
project up the ground
it's still
I mean since I've been ill it's been like
paused for a while
whole last month I didn't really do anything with it
why be paused when you can be pogged
why pog when there's nothing to look at
how can you pog when there's nothing to pog at Ben
did you see
on Twitter this week
there was some sort of kerfuffle
about
pogs like PAWGs
do you know what that is
uh fat ass something
white girls fat ass white girls
and
I gotta be honest
I did not look into like
what is the controversy about
I assume it's something about being white
um no I didn't
I've never I've not heard that
I deliberately didn't go and find out
like why are people arguing about
I was like I think I'm happy
or not knowing
maybe there's a PAWG
champ out there
pog I mean
if there's not
if there's not there should be
uh
yeah um
the pog champions my new comic
I wanna be a pog champ
but I can't
cause I'm a virgin
that doesn't make sense
well I mean I assume that
to be the champion
means you win
and to win
over a female
such as you fuck them
oh I see what you meant
I was thinking of like pog champion
being like a fat ass white girl
that is a champion
oh like I'm the champion
of them like I'm the king
of them oh no well
no
you're the fattest white ass girl there is
if only
um no
no no no no
yeah
okay
yeah top yeah
I wanna talk I wanna talk let me talk
please um no
okay
so the kato comic right
yes the kato anthology
or whatever it was called I think is that
yeah the kato anthology
yeah that is uh
it's ended so if you haven't submitted
you've fucked up submissions are over
submissions are over yes
um
and I this really annoyed me
because
I had I was going to
draw a new comic for it
but I was so
medicaled
I was so like hospitaled I was like
I was weak and
weary and I could barely
get out of bed a few days
and it was just sort of not
good so I couldn't
finish it I got like
two to three pages
lined I was gonna color them later
but I just I just ran out of time
so I failed on that and then
I put instead a snippet
of the lord of ghost comic so it's
it's something in there but
I'm mad
I'm a little mad
are you
gonna finish the thing that you made
the first few pages for
yeah yeah I'm gonna finish it
it'll be like I'll put it on give and take
dot site that's my site
and that'll be cool
oh
I still don't know what's wrong with me
I'm waiting on like blood tests
results yeah do you
want to do you want to say like
what's going on with your
condition publicly
you can I don't we talked
about a little before the show you can say as much
as you feel like divulging
okay so I forget
exactly where I was last
week in terms of
what is what had happened
but I had gone
I've gone to
doctor call me say get
blood test I go to hospital I do that
the lady who took
my blood because I'm scared of needles
so I'm like seizing up like
shit if I faint it's gonna
be really embarrassing and I want to
faint I'm just gonna I'm just gonna
like grip the arm of this chair and
just close my eyes and tense
my toes and hope that I
don't embarrass myself and the lady
taking my blood was like
I described
her in like a discord chat
as having big mama bear energy
she was really nice and sweet
and she calmed me down and I was based
nurses are epic
took my blood
shoutouts shoutouts
shoutout told them nurses out there
shoutouts to all our frontline workers
the true heroes of the COVID-19
pandemic
thank you NHS
thank you
well not me thank
you thank you
no one thank you
who is it that provides me
with a free
free healthcare access to healthcare for all
nobody oops okay
lol lol
owned
yeah so that was
blood taken I didn't faint it wasn't as bad
as being in an IV drip
I don't know whether I mentioned I was at that happened
I went in one time as an IV drip
because I was super dehydrated
super dehydrated I get the blood
test sent into the lab I get a text
a few days later they say
blood levels
all of these other all these tests we did for these
generic things these are normal but this one
thing is abnormal
and we're going to have to look into it
we need you to come back for some follow-up blood
tests about your liver
and then I was like
oh
because I think I talked about last time like I'm
scared what if it's diabetes
mm-hmm
is that a liver thing I don't know much
that's a kidney thing
so it's not a liver thing
diabetes is a kidney thing
I think so kidneys like filter the
water blood sugar
I don't remember
something about the kidneys is what I was assuming
the liver produces
insulin
right
oh god
am I making a fool of myself
the kidneys do that and the liver
is creates bile for
digestion
the liver might produce
bile but I think the liver produces
insulin
I don't think the kidneys produce insulin
no your liver
your liver stores
sugar as glycogen
yeah sure sure
okay so it might be
I don't know
diabetes
the point is
I'm wrong though the liver does not produce insulin
okay no
yeah so it's probably not that then
but it could be like hepatitis
because I was just I was going on like okay
liver
could there be like
is there like a terrible liver
explodey disease
could I have that I looked up
hepatitis seems to be one of those
things
that the liver could have wrong with it
so I'm just looking at liver diseases
I had gone to the doctor
got the second set of blood tests
they're in the lab
it's the weekend so I assume they're not
doing analysis at the moment
and I'm gonna wait for them to get back
to me so
I don't know at the moment all I know
is that there's something abnormal with the something
in my liver
and that's
that's it so I'm just sort of trying
to survive and drink water
and eat food and be okay
by something abnormal
I mean do you mean like
some kind of
hormone or some kind of like
some kind of I don't know
what's the word enzyme
or something or like some
sort of blood
juice
oh yeah wait
there was on one of the forms
they gave me
for the test there was like
because
you give these forms into the blood test and then
they write the thing on the labels
so that they know what they're analyzing
you know
there's like a little
area for comment from the doctor
and the doctor was like
Nash question mark
something something I can't remember because I've given the forms
and I can't read them
Nash
which is apparently non-alcoholic
steato hepatitis
it's a liver inflammation
and damage caused by buildup of fat in the liver
I don't know if that's it
but that was just one of the things the doctor was like
could it be this could it be that they put a few comments
and but I don't know
so it's probably
I did get a call and they said
it's probably don't
worry it's probably not that
bad I'm like okay yeah right
yeah you're just trying to make me
not go insane right now
but I trust
classic doctors
back on their bullshit
I'm gonna trust her because
I'd rather feel like it's not a big deal
and then be scared out of my wits when they
tell me I got cancer and I'm gonna die
oh no
it's
probably not cancer
but it could always be something
terrible so
when things go wrong
it's much more often
not a big deal
than it is a big deal
so I mean
I wouldn't get too worried
yeah yet no I
I don't drink a lot so that
it wouldn't be alcohol related
yeah so it's
I don't know you don't I mean you don't drink
so how could it possibly be non-alcoholic
steato hepatitis
it just wouldn't make any sense
maybe the
the prescription is to drink more
maybe they'll just say you need to drink
you need to get fucking wasted
you gotta convert it to alcohol
steato hepatitis which is actually a good thing
you like that
the non-alcoholic version
is the bad kind
yeah
I mean who knows
I gotta pee
hang on
okay oh god
Eleazar you know what to do
you gotta cut
you gotta cut that shit out
you gotta cut that shit right out
boy oh you gotta take it
you gotta take it all away
when you shove it
in my face
I'm living me
definitely cut that
definitely cut that part
don't let him hear
don't let them know
let it go
back anymore
sorry
you know people have been saying in the comments
that they want to hear me sing more
because they like the
chug jug cover
you know I considered recording like a full
version of that
or a longer version
at least with one chorus
with one verse
when I sat down to like decide what the words would be
I tried to write
a verse and the chorus
but I got stuck
I'm not very good at writing lyrics
so I got stuck writing them
and I just decided to only write
oh I'm talking about the
chug jug cover that I sang
and how it's only the chorus
and how I meant to make it longer
but I just
I was very lazy and only did
the like three lines
I'm very
particular
if I can't think of
if I can't think of a good
lyric that is like
funny and not awkward
and doesn't make me cringe then I'm like
no it's no good
throw it out
won't do it
throw it down these bare essentials
that's all
to put a cap on the
gib is
diseased thing
I don't know anything yet
I'm probably gonna be okay
don't worry about it
but if you wanted to know
I'll follow it up
if they come back
with the test and they say you have something
and I'll just say I have something
whatever
I don't want it to be like a fixture of the show
but I also don't want it to be a fixture of my life
so I'm gonna try and figure it out
we gotta have gib's disease corner
every week
gib's mystery disease
I can get a new one every week
guess the ailments
cool
what new malady is gib's suffering under
oh
it's just been
it's like low key pissing me off
a little bit I just
sure
you know on a good day I can get
a lot of work done
I can draw a lot of comics I can work on my secret project
I can do some stuff
these days I'm like
if I have a good day
I'm like thank fuck
I feel okay let's cook
some food
once instead of like ordering in
let's
tidy up let's
have a shower and let's do all this stuff
wash the dishes
let's sit down and relax
and I guess that's the good thing to do
but it does annoy me that the entirety of last month
went by and I basically did nothing
now this month has started
who knows how little I could get done
yeah
yeah not
that sucks
I
when you're
you just don't have the spoons for it
when you're sick you just don't have the spoons for it
you know what I'm fucking talking about
excuse
spoons like
alakazam from pokemon
yes
no like
wait the hussy references
in psycholoneals
once or twice
I don't know spoons
it's a metaphor
for like
people with like disability
when people talk about disability they talk about spoons
but it applies to everyone
it's just like the metaphor that
you only have a certain amount of energy
to expend
in a day and like when you spend all your spoons
you can't do anything else
and like when you're disabled
when you're sick it's like the number
you have fewer spoons than the average person
and you just can't
oh that's right there was that spoons
there was that spoons meter that depleted
I didn't know what that was about
Z has a
yep it's uh it's
I don't know I've heard it here and there
most in the context of
talking about disability
but it's generally applicable
it's like
I know I shouldn't beat myself up
over stuff and I'm not really doing that
but I can't help but
keep it in my mind a little because I want to
I want to like hit the ground running
whenever I can
if I get feel better and I'm like
okay no reason to like
ease my way back into work
if I feel good or if I get the medicine
I need and I can start I just
I want to be ready to get back
to doing things because
I have a secret project and I want to announce it
I want people to say oh this is based
that's what I want that's the only reason
I'm having a secret project is because Ben had one
I made it up immediately
as soon as Ben said I have a secret project
and I was like I have to copy Ben saying
make my own oh shit I need
a secret project now fuck
it's not true but I but I feel
I fear that some people assume that
just cuz it's not true
but it's not true and I know it's not true
but I believe it anyway
I believe it
do you have that do you have like fear
of like people assuming
you're a copycat I don't know what you would call
that
I feel like I've talked about it before
fear of people
I don't know if I
I don't know if that's a particular fear
I mean I
sometimes I don't really get
I'm not really like scared of it but like
it's something that comes up when like
ah I have a secret project
around the same time Ben does
oh yeah because every time
like I want to like review
Shrek 2
I'm like oh I want to do this but then like
somebody else on their channel
already reviewed Shrek 2
that I can't review Shrek 2
only one reviewer can have a movie
yeah no I know exactly what you're talking about
big copycat energy
and it's just a bad look
yeah no but like
yeah if I do something
something yeah with
I don't know I'm trying to think when the last time
I felt it was
I mean another thing
I guess if I do something like
like the Winnie the Pooh reviews
right when I did those I had a feeling like
boy
this is me like doing like
a retrospective about a cartoon
which like a million and one
other people have done that's like a pretty
common thing to do on YouTube feels kind of
derivative kind of just feels like
I'm doing what all those other guys do
people are going to roll their eyes at me
when I do it yeah like I had a bit of that
feeling so I know
I mean that's a little different because
my secret project is not the same
type of thing as yours
uh oh spoilers
um well
but there's other things
like I've seen this
and it annoys me a little bit I'm not that
bothered by it but like yeah
when people
ascribe like my transition
to Digi
or Trixie I should say
like Trixie transitioned
and that
like put in motion me and I'm like
no you don't understand
what was going on in my head before that point
no
and there was even a moment
in like at Radcon 4 when I was
wearing like the punk cosplay
or the
the uh the what
shoot for the calendar shoot
uh huh
like Trixie was not
like going for feminine
at the time no and I was
I was kind of going for feminine
yeah she did like the
I feel like she was inspired by the way
I looked and I was like
oh that's cool but now people
just because Trixie came out first
people think I'm
I was I'm not copying anyone
I think didn't
she say specifically
that she was kind of inspired
by
you know
she probably said it about other people
but she did she did
she did tell
she told
she told me that like the way that I looked
uh uh
was like
the makeup
with the eyeshadow and stuff
she said that like that
it was probably just all of us just like
seeing all of us like go for the girl look
I think yeah more
accurately it wasn't like anyone came first
yeah it was
the idea of it
was put forward
and then when we actually had to
do it some of us was like
uh oh
uh oh I like it uh oh
this isn't good or is it
and and that was that
um LeMau
well I wouldn't know about that
it is a LeMau moment
a big big LeMau moment
um
no um
no I like the I like the eyeshadow but in like
uh but in like a I'm a cool
I'm a cool like goth guy
in like a super masculine way like
in like a super masculine way though
in a real testosterone based way I love
in a very yes in a very toxic
masculinity kind of way like
really fucked up
like I'll punch people
uh
yeah not to imply that
you have to transition because
you like makeup makeup can be for everyone
that's true that's true
um but uh
sure I I
I well I don't
understand but I empathize
I I I don't know
okay how about I just say okay
how about I just say okay to all that
okay
fine
um right
so there's no there's no pressure
necessarily to do anything
okay well
don't worry about it Ben
I'm being peer pressured
I'm being indoctrinated into the cultural
Marxist cult
these pink pills I have here
they're just they're just like props
they're like theater props
I'm gonna I'm gonna abolish
I'm gonna abolish capitalism
one of these days I'm gonna do it
and it's all your fault
please dude please
okay cool very good
oh speak you know that segues
perfectly speaking of abolishing capitalism
yesterday was May
day
um and I
was invited to
a
a communist rally
basically that's what it ended up being
it was
not very big
it was in it was actually in the exact same place
that um the other one
the um
the march that I went to after the George Floyd
stuff
oh that was on the 4th of July
so this was on god that was almost
almost a year ago oh my god
it was in the exact same place
this one was much smaller
and it was a bunch of people
who were trans
not like most of them but like a significant number of them
um and they
you know they gave some
speeches this was like
there had been like previous
activities in other places
the thing had moved from like downtown to it had moved to this
the place was called newbie and square
this was in like a sort of
a slightly more off the beaten
path part of Boston
um uh uh
and then and then
it was sort of like the final
meetup followed by like one final like last
march like back to
the downtown area so there weren't that many
people there maybe there had been more in the day this was pretty small
there were probably like maybe
40 people 30 or 40 people
um
and um
they had they had uh the anarcho communist flags
uh you know they had red flags
and stuff they had
international workers of the world
flag I just thought was pretty cool
uh they gave some speeches they talked
about like programs
one girl gave
an announcement about like an org
that they were founding which actually sounded pretty cool and it was called
it was called blue
oh god
blue crime blue dime
that's what it was and it was an organization
dedicated to pushing
for like legislation
and like
court rulings I guess
in favor of police
basically being forced to like
pay for their own crimes
instead of like taxpayer money
covering it which is what
uh usually happens
so I thought that was pretty cool
um and we did the march
and the march was definitely
illegal
um the march was
nice the march was most definitely
not like sanctioned by anyone
there was no
there was it was like blocking traffic
cars were honking at us
uh
uh buses were definitely
held up uh which was very funny
uh the guy
I don't I actually
the the person leading it I
genuinely couldn't tell you if they were
a man or they could have been a trans mask
or a trans femme it was just
I just I just don't know I just don't know
but they were they were uh
they were yelling in a microphone
and we passed by like a restaurant
where a bunch of people were doing
outdoor dining and this
and they like screamed
in the microphone they're like it's May Day
it's May Day and you're all you're all
just out you're all sitting there like nothing's
going on fuck all of you
and I'm like
woo I'm laughing
I like it
uh I think I think it may
sounds pretty cool I think it may
I think some people some people
found it a little like oh this is
oh this is very this isn't what is this
accomplishing what is what is this doing
what is this really helping and I
like oh no it's great
no it's funny and it's cool it's good
uh I like it I'm totally
on board I'm in the road
I'm blocking traffic I stand in
solidarity um
where what are they
gonna drive to anyway somewhere
somewhere what are they gonna drive
to home from their jobs
to see their kids
god
give me a fucking break
we there was an ambulance
there was an ambulance and we did
like the the the announcer was like
everyone like gets the side of the road we gotta
let this ambulance by and we did so
you know we're not a complete
monsters about it
no it was good it was great
you know what's the point of it what's the
point of a protest what's the
point of a protest if it doesn't disrupt
anything like if nobody
is inconvenienced if no one
is inconvenienced by it if if you
if you get a fucking if you get
a oh yeah we scheduled
this with the local like with the local
government and like they coordinate off a little
section of the road and like they
coordinate off and like you know they're gonna get a police
escort you know get us through
you know it'll it'll last from exactly
you know five fifteen to six
to six thirty
uh you know during this time the roads will be
closed here there will be like an alternate route
later on if like it doesn't do anything
like the point of
I mean I guess a journalist
was go and have a look and I guess
but that would be about it
I guess like that's all fine if you
get your fucking protest like
approved by the local authorities
and schedule like that's fine no no
disrespect but like
you know thinking
back thinking back
I don't want to I don't want to compare myself
I don't want to compare myself to like
uh a fucking
one of the people doing like
us the civil rights movement
under like Martin Luther King or I don't want to
compare this to that I don't know grand
eyes it like that but I mean
those people did like sit-ins
and diners for instance
and like
you know that was the point
literally the point of that was to inconvenience
people and like not even
not even like the government
just like
people and it was just to make a point
and to make a public spectacle
the idea is to
get it to the point where the government
has to do something to alleviate
the situation thereby
causing the government
to pay attention to whatever was happening
and did it inconvenience
you know
random everyday people just trying to go about
their lives who had done nothing wrong
yep it sure did
but like
so what
so what you know
you can you can look at that
you can look at that fact
and you can think to yourself
well small price to pay
or you can be like
mmm you know
people should
maybe they should maybe they should be a little more civil
you know maybe maybe they're
pushing a little too hard for civil rights
mmm scoop
you know I kind of think that
Negro liberation
shouldn't maybe should
maybe we're not ready for it just yet scoop
maybe
maybe they should just stay in their lane scoop
you know what I'm saying
Shaggy why
he's
he's learning he's getting better he's getting better
he's not a Nazi anymore
we've de-radicalized him
he's got a lot to learn but he's getting better
I promise
who would have known that Shaggy would have been that guy and then Fred
was like the hardcore leftist
Fred became like an antifa
Fred Fred Fred is antifa
Fred is antifa he beat the shit out of Shaggy one day
he beat the shit out of Shaggy one day
we weren't looking
okay well
so that's so that's my thought those are my
thoughts on civil disobedience
I was thinking if I could scoop it in a word it's good
political affiliations where's Velma
where'd she go
I
there's um
there's a really funny video
I don't know if it's from a stream or something but it's um
it was re it was tweeted
by means TV you know means TV
nope
they it's it's the same channel
it's the same people that made
Nyan Cat
but they like they rebrand
themselves into just like a full on
like communist like media
collective that is
that is like a
yeah they're like a worker they're like a co-op
they're like a cooperatively run
fucking
youtube channel
twitter account slash you know just sort of like a
social media I mean
empire I guess would is probably
overstating it but a brand
if you will and
oh this video
it's a guy like going through the entire
roster of like the latest
Mario Kart
you know going through all the characters
all the different variations of dry bones
and all the different like koopalings and stuff
and being like yeah this guy is like
a hardcore Reaganite
yeah this guy is Antifa
you know this this guy
is like an anarcho primitivist
you know this guy is really into bitcoin or whatever
do they have reasons or are they just looking at them
in the same statements
he does give a little bit of justification
for most of them I'm probably not doing it justice
because he does kind of explain why he thinks
and it's really it's really funny
baby Luigi's a fascist
I don't remember
one or two of them were
well Bowser's a fascist obviously
but there was more to it
they weren't all like super obvious
I'm not doing it justice
it made me chuckle a lot
I wonder if I could find that
I saw it like months ago
baby Mario's an anarcho Bidenist
yeah he's a twitch streamer
he's a voshite
he's a voshite twitch streamer
a debate bro
lol
so that was my
that was my May Day
it was pretty
what if a political race had blue shells
a political race
you know like the race
like a Koopas
no like in like politics
so they say it's like a race
oh that's what they did to Bernie
Bernie was the front runner in the DNC
and then Biden fucking blue shelled him
so true
he was in last place
so he got the blue shell and it changed everything
it was the worst
mother fucker
it was malarkey
it was pure
unadulterated malarkey
um
that was my May Day
I have one, I have notes here
I have a couple of notes on my notepad
there's one
sad story that I have to relate
I think
okay
before Covid there was a thing
called mice
which stands for
Massachusetts independent
comics expo
and once a year
at a place pretty close to my house
like you know like two fucking bus stops
down for me or whatever
or tea stops
they would have this thing
and it's basically comic
artists go and they have tables
and you can buy their shit
and I hate it
I hate going to it
but it's because I don't want to buy anything
but for a couple years now I have been
wanted to like try tabling
cause like I've never tabled at a con
or anything but it's a thing that people do
that people like me do
people that sell comic books or whatever
and I feel like mice would be the perfect place to do it
and I
should really see if they're gonna have one
in 2022 and see if I can sign up for one
um
cause I still want to do it next time they have it
um but last time
I think this would have been late 2019
I went to it, I hated it
I did meet a couple of famous people
who I knew
Casey Green was there
he was sitting at a table, he was selling his shit
and there was also
you know Casey Green
do you know
you might not know this other person, Abby Howard
nope
okay well she
she does um
she did comics
I think she's
does a lot of like more commercial illustrations
for like
children's books
a lot of like zoology themed like kids
texts
and stuff I think is what she's doing a lot of now
but she um
she used to do comics but the reason I knew her is because
she got her break
I guess you would call it on
uh she was on strip search
she was one of the contestants on strip search
she didn't win I think she was like
she was one of the finalists though
and then she went on to do a kickstarter for
what she had come up with in the course of that show
the comic was called The Last Halloween
I think the kickstarter raised like $50,000
so pretty good
anyway she was there
and I got uh I said hi to her
she was on it and I was like can I get a picture with you
and she was like yes and I got a picture with her
and
I realized
yesterday I think I lost the picture
I don't think it exists anymore
I think
it was on my old phone that I lost
at that bar
um you know
early last year
yeah I lost my phone at that bar
and it was the worst thing that ever happened to me
did I talk about
that you did talk about losing your phone
and how I went back to the bar
and the bartender like sneered at me
and like glared at me like I was like
like he hated me and I felt like so bad
I still think about it
I still think about like god I
made that bartender hate me like I must be the worst
I must be the worst person
I must have been heckling that stand-up comedian
like so bad like everyone in the room
must have thought I was the biggest loser
I made a fool of myself and I can never
show my face in public again
I'm getting upset
I'm getting upset just thinking about it
um anyway
did it not go to like google photos or anything
yeah it's
it's worth checking
I actually I have a couple of like hard
drives that I think it's possible
that it might have backed
my phone up at some point on
and also it's possible that it might
have gone to like google
the cloud somewhere
maybe I don't know I need to check
but I as of right now
I'm afraid that that picture may
have been lost and I would be sad
about that
I'm not even like
I'm not even like a huge Abby Howard
fan it's not like I think
her work is like amazing
if she speaks to me or anything
I just
I know her from that show
she's kind of a big name
I thought it was cool that I met her
and I thought it was cool that I got a picture
with her so
I would be probably a little bummed
if it was gone but I
I'll look around and if
I do find the picture
I will tell Eleazar to show it
and if not
then
I had a thing
a few days well a few weeks ago
I realized that a whole like month
or something or at least
there was a day out it was my birthday
like a year or two ago
I went to see
I went to see the universal
Harry Potter like the
film set stuff
and I walked around and we took pictures
and I was like I want to look at those again
those are funny some of them
and they're all gone
that entire like block of time
is not on google photos it's not backed up
anywhere it's not on my phone
I do not remember deleting them
I have no idea
where they're gone and I was so upset
because I couldn't figure out
what the fuck happened because it was like
my phone went back to like
you know all the way to Redcon 3
and then like
everything before that
things after that but this one
like area there's just like
a few months where there's nothing
I was so upset
that it wasn't like stored in the cloud
I don't know what happened to it
I mean yeah
that would be
that would suck really bad
especially if there was like
some stuff that happened in that period that you
would like to have pictures of
that's lame as hell
why would it do
fuck god
who would have thought that
images
who would have thought that like entrusting
all of our fucking data
to these like monolithic megacorporation
who would have thought it could ever backfire
I mean it's weird though
cause like all of the photos are still
on my phone like physically
and they're also
okay so they're not gone gone
yeah I don't delete things
off my phone it's got like a big hard drive
capacity so I'm like
I don't need to delete anything
and I don't remember doing anything
like to save space
maybe I did
maybe they just deleted a few months of stuff
for no reason
maybe
sucks
sucks pretty bad
I went to see the gringots
I saw the gold
and I saw the spiders
I did post a few things on my personal instagram
and those are the only things I have
from that time
I guess I have the memories
which were good
that's pretty good memories
you can't get like likes
and subscribes with memories
you can't like print that on a t-shirt
you can't
you can't sell that on gumroad
nope
yeah I can make an NFT
of my time at the Harry Potter thing
I can make an NFT of my memories
it'll be like a notepad document
that says I had a great time
NFT please buy
damn
I thought
it seemed for a minute there
that NFTs were over
but I keep seeing them
so
they caused enough of
a hubbub
that some normies
I don't know really whether normies
are the right word but like
crypto freak
people who are like less
internet savvy
just wholesale
bought into it because it's like
oh dude money
dude I love bitcoin
I love something
and then you know there's like a few people
legitimately thinking it's
worth their time in any way
it's so upsetting
I saw a
tweet from Dan Olson
speculating that
like okay
that maybe just a lot of this NFT stuff
is literally just money laundering
like it's just
rich people with dirty money
doing this
NFT thing as like
a cover for just like
moving money around in a way that like
will hide it
I mean there's no regulation
for the crypto currency stuff
so that would obviously be the way
to do it
yeah
which
honestly if that's true
I hope that is true because it
makes me less sad than like
thinking that like
a real consumer market
for
nothing which is what NFTs are
like exists
and like will continue to exist
I would like to think that if such a thing
exists it's just a front for something
you know
bad but
at least comprehensible
yeah
so you know
world is a fuck
yeah
what do you think about the voicemails
I think voicemails sounds good
I think that sounds
a-o-k
all right
well you got them
if you got them up
the first voicemail
of the day is called
choose
okay on 3, 2, 1, go
big choice
let die the gummies you
love
or suffer the little children
now choose
the demand
what
I could make out some of that is he saying
you get the gummy thingy
or you kill children
oh I thought he said the commies
as in like I have to choose communism
or kids die
oh if it's gummies then that's
that's difficult
all the
the tiki mickey mickey mouse
saccharide
I can always make more gummies
but I can never make children
because I will never have sex
so I will sacrifice
the gummies
yes, yes
facts don't care about your feelings
Mr. Goblin sir
we got to choose the children
they're more mathematically
speaking they're more precious
just in terms of dollars in the sense
like if there are more children
then I can grow up to create
a malucaduca saccharides
that you could then use to make gummies with
we can put them to work
in the tapioca fiber farming
factory
exactly
next voicemail is called
autism part 1
there's a part 1 and a part 2
so part 1, 3, 2, 1, go
I'd like to weigh in on the whole
self-diagnosing yourself
with autism thing
for me personally
it's like
I totally get what you're saying
Ben
there's definitely people
who use that as a crutch
right to sort of
as an excuse to act a certain way
or to absolve
their actions
but it's like
for me personally it's like
I guess
it's sort of a
I see it as somewhat of a shorthand
to explain myself
I guess
I've generally found that there are
certain ways
that like people
generally aren't
able to accept
certain facets about me
and it's like
I admit that I'm somewhat
attached to this interpretation
of myself
but it's like
it's sort of this shorthand
to explain these things to people
in a way that they can like
understand
for me it's sort of
it's like a shorthand
in that it allows me to
you know
communicate things in a way that
people can like empathize with
and like actually like understand
as opposed to like sort of dismissing it
and sort of
expecting me to be able to conform
unconditionally
I get this like a shorthand
I feel like I get what you're saying
let's listen to part two
3, 2, 1, go
like
regardless of whether or not I'm actually
you know
high enough on the spectrum
to be categorically classified
as autistic
I relate to enough of these
characteristics
to like enough of an extent
at least that it is useful for me
to like
use that
to attempt to explain myself
to people to sort of like
to attempt to like
convey like why I am
the way I am right and it's like
fuck I don't know
I think
the problem with this is the
wait I want to
love you guys keep doing what you're doing
I don't know
okay I understand that like
it might be useful shorthand
for some things
but is it
does it explain anything
like I think I don't know if I can
make the leap like it
describes something like if you say
oh yeah I'm kind of autistic
lol maybe that
says something about the way
you think god I don't
remember like all the attributes
you know I don't know
rigid thinking
a you know a
you know a resistance
to like a change in routine
you know hyper fixation on
certain particular
interests whatever
inability to recognize social cues
whatever maybe it's useful shorthand for that
but does it explain why
or are you merely describing
a set of traits by invoking
the word I don't think it explains
anything
yeah I think my problem with
this is
the implication because he said like
some people use it as a crutch
and
you know like that
idea could be bad but for him
it's different I feel like
it's still
up in the air regardless
of whether you're using it as a crutch
or whether it's a good shorthand
or not people
people will not necessarily
understand or react in the same way
when hearing that you have autism
if you make a social faux pas
it could be because
you have autism or it could be
because
you have like a lack of social practice
I mean even autistic people
need social practice it's just
I guess
I guess I would wonder
what the purpose is in
assuming it's true
when
you could just say like
do you have autism I don't know
could be could not be never had tested
never been tested but like
it's
I feel like
in a situation whether you're talking to someone
and then you say something and you think oh god
that was kind of autistic and then you say
to them sorry if I'm a bit autistic
I have autism
and that's just how I am
like what is the goal
with that statement is it to
say please treat me
with patients
or
or is it saying I act
this way please don't expect me to
improve like what could it be
used for I guess is my
question
if you
as shorthand
for the traits
associated with
autism I guess I understand
why it would be useful
to describe
yourself or someone else in that way
I suppose but like
to make
the leap from that to saying
like I am autistic
I have autism
I don't know
if that's like the same thing
yeah I'm thinking like in a social situation
you say something that's kind of
a little cringe and you're like
sorry I'm not
very used to this or like I'm kind of
bad at talking to people like there are ways you can put it
that don't like ascribe a medical
something or other to you
that you may not have
I think being socially awkward
is like
it's something a lot of people have that doesn't
necessarily
go with autism
like exactly you can just be
out of practice
like I feel like I may have
thought I could be
potentially autistic but I also
don't know
whether it's just a
like a
general lack of practice
in socializing because I
don't like doing it generally
and that's like is that
an autism thing or is that just a thing
thing like it's like a life thing
you could just grow and have
preferences for types of interactions
I think the
it may be a good
shorthand but like
it's also a medical thing
I don't know
it's an interesting question because like
normal people don't
necessarily know what it means to
medically be autistic or not
if they associate autism with
like being a little socially awkward
and you say that then they'll get it
that will be true but I guess
it won't always be true depending on who you're
talking to
like if somebody knows more
about autism and then you say that
and they're like really
then it's confusing
things where it doesn't need to but
I guess I would find a different
shorthand way of saying
that you have these problems or
just get tested and then you'll know
I would
say
seeing as
unless I'm wrong
and autism is not
a like
biologically based
I mean I think
it's not like
it is a biological
thing like we don't understand it
but it's not like a learned behavior
it's not a
socially constructed
condition
it is a
function of your biology
you either are autistic
or you are not and it's determined by
your genes
I mean I don't know exactly how it
works but the spectrum
if I'm wrong then like
fuck me and I don't know what I'm talking about
but that's what I think
and if that is true
the spectrum
the spectrum became
like a thing
at some point
in the past I used to think it was like
you either have it or you don't then there was the
spectrum and I heard about that and I was like
okay so all I really know
is that the science is not
conclusive and it is being
worked on and like
understood more as time goes on
so like
it's a
I mean the spectrum is like
in the same way I mean there's a spectrum
of height where like
some people are short
some people are tall
but there is a wide gradients
of
numbers that you could be at
in between those two
and if you're kind of in the middle are you short
are you tall well you're kind of in the middle
I mean you know
that's kind of an interesting metaphor
because
if everyone
around you is a certain height
and you're a little
taller you would be considered tall
even though you may be like 5 foot
and everyone else is 4 foot
right so like
maybe autism could work the same way
like it depends on your environment
the way that you stick out
in the environment
is like the autistic
like are you suggesting
that maybe certain populations are just
generally more autistic than others
and like within those places
what I'm suggesting is that
it's more contextual
than it is like absolute
like how many autism
like points does a person have
before they're considered autistic or not
or is it just how
they differ from the people
like the general
population that they live in
like if you've got all the autistic people
and put them in one country
would that become a normal country to each other
citizens are they all going to be normal
who knows
I don't know
I feel like it could work more like that
maybe
if everyone
if everyone was just like
more autistic across the board
I mean
would society like change
if like the general population was just
like more or less
you know autistic
would society like look different
would we have structured
our
governments and our
communities differently perhaps
probably I don't know
it depends on
when you were talking about the effects
I actually know like
literally what
behaviors are caused
by levels of
autism
I mean I don't fucking know what I'm talking about
there's a lot of science to this
I want to
dovetail this
with just a mention
that some people
last episode we got a question about
isn't calling yourself
trans kind of like being
kind of like just calling yourself autistic
and I don't want to talk too much about that
but I just want to say
if you think gender is a
medical condition
or a biological condition
if you think it is something that you need to be diagnosed with
you're just an idiot
you're just a complete idiot who believes in fairy tales
and I don't even know how to fucking fix you
so I'm not even going to try
okay I just want to mention that
next voicemail I guess
that was thought provoking though
that was thought provoking
good voicemail
next one is from
Frost Drive
3, 2, 1, go
hey have you guys heard of the new underwater
magical roguelike game
it's called subnoidica
what
no
no I haven't heard of it
get out
ah
god dammit
okay at least it was short
next one is called response to
the behind the bastards guy
2 weeks ago
3, 2, 1, go
oh my god
oh my fucking god this fucking idiot who comes on this show
last week this fucking moron this fucking pawns
this fucking maroon who comes on and is talking about
how you bend these to listen to behind the bastards
and the robber Evans is an arachis
and it'll make them stopping a fucking lectures because he talks bad about Stalin once
when if you listen to any of the other
almost any other episode
it's all about how companies are evil
how nazis are evil how the right wing
is evil how liberals are evil
his twitter banner is like
obviously communists
cause Stalin wasn't
Stalin was an authoritarian
Robert Evans is an anarchist
anarchists fucking hate authoritarians
they hate capitalists, liberals, communists
they fucking hate you people
dude dude
wait, Stalin did some bad things
like oh shit I guess
I guess capitalism
does work after all
I guess we shouldn't
open up the COVID-19
vaccine patents to the other countries
Bill Gates is right
Stalinist Russia and Maoist China
they got the flag with the red and the sickle
that means everything socialist
and communist is exactly the same as everything they did
it's just like that
it's exactly the same
what? that's what we want to do
that's what we want to do
such
such base
takes
it's not true
you fools
it's not true it's libel
it's slander and libel
good voicemail thank you
thank you mister response to the behind the bastards
guy two weeks ago
next voicemail is from alaskanweeb
three two one
go
but yeah like behind the bastards
is actually pretty fucking based
Robert Evans used to write for Cracked
and he has another podcast also called
it could happen here that's about how the United States
is on the precipice of a civil war
and it was written about two years ago
so there's some parts that are more focused on the election
but in general it's kind of timeless
and you should totally fucking listen to it
I
I forgot to listen to it last time
maybe I'll give it a try
this will be the time that I actually do
since I've since I keep getting recommendations
for it
next one is called questioning
benjamin sainterman's
leftism
three two one go
being, why don't you ever bring
leftist onto the podcast
you bring cryptophascist
onto the podcast but you don't reach out to leftists
like who
you have people like hungry bowtie or epic hunter
or that squirrel person
that you were talking about the other day
you could invite many leftists onto the podcast
but you don't
I can't get Zae Squirrel
Zae Squirrel is too good for me
and I don't know who those other people you mentioned are
I would, what I look for in a guest
what I look for in a guest
is someone who is
I mean I got fucking
Minerva on
wait fuck you I got Minerva on
Malarion
die you piece of shit fucking kill yourself
what's wrong with you
this is cherry picking this is moving the goalpost
this is what aboutism this is
gish galloping
you piece of shit
okay
what I look for in a guest is someone
who is cool
but who is not too big
that they would
not
care about being on
you know a podcast like ours
with a few thousand listeners
Zae Squirrel
I don't know I don't know what Zae Squirrel is like
first of all I don't know
that she even like does
podcasts or any audio appearances
at all I'm not aware that she has ever
done such a thing maybe she has I don't know
but I mean she's like
she's got like she's got like 50,000 followers
she's a she's a much
bigger deal than I am
imagine how it looks think about how it looks
for some idiot
with 5,000 followers
to go to someone with 50,000 and be like
hey I'm a really big fan
would you like to come on my podcast
you look like a fucking moron everybody hates people like that
so I don't do it
yeah
and maybe do I maybe miss out
could there maybe occasionally be someone
who like I would be a big
a big scoop a big break a big hit
and they'd be like yeah sure and they would
gain to grace the PCB it's possible
it's possible I might have missed out
on some opportunities because of my Jim
kind of storm dancer on
we got Jim storm dancer on
but Jim storm dancer himself
is not famous frog fractions
is much more famous than Jim
storm storm dancer is
I guess so
I mean that's why I asked him
is because I looked at his Twitter and I saw that
like he's only got like 8,000
followers like he's not like a huge
personality
on social media he might be within
he's got a Twitter
he might be
you know willing and I was exactly
right and he was and he came on the show
and it was legendary
legendary
so
left us are small but
cool
are there any I mean if you've heard of them there's not
if you've heard of them
honestly I was shocked that
Minerva came on
she's got like
she's got like hundreds of thousands
of
well the reason I asked her is because
she like responded to one of my tweets
and like she knew who I was
so I was like
oh okay well hey would you like to come on my podcast
I wouldn't have just asked her that out of the blue
because
she's got more
cloud than me
your
Christian lecture has like
over a million views now right
it's got a million views but
my channel is only 17k
which is like more of a
people find videos and they're like
I don't know
you might be able to like
like say hey I'm like
I got a podcast
you want to be on it you've seen that video loads of people have seen those videos
that's true
I mean that is true
that is true
yeah but
you know what I'm not going to go around
asking like hey have you seen that Christian
lecture that I made it's got
a million views you must have seen it
it's got a million views
you must have seen it
yeah it's obviously not the way to do it like that but like
I don't know I feel like maybe you have more
cloud potential than you
realize
I
maybe but
I feel like
waiting for someone to know me
is the
is the only acceptable is like the only
like socially acceptable way to do it
sure I can't go around
go around asking people
yeah I don't know so that's why
but fuck you I've had
I've had a bunch of fucking left
us on just not just not specifically
the ones you're thinking of and I'm so
sorry okay
next one you know
maybe maybe I'm speaking out of turn to say
that about Minerva but I mean from her
tweets it really seems like she's
she's uh
she's of a mind she's on the
she's on the wavelength
that's just my assumption though
next voicemail is called
the third stage of grief
three two one go
does anybody else have contact with this
ghost lightning person that Trixie has
mentioned a million fucking times before
like anybody that Trixie
actually respects and will listen to
that isn't like a fucking crazy
sociopath or whatever
we talked to that person
can somebody fix this
please fuck man
um
ghost lightning is just on twitter
um they're not
like particularly well known or anything
I don't know if Trixie
even like communicates with him
anymore
probably not
Trixie doesn't like communicate with anyone
about her weird little her weird little cult
um
so
but ghost if you want to contact ghost
lightning he's just a guy on twitter
you can anyone can just talk to him
um
next voicemail is called time for
some jerking three two one
go
sometimes
when I look through my patreon
I forget that you guys are
really fucking talented when it comes to
drawing or doing what a recreative work
that you do and I just want to say
please keep going you guys are very
talented and I care about your work
thank you bye bye
what the fuck yeah that was nice
what the fuck
thank you
I will keep going I'm so you know
I had um
it was a it was a relief it was a relief
to put the game demo out because I felt
like it had been a while since I had really
put out like a substantive like
I made a thing
uh I had been feeling like
for a while like oh god I don't do
anything like oh god
um so that that feeling
has been um momentarily alleviated
uh which is nice
um
next voicemail is called
I don't know I didn't pay for
it three two one go
all right first time
here's my thought
that lecture that everyone's mad about
right yeah what if
it was just
some kind of technical failure
like you guys
were done recording then
Trixie looked
oh shit I didn't hit record
or like later
she puts it on some
shitty hard drive
without backing it up and it
just dies and it's kind of her fault
what if it
that's all it was
and she just decided
to make a big thing
a big ideological thing
out of it just
so she wouldn't have to admit
she fucked up
I mean
he's saying that that could be
the case I don't think that would be the case
well I
like why would she lie about that
I don't know why did she do
anything um
I would I don't think that's
the most likely explanation
but it could
I mean I could see it being
true maybe but if it was
true like it wouldn't really change my opinion
about anything
I mean if it was
true like if it was like a fat 32
moment and like
and and
and if that was the case
Trixie would just be able to say yeah
the hard drive failed it's gone
and then we'd honestly it would
be a better excuse yeah
that would be a much better excuse
that would because because what would we even
say about that like
we just have to accept it
like you can't really yeah honestly she should
have honestly if she just didn't want to accept
it she should have just quietly deleted
it and then like pretended that there was
that there was a technical failure it would
have worked out better um
so but
I don't know
who knows
um probably probably not though
uh next one is called
good taste three two
one go
hey Ben so listen into that
song you recommended a while back the uh
fucking come clean nightcore
song uh I just got to say dude
it fucking slaps
song it slaps
absolutely if there's any other songs
that you guys would recommend
to check out or you wouldn't be listening
to I'm always looking for new music to listen
to I so uh hook
me up I have what I'm not listening
to though fucking trial
of the golden witch baby
fucking no
success
anyway uh
okay PCP forever Tom will never die call
me back you know the drill base
um I have
had this week I have had
a um
a sea shanty
stuck in my head I've been like singing it
in the shower actually
I had a dream
I had a dream and I don't really remember
what the dream was I I remember
it took place in a school
and a song came on
on the intercom
and it made me cry in the dream
and I woke up
and I wanted to
and I just was
and I had it I was like what was the song
I couldn't really remember but I thought maybe it was this song
and it was the sea shanty
that I had heard posted around
like remember
at the beginning of the year when there was like
the little sea shanty fad
yeah
um it was a shanty it's called bones
in the ocean and I and I
put it on and I listen to it and I just
uh
and the and
that's no that's Wellerman
um bones in the ocean is different
bones in the ocean I didn't
realize this until later it's not
like a historical shanty it was made
in 2003
by a like modern folk band called
the longest johns
um which is fine it's still a good
song but I listened to it and I sobbed
and I cried and I bawled
I listened to it a bunch of times on repeat
and I cried tears
um
and it's been it's been stuck in my head
all week since then
uh it's a very sad
song but it's life affirming
it's a beautiful song I really like it
it's not very much it's pretty
not similar to
nightcore remix of come clean
by Hilary Duff it's a different genre
um
another song another song that I
have in my head and this one's very specific
and very weird it's the
do you know a channel called mandalore gaming
uh nope I don't think so
he does
video game reviews
I guess he did a
review of
mystery of the druids
which is the game have you heard of that
nope
it's it's famous mostly
for having a funny face
on the cover it's like a screaming
man
in like a hood
I might know that image
you've probably seen the mystery of the druids face
well he does a whole
like review of the game
and then at the end
he has like an original
song that he wrote
about the game with like
a CG like
movie of like the
characters like
running around and having like shenanigans
and it's really and the song is really
catchy and I've had the song
stuck in my head for a few days
it's the mystery of the druids
they all have
an attitude
it's the mystery of the druids
they all have an
attitude
it's a good it's a good song
and uh
it's stuck in my head
so yeah bones in the ocean
and mystery of the druids
are my two
song recommendations this week
you got any
uh song recommendations
yeah oh wait
wait how
what was it called
shit I was listening to it just
today
it's oh it it must
be loved by labby
sifre
how does that go? it's like a it's
uh it's just a
it's a it's a song by
a guy in the 70s
um labby sifre
yeah labby
wait I mean I'm gonna
hear it there's a much more popular
version of the cover of the song by
um madness
which I don't like as much and my dad used
to play this and I just sort of
I just felt like listening to it I mean like a
dad dad music
mood I guess
hmm
must be love I've never heard either of these
I don't know it's just it's just
sort of just lovely it's a lovely little
song I'm just gonna put it in here there it is
oh very nice well nice nice
little nice little diddy
nice little upbeat
tune
I could listen to this
I could spend three minutes and 34
seconds of my life listening to this song
perhaps if I was in the mood
uh
okay next voicemail
is called another
obligatory bend dick sucking
post three two one go
nice
delicious
thank you
everyone should
learn a thing or two
from this guy
next no
next voicemail is
is jeaness three two
one go
someone who really enjoyed
your undertale discussion from the early
pcp days
and someone who has recently finished
undertale I was wondering
what were your thoughts on azrael
dreamer as a character
thank you
um azrael is
real azrael is the kid right he's the kid
go yes um
I think
that azrael
I don't think
he's a great character
I think he's kind of just
no I think he's kind of
I think the story surrounding him
I think he's kind of just there
in the story because he needs to be
but he himself like
isn't really
much of a character he's a gut punch character
and I think his
as a character it's more
of like what you learn about
him than it is talking to him
uh
the whole like laboratory stuff
where you realize that
there was a fallen child that came
before you that was sort of
not you but it is you
or I can't remember the undertale very well
but I do remember really
enjoying azrael
uh boss design in like the
true pacifist ending
um because
it's like
really I don't know whether this was intentional
but it's like the sort of
like um
design that a kid would come up with
so like if azrael was
to choose his own form he'd be so
fucking badass with all these fucking
and like laser beams
and like the rainbow magic
stuff going all over the place
hyper ultra mega death laser
yeah and you
like that's sort of cute
yeah that's cute
but
but there's not much
there's not much more than the cuteness
he's a cute kid
and I guess he's been turned evil
by what is it is it the
fact that he's like trapped in like a time loop
he's become evil
yeah he's the sort
he is what you could become
if you do the genocide route but then he
is like overwhelmed by
how much more deadly you are
by when you do it
so you destroy him
and he's like oh shit
that's too much but in every other playthrough he's like
haha I know I can save
and load I know what you're doing
he's like he's he's he's
bigger than his britches
flowy is him right like flowy
is yes real okay yes
I don't feel like
okay I think what I don't like is that
flowy and him don't feel like the same
character even though they like canonically
are
like flowy doesn't seem
like a little kid
he just and he doesn't seem
like he would have these like
I don't know this you know
the high super ultra mega death power
stuff like that's
like as to as as real
as a kid and as real the boss
don't feel like I feel like that's
like was like maybe toby came up with that
at the last minute he's like oh what if flowy was
as real along but I feel like that was like an after
thought like after flowy was already written
no no I feel I feel
like this it's there is a dissonance
I kind of agree but I think the reason
of it is because you learn
about as reels past through
those like lot data logs
or videotapes or whatever you find
in the lab where you can like
hear him and like Kara talking
or
something and you get a sense he's like a really
little kid but then flowy
feels just like a cynical
edgier older
kid a little bit he's kind
of like
you could imagine him having a deep voice
but in the context of knowing
everything about as real and then seeing
flowy through all the different play throughs
I think it is more cohesive
a little bit
because it does feel like if a kid
was like you know how
kids can be cruel a kid
learns this power or is stuck
in a flower
and they play
this thing over and over again they can
kill people and then they can
go back and then they can kill them again
and over time I think that would make
anyone kind of evil
but flowy seems to
take a like a childish
glee in it and when things
get too real when you're the genocide
player he's like
he's playing tough
and he is tough because
of that boss thing but I don't know
the way that I'm coming off with this on the top
of my head because I haven't played in a while
I guess
I mean you can come up with reasons why
but just the way that he acts
when he's flowy and when he's
the flowy boss versus
when he's as real the
boss I understand that like
when he's kid as real he's like good
so like that's different so it's fine
that he acts different when he's kid as real
but like what is the difference
between when he's flower like
when he's flowy boss he's like
insane and crazy and when he's
like regular flowy he's kind of like
insane and unhinged but like in a sneaky
conniving way but then when he's
as real he's like
he's just like earnestly angry
anime villain like heartfelt
like kid who's who's been
turned dark but like has
like you know has like a
pure heart that you can reach if you try hard
and they don't feel like the same character at all
they don't act the same I guess I'd need
to replay it because I don't remember what
as real was like as a boss
yeah he's like
most of what I remember was sans
as a boss because I played that the most
yeah he when he's
he's like
when he's flowy he's like
sadistic and crazy but when he's
as real he doesn't he's like
he's like
he's like he says like don't leave me or stuff
and stuff and like
like how could like before you beat him
yeah I think like he's like
I'll kill you or something isn't it
like he's like mad that like
he thinks you'll abandon him or something
I feel like he says
something like that during the battle
I can't remember they
I don't know that's my thought is they don't feel
like the same they don't feel like the same
and I like that I don't like that they are the same
because when I think about them I don't
it I had to
ask to confirm because in my mind they don't
that doesn't feel real
it it is yeah like
I feel it as well a little bit
um but like
in terms of like what at
as real the as real
as as real boss and kid
I guess they feel about as fleshed out
as any other of the undertale characters
was just to say not a huge amount
other than they have a very
particular you know
character archetype that they
express very strongly
which is fine
uh
okay next voicemail is
Solaru
3 2 1 go
hey y'all
this might be a long voicemail
a few episodes ago Ben and Gid
talked about hiding and printing out their first
ludes in the other days on the internet
I wanted to share my story that I haven't told
anyone please
back in the mid 90s I would walk home from
grade school and junior high school in Long Island
I had no internet access yet
I was just thirsty all the time
as I walked home from school
there would be times when I would find business cards
on the sidewalk
these cards would have a topless model on them
on one side
for one 900 sex lines
on the other
I collected these cards wherever I could
yeah
I didn't have access to anything else
and I would just keep it close by
I needed a way to hide them
and knew my mom would search my room
constantly
so I managed to survive to tell you
the story since I did find a perfect hiding spot
under every first gen
nintendo console
there was a square dust cover
that would protect the accessories port
it's the one that they used
in Japan for the disk system but never came out
to America
I found that I could fold the cards and get them
stacked inside the tray
even though it was a great hiding spot
it came with paranoia every day
it was a great hiding spot
I was essentially
holding them on for a year
before I destroyed them as we moved out of the house
anyway that's my story
sorry
that's um
that's great
imagine the
with no internet access what are you gonna do
but you're a kid
but imagine
all you've got is these fucking
gentlemen's club business cards
on them
oh god
digerotype printed in
matte black and white
it's so much of it
is the imagination
you see it
and then you burn that image into your brain
and then you create something with it
in your brain
in your imagination
I feel like I've been in situations like that
where it's like
I don't have a lot
I mean you know what
there's moments where it's like
internet's out
oh no I can't look up porn
I have to think about it
I have to make it up
I have to remember what it looks like
like a barbarian
it doesn't always work
next voicemail is
fena2
3 2 1 go
ok
so the real problem with fena
alright the quality of his animation
the designs
the uncanniness
I can deal with that
I can copy the performer best anime in the world
I like rap boy genius
when I watch rap boy genius
that looks bad on purpose
I'm filled with happiness
when I watch fena I feel like
I'm sitting next to fucking george
from 6th grade math class
and he's like
this is
abel
he was killed by his brother
in the bible
and he thinks that genocide
and eugenics actually isn't that bad
and also
your dog doesn't really love you
it's just an
just a fucking animal
you idiot
fena just doesn't seem like a really good guy
he doesn't really seem like a nice person
he makes good things
I don't like him
that's interesting
I didn't really watch enough
I didn't really watch enough of the videos
to really
to get a sense of his
personality other than
that he reminds me of
that one german
asshole who kept asking me
to review his shitty
furry novel
yeah that's the one
I guess he was Austrian
I mean
it doesn't shock me
to think that maybe if I watched a bunch
of his content like his opinions
would strike me as those
of an asshole
that doesn't surprise me at all
I mean that's the sort of thing you would do
if you were an asshole is to make a youtube channel
is to be fena
you're right
you're absolutely correct about that
but
this poppy the performer
is from
a show called wolf circus
I get
I'm not really familiar with this one
but ratboy genius looks bad
on purpose
it's funny
the way it looks is part of why it's funny
so that's not
a good comparison
this is trying to look good
fena thinks this looks good
and he thinks he's done a good job
and the people that watch it
agree so like that's the problem
that's the problem
that I can't move past
there's a problem that I can't move past
I'm sure there's others
next voicemail is called
please god watch odd taxi
3, 2, 1, go
if you guys are still into anime
I'd like to hear your opinion on
odd taxi
because I think it's pretty good
and the fucking idiots
idiots on A are like
it's so boring
furry ship
when I don't think
I hate media, I hate people who consume media wrong
I hate them
but I hate them slightly more than fena
slightly
it's good, it's good
it's a crime drama about a walrus
who drives a taxi
there's a missing girl who we may or may not have kidnapped
there's a lot of drama
a lot of like intrigue
we're only on episode 3
and I made like a huge
sprawling chart of the characters
and their relationships
and yeah, it's really good
it's really good
I really hope that it doesn't like get left in the dust
this season
like I hope it becomes another mole car
it's really good
mole car? I don't know what that word mole car is
um
it looks like
it looks like a mole car
it looks like it could be fine
I don't know
oh wait, Nate
made a
made a video at some point
talking about a bunch of anime
from a season and mole car was a little
mole car
was a little something from it
I think
all one word
mole car anime
um
oh yeah, yeah, it's like a
it's like 3D
uh
a pui pui mole car
oh
is this the stop motion
thing with the plush hamsters
guinea pigs
a pui pui mole car
it's a weird name
um
oh this is great
they don't even turn their wheels
they walk on their wheels
it's adorable
moru is japanese
for a cavey
which is the like species name
for a guinea pig
okay, that's funny
um
morumotto
so
I don't know, it looks fine
it looks like
you know it's I guess it's
there's a thing now of sometimes anime
just have animals
you know there was um
agretzko, that was big
fucking um, what's the
one with the rabbit and the wolf
uh
bee stars
bee stars, brand new animal
which I haven't seen, I've seen like
one episode of agretzko
it looks fine
it's good
bee stars, looks fine
brand new animal, don't know anything about it
I'm sure it's great, I'm sure it's fine
this one, it looks fine
it looks great
I'm not excited to watch it
I probably won't
I probably won't watch it
I don't want to watch a fucking show
I think about watching a show
and I just want to cry
because I'm like why would I do this to myself
why would I spend
fucking 10 hours
I don't care, I don't fucking
care about media
god, I'm so bored, I'm so bored
just thinking about watching a serialized television program
to speak to shows
you should watch Buffy the Vampire Slayer
yes, but definitely watch
Buffy the Vampire Slayer
god, that was a really really funny
episode recently, but of course
I will not talk about it ever
because I don't want to spoil anyone for anything
wait, what?
there was a what?
there was a really really funny episode
I guess it's not really a spoiler
but it's like
everyone bursts into song
and the entire episode is a musical
and they're like trying to figure out
what could be making them
like what sort of demon is causing them to all burst into song
and have like choreographed dance numbers all over town
and there's like
they're doing all these songs about stuff
and then in the background
sometimes you'll see like some random lady
doing like a
her own little musical number
with a parking ticket guy
he gave her a parking ticket and she's saying
why, oh why
can't you like just singing
about that as they walk around
that was funny, that was good
very nice, very good
um
I'm sorry
voice mailer
your pitch just didn't land with me
your pitch just didn't land
I'm sure this isn't the reaction you wanted
I'm so sorry to disappoint you
I love you, I appreciate you
but I'm not gonna watch your fucking
bullshit anime
piece of shit
next voice mail
is called based joker 6
3, 2, 1, go
you know Batman
when you say peacock
well no one bats an eye
but when you say poop
yeah I knew it
well suddenly let's get that man off
of the mall PA system
you know it's a good bit
you know it's
you know it's a formula
it's a formula but you know
you shake it up
each time you twist it around a little bit
you do a new shape and you know it's evergreen
it's an evergreen formula
you know I'm reminded a little bit
because of that line
of the time
where double Batman was like a meme
we had
and like Radcon 1 or something
I like
I remember double Batman
I don't even remember like where that came
from I remember talking about it
at Bronycon
but that was like
wait did we
we might have been talking about it before
I remember it being like
in the car a lot
that was in the car at Bronycon
but that was before any Radcons
right?
yeah that was the Bronycon
that we went to
before we did the first Radcon
where we thought that would have been a better idea
yeah
so that's an old ass PCP meme
and I don't even remember where it came from
I really don't
do you?
I think it might be
footage in one of my
vlogs of the Bronycon
like the
I forgot what they were called
something to rather give and take
vlog
Bronycon part 2
I feel like there's a clip in there of that
because I remember having my camera out
I feel like there
but I think it was from before that
it was definitely
came up before that
there's a clip of it like
evolving in real time
because at that we joked about
Triple Joker
Triple Joker was only funny because
Double Batman was already a thing
I don't remember, I don't think I was around
for Double Batman
to come into
into existence
I can't remember, I have no idea
if any voicemailers remember
send us one
but not
imagine that like 30 people all send voicemails
that are all just like telling
I feel like the only people who would know
is Jesse and Trixie
it was from
the 30 voicemails that all just say
Double Batman came from that one episode
of the horse cast or whatever
oh yeah, maybe
like, comment, and subscribe
don't go back and listen to those
don't listen to anything I did before
like, comment, and subscribe if you remember
the horse cast
the progenitor
like, comment, subscribe
and
patron if you remember
the Norse cast
are the horse casts
still
around? I hope those are still
available somewhere
I mean, I haven't looked for them
it wouldn't shock me if like, wherever they were
had been like, deleted just because
like, entropy
but I hope not, I hope they're
somewhere
well, my horse cast live
is on
horse cast the second with Trixie
and Jesse is up
by just Google
they're all on Jesse's channel
on um
which channel, Endless Jest?
Manchild, Inc
oh, on Manchild, Inc
that was the one that used to be
used to be drowning in horses
why did he make a new channel?
for Manchild, Inc?
I think he just wanted to coast off
of stuff that was supposed to be like
corporate, like
no, no, no, no, Manchild, Inc was
no, but then he made a new channel for Endless Jest, right?
uh
no, drowning in footwear
became Endless Jest, didn't it?
oh, so Manchild, Inc
was a spin-off?
no, but
Manchild, yeah, Manchild, Inc was a spin-off
that I think he made
it was for like the plot line
that was supposed to
come around
after the horseshoe finale
there was like, there was like a
gonna be a plot line where he was like selling out
and that was like the gimmick
and that's what Manchild, Inc was about
something about a magic scepter
yes, the magic scepter, which I always
wanted, I always wanted to know
I always wanted to find out what was going to happen
and it never happened
what happened?
what was the wrestler villain?
oh, um
oh god, with the mirror mask
K-Fabe Commander?
okay, yes
but that doesn't make any sense because
why is the, if the horse cast
was a new channel made for that
then why is the horse cast
wait a minute, was one of them drowning in
wait, what do you mean?
because
because Manchild, Inc
uh
was drowning in horseshoes
that was the pony channel
and the other one, right, he had a separate pony channel
that's right
drowning in footwear
that's why the horse cast is on it
okay, got it
drowning in footwear was like video game reviews
and then a few pony things
and then he made drowning in horseshoes
to be specifically the
pony review show
and then horseshoe finale
and everything brony related
I'm so stupid, it makes perfect sense
it makes perfect sense, okay
that became Manchild, Inc
where it became Endless Jess
yes, understood
um
okay, uh
I guess next voicemail
uh, is spiral senti
wait, you missed cross
oh, I did, yeah, cross what makes a bad voicemail
excuse me
cross what makes a bad voicemail
3, 2, 1, go
Ben was talking about how he didn't like the idea of live callers on the PCP
because they would inevitably
ramble on and on trying to make a point
I was gonna send in about that Johnny P guy
but I didn't want to come off as pretentious
being like, now here's what our friend did wrong
but fuck it, it's suddenly relevant again
now given how many voicemails there are
bad voicemails are the ones that act like they are
in the call with you guys taking a lot of time
to make their point and clearly not scripting it out
this approach to conversation works when you're actually
talking to somebody but not when it's a pre-recorded message
because the listener knows that you won't
pause so that they can ask a question
or make a report
this is one aspect of a bad voicemail
the silent moments of the PCP members listening
to people inefficiently make their point
or if they do interrupt the caller
they end up talking over the voicemail and confusing everyone
you can make a long voicemail
but it has to be dense enough with information
and well articulated enough that the listener
can understand it instantly
that way they don't feel uncomfortable with just absorbing
the information even if it's for an entire minute
obviously this isn't an absolute rule
but the general takeaway is
script your voicemails
I wasn't gonna say anything
but the autism voicemails before
could have been a lot shorter
there was a lot of um uhs in that
that could have been like half the length
uh but
yeah it's true
yeah this true
okay next one is spiral senchi
um
if this is the same spiral
by the way I mentioned that there was
a guy who was going through
all the old PCP
um episodes
doing a count on n-word tally for everyone
uh I believe
this is the guy spiral
uh uh uh
he's actually he decided to actually go back
and start over and like do a more
like a rigorous count
like you know tracking like hard
r's and stuff and like and other things too
he says I don't I'm not even sure
but he's he's he's
what a strange thing to do
he's doing god's work though
um three spiral senchi
three two one go
hey PCP
it's
right now it is
May 1st
and about 14 minutes ago
I submitted
my comic for the kato anthology
yes
I didn't hear about it until like
a month in so I only had
well I had like a month to do it
and
my what I wanted to do ended up
being 12 about 12 pages
could have used more
not really good at comics yet
but I had never really done one before
so I don't know
I finished it and I submitted it
it's not very good
uh it's not
really complete either
but I got all 12 pages done
for the most part
um
yeah um
okay just wanted to thank you
Ben for
I guess retweeting it
I don't know that's a weird thing to thank someone for I guess
but here's just thanks for bringing it
to bringing it to my attention
sure I don't know
if I ever would have
completed anything without
seeing that so
good motivation and I really
I appreciate it
so thanks
I'm glad you got something out of it
and um I mean I
haven't um
I don't know
I haven't seen the um like the entries
like I haven't seen like what's been entered
except for
you and one other person I think like
posted uh kind overlord
spiral you and kind overlord
like added me on twitter like showing their
submissions which um
if anyone else submitted anything I would I would retweet
uh kato's submission just because
I think they're interesting
um uh so I
saw yours too other than that I haven't seen
any of the other entries so I don't know like
what the general
quality level is at um
but you know apparently they've
they've got a bunch I don't know how many
they're choosing from for their
submission maybe it depends on page
count um
it's nice oh
it's nice that it seems like a bunch of people
got uh uh inspired
and uh did
something for this
thing I think it's
nice uh
they are gonna I guess they'll be starting
uh they'll be starting a kickstarter
soon to fund like the actual
printing of it so
um I will announce
that when it happens
um
yeah
okay
next voicemail is called Riley
is bad at his job
three two one go
hey guys can we
just talk about how Riley is like
the worst promoter ever
like it's
insane he calls himself a producer
but he acts more like a promoter
if you leave the slightest bit of criticism on the yin channel
he'll send you a whole fucking paragraph
about how fans are
entitled and don't like don't watch
uh first of all mother fucker
they're not watching that's why you're making
a fucking
1000 video news per video
to 3000
video uh
because nobody fucking wants to see this shit
uh fucking
procrastinators fans
would have been on board but you tried to
steal radcon and now they hate you
uh fucking
cantent ended
they probably would have just said creative differences
but he's like oh well he doesn't want to talk
about it we will first of all
who's we right
uh and then fucking
the dick show guys he could have fucking
Ralph was the easiest slam dunk ever
he managed to fucking fuck that up too
uh the guy was comparing himself
to the fucking joker and got clobbered by a girl
and but at least
he fucking called in so people hate Riley
now uh it's just fucking
amazing just how bad he is at his job
fucking Trixie had a whole platform
that was really successful for years
and in like
four months Riley's managed to completely
squander that goodwill your wife
did not want to work with him Ben Riley's an idiot
you're you're right
but I dis I will disagree
with one thing
which is that I Riley didn't Riley didn't
fuck it up uh Trixie
Trixie is fucking it up all on her own she is
going along with Riley's ideas
true but like
she's doing it all under her own power
and I don't think it's helpful
to say Riley
Riley is doing it Riley's the one
like Riley's the one like making her do it
he's not making her do anything
so let's not get that twisted
um
what did he say about the
call in somebody called in
Riley called into the dick show about this
I don't know I don't know
what happened with like the Ralph
I don't know and couldn't possibly care
about the the drama
goings on of that
the dick show the Riley the
yeah Ethan Ralph
yeah I don't know about that
they're just they're just whatever
they're whatever
the the thing about
the canton
it I want to say
it was
because like Nate didn't want to say anything
and all he did was make that
that tweet saying that like
we're going on hiatus
and then
literally never mentioned it again
in any capacity anywhere which is
honestly
weird and like bad in its own way
um but like
okay
the fact that like apparently like
um Trixie and Riley considered that
to be a like
a big PR problem
that they needed to fix
and then like their
solution to that was to make that
video where Trixie
introduces
the yig channel explains what it's
about and then
in the course of introducing
it to potential new
viewers explains that like
by the way these other people
have like refused to work with me
on the basis of what this channel is
which is not even like true
like I don't even believe that that was
really like I just don't believe
that Nate would just be like
your I don't like your channel
therefore we can't
work together it can't be that simple
and yet it makes it sound that way
which is like so much worse
than the actual truth
which is just that like your mobile
lifestyle doesn't allow us to continue
doing the show together it's
I don't know
it's really baffling on every level
in a way that
like the idea that Trixie
would be like this is what I'm doing
now and everybody hates it
honestly yeah that's the two things
you don't really want to say together
yeah there's a big section devoted
in the like what
Yeeg Studio is about video
that is like
I'm and by the way
Yeeg Studio I'm
breaking off relations with the PCP
because Ben doesn't
fucking like me anymore
and Nate won't work with me
on Kansan anymore and like
she says it's like because
she doesn't like
like the Yeeg
content paradigm like that's what she says
was Nate's problem with it
which is not I don't think that's true
but it's like
it sounds like she's saying
my channel is so fucking toxic that people
are burning their bridges with me and cutting ties
with me over it and like it's
it's worse it's worse
than the supposed like thing
that they were upset about which was Nate's
like non-statement about it
through content
I don't know
that's
so weird to me so fucking weird
so
I don't know
voicemailer I agree Riley is bad at his job
but other people are also
bad at their job
okay
sorry to go on an unhinged
rant like that
next voicemail is called
monkey more like dumb
3 2 1
go
in the comments
always clamoring
for monkey
they are so great about him
he's pretty average you know
kinda
kinda lame
got him
um
yeah I don't really get it got him
I don't really get
the commenters in particular
the commenters in you think so
yeah
the fact that monkey was kicked off the show
a return
is like what they want
they don't care necessarily about monkey
being on the podcast
they just want the spectacle of like
it might even just be like
an anti-trixie thing as well
cause like Trixie had a beef with monkey
and monkey's back
and it's like haha
I think that's quite a lot of the reason
why people actually want to see it
okay that makes sense
I mean
yeah
yeah okay
I guess that's it
uh you're right
next voicemail
yes yes next voicemail
is called ben flakes a balanced breakfast
3 2 1
go
okay
oh god there's a whole
minute of this
simple enough right
was that Vsauce
next
voicemail
how does this knife
incite himself
the train is in trouble
this is some impressive
good profit
welcome to the league of
net fuckers
ben sage
no
god
impressive audio fuckery
I appreciate the length
I don't know
I don't know if it's good
audio fuckery but it's definitely
a lot of audio fuckery
well it's
impressive in that like there's clearly
skill involved in creation of it cause you
can't fuck around and come up with these
sounds you need to know how to make them
you could probably fuck around a little bit
it's not just like throwing a voice filter
on a thing like those
edit yeah okay
alright yeah it's true
that's true
next voicemail is called hugs
and kisses 3 2 1
go
konnichiwa
this is samurai sama
come to say o
arigato
and sayonara
the path
of osamore
noto pevo
byo heto
hito pevo witho
ravo
oneru and respect
true
samurai sama
disappointed by many
people
but noto yu
ben no sentosa
ben no san bring
great oneru
to kawasaki
i did
best of aprentice
ever have
yu keepo scroll
as o samurai
momento
samurai sama
always
bio ino yo harto
pcp
bad no besu
mostori gudo people
hito gibo chan
orso gudo people
okay
sayonara
i was waiting for
like a switch
like a fuck you
i was waiting for
the shoe to drop but it never dropped
damn
wow is this the end of samurai sama
there will be no next time
if that's the end of samurai sama
i mean
just a lot of honor
a lot of honor on display
it was an honorable
an honorable goodbye
sayonara
oh gosh
this is the moment
where you're like oh now i don't want the scroll anymore
but you can't get back
you can have the scroll
not take the scroll
it's not that big a deal
oh jeez
no
you must carry it with you
forever more
keep samurai's memory alive
samurai momento
i like that
i like the sound of that
always remember
every time i look at the scroll
hanging on my wall
next to my full metal alchemist one
i'll remember
the good old days
with the Kawasaki clan
and samurai sama
teach me kendo
teach me mento kote
which i would later go on to teach
phantom horn
passing on the teachings
to the next generation
wheels times
just keep on turning
beautiful
next voicemail is called
furthermore
three two one
go
hey this is Kasady
the uh i guess i
samurai sama's handler
we'll go with that
i just wanted to thank you guys
as
myself
you played the silly voicemails
and they made a lot of
people laugh
having that to look forward to
every week has been a very
positive thing for my
mental health
i kind of have to
leave the online space
some stuff happened i'd kind
of have to go
and more or less felt the need
to say thank you before i did
i know that there was some overlap
so to any pcp fan that
checked out my own shitty podcast
while it lasted
thank you for that too
there are a lot of
horribly hateful people in this
world
you guys and the community that you've built
are fantastic people
so
um yeah
i don't know
i don't know how to end this bye guys
elia czar that was too sincere
cut it all out
i don't want the people to hear that
there's too much love in this episode
it doesn't make sense
it's not on brand
we gotta get mumkey back
we gotta get his fan base
reintegrated with ours
we've gone wrong
we gotta get the mumkey and the dark cloud
the mumkey pestilence
to invade
please
kassidy thank you for all the voicemails
yeah
i will never forget
samuraisama
i couldn't
even if i wanted to
what else can i say
thanks for
your dumb bullshit
and your no problem
it's been a pleasure
okay
smash one in the comments
for samuraisama
dab
next voicemail
put a scroll emoji
if that exists
well on discord
there is a standard scroll
alright
if you are in a discord group
it doesn't matter which one
just put a scroll in it
scrolls in chat
every chat any chat
for samuraisama
if you're in the pcp
patron discord
scrolls in chat
if you're in any of our subdiscords
it's scroll week
okay next
okay
next voicemail
no no
he lives in my heart
there must always be a samuraisama
truth hidden
how many thousand leagues within your mind
three two one
go
here at the bottom
of the sea
there's a trench that's filled
with insanity
creatures
with 12 million teeth
there are more
that's scary
when you gaze at the
episode
it gazes back
have no fear
just grab a snack
kick back
relax and let the currents
phase
there are a million different ways
to delve into the depths
and find
a truth hidden
20 thousand leagues
within your
mind
i am pickle rick
a
error are is
art criminal
who should be
in voice jail
but we're at capacity
voice and pal down
down got me fucking got me next voicemail a message from your gaping ass three
two one go hey just woke up started listening to the new episode yes please
one nostalgia credit top it's so fucking funny sorry god fuck you next voicemail
three a message from your he's not he's not sincere right he's mocking us he's
mocking us no I thought I read it as he's like likes hearing about funny
nostalgia I don't think he likes it I think he's making fun of us but next one
message from your gaping ass two three two one go you know I remember the good
old days of the podcast so you don't have to always wrong and being put in his
place like the beta cuckie is me now he's always right hmm with the tricks you
shouldn't everything else recently makes you wonder when else was he right about
is going keto the correct path do I need to become a commie don't know makes
you wonder though every you always assume that every all of my decisions were
huge mistakes but now you want maybe I should maybe I should have bought maybe
I should have bought Bitcoin years ago hmm could it be well everyone says yeah
yes I was the first I was the first on the bandwagon I was the first and I
sold it all the bag I got rid of all of it before it blew I was that guy who
spent like the two Bitcoin on a pizza wasn't it one more like a like 50
Bitcoin or 100 Bitcoin I don't remember it was worth nothing maybe you're right
yeah when it was yeah no I don't remember but whatever it was worth like
millions they so yeah I would have probably been like a hundred Bitcoin or
something it's one Bitcoin is what like 50k next voice mail is called a message
from your gaping ass three three two one go you know
no sometimes I think about how cute that is what it would be like if I went
out to Boston man in person maybe slip a little something into his drink I'm
taking it back to my dungeon pretty based pretty
based I consent I consent I consent to be roofied it's not illegal anymore so
you thought you were going to have you thought you're going to rape me but
you're not cuz I consent haha I got you I fucking I took I took that from you
bitch that's the way to do it that's just consent but ahead of time and then
they won't care cuz it's won't be right I think then they won't do like oh fuck
oh darn it oh damn now it's not an expression of my toxic masculinity anymore
fuck that's the secret that's the secret they don't want to tell you the
the people in power the the elites don't want you to know the secret but
that's the secret it's not it's might not be the secret I don't know I can't
guarantee that it's the secret next voicemail is called the monopoly man three
two one go oh here's the law yesterday I got drunk real hard and I decided to
raise rent on all residential apartments oh that's so funny that's so
funny that's so funny that's so funny that you did that to me and everyone whoops
my fingers slipped the price up button on my monopoly man chair it's like yeah
he's got he's got a little like slider or a little dial that he could just kind
of like flick upwards a little bit just and then oh he says he slides it up
doubling rent every gentrifying everywhere at once that's tragic but you know what
that's you know what he worked really hard for his money he worked really hard
for all that property he should do what he wants with it I approve you you keep
you keep on keeping on monopoly man you just you know what's best oh next
voicemail have dire gentlemen as a guest three two one go you guys should have
dire gentlemen on the podcast he does really good media analysis and you guys
can talk about the styles you're critic I don't know that he seems like a cool
guy you guys can vibe with so yeah I don't know how reaching out for guest
works but have them on I think it'd be really cool um well let's see I mean I
don't know this I don't think I know this person oh wait oh he made the Doug
walkers haunting masterpiece video oh sure yeah this was one of the ones someone
linked me it was one of the couple that I saw last week that I liked it's a good
video um I mean I I don't know what I have to talk to him about other than Doug
Walker which I don't really have that much to say about he's only got 470
followers on Twitter so you know he's I mean he's I'm sure he might come on if
invited but I don't know to what end you know to what end what's really the point
of anything friendship yeah fun time enough fun conversation yeah shut the
fuck up next voicemail is called let's fire Riley three two one go if there's
anybody out there in the audience who hates Riley as much as I do the Dick
Masterson is thrown down the gauntlet if you can make $30,000 a month on
patreon then he will fire Riley on the spot now I don't know how much of an
overlap there is between dick show fans of procrastinators fans but I am one of
you and I know that others exist so this is a call to arms anyone who'd be
interested throw in a couple of bucks patreon.com slash the dick show let's
get this little creep gone once and for all no you understand you misunderstand you
misunderstand you go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators podcast if then if
the pro make 30,000 a month we will use a bullet to fire at Riley if we if we can
get back up over a thousand a month we will also fire Riley and it's much
cheaper it's much cheaper because we don't need to do anything because we're
already doing it but we'll make it official I I'm sorry if this bursts
your bubble mr. voicemailer but I do not like Dick Masterson I do not want his
patreon to reach 30k so I would consider that if his patreon reach 30k and
Riley were fired I would consider that to be a lateral move at best so no I like
your gusto though I like your spirit I like that you're making moves I don't
necessarily approve all the moves that you're making but I am but I like that
you are making moves I also think it's kind of a stupid like obvious like like
chump move to pledge to the dick Masterson patron cuz like if he wanted to if
Riley was actually a problem to dick he could fire him at any point yeah like
like if if it's it's it's clearly just like milking stupid fans because of drama
like I mean people will hate Riley give me money haha like it's so like there's
nothing there's not I mean I'm sure I mean I'm sure it doesn't I'm sure it
didn't work I'm sure it didn't actually I'm sure nobody actually was like yes
I'll donate cuz I hate right I mean nobody cares well nobody cares maybe so
and also people care I don't think I don't think I feel like Riley's more of a
figure in that crowd as me I don't think so I mean I'm not even convinced that
I'm not even convinced that he even works for dick I think dick paid him like
for once I don't think he actually does anything I think it's just a meme I
think it's just a meme that Riley just leans into because it's like his his
his keys to the lever of power or so he or so he thinks it's all he's got going
on he doesn't seem to do anything is what I'm saying and I don't know maybe
I'm wrong but it doesn't look like he does anything so I don't I mean that and
also I just don't believe that dick would keep his word like if assuming I'm
wrong and Riley does do anything at all for dick if dick does if dick does want
him around for some reason I don't think he would actually do it like I don't
think he would actually get rid of him even if we hit that goal but so so
there's that one it wouldn't even it wouldn't even accomplish the thing that
you think it would accomplish to it wouldn't even be a net gain because you
would have to do something bad i.e. raising dick master since patreon numbers
in order to accomplish it three I don't know yeah we need we need the money more
we're dying here we're dying we're literally dying yeah I'm wondering literally
dying it's true it's true see I would I've been I've been to the I can milk my
illness for money for cash if you want right if you want to help pay for Gibbs
oncoming massive medical bills and pretend you live in America please yeah
I I've I've recently moved to America right now this second donate to the
only way the only way to help get Gibb through this trying time is to donate to
patreon.com slash the Ben Sayeders yes that's right okay okay next voicemail is
called an an amendation on previous statements in hopes of exonerating three
to one go quick correction on the pro one on spamming the Ben discord the
members of the pro one on didn't he say alternative a coin so cals poor can you
get that was me the doing this the pro on ban it me also banner a you going to
continue making the asked kappa desk I understood about half of that yeah thanks
first spamming my just thanks for not spamming my discord anymore maybe one of
these days I will open the invites back up but not today next one is called who
is the best Tom three two one go hey PCP this is like my fifth or sixth time
recording this and it's like 5 a.m. specifically 510 and I had a question for
you guys where is the best Tommy Oliver OC when he when he first viewed on the
scene is probably curious I didn't think he looked that good he was just kind of
dark blue with a door you know the mullet he had the OC look kind of bland but
is actually coming to his own with tall tales nice red feather a nice unique
art style that really made him stand out from the crowd but then he kind of went
all lanky got all skinny long like an actual horse kind of interesting but I
think some people would find it weird and then there was the zombie version
that was used in some of analysis videos I don't I don't know if Tom had that
one that one's not even cannon count or even knew it existed or whether she'd
even count but then there's like his 2d like avatar of him which I think looks
pretty good and you know I was just wondering what you guys thought was the
best I think I personally towards the second one personally and I just
realized something just Tom have a 3d version of himself I mean he's a 3d guy
now so it would make sense and you're right you know you're right you should
make it you should make a 3d viewer of him then please please release it's on
which you want to I'm begging you come on come on you heard me say you heard me
say that it's coming it's coming after phantom's revenge this that was like a
keystone in what I wanted to do before release it we're getting there um yes
one should definitely make a 3d avatar that just seems obvious now that you say
it yes and I and my favorite so far is the the the classic the red beret
brony curious yeah original design I would have to be it stood out from all
the other brony analysis people and it was just really solid it just looks
great I would I would have to say I would have to say that that's the most
iconic was the yeah the beret tall tales not not the really tall one
cuz like you know that one was unique but it was kind of weird looking was that
drawn by someone else I feel like it may have been I don't think so I mean I
could be wrong I assume Tom drew it time to go to the brony analysis week I did
like find out I did like remember the you remember the avatar before the
beret right like when yeah with it way out of fedora with the fedora I mean I
liked that one and I liked that the horn like like pokes through the fedora I
thought that was pretty good the beret is more iconic I like that his design
was it looked oh it was drawn by him yeah it looks similar enough to like an
on-model like show accurate but it's it's different enough that you can tell
that it's it's drawn by him it's got a couple like the it's got like the kind
of the hair coming off the ears I think is a little different it's got yeah
honestly when I when I learned that he had the hat in real life like I at a
certain point the hat became an ironic statement but I believe that at some
point the hat was worn unironically which I gotta admit did poison the well
did poison the hat a little bit for me but you know once once it was moved into
since strictly ironic territory then I the healing could begin and in hindsight
yeah I would say that's the most iconic Tom Oliver OC is the beret wearing tall
tails the beret where it's just like the it's cute enough it's fluffy enough but
not too fluffy it's just that the proportions are very good it's like a
it's like a you know could fit in a in a sphere very nicely why that's part of a
good character design I feel like it is is that a hallmark of good character
well it's it's it's good for for like cuteness I mean like tall tails is cool
but he's too tall and thin he feels like he's not sturdy enough with their all
they're all tall guy this guy you they're all told I mean like tall as in like
little physical tall tall tails yeah the final iteration yes yeah yeah like this
one feels like you could make a 3d model of it and like print it out and then
have it like a little pony true I want one I want one yeah okay so you know what
I'm looking it looks even better than I remember it looks even better than I
remember it's crisp it looks great it's great honestly I'm like I'm feeling I'm
feeling it I'm feeling the nostalgia I'm feeling like that was those were the
days of this this particular pony you see hey you know what I'm more sure than
ever definitely this one look at the shading it's great yeah it is just it's
great what happened huh what happened three dimensions this was all it was all
all downhill from here yeah then the next voicemail comes with an image and I
must oh I must give I must give a content warning I must give a content
warning avert your eyes children I looking at it I'm looking yeah it is
sexual Eleazar and new and lewd in nature it's nude and lewd blurt Eleazar
pixelate it please please spare our young audience and let's listen to the
voicemail this is from oblivion fall three two one go I'm sure you're in the
middle of recording a podcast episode right now I'm just currently listening
to the previous one pretty interesting conversation about bail jpe and tiki
wiki mickey now lovely character she is then you mentioned several times this
word Maori I believe you were trying to pronounce Maori or Maori which is the
sorry indigenous New Zealand population I've only got like a little bit of Maori
on me so I can't you know really comment on this that much ctole is I believe
full Maori for the most part but again they grow up in Australia so I don't
know to what extent ctole is familiar with this stuff yeah so tiki is like
this like these wooden statues that you see around shrines and stuff they tend
to look very like actually like very different from what's in bail jpe like
completely different a lot more like circular patterns spirals and swirls and
they actually look kind of cool sometimes it depends on the one you look at if
you I guess you could see it if you google a Maori like wood carving or wood
statue so I know I just thought that was like an interesting thing kind of kind
of like Gibbs perspective she's very based based Gibb by the way I'm drawing
like a fat pair of titties as I record this I'm gonna leave a link in the
voicemail it's nsfgo you can't show it on the podcast but just I want to hear
your reaction if this fucking look well you heard you heard you heard our
reaction you heard what we think and yeah yeah oblivion fall at some point I
guess it's been a while since they've started but they just decided to start
drawing porn and like huge tits and stuff like for my now just just to do it
I don't know whether they've sold anything necessarily but it's just like
they enjoy the idea they're in the big booby mummy milkers server nice that's
us that's still a thing it's it's very quiet haven't heard much about that
lately but yeah I mean it's it's you know people people are occasionally things
they're they're making nice it's but people I don't think the bots working
that's sort of a lot of nothing to do but yeah oblivion fall is like just
immediately really good and it's been getting better and it's been annoying me
how good they are at drawing that sort of that the pornography I wanted to draw
the pornography but I can't do it it's too hard I need to learn things and
that's difficult these nipples but yeah I'm sorry I gotta say the nipples are too
big they're like I mean they do they do like the like the entire front of the
breast is nipple and I that's I don't like it I don't like that that's really
that's that's really actually turning me off quite a bit the more I look at it I'm
like God oh you know I can the the hair right breast nipples seems a lot bigger
than the the other one sorry that might just be the angle because like you
know the one you're kind of seeing from a more top-down angle versus the other
one you're kind of seeing from the side but I see what you mean yeah I see what
you mean like it could be it could be painful does draw really no no that
would make sense and be fine if the nipple is actually like wider than it
is tall but if it if they're supposed to be a perfect circle I think you're
right and the proportions are a little different yeah yeah yeah I believe in
full does draw like hyper large sex hyper large sex I hyper large sex that's
that's what they call it Craig Craig you fucker he left the truck didn't want to
left the call he was offended your piece of shit can't find the Craig I can't
believe Craig is such a virgin perma virgin nerd let's see can I get it can
I get him back in here no he's not listening if you want me to start
recording Craig is a volso I've been unexpectedly disconnected if you want
me to stop please okay this is like this is not even on topic right now but I
want to fuck with Craig I just want can I tell him to leave and then rejoin yes
but I didn't okay okay well whatever um you got anything to say about the tiki
thing yeah I'm not sure that I haven't seen many comments talking about it like
what like necessarily having like an opinion I think there was that one
commenter said hey I'm black and I don't care yeah so I was like yeah okay
problem solved I yeah it's not really problem solved but like it's something I
I don't really know exactly what to do yet yeah obviously a redesign is in order
I'm just trying to figure out how to do it what if you know what I thought about
I thought about this this week and like I had a thought and I don't want to speak
on it as though I have like any say in like what the character is or does right
so that's that's not what I'm trying to do but I had a thought that was just like
a what if and it was like I don't know this is kind of stupid don't take this
too seriously don't take this too seriously it was just a funny what what
if what if the character of tiki had a revelation that they were like huh you
know I didn't even know anything about Maori Islander culture I just made this
mask because I thought that's what a witch doctor should look like but now I
realized that this was like an insensitive racial caricature and then
she just takes the mask off and it's like I'm still gonna make potions and
stuff because that's what I do but I'm not gonna wear this mask anymore because
like I don't think it's appropriate that would be funny it's a little it's a
little like too like obvious self-insert meta humor sort of thing sure yeah
wouldn't it wouldn't be it wouldn't be canon I'm not saying whatever the
character I'm not I'm not saying but I like it it's funny I'm not saying you
should do that but I thought about that and I was like you know I feel like that
would that would be a solution that is like acknowledging like why the
character changes it but also not doing like a sweep under the rug like let's
just pretend she never looked like that sort of thing all right maybe I guess
it sort of opens again not my not my question not my character I don't have
anything about it yeah that the reason I would not do it that way is because it
opens up the idea that blackface and like indigenous cultures and being
offended from those things would all exist in this universe just in the
exactly the same way that they would exist in our universe and it's not
exactly what I want to go for but you know yeah that would sort of imply yeah
that would sort of imply that like yeah maybe not necessarily that it takes it
would sort of imply that it takes place in our world which like if it doesn't
then like it doesn't it doesn't make any sense yeah okay that's totally fair that
makes sense um LeMau it's it's I'm imagining her like I'm imagining she
takes the mask off and like she's got kind of like a long neck right and like
sort of and like the math I'm imagining that without the mask on she's got sort
of like a long neck in her head is like pretty like just sort of like small and
like a sphere it's kind of like a ball on the end wait a minute let me let me
really quickly like doodle what I what I think like the shape of her head would
be without wait this will take me two seconds get my stylist it's kind of
like here's her shoulder here's her other shoulder here's her kind of like
skinny neck
yeah that's perfect let me grab that with my little tool here and bam
like without the mask that's the shape of her head and it just and like and like
the mask is like thick wood and the mask has sort of like a perfectly
spherical like indentation in the back of it and her spherical head just kind of
like sort of sticks into the spherical indent like a ball joint not canon not
canon like a little snap Lego thing yes yes precisely food fan theories fan
that's just a theory a fan theory a bail theory
bail jpeh that is
I was thinking about like bail jpeh and like the the the fact that the story
continues but it wouldn't be called bail jpeh again because bail jpeh is just a
it's a silly play on jailbreak yeah and it's also barely makes sense bale
does not have anything to do with the comic and jpeh kind of does kind of
kind of it's jpeh but it's not bail related there's no bailary no no so
like if there was like an extended comic that you know one piece it's about one
piece and everything in the comic will eventually lead to one piece I need to
think of a name for whatever my big comic is that include like carries on the
story oh like the name for the and like the name for like the extended
universe kind of the ongoing series the ongoing series the main thing that you
know the thing leads into the pumpkin like bail jpeh would be the wanted to
whatever the one piece will eventually be oh I get it I get it hmm are you are
you saying that like you you plan to do like a like a is that your plan like make
a more realized series about it yeah I like the characters that I make but I'm
I'm like you know bail jpeh was you know I made it all up and then I went around
afterwards thinking like okay well all these things I introduce what how could
they fit into a world that I could build and then I did all that but nobody
knows anything about it and that was the plan going forward is to do that in
some form but I don't have a name for it yet it's the only thing is like oh it's
punks in it maybe could be punk related but she's not the main character is she
oh I don't know is she not the main character um that's also a thing I'm
not in I'm not even sure there's so many things I want to do and it's so
complicated hard to talk about yeah maybe I should make it more simple maybe
maybe you should what maybe I should make it more simple and just decide that
there is a main character and it is about them and their journey and these
other characters I have are secondary because at the moment I have like a lot
of secondary characters that will all meet together in one big thing but it
kind of does it it requires a protagonist and like a main one otherwise
it's hard to link everything together punk would be it probably I mean that's
just what I assumed that's just what I assumed but yeah I don't know names are
hard and so is basically everything when it comes to nailing down nailing down
the details it's like it's like painful right you know what I mean because like
when you're coming up with a story and you're when you finally nail down the
details of what it is you are throwing away like all the other things that
could have been everything things yeah and sometimes it's like oh that would
have been cool but I want to do this and it always comes at the expense of
something else and it's like it's hard it makes it very hard for me it takes
takes me a long time sometimes the only takes me a long time sometimes and
like sometimes the only way that I can be sure that a thing that I want to make
is definitely the thing I want to make is just because I realize I've been
thinking about this thing for a long long time and it has the fact that I keep
thinking about it means that I must want to make it and so that's what I'm
gonna do that's what that's what slime and pun not slime and punishment that's
what fandoms revenge was is I just kept picturing like what if it ended with a
video game and I kept picturing what it would look like and it always looked the
same way in my head and I was like well I guess I got to make a game that looks
like that and I did partially yeah I'm excited to see that the final thing
when the when the final thing comes out I definitely will not give up even if it
is difficult I have shit I have I have some the demo has no story to it at all
but I have a few big ideas I have a few big like story ideas that I'm like really
excited about I'm actually more excited about like what I want to present
story-wise in it than I am about the like the mechanics itself so like I
consider what's there right now to not even be like the most important part
that's like that's just sort of like okay I guess I had to make it an actual
game so you know that part's done now on to like the real work which is like
making the cutscenes which I don't know how to do making like I talked about how
hard and complicated it is just to make like one character do one animation I
feel like making a cutscene is going to be like a bunch of that plus a bunch of
like adding in like moments where like you know you gotta I gotta mix that with
like dialogue and like you know having the functions that like switch between
like progressing dialogue and progressing like character and it's gonna
take a lot of grunt work and I haven't really worked out how it works yet but
whatever I figured out everything else I'll figure it out too and boy I'm it's
very ambitious it's maybe a little too ambitious what I want to show but we'll
see we'll see yeah I wonder I mean game maker is very specific I don't know like
the way in Psycholonial's Hussie just has videos or like flashes probably the
play that would be like a rendered cutscene material right yeah rendered
video like it is not rendered in-game or anything so like if there's a way to
like play a video file in game maker I'm envisioning probably make it I was
considering maybe having cutscenes be presented as like a series of images like
comic panels I might I might do some of that but I would like it if the majority
of it was like it was like the actual sprites kind of like walking around in
the room like they're in-game sprites walking around you know gesturing at
each other having the dialogue boxes pop up as they talk to each other having
little like custom animations go when like when they do things like that's how
I would want to present most of it oh like like a little camera that's like
floating around and and looking at things and no you don't have control I
mean like I mean like you know like you know around in the no that's not what I
mean what I mean is like it's it looks like like you're playing the game like
you know at the very beginning you know Phantom he runs down the ramp and then
he stops and he stands there and then there's little dialogue box and then he
runs like out yeah imagine like imagine that but like with more going on like
maybe like in between lines like he walks around or he like he maybe does a
gesture or maybe there's another character who's like doing the same thing
talking back to him and like they have a back and forth and like they they
enter like they move and they interact and they have they animate with each other
to display some action that's what I'm talking about like it looks like it's
like in-game but if you I feel like this is a concept that there must be a
simple way to describe but I'm just like floundering and finding really
complicated ways to describe it it's like in like in game like gameplay in-game
rendered as opposed to a pre-rendered cutscene I don't know I just want to have
the fucking sprites move around and they go whoa that's it easy easy peasy you
there the they move around as if in-game yes yes like like an undertale cutscene
kind of exact yes I should have just said that I should have just said like an
undertale yes that's what I'm talking about you know like a video game like a
JRPG yeah like that lol I'm sorry I took so long to express that very simple idea
um oh my god okay we're at three and a half hours lamal fuck you Eleazar how
does it keep happening I don't know it's I just have I'm just so filled with I'm
just a full of ideas I'm just so filled with I'm not I'm just filled with
anything brimming brimming with creative potential that just has to flow out of
me and create content create content to be consumed be fed into the algorithm
disgusting it's delicious but I guess I guess we should wrap up if you're if
you're ready to call it a day yes yes okay well that's it then spend as a
voicemail at speakfab.com slash PCB voicemail if you want support us on
patreon at patreon.com slash the procrastinators for a billion fucking
bonus episodes for five bucks and I don't know uh see ya bye the yeah brain
goodbye good night yeah