Hello everybody and welcome to another fantastic, amazing, jammed,
impact, scandal-ridden episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am Tom Oliver, introing
the episode today, and with us we have the master of disaster himself, Munchy J. Trump.
This is a true anecdote. Every single time I open up Audacity Recorded PCP, I'm like
today, like I'm kind of low energy, I don't really want to, you know, like I don't really
want to be crazy, I don't want to scream or anything. I'm just going to take this PCP
chill and it's going to be a chill PCP. And then whenever the intro, whenever Nate's
like welcome to the PCP, I just get that fucking fire in me. I just have to ruin the episode
with my interjections. The low energy of Gibb seeps out of you and the high energy of Trump
seeps in. Yes, yes, yes. And on that note, please clap for Nate. Please clap. I need that
validation. We got Ben St with us as well. Hey guys, hey guys, sorry I haven't been on
a PCP in a while. I've been really busy with life stuff. Sorry if my voice sounds weird.
I'm kind of sick. That's actually true. I woke up today with a terribly sore throat.
I know it's going to get worse. I'm sipping on some hot tea, hot tea featuring apple cider
vinegar with quote the mother, which is a very spooky thing for an apple cider vinegar
bottle to say. The mother is apparently some kind of set of organic compounds that are filtered
out in the non organic in like the non raw. The translation we never got. Yeah, yeah. Instead
it was distilled and shoved into apple cider vinegar. That reminds me of that movie with
Jay Lawrence, mother, you know, the one she looks so hard. Oh, I'm sorry. Dwayne the
Rock Johnson. How was that? I hear it was the worst movie ever. No, no, no, I know I
watched it. It was great. They had the guns in the movie. There's a whole first person
sequence at the end. That sounds kind of cool, like a hardcore Henry style sequence. Yeah,
but like 10 years before that. Weird to have it like in an otherwise non first person movie.
No, it's like at the end and if you're watching the movie and you're like, oh, but where's the
video game? Then you see like, Oh, there it is. Like the very end. They finally like the very
end of this two hour movie. They finally give you what you've been waiting for and make you feel
like you're playing a video game. You know what they missed? You know, we didn't get with that.
We didn't get doom the movie the game. I would write. It's just it's just a modified wad of doom
like the original, but they replaced doom guys face with a pixelated version of the Rock's face.
Yeah. This is what every like the movie of the game thing is. It's just like it's a third person,
like almost collectifon, but like linear. Like a weird mesh of genres that don't compliment one
other very well. It's terrible. So I'm just imagining like this really like super saturated,
like chibi doom guy running around collecting jiggy pieces for only for the Game Boy Advance.
Doom guy Kazooie, the greatest platformer ever.
There's a series of Sam on Game Boy Advance. Yeah, it looks fucked as hell. It looks very
interesting. You know, I just happened to watch a slight update to my life. I actually have watched
a couple AVGN episodes recently. I'm changing my life in a positive way. And like, I'd seen like
one, but never was into the guy or had like, I know it's weird. It's weird. But I'd watch some of
a YouTube or not been into AVGN. I was into John Tron that I just like got into the game late.
I think yeah, like I think I was probably in like college when AVGN started getting big and I just
kind of missed the boat on it. I went back like maybe a year or two ago and marathoned a lot of
it just sort of on the playlist and I feel that coming for me one of these days. Sorry. But I was
just saying that there's a he did a Tomb Raider episode and there's a port of Tomb Raider one for
the Engage, the original PS1 game, which is fucking sick. I remember that was coming out that like
blew my mind that they could put that on a phone. It was crazy. It's a full fucking game. It is a
full game. Like portrait because the Engage screen was a portrait screen resolution and had like a
shitty little D pad. And apparently to get the game in this is fascinating. Okay, if you want to
put in a new game and you're fucking Engage, you pop off the back, take out the battery, put in like
the SD card behind the battery, put the battery back in, close it, and then you're ready to game.
That's because you're playing you're playing the bullshit taco Engage. You need to get the Engage
QD, the remaster version that's better. They redesigned it. It's sick. Is it really sick? Are
you lying to our audience? No, it's fucking shit. It's an Engage and I unironically want to own on
one day. But yeah, you know, do you know how you took phone calls on the original Engage? You had
to hold it on the side. So you had to like hold it like it's basically like if you had an iPhone
and like you put the edge with the buttons up to your ear to talk to it. That's how you talked on
an Engage. It was ridiculous. It was the worst thing of all time. And I want one horribly badly.
Speaking of SD cards, I just bought I just bought on a total whim. I bought Omega Ruby about
Pokemon Omega Ruby. Steve's got some choice words to say about that game. Yeah, I think the whole
world's in choice things to say that. How do you like that battle frontier? How are you enjoying it?
I haven't actually used it yet. I haven't actually played any of it. It's a joke. There's a battle
frontier isn't in it. Oh, I almost fell for it. I almost said, oh, yeah, it's pretty good. It's got
some problems. You know, it's flawed, but it's a pretty good. No, I don't know. Shut up. I hear
it's not good is what I hear. Is that true, ladies and gentlemen? I mean, I've heard people say
that it's the best. Like, I have seen people. Okay, maybe it was just a joke, but it seemed like
on 4chan, like on Oh, that's a joke. That's a joke. That's a real joke. Is it really? Okay. No,
yeah, it's not well loved. They absolutely hate that game. They think it's the worst. Do people
prefer like the actual Gen three games to the Omega remix? Yeah, they prefer. I fucked up. Yeah. Yeah,
whatever. You I think you literally have fell for a meme. I think you saw one thread that was like,
dude, why can't we go back to Omega Ruby and Alpha Sapphire? You read the title and then all the
replies saying that that game of shit and you're like, you know what, like, I just read it. This was
like a couple years ago. I think I just read a thread of people being like, what's the best gen
and like a lot of people were in there saying Omega Ruby, Alpha Sapphire. So I just thought, huh, I
guess those are pretty popular. Zoomers left and right, love and Omega, whatever. Alpha, whatever.
They need to be killed. We need to call the also we have to stop human progress. Do you remember
when you get like to like this, the sixth gym, like you just get to the second part of the game,
and then out of nowhere, like not in the original game, just like out of nowhere. Laudiasse shows up
and it's like, Hey, do you want to capture me? Oh God. Yeah, I know that that happens and it makes
me mad. Is that the one where someone just gives you a Lucario to that's not that's in gen six. Okay,
no, I meant X and Y. Yeah, that's in Lucario on that. And X and Y. You know, okay, okay, that's the
one I skipped. But the real is someone gives you an egg that has real in it. So I feel it's
slightly better at least work to get a sort of I guess like, I don't know. Yeah, like, didn't they
give you an EV egg in the original game in gen one, right? Gen one doesn't have eggs. It doesn't. No,
there's no eggs in gen one. There's no breeding. I know there's no breeding. Whenever you get it,
you get an EV from somebody if you go in like the back. Oh, they give you an EV egg and sun and
moon. What are we talking about? Isn't there like graffiti in one of the buildings where you can get
the EV egg? I think if you like clicking on the walls and you can read like someone was here. Is
that true? Yeah, like a meme program? Like the bloods were here, like the crypts were here.
Oh, how could I forget about that? The blood reds and the crypt blues, the legendary rivalry. Hey,
all this talk of Pokemon's getting me really anxious. Let me take a long sip of my off brand
LaCroix here and just relax for a second. Oh, my God, Nate, I just come up with some totally
organic natural conversation star point based on you drinking that LaCroix. Like just like you
drinking that drink and maybe think of a totally organic thing to say currently busly like continue.
There's a lawsuit against LaCroix. It's happening. It can't be. No. So tell me the deets. What's
that? Is it about cancer? Does it cause cancer? Is that something? Everything does. Okay, okay. Yes,
but but more like it will kill you. Like not like like in a cancer. Can I just point out? Can I just
point out what the fuck? No, it has been so bizarre to see these from zero to a hundred like spread
of LaCroix over the last like year or two. I no idea how that happened or even why anyone buys it,
including me. Why do you buy it? It's slightly it's slightly more pleasant than just drinking water
slightly worse. And then the other thing is the convenience of just grabbing a can of something
I agree 100% that is the only reason I buy it is because I'm conditioned to like can drinks. Yeah. And
this is just a way of weaning myself off like the poison that is the first time I ever had it. What
was it? Ben's house in Atlanta and I drank it and and and he was like, what do you think? And I was
like, I okay. I don't really like it's okay. Nobody likes LaCroix. I have I have negative
associations with LaCroix. But mostly I just like I like soda better. And like, I don't think
soda is poison. Tom like it has flavor. It's not keto, though. Isn't it poison? Oh, God,
this is my fucking pet peeve. People don't fucking understand what diet soda is. Oh my God,
they're everywhere. They're everywhere. Infecting society. It's so simple. I want to know sugar
in diet soda. Is it not real soda or something? How is it not real soda? It's it's like gay. What
Nate would say if it's you can't have diet and soda at the same time. It's not what it is. It
not made of like so like sugar derivatives that just yeah. Yeah, sure. But that doesn't count
because you don't digest them. I mean, I guess so. No, no, no, I guess so. There's no fucking
gray hair here. Well, okay, I mean, okay, if I have if I have like a four piece puzzle, and I
remove one of the pieces, I still have the three pieces, can I really say this isn't the puzzle
anymore? That's an insane thing. That's the word. I don't I don't deny what you're saying at all. It
is 100% true that diet soda is fine. But like, if I had this right, is this like a big thing that
happens all the time? If I raised my son to be in the military, my beautiful baby boy, I cut off
his legs, would he not be my son anymore? Ben, why are you taking this position, Ben? What's wrong
with you monster? It's like, it's like, I don't know. It's like if people thought that like,
there really were like little people in the in the television. And you're just like, and you're
like, no, you see, it's just an image, right? Like, it's just an image projected on the screen. And
people are like, and people are like, yeah, I guess you're right. But but but you know, it's kind
of like, it's kind of like there's little people in the television, right? Like, no, you're an idiot.
Okay, look, all that really matters is so so just consuming this in any way interfere with the
whole point of ketosis and the whole keto. Some people don't play well with certain artificial
sweeteners. So for some people, it might yeah, Tom was asking me about heavy cream before the
stream. But but for some people, artificial sweeteners aren't good for keto, but it depends on the
person. And in general, yeah, they're fine. As like, I think keto is becoming Ben's equivalent to
holocaust.
No, this is my anger is not it's not a keto thing. It's just like munchy.
It's that old keto rage. You're not innocent. You're not innocent. Because like, I talked to I
talked to you and and Kazi about like soda and you both did like a thing that was like, I don't
know if you're still doing it. But you were like, yeah, we're both cutting out soda, because like
soda, you know, is bad for you because of sugar. And I'm like, what about diet soda doesn't have
any sugar? And you both are like, yeah, but it's still soda. Like there's still kind of little
people in the television. So the only reason I don't want to drink diet soda is because I don't
like the way that it tastes like universally. Okay, well, that's a whole that's all right. That's
a whole other can of worms. And I don't understand people that think the diet soda tastes bad.
But I know that that's like taste like that's just up to an individual. So I can't argue with
that. I don't understand it. But I can't argue with nothing but water and juice for years. And
then like, like Michelle turned me on to La Croix, we've been getting that for a little while,
you know, La Croix variants or whatever. And like, I feel like it is a gateway to soda. Like
because I'm drinking these, I'm way more likely. But it's like, it's like vaping, right? Like, yeah,
you could argue that vaping is like a gateway to smoking. But you can also say that like if you
smoke, like drink soda, and you can vape instead. And maybe it has like none of the negative, maybe
you can replace the one bad thing with this less bad thing that doesn't have the negative side
effects. Go that way. It's all about your perspective. But if you're already straight edge,
then like why even entertain any of these? Vaping could be a gateway to smoking. Why
could I change the drinking calories life? Yeah. Vaping could be a gateway to smoking. I would
never drink a calorie except for heavy cream. But vaping could also be a gateway to quitting,
depending on which way you look at. Well, that's what I'm saying. Yeah, like, okay, for a smoker,
getting into vaping could definitely be a step in the right direction. Exactly. To like a healthier
life. You guys in your fuel, I want the post food life to be like calories or individual,
like Cheerios. And each Cheerio is one calorie. And you just count them out. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you count them out exactly 2000 different mornings. Yeah. And then I can divide each meal
by 10. So it's easy to multiply and slash or divide. So my breakfast could be like 100 calories.
I do have my fuel right with me right now, as a matter of fact, incidentally. I'm on my second
up. I restocked recently, by the way. So I've got two more bags fresh, ready to go, feeling good.
We actually returned to the LeCroy lawsuit. I just want to chill. I just want to chill for some
of the free advertising for tea. If you are like wanting to get out the soda life, I highly recommend
tea is tea is the best food. It is the talking about like, I'm drinking tea right now. As I said,
tea with apple cider vinegar with the mother is great. I was right the whole time. He tea is
the best. There was prep work, though, that a lot of people are too. Oh, no, very little,
very like like a 10 minutes, you know, you can take like, you can do this is what me and my
housemates do. We have like a big like a big mason jar, like a gallon mason jar. And we put
tea bags in it and you can put it in the fridge and let it steep. And like by the next day,
you'll have like cold brew tea. And you can make and you don't have to like spend any time.
The danger there is oversteeping. Because if you oversteep, it gets really bitter.
What I do is I have a David's tea seeper and I can just it's a super simple,
like streamlined ice. I actually enjoy ice tea more. I actually enjoy my tea cold more often.
I'm just drinking hot today because of my throat. Yeah, I almost only. I mean, what I would do when
I wanted to make like ice tea or iced coffee, because like back at my other house, we had
we had one of those water like coolers, but it had hot and cold water. You had balls. So what
you would do is you would just take the hot water, you'd steep the tea in that really quickly,
and then you just mix that with the cold water and then we get iced really quickly.
I want to tell my my first my first interaction with LaCroix. Nate, do you remember Alex,
our cousin Alex's wedding? You were there. Yeah, a nightmare. I don't think I was there,
but I remember you weren't. Oh, I was there. I hated it. It was horrible. Okay, I believe you.
But they had, but they had LaCroix. I'd never seen LaCroix before, but they had LaCroix.
And, you know, I think something was going on. I was like kind of over in a building. I was going
out to like go back to the tent that everyone was fucking around in or whatever. And I, I grabbed
a LaCroix thinking that because it has like a fruit flavor, right? It says like, oh, you know,
pear or whatever. And I was like, okay, in the factory where LaCroix is canned, like elsewhere,
in like a separate section, they're like processing fruit. Like that's how they make LaCroix. Yeah,
yeah. So, you know, I started drinking it and I'm like, well, God, because I am expecting something
sweet and like pear flavor, but it's only it's something that's just sort of smells like a pear,
but it doesn't taste like anything. Why that was what I was about to bring up next. How can
something that smells as good as LaCroix tastes so disappointing? Yeah, like it's a fucking trap.
So I went. So I went to the, this was pre keto, obviously, I went to the bar, like there was an
open bar, but it had been like abandoned because like, you know, the like dinner was about to start.
And I just went behind the bar. It was an outdoor thing. And I just grabbed some grenadine and like
just poured some grenadine into it to try and sweeten it. Someone thought I was trying to spike
my drink, but I was like, no, I'm just trying to make this LaCroix taste like real. So drink,
huh? Like a problem? Like, were they like, Hey, don't spike. No, they love, no, no, they laugh.
They're like, huh, trying to get trying to get wasted. I was like, no, just just kind of doesn't
taste very good. It is a wedding where people do drink, but okay, whatever. Yeah, no, no,
they weren't criticizing me. They were just like, haha, this guy is about drinking. It was like,
you and me, buddy.
Yep. So that's it. Best smelling LaCroix, best smelling LaCroix passion fruit. The LaCroix
lawsuit is that LaCroix is sparkling water and people are saying that that is false
advertisement because it says that LaCroix is a natural drink. It is advertised as a
natural drink. They're saying that sparkling water is not natural.
The carbonation is artificially added.
Yes. But we're talking about natural ingredients.
They're saying to carbonate it, they have to use pesticides and stuff like that.
All right. Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's the whole thing. There's like a chemical from like
cockroach insecticide that they use in LaCroix and people are really upset about it.
Okay. Now, I'll be happy to hear people out and see if this lawsuit goes forward. But like,
for example, there's also probably like, you know, carbon in like some like poison and then like,
hey, there's also carbon in the stuff that we eat every day. That's fucked up, dude. It's the
same shit that's in poison. You know, so like. I don't think the claim is that it's poisonous.
I think the claim is that it's artificial. This sounds like somebody in California
really just wants some money. That sounds like somebody in California really just thinks GMOs
are real. Yeah, this is my mom. My mom is the one with this lawsuit.
I gotta tell, there's like some of the stuff I don't want to say, but okay, like I'll just say
that like I have stories of people I know that like, for example, they work in like the food
industry and like there are people who come up and say like, does this have GMOs and they'll be
like, no, um, has it touched anything that had GMOs? And if the answer is maybe or yes, they're
like, well, then I'm not going to consume that. No, thank you, sir. Like even even being in proximity
to things like, do they have people know what a GMO is? They clearly do not poison you guys.
Is there's genetically modified GMOs in it? There's literally no reason.
Like, like, like, what do they think is going to happen? Like if you touch something that's
genetically modified, your genes get modified. Like, I think people, I think GMO just equals bad.
Is it like, is it like an ethical thing? Like, they just don't think we should be fucking with
nature. I shouldn't eat literally anything because there's literally nothing that we eat that we have
not genetically bred to be. What kind of person like would would not want to eat something that
had touched GMO on, like, ethical grounds as opposed to like, it seems like a health one to
be doing. My mom, my mom is this person, 100%. She is full stop like everything that is bad about
like that mentality. And you know what, even if in 50 years or 20 years or 10 years, one year,
whatever, if we prove that all GMOs are literally evil poison that are killing us 20 years early,
they still give no credit to the people freaking out about GMOs because they have no reason to
believe that. There's no way they could have actually known. They're just right by accident.
So I'm protecting myself from, told you so. I actually tried to talk to my mom about this because
she's super anti-GMO. And I was like, like, I was explaining to her that, you know, like, like,
this is nothing new. Humans do this sort of thing all the time. We're just doing it faster now. It's
the only distinction. And she just had, like, no response. But she just did like, well, like,
there's still little people in the TV like, yeah, sure. Like, it's still cancer.
Her soul, her soul retreated. Her soul faded from her eyes into the back of her skull that she just
heard, all around me are familiar faces. Yeah. That's what they do. That's, I don't know. It's
all a bunch of bullshit. Anyway. Do you think that LaCroix is false advertising? Do you think
that they deserve to be sued? I mean, if they're using, I mean, I don't know, what's the criteria
of naturalness? Like, what exactly does it mean? I'm going to go to Urban Dictionary and find out
right now. This will help. This will be very helpful. I'm sure the people on Urban Dictionary are big
LaCroix drinkers. I'm sure they are too. I'm sure that's actually true. Probably because they're big
lemurs. And it's kind of their big millennials. All right. I googled the proper terms,
all right, natural. Okay, this is now we don't want the noun one adjective.
Okay, no, that's not it either. Breasts that don't have implants. No, that's not it. I mean,
that is true. God damn it. These are all fucking nouns. Okay, no. Oh, does that mean that fake boobs
are GMOs? Yeah, exactly what it means. That and nothing. Okay, here we go. Number six down is
relevant. One, to be free of any superficial artificial media or society created additives.
Are we really using the Urban Dictionary definition to try and figure out, to try and like
decide this court case? What higher authority is there, Ben? To decide this court case against
against LaCroix? So you're like at the courtroom, the judge is like, hold on, before we proceed,
we must assess our definitions. And he pulls out his tiny little spectacles. The defense
Urban Dictionary defines it as, yeah. The prosecution calls for a sidebar. And like,
oh, it takes out their smartphone and shows this Urban Dictionary page. Well, you know,
the thing is, I pulled up the Google Dictionary one just now. The thing, there probably is a
very specific codified food, what's the food and drug administration, like definition of what
natural means. Like, for example, if you want to say that you have whole wheat, then like in your,
in your bread or whatever, if you make your bread company, you can have, as long as there's any
amount of whole wheat, it could be 99%, like white bread stuff, and then 1% whole wheat,
and you can get away with that. But specifically, the label of 100% whole wheat, which you should
always buy, ladies and gentlemen, buy the way, because that is better for you. Look for 100%
whole wheat. If it doesn't say 100%, it's probably 99% bullshit. That's just like filler.
Every time I think about the FDA, the only thing I can think about is this old Onion article,
that's like FDA and N, hold on, N, T, like the T, A, R, something.
It just matters. It's the food and drug administration and the like tobacco alcohol
and firearms administration, like get together to throw a rad party, and like the food and drug
administration, like we had tons of food and drugs, but nothing to smoke, drink, or fire.
So we got together with the Tobacco Alcohol and Firearms Association, and just,
and just threw a rager, and it was a great idea. Yeah. It's like the association of bad decisions.
And you combine them. I mean, if you're the smoking alcohol and firearms,
so yeah, just like nothing but bad calls all around.
There's the FDA, like it's the food and drug. So I imagine drugs are things like pharmaceuticals
and stuff. Is that like like hard drugs or something? Are they? No, dang dong. It's
that's like, they're the people that decide when like clinical testing has reached sufficient
like levels that like a drug is like sellable in stores. I just wonder if it was also under the
jurisdiction. No, because no, wait, like illegal drugs? Like no, they're illegal. Of course,
a government regulator doesn't have to regulate. Maybe they were the body chart of deciding what
should be illegal and what shouldn't. I mean, I don't know. Maybe they're involved in it. Maybe.
Well, there you go. All right. Well, we've said it in the Croy question. Yeah. Are they guilty or not guilty?
Absolutely guilty. Absolutely guilty. Absolutely guilty. Absolutely guilty.
The Croy is a crime against humanity as it stands. So even if, yeah, they're guilty of that,
hey, hey, speaking of groceries, I'm just going to gripe. I'm just going to gripe for a minute.
I've been trying to order my goddamn groceries. Like a couple of weeks ago, I ordered some groceries
on the internet. Instacart was the app I was using. Okay. And you know, it charges like a
little surcharge for the delivery, but like whatever it's really it saves me like two hours.
So it's great. Yeah. So I was trying to use it. And then today I go in and it's like a card
declined. And I'm like, well, I don't know why that would be because I just used my card yesterday
at a store and it worked fine. So I tried to pay with Google Pay instead, which did it. I put the
same card in Google Pay accepted my card. I hit send. And it's like, and it's like, internet
doesn't work. The internet obviously works because I'm using the app in the first place, like internet
seems to not be connected. It's totally connected. Instacart just won't fucking let me buy
groceries from it. I'm hungry. Damn it. I want my fucking walnuts. Hashtag let Ben eat.
Walnuts are expensive, dude. Holy shit. They're not as expensive as Brazil nuts,
which I was eating a lot of because they're very low carb. However, they're also very high in
selenium. And if you eat more like two Brazil nuts have your day's supply of selenium. What is
I was eating by the handful. So like hitting like thousands and thousands of my daily value
of selenium, which causes like brittle fingernails and probably death. I don't know.
This fancy steak dinner, dude, that's expensive. It's not as expensive as facial reconstruction
surgery. That's not that expensive. I don't know. For nuts, they're fine. I love and I just love nuts.
You know, I don't want to try especially ligmen nuts. Get it? What? I said, I love nuts, especially
ligma. What's Bofa? What's up dog, Ben? What is up dog? As the PCP turns into people clamoring to
be the next person to be post noun. Here's the newest post now that I'm going to introduce. I am
post groceries, because I have no need for groceries, because my entire life is now revolving
around Hello Fresh, which I have become a devote follower of. I don't tell me about it.
No, that's what I'm going to come right out and say before you. That's stupid. That's
fucking stupid. Why is that stupid? Why is that stupid? Okay, Hello Fresh, it's like buying groceries,
but they only deliver you as much as you need for exactly one meal at a time and they cost 10
times as much. That's Hello Fresh. Okay, they do not cost 10 times as much. And why would I need that
over flow? Why would I want more? I don't know. You fucking buy and bulk to save fucking money. You
don't, oh, they'll send you like, oh, they'll send you like two beef patties and one fucking mango
to make chutney out of. And that's what you get for like an entire day's worth of food with Hello
Fresh. Bullshit. That's all you need to make the meal that they have made. Yeah, you're one meal for
one day, which you get like three times a week. So you can eat three times a week on Hello Fresh.
You know, I, and it's great. It's a great time. I'm thoroughly enjoying it. My lifestyle has been
crippled by my inability to make time to go get groceries or eat. I want to use some of this
technology to solve this problem in myself. It may use Instacart. Instacart's really good when it
works. I've been thinking about doing Postmates. I don't know if that works. I don't know. I've
never heard of it, but I do it. Okay. Well, before you go on Nate, the reason I defend Hello
Fresh is small, like sample size. Yeah, tell me about it. It makes it super. Well, do you know
anything about Hello Fresh? You know what it is? Nothing. I want to be educated. Okay. Okay. Hello
Fresh is a service where you can pay like per, I think it's per week and they send you meals every
week and it sends you like recipes that they have made. It's like Hello Fresh official recipes
for these really great dishes and they send you literally everything in the recipe. Are you sponsored
by Hello Fresh? If not, why not? They send you the exact ingredients you need in the exact amounts
you need for a specific recipe for a dinner for like two or whatever. Yes. And it's great because
then you have the exact amount of things that you need. So cooking is super easy. And this
sounds good. This is like my gateway into cooking things is because that's what I want. I want
that so bad. I'm sick of being a failure. Okay, Nate, check out this shit. It is designed so that
every meal like like every single thing is 30 minutes to 40 minutes to make all total like like
Oh my god, 30 minutes? And at these low low prices? I can't afford not to. They're delicious.
Everything I've made has been fucking the cream to cream. It's been fantastic. I've been
doing everything. And not only am I getting to be able to cook, I mean, I'm taking off the train
wheels. I'm ready to cook things that aren't on recipe. I've been holding my skills to like do
things at once. I'm connecting with my mom. I do it with my mom. It's family bonding. All your
problems. Yeah, nothing is nothing is nothing in this world is less post food than what the
fuck. I don't even remember. What are we talking about? Hello fresh? Hello fresh is the least
post food thing ever. Why would I want to be? I am anti post food. I am anti post food. I'm
just coming out right here and saying no, listen, stupid. You'd buy just buy buy the
fucking bear is sent by the fucking basic building blocks of food and eat them in the amounts that
you need to survive. And don't even worry about anything else. Oh, great. I can put some I'll
have some fucking I'll braise these red onions to put on my on my my stupid, you know, a black
Angus, you know, bird patty with some some some some smoke out because when you want to eat foods,
you want to taste the food that you put the work. No, you want to taste the food. Literally,
who fucking cares? Everyone put the post food group cares about what they're putting in their
body. And this is the only reason the food is a cultural institution. The only reason it's
so that you can trick idiots into thinking you have a skill by putting it together like oh,
I looked at this recipe on Google and now it tastes really great. You can't do it. You couldn't
do it. So whether that's important, you know, I think I looked up exactly how to put this onion
on top of this cheese on top of this lettuce. So I have the perfect burger five minutes later.
It's destroyed and it's worthless. It's a totally ephemeral, pointless experience that adds nothing
of value to the world. Your life is full. Life is full of the value is cooking it in it of itself.
That is an inherent skill and waste my fucking time with someone else. Then the point of the meal
is not only arranging, arranging bits and pieces, arranging bits and pieces into a cultural
institution of unethically optimal. We've made all these different recipes now, these different
flavors. We've honed the craft of eating. This is part of our civilization. It's part of society.
We've evolved the business way. We've perfected this part of our biology. You don't even know
shit. No, no. Oh my god, shut up. It's a cultural and tribal endeavor. You are stuck in the past,
Munchie. You're a hardcore conservative. I am a liberal hero post food and we all need to evolve
past these pathetic, weak human desires for things that taste good and just get down with the...
Thank you. Thank you. I can rest easy knowing that the millenials, the simple, the simpleton
millenials are not in your favor and there are the HelloFresh subscriptions every single day.
I can rest easy. Me, CEO of HelloFresh, Munchie J.Fresh. You don't have Digi or Gib to defend your
weak team here. You're up against the full post food boys here at the spot. I want to say, I want
to say, I think that HelloFresh embodies the absolute worst attitudes of the 30-year-old boomer
and the intellectually laziest, least good segment of the millennial population.
The people that are getting HelloFresh, these are cowards who are, they are like, they are working
their nine to five selling beads on Etsy and thinking that that makes them artists. These are
people... Dirty poor, they're doing dirty poor. They're just mixing some paints together into a cup
and it's pouring onto a can. No, these are white picket fence motherfuckers. These are white picket
fence, you know, married with two and a half children, pieces of shit that are getting HelloFresh
and Munchie, I think you need to stop this. Okay, okay, like everything that you just said is
retarded. If you're coming home from work, then it's like, oh, I'm not going to do anything with
my, I'm just going to watch TV. But with this, you're cooking something, you're learning a skill,
you can do it with your family. And okay, okay, I literally, like for the first like five meals
in HelloFresh, here's what I did. I got downstairs, I was with my mom, and for the entire family,
we cooked a beautiful, delicious meal. Together, we were talking the entire time I was working with
my mom. I don't talk to my mom like outside of this. I was using that time to not only connect
with my mom, make a delicious dish for the entire family to enjoy. And then we all sat down and ate
dinner together. You could have been playing video games. You could have been playing video games.
Well, yeah. It sounds like the act of preparing a meal could be replaced with anything else.
I mean, but why would you want to be? Because you also get to eat at the end.
Yeah, but it's not, yeah, but it's delicious meal at the end, which is the biggest bonus of all.
Okay, I know that this is like a me problem that doesn't apply to most people, but you have no fine
con- with HelloFresh or something like that, you have no fine control over what ingredients go into
your food. You don't have control over what kind of- I think that's why people like it though.
What kind of macro nutrient profile you're eating. With me, with my, I can just fucking,
I'll just like drink like a quarter, I'll just drink like a quart of heavy cream or a pint of
heavy cream, and I'll eat like a piece of sausage for dinner. This HelloFresh even drop off
quarts and heavy cream. And celery and peanut butter for dessert, and I get the exact nutrients
that I want, and it's up to me, and I don't give a shit. Oh, okay, okay. Well, we'll say this. I
will say that HelloFresh is definitely like a training wheel situation. Yes, that's what I was
going to say. There's a long term, like I'm always going to be using HelloFresh for the rest of my
life. That's what I was going to say, Ben, that I feel like this could be a stepping stone for me to
possibly learn how to not be such a complete terrible human being when it comes to handling my
food situation. But it's definitely a way to open your eyes and be able to realize, oh, cooking
isn't that hard, you know, like the cleanup isn't that bad. It's really not a problem for me to
be able to cook every day. Like Tom, Tom, I know I am a post food boy. I want to be post food. Yeah,
how can you be post food and this at the same time? I'll tell you how. Because Nate's on the
edge, and he realized the errors of his way, so he just wants to see me. No, I haven't realized the
errors of the ways, but the thing is I have human flaws, and I sometimes crave food. We're not going
to get stuck if you just curb your entire brain power. This is how my life goes. This is how my
life goes day to day. That's what I'm getting right now. Okay, sure. I wake up in the morning.
I'll get a heel, and I'll do that. And then like it's later in the day. And then I'm like, well,
I've got no groceries around because I'm a lazy piece of shit who doesn't like plan ahead with
this stuff. What am I going to do? I'll tell you what I do. I fire up Grubhub or I fire up what's
it called? I get some fucking Chinese food. I know it is bad, and I want to stop it. Go back to the
fridge, you get another heel, and you realize that you've conquered your human weakness. I want to
do that, but I just like my hunger overrides my desire for fuel. Nate, try not to eat. Hold
down your finger on the Grubhub app, drag it to the trash, and never make this mistake again.
You can't. You just want to just know. Just know that you can not eat, and it will not harm you.
Intermittent fasting. Go OMAD, all right? You get your fuel, and then that's your one meal a day,
and you're done. You've completely destroyed your human weakness. Okay, maybe I should get into some
of this stuff and actually try it out and see if I can. Nate, when your beautiful son, top of the
class, comes up to you every night, and he's like, Father, Father, I'm hungry, and I'm sorry if you
haven't fed me in three days. Are you going to give him a drink of fuel? Are you going to pour some
fuel into his head and say, Here, drink this. No, you're going to give him a dinner. You're going to
give him a dinner, Nate. The only thing that's passing through your lip is the words of the Lord.
Now, hook up your fucking IV drip of fuel, and feed yourself your fucking weak post-food child.
That's what I'm going to say. I'll give him his daily ration of omega-3 pills and caffeine.
That's right. That's what it's going to be. It's going to be a beautiful future,
Munchie, and your kind will be gone. You'll be long gone. I hope so. I'm ready to die on this hill.
I do mean die. Well, with Ben's plan of just stopping eating, I mean that's... Okay, okay,
I mean it's not permanent plan. Contrary to what you may believe, I actually completely agree with
Ben, and if you choose to stop eating for a week, that's fine. Go ahead. Look, people are like,
oh, you're fashion for three or four days. That's so dangerous. Kyle, come on, dude.
You need to eat. Oh, you're going to... What? I don't know. Do I die? I'm going to...
Ball. Who cares? I don't know. I don't know. I know they had my best interest at heart.
But a lot of people in my discord were like, worried for me, and I did not understand why.
I mean, what's going to happen? What's going to happen? Just consider their life experience,
eating like several times a day every day their entire life, and they've heard about people starving
to death, and you know, I thought of the same source of death. I too have heard about people
starving to death. It's like a virus. If you've heard about someone starving to death, then you
will starve to death. I've heard rumors that if you don't eat, you might die if you go long enough.
I did the fucking research. I looked into it. Has anyone ever tested this theory?
I think not. How long does it take to die if you don't eat? The answer is like a month or more.
I just drive by, you know, like skinny African starving children. I'm just like,
these guys are living the life, man. These guys, they've got it figured out.
They're fucking keto. I bet if they peed on a keto strip, it'd be a dark purple.
Oh my god. Wait, would it be cheater? Which is in our new society. That's how we judge class.
That's how dark your keto is. We've come full circle because purple was the color of royalty,
and now we've come back. That's right. That's right. It's all connected in the great circle of life.
Would it be cheaper to, instead of giving like three meals a day to African children,
we give them fuel supplements. We give fuel to African children. That's kind of the thing.
Fuel supplements that they need. That's one of the like things that like fuel,
and like things like it might salt, possibly, if they could, you know. Do they market it?
It has like so many cute food shortages. Fuel's got to be some like some overpriced
fucking like nutrition sports supplement. Oh, it absolutely is. I mean, yeah. Yeah.
But like the way they're selling it is not like a world hunger solution. No, no, they're selling
us a convenience. The reason they say that is because like for all the fucking soy boys who
want to get on that shit, it makes them feel better about buying it. I guess so. Like you're
not, it's totally marketing bullshit. I don't buy it for a second. I mean, if they could theoretically
get the price really down low and they were able to like get all the you know, theoretically,
but right now they're doing nothing to help that at all. Yeah, like like Soylent was the same promise.
I'm sure we're gonna go to Ethiopia and be like, do you want to pay $60 for two bags of dust? Here
you go. Isn't there some like, isn't there some like rice, some like highly nutritious GMO rice
that is meant as like a world hunger solution? I believe that is a thing that I've heard of.
I've definitely heard something about it from India, I want to say, but I don't remember.
It's never gonna go anywhere though, because it's GMO and we have retarded people.
How dare we help those fucking starving African children. If we allowed GMOs to go
further, then we would probably be in like a utopia right now. Can you imagine like all the
crazy shit people would be able to do and like like weird DNA parts of animals to make foods for
foods and have all the creatures we need. Think of how much closer to Starfleet we'd be if we had
GMOs and stem cells just going full throttle. It'd be good, it'd be good. Yeah, pro stem cells.
The world does suck. So many aborted babies go to waste every year and we need to end this,
we need to end this waste. Yeah, we gotta use them. They've got those delicious little stem cells.
Less babies, more fucking biohacking, that's what I want. Less babies, more rabies, please.
More rabies, please, he says, holding down his hands.
So all right, well man, that was a raucous event, good. I think we all need to cool down after
that. So LaCroix is guilty, right? LaCroix, yeah. We are the judge's jury for the executioner here
on the piece. I've been doing Inktober and it's great. It's an absolutely great hashtag.
Where's day three, Munchy? Where's day three? Oh, I'm doing that right after this. I have the
entire sketch on it. It's like right in front of me, like as we speak. But it's already day seven.
I know it's already day seven, but... Yeah, I skipped it. I skipped it.
You've been posting one every day, but like this one from day three just was so complicated or
something that it was... I don't mean to get... Okay, we'll be up by the time that you hear this,
obviously, viewer. It's not going to be crazy, but I just wanted to do it,
Jessus, because it has somewhat sentimental value to me. Yeah, okay, sure. I can't wait to see sands
and the undertale. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I can't wait to see the first Munchy porn that you'll ever see.
Oh my god. Oh my god. All right, team now ladies. Get in there. Okay, people who are like,
oh, what Inktober? Don't you mean digitaltober? Haha, hashtag protest, hashtag digital art is just
as good as traditional art. There's like an alternate hashtag that's like, I don't know. I've
seen people use like spook, spooky, there's like, there's like alternate hashtags that don't imply
ink. And yeah, it totally gets away from, from what Inktober is. So, Inktober is supposed to be
specifically an analog. They feel so attacked that people are just like drawing traditionally.
They feel so like under pressure, like someone just in their own home is like making a drawing with
pencils and paper. Don't you know that digital art is real art too? Why are you attacking me like
the violence against their art form really? I think it's just because they want to participate,
but they don't want to like actually pull out pencils and paper. Dude, okay, it doesn't matter.
It's not a matter if it like that digital art isn't real art. It's not about having a diverse set of
scales. I mean, I agree. I do whatever I'm just playing devil's advocate. But no, like if Ink,
because like I was under the impression for a while that Inktober was just, just drawing like
black and white with ink, whether it was digital or not, because so many people I saw was doing it
digitally. But then I found out, no, it's supposed to be pen and ink, because like, that's kind of
badass. Like it makes more sense at that point to be a thing. Maybe the reason they're so upset
about this was because when they were a child, there's no control Z in real life and they can't
function without it anymore. They were a young child. These goddamn Zoomers don't know how to draw
with a pen. Yeah, they're walking home from just an average day of Inktober and, you know, holding
hands with their parents, you know, who had just been doing some digital drawing that day and still
were using the hashtag Inktober. And then that damn... They've been doing some digital drawing in
divorce court. Yes. And then that goddamn hardcore Inktober came out and murdered both their parents
and then they became, you know, Batman. It's like, you know, over their body like, no, they were one
day from divorce. I was one day away from two Christmases. So close. Listen, I'm not saying
that like I enjoy traditional drawing quite the opposite. It's like a huge pain in the ass from
stuff to finish. I feel the same way. But it's important to have those skills. It's important
to be able to work in whatever medium that you're given, because that will improve your art skills
just across the board. I don't even care so much about that. Like, I feel like you should just do
whatever works for you because like at the end of like it's good if you want to like kind of like
jerk yourself off about like I can do all these harder things. But at the end of the day, the
people who are going to consume the art, they don't care how it's made. They care what the actual
result is. You know what I mean? I don't think you need to do to know how to do traditional,
but it can't hurt, right? I just think the conceit of the event is to draw traditionally.
Don't be a fucking faggot and try and intrude on that. Just like if it's supposed to be a
traditional drawing thing, do it. If you want us to say like, I don't even have as much of a big
deal with these alternative hashtags. If you just say I want to draw, do a 30-day drawing
challenge this month, but I don't want to do a tober, and you make something else, that's fine too.
I think I'm gonna do like a challenge soon. I don't know. I really, really want to do like a 30-day
like page a day challenge. Like soon. Yeah, good. So that I yeah, and it's gonna be really hard.
But I'm not going to do it now, because I don't want it. It's not an Inktober thing,
and it's not supposed to be. So yeah, I will. You know what? Speaking of Inktober,
I want to give a shout out to Nexus Mania, who's doing a four-panel comic for Inktober.
It's fucking great so far. It is really good. I like it. It is really good. 10 out of 10, great
shit. I love Nexus Mania's art style. I've only really seen his digi art, but I like how stuff is
put in everything. Hey, I've got. I am games drawing. They did. Oh my god. That I am games was
so good. I've got a rant. You showed me that yesterday. Yeah, I have a specific rant about
Nexus Mania, now that he's come up. Whenever I am games. Nexus Mania, I've got a big problem with
you, and this is what it is. I do. It's that you are so good at art, and yet you waste your time
making fan art for people like me, people like Tom and Digi. Why are you doing? You should be
using this time. Tom's like abort, abort. No, no, no. Not even, not even at all. I think,
I think this is, this is a good strategy. And let me explain why. Because like what are you
drawing? Like Markiplier or like PewDiePie or someone who matters, you know? Agreed. No, Nate,
you fool. That's like trying to stream Fortnite. It's too saturated. You can't break into the
market. You've got to do something with lesser appeal. He's got this four-panel comic that he's
promoting right now that he's doing for Inktober, which is fucking great. But then he did the
I Am Games thing, and that got like a hundred something likes, that's what brings the people
in. But what does that translate to for the man? Like, what does he get out of this at the end of
the day? It's probably like a five to ten percent retention rate, but like everything's a five
percent retention rate. Nate, what it gets him is that we're talking about him right now. Exactly.
It's a good strategy. Oh, he's going to get a ton of shit from this, which he deserves. This is
how it works. Yeah, he's going to get a lot of shit. He's going to get a whole bunch of hate. Oh,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Straight to his fucking face. Hey, hey, see you in the car. And then I'm
going to bite bite him because he drew my face, and that's all I care about. Look,
he's a really great artist, and I quite like his stuff. Yeah, that's great. Nexus is unbelievably
good. It doesn't make sense to me. And like, I just, I am constantly astounded that he wastes his
time drawing like things of like me and my drugs. Oh, how disgusting. Oh, wait, did he do the one
of you fighting the girl? Yeah, he did that fucking Inktober of me fighting Cynthia, which was
awesome. Yeah, that's him too. Yeah. It's too good, Nexus. I don't deserve it. Hey, what's the name
of your fucking Super? What's the name of your fucking Gastrodon? Oh, Doon Koon. Doon Koon the
Gastrodon. Yeah, Doon Koon. We had a Doon Koon in the Pokemon XD Nuzlocke. He was a Clay doll. I
think he died. Doon Koon is by like the, he is the God of my run. That and a TTOMZ, the Gyarados.
They always are my two Titans, my two avatars. It's great. I always want to say that like even
really talented artists do fan art like Oda did fucking one or Dragon Ball Z fan art back in the
day. It's fun and they enjoy it. And there's nothing wrong with fan art. There's nothing wrong
with fan art as long as you don't have higher aspirations and you're ignoring them to do fan
art. That's exactly right. Yeah, as long as it's not, yeah, like you shouldn't, if you want to do,
fan art should be a subsidy of what you're trying to do to use as a promotion tool and not take
over your life. Like I ideally, I'd like to do one piece of fan art a month just to continue
perpetuating my brand and have it seep out into the greater zeitgeist of the industry. I actually
haven't done fan art in a long time and I probably should because it is like an important thing for
Yeah, it's a good thing for getting seen but also it's just like it's fun to do and also it's
Yeah, I mean I like it. Like all the fan art I've ever done was stuff that I wanted to do and liked
doing it. Exactly. In the vein of it being good for like promotion, I think it's good even in a
really abstract sense in the way that like if you're drawing fan for something then you like the
property that you're doing the fan art of. And if other people like that, they'll probably like
your art as well because there's probably some sort of like- And also it's a good exercise because
you're drawing something you probably haven't drawn before especially if you're knee deep in a
personal project you're doing the same things over and over again. It gets you to do something
different, breaks it up. My real point was just that like if Nexus or anybody like on their spare
time just wants to like relax and do like a drawing that you know if you're really good it's
going to be really good of something just because you like it a lot, of course that's fine. I just
wouldn't want anyone to waste their valuable time on little old me. On you. I agree. That's
literally what I'm saying. The point is less best guy ever fan art, more I am games fan art.
Confirm from Nate himself. Tom, what are you now? Like who's like like if we want to say best guy
ever then we say best guy ever. What do we call you? Worst guy ever. Worst guy ever. Number one result
on Google image. Confirm. Oh, I guess we call you Polystation 2. I guess that's what we call you.
I don't just- Tom Oliver, it's fine. That's just my name. That's yeah. I've taken the Green Rangers
mantle. Someday when I get rich I will buy a show accurate cosplay of the Green Ranger and
go around with it. It'll be fucking sick. You don't have to get a little more jacked first.
Well, that's that's why I'm going to the gym. They pad those out. They pad those suits out,
but yeah. Hey, can I tell a story? Yeah, sure. I do I do have something I want to bring up but
I will do it. It was relevant. This is totally irrelevant. Mine is completely a left turn as
well so go for it. God damn it. Help. Yeah, I don't have much time. I got to get it out.
Okay, so I would have told this on the last PCP but I wasn't on it. So like two weeks ago
I was walking through Harvard Square and I was like waiting what? Harvard Square is cool dude.
Big mistake. Don't go there. Yeah, okay. All right, so I was like headed towards the
I was around like the subway entrance and there was a guy right there was like a bald you know
20-something guy kicking kicking around a soccer ball kind of near the subway entrance and he says
hey as I walk by and I'm like hey all right so and I hear him like talk I think a police officer
walks by and like they chit chat or something like he's like he's talking to people right he's
just saying hi to like everyone and then I go and I do whatever it was I was doing I don't know
and like I walk back that way because I'm going to the train and he's says hi to me again he's
like hi I'm like a quick and I'm like hey and he's like want to play with me and I'm like well
no I got a train to catch and he's like okay uh do you want my card uh do you want to follow me on
Facebook uh and I'm like uh I'll take your card and he's like okay like I got a card I also got
you know like uh I also got a little like like print out here of like my latest uh like blog
entries and I'm like a print out and I'm like and I'm like you know what I'll take that don't
give me the card give me the full one give me like the full pamphlet I want to I want to I want to
read more and he's like okay here you go and I'm like thanks I'll read it on the train so I did
right uh so I don't know I'm just gonna I'm gonna start reading I won't read the whole thing but
let me just I'll just try and pick out what's in ready for this uh is it okay to say like real human
beings names on the show just do what would they rhyme with I mean I mean this is a guy who's looking
to self-promote so I think it's okay I guess I mean you're doing him a favor technically right like
this is okay I'm doing it I'm doing okay I'm doing it don't make fun of the train guy fans of the
PCB don't make fun of the train guys listen listen I'm not even making fun of him I I think he's
complex right okay I think he's value I think that I think that a lot of him I think that there's
a lot to recommend him all right I'm not being ironic I just want to say right off the bat like
this seems like a ridiculous thing to do but him handing you a pamphlet of his paper bloods is now
putting him in front of potentially almost 20,000 people right he's he lucked out he lucked out with
me that's um all right the saga of Jeff continues dot dot dot my recent trip to Mexico Cuba and Canada
my name around my name jeffrey thomas ferrell facebook
www.facebook.com slash jeff ferrell that's farrel dot 9 6 9 9 uh and then there's a bunch of links
to facebook things which I assume have like the same the same information and videos and stuff
part one mexico first I went to mexico mexico city specifically my flight from boston was on
may 11th 2018 there was a layover in dallas I used air b&b for lodging I got a room for about
ten dollars a night in venustiano caranza right near the airport some of the places I frequented
were the park on caye oriente 172 and caye oriente 168 mercado moctezuma white and black coffee
and herbal life club nutricional on nte 33 what did I do in mexico well first I concentrated on
learning spanish I taught english for free to various people in mercado moctezuma dude you know
he just walked up to people and said like do you want to learn english friend uh yeah wait yeah
yeah I used to see this guy's not a qualified teacher in any way so he was probably just like
he walks up to someone and says hello and they're like uh like I don't I don't you might that seems
to be his go-to strategy in general I mean listen I don't want to I don't want to input if this is
interesting I'll keep reading but like or should I just should I just like cut out snippets yeah I
guess snippets I don't yeah okay okay um later on I started playing soccer in the local park I
would most of the play teenagers but sometimes I would play with kids and adults they would often
cheer me on and call me quote gringo what they call white people from the US I don't think it's
I don't think it's what they're trying to cheer you on I don't think that's like oh like oh gringo
come over here please please sit down there's a link to a video um I played chess with people in
mexico but I do you watch any of these videos is he like I have not I have not actually looked at
any of this is a printout how's he gonna watch them oh I mean there's links but I haven't followed
them you have to type out the link into fucking yeah all right that's some work I need some QR
codes clearly yeah I played chess with people in mexico but I played soccer more often it was easier
and more convenient to hop into soccer games and try and convince people to play me in chess
I did however play some chess in the airport and with people in some of the stores apparently this
guy like apparently he's tried to like make money by like challenging people to later on in here he
talks about how like he wants to like bet money for for on chess games with people but Americans
or Bostonians specifically just aren't willing to bet more than like a dollar at a time okay uh
oh yeah using blah blah blah blah okay something about Cuba I think this is already on dude can
I can I get a link to one of these you want to read me a link so I can go to the fucking YouTube
like right now this is the show notes well his name is his name is I mean the link okay I'll google it
facebook.com slash jeff.ferrell.9699 okay I'm really interested in this guy but I just want to reiterate
don't don't like fans don't make a mug in in this guy's facebook he doesn't deserve it I mean I mean
I don't see why they would okay he's just talking about his trip to Mexico like I don't there's nothing
we're gonna get silly we might we might poke a little bit fun I want that to translate and then
sort of like yeah nobody the procrastinators podcast is not condone here here this this
this one this part stands out to me well hang on bet it was it facebook.com slash jeff then what yeah
.ferrell.9699 okay all right .9699 toward the end of my stay in Mexico I I moved into a five
dollar a night room in a different house this house was very close to the other house I stayed at
unlike the first location I was allowed to invite guests to my room at will here I brought Mexican
women back to my room and played them in chess haha is that a euphemism perhaps he
he I like to imagine that that he like actually did do that and and he was like he was like I mean
I pass it off I was only more than it was yeah no I think well here he continues yeah speaking
speaking of women on average the women in Mexico City are more flirtatious than women in Boston
I suspect it is because gringos are highly sought after there don't get me wrong a lot of women
don't get me wrong a lot of women I hung out with were just friends the thing was I was clearly
getting much more attention in Mexico City than Boston now here I am sitting in both in the Boston
area 26 and single haha haha I like that that's a right that that's a real right my friend I like
I like that part a lot um I was in Mexico City I'm skipping ahead a little bit uh one culture
difference is smoking is more popular here than in Boston for example no one in my family smokes
I was in Mexico City for about three months and I learned the bulk of my Spanish there
by the end of my stay I could say much more than keres hugar ad adres conmigo which I'm pretty
sure means do you want to play chess with me um he he lot he says that he lost weight quickly in
Mexico even though he was eating the same amount I bought a few shirts in Mexico City like the Mario
shirt and a duff one I also made a ton of friends there to the degree it felt necessary to write
many of my facebook posts in Spanish my facebook page is by this is getting a little tedious what
okay okay sorry sorry all right then he talks about Cuba hey hey do you want to know his favorite
quote from his facebook page please god yes all right check this out all right here's his favorite
quote when it gets down to having to use violence then you are playing the systems game the establishment
will irritate you pull your beard flick your face and make you fight because once they've got you
violence then they know how to handle you the only thing they don't know how to handle is non-violence
and humor and let me tell you my boy Jeff the humor is off the charts what the who is that a quote
from I have it does not say who it's a good myself maybe it's himself I mean let's not jump to any
conclusions yeah maybe it's maybe it's someone else yeah Google I'm trying to pop up if it's like
legit pop up it's a John Lennon it's a John Lennon this guy in the pcp okay is there any reason
why we can't do that oh god speaking of which I've been I've been talking to um laser butt fuck
yeah I've been talking to laser yes give me the laser butt okay he's been like a year what's going on
here yeah what the fuck well he was like oh he didn't have like access to his facebook for a while
so it's not all on me um he's got another series I think it's on youtube it's called mica rat and
he wants to talk about mica rat on the show what is it what is it give me I haven't actually read it
or watched it yeah he gave me the links is it like a youtube comic is that what or is like a video
what is it I don't I'm I don't know I wish I could tell you more but I haven't actually looked into
it I assume it's like one of those old ms paint fanamays which I love I love it so um if laser
bot did a fanamay I think I would like explode from joy that sounds incredible you do all the
voice acting himself hold on hold on maybe it's microsoft sam to help him I'm um let me see if I
can I can maybe I can pull it up right now uh yeah he he sent me a link to his old like youtube channel
which apparently okay he's out yeah linked to the first episode mica rat episode one part one I will
I will walk you through mics whoa okay uh so this was posted in 2010 um and apparently he's remaking
mica rat and that's what he's working on right now but this is old mica rat warning there has bad
language you must be 18 r older to walk walk this pro program this program may not be suitable for
younger viewers I hope you enjoy a pre apostrophe this program all right that's fine okay okay and then
and then it's basically a motion comic you know it's it looks pretty much um it looks pretty much
like uh tales gets trolled but you know there's like some some it's like you know shot by shot
minor animation on the mouse movie because you know uh tales gets trolled is mostly just
close-up shots of faces in like an interminable succession yeah and that is pretty much what this
is and there's like some some minor animation on the close-ups the mouse yeah this is great this is
great uh so uh when can we get him on I will I mean I will like watch this tonight and I will
send him a message and ask if he wants to be on next week yeah here's what we do we get the train
guy and we get ladies bottom the same and then none of us show up and we will and I will obviously
I'm gonna link mica rat in the uh I'm gonna link in the description so you so you viewer can be ready
in case we do end up if we can pay train guy like 20 bucks to pretend to be ben sane and
the spot will show up and like hey I'm ready for the pcb and he's like hey it's guys it's me ben
sane do you mean do you mean the new the new story are you talking about the new storyteller
no I'm talking about the guy you met that's jeff fucking jeff yeah oh the train I mean I would
consider him the soccer guy oh he was soccer guy he was I mean yeah he was hanging out near a subway
entrance but he was his most dramatic features are just kicking a soccer ball um that's his character
design he can't see with that he can't see the soccer ball else the silhouette doesn't convey
there is uh there is one I want to leave I want to read the postlude so at the very end he links to
some you know links to um you know he says he's moved he's back in America he's living in his
family's house with like the rest of his family um he says uh a few days after returning to
deadam for the first time in my life I'm noticing some gray hairs which is quite unusual giving my age
26 and heredity it's not that unusual uh the people here also don't appreciate my soccer playing as
much as in other countries some people are quite nice though and they take videos when I request
them my plans I'm looking for quick cash I could get yeah I could get a formal job same brother same
aren't we all I could get a formal job but that takes more time so I'm considering these options
in order of preference one panhandling while juggling my soccer ball in downtown Boston
Chinatown or Harvard I think you thought about me so apparently he went with that one yeah apparently
he went with that one yeah two playing chess for money in Harvard Square the people in Harvard
Square often make very small wagers over games they play five dollars less I I kind of want to go back
because like I think he's got a schedule of times he'll be there go back dude I might go back or like
maybe challenge him to a chess game like literally do it literally do it wait yeah is there any
reason why we can't go to Boston when we're in person get him and take him back to your apartment
to record rfck is there any reason why we can't do that I mean he'd have to consent to it that's
that's the only hurdle I can see a hurdle right there but you know we have ways of getting around
that Jeff I know you're listening to this let's make this my people talk to your people Jeff we'll
get this going and then and then three freelance programming work on craigslist or a similar site
I've done this a couple times but the gigs are hard to come by program for uh yeah he apparently he
saved up money for travel by working a programming job and he mentioned this earlier in the thing but
I skipped it and therefore teaching Spanish the problem with this is that my Spanish is quite
bad compared to native speakers why I feel damn this this cursive fate why why couldn't I just speak
fluent Spanish and I feel uncomfortable teaching something I'm bad at well imagine that unlike
other people and you did school teachers stop you yeah all right so that's Jeff so that's Jeff
Pharrell uh an oddball vagrant that I met in a legend Jeff I mean this unironically he sounds
fascinating I wanted yeah yeah okay yeah and they're on the Grayson no it just imagine it just
and that starts us out at like a train station yeah well I mean it takes all like imagine just
like flying to Mexico and like hanging out in the fucking like town square kicking like juggling
a soccer ball like meeting like kids and adults and stuff and like playing them and women and luring
them back to your house to play chess with you yeah yeah yeah sounds like you know scold them I mean
I mean the the way that he the way that he was just like hi like at me twice like right yeah like
two times I passed him and both times he was just like hi and the second time he was just like want
to play with me like this I don't know you know okay you know what it's gonna sound like it's gonna
sound like an insult to say that he seems like a little autistic or a little off or something but I
don't mean it in a bad way it seems like this is this is like missing that's what this is he's not
in tune with his inhibitions like normal people would be like scared or worried if you do that in
public this seems like this guy just doesn't give a fuck and he just wants to go out he is a respectable
thing yeah yeah yeah have you guys heard the theory that we're surrounded by NPC characters in our
lives and that a lot of people around us don't have souls because there was a there was a set number
of souls in the universe and you see we just keep expanding the human population and so not everybody
has one you know there's one soul it's the same soul reincarnated across time and every individual
transubstantiation I invented it Nate give me I have somewhat related to this I've I've
along because like there's always that that uh that theory that like we're in a simulation
and all that shit yeah yeah right and so like even before I heard about this like NPC thing I always
wondered about the simulation because there are many times that I'll just be out and about and I
will notice like people just randomly walking around that seem to have almost identical faces to
people I've seen before and it feels like the random character generator is like starting to loop
it's like terrifying yeah so often I will see someone and think okay I said this to a friend
the other day and they laughed at me because in a way it's obvious I said lots of people look like a
combination of two other people which was sure was dumb because everyone has two parents that
they're a combination of but that's not what I mean fair enough I mean that all the time I'll see
someone was like oh that looks like you know you know my friend my friend Tom and my friend John
that looks like a combination of you know if anyone looks happy and and so and so or something or
that looks like well my instincts tell me about that which is probably true is that we kind of
pick out features that are recognizable and the people that we know in our lives I'm sure it's
it's like that I mean because like we're humans are great at patterns so I'm sure yeah we just
ascribe that to it but it just it feels weird to just be out and about and being seeing like someone
who's clearly not that person that looks almost identical but like here they are in a completely
different scenario and situation and it's just like oh god oh god I'm starting to see NPCs repeat
themselves this is this is pretty fucked up and it's terrifying ever since I saw the Truman show
I've always been afraid that like I'm in the Truman show but like a virtual reality version
that's way more like intense and like sure yeah yeah and it's just like made me and like it's like
oh god everything's a lie and and ever since I saw that movie it's always in the back of my mind
and uh it's not even that I think like I'm that important it's just like a terrifying thing to
me to think like this whole thing's a joke and everyone's watching me all the time okay I'm about
to speak in really cynical like vocabulary but I do not mean it in like a mean sort of way
whenever I see those sort of people like like like soccer guy I always think like I realized too late
that it would be fun to not like mess with him but I would describe as like mine him to be able to
like talk to him and like exhaust his dialogue options yeah yeah yeah yeah like like like like
like a quest person and I want to I realized too late that I what I should be doing instead of just
saying like oh like no like no things just you know and walking away or instead of just like you know
like someone looks like it means like hey I have a dollar I'm like uh yeah okay and then what's the
what is it I should talk to him what's that what's that alt rfc k it's the pissy baby something
fucker fappers right I feel like that's the pissy baby route just be like yeah no I gotta go
I can't stay as opposed to the rowdy fucker who'd get in there dude and make a best friend
yeah it's like it's like a pissy baby fapper fuckers there's also the adult baby diaper lover yeah
hey does my mic sound weird because my my computer just made a weird noise at me and now I'm
worried you sound fine to me right I sound fine yeah okay then yeah it's okay yeah it looks it looks
alright okay it's not only a matter of me like not wanting to it's just a matter of like oh wait
fuck that was one of the people that I can do that too it's like you can't do that to just like
everyone it's not like when if you someone says hi to you it's gonna be a normal person like
if someone's got a guitar and they're asking for money they might have a story they might just be
like a cynical you know just like oh you're trying to make a quick buck you know by lying to people
or whatever but I think I think there's a very good chance that people like that like street
performers are like fucked up weirdos not in a bad way clearly just they're just fucked up weirdos
and it would be fun to talk to them and I just it's a real issue like if you see somebody like
that they clearly have a story yeah and there's so many opportunities that you're passing up
by not investing this guy's definitely got a story it's like it's like a massive like what what
compelled him what compelled him to travel to Mexico Cuba and I forget what the third one is and
juggle his soccer ball in a public square it's it's what compels him to do it even now what what's
his deal like how did you get from like a normal human upbringing to this it's it's it's it's just
you know you know exactly we're the ones all stuck in the box and he's the one thinking outside
I would agree it completely that's why I was like no fuck don't give me your card give me your full
fucking printout yeah yeah I want the full story he's clearly much more free than we are yeah I mean
that's true well for a while it seems like he's run out of money and now he's moved back home
another plane but he's his spirit is still free he can always get another program a job somewhere
I'm sure yeah right yeah well what a fascinating experience to hand out your blog entries printed
out in public like this is going to return on investment you know doing that if he gets on
that's what I wonder I wonder if he thinks I like I wonder if this has any like monetary return for
him or if he thinks it's going to or if it's just a social show well yeah yeah he's gonna make bank
off of that yeah it's good it's gonna be it's gonna get that sick we're gonna pay him an exposure
and then he's gonna get tons of fun not to draw a particularly unfavorable comparison on purpose
but like this does sound fairly similar to the like need gf sign that chris chan would hold up and
kind of you know well only only vagus sessions no but well I wouldn't say it's malicious it's just
creepy like that I'm not even trying to say he's creepy I just mean it well well chris was being
creepy holding up a sign that's like come and talk to me if you want to be my girlfriend like I
don't know it's so creepy though I think it's not gonna work obviously uh yeah I think it's just
such a social it's not malicious it's not bad it's not evil but yeah it's it's icky and it's like
what what I mean what are you doing yeah that that's fair this guy I just I don't know I don't
know what the end goal is here I wonder I wonder if it's just like it's like just very raw and
honest it's just like I want to share this stuff that's why I put it on Facebook and now I'm bringing
it out into like the real world you know I'm sharing my Facebook post in the meat yeah I have a I have
a crazy crazy theory maybe he just wants to make friends because friends are good I'm staying
in valuable and increase the worth of your life maybe that's why I thought of the question can you
imagine because someone like chan would want friends but no cuz because yeah we have a sign
like advertising himself like for friendship you know with a girl but still same no me it's not
the same at all totally different totally different alright this is what this is literally
out of no no no no no no no no no he's out he's out no he's out he's not the same as
fucking with a girlfriend this is why it's different I don't get it this is why it's
It's different because with Chris Chan. He's saying he's like imposing like you become my girlfriend
What what this guy's doing? He's just putting himself out there. Yeah letting you come to him. It's totally different
But but he's just doing that too. He's letting you come to him
No, because because Christian is starting with an ass. He's saying like be my girlfriend
Yeah, I was saying like be my friend. He's just saying hey, I would say that I want to play soccer
I would say that the implication of Chris's sign is that anything less than a romantic connection is
Unwanted and unwelcome sure okay, but like this guy. I'm sure this guy
I'm sure if this guy got a girlfriend from doing what he's doing. That would be fine
I'm sure if he had sex with a lady. Yeah, or whatever wink or better yet
Play chess that would that would be fine. Yeah, or playing chess in his hotel room
This guy is like just looking for any kind of interaction. It's sort of as little as like taking a piece of paper to like maybe
I'm being on a podcast. Maybe it's just maybe there's no business goal here
Maybe it's just as simple as go out there, you know panhandling because he says panhandling in the thing
Yeah, go out there, you know have a hat like if people want to give you money to juggle
So it's the soccer ball meet people and be social and you know reap the benefits that come with that
Generally seems totally fine. Whatever they may be. I want to move this from joke to reality
Literally, can we like if we see him in a harper's grave cuz I'm sure we would go there anyway regardless
Let's really get him in our an RFC camp. So there's no reason not to let's I really
Really doubt that he's gonna be down to come
Like hey do you like me on a blog? Do you want to be on a let's play with us? I
Don't think that would I think I think he's the kind of guy that would go for that
I guess I guess we could ask
Let's ask I don't see it. I don't see it working say is yes, and then murder you
Cuz he's probably got plans
He's got big plans. Okay. I think he's the type of person who would have a free calendar and be down to not only just come on
This let's play for fun, but also to like push his
He says he needs a permit
I think that he's got a permit and he's probably got a plan
He's gonna be there from such-and-such time to such-and-such time
When he's free, I don't know maybe maybe I think we should ask I think we should definitely ask him can't hurt
This might be the adult baby diaper that we don't I don't see it working out
I don't see it working out. I'd be surprised if we can
If nothing else you should just do something for rowdy fuckers on the spot right there
I
Seems to like he seems to like strangers taking videos of him. I mean there you go
We could just record ourselves playing. Oh, they will be a let's play of soccer. We can just we need to stop
Let's play. Oh, let's just let's play time to talk, you know
Yeah, all right. All right guys the only way this will fail if he sees not there
We will get some sort of RBCK content if he's there even if it's just us record
Yeah, I think he's got a schedule
Maybe or you can just message him on Facebook. That's true. We have this contact. Oh god. We could do that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
What's his Facebook? I've got a link. I'll post it later. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I've got you
So that's so that's Jeff that's Jeff the soccer guy. Yeah, what what a what a legend
What what a what a what a sick dude coming soon to a podcast near you. I sure hope so
I wait with baited breath. That would be pretty that'd be pretty neat. That would be pretty fucking neat. Well team
What do you say? We just transition to questions now? I feel like we've really done a bunch of good shit here and
I don't know high note. Yeah. Yeah
That's a good idea. All right. All right sick. Let me uh
He's not up there at the pantheon of the likes of like Colt Corona and
I don't know. He's a great PCP character. That's right. He's going to be the wrong one real quick. If he's on the RFCK
He's going to be in the next round
I mean, can we give him a soccer ball or something? Maybe. Yeah. All right. All right. Soccer guy soccer guy's soccer outfit
I don't know or what is it? It's uh, so everybody voice mails. Here we go
Oh, I didn't ask for questions in the in the lounge. I'll do that right now. Oh, yeah, I do it
You know what we're skipping Twitter this week. Fuck you people pity questions are dead
No, okay. Yeah, we have a boy have a better way. Yeah, you know what?
I am out of pity this week just because I forgot so sorry everybody
But I didn't tell you that there'd be any questions. So you haven't lost anything. All right. There you go
I feel like I feel like audio questions carry us like pretty far
We've got quite a few things that say like just literally stop doing the text questions and we could definitely possibly
Yeah, I mean, I've been thinking that maybe they're just like this is just a better way. Yeah, let's just
Let's just cancel it. Let's cancel text questions. Why don't you go cancel that?
Okay, okay, I'm literally going to say actually never mind literally. I'm typing it to canceled
All right, I'm sure I'm doing it hang on where can our viewers go to ask us an audio question
They can go to speak pipe comm slash
PCP voicemail, right? Correct. Yeah, that's the one. That's where you go people
All right
Shit everyone's freaking out now that we're never doing again
Who cares if they got a question they can ask it in speak pipe
Okay, here I go. All right. Here we go first question
We got to check in of course with with one spar on his continuing quest to do something very true
Yeah, I feel like I'm out of out of touch with the saga. Yeah
He was like he was arrested by the police last episode. I think because he was trying to get in starbucks time stamps
Oh, yeah, that's right. He was kicked out of Starbucks as he was using the public Wi-Fi
The whole quest is one spot to get all the time stamps if every time we've mentioned Starfleet
Yeah on this podcast which one spot that yeah, we have we haven't we did have a reference to Starfleet in this episode
That's rich did offhand. I don't know if that counts. So that's what uh, so
That last week he got a he got arrested at Starbucks before he was at an insane asylum
Yeah, he's just he's like bleeding out the eyes and they took him to a regular hospital and that's how he escaped
He just needs those time stamps man. This is very we don't know why he needs them yet
It is no no the mystery about that. All right. Let's let's let's go to the let's go to the thing
All right, let's see what you got once bar late late honest friend
Those guys who were cops they had some red shirts on I broke my legs and they threw me woods
But that's not the worst part. That's like the document. There's like there's like almost no time stamps
Oh, man, I'm really discouraged right now
In fact, if I if I got even one piece of constructive criticism no matter how valid it would break my will to live for sure
I
The PCP I'm gonna play real quick. Okay one spot the number of Google search results is not a data point
Putting actual effort into his question that's a one-spot one-spot weekly set the bar too high for any of the rest of you
Please help this man with his time stamp shit
Where's like post in the comments one spar like where they can?
I don't know where this document is with the updates. I assume it's on somewhere
I guess we could put it in the show notes. Yeah, we maybe we should
Yeah, all right. Well anyway, let's move along here. We've got another one here from
Tomaso Choco Choco another favorite Ohio Ohio to you Choco. Let's let's see what you have to say years ago
I was at a slumber party
My friend said hey, we got cinematics. Let's stay up late and watch porn
I said, all right, so we stayed up late and we started watching the porn now
I was the channel god. I hope this isn't going because I think it's second and work half the time
So while I was sitting there
I heard my friends like arguing for a bit and then it got weirdly quiet
So I was like, all right, what the fuck's going on?
So I turn around and my friend's mouth is an inch away from my other friend's dick
And as soon as his lips touch that dick come just shoots into his mouth and you start screaming and
Crying and everything we're trying to get him to shut the fuck up
but through the commotion we got caught and
he had to swallow the cum because
Because his dad is a pastor. Can you imagine a worse thing to see what was in his mouth? Oh
What was the gayest thing you've ever experienced?
This voicemail
I've never uh-huh
Experienced anything anywhere close to that gay, you know not not and I never will knock on wood
Yeah, let's let's pray for that
I mean there is that story that I've told before about how me and my buddy John college roommates
You're just both lying in bed, you know across from each other. Yeah. Yeah, look
I know it's that look we're in two separate beds across the room
What was it?
John just says to me hey like it like we're both, you know tucked in ready to go to sleep
He's just like hey, dude my dick's out right now. He had like under the blankets
He had taken out his dick and I just say oh you do it. I'm gonna do it, too
I yelled to him across the room and he's like no don't do it. We'll be gay and by the time
I got mine out luckily his was was tucked away safely so we weren't
Narrowly avoided being gay a happy ending
Anybody else
I don't think I've ever been gay
Everyone thought I was gay, but I didn't actually I mean I mean I mean I was gay in the sense that I was a faggot
But I don't know if I was gay
Yeah, I guess I guess I guess the only kind of gay thing I've experienced is what I was telling Ben when he was over
We were getting Wendy's was that uh that I I'm on tinder. Yeah, and and since since I am bisexual or as I call it part-time gay
I found out you're a you're a you're a fair-weather faggot
Agreed agreed
That one for sure. That's a good one. So so I've just found out that I'm either I think gay guys are just much more desperate
Because I'm much more popular with gay and then with women men in general desperate for sure
Men I mean men are just more. I mean I'm desperate. That's why I'm on tender fair enough
Yeah, like men are just willing to fuck way more easier than I mean men men just men just are men are more proactive men are
Expect men have to initiate the conversation almost all the time. Yeah, it's very sense make sense. Yeah. Well, all right
You're well on your way. Yeah, and I guess that carries over to the gay sphere as well
Let's see. Okay, so here's another message. Oh, yeah, I think the gayest thing I've ever experienced was one time
I was like, I don't even know what I was doing. I was just hanging out behind my my middle school
And someone came up to me and said so like you're gay, right?
You're gay. Just wanted to make sure like you're gay, right? Wait, was this a man saying this? Yeah, this is another man
And I was like no
And then they was like, okay cool, and then he went away I in high school
There was a girl who wanted to date me
Yeah, and I didn't and and we went on a date to the mall and I didn't really like her
She asked if she could kiss me and I said no well and yeah, and I wasn't feeling it and
She tried to she's she you know she utterly devastated me my reputation by spreading the the heinous rumor that I was gay
It didn't stick at all and it meant nothing
You know, I found it mildly amusing that an attempt made was was made
Yeah, I feel I doesn't go anywhere
I almost sort of see why she might think that if she thinks that she's attractive and it doesn't make you know
Yeah, it's like oh he must be gay. Maybe it wasn't delicious really. I don't know
I mean you're spreading a rumor
I mean even if you think even if you think it's well even if you think it's true
If like you're going around being like oh that guy that was a way to protect her ego like she could have just said immediately
When you said no, it's like oh is it I mean nobody had to know nobody had to know that this has maybe I mean
Maybe she told her friends, right? That's all you know. Oh, you know, he's gay
It's he must just be gay or else he would have and then the chatterboxes begin and then
Oh, yeah girl. Oh, he's oh, he's definitely gay. There's no other reason why he would have snubbed you like that. Oh, yeah
Yeah, well, okay. Well, he's fucking gay. Yeah, and he's a denny's a jerk, too
Yes, yes, yeah, also he did try to rape me that was
Well, that was true. That one was true
I guess he thought that it was a guy or something because like yeah, he tried to rape me still so I don't know what's going on there
Excellent. Oh, there was that like I guess this was also pretty gay
There was just that one time that someone comes out. I didn't have gay sex. I forgot about that girl
Well, yeah, Nate that see that girl over there
She wants to date you and I just sit there say okay, and then do nothing. I did nothing
I didn't exactly reject my mind. Did nothing kind of reminds me of the girl in only yesterday
I mean like the girls the girls march up to her in lockstep and they announce like so and so has a crush on you
They run away. She's like
Okay, oh dear
I don't know, you know women. It's like it's different. I guess because there's like different standards for this stuff
I don't know whatever because it's different for girls. Everything's apparently all right
Let's play another one is here's one from ironclad argument. Let's uh
Is this guy's name? So I'm listening to the podcast and I hear did you come out with this like ironclad argument?
Name drop. Why do I have to be smart? What's the benefit?
Right, why do I need to know things you're so smart did you but I don't know where everyone turns his back on them
and starts saying
Cuz it's cuz it's good to be smart
You know, it's a good way to have arguments and truly know things
Not be smart and continue to ask ask why instead of answer the question
Did you what the fuck kind of argument is that? Oh my god? I got a fucking hemorrhoid
Yeah, all right, so so
Did you was arguing as he does that like was this last episode?
Okay, okay, I can't remember why something something we were talking about
Did you was saying you don't need to read books because you can just
The argument against was like books give you more context you can understand the idea is better
Yeah, did you is like if I know what the idea is why do I have to understand it?
Why do I need to be smart? I'm just another one of those stupid things
You just have to push under the rug and be like I guess I could still be his friend
I guess so great if it's so great to not be smart if being smart is so bad then why then
Mr. Ironclad did you say that the idea that you should be smart is dumb
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I thought that was sarcasm. I thought he was
Yeah, yeah, okay, so I'm his master plan right
I'll be smart enough to follow that but yes, I'll explain it for you
Here's one
Digi's Digi's an idiot. There we go
The comments from the last episode as they appear currently and in my present may not be for your present viewer
But they're basically all just WTF the PCP is good now question mark and also did you what the fuck are you talking about?
To comments that we get. Oh, yeah
You know what you know, it's great. You know, it's great about the setup like cuz we we the episodes go up on Fridays, right?
Yeah, that's right. That's right
That means that like people will listen to it on Friday then right after that they can go to the
Whatever I forget the site, but the one where you send your email or your audio mail
Yeah, yeah, like you can send it like right after you listen and then we record the next episode like a day after that
Yeah, yeah, right
Yeah, yeah, it's almost like that was intended so we could get back shortly before we record I see I see well
I'm sure that no one I know
Here's another message from our good friend at DeVry University
What do you got no you hit this is please discuss the fetishization of autism. Oh
Oh
Yeah, that's it
That's the whole time. I want to say shout out shout out to shout out to John Boyce on YouTube
He's got a video about the history of the highest scoring basketball game ever I think
And it features one of the teams involved was the DeVry University basketball team
Which almost doesn't really exist but sort of but does just enough does that they technically did take part in
Technically the highest scoring basketball game of all time does DeVry University even still exist at all
I think so I believe it does. Yeah, and it and some of its campuses might even have a basketball team
I don't know what DeVry University is. Is this like a 1980s?
No, they're a no it was like one of those for-profit colleges and they advertise on TV
If you want to be like you guys you want to design video games come to DeVry University, you know one of those guys
Yeah, yeah, I think the reason I don't think they exist anymore is I just don't watch TV
So I haven't seen an ad for DeVry in literally years. Yeah
See then to watch TV after like obviously not and be on the air and being able to have ad block on and just
Yeah, whatever you want. It is cancer. It's like strapping. It's like strapping
you know how the thing in
In the Fantastic Four of Fantastic Four fame he is the thing where he's made of rocks
But there's also an effect where like because he's being turned to stone
It has an effect on his mind and it's hard for him to think and it like slows down his thoughts admit
Which is kind of fucked up and like watching TV has that effect on me
Like my brain morphs and becomes solid and can't like it smooths out the wrinkles you guys all those wrinkles
Smooth write the fuck out. What a shame. Yeah, that's what it does
I mean, I haven't turned on a television just to watch like broadcast or net or cable television and yeah
I can't even remember. I don't I don't even remember
My mom's watching TV so
It'll be interesting to see what like it's like for like our kids when they're like like what are they gonna grow up?
Consuming media with will they be on YouTube? Will they be on Netflix? They'll be on Twitch watching their favorite
They'll be watching their dad stream
Dragon Warrior monsters yeah tonight on twitch.tv slash st. Comics with an X
Well to answer the question the fetishization of autism is that like when you've got like a really dumb anime girl with like really big tits
Is that I think what he means is the idea that autism is now seen as like as like a
pseudo good thing or potentially a good thing or like like
That gives people superpowers in certain contexts. You know who's into this. You know who's way into that did you?
I thought he was referring specifically to digi and I think did you said that he talked about it on like a pub crawl or something
I'm kind of glad the digi's not here because I don't want to hear his answer to this question
Fuck that I mean, I don't know like I think digi is not wrong that like it could be like it's useful
Like did you just uses the autism as a synonym for new types from Gundam so anytime you hear autism just
Have very few similarities between
Autism have their strengths, you know, they have things that they're hyper focused on and drives them to to you know to great knowledge
Okay, not to be I'm not trying to get overly
Critical whatever like I feel like if you asked like the mother of an autistic child like hey
What do you think about like your kid having autism? I don't think they'd be so positive. I don't think you like no
I think it would depend. I mean
Yeah, well here's the thing dude
Millennials can have kids now and millennials like if you're like a super progressive leftist millennial
You bet that they're not gonna say anything bad about it
Okay, that's somewhat of a warp perception because I think even baby boomers would be like my son
What what do you like autism isn't that bad my son my son can do anything that another another boy can do
Yeah, you know, he's not he's he's just you know, he's a little different. He learns a little differently
You know, he's very smart. They do believe that I'm sure I agree with you that it must be some part of some people's minds
But who are you to say that that is how they all think? No one at all. No one at all
Yeah, that's that's owned that's fair owned
Um, I don't know. We've got we've got a lot of people in this chat that are just sitting on the sidelines
It's just waiting for the mouse to be fed. That's true. That's that's fine including the rhythm bot. What do you have to say for yourself?
Yeah, they just waddle on up to the trough here and just
I don't know. I just want to say about this thing. I feel like
The way we talk about autism is just extremely uninformed. Am I wrong there?
No, of course, so and you know what? I bet not to be you know, I bet we have a fair number of autistic people listening right now
Yeah, let us know what you think about this fetishization
That would be interesting because like I always feel like
The the whole like autism joke is like very much like done intentionally
Yeah, and it's just for the the giggles right and like no one should be taking it seriously
That's very true. I wonder if Digi takes it seriously. You have any expertise. Let us know ladies and gentlemen
Oh, yeah, all right. Let's see. We got here's another one. Oh boy. I think I know where this is going
This is from how many more do we have? I've got six more
Okay, yeah, that's reasonable. We've got dentist defender. Let's uh, let's see what he's got to say
I know that digi's not going to be here because the podcast never works the way that it should
But the idea that brushing your teeth is not necessary is just so smooth brain
I'm really screaming in the car when I heard digi talk about this. So he's only focused on cavities
Essentially, well, there's so many other aspects of your teeth that you need to protect
If your enamel gets thin boy, you're gonna get fucked up
There's so many things that brushing helps with and like if you have your wisdom teeth in like you got to clean those
And let me recommend boys flossing is a must
Well, that's it. It's getting long and I just I I was screaming screaming and in my car
Please stop this man. I was digi was digi. He was again. Yeah, he sure was. Yeah, he was. Yeah
Well, okay, we have a dentist listening to our podcast, but well, this makes a dentist defender
Maybe we cannot we cannot we all agree that he's wrong. Oh, yeah
I I mean, there's people here in this chat. I mean, I mean, I don't take great care of my teeth
I'm sure Nate takes really good care of his teeth. I try all across the range of spectrum here. We can all agree that
Yeah, I would assume that I probably take only slightly better care of my teeth than digi
But I'm a hundred percent able to confirm and like admit that it's a terrible decision
And I'm a worse person. Yeah. Well, if I if I don't brush my teeth, I know that I'm doing something wrong
It's a mistake. I think digi would agree. I want to speak on his defense because this is not here
It's just like the things that we care about that are helped by us brushing our teeth
Could those just be things digi does not care about and therefore there's no objective standard
Well, no, no, you heard him talking last episode. I'm very convinced that digi is not educated on what will happen to your teeth
That's unreasonable
Like maybe maybe maybe if we looked into it, right? Yeah, maybe if we looked into it, we would find
That not brushing your teeth does not, you know, it does not have certain effects on
But like there's so many things that yeah, this guy's right like like like worn enamel and and stuff
And gingivitis and shit, you know got clean your gums, you know
Yeah, your gums gingivitis your gums, you know, you can get fucking you can fucking rot your teeth roots and need a root canal
like there's
there's
Well, ben did you just oh, I know I know there's a point wasn't like just neglect your teeth
He was his real point was like and this guy was just refuting him that like if you just don't consume sugar
That like solves most of the issue
Uh
That was his major pretty sure that's totally wrong and stupid. I don't know. Uh, well, I think I don't know enough to say one way or the other
But it sounds more wrong than right that would affect that that that sounds like some bull that sounds like some bullshit
Childhood like parents saying oh, don't eat sugar. It'll rot your teeth like grown up
I
That's not the be all end all like like thing that has to do with teeth health
That's not the only thing that matters. It might be the biggest one. I mean, I don't know. I have no idea
I have no idea. I don't think I don't really think back in the middle ages
There was not a whole ton of sugar for the peasants and I don't think they had perfect teeth
Just throwing that one out there
Fair point
But I will say that when sugar did was introduced in like, you know, like like late renaissance
They did have really bad teeth sugar is bad for your teeth, but not so bad. Fair enough. Fair enough. It is the be all end all
That's all I'm saying. All right. Let's let's move on or next one here. This is from uh, keep it going. She pollution. She pollution
That sounds like someone else go
Hey guys, so I followed Ben Sain's advice and started fasting. My goal was reach a week, but sadly
Uh, a few hours ago. I ate something
I really hate myself now actually like
Yeah, I think you too. It tastes good
so
Yeah, I mean, I guess I can still be proud of myself for reaching for
three
Yeah, it's three hours without eating food
There it is. Please let me know if you have any advice so I can reach a week and it's not um
To the other members my question is what will you have a hard time not doing for a week that isn't a basic human need
or sexual
Okay, my yeah, what do you got my?
My advice you made it to three. Well, can you count to uh seven times 24 is 140 is one
16 can you count to 168?
Just make it to 168 and then and then you'll have done it do that
Hourly add one to that and then just do it. Yeah. Yeah. I mean don't eat until you hit 168 practical advice
He should probably take like vitamins and water lots of water. Maybe
Yeah, yeah, you keep like drinking water like you just fill up your gut. You don't feel like eating
Take a multivitamin. You know drink drink tea drink drink tea. Yeah, apple cider vinegar
As caffeine it tastes great zero calories
Tea is beautiful caffeine has so little I mean tea has so little caffeine that might have you always say that
I don't feel it. I don't I feel the caffeine rush and I drink caffeine. I'm desensitized do it
Speaking of caffeine. I remember when we were young. I remember one time you bought like a powdered keg
Not like a bottle of powdered caffeine or something. Was that am I remembering that right? Is that a real thing? Was it creatine?
I thought it was fucking literally caffeine and I don't remember buying powdered caffeine
I'm pretty sure like like caffeine is lethal if you eat it straight. I mean, that's why I was concerned at the time
I mean actually my housemate had like a bag of like I probably wasn't straight
But it was a bag of powder and I would take like a little scoop of like
A tiny like a core like an eighth of a teaspoon or something and I would like dissolve it in my in my
Some of the time dude the first time I ever had a five-hour energy
I felt like I was the elephant's foot from Chernobyl
I felt like like like like the acid was going through my throat and infecting all my body from the inside out
And I was turning into like a small blob of like radioactive energy and that like all my friends were going to have to build like an
Iron cast around me to keep the power in because I was like I was like I was like turning to like a black hole
I was going to like exactly one by one
Minecraft dot block and once I reached maximum capacity. I was just explode out in all directions in fact all around that's why I felt
I'm drinking one sip of a five-hour energy
Uh, I've never had I've literally never had a five-hour energy. I don't know if I'm having this
Okay, okay
The most distinct thing about fire energy is that you'll get super hot and you feel like you're on fire
You feel like you are in acid and on fire. Yeah, that sounds awful. Yeah, it's really awful
It's really like crazy. Those be vitamins. Well, fuck. Yeah
Does anyone have an answer for this um like things that you could go
For a week without doing sexual or food or something
I mean video games. I guess like I really like video games though. I pretty regularly can go for a week without playing them though
It would really be hard for me to not go on the internet at all. Yeah
The internet oh social media in general would be a tough one. Yeah, which is relevant because it's funny. Michelle
Just got fucking banned from twitter and it's really fucking up. Yeah. Yeah big big champ big champ came after that's right
That's right. Yeah, and uh, yeah, they they came after her oils. She was she was trying to spread the word to protect us all
She's trying to she's trying to protect the power oils and they fucking they closed her down
Hopefully she'll be back in a couple days though. Hopefully
Michelle's really funny on twitter by the way, you know, there was another message
I didn't want to play because it was overly personal, but somebody out there just said how funny michelle was
On twitter and i'm not gonna get into it, but they also said someone else was not real funny
Which is why I didn't want to play it. Um, but yeah, you're you're you're beloved michelle
Can I can I can I ask you who after you ask me who after sure? I'll link it to you
Okay, I'm very curious. All right, let's instantly I believe that it's me and I'm sure that it is
Is it is it is it a member is it a one of I I will not comment until the end of the stream
I will not say anymore. Is it you Nate? I won't say anything. God damn it. Okay. All right. Here's one from from clab
clab
if you got
Hello
I'm a big
Nate fan the only kind of fan that is
Ashley appropriate. Yeah, and I'm wondering when is Nate gonna start the third right of the pcp so we can
purge all these
dream levels. Yeah. Yeah, fuck
utilitarian
ideals going on here because
Without Nate constantly speaking about starfleet. I my soul my bean has been crushed
And I don't know what to do anymore. I have something important. So, um
Yeah, I'm 17. I have no direction. I need Nate to tell me
And uh, the dreams are not good despite what everyone tells you. Uh, stop also, um
Voice smells are much better than the stupid
Uh, twitter shit. Uh, never do that again. Thank you. Uh, good night
Perfect vertical slice of a terrible stupid question
Uh for that the pcp
It has every everything bad about it
As long as I continue to hold a supreme authority over the voicemails. My people will have their voice
As long as you allow in the 17 year olds with no direction who want to just pair everything that you say and claim that's philosophy
I just feel like this is how a cult starts with like aimless 17 year olds who will just you know, they want to they want to hear a
Voice of a of strength and direction in their lives
Clab you and me buddy. Nobody have to settle with you. Why does this person think that he's the only one that didn't like the dreams
Nobody like like the dreams everyone in the comments was like don't let anyone talk about their dreams again
This isn't a point specifically about the dreams. I think this guy is talking about like in the there there's been in the discord
Uh thing there's been people being like hashtag let mage dream and then I've just come in saying like no dreams are banned
No dreams of any kind pure raw
Materialism like I think that's what he's talking about and and shit. Yeah. Yeah, I see. All right fair enough
So so good on you clab. Uh, you're a good man
I got nothing but respect for you. You want to tell him how to live his life. He needs direction
Just uh, uh, check out new we Agua one of these days. Hey guys
It's me a best guy ever fan and I just want to say I really I really agree with Nate's strong
Passionate speech
I really find best guy ever is passion inspirational and it's inspired me to make my own youtube channel
Where I will be discussing my favorite anime. Uh, just like my hero
Only to destroy him and and take his power one of these days
I plan to trample him and leave him in the dust do as I say not as I do
And I know and I know that he would do the same for me. So no hard feelings buster
Thanks for thanks for taking my call and have a nice day
Hashtag racism
Hashtag a future for white children. Uh, all right moving on. Uh, this was one from uh,
Okay, this is a weird. I think it's a polish name. It's like
simon with szy mo n
with
new ski
size
Simon with new ski. All right. Let's see what he's got. That doesn't sound right
I don't even know why I'm here. I can't even speak english properly
I'm from some shitty eastern european country
fuck
Well, okay, what I'm trying to settle down is hearing mage talking fluent english despite not being a native speaker
It's very
motivating
And I think I developed my vocabulary and listening comprehension skills
Thanks to the pcp
Thanks. Okay. Okay. Good job mage mage mage says don't play voicemails that are just questions
People who send them are basically cheating and it's kind of redundant because you know, you have
Not anymore. Not anymore. Yeah for that
Okay, duly noted. Okay. Okay mage says that her mage says that her
Knowledge of english that her like ability to learn english was like her best subject in school
And like she says that she's just like real just took to it really really, uh
Fast. I I want to guess. I'm going to ask you. Are you
Austrian
I want to know are you ash or some country around that area? Please respond. I'm based on his name
I'm guessing he's polish because like his name matches the polish, uh, like ski at the end. Oh, what was it?
Yeah, it's yeah, he's probably was new ski something like that. Okay, uh, oh wait
W's or v's in polish, right? So it's vizniewski. No, that's not right. I don't know whatever and I think yeah, okay
So that's he'd probably polish or or I don't know ukrainian. Yeah. Okay. Uh, anyway, uh, what was this question?
He didn't have a quote. Well, no, what do you say? Oh, well his like point was that like he was saying he was
Oh, but he's saying that non-question. Yeah, non-question
voicemails shouldn't be said because it's redundant
Uh, but now it's not a problem because I guess we've just killed text questions
I want to say stick with learning english and I also want to say similarly that I love you
You you live in europe and I love you and I respect you and and like hashtag god
I wish that were me munchie. You're one of these fucking americans who's like, oh my god
If only you lived in europe, I'd have so much culture and personality and I'd actually have a yeah
Why don't you go vote for obama? You fucking lived hard
a globalist piece of shit
Okay, I want to go to a country to experience what the country is like and its specific culture
How embarrassing america is the only culture you need to know about boy. So get used to it
You should visit other countries
But like if you lived in another country, then there wouldn't be anything special. I got a plan
I got a plan for you munchie. That's not true at all because I
I've grown up in america. I've grown up in america. So no, no, no my what I mean is if you had lived your whole life in like
Like if you were if I don't let's say this guy's polish. There's nothing. There's nothing cool about being
Sorry, wizniewski. There's nothing cool about being polish because it's just a country like any other country
Well, okay, I argue that there's cool things about being polish in the same way that there's cool things about being america
You guys are just reading anti american sentiments for no reason to what I'm saying
I'm saying that you seem to you seem to be jealous that he lives somewhere other than america and I'm like
Nowhere, it's cool. I'm I'm not saying that america is bad in any way
I know you're not saying that I appreciate the culture from which from whence this guy has crawled out stop
Fetishizing foreigners munchie cease it immediately. That's you stop sexualizing. It's you. He's a good man. He doesn't you don't know
You cast an elsewhere friend. You don't know anything about his culture. Why do you respect it? Yeah?
I don't know. Okay. I don't know. I I literally okay. I don't know what country. He's from but I do exactly
I like the general history from that that that from eastern europe
I like I like the sort of things that have occurred there
I think that they're interesting and I enjoy the history from whence he has crawled out from
I wonder if any poll would be offended for you to lump all of eastern europe in together into one thing
You'd be like, oh, it's all you know, I like the general things
They're all the same
Apparently people in what we call eastern europe do not like that turn really they don't like being lumped together as quote eastern europe
Hashtag munchie is racist
But I've also got a plan. I've got a plan for you munchie. Here it is
You're such an absolute unit such an absolute massive lad
Then why don't you individually secede from the union and go be a individual member state of the united of the european union
Just go like float out in the ocean and just attach yourself to the you know the the big octopus tentacles
Go join all it all i'm hearing right now. Yeah is you like something else and that's a problem
Like where you are now that's like you you just can't like anything else if you like another thing
That means you pride that above literally every other like nation on earth
Okay, I will say I will say that I think that you have a little bit of grass is greener going on
I think a little bit of that. I I don't think america is bad in any way
But I've said I said nothing about america being even you're like, oh, oh you grew you grew up in some you grew up in poll
Oh, that's so cool. Like that's
Why is it bad to say? Oh, that's an interesting situation that you have come from an interesting situation
Literally everyone in the world has an interesting situation then because they grew up in x country
Yes, that is true. Yeah, I know everyone's boring everyone's life is boring and dumb and I don't care
Um, I'm saying is that I'm period and I'm deeply in a romantic love
With all things history and european and I think it's nice when we get to have a fan
That's not from america because that's the majority of east
We've got a lot of fans from we've done a lot of like south american fans and european fans. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's it's
I shout out lat american pcb fans of their day and everyone's like oh like uno uno uno uno. Thank you, manci
Thank you very much. Listen manci. We tried multiculturalism. It didn't work. We're shutting it down. We're ending this once and for all
It's over. Yeah, okay. That's all right. Let's do it. Okay. I'm like a true bloomer
Like i'm julie says i'm just like attacked on the senate floor and i'm just being like like gang mob friend
Because I said that I like hearing right now. I like europe. That's that was my crime here that I liked europe
Yeah, I bet you also like uh, you know, and I also like fascism and communism too much
I bet you also hate capitalism. Don't you?
Uh, speaking of capitalism, we got another call from a dank wizard
Phone and in from eastern europe to use the racist term. All right, here we go. What do you got?
Hey, nate. It's your boy. Uh a dank wizard. Good to see you
I'm the dude who sent you those kingdom hearts cards a while back
Oh, yeah, you didn't open all of them. You fucking piece of shit. Where the fuck did you?
What did you do with them? What the fuck did you do with them?
They're I want to know what the fuck you do if you
Actually, yeah, I think I did because those things go for a shit tone on ebay. God damn it
You only open like
I think you had like three or four more you can open it like six packs or something and you know, I
I appreciate that you even who would think these are valuable. They're shitty knockoff kingdom hearts trading cards
I was just wondering if you were gonna ever like open up again like on a video
I can't believe you would throw that away. I can't believe that. I open like three and they suck also
I totally relate to you with that blanky story in the last episode man
Like me and you all yeah exact same experience with the blanky like I would shove that shit up my nose too
Like the only different thing is I would like hell. Yeah
Feel between hell. Yeah, there was really fucking weird and gross
For some reason insanely gratifying really fucking weird, but uh, I have a stroke
I remember blanky very clearly and I but I I had no idea you were selling
Okay, all right the whole shoving it up my nose thing's a bit blown out of proportion
Like I did that sometimes. I don't let's forget. I was like five at the time. So let's not be too hard
Yeah, last last episode I think I told the like, you know, maybe it was more than one episode ago
I don't remember. I don't remember. I'm using my mind. It could have been too
Wait, was that not on the bonus episode? Which by the way, you can get access to at pc at pay at patreon.com slash
Uh, god, what's the procrastinator? The procrastinators this month, uh, the bonus episode we reviewed. It's a film cast
We reviewed classic film the ant boy. Indeed. So if you want to hear our thoughts on that check that out
Toss us some coins. Listen a dank wizard. Uh, I apologize. I definitely threw those away
I had no idea that they meant anything to anyone and uh, I don't regret it either
Wait, what were they? What kind of cards? They were kingdom hearts trading cards an apparent dude
I don't believe that they're valuable. How much could they pass? Look you see you send anything to me
It goes into a black hole where you have no control over what happens to it after that point and everyone needs to know that going in
um
So, you know, I appreciate you sending stuff and I would hope that you would be not discouraged from doing it again
If you were so inclined, but uh, like like what am I gonna do fucking open up a bunch of packs and be like, oh
Yeah, I recognize heartless and nobody's and so yeah, dude, um
Like like three three kingdom hearts original booster packs go for like 25 bucks
So that's too little money for me to worry about like selling them on ebay. That's too much work
That's a lot more than I expected about single cards though
If the packs are worth my the single cards are probably worth more
If we're talking about like I mean yeah, it's like the rare ones probably
Exactly. That's where the real money's at magic the gathering or even yugio
I have some context as like what's a good card?
What's a bad card and to like know and like I can get excited when I open them. I have no
Ground like I'm not grounded to know what's a good pull. What's a bad pull?
So it's totally boring to open those packs. It's just like, uh, yes things from kingdom hearts
I could also just gotta find out what the chase cards are. Yeah, I mean, I guess you're right
Okay, uh, sora wisdom form level three kingdom hearts tcg card, uh, 40 dollars, uh buy it now. It's not bad
That's all right. Roxas level one, uh, sr foil break of dawn kingdom hearts tcg card
Also, 40 dollars behemoth level six sr foil disney kingdom hearts tcg 15 dollars phantom level five
18 and so on and so forth they could have thrown out
Whoops a hundred dollars worth. He might have maybe I mean it's possible
Look, I'm sorry dank wizard. You obviously are into it. I apologize as a non player
I had no grounding. He didn't know what I got and just assumed they were worthless. So my bad
All right, we got one more voicemail here. This is from a mozilla fennekin long time
Yep, yeah, let's uh, let's see what he's got for it. I know that person as a ben saint patron. That's how I know him
He's a patron of yeah, too. I think
Which pokemon would be the best podcaster? He was uh, he was in one nuzlocke. Oh
Hang on which pokemon to be the best podcaster cast for him
Wait
Oh, it's a joke. Oh, it's a joke you guys
Oh, how unfortunate
Well
Yeah, they both got cast their names come on down to neo milwaukee. Yeah, but which but which form of oh, uh, I love that
So in new Los Angeles city, you can see this line you can see economy crumble
No, that song sucks
All right, it's actually pretty good. Okay. I can't believe
Okay, that's such a cold reception. I got such a cold. I don't know why I don't know. I have no idea how
Why for me by the way, we're talking about ratty fuckers cop killer stuff at the moment bear with us for a second
This was from the uh from the flag slash national anthem slash tourism video content. I'll tell you why munchie
Uh, that's rich dot tv slash ratty flickers cop killer. That song was fairly verbose and I couldn't
I don't know. I couldn't like get into it at first and the melody wasn't particularly memorable
Uh, I don't know. Okay. I liked it and I think it is a good and suitable anthem for the city
I don't think it's sixon's best. Well, you know what it is. It is his best work, but I do like it
I don't like that song whatever like it doesn't have like a memorable like crazy hook or anything
But the thing is I liked the rat. I liked the rap more. I liked sixon's rap more, but it was less of an anthem
Uh, fucking what is it? I was gonna say the thing is like a j schoops
Like I I think of so much more fondly and then I'm just like I'm not saying it's like a million times better anything
Even though it is uh, but what I'm saying is uh, like I I listened to that a bunch and like
Listened to it a bunch and got way into it
And that was cool. Uh, whereas I like didn't do that with sixon. So like
Okay, I like that sixon's was like a real anthem, but also had rfc k stuff in it
I feel like that was it was a nice touch to have that's sort of like yeah
Like our world it is a national anthem that you could hear but had in this war calling cards
There's the best thing it was the
Tom you gotta join rfc k you gotta join so god listen. No, it's it's common digi
I want to fucking punch both of you and your stupid faces. You're so dumb. You're so fucking dumb
You can't even fucking beat mega man 11
Well, I would have okay, I had to go to sleep. Um, it's just you just listen to what we're saying. We're speaking plain english
We're talking about uh, uh, there's a there's a fucking city
It's full of slime and we had a contest to pick the national anthem and we fucking run
That's it. There's how hard is this to understand?
Like people just don't get so much about it. I understand linguistically what you're saying
But because I'm not actively participating the context is not there therefore. It means nothing to me
It takes a while to understand what's going on. This is why me and digi both said
Ben please make a pcp university slash style video on
Whoa, whoa
It would be a joint one if anything. No because ben was here when we asked it, okay
I've just I mean, I've just got the I've got the necessary charisma
Oh
That's something a killer would say so that's that's a brazen lie that a killer would say
Um lying right through his fucking shoddy teeth. All right. Well, that's it for questions and uh,
Okay, just just one more quick thing. I know I know it's going on about rfck
But like I I've literally written a new like text channel that is like the text that you are set into if you join the server
From any of the links now, so no matter what whenever you join the server you go to this channel
Much easier, but I don't but I don't actually find much you need a video. I don't actually
No, I said it. I made it so that the only invite link is going to that channel
Does it do you do you get a little like response blurb? That's like you have arrived at the juvenile detention center
No, me and me and me and john me and jubo. We're talking about that much. That's great ben. That's great
What you need is a video an introductory. Yeah, you're right. You're right. You're right. I don't disagree
But I'm saying is we need a what is endless war kind of like how to play
What is I'm saying is that if you join the server then you can tell with like literally less than one minute of reading
Exactly what is going on in everything you need to play the game the secondary thing that made me
Hesitant as ben has said it took like it's going to take like at least an hour a day of like effort to keep up with this
Shit, and I don't I guess
All you know like all I know what we're saying just read that blurb and then you know the basic what's happening
I think you can you could give it as much or as little as you want, right?
You can engage with it as much or as little as you want and you know, but you won't get that respect until you really come in
I was just saying that since we nerfed sparring
It's not like Nate you were you were sparring. I was just sparring ben, but now I've been completely fucked by
But that wasn't that hard to do because you could just kind of pop look at your phone every 10 minutes or so
Pop off a scar and then it was great. I missed it so much. Yeah, but it was but it was too it was too good
In fact, it's so sparring was you were literally you were literally the only one. Yeah, literally the only one
The only one who matters I am the ultimate
All right, I am the slimecorp delegate and I will be treated with respect god damn it
Well, then how come you got fucking iced by fat yoshi?
Fat yoshi is a piece of shit coward who didn't have the balls to follow me to the mind
He's never done a day of work in his fucking life that fat
Okay, okay, you you are in a possibility. Let's end this let's end this but you slipped you slipped dude. All right, right
He's right. We'll settle this another day. All right
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators people one dollar get in the bonus lounge. All right, you want to be there?
It's fun times kill yourself
second thing
$5 pledge
You get all the bonus episodes. There's suggestions suggestion
Pledge pledge to patreon.com slash the procrastinators before killing yourself. That's a good idea
Do not alert your credit card company that you are going to kill yourself. Do not let them discover your body. Yeah
The larger we can go ladies and gentlemen. Yeah, just let it roll. Just let it roll
But once they do have a will that says all the money in your bank account goes to the progress
That would be really convenient if you could do that
And also at tpcrastinators on twitter follow us there for updates
It's it's a good place to be and of course the youtube where you're watching right now probably
All right. Thanks for being here everybody. We'll see you next week another episode another nutter butter for your mother
Goodbye
Hey