Hello everyone and welcome back to a new post Radcon 4 episode of The Pro Crastinators
Podcast. I am the best guy ever. Oh by the way this episode, 203 love numbers. I'm the
best guy ever we got Gibbontake over here. Oh my god, Radcon 4. It feels like it didn't
take any time at all and basically it didn't even happen. It was so quick. I'm just the
video. Nothing has changed. I'm back in my seat. I'm just looking over and I have two
new pins. One of which is a Radcon 4 pin. How interesting. Tom Oliver is here. Don't you
love how we had that brief spike of interesting mix up content and now we're back to the same
four people who are always on the podcast. It's great. It's great that we're settled
back into our monotony of weekly output. We're back in all the wrong ways. Speaking of our
monotonous fourth individual, here's Ben St. everybody. Hey guys. Shit. Fuck you. I had
something I was going to say. No. Stop. We're not moving on until I remember what it was.
Oh. Radcon. We're really fast. What? Life comes at you pretty fast. No. No. No. Sorry.
We're going to take as long as we need. Something about how fast it went or going. You idiots.
You idiots said things about Radcon that were sort of related to what I was going to say.
I said that Radcon felt like it was going real fast and it's like basically nothing happened
at all. Is that what it? True. Oh, I was going to say because it was going to make the brilliant
observation that it's been like a really, it's actually been like three weeks since
we recorded a regular episode and it feels weird. Indeed. Yeah, because we didn't do
one last like two weeks ago and then the one before that was the one, the live one. Right.
Yeah. Weird. That's right. Weird and wacky. Well, we're glad to have you folks back and we've
got tales to tell and stories to divulge about Radcon, the content we made, the meetup, all
kinds of fun stuff. No, we don't. Yes, we do. We've got like, we've got stories. 7-Eleven.
7-Eleven was a cool thing. 7-Eleven. Radcon 4 sponsored by 7-Eleven. Radcon 4 was sponsored.
It was maintained by 7-Eleven. You know, I was really hoping we would see the return of world-famous
beloved character 9-Eleven and the Royal Rumble, but I hear he came down with that
coronavirus. Oh, yeah. Fucking 7-Eleven should have been in the Rumble. Coronavirus is hot
enough to melt steel beams. This is bullshit. Next time we got to bring back 9-Eleven and
his son, 7-Eleven, as a tag team duo. It's only two years younger. Hey, speaking of pins
that I mentioned before, I don't want to tell this tale. So we had the meetup and oh, you
know what? Oh, I want to say it, but something isn't out yet that needs to be out as a part.
Okay, I'll just tell you what I can tell you, which is that at Radcon 4, the meetup on
Pi Day, March 14th, it was a great time. We got images, show notes, look at all the people
who showed up. Oh, by the way, guys, I didn't show you yet, but Victor sent me the pictures
of the meetups and the OVA photo shoot calendar pics that they exist. So I'll get them to
you soon. Oh, and the big group shot of all of us at Radcon. Maybe I'll grab that shortly.
I was going to say about the meetup. It was a great time. People showed up. Not too many
people were spooked off by the virus, which was nice.
This was before. I'm sorry. I was going to say, it's funny. I feel like the coronavirus
thing went from spooky rumor to real shit pandemic while we were at Radcon. It's very
funny. Once we were there, we realized, oh, shit, things are getting real. Hippo, you
real possibility that you might not be allowed to fly home didn't end up happening.
I never felt like that was a possibility just because of why would they not let a foreign
person leave? That seems like anti-American. Well, the UK might have said no flights from
America or something. Maybe. I mean, I don't think... That's true. I guess I just wasn't
thinking that that was going to happen in the time frame. That had entered my thought,
but I was just like, even in the worst case scenario, Gible just stay with Digi for a while,
who lives right there and it'll all be fine and good. I'll do a bunch of weed and I'll be completely
destroyed as a man. That would have been so funny. Imagine how much weed you would inhale just
passing Digi on an average day at his home and his base. It would be nightmarish. But hey,
about the meetup, I just want to say that if you came, I'm sure you had a great time as we all
did. Part of the photo, go down the legacy. It was the first dedicated PCP meetup, I think,
not like a RFCK thing or any of that side stuff or a BronyCon one. This is for the PCP,
Radcon specifically. And you people, if you didn't come, boy, oh boy, did you miss out,
because at the brilliant suggestion of Tom Oliver, we're produced, and there will be links to this,
the wonderful PCP pennies, the crypto currency, decentralized crypto punk currency,
that we gave out in real life to all attendees for free. And we're on the streets, they're going
to the moon. It's such a powerful cryptocurrency that it only exists in physical space. You can
only have physical points. I've been looking at the stock markets. The economy is tanking,
Ripple is way down, but PC pennies are picking up the slack.
Remaining stagnant at value of one pin per pin. You're just not fluctuating at all.
To go to Gibb's point, it's not so much a cryptocurrency as it is a cryptid currency.
They apparently exist out there, but the sightings are very slim.
Please, click the link in the show, it's if you don't physically own one, you hack, who didn't
even come to Radcon meetup. Tom made the design, it's beautiful, it's real. I'm holding it in my
hands right now. It's next to my Radcon four pin, and we gave them weight for free to the people
who should have extras. Wait, before we move on, at the meetup, who was it? Who was it? I'm trying
to find the name of the guy. Ben Rodea. Ben Rodea came to the meetup and he had made a gigantic
punk plush. Of course. The life size punk plush that I have on my chair right now,
she's doing like a cool like sitting down, like what are you looking at? Sort of pose.
Legendary. Legendary weight. It was unveiled right at the end of the meetup too. None of us
saw it coming, and then all of a sudden there was punk, life size. Yeah, he just ran to his
hotel room and got his. So cool. Let me say, friggin Eric was there, Dune Koon was there,
endorsing slavery, like the hero he is. Friggin Eric. Friggin who made the ride shot. Friggin
Eric. Oh, oh, oh, right. The gunsmith. Gotcha. Gunman. And it was all kinds of kooky characters
that came to that place. It was great. It was such a wonderful experience. We were there for like
six hours walking around Virginia Beach. We hung out most of the day. Well, almost the evening,
I guess. And there will be, I'll make sure those images are left. Zen Uxtable came.
That's right. Zen was there for a day. He was involved in a little bit of RAD content,
which was cool. I won't say what, but it'll be out pretty, pretty darn soon.
There was, there was that, that Fern guy that I know, tangentially a little bit about from.
Oh yeah. But he wasn't there for RADCon. So fuck that guy.
I like, I like, while Zen was there, I was like, I was, I was asleep. I was like asleep the entire
time Zen was there. Well, I think because I had, oh, it's because I had stayed up the previous
night making my either, uh, I was doing, doing something for one. I think for the,
you, you were working on your board for the Christian lecture, while me and Jesse were
streaming. Right. Yeah. During the stream, I sat there trying to write shit on the board,
but like just getting distracted and not getting any work done. I did like 70% after the streaming
that entire week. Me, you and Jesse and Gib, we were all up all night, every night streaming
like badasses. It was sick. That's true. That's true. I was, um, actually the first couple nights
I was up for a long time every night, uh, in my bed reading one piece on my phone,
at which you ended up being a big waste of time because I didn't actually manage to quite, I'm
still like 30 chapters behind. So I didn't, I didn't catch up in time to get on the podcast,
but the, you still could any time. I probably will. Actually, I forgot about that. But yeah,
I'm like, I'm almost, I'm almost caught up now. Word. Yeah. Word. There's so, there's so much
things that were recorded. It feels like because of the, the, the whole thing with, there was like
six, seven, six or seven lectures. And to do the lectures, people, we didn't like perfectly
figure out exactly everything before we arrived. I think most of us had most of the general idea,
but like so much time was spent finishing off notes, writing stuff on the board, and then doing
the lectures, like so many hours of the, the 10 days. You, that's true. You all, not you,
hippo, but you all fuckers. Why are your lectures so fucking long? I can't talk. I don't want them
to be. I can't talk for tonight. I can't talk for a while. I just, I'm just, I'm just so talented
that I can get, I'm so succinct that I can't make a lecture more than two hours, even if I try.
I thought the Christian would be longer than that, but it wasn't. Yeah. It served you well.
But it, yeah, we spent a lot of, we spent a lot of the time just in these fucking
unbelievably long lectures. It was like, especially towards the end.
Uh, you know, I haven't done the math, but I, we like either tied or slightly more lectures at
Radcon four than like any of our previous radcons. I can't quite, I mean, whatever. I'll do the math
later, but, uh, how much math is it? You just got to count to seven. Well, I just don't remember
is the issue. I guess it's not a math question. It's a simple remembrance question of how many
fucking things happened, but it doesn't matter. Uh, nonetheless, it was epic and the classroom theme
was, uh, was good and fair and it pervaded lots of the stuff. When we were coming up with scripts for
various of our productions, we were able to incorporate the, uh, the school PCPU theme
very well. So that memes really got legs. It's really, uh, it's really going places.
Um, it's good stuff. Uh, Radcon four, what do you guys think guys? Let's, let's take a vote.
Radcon four, based or cringe? I, I would say based, but I wanted it to be longer.
By the time it was over, I was like, damn, is that it? Let's address that real quick. Cause
okay, at Radcon three, like Ben showed up halfway through. So like we couldn't do lectures until
that point. It's so strange to me to think that I was not even there for like, I was only there for
like a little over five days or so. I don't know, but like, and Radcon four felt way faster. It did.
It really did. I think, I think it really came that comes down to like the, the first few days
we were hardcore filming really, you know, the, the OVA was a big project. Um, the, the, the, uh,
the day out, the, the meetup was a whole like day out. So it was like, and basically everything
else was like really strenuous, like constant work. And I don't know. It was, it was, it did
feel like constant work. Yeah. We felt like we were, we were really busy the whole time.
Like time flies when you're in, uh, when you're doing work, I guess. Yeah. Because we crammed
so many, we did like three lectures in one day at Radcon three, if I remember correctly, because
we were hitting the wall and we had to do it at three. Yeah. I think so. I don't remember. Well,
maybe, maybe it wasn't, maybe, maybe it wasn't three lectures at least two, least two. Yeah.
We were going pretty early into the morning at Radcon three. Yeah. We went like all night.
Oh yeah. I think, I think in Radcon three it was like Tom's lecture followed by Nate's
Final Fantasy lecture was one of the days. Oh God, did we do both those the same day?
God, what a nightmare. Yeah. Yeah. We did two, we did two lectures, um, in a row this time too.
One of them was hippos and yours was reasonable. Hippos was mercifully shorted and it was already
out. Yeah. Go click the link. Uh, I, I don't think we need to release them that fast. I mean,
yeah, it's not super important. My, um, my Jennifer Diane writes lecture whose title I'm
still debating. I'm constantly going back and forth on what I want to title it, but, um,
it's almost ready. Just, uh, it's, it's basically all edited. I just have to like figure out some
like weird editing, or weird like rendering hiccups and that's basically ready to go. But like
the CWC one probably, I am probably not going to do that one for a little while. I will,
that's going to back burner that while I work on, um, finishing the slime and punishment finale.
Sure. Um, I don't know. I might just kind of, I don't know. The people want to hear that.
How many lectures, how many lectures can, are people going to watch in like,
are people going to watch a lecture every day? No. Uh, well that's fair. Maybe.
Some might, some might. I think given them like, uh, I don't know, two or three days,
like if like, I wasn't in control of releasing exactly what, I'd release one every maybe like
two days or something. I think that's enough time for the people who are the most interested to
consume and whatnot. God damn. The red con, I mean, we're, I, it was frustrating at the time,
but in hindsight, I feel like it was maybe a good thing that the content from rad con three
took so long to release and it was trickling out over the course of like a year plus.
That's not a terrible thing. It keeps people interested in, uh, the rad con cycle turning.
It took a full year for TBAP resurrection to come out and I don't really think it hurt anything
particularly. I don't think, I don't think so either. If anything, it kind of kept like interest
alive in, uh, rad con overall. Like imagine if they'd all come out in like, I don't know,
two weeks and then you had two dead years. Ten? Well, well, I mean, maybe if we had gotten the
content out faster, we would have thought about organizing rad con four sooner. Think about that.
That is true. That is true. I mean, I wasn't even thinking about it because I was so swamped with
the stuff we were still doing. So that's, that's fair. Yeah. Um, like this time probably we're
going to have like the OVA will probably take at least a few months, a couple months to come out
and the dojin will probably be after that. Probably. Or maybe they'll come out together. I don't know.
The music video, I don't think will take that long to get done, but we have some work to do
on it still. Yeah. The music video will be out less than a month probably, right? I would assume so.
Probably. If we get all the song release stuff arranged, which shouldn't be too complicated.
Yeah. Yeah. Taste. Hey guys, what did you think of my first lecture? My first foray into talking
in front of people. Dude, it was good. It was good. It was a good lecture. It was good. I would, I,
I mean, it was the first very small like focus, although it was more, it had more like lower
than I expected it to. It went a little longer than I expected, which wasn't a problem. It makes
sense. This is a new territory of small, very specific lectures that we need more of. This
could be the future of lectures as we're out of gigantic big series that we could talk about for
four hours. We're not out of those. We're not out of those. I think it's good. It's a good precedent
to set though, because there's, I think we all have a lot more of those kinds of lectures in us
than the big four hour ones. Yeah. I was always debating for so long, like before, like,
do I even know enough about a big thing that I can talk about a whole big thing in a lecture?
And I guess I forgot about one thing that I could do next time.
So that that's a secret tease for the next year. Yeah, I'm not trying to imply that there aren't
any. It's just get your wallets out for Radcon five boys. Gibbs already ready to go. I guess next
time I'll I'll do that. I'll do that. Oh, Lillia one. But I really doubt it'll be like long.
His it's actually pretty. It's actually pretty quick to explain what his books are about.
They're pretty. They're sort of they're sort of devoid of interesting facets.
Well, I mean, I am curious how successful like a half an hour lecture would be as an example.
You know, in the same style, probably probably I'm sure it would do fine. I'm sure it wouldn't
be a problem. Yeah. Yeah, certainly. Certainly. Yeah, I'm going to vote. Radcon four was cringe.
No. No. In what way? Sight your sources, explain your argument.
It was cringing that I had to wake up and do things. Oh, that's cringe.
Yeah. Thank you. No, it was really cringe about Radcon four, our diet the entire week. It was
that's terrible. Some might argue that's based. No, no, it was. I feel like I feel like it was
better than than Radcon three, because three was almost entirely cereal and then fast food.
Well, that's true. The first half of Radcon three's diet was cringe. This this time we had bacon and
eggs, which is sort of bacon. It was a staple for survival. There was more. There was more alcohol
at this one. The second half of Radcon three, Nate's and Ben's parents brought us over like
real food. So the second half of Radcon three, definitely bring like Turkey or mashed potatoes
or something. Yeah, yeah, stew or something. There was a lot of like just like real food.
Yeah, it was good. And to the point where we didn't use like half the groceries we bought
the beginning of the week. That's true. That was pretty much nobody drank any fucking beer.
I was like the only one that drank beer. I don't even like drink beer usually, but like we were
there at Radcon. We had a big case of beer. I was like, well, I feel like it's in the spirit of the
event to be drinking this all the time. I don't much prefer beer hard liquor in any capacity.
If I ever choose between a shot of vodka and a beer, I'll take a shot of vodka
every time. 100%. A beer is pleasant. We were on vacation. I don't know why everybody didn't
constantly have a beer in their hand. It would have been funny. Because you had them all, Ben.
I would have if it was like brought up more. I wouldn't have had them all if other people
had been drinking them. This is a chicken and egg situation. It is. It is. Like the whole tiki bar
aspect, I don't think I was there for like coming up with that for the Kickstarter. So I wasn't like
thinking of this as like, oh, the alcohol Radcon. So I never really thought to do it until it was
a stream time. Well, you know, the first night, I definitely got significantly drunk. That was
the best night. That was the best night. That was the best night. It was the best night until
after the stream where I literally threw up in my sleep and woke up covered in puke. It was. Oh,
God, did that happen? That did happen. Oh, that's awful. Yeah, it was fucked up. I mean, I puke,
but famously, I deliberately strategically puked during the stream and it worked like a charm and
it was the best decision I ever made. I should have done what you did. I've never been that drunk
in my life and I never will again. I've learned my lesson. Law. Law. I've been way drunker than
that many times. As have I. As have I. But I've made a, what's the word, a conscientious objector
stance? It's morally wrong and no one should do it. It's immoral. Terrible. Terrible. Anyway.
No fun allowed in Nate's life. No fun allowed. And fucking, I'm disappointed. We had to leave
all the extra alcohol with Digi. So now he's got like half a handle of gin, half a handle of vodka,
and half a thing of like. Amazingly, the people may know as we were transporting those out of the
house, we like lost all the lids. Yeah. So these like open containers. I had to sit in the back.
I had to sit in the back of Jesse's car with these open liquor bottles, which I think is illegal.
That's illegal. That's definitely illegal, but I did it anyway, because fuck the Polis. I mean,
it's not illegal for you. I think it's illegal for Jesse, since he was driving. Oh yeah, true.
But whatever. Even if like they breathalyzed you and you had no blood alcohol. It's still illegal,
because I mean, you might just be, could theoretically be sipping a little bit or something,
and it's just a discourage, you know. I don't see why it would be illegal. Okay. I don't see why
it should be illegal to drive with open containers if you are like demonstrably not drunk.
You know, there have been times this has amused me when like, I remember when I was in college or
something, and my dad would pick me up from the airport, and dad would greet me in the car,
and he would have like a beer for me, and generally not to shit on my dad, but also like one for
himself. Oh, don't say that. Oh, don't fucking tell me that. That sucks. That fucking sucks.
It was like one though. It wasn't really that bad or that serious. That fucking sucks. It just is
technically illegal. Sucks. Which, you know, is amusing. Uh, dab, ACAM. Oh, dad. I mean,
that's one of the cool dad things that dad does sometimes. No, it's not. What? I think drunker
is not going to make you. It's not cool dad behavior. Do you explain why? Why is driving drunk
not cool? I don't know, Nate. Is one beer going to get our dad drunk, Ben? Is that the point?
I guess not. I guess not. All right. You shouldn't fuck, whatever. I'm not encouraging it, but if
you want to be cool, I'm just, you know. Nate, your sense of cool is like fucked, and it sucks.
Okay. Well, luckily, everyone listens to me when I tell them what's cool and what's not.
Based, dad. Nate heads, consummate drunk drivers. What else is going on? Starts an epidemic
in the PCP audience. Nate has never drank except when driving. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Dad's a better driver drunk than sober. He's actually more dangerous with without all boomers
are with it. I believe it's Joe Biden's main, main, you know, presidential criteria. Oh, yeah.
All those times that he like is confused and doesn't know what he's doing. Like that's when
he isn't drinking. They get him liquored up before like a debate. So he can like seem
coherent. It's very wise. Just long enough to ruin America. Yeah. Okay. What other highlights
we got here? What else went down? Let me look at my notes. Yeah, let's talk about the Animorphs
lecture. Now, okay. First of all, you released your Animorphs lecture. Everybody loved it. We
were there. It was great. Way better than I thought it was going to be. And first of all, on Twitter,
who was that I saw commenting on the fact that his creation had had this big lecture made about
it? Was it K.A. Applegate? It was not quite. It was her husband who co-wrote the books. He's
someone linked him the lecture and he saw it and liked it. What? Excuse me? Yeah. Yeah.
Fucking excuse me, sir. And just now that I just retweeted, Catherine Applegate herself
responded with a heart emoji to the reverse. You've got to be shitting me. No way. It's made
it all the way to the top. It's funny because I was looking. You've got to be shitting me,
dude. No, bro. It just happened. It's real. Fucking ridiculous. How did she find out about it?
You'll link that tweet, dog. Link that tweet in the links. Yeah, someone sent a message to
her husband saying, hey, here's a lecture. Oh, my God. And it just went up the chain,
which is fucking insane. Catherine Applegate at K.A.A. author. Holy shit. Yo, this is
definitely hashtag Applegate happening right now. It's busted. The gates of heaven wide open.
Did she like retweet your lecture, maybe? I don't think it retweeted. I think she was just
responding to my comments saying like, hey, I did this thing. It's fucking lit. Why wouldn't
she do that? I don't know. Why wouldn't she do that? Because she can't sanction all of Tom's
ooze. I think because Nate was a raging misogynist throughout the entire video,
which people are mad about. You were a bigger misogynist than I'll ever be, Tom. Well,
endorsed everything I said. I did. And you loved it. I do not disavow. In fact, I avow. I avow it
off. I don't love bass, Tom. That is, that's so cool though. It's Applegate. Applegate herself
saw the lecture. Well, it's so weird because I was looking, I was uploading it and I was like,
I need to think of a title for this. It's like, what have people been like,
titling things for animorphs on YouTube? There's nothing. There's like, literally nothing. Like,
the top results are the number one result when you search for animorphs is someone just made a
video of the entire Nickelodeon series. There's one big video that's like four hours long and then
didn't someone have like a animorph sucks. They had like 4000 views on some channel. I thought
somebody had, I mean, that's small. There's like the only big project with animorphs is some guy
over the course of like seven years did like long reviews on every single book, but they didn't
ever seem to hit animorphs. Animorphs is one of those like early, well, I don't remember what time
period is like late nineties, early 2000s sort of thing. It's well, it's one of those things that
came up and was its big heyday before the internet, before people could post like DeviantArt things.
That's true. That's true. It reminds me of like, like, like certain video games from that era
where like one or two pieces of fan art, but if they were posted nowadays, there'd be a million
videos, a million pieces of fan art. That's true. The times have changed. Press B in the chat if you
want the mythical Victor Beast Wars lecture one day. Oh God. Beast. Yes. I'm not ironically want
this so bad. Actually, yeah, not a bad idea. I like Beast Wars. I just, I searched on YouTube for
Jennifer Diane writes and nothing. There is not, there is not, there's nothing. There's no video
that like has that in the title. Damn. Yeah. When it comes to like interesting,
Kokoro Wish is probably a little more popular. When it comes to like interesting subject matter,
Vriska is not like that obscure. So I kind of like failed in that aspect, but you know,
I just don't know cool weird things that nobody knows about. No, there's nothing. You search
Kokoro Wish and there's a channel called Kokoro Wish that has 37 subscribers and that's it.
Okay. There's a music video called Eternal Kokoro Wish. It has 185 views and that's
literally it. Ben, what do you think is the likelihood of you making this lecture about
Jennifer Diane writes and then that spawning a, what do you call it, a gold rush of people
making like a lectures and analysis of, you know, down the rabbit hole with this person.
Yeah. Wait, who would be doing that? Just people, just YouTubers would be like, oh,
what's Jennifer Diane writes? Oh, this gets lots of views. I'll make a million videos about it.
Wait, wait, wait. Oh my God. Funny, Nate, get ready. One of like the six, like a dozen results
down. One of the videos that comes up is actually Legacy of the Pony, part two from T-Bat Plays
titled Big Boobs Bad Webcomic. And I guess- Oh no, that's heinous. In the description, I linked
to the Jenny verse because I guess we talked about it. You must have talked about it. Yeah, yeah.
God, T-Bat Plays was- Back to live T-Bat Plays, guys. T-Bat Plays was peak content. I swear to
God, like this was the point. You would, if you had watched T-Bat Plays, you would already,
you wouldn't need the lecture. You would already- That's true. Ben, remember the intense controversy,
the T-Bat, we were almost closed our doors. We almost shattered our windows at this event,
where because we did 10 minute episodes, I insisted that we stop filming an episode
in the middle of a boss fight during Equestria Bound and we'll be back next time. And by this,
I mean, maybe like two or three people commented saying like, that was fucked up.
I do not remember that, but I'm sure- I'll never forget that day. Sounds very on brand, yeah.
It had to be done. I mean, hey, since K. Applegate is fully endorsing Tom and all his political
beliefs, I can't wait for Diane Rice to do it for Ben and for Vriska to do it for Giv. Jennifer is
online. She is on FIM Fiction. She's actively writing and commenting and stuff on FIM Fiction.
She has a YouTube channel. It wouldn't surprise me at all if she-
Yeah.
If she called for the lecture and maybe saw it.
You should do a like T-Bap, so it's like Friendship is Magic related, T-Bap transcript
of like Phantom Horn saying your entire lecture as a fanfic. And then she can comment on that.
Wait. So it's on fanfiction.net?
Okay. No, the entire fanfic is just like starts like scene, a tropical house. Phantom Horn walks
out in front of a whiteboard. Quote. And then it's just the like the full transcript of the lecture.
And-
Do it. Perfect.
Why not? Why not? That's so- I'm- you think Andrew Hussie will see the Vriska lecture?
I mean-
No.
It's Andrew Hussie. He doesn't give a shit.
I mean he might see it, but like nobody knows anything he sees because he never does anything
online anymore. Like if he liked it, he won't click like. He'll just sort of like smile.
With his nasty fat lips.
You know, maybe he does a fat lips. Maybe he wouldn't appreciate a fellow Vriska connoisseur
in this particular unique format that makes the kids go Goo Goo Gaga because they are babies.
Babies enjoy the lectures is my point. Maybe this is like a kind of format that he would
like more.
Maybe.
My thinking about my choice of lectures is like, I know the people crave- they've been crying out
for CWC 102, right? Part two. That's- that's me like giving- that's me giving like the people
what they asked for. That's me like being like, okay, here's what the people expect of me,
here's what they want. I'll give it to them. To Jennifer Dayan Wright's lecture is me
exercising my artistic power to give people what they do not yet know that they want.
Of course.
The- the- I feel like this- I feel like that one is super cool and interesting and people
who watch it and listen to it will be like, wow, that sure is fucking neat and I never would have
known any- I wouldn't have ever heard- ever heard of any of this stuff if not for this.
Because that was largely our reaction upon listening to the lecture.
That's- yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I was watching- I've watched it back like so many times because
I've been going through and editing it. I've-
Right, right.
I'm sick of it.
Also, as a- as a treat, as a treat, I put in, um, okay, remember- remember in the lecture how I
mentioned that before she started making web comics, she made a thing called Kami Shibai,
which is like a little like interactive like-
Yep.
Like game. In- in the middle of the lecture, there's like a little 10-minute block in it
where I just play the Pastel Defender Heliotrope, um-
Sick.
Kami Shibai, uh, you know, from 1998, like six years before the comic started, uh, and it's-
it's actually kind of cool. It's got like- it's got like pretty hype anime chiptune music
that plays over it. Like, that's- that's like in the original thing. I don't know where she
got it from. I don't know who made it, but uh, it's- it's sick. And again, and that's like nowhere.
You can't see that anywhere unless you go and download the Kami Shibai and download the files
and play it in the thing, and nobody's gonna-
Was it hard to find?
Can do that. Yeah. Uh, I- I feel like it sort of feels like lost media, but I'm sort of recovering
a bit.
Good. Good.
Yeah.
That's kind of what I hope these things to be.
They're- I don't know, they're a little bit more than just a video. I mean, uh, you know,
a lot of it is like, uh, we were talking about, like, how long it takes to make notes. Like,
sure, it takes a couple hours to put together notes or whatever, but really it just takes,
like, a lifetime of dedication to, like, either a particular media or, like, some- some, like,
genre. Like, like, Gibbs proposed, like, a YouTube poop lecture that may or may not exist one day.
Something like that. And with all the, like, things that you wouldn't find scrolling through
the fucking Wikipedia article, you know, that you can bring to the forefront and make interesting to
people. That's- that's what I like about it so much.
The thing about the YouTube- I was considering that for a while. I think the thing about the
YouTube poop lecture is that it would make far more sense as a video where you can show examples
of things. Because if I'm just talking about, like, hundreds upon hundreds of different styles of
video editing, but I'm not doing video editing-
You could do it as a lecture. If you just, like, mentioned, like, it'd be almost like a political,
like, a military battle. Like, you describe what, like, X General did with his troops and how that,
like, changed the board over some span.
Maybe. I feel like- I feel like the person who would do better at, like, making a YouTube poop
style, like, explanation is Emperor Lemon, because he's done stuff like that before,
and he was in, like, you know, the community at the time. He has more insight on-
You can even share a poops as well.
I- I mean, it's not about- I haven't made any, really, but, like, um, I don't know.
I feel like- I feel like it would require far more research in order to make a satisfying sort of
product.
Sure, sure. It's like how- all those guys who make those, like, fairly popular speedrunning videos,
generally they intersect with the story at some point, because they probably are speedrunners,
or were at some period of time, so they know this shit, uh, pretty in-depth.
That's been what I've noticed, anyway.
Hmm.
Hey, so-
I don't think of anything else.
Well, about- let's talk a little bit about the OVA and the fact that we all were anime girls
for a while there.
Oh, okay, sure.
Um, Lamau.
We could- we could, you know, if you guys want, we could, uh, perhaps provide some sort of hints,
perhaps of an image attached to this, or should we keep everything secretive?
I mean, well, that- that video already came out where, like, Ben and Munchie were in, like,
their costume.
It's true.
Not everyone was-
But that's just for backers, right?
Oh, is that just for backers?
That was probably-
I thought that was-
Was that one public?
Okay, okay, but one grainy phone video with a couple of us is different from, like, revealing
a full spread shot of all of us.
So, I don't know, I don't know.
Well, I'm more like talking about, like, the experience of doing it,
because I had, like, a bit of a weird, like, thing.
I think everyone else was just sort of like, ha-ha, this is funny, and I was like, uh, uh, uh,
lol, um, um, I kind of like this, uh, and I had that, like, that one tweet about, like-
Right.
Like, going a little crazy, going a little, like, um, I don't like admitting that I-
I'm wearing women's clothing and it's kind of cool.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
That's it, that's all I wanted to say.
I don't really know how to elaborate on it, it's just sort of an interesting-
I mean, I don't know, we all enjoy doing weird, silly stuff sometimes.
Maybe it does mean you're gay, who knows.
Maybe it does.
Good luck on your quest.
Yeah, I guess this isn't-
This podcast isn't really the best place to explore ideas of that nature, because, uh, lol.
But it was just, it was just a thing.
It was, it was a thing, I don't know, why is Ben muted?
I thought Ben would have something to say, because he was the one wearing makeup.
Yeah, like a big gay, as the days do.
Man, remember, remember how Ben was constantly like, I gotta go fix my makeup guys, and then
we'd have to wait, like, 10 minutes.
Yeah, if there's fucking stop shots, well, Ben fixes goddamn makeup, it's really annoying.
And then you would go to get Ben, and then Ben would come back, and you'd be inside doing
something, and be like, oh god.
That was a running gag.
It was-
It was always a chimilin ski.
Yeah, dead name, sorry.
Whoops, bleep that out, bleep that out.
It was always a teabag.
It was always a bestman.
Two best brothers delay production entirely.
How do we call, what is your fake brother name?
Is it, is it best saint?
We don't have a fake brother name, you can call us teabag, I guess.
It's standard, it's keg standard and substandard, that's canon.
That is true, that is true.
Jesus Christ.
That's the one name that unites fake fans, including the creators of characters, fake fans.
Disgusting.
Um, yeah, I mean, that, that whole production, I mean, none of it would, it's just that it
goes on for so long.
I mean, we filmed the OVA, and miraculously, we were, excuse me, able to get it done in
one day of filming.
And thank god for that, because we were dreading, like having to spend a second day, and probably
a large amount of the day, because we start things late, and because people are cowards
and weaklings.
Did you have to get up and come over?
Right, it's like a half an hour drive to the house.
You know, we should talk about, we should talk about the fucking dog, the dog that
tried to fuck up our, our shoot.
Sure, sure.
So while we were filming the music video, there, I won't describe in too much detail,
but at the, at the seminal shot, as like the lights are going down, the sun is setting,
and we're filming a very important dramatic shot for the music video, a fucking little
pug, it just walks into the frame, right where we're filming.
And okay, like, so some guys walk in his dog, and I think he had like two, there were two
ladies with him, I don't know if they were with him or whatever, and okay, that's fine.
They're there for a second, it's okay.
Okay, cut to like five minutes of this like teenage motherfucker, like lazily, slowly like
circling our group, like trying to get the dog, but really making just the least possible effort
to grab that fucking dog.
And I would have grabbed that dog, but I was indisposed and could not do it at the time.
And by the way, I love that dog.
He was cute and he was great, and I was happy to see him.
But nonetheless, we had a fucking job to do.
So this is not, not good timing.
And he was hard, I mean, he was a hard dog to catch, like I tried to grab it myself,
but he like skidded, scampered away like, like really fast.
But like the guy was just sort of, he was just sort of like amused and sort of standing and like,
what would you call it, like orbiter sort of did orbiter distance, better orbiter distance
around us.
Yeah, he was just kind of like watching with the used interest as all of us are freaks trying
to get this photo, like video thing done.
And he just made no effort to be like, hey, clear, you guys are in the middle of something.
Maybe I'll get my dog out of the way.
He's just kind of like standing there.
Dogs, am I right?
As it's like running around us.
If I can have a conversation with that man, maybe you can tell me why he is being such
a slow moving, uh, lackadaisical, because he doesn't know any of us.
He's too shy to come up and imagine your dog runs into a group of people,
not even clearly filming something, but just standing there and the dog is like fucking
with him and not fucking hustling at all to get that guy who jumped in.
Yeah, we're talking about the dog.
Yeah, fuck that guy.
Ben was really mad.
All of us were just like, haha.
Ben was the most mad.
But Ben, Ben was the most blatantly mad.
Like, like even when the guy was hanging around like, I'm gonna fucking kill that dog.
I'm gonna fucking kill that dog.
I mean, I was, I was like a little amused and a little annoyed when the dog showed up.
But like after the dog was like running around, like for a while, like while and like the guy
is right there and he could easily pick his fucking dog up and get him out of there.
And we're clearly doing something and don't want the dog there.
And the sun is setting as we have like a tiny window, sliver of time to finish this.
I'm like, oh god, we're gonna have to redo this entire shot tomorrow.
This dog doesn't get the fuck out of the way.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, he got him eventually, which, you know, the least he could do.
Better late than never, I guess.
We will obliterate him.
I don't know what, I don't know what.
Okay.
Nobody else said anything.
Like everyone else, you all just made fun of me for being mad.
But like clearly it wasn't a problem.
I just did like the dog.
That's all.
I was just sure.
The dog was fine.
We really did not have any use for him.
But at the time, like we really did have, I mean, probably like, I don't know,
half an hour to get this shot done.
And we were, it was like the very last thing.
And you know, it did take the dog maybe like, maybe up to like three,
four minutes to like be removed.
So like that wasn't, it wasn't like an ad coming back.
I don't think it was longer than that.
Those minutes are.
It definitely was.
Well, he came back.
And like came back a few times.
He came back a second time.
And it was, he was in like the final like drone shot.
And we were just like, oh god, that might be the best take.
He's in the fucking drone shot.
That piece of shit.
I think we have a shot that he will not be in as our final shot.
But I remember Victor saying that one with the dog was the best shot.
So it's not a problem if the dog is in the drone.
No, it's not.
But it's just like, come on, man, come on.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's cute.
The dog was also there.
That's the end of it.
I have no problem with the dog.
Including a dog increases production value.
Fucking not controlling their dog.
It is a public area that we were doing that in.
You're supposed to have dogs on a leash.
She was not on a leash.
She was just running around.
And you're not supposed to film without a permit.
So who's the real criminal?
What do you mean you're not supposed to film without a permit?
That's Victor.
You're not supposed to film.
That's it.
You're just not allowed to record a public place.
Yeah, it's barely public.
It's right outside the house.
You know better than Victor?
I don't.
That can't possibly be true.
On a phone?
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe it was specifically using the drone.
But that person would be the drone.
That's the only thing it would be is the drone.
Well, I think he specifically said filming.
And then the drone was a separate issue.
I have no idea.
No, there's no way.
What if you just take your phone out and film?
I don't care at all.
But, you know, I would do it anyway.
I don't give a shit.
It's pretty funny.
To put a cap on the whole like me,
like Ben, you weren't here when I started talking about like the.
Sorry, I suddenly had to shit really bad.
Lol.
Of course.
But what happened?
I was talking about the wearing of the OVA female attire.
And you with the me with the.
I'm just going to say it.
Fascination with the stuff.
I look the best.
I was the hottest girl.
That's not accurate.
Nate, you were the only one that even came close.
But I'm sorry.
You're second place.
You're second.
I see.
Nah, nah.
It was me.
No.
La Ma.
This is shit.
And I am.
Everyone else was cringe.
And I was based.
I really.
It was really funny.
I had to ever like every ever after every couple shots.
I had to run inside and like redo my makeup.
We were talking about that.
It kept getting like we hated it.
It kept getting fucked up.
But it was worth it.
It was worth it.
Okay.
That's called commitment.
That's one word.
It was really funny.
Like like at various points where I wore like the punk costume.
Where people regularly did not realize that I was me.
And thought Michelle was in the house.
What did you say?
Well, did you said that?
Like he would see you give out of the quarter of his eye and be like,
Oh, is that Michelle?
Hold on.
I never thought that.
No.
That would make me fucking gay.
Yeah.
We all know Ben's gaydar is not active.
Digi's totally is.
Digi's definitely way gayer than Ben.
Indeed.
Yes.
Anyway, wearing women's clothes is based.
And that's all I gotta say.
I just thought it was funny that like day one
Gibbs on stream and everyone's like, Oh my God, Gib cut his head.
That's Gib.
I didn't even recognize him next day.
Gib dressed up as pump.
Where's Gib?
Who's the girl in the stream?
You were just a ninja.
I decide half the time.
I think I decided that I think makeup is cool.
And I sort of wish I could wear it.
Not in like a I want to like wear lipstick and look like a girl way.
I just think it's like cool that you could like just like paint stuff on your face to
make you look a certain way.
You can just kind of like apply imagery to yourself and the way you look.
I think that's neat.
It is pretty bad.
Ben leveled up and it unlocked new avatar customization.
He's really yeah.
Yeah, basically.
Alas, it has been.
What's the word?
Socialized as a feminine trait.
What can one do in this Western hegemony?
Why we got to abolish gender and then I can.
I don't know.
I can I can put I don't know what I put on my face.
Some just like I'll just probably come.
Probably come mostly would be the just draw some common there.
That's pretty manly.
Right.
That's like the manliest substance there is.
Here you go.
It comes straight from the man.
Yep.
Straight from the store.
Pure testosterone.
People will walk by and I'll be like, no, no, no, no.
It's my own cum.
You fucking fag.
That's what I'll say.
I'll get arrested.
You know, here's something interesting I was thinking about.
Like when we were leaving the house,
I was like, we didn't get nearly attached to the location
as we did last time.
Because if I recall during ragcon three,
there were like multiple times when we were like,
oh, we got to do a fucking house tour.
We got to go through the entire house and like explore it
and like show it off in videos.
I don't think we did that for.
For this was way nicer for the first one.
It definitely was.
Right.
Country was like, whoa, didn't you do that like the first day
when you saw when weren't you running around filming the house
and like doing a tour of the house
and you found the like the bloody footprints
and smears and stuff?
I mean, I wasn't.
I don't know if we were recording that.
I think it was just happening.
I swear.
I swear someone was filming that.
It definitely got filmed in one of the videos or something.
But I mean, one of the things that I had in mind,
like I really wanted to do a house tour
of ragcon three house, the arena,
specifically because I was hoping someone would make
a quake stage using the map of the arena.
So that was my biggest motivation.
No one has done that.
But the challenge is still open.
Someone wants to do that.
Although I just don't want to wake the other day
to make room for doom eternal on my computer.
I mean, it's been two years since ragcon three.
I think if anyone were going to do that,
they would have done it by now.
It's true.
True.
Someone's just been working away this entire time.
Like he started day one.
He's still putting the finishing touches on everything.
Hey, maybe.
I just remembered that we forgot to put patches
from Dark Souls into the Royal Rumble.
Oh, we didn't put patches, did we?
That's pretty true.
That's pretty fringe.
The Royal Rumble was another event of note
that we used some, I don't know.
It was this election of memes was interesting
considering now we've really got a large pantheon
and not everybody can fit even in like the 40 man one.
Such amazing characters as Big Dig,
the Samurai Ning who made it in.
Everybody loves that guy.
God, did you know he's just so shit all the time?
Can we just, you know, so bullshit?
At least he now has purple hair girl who I actually like
and is a good design that is cool.
So that's one.
You got one Digi.
Your whole light novel cast of characters, they're all fine.
He said that character just is Sabrina.
Oh, that's right.
She's Sabrina from Pokemon.
Just Sabrina.
That's very true.
But to be fair, like every anime character
is just some shitty trope with a different hair color.
That's true.
So, you know.
That's pretty base, dude.
I love anime.
It's well done.
They save us the trouble of like having to like get to know
or understand the peculiarities of new characters.
Yeah, because you can just see someone.
Oh, I know what this person's deal is.
No worries.
Sick, dude.
I love...
I love that.
Modernity?
I don't know.
I don't even know what I'm supposed to complain about.
I love modernity.
Modernity, yeah.
So how do you think the Royal Rumble
stacked up to old eras?
Because we had a new champion this time.
We're not going to spoil who it is, right?
We can save it.
I mean, people could have watched it any time.
We're not going to...
Oh, wait, it's already out.
Yeah, we live streamed it.
Oh, I'm so fucking dumb.
Yeah.
Yeah, no.
The ending was hype.
I don't know if noise ninja winning...
I don't know if the HTB guy winning was as hype
as the arm retrieval arm.
The arm defeating...
No, the arm was way too hype.
Especially the pose at the end.
The pose at the end, yeah.
But we were...
It was hard to beat that.
Perfect.
At the end, we were all definitely rooting
for noise ninja at the end.
Especially since Brad...
It didn't look like he was going to win,
but he pulled it out.
Especially since up until that point,
I had kind of forgotten that Brad Garlinghouse
was in the Rumble and he came in right at the end.
He was the last guy.
He had a good chance.
Like the best part.
A really good chance of winning.
It's like, shit.
After all this time, Brad's going to come back
and destroy the channel once again.
I was terrified he was going to win.
How bad, how sad would that have been
if Brad didn't won the Rumble?
The optics would have been all wrong.
It would not have been good.
Yeah, I know.
Thank God.
No, no, it didn't happen.
I mean, I loved having him there for the lecture,
of course.
We all loved having him.
Absolutely.
Pleasure, Brad, come back any time.
But also, fuck you.
Oh, wait.
Chemonically.
Is he even alive anymore?
I don't know.
Oh, shoot.
Yeah, he's alive.
Oh, sure.
Chemonically.
A ripple tanked and he committed suicide.
In some sense.
He must live.
He's got to live.
There must always be a Brad Garlinghouse.
A Garlinghouse is chained in the basement of my Garlinghouse,
and that's where he'll stay for all time.
It's like the Santa Claus.
Like if you kill Brad Garlinghouse,
you become the new Brad Garlinghouse,
and you start finding garlic in your pockets.
And you get your bank account and just skyrocket.
It goes to the moon, in a word, in a phrase.
We've got to do Redcon right now.
We've got to do Redcon again.
Redcon 5 to the moon.
It's in space.
It's on the moon.
We do it on the top of up.
It just feels like we were working the whole time.
We didn't really hang out enough.
We didn't stream.
There wasn't enough casual streaming just to be cool.
I do think of enough.
I do think the reason why it felt that...
Yeah, I don't feel like I got to hang out with everyone.
I don't feel like we hung out as much.
Even though I was there for less of Redcon 3,
I feel like I did more just hanging out.
Yeah.
And a lot of the time we were all spending
when we weren't doing a video or streaming
was typing up things for research notes
for the lectures we were all doing
and just looking at our phones.
It's like we're all scared about the coronavirus
and just looking at things like,
hey, do you know about this thing
that just happened in the coronavirus Twitter feed?
And it's like, yes, yes, we all know.
Lol, scared, cry, cry emoji.
I got to say, I looked like a real...
I didn't even walk on the beach enough times.
I wanted to do that more.
Yeah, that's important.
On the last day before we left,
I went out for one final walk up the beach
and I looked at one of those big weird pipes
sticking out of the sand and was like, hmm, bizarre.
Those are cool.
Speaking of the coronavirus,
I walked to Whole Foods today
and I looked like a fucking urban ninja
because I was wearing...
I was wearing like...
Well, when I went into Whole Foods,
I put on gloves and I wore a scarf over my face
because you're not supposed to breathe on stuff.
Right, right.
And nobody else was doing it
and I kind of started to feel stupid,
but I'm like, no, no, I'm right.
They're wrong.
I'm doing what I'm supposed to do.
Yeah, that's true.
Massachusetts is gonna get closed down soon
if they're not already doing it.
I was gonna ask, what's the status
of everybody's state or country or location?
Ohio just said they were locking down, right?
Like today?
I don't fucking listen to the news.
If you say so, okay.
Yeah, because my friend Ashley lives in Ohio
and she messaged me and was like,
yeah, they're locking it down until April 6th.
Wait, who does?
My friend Ashley.
Ohio, apparently.
Oh, yeah.
I have heard that they might lock down Massachusetts
or some part of it soon,
but they haven't done it yet.
I don't know.
Well, fair enough.
It's probably a good idea.
Honestly, I won't make a difference to me at all.
Because even if it's locked down,
even if it's locked down,
you're still allowed to go out and buy food.
Yeah, which is all I do.
That's the only reason I would leave my house anyway.
So like, whatever.
All this time, we were all preparing for our global pandemic.
Our lives were not pathetic.
We were just ahead of the curve.
It's a great time to be a neat, truly great time.
I'm the most patriotic guy around.
I'm doing my duty.
Yeah.
I love being a doom boy.
Doom Eternal is great and I love it.
I'm glad it exists.
And thank you, God, for making it for me.
It was really nice of you to do that.
God didn't make it.
This isn't a Christian game.
They made this a person who made this game.
Because you're going to kill God.
Or I don't know yet,
but you wouldn't go to heaven or something.
And I can't wait to kill God.
One of the tenants of Christianity
is that you kill God at the end.
You must kill God.
Well, they literally did that in Christianity, bro.
Remember that?
They did.
I mean, it sure was frowned upon, but it did happen.
They put them on a tree and they caught them.
They stabbed them in the chest.
They crucified them.
That's how it went down.
Pretty based.
Oh, I got nothing to say.
Doom is good.
Tom, I saw, of notes, just while we're on the subject,
I saw you saying, I think on Twitter,
that something about it didn't click as much for you.
What was that about?
Yeah, I'm not.
How do you, how so?
So far, I just beat the first boss, the doom hunters.
I just got to them this morning.
And I don't think I like it as much as 2016.
I think they went too far.
I think it's too frenetic.
I think it's too much.
I think the game has so many tools available to you.
I feel like it requires the precision of a mouse,
but it has so many functions and things to do
that it wants a gamepad for all the buttons you have to hit.
And I feel like there's so much going on in the game
that the first person perspective is a detriment.
And if this game was developed as a new IP,
it would have been a third person shooter
because of the situational awareness
you need in order to play the game function well.
I do find myself scrambling to remember
all the buttons for weapons I have available on my, you know.
They're all, they're all like necessary,
like using the grenades necessary, using the flamethrower.
You got to use that flamethrower to get the armor.
You got to be bashing people.
Yeah, I mean, that's true.
So it's all, it's not like you can just like
settle into your favorite really.
You got to, you got to use every tool at your disposal.
And so for all those buttons, I'm like,
this is clearly designed for a gamepad.
But then like, because you have to hit certain sweet spots
on the enemies, it's like playing this with,
like dual analog aiming would be a nightmare.
So it's like, you're trapped between two things.
And yeah, I just feel like it's a lot.
Is this compared to 2016 or classic due?
2016, 2016 was like, was frenetic, but not nearly as much.
Like they clearly dialed everything up to 11.
And as much as I like a lot of the improvements,
like the dashing and stuff is like really fucking sick.
Yeah, I love that.
It just feels like, I mean, I don't think it's a bad game.
I still am having a lot of fun with it.
I just liked 2016 more because it felt like more cohesive,
I suppose, in terms, I never, I never felt like,
I felt like exhausted at the end of a lot of the encounters
in 2016, but never like overly so.
Because like the Doom Hunter boss,
because I don't know how far you are, you're in.
I fought them, yeah, at least to that point.
It just takes too long, because like.
You got to switch between your fucking energy beam
and then you got to go to like rockets to blast the bottom
and then the shields back up.
And I'm out of energy bullets now,
so we got to go chainsaw people to get back,
you know, ammo and everything.
It's a lot, it's a lot.
The intensity is like always at an 11.
And I'm fine with that, but like it goes on for too long.
Like it just becomes monotonous,
because like the boss, you're fighting him
and you're like, all right, I'm almost done with the boss.
And they're like, oh no, he has multiple life bars, fuck.
So you're still going and then like you kill him,
you're like, all right, I did it.
And then you drop down the hole, now there's two of them.
And it's just like too much, too much, too much.
Like if this encounter came later, fine.
But like putting them back to back, like no, no, no.
Like you're firing on all cylinders for too long,
pacing, very important.
I see your point.
I don't know if I quite agree,
but I certainly do feel like my fingers are stretched
to the limit.
And it is a lot to keep track of at any given point.
Okay, anyway, anyway, there's your little doom review,
doom eternal.
I'm very excited to play more though.
And I can't wait to go back.
I'm definitely going to finish.
Yeah, no, no, I'm actually,
I didn't do this in DOOM 2016, because I, oh my God,
I played that on Switch, Jesus Christ.
What a fucking retard I was.
But I have this one on PC, thank God.
And I mean, I'm actually really excited.
The first perks I got were like,
where all items are on the map and like how to,
like what items they are.
So now I, after I beat a level,
I'll immediately go back and get all the secrets I missed.
Oh, it's so much fun.
Oh, I really like it.
Really, really good game.
I should do that with 2016 as well.
I should play it again.
Okay, anyway, anyway, enough of that.
Did anybody get Animal Crossing?
Just out of curiosity,
because this is the other one everybody's talking about.
I've never been, I've never been a big Animal Crossing guy.
I played one Animal Crossing on like the DS,
I think for a bit.
I played that game a ton on the DS.
Wild World?
Maybe we were playing the same copy.
No, Wild World was the three DS.
What?
I thought that was the DS one.
Oh, okay.
I thought New Leaf was the three DS one, right?
Oh, you know, maybe you're, hang on,
fucking DS, Animal Crossing.
Cometers, let me know if I'm based a cringe on this.
Okay, you are correct.
It was Wild World, okay.
Hell yeah.
That's the one I played a ton.
But I want to get it,
but I think I will lose time and efficiency if I own it.
So I'm being a responsible adult and not buying it,
even though it does look pretty fun,
because now you can like customize your town
and you can like actually shape the terrain and the geography.
Something I've always wanted to do in Animal Crossing,
but I'll be a good boy.
Oh, plus we're on a tropical island, which is-
It's on brand.
Radcon, for Paradise Anybody.
Do you get it?
Mm-hmm, I see where you're going.
I'm picking up what you're putting down here.
Oh, it's fun.
They're cool games, but whatever.
Oh my God, guys, are you like shipping?
Like I am like Doom Guy with Isabelle,
because like their game's like same day, bro?
What if different game, but same day,
characters had sex?
What if?
Are people doing it?
She's just a dog.
She's just a small dog.
You can't have sex with a small dog.
I've seen a lot of fans on 4chan.
Well, you're on 4chan.
That's your first bra.
Bro, but the deep lore is that the fucking-
The Doom Guy had a pet bunny.
I know Isabelle is a chow-chow, but it doesn't matter.
Small cute animal that he loved, and then it died or something,
and that's what made him so mad, among other things.
So it's like he has a history of loving cute little animals.
So he could definitely be shipped with Isabelle by me,
and it would be totally legit.
It's based.
I know this is what people want and are dying to hear about,
so you're welcome, bro.
I'm keeping you up to date.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, video game talk over.
Ooh, finally.
What else is going on in the world?
How about the corona?
We can talk about the corona a little bit.
I feel like I talked about that.
We're going to get demonetized.
I guess you're right.
You're literally not around talking about the outfit.
I've got something that I've just sort of realized,
which is going to bring the mood down.
I might die.
I might be going to die.
But on the plane ride home, I was feeling kind of cramped,
and then when I got home, I had diarrhea and a fever,
and I was like, ah, shit.
Of all the things to get,
it was something that wasn't the coronavirus,
but still hurts a lot.
I'm looking up the thing,
because Digi just said symptoms of that do arise with coronavirus.
And I looked it up.
Apparently, it's less likely, but it does happen.
So I might have had the coronavirus this whole time.
It's possible.
I mean, we were saying before,
I was feeling a little under the weather.
I skipped my last two streams,
because I haven't felt great the last couple of days.
Like, sure.
Theoretically, it's possible.
If you came to the meetup and you talk to me, I'm sorry.
I mean, maybe they infected you.
They should apologize to you, Gib.
I mean, it's possible, I suppose.
But you can never be sure of these things.
I'm just going to say whoops in case.
But it also says there's a higher mortality rate
for people who have the diarrhea alongside
and it also says that you could have the diarrhea,
but without the coughing, which is why I didn't think I had it.
So I haven't been coughing at all.
I should probably fucking get myself tested.
You know, the funny thing about the testing,
when I just didn't feel great, I was like,
I guess I'll just go to the doctor and get tested or whatever.
You can't, because there's not enough testing.
It's only for medical personnel.
And I think it was like people confirmed to have it.
Okay, well, that doesn't make sense.
Why would they test if they know they have it?
I don't know.
It was very limited.
It might have been government officials or something.
For me, I assume it's going to be a waiting list sort of deal.
You press 111 on your phone right now in the UK,
and you get the coronavirus hotline.
Get Munchie's voice in the door.
Do you have coronavirus?
And I say yes.
As he does.
Yes.
And say, okay, go to bed and stay there.
Maybe I should do like an I'm dying stream,
where I just play a branching clank or something.
Because I don't expect to be able to get into a hospital at this point.
There's so many fucking people already with the thing.
The webcam's just going to go up.
You in bed wrapped up in blankets.
We'll just clarify.
I should definitely try to get a test.
And if I can't, then I'll try to rest it off.
Because I assumed the diary had stopped.
It was all fine.
It was just a little bit of stomach bug.
Yeah.
But I'm not perfectly fine.
So it could be like the beginning signs of having the coronavirus,
or my start coughing soon.
We'll just clarify.
If this is the beginning of my death.
Well, I can be ignorant about this.
I think I know the gist though, or at least some of the facts,
that like, I mean, you don't feel deathly ill,
as I understand it.
You're just concerned that you may have this specific illness.
I have like a very vague headache.
Almost no chance that you'd be seriously hurt by it.
Well, I mean, when I was like in my massive pain,
like when I came back and I had the diarrhea,
and it was like fever,
I couldn't really eat anything,
otherwise I'd vomit it up.
And I couldn't really, you know,
it was just sort of like, couldn't retain water.
It was very painful.
Okay, sure, sure.
I was in bed for an entire day and a half,
and I couldn't sleep.
So if that happens again, that will be bad.
That's not good, okay.
That's not good.
So I assume I'm over the worst of it,
because, you know, I'm like 26.
I'm not likely to have a, you know, massive thing.
But I don't know how this thing propagates.
Does it come in waves?
Maybe it does.
No, I'm not really sure.
Like, can I feel better and then feel worse later?
I'm not sure.
I mean, it's probably possible,
because like, if you're like something happened
and like your immune system got worse for some reason,
and it got a second foothold on, I don't know,
your body fights it off.
And like, if you're healthy, most of the,
if you're not ancient and you're healthy-ish,
most of the time your body fights it off in your esophagus
before it gets to your lungs.
And then you're, and that's when you have mild.
You get bad coronavirus if it gets to your lungs.
That's the confusing thing.
That's the confusing thing, though,
is like, if it's going to my intestines instead,
like, could it then...
Well, it wouldn't be the virus.
It's not, the virus is not in your intestines.
It would be, I don't know,
some kind of secondary bodily response.
In your butthole, just hanging out,
converting poop to diarrhea as it passes through.
It's a tricky one.
Maybe I sat on a virus and fisted to dildo it,
and that's what caused it.
Well...
I heard one fact that,
I mean, I don't forget where I heard this,
but I heard, I'm hearing so many of these things
that may or may not be true.
I've heard that like, 99% of people,
I believe who died,
only died because they had a second,
like, debilitating illness
that made them particularly vulnerable to the corona.
I mean, usually, yeah.
Usually, yeah.
Like, it's not necessarily the case.
That's true, it's 99% it's not 100%.
It's not guaranteed.
You can have, I think there have been cases
of like someone with, like, a young, healthy person
with no underlying issues can like,
just get real unlucky,
and like, they'll go to fucking critical condition,
because like, it gets in their lungs
and it fucks them up and they can't breathe
and they need to be respirated or they die.
It's, be afraid, people.
Be afraid.
Yeah, I'd run it in the sight of being afraid.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, I mean, if you feel bad.
I'm gonna deal with that as soon as we're done here.
Yep, that seems like the right thing to do.
And I would encourage anybody who feels similar to Gabe,
if you feel, you know, this level of bad,
if you just got a little cold, I'm sure you're fine.
But if you got, you know, any of the symptoms he's saying,
that's, you know, reasonable to get that kicked out.
Something to consider,
because I, like, a couple days ago, I Googled,
like, what are the symptoms of corona again?
Oh, respiratory problems, cough.
Okay, I don't have that.
Fever, cough, trouble breathing.
Yeah.
If you don't have that, it's probably not coronavirus.
But I do have the fever.
And so with this, like, diarrhea thing,
it's like, that's linked.
If all you have is a fever.
There's probable cause.
There's probable, what's the word, to, like,
there's reason to suspect.
Yeah, I don't, I don't know.
If all you have is a fever,
it's way more likely to be something else.
Like, there's plenty of things,
there's plenty of more common things that cause fever.
Like a cold or a flu.
Maybe, but like, not many fever things cause diarrhea.
I'm just saying, I just looked this up.
Do they?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, plenty of, you can definitely get diarrhea
when you just have a cold or a flu.
The virus does not, like, directly cause that.
The virus is in your lungs.
So if, if you don't have, like, breathing problems,
I mean, it's probably not coronavirus.
Most likely, I mean, it could be anything's possible.
I'll, I'll check it,
cause I'm, I'm all spooked by this new knowledge,
but whatever.
Okay, I'm, you're, it doesn't sound like
it's likely to be coronavirus.
If it was something significantly worse.
Who knows?
Sure.
Yeah, definitely.
Right.
Oh, it's way more likely to be something much worse.
It's, what could it be?
At least it's not, at least it's not,
if it's something worse,
at least I won't kill my family with it.
That's the whole thing.
Oh, no.
Oh, you will.
It's way more, whatever it is.
You will kill them,
but it won't be related to the virus.
You're just going to get mad, you've got chainsaw,
and just fucking massacre them all.
Maybe I got coronavirus too.
And I'm going to propagate vans from the UK.
The coronavirus too comes out.
You got the HD reaster of coronavirus, you know?
Yeah, it's like it's bigger,
better, and stronger too.
It's the second member of the coronavirus crew.
COVID.
COVID-19.
No, COVID-20.
And then COVID-21,
and then Goku comes back,
and he's like,
I'm not going to die anymore,
and he punches the virus.
Damn.
Remember that?
Remember Dragon Ball?
I do remember Dragon Ball.
Epic.
Hey, me too.
Well, I mean, if you guys want,
I've got the voicemails,
but if you've got anything else you want to talk about,
feel free.
Have we given the people their money's worth yet?
I mean, it's over an hour.
We're only an hour and 10 minutes.
I feel like it's been three weeks
since we had a fucking episode.
Yeah, let me look up the list of things
that happened during Ritecoin
if there's something we didn't talk about.
Did you keep a journal or a list?
I kept a little gay journal, you know?
Hey, you know, I'll let you look that up.
I'll give people one interesting fact
that I just think is fun.
So while we were at Radcon,
we've been talking about like,
so the reality of Radcon is that like,
we got like $34,000 or whatever,
but much of that we knew would be absorbed.
Like a minimum of $10,000,
and that's before all the additional stretch goals
we promised in order to just to break even.
So I mean, that seems like,
okay, it's like $24,000 cleared.
Great.
But then also there's, you know, production stuff,
various things that are also going to eat in that.
Okay, cool.
So what I did finally after Radcon was
we've been documenting all of our expenses and stuff.
And what I have now is a running spreadsheet
that like every expense I can now plug into that thing.
And at the bottom, what it has is it spits out
like how much profit each of us is going to make off the top.
And I'm not going to talk about how much it is,
because that's private information.
But it's fun for me to watch
as every expense gets added to it,
like how that number goes down.
And we want to maximize our income, obviously.
While delivering on each of the promises that we've made,
because that's the agreement, of course.
But it's a fun exercise of me, spreadsheet man,
that's my superhero name,
to be upkeeping that with all the expenses
and being just really mad at all of you guys
for daring to expense anything
and not just giving money for free for no reason
to all of us so that we can all make more money.
It's very selfish of you guys.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
True.
Guilty as charged.
That's capitalism.
I love making money is the point of that.
Expensing things was so cool.
It felt so cool every time I would go shopping
and be like, uh-huh.
Yeah, I'm spending all this money on groceries for the house.
We actually have money to cover the things we need
to make Radcom this time.
Spending all this money on groceries at the house,
put it on my tag.
Put it on the expense account.
Yeah, work will cover, yeah, on the expense account.
It felt like a real jet set radio.
If you know what I mean.
It's fucking great.
God, if we just, if we clear like a little-
You bet we can't live like that.
No, if only.
If the PCB got vastly more successful.
I mean, I just think about like those fucking guys,
like Come Town and those other podcasts
that make literally too much money.
It's not right, it's wrong.
Imagine if we made like that much money.
We could just live our lives being like,
eh, put it on the PCP account.
Pretty much, pretty much.
Do you know who I am?
I'm on the PCP.
It's free.
It's great.
Okay, I guess the only different thing that I have here
is that I shave all my fucking leg hair off.
Oh, God, that did happen.
Oh, I shave all the hairs off my hands and legs
and arms and feet.
I've talked about doing that, but give was the one
who actually committed.
Punish Gibb and take.
Jesus Christ.
It was extremely gay, but I do think
that having super smooth legs is very based
for like five minutes.
Sure, sure.
Because it feels like, whoa, these are on my legs
and you touch them and you're like, that's not my leg.
That was fun.
It was interesting.
Which lecture was it, Gibb, that you,
because you were in a lot of pain.
It was my lecture.
Yeah, it was the first lecture.
Tom's right, okay, okay.
We're like, because we, I shaved my legs
and then I didn't know how to do it,
like I did it wrong.
I didn't realize I was giving myself
like thousands of tiny microscopic cuts.
I didn't see any blood.
I mentioned that to Michelle later,
and she was like, it should not hurt that much.
That's not good, that that's.
I was using like dull, like 7-Eleven razors.
And I was scraping it all off.
And the day after, well, I do it during the night,
and then the day after, we did the OVA,
which involved running around on the beach,
rolling around in the sand,
getting in the salty seawater,
which fucked them up quite a bit.
Low.
And like that night, I think,
when did we do the first lecture?
Was it the day after that?
The third or the fourth day?
I think it's the fourth day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Monday the night.
The day after, I believe.
They were in extreme pain.
I was in constant pain the entire day,
and I hated life.
I regretted everything.
It sucked.
Yeah.
Don't do it if you don't know what you're doing.
But on the other hand, pretty fucking base.
Just fuck it, man.
Just do it.
Pretty base, though.
Yeah, pretty base.
It was pretty base to do it.
I've never felt so smooth.
Indeed.
You're a hairy man.
Gross, dude.
I mean, I am a hairy man.
I have shaved my body before,
and yeah, it feels terrible.
No, it doesn't.
And it lasts like a day.
I feel like once, like for a few minutes,
it feels like really good.
And then when the pain sets in, then it feels terrible.
But when the hairs come back, they stop poking through.
Well, when I shaved my torso now,
and then until the hair starts moving around,
I feel my shirt on my skin in a way that is very distracting.
It's not painful exactly, but it sucks.
I don't have a lot of chest hair,
so that's not a big thing for me.
But once in a while, I will shave my armpits
just because I'm like, well, this is too long.
Let's just start over again.
I have done that before, and it also feels bad.
And I hate it.
It fucking hurts, especially when it grows back a little bit.
And then there's prickles,
and then you're stabbing yourself with your armpits.
The armpits are the least bad part, I feel.
You think so?
Yeah, I don't know why.
Well, maybe compared to other stuff.
I mean, the armpits are fucking sensitive.
I guess they are.
Maybe I'm hard as nails.
Maybe I'm the tough man.
Like, I didn't pass out when I should have.
Hard as nails.
It ain't hard to tell.
I sat through that whole Animorphs lecture.
I learned about yirks.
Yeah.
Watch the fucking Animorphs lecture.
There's a bunch of people.
Go watch it.
The reaction's been incredibly positive,
which I'm happy about.
K.A. Applegate approved.
Because I was like sweating balls sitting there
before we started being like, this could suck.
Yeah, yeah.
But no, it was good.
Yeah, I promise you.
And now the people are getting to voice their agreement.
And it's great.
I dig it.
My favorite thing by far was this shit about zero space.
I'm so happy that they came up with their own system
of fast and light travel.
It's at 11 K views already.
After what, like two days?
One day?
Less than two days.
And the lectures are slow burners.
They retain serious viewership long-term.
And they just spread like a virus.
They got big aroma.
I really don't know how much the risk of lecture.
Because the content of it is like, it's pretty good.
It's not like the best it could be.
I feel like I fell short in a few areas.
Yeah, they never are.
But the subject matter, there's a lot of homestucks out there.
And Vriska is a very contentious character.
I title it like the best character in Homestuck.
Indeed.
Vriska 101.
That makes me mad and angry.
Are people going to jump on there and say, no.
No, it's not true, Vriska Stucks.
Is that going to bolster the views?
I hope it does.
Tom, when your lecture came out, I thought, oh boy,
someone should post this on Reddit r slash animorphs.
But then I was like, there's no way that exists.
Or if it does, there's like five people on.
Right.
But you should definitely post the Vriska one on r slash Homestuck.
Oh, I might get destroyed.
But yes, I should.
No.
Wait, is it like a universal thing
that you're not supposed to self promote on Reddit
or is it only some subreddits?
I assume it's, well, maybe not.
Not every subreddit enforces that,
but it is like general practice that like,
unless it says otherwise, you're not supposed to self promote.
Well, I mean, I'll fucking post it for you if you want me to.
Yeah, I mean, I think it's fine on the Homestuck Reddit.
The reason I have reservations is that Homestuck fans,
like vast majority, are people who are still into Homestuck.
Ergo people who are stupid.
And they don't understand things like act six wasn't as good
as the rest of Homestuck.
Vriska did nothing wrong.
They believe that all of the bad things.
And they are the, you know,
so those are the people on the Reddit
and they will come to the video and they will say no.
It would be like talking about,
it's like when the Brony lecture is going to drop.
And, you know.
Oh yeah.
I'm so excited for that.
I forgot about that.
Imagine all the comments that'll be in there.
Dude.
It'll be sick.
I would love, I would love fucking.
For the response to that one.
I'm pretty excited.
Yeah, I would imagine.
Imagine if FNGR does a huge big thing.
Imagine if anyone, like a misanthropony does all the little action to it.
FNGR is such a fucking piece of shit that like,
it would be so funny if,
like if he tried to do anything about it,
it would just like be,
it would just make it even cooler that like,
oh, FNGR went and like,
he said all this shit in response to this video.
It's like, that just means we're good.
Like if it makes FNGR mad,
that just shows you that you're on the right path
and you, and you should continue.
Shout out to my boy FNGR.
Shout out to FNGR.
Face to this very day.
Love you, buddy.
What was I saying?
Oh, hey, did, did anyone ever post like,
was there ever like a thread on Reddit about arm retrieval?
Did that ever get posted there?
I don't know.
Did like, did, did, did R slash Homestuck have any response to arm retrieval?
Strong disavowal, I'm sure.
I feel like if, if it's as you say,
and the people on R slash Homestuck,
and I'm sure that you're right,
that they're all like, no, no, X6 wasn't that bad.
No, no, no, the ending was good.
No, they probably hated it.
Not all of them, I think it was posted there a little bit.
A few people from who found arm retrieval via the Reddit
are now like in RFCK.
I think Shaddock was one of those people.
Sick.
He was a Homestuck man.
He found arm retrieval and he was based, so he liked it.
But it didn't get a lot of traction on the Reddit, I don't think.
Speaking of Shaddock, I am having him, her,
I don't know what Shaddock is.
Sure, it's a him.
I only know Shaddock has a gray blob from...
Yeah, yeah.
But I'm having Shaddock make a little thing for,
for, for, I'm commissioning for a little,
a little, little treat to slap into the fucking CWC 102 lecture.
It's gonna be fun.
Of what medium?
It's gonna be...
Are they, are they an art person?
Animator.
Oh, okay, okay, cool.
This is gonna be a little funny, a little funny thing.
They did the very first arm retrieval animated,
if you remember that.
Oh, that's right.
Okay, right, right, I remember now.
Based.
It's based.
It's based, dude.
It's fucking based, dude.
How long do you think the based cringe meme is going to subsist post-radcon?
I thought it was dead.
Because we're all still at least a year.
At least a year.
I, I think, I thought it was like dead a few,
like a day or two ago,
but now that I'm in this call and I'm hearing it,
I'm just like, yeah, you know, based on cringe is still based.
Well, I know that it's not dead,
because I am still saying it constantly in my real life.
And that's, that's all it takes.
I'm just, I'm gonna carry the torch to my grave.
I wanna challenge someone to make images
that we can use as emotes in the PCP Discord server
that are based on cringe,
that we can then upvote and, you know,
make, let's keep this thing going.
There's no, they don't look like anything.
Well, just, yeah, well, I use some artistic ingenuity folks
and, you know, just sign on the look here.
I'm, I'm, I'm remembering, uh, uh,
Milhouse's dad playing, uh, uh, uh, uh,
Oh God, what's that game where you draw?
Pictionary?
Not Pictionary.
Is it Pictionary?
Yeah, playing Pictionary and he draws the squiggle.
It's dignity!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, exactly, that's what I hope to see.
Man, what the fuck?
Milhouse's dad is the worst guy.
No, he's the best guy.
What the fuck?
Kirk Van Houten.
Oh, dude, next Radcon 5, Kirk Van Houten lecture.
Oh, definitely.
That's a meep lore.
That's a, that's a risketeer lecture in terms of scale.
You know, I, I, I'm the subject of curse here.
Single character lectures.
Yeah.
Uh, fucking, yeah, be a risketeer, risketeer, ask.
Um, so in that episode, he's like really mean to his wife
and he's like yelling at her and like taking her for granted and stuff.
I'm just curious, in any of his appearances,
if he in fact had appearances before that episode,
was that like something like he was shown to be like aggressive or rude to his wife?
Or was that like kind of made for that video, for that episode?
Was, was he, I mean, was he like the bad guy?
I think it's, I mean, if I remember that episode,
like that, he was being very rude and mean to his wife.
I kind of just remember that like they just are angry at each other like the whole time
and then they get divorced.
Historically or just in that episode?
Just in that, just in that episode.
They were like just like normal parents, I think before that.
I think that's true.
There's, there's the one where in the magic eight ball episode,
when Bart and Milhouse are like beating the crap out of each other,
they come out and the mom is like,
Milhouse is out of bed and full of beans.
And it's like, it's a miracle and they just leave.
That seemed like a pretty happy family at that time.
They were doing good.
Wait, wait, why was he full of beans?
What did that mean?
It was because he had in that episode.
In that episode.
Yeah, he got broken up with by the girl and he was like in bed and he was depressed.
And then he found out that Bart did it.
And he was killing Bart at that very moment.
He like he left.
He just started strangling Bart and kicking his ass.
And they're like, oh yeah, he's back.
Milhouse is back, baby.
I remember that.
Oh, that was great.
That was fantastic.
And ironically, the Simpsons is so old now,
you could do a lecture on the Simpsons
because so many new people don't get into it.
The lecture on the Simpsons would be,
there's way more of the Simpsons to talk about
than there is of like Homestuck.
It would have to be a very specific focus on like.
I mean, you would have to be.
I mean, do you guys know that?
Fucking Hans Molman lecture.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you guys know the channel The Real Gyms?
I think you've talked about it before.
Yeah, The Real Gyms, he not like lectures, but he does like
YouTube videos where he'll like spot like a character
and talk about like their entire history throughout like the show.
What's like the length of one of those?
Just out of curiosity.
Maybe like 20 minutes or something.
Yeah, okay, okay.
So you got to keep it limited scope.
He did one on Hans Molman.
He did an Edna Krabapal.
I don't think there's one on Kirk Van Houten,
but there might be.
There should be.
Let me find out.
Why do we start talking about the Simpsons?
I have no idea.
I don't remember.
Because it's a great show.
Because it's a good show and everyone who didn't watch it
missed out, didn't have a child.
They're fucking Zoomers don't know back in the day.
It's still going, right?
They could watch it today.
Yeah, but it's not good now.
It's passed us from him.
Yeah, it's not relevant.
One day, every single person who worked on the first
series season of The Simpsons will be dead,
but The Simpsons will be alive.
No, there is no Kirk Van Houten episode.
Update your shit, bro.
We need it.
Real gyms.
Okay.
Well, hey, that said, how about voicemails?
I got them right here.
I'm ready to go.
I guess we might as well move on to voicemails.
Excellent.
I've got a selection that will titillate the senses.
I've no doubt.
So everybody, of course, you know,
speak pipe link down below, click on it,
leave voicemails there, et cetera, et cetera.
Now, of note, it's been like Ben said at the beginning.
It's been like three weeks since we've had a real episode
where we can answer voicemails.
Now, there aren't that many.
I think I have seven total.
There's more like six, because there's like some
two part of stuff here.
But let's let's take a look.
Here we go.
First one is from Clyde Caliber.
And let's see what he has in store for us and go.
Best date idea you've ever heard in your entire life.
Three, two, one, go.
Take her to Best Buy.
Go to the back where the blue rays are.
Tell her to pick out whichever one she likes best.
It doesn't matter which one it fucking is.
You immediately go and buy it.
If she's confused as to why
and she doesn't want it for some reason,
just tell her it's for your dad.
Wow.
That's his suggestion.
You really know how to pick them, Naean.
I liked it.
What's your favorite date idea, guys?
Jokes on him.
Best Buy literally today announced
that they're closing all of their stores.
You can't go inside them.
All stores?
Wait, is this a corona thing?
For the pandemic.
For the pandemic thing.
But you can only do curbside pickup now.
So your plan is foiled already.
I prefer a curb stomp pickup
where they just kill me on the curb when I pull up.
Maybe they can do that.
When I go to Whole Foods,
my local Whole Foods is connected to a Starbucks
and it's funny.
I see people wait outside the Starbucks
and the barista comes out the door,
asks what they want,
and then brings it outside to them.
Fascinating.
It's very weird.
Best date idea?
I don't fucking know.
Hey, hey, you know what is funny?
Why would you ask me that?
Yeah, Ben has no ideas.
Clearly.
My favorite date idea is self-isolation.
Just stay indoors and you don't talk late.
Yeah, Skype with your GF.
Great idea.
Okay, well, you know what?
It doesn't matter.
One of the reasons that I wanted to play this one
was to remind me that I just watched
the Steven Universe episodes.
There's so...
Oh, God, I haven't watched any of those.
They're not all bad.
I think they're 16 out now.
I never even finished original Steven Universe.
You should.
I didn't watch the last five episodes.
So you haven't seen the movie yet?
I did see the movie.
Oh, okay, good.
That's better than the episodes.
Fuck the episodes.
Although there is some good stuff there.
Okay, whatever.
I was going to say that in the last...
Actually, of note, this Friday,
in fact, the day you're listening to this
at like 7 p.m., the final two episodes,
so there's like four of the mini half-episode episodes.
That's how Steven Universe works.
The final four Steven Universe episodes
are airing like two day,
and the series is ending forever.
Steven Universe's future is over
as of a couple hours after you're hearing this.
So that's interesting.
I guess the movie in a season afterwards
never really caught on,
because I completely forgot immediately
that it was a thing.
I don't blame you.
After I heard that it was a thing.
Michelle's been watching and been reminding me,
and I finally caught up with her yesterday.
And as always, I still like Steven Universe a lot,
though I always make fun of it because there's some dumb shit.
Okay, but there was one...
What's the general plot?
What does Steven...
Oh, sure, sure.
I think...
In summary, so like Steven Universe happened,
then they saved the world,
then the movie happens,
and they're dealing with like fallout of,
you know, like some fucked up shit that's still going on.
Now that that's done,
it's just a little bit after that,
and basically it's just the story of Steven
having PTSD from his experiences,
and like acclimating back to being like a normal teenager.
I think you maybe explained that somewhere before.
Yeah, I mean, it's a little hard to see Steven
be such a whiny baby when he used to be such a Chad child,
but you know, it's understandable.
Doesn't he have like PTSD now?
Huh? Say what you said.
Yeah, yeah.
What?
That's pretty much the issue.
That's almost exactly what they're implying,
that yeah, he's got like PTSD,
and it makes him all fucked up in some ways.
He's got like weird...
Everyone's like going off to college
and like doing their own thing,
and Steven doesn't know what he wants to do,
and he feels really lonely and scared,
because he's missing people that he loved and stuff.
But...
Post-traumatic Steven disorder.
The reason that I mention it is because,
okay, here's a spoiler of an event that happens.
I won't tell you how it goes.
Okay, I have to tell you how it goes
for the sake of this event,
but Steven, like I said,
he's feeling really lonely,
and Connie is going to go off to college,
and Steven doesn't know what he wants to do.
So he talks to like Ruby and Sapphire separately,
because they're doing their own stuff,
and they both suggest that Steven propose to Connie.
These two have never been on a date.
What?
Connie gave him a kiss on the cheek once in the movie
to propose marriage.
They're Jim.
Is the proposal.
They're Jim fucked before.
Actually, Garnet later says like, yeah.
Are you trying to tell...
Nate.
What?
Are you trying to tell me
that you don't think Steven and Connie
like know each other well enough?
Ben, they have not been on one date ever.
You think marriage is the appropriate step there?
Are you fucking insane?
They've spent like three seasons together.
They don't need to go on a date.
They fucking spent a huge amount of time together.
Well, I guess it's a good thing
that the narrative literally agrees with me and not you,
because Connie says, obviously, no,
I'm not going to do that.
So there you go.
Why did...
Well, look, I'm not saying they should...
No, you fucking idiot.
I didn't say yes, they should get married.
I said it doesn't matter
that they haven't been on a formal date.
Well, okay, I mean,
I don't think that's how romance works,
so whatever.
Look, the point of it is...
What?
Ben, what is wrong with you?
No, it doesn't matter, Ben.
The point is that in this fucking retarded ass situation,
Steven sets out this like amazing spread.
It's an incredibly romantic scene,
and he like sings the song for Connie,
and Connie is visibly wooed
and would definitely fuck if pressed.
But instead of like doing anything romantic,
he just jumped straight to marry me.
And I just wanted to say,
everything about the way he did that was perfect,
except he had way too high of ambitions
for this one scene.
But it was like a really great romantic scene
that he just, for some reason,
in his weird asexual autistic brain
thought that marriage was the appropriate step to go to.
Aren't they like 16?
Yeah, yeah.
That's super weird.
How is she going to college at 16?
She's actually like a year younger
than Steven, I think, too.
So I don't know.
You tell me.
The fuck?
She's really smart.
Is this, I cannot imagine.
Is this played for laughs?
Um, okay, I mean.
The entirety of Steven Universe is played for laughs.
The setup is absolutely played for laughs,
but the emotional consequences of Connie saying no
is legitimately devastating to Steven.
Well, okay.
I guess that makes sense.
Yeah, yeah.
Hmm, I don't know.
I don't know if that was pretty good.
But I wanted to win.
I'm pretty excited for the finale of Steven Universe.
I'm looking forward to it.
I guess I'll get caught up.
But anyway, you should.
I mean, I'll do it.
The idea is that he needs to propose to her.
What, to like keep her from going away to college?
Oh, you know what?
He specifically proposes.
Yes, Ben, but even more than that,
he proposes to say like,
because he gets the idea from Ruby and Sapphire,
let's be Stevonnie forever.
Let's like do that.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's fucking weird.
Yeah, it's what you get for listening to Gens.
I mean, it's funny because Garnet herself says like Steven,
you listen to Ruby and Sapphire to like love-addled retards.
Listen to me, Garnet, because I'm smarter than them,
even though I am them.
I don't quite get it, but.
Garnet is that.
For this particular scene, she needed to not be,
so she wasn't.
And it was perfect.
Love that.
Yeah, I know, I know.
It's not perfect.
Next voicemail, Jesus Christ.
Okay, okay.
Oh, you're gonna love this.
This is from Virgin Rage is calling in.
Let's hear what she has to say.
Go.
I can't wait.
Oh, you're so nice, Jacks.
You're so sweet and kind and wonderful.
And oh, I love that new haircut you got.
Oh, you're so handsome and you're so funny
and so talented and nice and strong.
And you'll make a perfect boyfriend with it.
Oh, you're gonna make a perfect husband when you grow up.
You grow up.
Then I won't hit him.
You just fuck me over.
That's it.
Because they're lying to you, they don't actually mean it.
Hard to agree, I guess.
Hard to agree.
I think they mean it.
I'm gonna vote yes on that.
These women are gaslighting you and that is emotional abuse,
that they're not having sex with you.
Got to agree.
I mean, imagine your whole day being told how handsome and cute you are
and none of the women are having sex with you.
Something's wrong.
Don't let them get away with it.
Make them pay.
Yeah, that's the only thing to do.
Because they get what they fucking deserve.
Make them pay.
Fuck it.
I'm not telling you to do anything specific.
Just use your imagination.
Yeah, yeah, no, no.
Make them pay for your only fan's account.
That's the way, that's the way.
Okay, next one we've got Radcon Forever.
Okay, and take it away, go.
Bro, so like, what if you guys get stuck in your old Virginia place
because of the corona shit?
Like, what if, what if like,
great question and like, none of you guys can like, go anywhere?
You're stuck in Radcon Forever.
That's the joke.
Bye-bye.
Excellent.
I guess, I guess we would have just had to like,
crash at Digi and fix a house.
That's, it would have been the only thing to do, yeah.
Or, I mean, the alternative would be drain the Radcon fund on like,
getting a fucking hotel until the next time as we can leave.
I would have considered just like,
renting a car and driving home.
I mean, obviously, the only viable thing would have been
immediately kickstarting Radcon 5 and doing it.
Yeah, yeah.
Spend your precious money.
You don't have the ability to go to work anymore.
Spend your money on us.
Right, right.
Please.
Imagine, imagine if there had been like,
I mean, I can't imagine that they would have like,
said like, no traveling within the country.
But like, I can imagine a scenario in which like,
flights stop leaving the country.
Yeah.
And that would have been.
That's definitely possible.
It was the most vulnerable probably.
It would have been really funny if you were just stuck here for like,
a month maybe or something.
Years.
Lol.
I mean, on the one hand, it's, it would be pretty scary because,
I'm, you know, just like coronavirus, it's a pandemic.
I want to be, I don't know, in a place I'm used to the least.
A place where you can get healthcare that doesn't cost
$3,000 to get a coronavirus test.
Yeah, that's, that's also the thing.
But like, on the other hand, it would be pretty cool to have an excuse
to stay in America for an extended period of time.
Sure.
It's, it's not really a thing to like get a flight and that leaves
like a bunch of months later.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Like you have to stay for a certain amount of time.
And then if you stay for too long, you're an illegal immigrant.
You got to get out.
You know, I got a good deal on me and Tom's plane tickets.
But it's hurt, like, I guess like the price of tickets drop precipitously
because of the pandemic.
So it actually would have cost less if I had waited till the last minute.
Ah, it's one of those things.
No way to predict.
Yeah, there was no way to know at the time, unfortunately.
Hey, you know, I just thought of something.
I realized that I'm so scared of flying.
I'm so afraid of it.
You said, you say you realized, was this not a thing earlier?
I was so uncomfortable being there,
watching you have like all but a panic attack while flying
and being completely confused as to what to do,
if anything, to comfort this poor man.
No, I mean, there was nothing you could.
It was just like a descent into just like madness
because like we're getting on the plane,
we're getting on the plane the first time.
I didn't used to be like this.
I didn't used to do.
You just have to understand this from my perspective
because like we're getting on the first flight
and we're walking down into the back of the plane
because we're in coach.
And like you just like are like still in generally good spirits.
And you admitted off like comment of like,
oh yeah, I'm not really a fan of flying.
And I didn't know how serious to take that.
And like you were hamming it up
because like we're walking past one of like the stewardess who's like,
hey, we're going to be okay, right?
And he's just like, yeah, we're going to be fine.
And I was like, oh, there's Ben having a good time,
riffing on the help.
How hilarious.
Not realizing he was deadly serious about this question.
My mask cracked.
My mask like progressively cracked.
I got more afraid with every flight.
I was worse on the second one
and worst on the third on the one home.
You'd think it would go the opposite way
because it proved to, you know, turn it okay.
I'm not kidding.
I spent like every night at Radcon like,
and it got worse as it went on.
I was like, I would like have trouble sleeping
because I would be thinking about,
oh God, I have to take another flight home.
I have to fly again.
Like it cost me sleep and it was upsetting.
And I don't know what's wrong with me.
This is like a new thing.
This is like, like I flew to Radcon three and did I like flying?
No, but I didn't like flight of Radcon three
because you lived in the boxing area.
No, you flew.
No, I lived in Georgia at the time.
Oh, that's right.
That was back in the day.
Yeah, and like I didn't, on the flight home,
I had like such a strong like fucking episode
that I had to like get out of my seat
and like fucking hustle to the front of the plane
and be and like accost the flight attendants
and be like, what is happening?
What are we doing?
Why, was there turbulence or something?
While you were in flight?
Yes.
There was no turbulence,
but Ben was just like constantly like looking out the windows
and being like, where are we?
I don't get it.
I don't understand what's going on.
And I'm just like, Ben, we're above the clouds
and it's nighttime.
That's why you can't see anything,
but like he was not having any of this shit.
I could see the clouds.
I could see that we were above the clouds,
but I kept feeling as though I had a constant feeling
like we were turning.
We weren't turning,
but I kept thinking that we were turning
and I was like, why are we turning?
Where are we going?
And then we changed altitude at some point
and I was like, why is this happening?
Why?
No, no, something's wrong, something's wrong.
And I had to go ask the flight attendants,
like, is this normal?
Is this normal?
And they were like, yes, this is normal.
And I'm like, okay.
And I sat down again.
And it was fucking based.
Did you have like, did you have like action movie like?
There was no screens or anything.
No.
There was, was it like, like intense music?
The first flight was better
because we had the screens and it showed our altitude.
So I could watch the screen and be like, okay,
I see where we are.
I see our altitude.
It's normal.
We're not like, we're not plummeting.
We're on track.
This is reasonable.
But the second two flights did not have those.
And I, you have no idea what's,
there's no frame of reference, what's going on.
I don't know if every flight has this,
but I, I've discovered recently that when,
when planes don't have the screens that show a thing,
a lot of them do have like a Wi-Fi connection thing
that you can use to actually show the progress
and all those stats on your phone if you connect to that.
So perhaps that would be a helpful thing.
You could usually go to pay for that though.
And that's, I mean, it's been freed.
I mean, my flight had free Wi-Fi.
I've never had a free thing.
My, my flight had free Wi-Fi.
Anyway, I just thought I'd mentioned that.
It was a weird and unpleasant thing that happened.
And I don't like it.
I hope that gets better.
Yeah.
I know that statistically flying is the safest way to travel,
but it is also the scariest.
You know, I mean, you're the least likely to die.
Sure.
But, but I constantly think I am going to die.
I understand that.
You're the most likely to shit yourself.
Maybe you're more comfortable like, I mean,
imagine Radcon 5, let's just say theoretically,
it's in Virginia Beach again or whatever.
You could maybe take a train.
It would take longer, but you know.
It was so bad that I'm considering just never flying again
and taking the train just to avoid feeling that way.
I don't really see any downsides.
But then like, even though it would probably be more expensive
and take like 10 times as long.
Possible.
Smash cut to you being on the train.
You look at the window and it's dark and you're like,
wait, where are we?
Where are we going?
Oh, and the plane is plummeting towards the train
directly at Ben's window.
What, what, why is our altitude changed?
Where are we going?
Like, like the, like the shitty trains,
like the commuter rail sucks.
But like, like a good train, like a cellar or whatever,
is like, those are a joy.
Those are just a fucking, like a cross-country train
or just a treat.
They're just a treat.
Ben, your insistence on taking the train
reminds me a lot of one Joseph Biden
talking about investing in rail.
He loves, that's the one thing.
That's the one thing that I got it.
You got a hand, it's just like ISIS.
You do not have that.
Biden, you got, you got a handed to him.
He's a big fan of rail and so am I.
Fair enough.
Good for him.
And so is ISIS.
My hashtag, my president.
All right, let's go on to our next voicemail here
from an individual named Corn.
All right, Corn, take it away.
Hey, PCP, y'all better stay inside
and be practicing that social distancing.
Because if not, you're all fucked.
But anyway, my question is,
do y'all have any like media you'd recommend
people going through while they're stuck
holed up inside?
Like YouTube videos, TV shows,
Vidya, anything that you'd just like recommend
for like coming to Mumps?
Is that it?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Got it, quarantine media recommendations.
Got it.
End of, end of, end of voicemail.
Y'all better be social distancing.
I have a bunch of things that I like.
Here, I'll tell you what I really long
final fantasy, let's play, or speed runs from like a.
Just play the game.
No, it's gay.
No, like, like speed runs of like final fantasy,
seven, eight, nine, six, seven, eight, nine from,
from like GDQ.
You learn a lot watching speed runs that you won't get
just playing through anyway.
Yeah, not every speed run is interesting,
but the final, the really long final fantasy ones,
I can't get enough.
Bro, I was just, I'm just gonna, I said this the other day,
but I was just watching a speed run of Chrono Trigger.
It just felt good to just look at that game.
Oh, God.
Did you watch the one by Puexel from like 2016 or something?
The one, I remember, the Chrono Trigger one,
it was like the final game of like some AGDQ.
I think it was that.
And like, at the end, like they passed $3 million,
and it's like, the crowd goes fucking crazy.
It was great.
I love it, because they did all the end game quests and stuff.
Oh, it was satisfying, you shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good shit.
My other recommendation would be.
Remember when Square Enix was good?
Ah, kill me.
I'm sorry, go on.
No.
The fucking Yogg's cast, Shadow of Israel,
I haven't watched it in a while,
but I watched it like maybe like six or seven years ago.
And when I found it, I thought it was like the coolest thing ever.
It's a really long Let's Play series,
but it really goes places you don't expect it to go.
I would, if you've never watched, I don't know,
I feel like Yogg's cast isn't that relevant anymore,
but like, I don't know, Shadow of Israel
was a very cool Minecraft series that is not.
Oh man, did all of those guys get me tooed?
Can I ethically consume this content?
I don't know, did he?
Is that true?
I think so.
I don't really know.
I disavow that I said that.
I don't know.
I don't know, whatever.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
Give it a shot.
Have I talked about it and how it's like,
you think it's just...
You have talked about it, yeah.
You think they're just playing Minecraft,
but then like some weird shit starts to happen
and like suddenly there's like this whole narrative
that emerges and it's cool, man.
I guess I've kind of spoiled that reveal
just by talking about it, but like, it's cool, man.
People need to know the hook anyway.
Yeah.
So there you go.
Okay, give Tom, you want to suggest something?
I got a few.
Animorphs, obviously.
Fucking based.
Read that.
That's the time.
All the...
It's all like PDFs are available for free, right?
They're all available for free.
How do I open PDF?
But how do I open PDF?
Exactly, we're trapped here.
Listen, Jack.
Actually, speaking of Jack...
Hey man, hey Jack.
How do I open PDF?
You're a dang, you're a dang junkyard pole cat.
Oh my god.
The second thing I'm going to recommend
is Tales from the Gas Station,
which is a series starring character named Jack.
I thought you were going to go with Metal Gear Rising Revengeance
because there's a Jack in that as well.
There is a Jack in that as well.
Jack is a common name.
I don't know if you're aware,
but there are many Jacks throughout all of the media.
I don't know if he claimed that being in stock.
That was fucked up.
Yeah, yeah.
Jacks had a long and storied adventure
all throughout the years.
But yeah, no, Tales from the Gas Station's great.
If you like creepypasta kind of story,
but it's humorous and tongue-in-cheek.
It kind of pokes fun at the genre.
It's pretty great.
I love it, 10 out of 10.
Let's give people, since this is a practical question
of all this quarantine,
do you know where they can find it?
Where it's available?
You can, it's on No Sleep, on Reddit.
But if you prefer listening to it,
Mr. Creepypasta does a narration of it on YouTube.
And it's very well done.
That's how I listen to it.
I highly recommend it.
And if you really enjoy it,
Jack, Gas Station Jack,
the guy who writes the stories,
also has two novelizations
that expand upon the story available on Amazon.
I have both of them in hardback.
They're very good.
Cool, cool.
And the last thing I was going to recommend
is, I don't remember.
So I'm just going to say those two.
Sure.
All right, Gabe, what do you recommend?
Go to Gibb and Take.Site and read Bale, Jaype,
and the Lord of Ghosts comic.
Those are base.
Those are good.
Aside from that, I guess most people probably have
a long list of things
that they've been meaning to get around to.
Just do one of those.
Yeah, check your back.
I would probably, if I have, I mean,
I can work on the internet,
so I have no real excuse to not work.
But if I'm unable to do anything,
if I'm unable to move,
I'm going to try and figure out
how to watch all of Star Trek,
the next generation of the meaning to get around to that.
Queen.
That's what I'm talking about.
I should do that as well.
That's a big one.
And yeah, big old things
that you don't have the time
to usually get around to.
Smart.
Watch every video by Thought Slime.
Listen to Chappo, Trap House.
Get radicalized.
Now's the time.
It's never been a better time to see
in your house than right now.
It's never been more important, guys.
Oh, and play Pokemon Go.
Oh, you can't.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, I got a couple.
The last thing I was going to say
was a critical role.
If you want to just like literally do nothing,
like there's so much fucking critical role
to get caught up on.
There's like literally thousands of hours
of over the two campaigns.
It's super fun.
It's great.
Critical Role is like a bunch of professional voice actors,
DM'd by Matthew Mercer,
playing a Dungeons and Dragons campaign.
And it sounds gay, super fucking based,
because they all are doing like professional voice over
for all their characters.
And they get into character and like Matt Mercer
does like 50 different voices
and does voices for all the enemies
and all the NPCs.
Oh, it's grand.
10 out of 10 love critical role.
Definitely watch it.
I guess I could get maybe I'll start watching.
I'm sort of I'm sort of out of things
to watch on YouTube these days.
Maybe I should start watching.
I should go back and catch up on the seat.
This the the the the the sea team that fucking.
Oh God, what's the acquis acquisitions incorporated
the sea team?
Yeah, the like they do like a D&D thing.
Yeah, it's the penny.
It's the penny run by the penny.
I don't actually I don't watch the main series.
Acquisitions incorporated.
I own I mostly watch the like side series
with all their like fucking second rate friends.
You nobody's ever heard of now base.
Well, I've got some obvious suggestions.
But look, with the amount of time you got here,
there has never in there will never be very likely
a better time to catch up on one piece.
It's still my favorite thing.
You I mean, you can catch up on one piece
if you dedicate yourself over like two weeks
without too much of a sweat.
I would say.
Oh, yeah.
I have a little one piece to catch up on myself.
And then you can listen to the podcast every week, folks.
Wouldn't that be fun?
And you definitely start track.
Next generation is the best so far.
But if you like a little more edgy war stuff,
you can check out Deep Space Nine or the original
if you like more goofy shit.
And also it's a great time for big, long, old RPGs.
So how about fucking, you know,
Chrono Trigger, Final Fantasy, any of them seven
is a good place to start.
I guess six, five, nine.
I realize I forgot that I had like Final Fantasy nine,
like the PlayStation one version.
Just I bought it one day and I never played it.
And now I'm playing it.
Do it.
It's a great game.
Dude, you would love nine.
I think it's really mine is so fucking good.
Going off the Star Trek recommendation,
if you like Star Trek and you finish Star Trek,
Babylon Five is so fucking good.
It's amazing.
It's another show that came out around, you know,
a little like a couple of years, I think after TNG,
it was like mid nineties, really fucking great,
great characters, great story.
Love it.
If you want more like cool sci-fi stuff,
Babylon Five does not disappoint.
Did you say bad that you hate nine just now?
No, I said I never beat it.
Oh, okay.
Well, that's, that's fine.
That's fine.
I still have to go back and beat three and eight.
I never beat six.
I never beat six either,
even though I consider it my favorite one.
That's all right.
There's tons to do in there.
Oh, they're good, good games.
Was there something else I was going to suggest?
Also, how about Legend of Dragoon?
There's a classic game that nobody talks about anymore.
We'll play Legend of Dragoon.
Great game.
I never beat that one either.
That game gets off the fucking rails in a good way.
Remember that legacy, Ben,
of how our disc three of Legend of Dragoon was broken
for so many years we could not play?
Jeff or whatever.
I think it was Matt.
Matt, he was playing Frisbee with the disc.
Oh, wait, no, that was later.
What about Buck?
Yeah, a guy in our fucking Boy Scout troop broke
disc three of Legend of Dragoon,
and it took forever for us to get our parents
to talk to his parents and make him fucking
buy us a new one.
I think ultimately, I think that did happen,
but I didn't even play it.
And then I lost it, and I was sad for years.
But then I think Ben, for Christmas one year,
bought me a new copy of Legend of Dragoon,
and with that, I finally beat the game.
Did I?
I think so.
That's my recollection anyway.
I vaguely remember that.
That sounds like it might have happened.
That's how I remember it happening.
And I'm glad it happened, because it was good,
and it's a great game, and literally save Legend of Dragoon.
Please, bring them back.
They're dying, and they deserve more.
There's no GDQ.
I would love to watch a speedrun of it.
I would love to watch a GDQ, but there's none.
There's like one speedrun video on YouTube of it,
but it's just like some guy.
And it's not that interesting,
because the commentary is very low energy and sporadic.
It doesn't strike me as a great game for speedrunning anyway.
It would like the weird ways that the encounters work,
and other stuff.
Ah, I don't know.
I don't know.
All right.
Well, you got plenty of suggestions there, folks.
Play some Viggy games.
Play the new Doom.
It's good.
I like it.
Or the old Doom.
That's also good.
Okay.
Play Kingdom Hearts.
Ooh, now's a good time to play the good Kingdom Hearts.
One, Chain of Memories.
Two, and I guess I'll put three in there,
now that there's good DLC for it.
Skip everything else.
Okay, we had more questions here.
Let me see.
How many more do we got?
Three more total, but this is like two and one.
So let's, we can do these real quick.
I'm still, I'm being like,
I've suddenly come over, been,
been swept over with a wave of fatigue.
Well, luckily.
Which is one of the symptoms of the coronavirus.
No.
Write it out, Ben.
We're getting there.
Okay.
Good news, everybody.
Get ready to have fun,
because it's riddled my ass Batman
with the Scooby-Doo murder mystery files.
He's calling in.
Oh, and by the way, he asked me to remind everybody
that canonically what's going on
is that Johnny Bravo is playing
who wants to be a PCP millionaire.
And so that's what's happening
when we last left our hero.
He missed his chance
because he didn't show up to the meet-ups
to get his PC penny.
Is that what, I'm sure that's true.
Well, that's how,
that's the easiest way to become a millionaire.
That's true.
A PCP millionaire specifically.
So let's see how things go for our hero.
Okay.
Take it away.
Go.
Well, Johnny, would you like to continue?
We've been away on break for a while.
Is it like,
lay it on me, brother.
I really want to earn some money.
Hoo-ha-ha.
Take it, take it.
Okay.
Next question.
Who is about to kill Johnny Bravo?
What are you talking about?
Hoo-ha.
Oh, fuck.
Scooby-Doo-Doo.
That's who.
Where's my money?
Scooby-Doo at gunpoint?
I always knew I died this way.
Stop stalling.
Where's my money?
Scooby-Doo, give yourself up.
You're highly surrounded.
Better be careful.
I have one of my ass batman at gunpoint.
Like Scoob?
You don't have news, man?
Raggy, I always knew you'd betray me.
Hey, Scoob.
Yeah, where do I ask Batman?
Your plan has one fatal mistake.
Oh, yeah?
What would that be?
Before you killed Johnny Bravo, he taught me karate.
Hi-yah!
Karate suplex.
Well, well, Raggy.
Take it away, boys.
He was like, I would have gotten away with the two that weren't for you.
Where are my ass batman?
You meddling kids.
Thank you.
To the next time for the exciting backstory of the predicament.
And Scooby-Doo, mystery murder files.
I'd have to know the backstory.
I'd have to know the content.
Yeah, I'm dying.
Mystery murder files.
What?
That's got great news.
The little full starts make this like elevated like seven rungs up the ladder of greatness.
It's so true.
It's so keep it going riddle my ass Batman.
It's so weird.
I think he wanted to come to the meet up but he couldn't do it for whatever reason.
So we missed you, buddy.
We missed you.
What a shame.
We have you in our thoughts and prayers.
I had forgotten the joy of a riddle my ass Batman voice.
They never fail.
And so I forget it like with the Johnny Bravo thing.
I think that was just called who wants to be a PCP millionaire.
If I remember correctly.
I just happened to have Johnny Bravo in it.
But now the fact that it's called the Scooby-Doo murder mystery murder files.
It's actually Scooby-Doo is doing the murder mystery.
He is the criminal in these in these files.
And I wonder if there'll be more.
Right.
Scooby-Doo sounded a lot like Batman.
He did.
Yeah.
He occasionally sounded a little bit like Batman.
Sometimes.
Okay.
Say what he said.
Racky.
That's I've got good news.
We heard a little bit of it there at the end.
But we've been provided a full Scooby-Doo mystery murder theme song by riddle my ass Batman.
So let's let's listen and enjoy.
Take it away.
Look out for Scooby-Doo.
He's going to murder you.
He's going to rape you and I see you Scooby-Doo and your Mr.
Murder Crew.
Look out for Scooby-Doo because he's going to murder you.
Don't look back till you find a safer path.
Scooby's wrath will be waiting there for you.
Look out for Scooby-Doo.
He's going to murder you.
He's going to rape you in the butt.
I see you Scooby-Doo and your Mr. Murder Crew.
Look out for Scooby-Doo because he's going to murder you.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na.
Scooby-Doo's going to murder you.
Say it again.
Yeah.
More on-core.
That was great.
Is that the second OP?
Maybe it is.
Yeah, maybe it is.
That's my favorite one for sure.
Incredible.
Keep it coming.
Love it.
All right.
We've got one more, one more message and this one's coming in hot from an individual known as
The Big Gay.
Okay.
Let's clear the floor and let them see them.
From RCK?
It could be.
Let's find out.
Take it away.
Go.
I am a big smelly gay demon and I hate everything good.
That is why I hate the PCP dating sim releasing on April 1st.
Don't play it unless you want to have a good time.
Don't go to Twitter at PCP dating for updates.
Don't download the game on April 1st.
Especially don't live stream it if you're a PCP member.
That would be terrible.
You don't want to end up gay like me.
That, that voice mail, that was from Oblivionfall.
He told, he told me he was sending it.
Classic, classic Big Gay.
And so when you hear this.
Five days, April 1st will be the release of the PCP dating sim according to this.
Is Oblivionfall the Big Gay?
It sounded like them snakes to me.
It sounded like them snakes.
I was thinking it sounded like a little like them snakes too.
Is this just a coincidence that there's another guy called The Big Gay?
I feel like it's a coincidence but I don't know for sure.
I'm not sure.
Oh god, what a fucking quagmire.
Indeed.
Didn't the demo for the PCP dating sim come out last April 1st?
That sounds right.
It did.
Yeah, and we all thought they were joking and it wasn't a real thing.
That is true.
You see, I was gonna say, let's not ignore the fact that they're releasing this quote
unquote project on quote unquote April 1st, April Fool's Day.
That's what we thought last time.
Yeah, it is.
But then it really happened.
The joke then.
The tweet literally said the joke was that they spent way too much time.
Right, right.
That was the joke then.
Now the joke is that that was all a joke and none of it's actually coming out.
There is no game.
It's a first tapestry.
Yeah, I mean, they swiped this joke.
They said it would come out before Radcon 4 and that we could play it live.
But they failed.
That's okay, that's okay.
They fucked it up.
It's all a big joke.
They're just gonna, they're gonna post.
They're just buying time eternally now.
They're just gonna post a PDF that you can't open.
I won't be able to figure out how to open that.
And that'll really quagmire my presidency.
I'm very excited.
I trust Oblivion to deliver this message.
I believe that it's true, even though I don't have any proof or anything.
There you go.
April 1st people.
We have only his word.
Indeed.
I assume on the behalf of...
I don't know if Oblivion even worked with them to work on it.
Maybe they just asked him to convey the message.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I don't even know if that was like his recording.
Maybe he was like past it a lot.
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on.
But April 4th people, go follow at its PCP...
You mean dating.
April 1st.
April 1st, that's right.
Which is gonna be five days after you hear this, people.
So pretty soon.
Oh god, it's upon us.
It's upon us.
We were just last episode saying like where the fuck is it?
I don't consent, viewer.
You're not allowed to fucking use my route.
My route is off limits.
It's for me and my future god-chosen, destined wife.
Jennifer Diane Wright.
Jennifer Diane Wright's aunt, yes.
And Steven Lepisto.
And Sandra Woodruff.
Join the Collective.
And fucking...
Ben's joining that Polly Amherst relationship.
Whatever the fucking name was.
The real life Borg cube over there.
It's based.
Well there you go, people.
I'm pretty excited about it.
That was our last voicemail update with the PCP dating sim.
Very excited to see how that turns out.
So check out it a couple days.
Eldenath.
Eldenath de Vilio, that was the fourth one.
Who could forget that memorable character?
All right, well that's it everybody.
Hey, leave more voicemails.
Speakpipelink is in the description.
Keep them coming.
We will be listening to them and rolling them out
and enjoying them as you've seen here.
And other than that, at...
No, not at.
It's patreon.com.
Flash the procrastinators is where you need to go for all.
Excuse me.
The best PCP related bullshit.
I think when you hear this...
Bonus episodes.
A bonus episode is coming out like a couple...
Oh well it should be on April 1st.
Which will be the day that the bonus...
The fucking dating sim comes out.
So get ready for that ladies and gentlemen.
And there's like fucking 35 other ones.
So what a deal.
$5 a month or so.
Give us money.
We would be eternally grateful.
And more and more PCP stuff from Radcon 4.
We'll be rolling out as you will expect.
So watch for updates on the Kickstarter page.
I'm sure we'll be announcing and retweeting a lot of them
on Twitter at TPCrastinators.
So as always follow that for updates and stuff.
And I think at some point I think we want to make available
via purchase to those latecomers the like the bonus footage.
We'll probably sell it for some amount.
Kind of like we did with the Radcon 3 stuff.
So if you missed out you may get a chance
to catch some of it later on.
But we'll we'll keep you posted about that.
Probably be another thing on Gumroad or whatever.
In any case that's going to do it.
Cool.
That's it for the episode.
Sounds pretty base.
Not bad.
If yes.
Ooh.
Very little cringe.
Ending the episode though.
Totally cringe.
That is cringe.
Not base.
In fact that's not three, four, five hours long.
A pathetic two hours.
Not not.
Particularly base.
That's all there is to say about it.
Okay I gotta go.
I gotta go play Doom.
I gotta go work on videos.
I gotta fight more bosses in Kingdom Hearts 3.
Remind.
Oh my god I love my life.
And I love my body.
Thanks everybody for donating to the Kickstarter
and making Radcon 4 up.
And we got more content to make for you.
And we'll see you back next week with another episode.
Bonus episode soon.
That's it.
All right see you then.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Bye everyone.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Don't die.