Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever, and we're joined today by Tom Oliver.
It's like, I've just been talking about it on Discord, like it seems to be everyone in the world has seen this as a child and knows about it, and I've never heard of it until the end. Yeah, this is an old movie, like near the beginning of 3D, I suppose, where it was just like really badly made, and it's got some famous people in it. It's kind of like Aunt Bully, but worse.
Yeah, it's probably before they figured out what are these activities based on the movie. It's gotta be like a coloring book, right?
Okay, this is probably like a coloring book that comes with it or something. Man, this looks terrible. Well anyway, so what else is going on people?
Oh, I get it, it's like Red Riding Hood Winked. Yeah, yeah, I think so, and these are all the characters, the woodsman and the frog, famously. Yeah, he was always my favorite guy.
The detective frog, Mr. Frog. Oh my, what a green skin you have. The grandma's spicy lover.
Hey, so this is the first week. You'll be hearing this, I think, yeah, one week into the hashtag PCP editor contest is up and running people, so let me just get that out of the way.
You'll still have one week to make a fucking entry. We'll, again, put the link in the show notes. There's a video on this channel with just the condensed stuff, so you could just go fucking check that probably.
Maybe we'll just link that in the show notes instead. Yeah, go fucking enter the contest if you want to be the official every week PCP editor. All the details are in the document and in the video, so go read this carefully and enter if you care to.
We've already gotten a bunch of submissions though. Remember viewers, whether you think you can or you think you can't, you're right. That was, Albert Einstein said that.
That's very wise. That's very wise. Carl Sagan said that. Michio Kaku said that. Black Science Man said that.
Orange Man Bad said that most famously. Dude, I love Orange Man Bad. I follow him on Twitter. I saw Orange Man Bad today in a Cheetos ad. It is Chester Cheeto we're talking about, right?
Yeah, no Cheeto Man, Cheeto Man. Oh sorry, Cheeto Man, right.
I have been recently getting absorbed in watching my brother play a video game. It's like a personal stream. That's what I did when I was young.
And it's cool because in his room. I would just bully Nate and make it. Well, Nate, did I? I was pretty content.
I was going to say, yeah, I didn't have to make you watch me play video games. You just liked to.
Yeah, I mean, I was like around six to ten probably in those videos.
I think sometimes I felt bad like I was like being mean like, oh, I'm hogging the video game. But like, I think that was just kind of what you were into for a while there.
Yeah, I mean, not exclusively.
People with siblings who play video games understand like the appeal of let's plays before they were real.
Yeah, because it's sometimes it is just fun to just sit back and just watch somebody play a game.
Share both similarly friends simulators, but not real friends.
Podcasts and siblings, both social relationships.
Yeah, but it's good in his room because he's got like a big old like a big old widescreen TV from like when we upgraded the TV downstairs.
You've got the big word word and hooked it up so that it's like a huge TV up on a table.
And he's got this chair and I just sit in the chair and it's like a cinema.
I'm watching him play this game called Kenshi, which is really, really cool and really in depth.
And here's my game review is my hypocrite game review. I'm coming back.
This is where you get the information. Kenshi, it's a game about it's a survival game,
but it is incredibly rich with depth of like mechanics and systems.
Basically, it's it's hard to explain really quick.
But if I had like words, it would be like a rustic, like unrefined looking reality simulator.
You have your guy that you you can create and it's got he's got like D&D RPG stats.
So like all sorts of stats like thieving, farming, fighting with certain weapons and things, toughness, you know, and all these different races.
And you can recruit people in bars and you can form a squad and you can steal and you can fight and you can you can band together.
And you run around in this huge open world landmass and you just you just survive, you just do whatever you want.
You can mine materials.
Is landmass the name of the continent?
Yeah, why not?
I hope so.
From the southern reaches of landmass where we all call home.
And it's it's got the like the same energy as Minecraft.
It's like a fucking age of empires, but each individual person in your huge team is an individual person who has like a personality and can interact with other characters.
It's like D&D if it was like a time a turn based RTS, which is a strange way to put it, but it's like you can pause the game and like move inventory while it's paused.
And like, you know, you have people like you can assign jobs to them.
So like if you have, say, a farm, you need a storage for the wheat so that the wheat can be put somewhere once it's been harvested.
And then you have a grain silo where the wheat goes in and then out comes flour and flour has its own storage box.
You put the flour in there and then you can take it out of there and put it into the bread place to make the bread.
And then you have food and you have a person you right click you shift right click on like the bread and the person you shift right click on the bread oven.
And the AI will be like, okay, I need wheat, so he'll go check the storage.
If there's wheat, if there's no wheat, he'll go immediately to go, you know, do all the other things for them.
Yeah, like, yeah, it's it's really advanced AI.
It looks like a really old game, but it's I think it's kind of new and it's like a Kickstarter or early access something or other that's now PC.
Yes, on PC.
Pretty cool.
Well, it came out 2013 looks like.
Okay.
Yeah.
And it's just it's just there's so much to it.
It's so cool.
It's like the biggest in depth RPG world big thing of all time.
And I really like it.
Well, dope, dude.
We need a WRPG on this.
I've been.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, I was gonna say you mean.
Oh, wait, I get it.
I get it.
You're making because it's g r p j.
Well, wouldn't it be wouldn't it be g r p w.
Yeah, g r p.
Okay.
Yeah, good reason to play Western RPG.
I guess.
Yeah.
I've been playing.
I've been playing Stardew Valley.
I mean a little bit here and there.
I've started just for the rfck episode.
I started a file because I was like, well, this is a good game to play.
It's like fucking, you know, yeah.
It's a great game for that.
And then I started a file and I created the character of Jenny.
Jenny the Juvie, who is a farmer in Arson Brook Farms.
And I fell in love with Jenny, who is a man.
I am gay now.
Oh, okay.
But the thing is, okay, so this might be a little bit of spoiler, but I have plans.
I have plans for anyone who has played a lot of Stardew Valley will know this,
but turns out you can breed and farm and ranch slimes.
Yeah.
And so I'm like, well, I think I know what Jenny the Juvie has to become.
I like, yeah, she's sorry.
He, I get confused.
He's a slime rancher.
He's got a quote unquote slime rancher game.
If you, if you, if you will, God, I wish slime rancher had multiplayer.
But, but you did.
So, I don't know.
Jenny's got Jenny's got a really nice functioning farm, you know, cows, sheep, cheese,
goats, what?
Tomatoes, you know, Jenny's raking it in.
But I think, I think what she said on what any good Juvie is heart is set on,
and that's slime.
So he's got, he's got his work cut out for him to, you know, to, to, to, to go about
achieving, you know, do what he wants to do.
He's got my poor abandoned Stardew Valley file.
I haven't played in, I don't know, six, seven, eight months or so.
I'm sure they're doing fine.
Yeah.
So it's not like, it's different from Animal Crossing where it keeps track of time
that passes while you don't play.
Oh God, imagine if you went back to your farm and it was like,
wrecked.
It was, it was just like, it was all like rotted over and the trees were all dead.
I mean, the Animal Crossing system is rather cruel.
Yeah.
To just, like you have to keep playing it or things fall into despair.
And it's a nightmare.
It's very cruel to do.
You get back there and fucking, and fucking Sally, Sally the goat or whatever, like the
bank foreclosed on her house.
Yeah.
Like, and like, you know, Johnny, Johnny the, Johnny the sea cucumber.
It's like, he never leaves his house anymore because his only friend in the world stopped
calling him and he got depressed and he went off his meds and stuff.
Yeah.
Much.
You know.
I mean, I'm sure you guys have all seen that one comic about the dude who has like his
DS, whatever, version of a movie for whatever.
Oh yeah.
And he's like playing and he hasn't played in a while and he's like, you know, I want
to go back, but I'm, I'm just so like, if I pick it up, they're going to be so mad at
all my friends.
They're going to, they've all forgotten about me and moved on.
And then he, and then it just cuts to the world of Animal Crossing where they're having
a little party with like a framed picture of his character saying like never forgotten
as they all like party around a fire.
Oh no.
I thought you were going to talk about the one, have you read the one where like the kid
is playing, like the kid's mom had cancer and she started playing Animal Crossing and
she really liked it.
Oh yeah.
And then he started getting gifts from his mom, but like, isn't that just a thing that
happens in the game?
Like it's not like his mom actually sent him gifts in Animal Crossing.
Okay, but it probably made him feel like she was still there or something.
I felt like the story implies that like, wow, my mom did all this in the game.
Like just, she just wanted to express her love for me in her final days.
It's like, I don't, I don't know about all that.
Well, okay.
This guy needs a fucking wake up call.
Your mom's dead and she never loved you that much too, so it's time to get over it.
She just liked fucking Tom Nook.
She just was a big, she just really liked gathering coral on the beach.
You idiot.
Okay, that might be true.
You know, Stardew Valley is just Terraria flattened and Terraria is just Minecraft flattened.
And Terraria and Minecraft is just a Moon, Harvest Moon, but in HD.
But the same.
Yeah.
And the best one, the best one I still think is, okay, Minecraft is pretty amazing, but
Terraria I think is the best like game.
Nope.
It's the most fun to like play through.
No?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I always get bored of building because like your base is just, I guess it's just a load
of sideways.
A load of bullshit.
It's not, building bases in Terraria is not as interesting.
In Minecraft, you can go really crazy.
It's, it's, yeah, it's definitely better in Minecraft, but, but it's a trade off of less.
I mean, Terraria doesn't really have much of like a building aspect to it.
No, but what it does have is like the unlocking new biomes and like exploring the world.
Yeah.
And like that's way more satisfying in Terraria than it is in Minecraft.
In my humble opinion.
That is, that is true, but I, there's something about.
Minecraft has very, it doesn't have that sense of progression.
Yeah.
I suppose so.
Not as much in Minecraft.
But like as like, I mean mining and crafting and, and building the three things.
I love building and walking around my creations.
Like I see a mountain.
I don't know why they didn't call the game Minecraft build.
Yeah.
I see like a cool, like a recently before I stopped playing games forever.
I was in this Minecraft world where I had built this cool base.
There were like four, like really steep sharp hills that went straight up like spikes.
And I built a house on all four, all four corners of those hills.
And it was just sort of like, looks like it was supported by them.
How do you get up there?
Oh, the house is sitting on top of the, there's like the pillars.
And the floor is glass and the ceiling is glass.
So the sun goes all the way down to the bottom and it's really cool.
And I had like another fortress, another gate and I went through it and I found myself in
a big old desert and it just started building a real pyramid.
It was just like, I just love stuff in Minecraft.
It doesn't even need to be like interesting or like, you know, the coolest like gameplay
experience of all time.
It's just like the slow progression of carving the world to make it look how I like.
It's really, it's really engrossing.
Have you ever seen, you ever watched Shadow of Izrafel, the Yogscast series in Minecraft?
I've heard you talk about it before.
Have I talked about that on PCP before and how much I love Shadow of Izrafel?
Man, well, I'll give a brief recap.
I won't get too much into it, but it's a long, it's a long like Let's Play series where Simon
and Louis, Simon and Louis, Simon, they're playing, they're playing Minecraft.
And at first, like they're just, you know, they're building a base to try to survive.
They're just, they're just playing Minecraft, but then they find this like pyramid that
they didn't build.
And there's like a little sort of like game in there where they got to jump across like,
like blocks to get across lava to find the chests with stuff in it.
And they're like, oh, I guess, you know, I guess there are other Yogscasts people like
put this here.
How, how, what a goof.
And then like they find, like someone else logs in and they don't know who it is.
And it's like, it's someone else and, and like he's just, and he starts attacking them
and they're like, who is this guy?
And then the guy runs away and they follow him and they find this road.
And the road like leads to this town that is populated by like other players are in there,
but they're like role playing as like villagers.
There's this guy called Old Peculiar who is like their, their spirit guy.
And it leads, and it's like, it's like they're playing D&D in Minecraft.
Like these other people are like building all this shit.
They're like building stuff in the game for Lewis and, and Simon to like find as they,
as they play through, through the game.
Yeah.
And like they, it seems like they don't necessarily know what it is that they're going to be like
seeing that episode, but like, I don't know, stuff is just being built for them to like
play through an experience in, in this Minecraft world.
It's like the coolest fucking conceit of a, of a series.
Yeah, it's pretty amazing.
It's pretty dope.
That exists.
It was documented for all to see.
All this fucking gay shit, this mining, this terrarium.
Devil May Cry 5.
The demo finally came out for PS4 and I was playing it nonstop for IM games and after IM games.
And man, what a great time.
Yeah.
Holy, holy.
Could it be better than Kingdom Hearts 3?
The greatest action RPG ever made?
Uh, by a landslide, my dude.
Oh, boy.
The combat's great and not floaty and, and, and I don't have to like summon like bumper
cars to do damage to things as well.
Yeah, but can you meet Woody?
Uh, yeah, idiot.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
But you can get Woody while you're having super fun.
Can you be best friends with Woody the whole time?
I'm not surprised.
It was fucking great.
Um, yeah, I'm really, I'm really excited about this game coming out.
Been waiting forever.
Didn't think it was going to be real.
It's real.
It's coming next month.
And holy shit.
It's just, it's everything I ever wanted in a video game.
It's great.
You play as Nero.
You just like three characters.
The demo had Nero.
You got the robot arms.
You can like punch people from far away and like there's tons of cool sword combos and
the boss fight was great and I beat him without getting hit and it was awesome and everybody
should watch the stream on IM Games because it was a fun, great time.
It was the happiest I've been in years.
Uh, yeah.
Tom enjoying a video game?
It was, it was a rare, it's a rare thing to happen on IM games.
So like everyone in the chat was just like, this is incredible.
Tom's happy.
What is going on?
And I was like, that is great.
I downloaded the demo, but obviously with Kingdom Hearts 3 stuff, I haven't had a chance to
play it yet, but I will get to it.
The interesting thing is like, because like now, now that the demo is out, I didn't, I
didn't want to like spoil too much, but like now that I've just got a taste, I'm just absorbing
all the content that's been like coming out like for previews of the game.
It's only like a month till it comes out or something, right?
Yeah.
So it's, I mean, what's to really just spoil anyways at this point, you know, it's not
like there's a story I give a shit about in the game.
Um, but there's this new character in this game called V and he just looks like Kylo Ren
and he's like a total, you know, edge lord.
But I was like looking, I was looking into his gameplay because I guess there's gameplay
trails and stuff for him out now and like the whole.
I'm just curious, who in the demo can you play as?
It's only Nero.
It's just the Nero demo.
They had it like games, comma, whatever.
Um, but yeah.
So V is like the interesting thing is he's totally different than any other devil may
cry like character because he doesn't do direct combat.
He does like, he summons guys.
He has like three familiars you can summon and they do the fighting.
Um, and I was kind of like weirded out about that.
He's a Pokemon trainer in DMC.
Yeah.
Exactly.
He's like a really edgy Pokemon trainer, essentially.
And I was watching the trailers and it was very weird.
The trailers and it was very like concerning because I'm assuming he's going to be like
a third of the game and he moves really slow and like everything's just happening far away
from you and he's like a glass cannon.
So you get hit too often with him.
He just dies because he's weak and shit.
And I was like, this looks like not like what I want out of devil may cry.
That sounds really scary.
It just reminded me of chaos legion.
Have you ever played chaos legion for PS2?
Oh, I have.
Yeah.
I don't know what it was, but I played a bit.
It's like, it's a game where you basically just summon a bunch of guys.
Like that's considered the game.
You're a summoner and they just fight for you and you kind of just hang back and like
watch them play.
Okay.
Which I think I remember seeing chaos legion in game and former magazine.
Yeah.
I mean, that's what I saw.
And then me and Digi played it at one point because you were considering doing it for I am
Games or both like this is boring.
So that's what I was worried about.
It's like as a third of my like game of the year just going to be chaos legion.
But no, I watched, I watched the gameplay demonstration.
And how it works is that by default you have two summons.
You have Griffin and you have shadow.
Shadows like this Panther guy.
It's actually like the, the weird shadow cats from Devil May Cry one.
Like one of them is his summon, which is fucking sick.
And then like Griffin's a reference to the boss Griffin from Devil May Cry one.
And so they replaced the gun and the sword button.
So Griffin is far range attacks and shadow is close range attacks and you control them
in real time all their combat.
While you're also controlling B and moving him around.
Imagine if it was Griffin from Berserk and shadow from Hedgehog.
Oh.
Well, now I hate the game because it's not that and not that cool.
Let's get the modding community in on this.
Imagine the bromance.
Dude, those guys, they have the same mentality and the same energy.
They'd get along swimming with me.
Oh, I think so.
Yeah.
Imagine, by the way, they'd meet as enemies, but they'd fight.
They'd be an even match and then they'd shake hands at the end.
Guys, Sonic, Shadow, Guts, Griffith.
Well, we'll never have that game until someone mods it on PC.
Just out of curiosity, who's the third summon thing?
So your devil trigger replacement is you summon Nightmare,
which is like this big Golem guy, which is also a boss from Devil May Cry one.
And eventually you can level up.
So he's just like an NPC guy who walks around and beats the shit out of everybody.
But you can eventually upgrade him so you can ride him and control him.
I do all this fucking crazy shit.
And so I guess the way the summons work is they can do damage to enemies,
but they can't kill them.
They just put them in a stun state and then you have to teleport it
and stab them with your cane, and that's how they die.
So it's like a risk-reward system.
In order to actually kill things, you have to get close,
but if you fuck it up, you can get hit.
You can die instantly because it's so weak.
So it's a really interesting mechanic system,
and it seems like there's a lot of complexity to it.
And so my fears were instantly assuaged.
I'm like, this looks great.
I'm totally ready for this.
Oh yeah, it sounds pretty fun.
Yeah.
I have one.
Guys, the Sonic and Shadow,
Guts, Griffith.
Which one's which?
My god, I can't tell apart.
They look the same.
Like Sonic, I don't know whether he would be Guts,
because Sonic's too...
I think Gryphon and Guts are both just Shadow.
I don't know, I feel like Sonic is the Child of Light,
the prophesied one who is the Antichrist,
who is, you know, Sonic is Griffith.
Whereas Shadow is more like Guts,
because they both live a truly punished existence
in the darkness and are trying to overthrow, you know,
the evil, light guy that is the other one.
I don't know.
That's the best I got.
I just want elaborate fan fiction retelling
of the story of Berserk, but with Shadow and his Guts.
Dr. Robotnik is definitely,
what's his name, Void?
Like the leader of the God Hand or whatever.
No, I'm thinking of the Skull Knight.
Skull Knight would be like Silver or something, I think.
Yeah.
Skull Knight, he's determined to track down the Iblis trigger.
Is Void like the short dwarf looking motherfucker?
No, that's one of the other ones.
The one I'm trying to think of is the one with the brain
outside his head.
Yeah, I remember him.
Who's the big, like, the main first big demon guy
that keeps coming back?
Oh, that's Zod. You're talking about Zod.
That's probably chaos from Sonic, you know?
He's Tails.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Is Zod just like a big minotaur, basically?
Yeah, basically.
No, he has wings, I think, as well.
He does have wings.
So he's Tails.
Tails would be Costco.
You're right.
When you're right, you're right.
I have one more thing I want to say about Jenny the Juvie.
And that is that to build what's called a slime hutch,
which is where you breed slimes and have them produce slime balls,
you need a rare mineral called iridium.
And I didn't have any until a meteor landed on my farm
and I farmed it for iridium and I got just enough
to build a slime hutch.
So this is destiny.
I don't think that ever happened in my fucking, in my game.
I thought it was a scripted event,
but it seems like it's random and I think I got lucky.
I mean, you can get iridium from later in the game,
like the more advanced mind, which I'm just getting at.
Could this be the influence of Endless War,
which is inspiring to shape the world?
Some say Endless War came from the skies above.
Others say it came from the ground below.
No one truly knows.
So your guess is as good as mine.
I can only speculate.
One quick thing about Devil May Cry.
First game, I understand classic, good game.
Second game, shit?
Is that the shit one?
I rented Devil May Cry 2 and I played as the girl
and it sucks.
I have the shit one then.
I have the second one on PS2.
Okay, but can we acknowledge the fact
that Dante looks the sexiest in Devil May Cry 2?
By far.
Hold on, let me take a look.
Just take a fucking look.
It's super fucking cool and it's very hot.
It's super dope, DMC2 Dante.
This goes in the show notes.
I was so fucking hyped for that game, seeing those images.
He's wearing like a vest over his trench coat.
He wears a vest over his coat with a big old collar.
It's the best he's ever looked.
He's very...
It's just like everyone's favorite outfit,
the coats from Organization XIII.
Which everyone agrees are a masterpiece of design.
Alright, here's my main problem.
I was looking at them because I was playing Kingdom Hearts 3
after that discussion last episode about the coats.
They are varied and the things I hate the most
are the flared arm things.
Maxxel has arms that are tight to his arm
and then he's got gloves and he just looks cool.
He is cool.
And then Vexxon has like really extremely long sleeves
that are flared outwards.
They look like they're stupid.
They look like that Kawaii thing of like two long sleeves
looking up right now.
Extremely, extremely long sleeves and the flared sleeves.
No, that's Lexius.
Vexxon's the ice guy from Chain of Memories, the scientist.
He's the replica man.
He's got like the punching dagger thing on his arm.
I think the problem...
Effectively yes, but it's a shield.
With the flared arm thing though, is that just a limitation of the PS2?
Because they're supposed to be baggy sleeves
but the PS2 can't do real time cloth deformation.
So they're just kind of flared out to make it kind of look like they're baggy
but it sucks and it looks like shit.
That's fair and I don't think in Kingdom Hearts 2 Final Mix
Vexxon had those like overly long sleeves.
I'm having trouble finding like a high res image of every member
so I can compare.
Here's Axl.
Axl is good. Axl is alright.
Axl looks dope.
But everyone else seems to be including Xemnas.
Axl's on his way to the Gay Rave.
Vexxon is on his way to Science Composite.
Yeah, he owns the leather.
All these other people, they're just sort of like hiding away from it.
That's a stupid guy.
His hair looks retarded. I hate that character design.
Look, we all know Vexxon is the ugliest sin.
I don't like him. He looks dumb.
His face is like weirdly skull-like and unflattering in general.
He's the ugliest one for sure.
I just don't understand how he has like this long hair
but it looks like he has long hair
but he like gelled it around his forehead to go up first
and then come down.
I think Lexius is the ugliest one.
I don't like his haircut.
He gels it.
Guys, guys.
But wait, I like Vexxon because his looks specifically like a robe.
He's like a scientist and his coat looks the most like a robe
as opposed to like a coat or a jacket.
I suppose that's fair.
I just don't like the flares.
But more importantly,
Which ones are sonics? Which ones are shadows?
They're basically all shadows.
Roxas is a sonic and the rest are all shadows.
That's fair. Yeah, that's fair.
You know what, no Larzine.
Larzine's gotta be a sonic.
She's so mean as fuck.
Does Larzine use light or lightning?
She's the lightning. She's a lightning one.
Or at Roxas, she's the light one.
You don't know, no, no, wait, Demix.
Demix plays his sitar and is a canonical radical dude.
He's gotta be a sonic too.
Demix for sure.
Larzine looks very strange in Kingdom Hearts 3.
You think so?
I mean, I just think the aesthetic, like the art design,
is just rather unflattering to every single character.
It may be just that it's unflattering in such high definition
because look at her boobies.
Look at how weirdly they go.
They do look weirdly squished and uncomfortable.
They look like pecs.
That is unfortunate.
Look how broad her shoulders are.
Right, it's the broad shoulders.
Because she has that V-shaped torso of a jacked dude.
That is not an attractive build that she has right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's despicable.
Yeah, yeah, her waist is really tiny,
but her shoulders are so wide.
Dude.
Her shoulder, she's got that tapered triangle shape.
And her arms, maybe it's just the robe,
but her arms look really thick.
It's not, though, because her arms are coming out from like,
it's not like she has like big shoulder pads or something.
Her arms are coming out from that area.
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
She just has disgustingly inhumanly broad shoulders
and I'm repulsed.
Okay, you're right guys, but let's get off this whole visual discussion
because this is not to the strength of our audio show here.
Okay, despite it being in the show notes.
Hey, on the subject of Kingdom Hearts 3,
I have beaten it, have beaten it, and that was cool.
And I'm going to be making a video about it shortly,
but I thought it'd be fun.
This is seeing people's reaction to Kingdom Hearts 3
as such a landmark release from a formerly great company
like Square Enix, or Square, I suppose, whatever,
Square Enix produced Kingdom Hearts 2 Final Mix,
so I guess it's the greatest company that ever lived.
But listen to my boy, Leffen.
I read this on my stream yesterday.
Leffen, who is basically the sixth god of melee,
he's the godslayer, whatever.
So this is like one of the big guys,
competitive Smash and whatnot.
Listen to...
Okay, so he played Kingdom Hearts 3, alright.
He has played none of the other games.
Just listen to his comment from February 8th,
on his experience of...
Wait, where was this comment?
On Twitter, this is on Twitter.
At TSM underscore Leffen.
Okay, there you go.
Alright, listen to this, here we go.
Kingdom Hearts 3 is an actual 3 out of 10 game.
I haven't played the prior games,
but honestly, I'm happy I didn't,
because waiting 13 years for a story and gameplay
this garbage would have fucking ended me.
Graphics, dialogue, combat, it's all shit.
Cut scenes and VA?
Shit.
Cost $70, LMFAO.
I mean, he's on point.
He's...
Okay, guys like you, Tom, I get it.
And like, Dunkey made a video that I have gone out of my way
to not watch, because I don't want to watch until I made my first video,
where Leffen says later, like,
well, Dunkey agrees with me.
So I'm gathering that like,
to people who have not played like every game in this,
I did play all of them, and even I don't like it.
In...
Well, whatever, I don't want to get into it too much here,
but it's just like, I certainly understand
why people find the story.
Well, here's the thing, and as someone who's played all the games
and has finished 3, maybe you'll agree with me,
I feel like this game is for the fans who are knee-deep in it,
and that's it.
Like, it doesn't seem...
It doesn't seem like the narrative is even like,
comprehensible, unless you're like a scholar like yourself,
and I think the gameplay is just...
I don't know.
I don't think the gameplay is good, but I think you can deal with it,
because like, you're just emotionally invested at that point,
and you want to slot through.
That's true, and the fact of the matter is,
while I know the lore, I am no longer emotionally invested.
You know what, I'm emotionally invested
with everything that happened up to Kingdom Hearts 2
and a little bit beyond.
But everything that happened beyond that,
Dream Drop Distance, the mobile game,
and a bunch of stuff after that, I just don't care about,
and it's totally boring and uninteresting.
I'm aware of what's happening,
but I have no emotional attachment.
I like Aqua a little bit, I like She-On a little bit,
of course like Roxas and those guys,
but beyond that, there's like...
Leffen's comment here makes 100% sense to me.
Even I would happily say,
the cutscenes are directed like dog shit.
You don't, and this is what babbles me the most,
no matter how bad your lore is,
no matter how convoluted or fucked up
the actual narrative has become,
at no point do you have to direct your cutscenes like garbage.
They did that in addition,
and I just don't know why they did that.
I guess because it's a baby game,
and they felt they needed to give us 5 seconds
in between character speaking,
so we could catch up with our retarded slow brains.
I don't know.
It's strange that it took so long
for this game to come out,
and they didn't anticipate that the fanbase
had also grown about the same amount of years
in that time span.
I was 15 when I played Kingdom Hearts 2
and fell in love with it at the first time,
and now I am 28,
and that is a big fucking difference.
You know what?
I know we were making this comparison for the lulls,
but seriously, the cutscenes in Kingdom Hearts 3
from what little I've seen
feel like something out of Sonic Adventure 1,
where it's just really stilted dialogue
and odd pauses.
I don't know if you're familiar enough with that game
to know what I'm talking about.
I mean, Kingdom Hearts 1 also had that,
and Kingdom Hearts 2.
But back in the day, that would have been more acceptable.
Absolutely true. Plus, it was a relative...
I mean, it wasn't an early PS2 game,
but it was the PS2 era.
We were all more accepting of those sorts of things,
and it's just, was this a stylistic choice
to keep the kind of pacing of the old games?
I mean, this is the thing that I give...
I want to criticize the game for.
There is a concerted effort in terms of gameplay.
They have absolutely sacrificed
responsiveness of controls
and tight gaminess,
something that I'm sure Devil May Cry 5,
hopefully, I haven't actually played it,
has not done.
Oh, it's cool.
Well, great.
But, like, here's just one example.
When you turn around...
I know I've talked about this before.
When you turn around in Kingdom Hearts 3,
Sora does a big whole, like, walk around
step, step, step animation.
It's not just an instant boom, character flipped,
facing the other direction.
And that function has actually made it very hard
to stand in particular places on ledges
to do some of the things I was trying to do
with, like, lucky emblem pictures and stuff.
And it's...
So all this sacrificing for realism,
and yet the cutscenes are just dog shit
in terms of, like, editing.
I don't know.
I could improve every cutscene in the game
if you just gave it to me to edit them down
to just the dialogue and cut out the space.
It's very weird.
I mean, I didn't get very far into it, obviously,
because, like, I was telling you, I think yesterday,
we were talking about how I want to play everything.
You should make a Kingdom Hearts story abridged.
You should just, like, make a shortened version
that is not...
The fan edit.
Yeah.
I mean, people...
Oh, you mean, like, take the actual cutscenes
and, like...
Yeah, like, splice it all together,
edit it to be more bearable.
That is not a bad idea.
You can probably get a lot of views from that.
And you know what?
Some people have done things where, like, there's this guy,
I forget his name,
someone has taken, like, every cutscene
in all of Kingdom Hearts
and, like, strung them together
in a, like, chronological sequence.
Yeah, to make, like, Kingdom Hearts the movie.
Is that like an autism test?
If you make it through that, like, you're certified autistic?
I mean, even I haven't made it through,
like, every single piece of, like, the un-chained key,
like, the mobile game stuff.
I'm up to date on everything that matters, but, like...
Is that the un-chained key or the un-chained key?
This is actually the un-chained key.
I thought so.
I thought it might be.
Yes, indeed.
They also call it un-chained cross, but whatever.
So, yeah, I mean, an abridged thing
would serve the world greatly.
I mean, you know, you got Barry Cramer with his videos
just to summarize the story,
but I mean, he doesn't talk about the mobile game,
at least not very much.
You know what? Whatever. Who cares?
That's all I want to say.
And you know what?
Despite everything I'm saying here to be critical,
I absolutely do not hate Kingdom Hearts 3
and did have a good time overall
and am excited to do the end-game content,
like, get the ultimate weapon and whatnot.
So, you know, it's not a, not a shit game or anything,
but I'm gonna get into my details in my Weagua,
hopefully coming up either before this comes out
or maybe a couple days after. We'll see.
We'll see.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, buddy.
Hey, you know, since this is, like, a gaming-themed episode,
I may as well, like, continue that.
Ben, you did a whole big gaming...
Yeah.
Very recently.
A huge gaming.
I was talking about, I was gonna say, like,
speaking of streaming before, but then we got off the topic.
Yeah, yesterday I did my 24-hour continuous stream
to celebrate hitting 1,000 followers
on twitch.tv slash saint comics.
How'd it go?
And Hippo, you showed up and raided me,
Nate, you showed up and raided me after a minor kerfuffle,
but it was fine.
I tried to raid someone called Ben Saint,
but apparently there's another Ben Saint.
I don't think there is a...
Wait, is there someone called Ben Saint?
Yeah, he brought me to a different page, I think,
when I did it.
Wait, really? Okay.
I think so.
Well, then when you raided, wouldn't it have, like,
okay, because you eventually did raid me
with a party of, like, 40 or something.
Yeah, yeah.
And so if you had raided someone else,
I would have thought that all your followers,
or all the people watching would have gone there
and you wouldn't have been able to raid anymore.
You know, I'm not an expert.
It was my first time ever raiding.
I think they have to, like, opt into the raid or something.
Oh, yeah.
Or maybe it's because they weren't...
Also, I'm creeped out that there's someone
called Ben Saint on twitch.
I don't like that.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm saint comics with an X.
Indeed.
But, yeah, that was cool.
It was really great.
It was really tired.
Okay, so I had decided to do a 24-hour maple story stream
for the meme because maple story is a horrible Korean grind fest.
And I was like, what's the worst game that I could play
for 24 hours?
I'll do that.
And so that, I know, I made it like 10 hours.
I made it like 10 hours of maple story.
And then the game crashed and I couldn't bear it anymore.
So I didn't start it up again.
I defined mercy given to you.
There was a guy in the stream, Zad, who...
Yeah, that was Zad.
Yeah, he came...
He had, like, thousands of hours logged in maple story.
And he showed up as one of his characters
and was showed up to the maps I was on
and cast spells to make more enemies spawn so I could grind faster.
Oh, that's nice.
It was pretty nice, yeah.
He also advised me.
Apparently one of the servers is for...
It makes it easier to level.
It's called the reboot server, I think, or something like that.
So I had some help.
But 10 hours in, I was like, I can't do it.
It was not a fun game to watch, be streamed.
Did you get to the class up at all?
Did you do any of that business?
I got to level 60, but I didn't get a class up.
I just got a new folder, or I just got a new page
of skills to start leveling.
Also, I played one of these new classes
that is not a class, it's just a character.
Okay, well, I'm not familiar with that at all.
Mine's name was Kadina or something,
and he was an urban chain warrior from some gang city,
which is pretty cool, I guess.
Back in the day, it was archer, warrior, thief.
Yeah.
I booted this up and I see you could be Kadina,
a street smart man warrior.
Oh, I hate that.
You could be iffy or whatever,
a fucking ice wizard man pair.
For vice.
Yeah.
And so I was like, boy, MapleStory sure has changed
in the 12 years since the last time I played it.
Yep.
Anyway, so I switched to Return of the Overdinn,
which my friend John got for me.
It was really cool.
I played the demo of it when it came out a couple years ago.
I played...
It was sick, and it played sick,
and I really liked the visual aesthetic.
I spent like 12 hours playing Overdinn.
I played the entire game.
I solved every character's fate I found.
I got the good ending.
I got 100% of it right in the...
Well, I went like slightly over 24 hours
because I just wanted to finish it and get the good ending.
And that was really fun.
It proved to be a way more interesting game to stream.
I thought anyway.
Like 10 hours into MapleStory, I was dying.
My brain was shutting off.
I was suffering.
And then I started Overdinn,
and Overdinn engaged my various brain lobes to a degree
that it was not as painful to continue.
Thank God.
Yeah.
I was thinking about how to do a 24-hour stream
with a single game and not kill yourself.
Like what sort of games could I play
that would work for that?
Because in the past, I did a stream of Hollow Knight
that just ended up going for 17 hours by accident.
And so that was a pretty...
I probably could have done Hollow Knight for 24 hours,
and it wouldn't have been too bad.
I was going to say any game with satisfying progression
that keeps rewarding you with new stuff to find and do
probably would be terrible.
Yeah.
So because I had done that 17-hour Hollow Knight stream,
I knew that 24 hours was doable and to be fine.
It was really fun.
And I gained a bunch more followers.
A bunch of people subscribed.
A lot of people donated because they were like,
damn, 24 hours, nice job.
Here's a tip.
And I was like, fuck, yeah.
All right, sick.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was an event.
Getting paid for the pay.
Oh, and A.J. Shoup wrote a song.
Oh, I wanted to play that.
It wasn't loading on my fucking phone before.
I tweeted it after the stream.
A.J. Shoup wrote a song that is just about how Ben St. has
got to 1,000 followers today.
And it's really good.
It's great.
He made the whole thing in like a couple hours
while the stream was going.
He was just like, I will be back.
I will start a song right now and come back
with a fully realized piece of music.
And he did.
What a legend.
Yeah.
You know, I looked at my follow account
and I somehow have more than 1,000 already.
And I don't know how because I get like,
20 viewers per stream when I stream.
I stream all the time though.
I don't know.
I mean, because the stream went on for so long,
I wasn't getting like my huge numbers.
I get, I'll get like 50 to 60 on a normal stream.
This time I was averaging like 40 ish or so
throughout the whole like 24 hours.
I really, I am very envious of you, Nate,
that you're getting that you were getting numbers
that are reaching the point where you could hit partner.
I'm not doing it.
I'm finally there.
I just, it's just, I don't stream enough to fucking
actually be a partner.
You've got to be getting like 75.
75 is the average number you want to hit.
And I'm like probably like 50 or something.
My, my, you know, even while I was doing the Pokemon thing,
like my numbers were not at a level that were above that.
But it was like the finale of the Pokemon thing
was a big event that a lot of people came out for.
And then ever since then it's been like,
I don't know if it, I'm curious if it's due
to the goodwill generated by how dope the finale was
or if it was just that people aren't like,
they're a glad we're not doing Pokemon anymore.
So they're actually willing to watch.
I do not know which it is.
In any case, I'm definitely going to do another fucking
Nuzlocke at some point.
So get ready, people.
Heart gold.
It's coming.
One of these days.
The best game ever made of Pokemon.
Oh my God.
Yeah, hippo.
You got the, you got almost 1300 and I didn't realize.
Yeah, I don't even, I don't even know how.
I guess maybe from the couple times I mentioned it
on Hippocrite when it was like the Heroes of Might
and Magic streams and I did a couple of those.
That's possible.
Maybe, yeah.
Hey, do you guys want to hear about my tale of epic agony
and pain that I experienced the other day?
Yeah.
It was pretty dope.
Okay, so there's, this is, this is a,
there's a hilarious ending to this, but okay.
So, so on like Friday morning at like 5 a.m.
I wake up with a horrible pain in my gut
because the previous night on Thursday,
I had done like a seven or eight hour gauntlet
finishing Kingdom Hearts 3,
getting all the way from like the last world
being that to all the end game stuff,
which does take an eternity.
So I finally beat the game at the end
and while I was doing my epic gamer sesh,
I thought I'd be a really healthy boy.
So I had a gigantic bag of carrots in front of me.
So I was just eating those, like little baby carrots,
but there were so many and I ate the entire bag
over the course of several hours.
Uh-oh.
Um, so I did that and there's,
they're very fibrous, these carrots, don't you know?
But they, they go down real smooth.
So I just chowed down.
Um, so, so,
Wait, these raw carrots?
These were, yeah, raw baby carrots.
One, I hate carrots.
I hate raw carrots.
I like them.
What can I say?
I like them like cooked in a soup maybe.
Like, but, but like eating them raw,
like my least favorite vegetable.
Fair enough.
I don't know.
I like it way more than something like,
I actually kind of like most vegetables.
I don't like,
I do like a lot of vegetables.
Carrots aren't one of them.
Well, okay, fair enough.
Anyway.
They're my, they're my, they're my kryptonite.
Fair enough.
So I, uh, uh, wake up the next morning at like 5 a.m.
Pain, horrible, sucks, try to shit, can't.
I'm like, okay, whatever, go back to sleep.
Uh, and it's, it's a, it's a pressure, you know,
a lower gut pressure is building in it.
Doesn't fiber like make you shit better?
Okay.
What I think more fiber in your diet,
like gives you more poop,
which is good for moving things through your digestive system
and just generally is good for you.
It's literally bulk that you can't digest
and just gives you more to shit.
And that's like good for you as I understand it.
Yeah.
But when you, I think when you just eat,
when I ate,
Exactly.
But, but it is insoluble.
And I think I just ate so much so fast
that it just created a plug that just stuck up my guts
and nothing was moving.
I mean, I couldn't fart.
I couldn't shit.
I was, I was trying to belch to get things to come up the other way.
It was not happening.
I don't know.
I probably should have tried to puke a little more,
but okay, we're just getting started here.
Sounds like a fate worse than death.
Well, if it's in your guts already,
then puking won't do anything, right?
Do you do the same thing?
That's what I mean, maybe.
When you're like stuffed up,
do you do the same thing where you're like,
you can feel it in your gut
and you sort of like squish it
like as hard as you can with your hands
and like punch it?
Yes.
I did try to do that at first.
Punch it.
I mean, I literally did that
and I thought that I should maybe try to go for a run
to like shake it loose,
which I was too much of a pussy.
I let the pain beat me down
and I didn't go do that.
I probably would have been better off if I did,
because okay, here's what happened.
So I wake up, I'm in pain.
I kind of, you know, like I'm supposed to be at work.
I'm like, guys, I'm in a lot of pain.
I'm gonna come back later.
So I'm out.
I feel a little better as the day goes on
and here's where I make a tragic mistake.
So during like the morning meeting at work or whatever,
like I, for some reason,
I come to the conclusion,
despite knowing about this whole carrot thing
and feeling in horrible pain all morning,
it has started to abate.
So I say to Michelle, Michelle, I've got it.
I think what this might just be is,
so carrots aren't super satisfying.
I think these are just hunger pains.
So what I need to do
is just eat tons of food really fast
and that will cure this pain.
Sometimes you don't know what a feeling is.
That's true.
It's absolutely true.
And I incorrectly deduced
that this was actually secret hunger pains.
So we order, I got a gigantic, fully loaded,
tuna sub from Subway.
And like, cause I am quite hungry.
So I down that thing in like 30 seconds
and all of a sudden the pressure is back on
worse than it was by a significant amount before.
And from then on, it's something like a 12 hour gauntlet
of me writhing on the ground, like in my bed,
just attempting to shake my ass loose.
But nothing is happening.
Nothing is budging.
Nothing is moving in any way.
And I'm, Michelle is in the other room
enjoying the nice snowy day.
Well, I'm writhing.
She's going, ah!
Ah!
I'm literally doing this the entire day.
So at around, it's at 10 p.m.
after all the urgent care centers have closed.
So all that's left is the ER.
And at this point, I have hit my breaking point.
I am getting the shakes.
I'm getting the sweats.
And I'm not sure how much longer I can last.
Just enduring this.
I was hoping it would just go away.
But I'm like, Michelle, I need to go to the hospital.
Let's go.
I'm going to die.
I am.
I mean, the only, nothing had felt like actual death.
It was just pain of a, I would say it was like
a five or six out of 10.
But for an entire day, I just was like,
my HP bar has to be low at this point.
And I'm running low on few.
I don't have any potions.
So we get to the ER.
And so we're there.
They do, they signed me in to do my blood work.
I'm there for a total of five hours before the doctor
actually sees me at like 2 a.m.
or whatever.
It was, I mean, they said it was particularly bad day.
It's always forever.
I mean, that's why you go to urgent care.
Don't go to the ER people.
Just unless it's a true emergency,
then they will prioritize you.
The life hack is you have to call an ambulance
because then they'll rush you in immediately.
But that cost so much more money.
Don't you have to pay for that?
Yeah.
Sometimes sacrifices have to be made.
How much five hours would do?
I mean, that's a good question.
I lost my entire day.
But so the point is, this is the thing.
When I get to the hospital, I'm in the worst pain of all.
It hasn't abated at all.
It's sharp, it's constant.
The pressure, I feel like I'm going to blow
and I'm worried that my intestines will rupture
and just nothing's moving.
Jesus Christ.
Yes.
And so it was during that five-hour period
about four hours into it,
as I've gone in, they took my blood,
they fucking, I don't know, they took my name
and they asked me a bunch of questions and shit.
As I'm finally getting close to seeing the doctor,
I go to the bathroom and praise God almighty.
There is some movement.
I do a bit of a shit
and there is some gaseous release.
So it didn't have anything.
They didn't do anything for you at the hospital.
They literally did nothing.
No.
Things took so long that nothing happened.
That the problem just resolved itself
while you were waiting.
It resolved itself.
Now, I haven't gotten any kind of like bill yet.
I mean, I have insurance.
So like, it's probably going to be something, I imagine.
But like, I don't know.
I was happy to be there just to feel like,
okay, no, if I collapse here,
I will not die.
So that's good.
Yeah, they'll give me emergency surgery
if needed.
Indeed, if needed, if necessary.
But it did not help.
A lot of parent out of your guts.
Indeed, exactly.
But I mean, so by the time I finally saw the doctor,
the pressure was down from like,
I don't know, like 90% intolerable
just because it's going on so long.
That was like 10%.
And it was just feeling way fucking better.
And so whatever.
They gave me like a medicine to like help with like,
fucking a laxative or whatever.
Just to help in general.
But by this point,
the problem had basically fixed itself.
I go home and I'm feeling fine.
Things are okay.
But yesterday.
This is the amazing part.
I message Digi.
And we do the Shield Hero podcast.
And Digi is just like,
so Nate, I heard you were sick.
Like what happened?
And I tell him that whole story.
And he's like, dude,
that exact same thing happened to me
like one month ago or whatever.
And I wrote a song about it.
And it's here linked in the show notes.
Who was this?
Digi.
So MLP wrote a song about the exact same experience
that he experienced.
It's called Boiling Guts.
Go listen to it.
It's the banger of the century.
It completely encapsulates artistically
the experience that I went through
and Digi apparently did as well.
Just listen to that.
10 pound brick in my colon.
Man, imagine when it's going to drop,
going to part the ocean.
But oh shit.
There's no shit coming out.
Rub this tummy down.
Squeeze me out like some cheese whiz.
Feeling like a geek kid sitting here an hour.
Going both before and after the shower.
Fist clenched going Super Saiyan trying to power.
And it just goes on.
It just goes on.
This is everything that I felt.
Beautiful.
It was incredible.
Oh, and that reminds me.
There was one other facet.
I almost forgot about this hospital experience,
which was while we were there,
there was a family with a bunch of young kids.
They were just like listening to loud,
like YouTube auto-recommended playlist music.
And that was fine.
But then, all of a sudden,
one song, one fateful song comes on.
It's, I am not afraid of puppeteers.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
It just comes up like,
comes on like the radio?
Well, they're playing on their iPad loudly.
Like for all to hear, no shame.
There's no attempt to, you know,
not annoy everybody else.
And then they finally get to that triumphant chorus
and it keeps going,
discard!
I'm howling at the moon,
I'm sleeping in the middle of a Sunday afternoon.
They did it.
Was it before or after?
This is pre or post-shit.
This was while I was in my most intense agony.
So was this like a fever dream?
You were like afraid that you were actually
the hallucination?
At like 1 a.m. at night.
I'm writhing.
I think he hallucinated.
This sounds like a hallucination.
This doesn't seem real.
It was sympathy hallucinations.
Oh my God.
And so that's the complete saga.
I'm fine now.
Thanks for asking.
You should have wrapped T-Bab.
They obviously were bronies.
You should be like,
if you guys are going to watch T-Bab,
it's good.
Subscribe to T-Bab, guys!
I could imagine in your head you'd be like,
oh yeah, I'm going to howl at the moon
just for five minutes.
I've been howling at the moon all night.
So there you go.
It was interesting.
It was probably the worst pain I felt
all day in my life.
Oh, and I almost forgot.
On the way in, as I'm stumbling in,
like writhing in agony,
Michelle's like helping me get inside.
There's just like some lady who's just like,
excuse me, y'all, can y'all spare some change?
Like, I got to get the bus in a couple of minutes.
I got to get a taxi to get home.
Like, to me, as I'm dying of agony,
stumbling into this ER at like,
I guess at that point it was like 11 p.m. or something.
Needless to say, did not.
Definitely a good place to find really sympathetic songs
going into the hospital with medical problems.
Indeed, indeed.
Okay, there you go.
There's the complete saga.
It was fun.
It was legendary.
It was pretty good.
Yeah, good time.
How would you rate the experience?
I had a great time.
It was, you know, pretty fun.
I mean, it was better than, I don't know,
being, I don't know,
something worse, I guess.
Yeah, better than being gay.
They got that gay gene out of me.
The surgery was a success, everybody.
I could get last.
Oh, fuck.
Hot dog.
Well, what's next on the docket?
I'm out.
We got some hot boys here.
I want to talk about the greatest item I've purchased
in a long time, which is my new iPad.
Holy fuck.
Yeah.
I bought this on the recommendation of my sister,
who is a professional user experience designer.
She's real.
She makes like real money, has like real things.
Great.
Dope.
So she's like, we meet up sometimes at Starbucks
because like the traffic to get back to where she like...
To do a quick Q&A at Starbucks.
Yeah, a quick Q&A.
And we'll just hang out.
And she's like, you got to check out this iPad.
I just got it recently and it's like changed my life.
I'm like, really?
And she got the base like cheap iPad and the Apple Pencil.
She's like, it's so much better to draw on than anything.
And I'm like, that's fucking bullshit, no way.
And I tried it and it was like legitimately great.
And I was like, all right, all right, this is pretty cool.
Because I was thinking about trying to get back into drawing
just to like post stuff on Twitter and shit in between.
Like working on games and 3D.
Wasn't the plan to like promote Izumi by doing a bunch of art
for it for like a month there?
Yeah.
And I have like, you know, my little tablet I have left
from like all the stuff I had from Rebel Pixels.
And it's just not that great.
It's fine to draw in, but it's not great, you know?
It's not like a Waycom Sintique or anything.
So I was like, well, this seems cool.
I'll give it a shot.
And I bought it and it legitimately is like the best drawing device
I've ever used.
Like, because like the weird thing is that, I mean, Ben,
you and Gib, you've used Waycom device before.
You know how they have like the hover.
So like you're over the screen or you're over the tablet
and like it shows the cursor and you can hover the pen around.
This doesn't have hover.
So I thought that'd be really weird to know where I placed the pen
to like close lines and stuff, but you don't need it.
It's so accurate.
It just feels like using an actual pencil.
It's incredible.
Wow.
There's this app called Procreate, which is like apparently,
despite having a terrible name that sounds like, you know, reproduction,
like it's replaced like Waycom Sintique and like in like professional artists.
Like it's like the number one thing that like professionals use to draw
now apparently.
And so I'm using it and it's the stabilizer built in is incredible.
The brush engine is amazing.
The accuracy is supreme.
And it's like, I got this whole setup like the pencil,
the iPad with 128 gigs of storage, a cover and a keyboard for like 400 bucks.
And it blows away anything I've ever used before.
It's like the best drawing device in the world except for probably
the more expensive iPads.
It costs like four times as much, but like it's insanely good.
How big is the screen?
The screen is 10 inches.
So this is a very small one, but I'm finding that it's for me, it's fine.
I have no problem with the size because here's the interesting thing.
Before I've never like used like rotating the canvas or anything
because like usually to do that in Photoshop or Clip Studio is like,
you have to drag a slider and it's really annoying.
And none of the pen displays I've ever used have multi-touch because it's like
really expensive because it's been like three grand on a Sintique for that.
Since this has multi-touch, it's super easy to just zoom in,
rotate the canvas really easy and always have your pencil like,
like the stroke angle being right in aligned with your wrist because it's so easy to do.
So I'm rotating my canvas now constantly.
I mean, I rotate my canvas constantly.
I've never done that before because it was just too much of a hassle.
So like this is so fucking transformative.
Like the quality and the ease of use and the multi-touch, I'm a changed man.
This has changed my life and I'm going to evangelize it.
Everybody should get an iPad to draw on.
It's better than anything.
I mean, I've pretty much fully transitioned.
I don't eat my Wacom bamboo, which I held.
I had the Sintique that Arthramus gave me for like a year and I hardly used it
because I was just accustomed to my Wacom bamboo, $50 piece of shit,
like six inch like surface area.
But it finally, it was like broke.
Like it kept like disconnecting and reconnecting like the connector was spotty
and like I couldn't keep using it.
So I pretty much completely transitioned to the Sintique and it's been painless
and I feel dumb that I didn't do it earlier.
Like it's not that it does anything that I couldn't do before, but like, I don't know.
I found that when I made the leap and I finally just like took the Sintique
and put it like front and center on my desk, like this is what I use now.
Like this is my main monitor.
I found that it was like easier to draw.
The creature conference are just like, you don't really expect them to be that much better
until you kind of get used to it.
And then going back, you're just like, ugh, ugh.
The one thing, psychologically having my Wacom as my main monitor
just like made me like, just like incline me to draw more readily, you know?
Yeah, definitely.
Good stuff.
I draw way more now because it's so easy to just like,
because like there's no booting up an app or like booting up the computer or anything.
I just like open the cover.
It's on.
You use touch ID to log in the apps right there and I just go and it feels great and I love it.
It's amazing and everybody should buy it.
I'm going to praise it from the rooftops.
It's totally worth it.
I'll think about it.
How much was it?
Well, I got this one.
The thing is like I was kind of dumb because I know they're going to replace this model
that I bought with a new one in like two months,
but that does mean it's like on sale everywhere right now.
So I got it for $100 off, brand new.
So it was $300 for the iPad, the pencil I got for 70.
And then I just also got a cover to protect the screen,
but altogether it was like less than 400 bucks.
And you could get it cheaper because I got the 128 gig model,
which I didn't even really need and get a 32 gig one for even cheaper.
So like $270 gets you the iPad, the pencil you need.
That's another like 50 to 70 if you get it online and you're good to go.
It's totally worth it.
I have my mom's old iPad and I've been trying,
I've been thinking like trying to use it for, you know, for my own purposes,
but it's sort of like locked into her account.
I don't know how to like factory reset it.
But if I could figure out how to do that, I could buy the pencil maybe.
I don't know, this is a pretty old iPad.
Yeah, the problem is you have to get either the sixth generation,
like the current iPad, the base iPad or the iPad Pro.
Those are the only ones that work with the pencil.
The older ones don't, which sucks because I had an older iPad as well.
Because I had an iPad mini back in like 2013.
I got the one with LTE to replace my phone because I just,
my phone broke and I wanted an iPad anyway.
So I just like got an app that let you make phone calls and just use that for everything.
So I was like this weirdo with this big iPad walking around and that was my phone.
I have a little headset if I need to talk to people.
Man, some people do that.
It's the most awkward thing to see.
I mean, I never, I made phone calls like even then, like never.
So I was just texting and it was fine.
It's a bigger screen to have more text on the screen.
And I was using that for everything until Verizon like blocked my phone app
because they're like, you need to buy a phone plant to use this.
I'm like, yeah.
So that was the end of that.
But I was even using it for art back then, but there was no Apple pencil.
So the support was like kind of shitty and you kind of just like finger paint on it.
It was weird, which was not great.
So that's why like when the Apple pencil and shit came out and like,
I don't know, I've tried this whole iPad drawing thing before.
I'm not convinced, but then I'm a believer now.
I'm on it hardcore. Everybody should do it.
It's great.
Whoo.
I'm convinced.
If only I had any knowledge of drawing whatsoever.
It's never too late to start.
Here's what you need to know about drawing.
Drawing is the act of making a mark on the world.
Drawing in the dirt, you're an artist.
What if I draw, you know, in video footage with editing?
No, it's the one thing that doesn't count.
If you draw your mouse across the screen, that's art.
If you draw the curtains, you're moving the curtains, you're creating light.
You're an artist.
I'm going to draw my gun and fucking blow your face off.
That's fair.
Thanks, Tom. Go to Quick Draw, the new channel, the new drawing channel for art people.
I didn't even know about Quick Draw. No one told me about it.
Yeah, no one told me either.
You've been away. You've been like not paying attention.
We've been adding people. I guess I suck.
No, you're in. Just join it and you'll be in.
You'll be a Quick Drawer.
I think, hopefully, I have no idea actually.
No, not that. Hopefully, Munchie will have made the first episode by the time this is out.
I don't actually know.
I just want to watch it because I still don't even know what the conceit is.
It's basically the draw cast.
It's the draw cast, but it's on the same channel.
We're going to do other kinds of draw challenges, but baseline, the draw cast is moved to the draw.
This reminded me. One of my favorite things about the iPad in Procreate, which is cool,
is that with Procreate, it automatically records everything you do and saves it as a video file.
You can do speed draws automatically. You don't have to think about doing it, just does it by itself.
That's cool.
I used to make speed draws and it was annoying.
It was just really annoying setting up OBS to record my screen.
That's why I never did it either, but now it just does it.
You can look at it at any time.
You can scrub through it and see how things are going.
At any point, you just export it and then you can use it for anything.
It's great.
That's cool. That's very cool.
We'll do it.
Anybody want to get to the fucking voicemails?
Is there anything else we should talk about?
I'm out. That was my one thing I wanted to evangelize.
Very good.
I guess I'm out. My 24-hour stream blew everything else out of my brain.
Understandable.
There's nothing else left at the end.
The only thing that I could mention is this silly project that I started.
You may remember a long time ago on the Give and Take channel, you've got Chainmail,
where I show the Chainmail bodice torso thing made entirely out of paper clips.
I wear it and it's really cool, made out of at least 2,000 paper clips.
Epic.
What are my favorites?
Have you been wearing it now?
Yes, every day.
I always thought I should make some plate mail armor,
some plate armor, and I was gathering cardboard for a while there, months and months and months ago.
Gathering cardboard, but it was always too thick or too inconsistent and it was hard to cut.
I was like, this is terrible. This is never going to work.
But then I had the big brain.
The big brain thought.
Yeah.
Plate armor, paper plates.
Yeah. Good.
I have made, I will take a picture and I will show you.
I have made the gauntlet, one of the gauntlets out of paper plates and paper fasteners.
I wanted to start with the gauntlet because that's probably the hardest part.
I don't have enough paper fasteners to finish it, but I have plenty of paper plates and it looks and feels incredible.
It's basically the way to make a gauntlet, I have learned through using hobbyists and things like making forums about all this sort of stuff,
is that you need to have a glove and then you basically staple the pieces on in a certain order from the tip of the finger down so that it curls around.
My mom and I made a Vincent Valentine cosplay way back in the day when Mr. DeCons.
I made a glove with something like that, but yeah, it was cool.
I'm going to take a picture of it right now and I'm going to send it to you.
Sick.
I am excited. There better get a video as legendary as You've Got Chainmail associated with this incredible creative vision
because I have long remembered back. I've watched it several times, You've Got Chainmail.
It's one of the premier give and take content ever produced.
I can't wait to have a full suit of armor made out of everyday items and you just cosplay like the everyday Dark Soul guy.
You just go around and just slay random items throughout the world.
When I worked at Astro Camp, we would have staff events, just like fun shit that we did with each other on weekends and stuff.
People would sign up to schedule an event that people would go to.
One weekend, it was like a water balloon fight, but it was like water balloon slash larping.
There were rules. You had to like...
Oh, I'm seeing the gauntlet. That's really funny. That's really cool looking.
It looks like a Kingsguard, like a Kingsguard white plate.
I'm going to be a white knight. I was thinking of potentially painting all the plates, but then I wouldn't know.
White body.
And now you can eat sloppy hamburgers and just drip it all over yourself.
It doesn't matter because you shielded.
Yeah, it's a project that will be like many months in the making if I ever get round to buying enough of the materials.
But really cool, I think. I really like this.
Excellent.
But in this water balloon thing, you had to pick a class. You could be a major warrior.
If you were a mage, you had more water balloons to throw, but if you were a warrior, you could take more hits with a water balloon before you were dead.
And you were allowed to make a shield that could block a hit.
It had to be a certain size and stuff, and you could only have one.
And basically it was like, if you got wet from the water balloon, it counted as a hit, but if you blocked the water and you didn't get wet from it, then you were safe.
And it was like an all day run around and try and form teams and try and ambush people. It was very fun.
The girls are going to have a major disadvantage against me seeing my manly performance because they were all going to get wet.
No, I'm saying girls.
I am a heterosexual. Please believe me.
Yeah, the operation was a success.
Alright, well that's dope as hell.
Let's go fucking listen to some voicemails, I guess.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, of course, everyone, SpeakPipe.
What's the URL again? I always fucking forget.
I believe it's pzpvoicemail.
Yeah, speakpipe.com slash pzpvoicemails, I think. Link in the description either way.
Let me see, first one here is from Rizzy the Weeb.
Rizzy the Weeb and Commence.
Hi, so this is just a bit of advice to all the young PCP fans out there wanting to make their own YouTube channels.
Don't.
I started watching the PCP when I was 12 and before it I was a happy, cute, young girl with dreams.
And then I started making YouTube videos and now I'm gay.
What did you say?
Just like digital and don't even get me started on my friends.
They make this shitty YouTube lore that's fired by Jesse because even though they did watch it,
no one listened to the message of the horsey Ustaga one year later because they're all stupid
and it ruined their lives and I've disowned them all.
So please don't be like us and have a nice day for once.
Dude epic.
Cutting right to the heart of the matter.
Yeah, it used to be 12, now it's a strong 13.
I had no idea the PCP...
I had my whole life ahead of me back then.
I had no idea the PCP fanbase was so young.
Well, they're not all, but some of them are.
No, all of them are, they're all little baby moms.
That's fair, it's fair.
And that's why we had to start RFCK to round up all the child soldiers and get them and put guns in their hands.
The way God enchanted.
Or nunchucks, or brass uncles, or whatever.
Would you believe Paradox Crocs is only 11?
Incredible.
Shocking.
Well, there it is, the voice of the people.
Don't do YouTube, it's a mistake.
Alright, next one, voicemail from the talent man.
The talent man.
Let's see how he's talented.
Hey guys, I'm Hippocrite.
And you know, and you know, and you know, and you know, and you know.
Hey guys, I'm best guy, Hippocrite.
I love copy the listen.
Do it, wish me happy.
Hey guys, I'm the boo.
Creep, creep, creep, creep.
And now I'm just, I'm funny.
Wow.
You know, I was doubtful.
That is so, that is so something he'd say.
You know, you know when you're right, you're, you know, you're right.
Because I do say you know a lot.
You know, yeah.
But you know, it's all fine, and it's all good, and it's all part of my mystique.
He really is the talent man ever.
Alright, let's just move on.
Next one, normal quick draw, saloon advertisement is the name of this one.
So let's, let's see what's on deck.
Oh.
18 naked cowboys in the showers, a quick draw saloon.
Big hearts, robbing styluses, waiting to be sucked.
18 naked cowboys, waiting to be colored in.
Cowboys in the showers, a quick saloon on their knees, waiting to draw cowboys cracks.
Quick draw saloon.
Oh God.
That's it.
Put it in the show notes, put it in the show notes, a link to join the quick draw saloon discord.
Okay, we got, please do so.
Good, good.
This is the advertisement they needed.
This will send them flooding, quick draw saloon.
Okay, next one.
This is from YouTube recommendations God, that just what we need, okay.
I am the YouTube recommendations God.
I subscribe to no one, and exclusively use YouTube recommendations, which brings me what I watch without failure.
Which is the procrastinator's podcast.
Yeah.
Every Friday, as soon as it releases, and I enter YouTube, it brings it to me because YouTube is my bitch.
And I have made it my bitch.
And I don't subscribe to you, or pay your stupid God Sam patriarchs.
You're just missing out.
Okay, there you go.
He just disappeared into the ether.
A message of hope.
Maybe YouTube isn't so broken after all, there's hope from God himself.
I would like to know if anybody was just like, oh, I'm just on YouTube recommended.
Oh, what's this, the procrastinators podcast, PCP, I like drugs.
Like, did anybody find us through that?
God, I hope so.
We've got a large drug using demographic, I have no doubt.
The only drugs our viewers take is there a hormone replacement therapy.
That's what I mean.
When you're right, you're right, Ben.
Alright, next one.
This is from I'm Just Being Chad.
So, get to it.
Alright, I'm Just Being Cool Purple Hoodie from the Teespring officially.
And here's what I'm doing.
I got that on, and imagine I got a fanny pack.
Please do.
This sounds like a minimized 50% munchie.
The music songs are the good ones, and I'm jamming out in the hallways.
Hardcore, fucking real shit.
And it reminds me I'm the cool kid now, except still no GF,
but I don't even fucking care, because it's so fun to just be cool.
And it's the best thing ever.
Thanks for liberating me.
Oh, Just Being Cool!
There he goes.
Oh, there he goes. Mr. Weezerman.
Okay, good. Good.
I think we've heard enough.
I like to imagine that this boy has just got a grand piano.
It sounds like a normal piano, but it could be a big grand piano that was super polished.
And this is the richest boy in America he's wearing in.
He's wearing his I'm Just Being Cool hoodie in the fucking Carnegie Hall opera house or whatever.
No, this is a big anime fan, a fan of anime podcasts, The Procrastiners Podcast,
of Baron Trump calling in from Trump Tower to give us the stuff we need.
That's why he's a chat.
Thinking about him just tuning out the world to his tunes, wearing his purple eye,
it kind of sounds like the worst guy ever, a little bit.
It kind of sounds like there's maybe some resemblance.
No, the worst guy ever has no abilities, such as piano playing, speech without impediment.
The idea of being cool, he would never call himself Chad.
That is a patriarchal term that I'm certain he would never use to describe himself.
So we can roll that one out for sure.
But good news, new voicemail, it's time to shit on the Pizza Party podcast.
Yes, finally!
Everyone's favorite segment.
Let's play it. We need to make this a regular segment.
I want to hear that every episode, and we all bring a list of grievances.
No, let's seriously do this.
I know nothing about them.
Let's start right now.
I will bring a list of grievances starting this week against the Pizza Party podcast.
Okay, grievance number one, pizza's not keto.
Number two, movies don't like them.
Number three, parties.
I have no affiliation with any political parties.
What is this political hackery, guys?
Cut it out.
Number four, never listen to the podcast.
Where is it, guys? The end.
I'm convinced, man.
We'll be waiting for your diss track next week.
Where's the Pizza Party podcast?
That's all I'm saying.
I'm just waiting. Where's the podcast, guys?
Where the hell is it?
Double PCP member.
Okay, let's go.
Next one, Steven Universe Gay.
Commence.
Steven Universe, more like gay.
Steven Universe is gay.
What does everybody have a piano?
What does everybody have a piano this time?
Is this the same guy?
No, that's a different guy, I think.
Okay, there he goes.
Maybe it is the same guy.
There's no way for me to tell.
Good.
There he goes.
He's really going for it.
He's going for it.
I played this as an apology
to everyone who's bored of Steven Universe topics.
So am I.
No more of that.
And I'm stronger than you.
I didn't even give him a fair shake.
Good job playing the piano, sir.
It's just that it happened to come right after another one
who also did, so you've been upstaged.
It was good. That was a really good piano.
It was good, yeah.
It's true.
I like the warbliness of it.
Next one is Thu for you.
Could this be the return of our hero, Jeff?
Let's find out.
This voicemail is brought to you by
bonus episode number 22, Dreams Cast,
in which Nate mentioned an octopus story,
which he failed to recount,
because apparently he said it many times.
I want to hear Nate's octopus story.
Tell me about the octopuses.
This has been from the Dreams Cast,
making you shit the bed every single time.
First of all, I wish I could have shit the bed
the other night, but beyond that,
if you want to hear the full context here, people,
the low, low price of $5 on patreon.com
slash the procrastinators per episode,
get in there, and you're going to want to hear that.
But in brief, I had a dream once that was me
becoming a viral internet sensation
because I went up to a takoyaki stand
and demanded, quote, unquote, octopus balls,
which is, I suppose, one to describe takoyaki
as they are little balls of dough with octopus inside them.
And someone captured this on film,
and this became a viral sensation,
Nate and his octopus balls, and that was the dream.
Wasn't it in the clip, weren't you yelling,
like, I want my goddamn octopus balls?
That sounds right. That sounds right.
I think that's what you said when you told me about it.
Because I know I've talked about it before.
So yeah, and it was that.
And everyone thought that was so fucking funny,
like so random, dude.
Like, who would even say that?
Oh, my God.
And this dream did become a DBZ battle
shortly afterward.
That was pretty cool as I flew through the skies.
With who?
Well, I don't know who I was fighting,
but I was presumably using my newfound internet fame
to fuel my flight and my strikes.
That's all I remember.
Okay.
I think that was it.
Okay, anyway, so there's the story.
Moving on.
Next one is from Art Director 69.
Oh, I typed the right command here.
And go.
Hey, what's up, Art Director 69 here with a question
about self-expression.
How do you feel about artists being vulnerable
and emotional in their work?
Don't do it.
It's prevalence in music,
but I'm talking more specifically about games,
comics, and film.
Do you think you will ever bleed onto a page?
I fucking bleed onto the page every day of my life.
Let's wait.
My fucking wrists.
Oh, yeah, that too.
What do you think?
I guess I'm trying to think about,
like, being emotionally vulnerable in the art.
Like, you write a book and it's like a thing
that's very close to your heart and then somebody says,
this book sucks and you get really hurt
because that's you, basically.
Yeah, that's one way.
Like, is that sort of like a vulnerability
that he's talking about?
Okay, with, yeah, go on, go on.
It depends on how much you want to express that.
Yeah.
But like, in any art, if you express yourself,
and people just hate it, then, I don't know.
You're gonna feel sad if you care about something
that you make and people really don't like it.
Yeah, that's definitely true.
But you wanted to make it in the first place.
It's just a matter of degrees, right?
Like, everybody's expecting, you know,
putting themselves into their art
because that's just the nature of what it is.
It's just depending on how direct
or how deep you want to go into it.
When I think about being emotionally vulnerable
through your art, I think of something like,
you know, like you basically put yourself
into the story, right?
You have like a character, have like an emotional conflict
that is basically like it's yours, right?
Like you write a story about how your wife left you
because you really like suck and dick.
And then you put that in the story
and you make that the main character's conflict
and you make it relatable.
There are like degrees of separation,
because like in music, he said as the prime example,
a lot of people will sing in the first person
and be like, blah, blah, blah, she left me,
I was really sad, et cetera, et cetera.
So, and like if you write a story,
there's, you can always hide behind a veil.
I mean, even with music, a lot of people say like that,
you know, they amp up the emotions being portrayed
in the songs and the lyrics and whatnot.
I mean, obviously they are.
Remember that book, How Not to Write a Novel?
Of course, yes.
Okay, I remember there's one example
of like badly written like putting like obviously
the main character is the author.
And it's like, it's like the passage is like,
he stared into his beer, you know, you know, morose.
You know, he had tried to deny it for so long.
He had thought he could fix the problem.
He had tried everything, but the time had come.
He had to face the harsh reality of the situation.
I was impotent.
That's, okay, that's pretty good.
I guess that would give it away.
That would.
Yeah.
But that's what I, that's what I think of when I think of like,
you know, being, making yourself emotionally vulnerable
through your art.
I mean, story about some hard shit that you had to deal with.
Yeah.
And put it on display, even if it is in a fictionalized context.
That's true.
I think it just depends on.
You write a story where people read it and they're like,
I can tell that like the author went through this.
The author knows how this feels.
I think it depends a lot on like how much you feel the need
to tell the story at all.
Like if it's, if it's hurting to keep it bottled up inside,
but you don't want to just talk about it in a normal conversation,
then art is the way to go.
But like if it's, if it's just sort of like,
you could write a book about it and it's embarrassing if people
thought it was you and you'd be, you know,
you'd feel vulnerable about it,
but you don't, you don't, you could just never talk about it
and it would be fine.
Well, you know, that's kind of interesting.
Like, you know, serious question, slightly rhetorical,
but it's like, what, what is the point of like putting your emotions
into a story?
Like to put your emotion, your emotional vulnerability in it.
And like, like, why not like, I don't like go see a counselor
and like work it out or something.
I suppose it's to exploit it for literal monetary gain, right?
I don't think it's necessarily to exploit.
Cause you could have like, you could have like had an experience
and then gotten over it and then you still remember the experience.
So you could use that to inform a character.
I think it's like writing what you know, you know,
if it's something that you have experience with,
it's like you can, you're going to be able to give whatever story
you're crafting a degree of authenticity.
You know, you're not making something up.
And it's true.
And it's, yeah, it's not just authenticity.
It's just like also easier to work on something
when you know what you're doing.
Like if you, if you say, oh, what's hot right now,
characters who have no legs.
All right.
I don't know what it's like, but I guess I'll try
and write a story about the guy doesn't have legs.
Yeah.
It's going to be more difficult for you to do that
unless you're a complete hack.
Well, that's certainly true.
And you hacked your legs off.
That'd be commitment.
This makes me think of, I don't know,
there's some mediums that are different.
Like when you're writing a story about another character,
you can definitely make it about the issues that you care about.
And probably without, without exception,
almost every, I suppose I'll say,
every like sincere story that's written
will probably be informed by some experience.
Like at least to a degree.
Like the author has had.
I literally don't know how you couldn't do that.
You have to on some level understand.
It's mandatory for an art by one person.
When you're working in a team,
people's ideas and values get squished together
and compromised and, you know,
the bigger the committee, the weirder it is,
the less fair to say.
Less of a personal project it becomes.
That's true.
And you could all, I suppose you could literally like,
let's say that you just, yeah, you want to write about depression.
You literally like Google someone's book about depression,
read it, and then attempt to like, you know,
just do what they said or something.
But I'm not.
I mean, to a lesser degree, I think people do that all the time.
They're trying to, you know, be accurate to what they're trying to represent.
And they want to have a certain aspect in the art,
but they don't have personal experience.
They look it up to try and model it.
In Vapors 3, Magda goes to the hospital.
And I remember when I, this was like, planning out the story,
I talked to-
Does she also not be able to shit?
Stop ripping off my stories, man. God damn it.
I, um, like, I wanted to write this, but I was like,
I don't really know, like, how the procedure would,
like, I don't know, like, what the hospital protocol would be for this.
So I talked to, fuck, what's your friend's name
for your high school friend? It doesn't matter.
But you know, yeah, you had a friend in high school,
a girl who, I, she was like a nurse or something.
And I, and I called her.
Oh yeah, I know her.
Hey, like, you, you work at a hospital,
tell me how you think it would go if XYZ happened.
What would be done with this person?
Yeah, okay.
And, uh, so I-
She said, who the hell are you?
Yeah.
Was that, was that recent, or was that a while ago?
No, that was, like, before I even started making it.
Okay, okay.
This was just like to get, like, how would this go?
And then I was like, okay, so here's, here's, okay.
So I, I have at least one, like, professional's opinion
that this is more or less what would happen.
And I was like, okay, well, you know,
maybe it wouldn't always happen, but I'm satisfied.
I'm satisfied that my story is not, like, stupid and ridiculous
and someone would read it and be like,
this would never happen.
This doesn't make any sense.
Hospitals would, you know, wouldn't do this.
Um, yeah.
Well, that's cool.
But I mean, to get back to his point of, like,
specifically emotional vulnerability or whatever,
I mean, the first thing that that made me think of
was, obviously, like, music comes to mind.
But, like, for something that I've done,
like, in Gurren Lagann, part two,
there's that moment at the end where I specifically
draw the focus to, like, me
and how, like, I personally, like,
I'm like, blah, blah, blah.
This story could really make a difference.
Like, let's say, like, a sad, lonely guy,
like, making videos in his mom's basement or whatever,
or, you know, like, in his, whatever,
in, like, a shitty apartment that, you know,
and he knows by only, like, working hard
to improve his life and stopping addicted to, like,
sex, video games, drugs, or, like, whatever,
really, like, improve.
And there's, like, a picture of me on screen.
I am saying this about myself.
And so, like, so, like, this is what it meant to me.
And I'm saying, like, yeah, like, I fuck up.
That's not a particularly vulnerable moment,
or anything.
But, like, I really don't like being vulnerable
pretty much at all.
Though, obviously, it's...
But you know what I was gonna say, though?
But I definitely recognize,
and I kind of feel like,
like, using quote-unquote vulnerability,
or at least signaling vulnerability with, like,
sappy music or, like, talking softly,
sure is a good way to, like, make people give a shit.
Or, you know?
There's a...
Yeah, it's just something you see on YouTube,
like, someone will just do it.
I don't know, there was one...
I remember Logan Paul crying when he could see color
for the first time.
I don't think that's actually being vulnerable.
If you're hamming it up on purpose,
that's, like, a marketing test.
That's my point.
Yeah, yeah.
And, you know, it's hard, because, like,
you see YouTubers do it all the time,
and you don't want to be like,
oh, this person's just faking that.
This person, you know, they're just doing it for the view.
Like, you know, I think in any...
Okay, this is a piece of art that someone is making
to put out for public consumption.
So, in any of these scenarios,
there is some amount of, like, performance
and, like, selection.
Like, some thought goes into how this will be presented.
Even if it's just that they chose to release it
versus not release it, they chose that.
Yeah, even if it were totally candid,
this is being, like, put out on the internet.
But, like, yeah.
But you can't...
You can't say, oh, this is all fake,
because, like, obviously, if there's a motion there,
it must come from at least slightly a real place.
Like, they must at least know some...
Like, I don't know.
I mean, I guess some people could just be lying,
but I'm sure that's...
They're not.
I'm sure most people are...
I don't know.
Someone will make...
They'll have one episode where they talk about suicide
and then they'll be like, actually, guys,
you know, I didn't want to talk about this,
but, you know, I actually tried to commit suicide once
and I was like, oh, my God, me too.
Yeah, on this subject, I'm definitely guilty of hyperbole
at various points in my output of content and whatnot.
I...
My highest virtue is honesty,
and so I always try to avoid it,
but I'm certain that I've...
Might as well you avoid honesty.
Well, did I say that wrong?
Well, no, it sounded like you said
my highest virtue is honesty, comma,
so I always try to avoid it.
Oh, yeah, okay, okay.
Well, so that's important.
That's one virtue I'm trying to purge myself.
So I don't know.
Like, I'm certain that I will continue to do things
that are at least somewhat emotionally,
whatever, vulnerability inducing or whatever,
but I don't know.
It's not something that I really like to do that much.
I don't know.
That's all I got.
Okay, we got one more.
We got one more,
and this voicemail is from a friend of the show,
Niggas Flexin and Still Hatin.
So let's see what he's got for us.
Go.
Hey, take a big hit.
Talk a little shit.
You know what I mean?
Your niggas is coolin', doin' what you doin',
fuckin' with the PCP.
Y'all should come out to the hood sometime.
Your niggas is good and boptin'.
Peace.
Wait, what was that last one?
He said peace.
Your niggas is good and bumpin'.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I like bumpin'.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah.
I appreciate that.
Well, Ben, you headin' out to the hood?
Yeah, headin' out to the hood to get some milk.
I'm gonna bump down the road in my bunker car.
Chocolate, strawberry, whole milk, skim milk.
The choices are endless.
Oh, my God.
Wow, was that president of Hood Corporation,
a niggas flexin' and still hatin' the man himself?
Thank you.
What a character.
Well, I can't.
You can't.
No, I'm gonna get some heavy cream,
because it's key.
Yeah, of course.
You guys got heavy cream?
He'll hook you up.
Can we get a sponsorship by the Hood Corporation, perhaps,
or a heavy cream on the PCP?
Please.
I'll drink it live.
Okay, let's go.
I think we're done here.
That was the last one.
We're wrappin' it up.
Okay, so patreon.com, people, slash the procrastinators,
give us $5 for the bonus episodes.
Dreamcast, you heard a little discussion of it.
Get in on the action, people.
You don't want to be left out in the cold.
You want to be in on the party.
So give us your money, please.
Twitter, at TPCrastinators.
You know, we're doin' our thang on there.
So go follow for updates and whatnot.
Speakpipe, of course.
Speakpipe.
Of course.
Get in there.
Link in the description.
Leave us your voicemails.
There were a lot of voicemails this week.
A lot of them were, like, kind of bordering on good,
but I had to cut many of them anyway.
So keep up in your quality, people.
Keep workin' on it.
Oh, and the only other thing is, of course,
let me remind everybody, again,
the hashtag PCP Editor contest
is goin' strong for one more week.
You've got one week from when you're here in this
to enter if you so desire.
And one week should be plenty of time to get it done.
So there'll be a link in the show notes,
and there's a whole other video,
the one probably that came out before this,
a hashtag PCP Editor contest.
Go watch it.
Read the document.
It's important.
Make sure you do all the steps.
And there you go.
Best of luck.
I mean, the best individual win.
So that's it.
Excellent.
Thanks for being here.
Another one in the bag, boys.
That's correct.
Another paycheck cashed.
We did it.
Thanks for being here,
and we'll see you next week, everybody.
Bye.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did I come jerking?
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.