Do-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu-nu.
Hi, everyone! Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Hey, it's just me. It's just Ben here.
And I'm here making a protest bonus episode.
Not a bonus episode, but some extra, extra content.
PCP, extra credit.
It's protest. I object. I object, sir.
To the last episode,
Tom and Gibb did a great job, did a bang-up job, loved the episode, 10 out of 10 quality content.
However, I was thrown into a blind fury that so few of the voicemails will listen to.
I believe in egalitarianism, I believe in voicemail anarchy, I believe that all voicemails, even the shittiest voicemails,
deserve a chance to prove themselves in the marketplace of ideas.
And so here, now, for you, I'm gonna make a stand.
I'm gonna stand against tyranny, I'm gonna stand against exclusion, I'm gonna stand against the PCP oligarchs that run everything,
the fat cats that are trying to keep the little guy down.
I'm here, what you want to say, I want to hear it, and that's what we're gonna do today.
And I apologize in advance.
So, without further ado.
Wait, where did my notes?
Where's my notes?
There they are.
Without further ado, let's get into it, shall we?
Now two episodes ago, the last episode, the last voicemail was from Darren the Red.
So the next one we got is from, it's from someone called
Listen to this, ooh-ooh, and there's a huge,
there's a link, there's a link.
Anyway, let's hear the voicemail.
Please enjoy this extended rating
of a tweet thread directed to Ben Sinked.
Oh, I know what this is, I know what this is.
This is the, this is the, this is that, that, that.
The hate thread, the hate thread I received on Twitter.
It's another extended read.
All right, I'll put the link in the description.
This is the second dramatic reading
of that legendary tweet thread that I have heard,
but it never gets old.
Thank you very much.
Next up, we've got Salad Boys.
Hey, what's your favorite salad?
Grrr.
Okay, you know what?
Just today I invented a new salad, a hamburger salad.
I'll tell you the recipe right now.
You put lettuce in your bowl, right?
That's garnish, whatever.
And then you cook, you cook your brown beef in a pot,
and then you throw in chopped cauliflower, steam it,
steam it till it's soft, leave it hot, crack eggs into it.
Just crack eggs into it, leave it in the pot covered.
15 minutes or so, the eggs will steam,
they will, they will cook in there.
The yolks will still be runny, that's what you want.
Chop it up, mash it up, mix it up, switch it around.
Salt, pepper, mozzarella.
Swirl it around, becomes kind of like a mush.
That's what you want, kind of a jumble.
Scoop it into the bowl on top of the lettuce.
Ketchup and mustard on top.
This is apparently controversial.
Some people don't believe in ketchup and mustard on burgers.
I think that's frankly un-American.
Garnish with a pickle, spear, obviously, no slices.
And there you go, a hamburger salad.
For me, you boy, Ben St, enjoy, it's low carb.
Cut out the ketchup if you're really concerned about sugar.
So that's my new favorite salad, and I'm so glad
I got the opportunity to tell you all about it.
Next up, we've got the big C question.
Let's hear it.
Okay, so I got a quick salad question here.
You know, whenever you're eating a salad,
do you ever add croutons on, like, everyone's into croutons?
It's nachito.
Except for me, it seems.
So like, what's the deal?
What's the appeal of croutons?
And if you do, what's the best quality of croutons?
And why do you like it?
Thank you.
I like croutons.
They're just like garlic bread, but hard and crunchy.
That's the appeal.
It's very obvious, but I don't need them anymore
because they're nachito.
Thanks for calling in.
Next up, we've got fruit burp.
Here we go.
Progressioners, what's your favorite fruit
to have for fruit salad, my dudes?
Fuck fruit salad.
I don't know.
Pineapple, I guess?
Pineapple.
Next one, we've got brobroni.
Here it comes, coming at ya.
So Jenny Nicholson recently put out a video
looking at the history of bronies and bronicon.
And as someone who isn't that into the whole brony thing,
I thought it was a pretty interesting deep dive
into the subculture.
Since y'all have a past in that,
I just want to know what your reactions to it were
and if you had any dissenting opinions
against what she said.
Thanks.
Hearing Jenny, I watched the video.
I really enjoyed it.
Hearing Jenny talk about bronicon,
in brony, ponydom in general,
and the last bronycon in specific,
throat's dry, I got some seltzer.
I got some sparkling water.
Delightful.
Hearing Jenny talk about that was like,
was like reminiscing about the good old days
with a friend, you know, you just,
Munchy didn't like it,
because Munchy said that he thought it was very surface
level, like duh, everyone knows that.
And like, yes, I did already know everything she had to say.
So in the sense, I agree.
But I think that's really dumb.
And I disagree, I thought it was really fun.
It's like when you get together with someone,
you go, hey, remember that, remember that,
you reminisce about the good old days
and you just have a good time,
just sort of bouncing these ideas around.
Just hearing them, just repeat them for old times sake
because it's fun.
That's what I liked about it.
And it was great.
I loved it.
I thought she was a little weird about like the,
she seemed a little judgy,
not just about like the, like,
she mentions like having like fillies on pillows
and like, I get that.
I don't know if I like that so much,
but like, she seemed a little judgy
just about like porn in general,
which like, I don't know,
get over yourself, like everyone jerks off to everything.
Like it's, why are you acting like it's weird?
I don't know.
I don't understand that part.
But other than that, everything about like,
you know, when she talks about like some outsized egos
from people who were not famous,
the other like 20, 360 days of the year,
but then they get like weird rock star complexes at,
I was like, yes, I want 100%.
That was me a little bit, maybe just a little bit.
I mean, I wasn't, I don't think I was a dick about it,
but like, I know that feeling.
Like, I knew people, I saw people being like that
and to a little bit, I was that.
And it's just like, how silly,
how silly of a time to look back upon and reflect.
So those are my thoughts about that.
Next one, next one is from The Jocker Threat,
which they did, Tom and Hippo did, listen to,
good on them, good job, credit where credits do.
Next one is called I'm Ben Saint,
and there's a YouTube video attached, so let's hear it.
I'm Ben Saint.
Okay.
All right.
Let's check, let's check this video out.
This is a certified,
oh it's a,
I'm Ben Saint.
It's a song.
I'm Ben Saint, oh I'm Ben Saint.
I'm Ben Saint, Oh I'm Ben Saint.
The lyrics are,
yo, bitch I'm Ben Saint over and over again.
Oh, no, there's lyrics. There's lyrics. There's gunshots. Okay, I'm not gonna listen to this
whole thing right now. Link in the description. Go listen to Starman's, I'm Ben St, featuring
Simon. Dab. It's a banger. The screenshot is, what is this aspect ratio? It's in square
aspect ratio. Why? But it's me eating PCP killer pills, which I appreciate. It's true.
It's true. Killed it, baby. Next one. Daydream Honeybee. Let's see what you bring with the
table.
It has been brought to my attention that in addition to committing the capital sin that
is crustless key to pizza, Ben St, whom you might know for having dug himself into
a hole where what personality he had that made him unique and defined has what interested
until it become indistinguishable from the cultic ideologues he now parrots and promotes
has been wasting perfectly functional nitroglycerin components on candies. I naturally hope that
is ashamed of himself, but I'd like to know at the very least if those chemicals haven't
been wasted in vain. So tell us, Ben St, when was the last time you had an original thought,
Ben St? I thought that, oh excuse me, I'm still reading Ash of Empires' excellent thread.
Anyways, the people want to know, where them gamys any good? Answer, Ben St.
You know, I made a, the other day, I was cooking it, I was cooking gelatin, right? I put all
this, right? Because, alright, to make gelatin with no lumps, you got to have like a high
ratio of gelatin to water, right? I have found that I can get away with maybe like one tablespoon
of gelatin in a quarter of a cup of water. And I can only do that by using like a wide
pan and putting the water in the wide pan and then sprinkling the gelatin on like over
the very top to get to the maximum surface area. Because the key to smooth gelatin is
you have to let all the granules hydrate. They must be spread out through the water,
they must have contact with the water in order to hydrate. And if they're clumped up together
or you dump it in one spoonful, it's going to clump, it's going to be hard and chewy,
it's going to make lumps, it's going to be bad. You have to get it smooth. And so that's
the best ratio I can get, but it's still not enough. If you do that, it is still too watery
and your gummies will come out too wet. So I had to do that and then cook it down. I
cooked it down to about two thirds of that level. It started at six cups, cooked it down
to four cups. Honestly, I think maybe I should have taken a little further, but that's what
I did. And then I used the last of my previous Jell-O that I had done. I had made a big batch
of it and kept chunks of it for heating up later. I used the last of it and the last
of the isomaltooligosaccharide syrup that I had cooked down to a cooking temperature
of 120 degrees Celsius, which at which point it becomes dense enough, it's dehydrated enough
that at room temperature, it becomes hard. You have to heat it up for it to become liquid
so that you can pour it and work with it. So you heat that up, you heat the gelatin
up, you mix it together and mix it together. And I put in the last of my mango flavoring
and blah, blah, blah. And it turned out this batch came out a little fucked up because
I did not put enough gelatin in. It was too syrupy. It's too stretchy, but also it like
froze on the inside. So it's like, it's too stretchy and gooey. It's not gummy-ish enough.
It's not solid enough or chewy enough, but it's also got these like hard lumps on the
inside. It's not gelatin clumps. It's like the syrup. It's like chunks of the hardened
syrup as though it were room temperature. It didn't mix into the gelatin well enough.
The flavor is like overpowering. I put the last of the mango in so I just kind of dumped
the rest in and it was too much. It's too strong. It's overpowering. It's unpleasant.
So that was the last batch I made and I'm not willing to throw them away. So I've just
kind of been like having one every like eat like part of it and try to avoid the hard bits
like, okay, I like the tanginess. Even if the flavor is a little weird. So I've been working
my way through that. I have another batch of the cooked down gelatin in the fridge. I made
a lot of it, but I still have to cook down more of the syrup because at like normal temperature,
the concentration I have it mixed at right now is unworkable. I have to cook it down.
It's very important that the final product not be too wet or it's just like bleh. So
this last batch was not great, but I have had good batch. I've had a couple of really
good batches lately actually. So yes, I guess, yes, question mark is the answer. Lamal.
Next one was from smear, which they listened to on the episode. So I'll skip that for now.
Forever. Look, next one is from Woo Woo. Here we go.
Hello, a PCP. I was wondering, what, do you like, do you like pineapple in your salad?
I already said yes. I already said pineapple was my favorite fruit in a fruit salad. You
know what, you know what, you know, let me, I like, if I'm in the right mood, sometimes
a fruit salad has like cherries in it, not like maraschino cherries, not like the ones
in the soup, but like the fresh ones, a little dark red ones. I might, I like those because
like you can like pick them up and eat them and they still taste like a cherry. They don't
have that in a fruit salad. You know, I take it back. It's not pineapple because pineapple
absorbs the flavor of all the other. I don't like it. I don't like it in a fruit salad.
It all, each of the fruits absorb one another's flavors. I hate that. And pineapple is guilty
of that. So pineapple might be one of my favorite fruits of the fruits among the fruit salad,
but in a fruit salad, loses its individuality and I don't like it as much. So I'm going
to amend my quest, I'm going to amend my answer to cherries, but only the fresh kind, not
the soggy kind. Next one, the tea question. We need to address the elephant in the room,
the tea question, the tiny Timmy question. This guy submit so many goddamn voice mails
every week and everyone agrees that they're shit. How is he not in the voice jail by now?
Look, I know I'm not one to point fingers, but Jesus Christ man, he submits like 10 fucking
voice mails a week and now that they're democratized and they're all being played, it's fucking
hell. I've exacerbated the problem. I don't remember which ones are Timmy and which ones
are not. I'm actually pretty bad at distinguishing voices. So for my part, most of the time I
probably don't even realize when I'm playing a Timmy voicemail. So, I don't know. Whoops.
Next one, BGE monthly cast. What's that? Hey guys, don't want to turn this into the fucking
Nate podcast or anything, but just because you guys mentioned it last episode, yeah,
Nate does have a patron only podcast that he does, but what do you know? What's today?
August 1st, and he didn't release one in July. What do you know?
Okay, thanks for the update, my man. Next one's Margar, already played it. Skipped
it. Next one, Dirty Hippie with a clean butthole. Let's see what that's all about.
So I was like hanging out with my fellow dudes or whatever and like while they were taking
turns eating on my asshole, I was like, why do they call it getting your salad tossed?
And I was like, what kind of salad would my asshole be? I don't know, bro, but what kind
of salad would your asshole be? It would be a fruit salad because I am gay. It would
be a hamburger cauliflower salad because it just would be, I don't know, that's just
how God made me. Thanks for your input. Next one, please God you stupid fucks.
This is a criticism of the PCP. Every single fucking episode, someone believes a sarcastic
voicemail like, I'm a person with dumb opinions, I believe this in every single time, without
fail. Someone's like, man, why does this person believe this dumb thing? These aren't text
messages, you can hear tone, you can hear the tone of my voice right now. You can hear
the tone of their voice, you can hear them going like, I believe that communism is bad.
And then Ben's like, communism isn't bad. Like Jesus Christ, this person is agreeing with
you, please, please God, okay, that's all. I don't just feel bad, feel bad about yourselves.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you. I will take it under advisement. I apologize for everything. What do you think
everyone? Do we not pick up on social cues? Okay, next one is from crack and I know they
played this one on the episode, but I have, I have reason to believe that there's more
to this one. So I'm going to play it again for context.
Hey Ben, did you see all the tweets about UFOs being real?
No.
It's really funny how everybody was saying Space Jam was real when they canceled the
NBA for the virus and now aliens are just real. You're an astronomer, retired space
counselor. I know you're on top of it. Just thinking about you.
I, I don't know about aliens being real. I didn't see anyone saying Space Jam was real
when the NBA was canceled. But these concepts are not so outlandish that I cannot close
my eyes and visualize and see them as though, as though they're coming true before my eyes.
Okay, I can see it now. I understand. I can infer context. Okay, got it.
Next one, Mickey Mouse.
Hey Ben, we're in a real dilly of a pickle here down at Walt Disney World. Our gas
members are dropping like flies to the coronavirus and we got a big game coming up.
Lace up the basketball shoes your mom gave you and get down here to Orlando, Florida.
We need to beat these monsters. Lace them up, Ben, or you'll have to dribble again.
I don't believe that I don't believe Mickey took place in, I don't believe Mickey or any
other Disney characters took part in the battle against the monstars. Neither, they're not,
I don't remember the name from the movie. They certainly weren't in Charles Barkley
Shut Up and Jam Guy Den. I think you perhaps might be thinking of Who Framed Roger Rabbit,
which as we all know is the prequel to Space Jam, took place before the Disney apartheid
that saw all the Disney characters shunted off into the ghetto, which is why they don't
appear in Space Jam. I don't know. That's it. So where in the timeline, where in the
timeline of Who Framed Roger Rabbit, Space Jam, Charles Barkley Shut Up and Jam Guy
Den? Could this voice, I don't know, probably, you know what? Write me a fucking, write me
a two and a half page short story about it at me on Twitter and I'll read it. Someone
explain this shit to me. It doesn't make any sense. Where's the historicity? Where's the
verisimilitude? Next up, Ben S. Who could this be? Let's find out.
Listen here, Ben, Saint. Facts don't care about your feelings. But I do. How you doing, man?
How's it going, how's it going? Hope you're doing well.
Yeah, thanks. I'm just mad on Twitter, man. Just mad on Twitter at people like you.
Okay, great. Next one is from, wait, they listen, this was Simon's I Don't Like Salad. After
all these fucking salad posts. Everyone fucking salad posting in the voicemail this week. What
is some kind of virus? It's as though some kind of virus we're spreading among people
that makes them think about salad or something. I'm not sure what to make of it. Next one
is called Yeah. You know, there's something reassuring about the fact that Nate will most
likely, likely die before you. Knowing that he will have to face his death in his own cowardly
pathetic way. I do, I do. A truly sense of curse of curry.
Who's going to die? Did you say Nate was going to die? Did you say Iowa? Speak up.
Your message was muddled. Terrible. Bad, bad job. Next one, your eating preferences.
Alright, you fucks. Do you prefer eating salad on a plate or in a bowl? And double question.
When you're eating salad, do you prefer a fork with long prongs or short prongs? We
need to know. Um, all my forks have the same prong length. I never think about prong length.
I don't know. I have no idea. Um, who the fuck would eat salad on a plate? I guess like
that's awful. Imagine trying to eat salad on a plate. I, I don't have bowls big enough
to make salads that, that do it for me. Like I, the biggest bowls that I have are these
like, kind of, they're sort of like long-ish bowls, like you might serve soup in. And like
they just don't hold that much salad. So when I make a salad, which I do a lot lately,
um, just, just spring mix, Caesar dressing, grated Parmesan cheese, baby. No, I don't
even mix it in a bowl. I mix it in like the biggest tupperware I have. Like a big, maybe
like, you know, I have a big, I don't know how big it is. It's like maybe like nine inches
by nine inches square and kind of deep. I don't know. It's, it's, I mix it in that because
I just need the biggest vessel because I need to fucking mix it all. I need to mix all the
leaves up because they're not packed that tightly. I have to, I have to toss them around.
You got to toss them around. And if the bowl isn't big, if there's not excess volume, they're
going to fucking come out the sides and I have to clean it up. And that's stupid. No, no,
no, no, no. Big bowl, deep bowl, no plate. Give me a, give me a freaking break. Why don't
you? Um, next one, weird Al Yankovic. Hmm. Although they spelled it Yankovic, but whatever.
All right. What's, what's up? Hey, it's me. Weird Al Yankovic. And I got a pirate lead
from Ben's song from the last episode. It sounds just like him. I believe in the Quran and the
people of Iran. Please join us. Okay. Thanks for, thanks for parodying my dream song to make
out Islam. That's, it's, it's pretty edgy. That's pretty edgy for compared to your usual content.
Mr. Weird Al Sir. But I, you got to take chances sometimes. You know what? You got to speak truth
to power. Appreciate it. Next one. They listened to Why Munchy Why. So we're, we're there. We've
arrived. The last one that was skipped over last time was called left. Actually, I think
maybe that this one was not posted by the time last episode was, but we skipped it and
thought we did and didn't read it. So I'm going to read it anyway. It's called leftism
in my PCP returns probably a week late again. So let's hear that. Yeah, this is the guy
that left the voicemail where I not so subtly through shade at Nate because I think he needs
to read another book. Right. I still think that, but I want to apologize because I left that
expecting Nate to not be there to defend himself and that's, that's not cool. And also
I am clarifying that I was talking about the conversation that Ben and Digi were having
on the episode where they were together before Gib came in and not the episode where Ben was
just rambling on his own because I don't think Ben talked about politics when he was just
by himself. Not really. I'm not going to go back and double check that though. So maybe
I'm wrong. I don't know. Thanks for everything. All you guys do, including the ones that I
not so subtly make fun of. Yeah. I shit. I don't remember. Right. This person wrote
in or called in another voicemail called leftism in my PCP. And I'm sorry to say, but I don't
remember off the top of my head what you said in that one about Nate or anything else for
that matter. But if, but if, oh wait, I see it. I'm not going to listen to it. Whatever.
Maybe you, the viewer, remember that voicemail and you can draw in for some context and glean
something about what this person's intended message. As for me, I'm too stupid and that's
going to do it for this extra special edition of PCP extra credits. Ben listens to every
voicemail in protest. Um, that's so the next time, the next time you fat cats, the next
time you fucking bourgeois PCP members want to go and, and, and, you know, ruin, destroy
post office, you know, a gerrymander against, against, uh, against voicemail on a gerrymander,
the voicemails want to do some voter suppression against our beautiful Colin, Colin fans. I'm
here then saying the people's champion to lift up the marginalized, downtrodden, disenfranchised
PCP listeners, um, so that everyone can make fun of them and their shitty voicemails equally.
Thank you for listening. Good day, sir. And madam.