Click and click down the track. Welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, everybody. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, where we decide that The Pro Crastinators Podcast will be slaughtered or salvaged.
Don't you guys just hate it when you're crying while masturbating with your fucking claw hand that you've accumulated from just jacking off three times plus a day?
Thinking about your various classmates because they've worn a nerd girl t-shirt once? I do that all the time and it just sucks.
Come on, hand. Can't you keep up the heat? Get out of the kitchen. Cyborg hands for jack off two. Classmates go now, too.
You know, I read this book by Jordan Peterson. I don't like the Jews either.
Who are you quoting?
This is not PewDiePie. That's obviously PewDiePie.
You're a master of speech.
That's all I'll say is that you're a master of linguists and you're a master of impersonation.
Hey, how you say it, this is me, PewDiePie, haha, Brofius.
This is a Swedish accent. He's Swedish, right?
Yeah, but he's not like...
So he sounds exactly like the Swiss shit.
No, it wasn't. I was doing the Swiss chef accent.
Well, okay, as you can see, everybody, we got everybody here. We got PewDiePie here.
God, intros are so better. Intros are so better. I hate the cold intros. I love these valuable, like, productive intros we have.
I mean, I agree. I agree. But just for the sake of information, me, Bestie Boy is here, Hippocrite, Mage, Munchie, Ben.
There you go. That's who's here. Alright, moving along.
What's up, guys? You like Caramel Donson or what? Are we gonna Caramel Donson or what?
I like Caramel Donson constantly. Honestly, but listen to it constantly.
I was just saying to Munchie before we started that Munchie is a...
He literally embodies the soul, the departed spirit of the 2006 anime congoer.
It's the nicest thing anyone's ever said to me. Niceest thing.
Ben and I would both know. We were there.
It was a special time in a boy's life.
You were around zero.
Imagine me in my Disgaea cosplay at Anime Boston 2000...
Was that guy's name? Serif, something?
He was the Serif.
He's the angel leader guy. I can't remember his name.
That might have just been his title was the Serif. His name was Master Something.
He had kind of like an English or a Swedish sounding name or something.
I'm gonna find this right now.
Master Something Son.
Lammington? Lammington.
Master Lammington, that's it. Yes, that's it.
Okay, got it. Flansboss.
Imagine me in my Master Lammington Disgaea cosplay at Anime Boston 2006 at a FreezePop concert.
Glomping hard to FreezePop on the dance floor.
I still have a special place in my heart for FreezePop.
Boston-based band, as it so happens, didn't even know that at the time, but it's true.
You have a connection to one of the PC Pimmers with a blankets concert at Anime Boston, right?
Question mark?
What the fuck are you talking about?
You're talking about the pillows, my dude. You're talking about the pillow.
Oh, the blanket.
Sorry, I don't know.
Unload a fucking blanket in your skull.
Yeah.
Wait, that won't be a problem.
It'll be a real wet blanket if you were to do that.
Hey, Munchy, recently I saw you did a little animation of a lateralist of RowdyFuckers Copkiller's fame
doing a funny dance that was similar to the Caramel Dancing.
I just wanted to ask you, why? What'd you do? Why do you think of that?
Well, the reason I did that is twofold.
Number one, I'm animating on the side now.
Now, guys, exclamation point, stop.
Also, I'm doing another thing that features Lateralist Heavy that I'm not going to speak about.
Don't get your hopes up, question mark.
Are you talking about Lateralist Heavy like TF2 Heavy, like big donut sandwich?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's the thing going on?
Oh, yeah, yeah, believe me.
Okay.
Lateralist Heavy, a frame scout, a six-ton pyrogue, the list goes on.
That's a terrible lineup.
Wait, what's his face would be spilling?
I already have the lineup.
Camman is tracing.
Camman's spy, right?
No, okay, here's the thing. Crocs is Heavy.
I don't know the rest.
There you go.
It's not that easy, is it?
It's all there is to say.
Why do you ask? Just want to know what's going on?
No, I just thought it was a really nice little gif.
Yeah, if you're doing animation on the side, it's like...
Link it in the show notes. Let me see. I haven't seen it.
Okay, do that. It's in RFCK, but also...
Speaking of nice little animations, there's on the Gibb and Take channel, there was those
two combined little snippets of animation from the upcoming...
What is it? Reanimating project of...
Well, it's called Hashtag Rise Up.
Is that the name of the show?
No.
I think that's what it was, right?
Hashtag, dude.
Hashtag stand again.
Nate, are you looking at YouTube?
Are you looking at Ben Sainz's leftist Twitter feed?
Yeah, I might have confused the two.
Sorry, Gibb, please extrapolate.
It's like a little animation thing of...
Oh my god, 43 notifications.
Of from the Homestuck-esque, collide reanimation product.
My favorite flash, our favorite cliff flash.
Yeah, you know, I'm not like that big a fan of the flash for story reasons,
but parts of it are really cool and the music is pretty good.
And there's numerous reasons to do it outside of the flash itself.
I'm happy to be involved in a big collaborative project.
And more so than ever, you've made Arm Retrieval Canon 2 Homestuck.
Yes, that was my big goal, is to do one of the first scenes.
I didn't think you needed help with that.
Wait, is this an official What Pumpkin project?
No, it's just like a fan who said,
hey guys, let's reanimate collide for the 10th anniversary of Homestuck.
But I mean, Hussie gave up all rights to artistic control over Homestuck a long time ago.
When I disagreed with the direction he took the series in.
That's exactly correct, that's exactly correct.
Now the, what is it, the lunatics are running the asylum as it were.
Well, hey, yeah, go on, who's got something?
I got things, but go on.
Okay, okay, well I want to continue on what we were just talking about.
So, you started this animation kick hippo.
I know that you've also been animating other things.
I don't know if you've said them on the show question mark, but I don't want to dox you, you see.
Oh, no, no, I've mentioned that I'm working on the finale of Bail Jape.
That is the animation I'm doing.
So, you've been in a real fever, you've been in a real fever pitch for animating.
Yeah, I'm, you know, I'm dreaming of in-betweens at this point.
I'm just thinking, ah, yes, smooth and jumping and key frame cool mode.
Ah, I love it.
In-betweens, the trans people of animation, my favorite.
Well, yeah, literally transitioning from one key frame to the other.
Indeed.
I, again, myself have been doing stuff on the side for personal reasons.
And I just want to say that I kind of suspected this was the case.
But, like, I feel like animation is, like, speaks to me on a more fundamental level than any art that I do.
It really is something that I, like, appeals to me.
Like, just the busy work of doing in-between frames and, you know, just animating.
That is just an inherently fun process to me, to watch something come together
and just to be able to kind of almost zone out in a way.
Once you have your key frames and you've done all the thinking hard work,
then you can just fill it in, that's really, really hot.
You know what, you know what I think about that.
This is something, okay, because we recently finished all those big video projects
and I've gotten back to drawing more, I have been facing this prospect more
and remembering the weird contradiction.
I feel the same way about starting to draw.
Because, like, once you start drawing, it's fine.
But I feel the same way about doing that as I feel about sleeping and that it terrifies me.
Because, like, yes, because I'm afraid...
I know exactly what you mean.
I'm afraid to let my, to turn my brain off.
I'm like...
Oh!
Okay, that's a very different way.
Really? Okay.
Is this the whole, like, you don't know if you're the same person when you wake up, sort of thing?
No, not exactly. It's not rational like that.
It's just, I don't want to do it.
And I know when I start, like, why don't you,
and Hippo and Mage, do you feel this way when you're thinking about maybe starting drawing
and you're like, oh, but I don't want to start that, though,
because then I'll, like, I don't know.
I don't even know what it is.
You know, I think I might know where you're coming from.
It's like the prospect of, like, I think about this sometimes of, like,
getting started with something means I know that if I get going,
I will be doing it for a certain amount of time.
And I won't...
Mage, don't just jump in and interrupt the middle of a sentence.
Like the... fuck.
Yeah, where are you saying?
I don't know. I can't remember.
A way to go, Mage.
I'm trying. It's one of those things where, like, I can't fucking think of the word.
You know that thing where, like, you think of the word?
Guys, what was he saying? We were all listening.
I was too busy yelling at Mage. I can't remember.
Dude, this is a great podcast.
Okay, okay.
What was the question?
Ben, you feel like you don't want to start drawing.
I do that because you know that once you're in there,
anything that comes along that could potentially interrupt you
will piss you off more than it would otherwise would.
And you don't know whether your future is going to be completely, you know,
devoid of interruptions.
And you're like, I need to wait for the perfect time to start doing this thing
that will take hours.
Yeah, that's part of it.
It's like, oh, maybe I shouldn't do it now.
It's not so much that I'm worried about being upset, about being interrupted.
It's just like, does this feel like the ideal moment to start on this?
Am I in the perfect headspace to do this now?
Maybe I should just wait. Maybe I should just wait in a better time.
A better opportunity will come along, which is ridiculous.
I'm going to level with you. You've got a pebble in your brain,
and you've got to drink something to get rid of.
He's got a pebble for a brain, if anything.
You've got to drink some carbonated soda to wash that down,
some bang to wash that down, because that's an extremely terrible mindset to have.
And I have that too sometimes.
I'm not saying this is right. I'm just saying this is my problem.
I feel that way too sometimes.
And I know that the way to fix it is to push through it more often.
But because I wasn't drawing much for a while, now I've started doing it again.
I've been facing this.
And I know that the way to bust it is to keep doing it and keep resisting it.
And I'm still working through that for the time being.
But it's getting better.
For a while.
For me, it's not that I feel like I should wait for a better time,
or something's wrong and I should wait.
It's really just that I don't want to do it because I'm lazy.
It's partially that.
The things I usually do to get over that initial thing is have a small ritual.
If I'm slightly hungry or tired, I will go downstairs, get a cup of tea or a small snack,
eat that, drink that while listening to something or reading Twitter or Discord.
And once I'm done with the eating, then I start the work and I drink the tea.
Music makes me more productive.
It definitely does, and yet I never listen to it.
It's just not something I do.
When I do, the results are always good.
Lads, we've got to talk over each other a little bit less here.
We're getting all tangled up.
This is particularly...
No, that wasn't even directed at you, Meiji.
I think Meiji needs to learn to interrupt better.
Not more, but better.
I was trying to make a point because there are a lot of people that say,
Everyone, guys, I have something to say.
Make sure you just go in and interrupt.
I tried two times and you guys...
There's an arc to this.
You said it while we were talking.
Here's my strategy.
Let's compare strategies on how to talk over each other.
You guys don't pause. Where am I supposed to start talking?
You look at strategic gaps in the armor.
Right there, I found one.
You wait for a strategic moment.
You can do that.
The way that I create a strategic moment.
It's about creating opportunities.
It's about visualizing the future you want to see,
and then the universe will bring it to you.
Here's the thing.
I feel like I interrupt properly.
When I say, guys, I have something to say.
I usually try and find a moment.
I don't think you're just better served by saying...
Instead of saying those words, being like...
And then they will make space for you.
And then you just launch into it.
My strategy is that if I'm trying to say something
and someone else is talking and I want them to stop,
I will begin the first word.
I'll say the first syllable.
People feel the anticipation there.
And I'll just...
And I'll keep doing that until the person speaking notices
and it disrupts them.
And then eventually they will...
It's a psychological battle of wills.
Why do they do this? There's no time limit here.
It just lets the person speaking know
that something is going to interrupt them
and they better just accept that possible.
I'll tell you why.
On one hand, it's like...
If people are interrupting each other,
that means they have things to say.
All the other boys have a lot of things to say about this
and it's an interesting topic.
However, it would be more easy to follow
and more interesting if instead of just
spitting out...
We actually thought
for even narrate a millisecond
to construct our point more.
I'll tell you my reason.
There's an elaborate series of reasons as to why that's done.
I'll tell you the biggest one.
One is that the conversation,
if you don't seize the moment when you have something to say,
could just move on
and then your thought will no longer be appropriate.
And the other real thought I have
is I will literally just forget
what I was going to say.
Actually, right now, for the last five minutes,
I have had a thought on my frontal cortex
waiting to be ejaculated
into the conversation
and I'm waiting for a lull to go back
to a thing to say it. And I could lose it at any moment.
It's precarious balance
and my psyche could be disrupted.
But then you get the...
Is this good for you, Buntie?
Is this what you want?
Hey, can you hear this?
Hey, can you hear this gun shooting your head?
That thought not.
Thought not.
Got a silencer on it.
A pen and pencil might actually be the solution.
Or like a pen and paper.
Oh, wow.
Munchie solves world hunger yet again.
Just a snatch in a way.
A pen and paper, tabletop, RPG,
dungeon crawl with the PCP.
Bonus episode.
What a race is all I'm trying to say.
We can all say everything we want.
And this isn't me an anti-conversationalist.
You're not accepting the full reality
of the battleground
that any given conversation truly is.
No other podcast is like this.
By saying that there's no time limit,
that's ignoring the fact that conversations
can simply shift
and then you just don't have the chance to say your thought
on what the conversation was.
Conversations only shift when people want to change the conversation.
No, that's not true.
It just evolves organically, dude.
Unless the Russians collude
and force a change in the conversation.
There's definitely something to be said
with regards to letting people
speak
when they
need to get something out
of their chest.
But I totally see what Nate is saying
because a lot of the times
I have a thing
that I didn't anticipate the conversation
going this way, but now I have something
to talk about this thing.
I haven't written it down.
And I don't know how to use a pencil,
so I'm just gonna forget about it.
I was surprised.
Not everyone agreed with me in the comments last episode,
but there were quite a few people
who were like, I like that
being a little bit of a clusterfuck.
I like a little bit of people interrupting each other.
Let the pod just let it be what it is.
And I was like, I'm glad I'm not the only one
that sees it that way.
And let me defend myself.
I am the first person to admit that I like
how frantic the PCP is sometimes.
I'm not saying it has to be another
boilerplate podcast.
Everyone just waits their turn
and just speaks only when they are
called upon or highlighted.
Why did I think that the phrase you were about to use
was boilerplate apocalypse?
I don't know.
However, I think
there's a balance here.
Moderation and all things.
I think there's a time and a place for clusterfucks
which could be even often.
And the time is now.
Okay, let's do it.
Hey guys, it's me on the podcast.
Don't interrupt me, please.
Wow, that was a great joke
and I'm glad everyone committed to it.
I didn't have anything to say.
That was awful.
What were you saying?
Art is shit and I'm glad
I'm not doing it anymore.
Hey guys, I just want to let you know
that I'm retiring from the podcast.
I made enough money. I can live for the rest of my life.
That's fair. We all can.
But we are greedy.
We want to steal the money from the poor
by continuing to make the podcast.
No, it can't happen. We were having a great conversation
and now it's back to the shit.
Guys, dammit.
Please support my empire at patreon.com.
I'd really appreciate that if you just keep sucking up
by vacuum on the poor.
Just giving it straight to my bank account.
My personal goal is to
make a living in a way as opposite
to my personal and political beliefs
as possible.
I thought you were going to say
as opposite to Nate as possible.
I just want to let you know
that I'm extremely suspicious of you right now
because you said something
which hurt me
deep in my arteries.
You said you check Twitter
when you get your T.
On what device are you checking Twitter?
What do you mean?
On my computer?
I think that's a pretty straightforward question.
Stop dodging the question.
Wrong answer, dude.
I don't understand.
He's showing weakness. Get him.
Everyone talk plow.
In my head, I envisioned you
walking downstairs and drinking tea.
But I guess the next sense,
if you were on your phone using Twitter,
I would have said tisk tisk, not strongly.
Oh, no, no. That's not on my phone.
Okay, I'm glad.
I have also...
You see, I'm following your footsteps.
You're a big daddy to me,
and I would appreciate if your cock could come out soon
rather than later.
Because my phone is basically
not connected to the internet whatsoever anymore.
No social media, no YouTube.
No fucking web browser.
Literally no web browser.
It's gone.
I have not...
I don't even look at my phone anymore.
Just because it's a piece of shit.
Well, I mean, it's not
aspirational. It's because
the thing is just really old and stuff.
Ben's truly stumbled ass backwards
into the perfect lifestyle.
It's not, because anything that I would
be wasting time on looking at my phone,
I just look at it on my desktop instead.
No, I'm not aspirational
in this regard.
Or any regard.
I'll fucking kill you, dude.
A couple of days ago,
I wanted to get really serious
about my phone
chewing up time, because I have had
the social media stuff off my phone
for a while now.
When I delete Twitter from my phone,
I just basically stopped using Twitter
altogether. I don't even know
the last time I looked at my Twitter.
I have no fucking clue.
Other social media stuff also falling off the map
as well as Discord. I have a mobile account now.
That's been for a while now,
but I finally took a big plunge
and just basically deleted everything
off my phone that was not
inherently work or
communications related.
That's fine.
I only have one screen on my phone
and it's all just like writing apps.
I'll just write apps or
my default music player
and that's basically it.
It's just a brick.
It's a brick of
pure writing and it feels
so good to be liberated from the
distractions that come with your phone.
Not only that,
I've turned it into a pure
work beast.
Finally, for the first time in my fucking life
gotten
a to-do app,
a task app
and a schedule for myself.
I finally have
a bedtime
where I'm going to bed at a single time
and I'm waking up at a single time
every single day.
Don't embrace this meme of this Digi Bro lifestyle
which I'm sure he would agree with as well.
Having a set time to go to bed and wake up
is just good for you.
I'm pretty sure
because you have an internal clock.
When you wake up
you don't feel like you want to die for two hours.
Imagine that.
So I'm
trying to go to bed at the same time every day.
Oh and big thing,
I have a journal now.
I had a journal before but I was not sticking to it.
Now I have a convenient app
called
Day Leo
and it is just a small
app that reminds you
every day at a certain time
to write about your day
which is what I've been doing every single day for a while now
and it's extremely helpful for my memory.
That's cool.
It's really nice so I've locked down my phone
and it's really great.
I'm really happy about it.
Is it something that you like?
I mean
I had my journal
that I would bring on holidays and stuff
to record events.
Sometimes
the day was so full of stuff
and by the time I remembered that I should write my journal
I was so tired I was just like
I don't know what to say.
I want it to be like a thing I can come back to
so I don't want to just write nothing.
Ironically
those are the days you need it most, right?
I've had that all the time.
I had a physical journal
and I use it.
But I have a physical journal
that I would have that exact same
scenario.
I would try and write every day
even when I was not on trips
and it just would fall through.
I just couldn't keep it up.
I would do it for the first couple days of a trip
and then it would be like I did so much today
I'm just fucking tired. I don't want to do this.
I hate writing by hand.
It's just a fucking nightmare.
However, with this
app, it's specifically incentivized
for you to write short sentences.
For instance,
yesterday...
It's like Twitter but only you can read it.
Literally yes.
Literally yes. It's like for that
basically.
There was a...
So you just at least have a record of what you did
the previous day.
And when I have something more interesting to say
that's when I break out the journal.
So I have a system here. It's every single day
and then when I have something more interesting
to write about and I have the free time
to do so, I'll break out my journal.
And that means it's not like a commitment
that I feel bad about breaking
that is writing in the physical journal.
It's just like a...
Whatever I break out the journal, it's just non-stop
good interesting things that I've chosen
to write about and therefore it feels more
important and better.
The Penny Arcade guys had a little inside joke
running for a while
about an app called Twonter
which is just Twitter, but instead
of posting your tweet, it just doesn't go
anywhere and nobody sees it.
It's like you get the satisfaction
of making an angry tweet with none
of the fallout or problems that come from it.
It would be a good system.
Everyone should get that and send
everything they want to send on Twitter on
Twonter first, see how they feel
about it and then decide if they want to
re-send it. Yeah, come back the next day.
Yeah. Do I want to tweet my...
No, the answer is always
the answer is always no.
Sometimes I go on Twitter
and I'm like, well
let's try and think of something
to say. Let's try and think of something funny.
Usually it just results
in me saying something stupid, but you know
whatever, but I shouldn't
feel the need to post anything
if I don't feel like there's
anything to say and yet there I go
trying to...
The most recent one was like Jimmy
Neutron meets Jimmy Page.
I was like, I mean it's kind of funny
but like I only did that because
I was on Twitter and I was like, I should probably
tweet something. It's been a while, it's been
a few days.
It's kind of stupid.
It's just so boring, honestly.
After a while it just becomes like
do I really want to know
what everyone else is saying?
Not in the sense that I'm antisocial, but like
I've known everyone I'm following
for so long, like I know
what they're going to say, it's just going to be more
bullshit.
Nothing's new there.
I'm not getting any new stimuli.
It's just keeping up with people
it's keeping up with you guys
exclusively. I've been getting
new stimuli from Twitter.
I've been having a great time
tweeting about what a lefty
I am and getting
people mad.
People aren't fucking argue with me.
On that subject Ben, I just want to let you know this is no disrespect
but I find that so
tasteful that I just have muted you
and have no interest. You've muted me?
I had no choice Ben. You've muted me because
I made like six tweets in the past week
are you kidding me?
Ben, okay here's the thing, maybe you should blame Twitter
because for some reason at the top
of my feed out of chronological order
it just kept showing
like one of your particularly
political tweets and I was like well I don't want
to deal with this, what are my options here?
I make one every like two days
one every two days for the last week
or so. That's a completely valid
move Nate. I haven't done it to Ben just because
I haven't done it to Twitter. I do not apologize
at all. I'll mute whoever the fuck I want
anytime. Twitter is for my fun and
enjoyment so I make no apologies
but that's the thing. But Twitter is not fun
I agree with my sheet
but it's not a good time. I disagree Ben.
I go there to have a bad time and make sure everyone else
is having a bad time too.
For me, who I follow on Twitter
is a bunch of people I generally like
not everybody 100% like people like
all of you who I like basically everything
you do and I retweet a lot of it because it's fun
and good and I like people to see it
and then also like anime cat girl bots
these are the things I follow
and they bring me such joy
and so Twitter for the me is mostly just a great
time and you know what
maybe I'm just not the right audience
I'm just saying this is a consequence
of the you know
of the political spin here. The main thing
I think of when I'm like should I delete
Twitter? Probably not
is that I follow a few artists
and I like when I see good art
and I want to share it with the people who follow me
and
it's like you know it's a nice feeling
to share someone's art when it's good
and to just see
oh there's a new Jade Maraud tweet
I like her stuff every time
but I don't see it posted anywhere else
and I don't really follow her in other places
so I'm like
I don't know
it's convenient enough
to keep around
I think I maybe should just unfollow
everyone who says words
I mean kind of
and I know that I too do this
so I would not blame people
if people just don't want to hear me say any thoughts
I totally get it and I would say then yeah
absolutely unfollow
whatever it's not a pure just fun
time all the time
Honestly I think a lot of my
disfun comes from
very structural foundation
things about Twitter
I'm thinking right now what if I had a Twitter
that was just
literally all images
and they were all drawing some artists that I liked
and I'm imagining on that white
Twitter page just scrolling down
and I just can't help but think
I would still feel terrible
using the light theme
what is the light motif
yeah something like that
I think I switched to dark but whatever it doesn't even matter
I would still feel bad
because I just don't want to just
it just feels unproductive
it feels like even
more terrible than like watching
something
it feels like
you're doing cookie clicker
but if you get more cookies
you get internet cookies
I mean at this point
watching an anime
for example for me feels like
homework
for me I'd just rather read a manga
because it goes way faster and feels like less of an obligation
I feel like Twitter is like a similar
sort of thing that it's just like
it's one level easier
than like now we have all the media we can consume
infinitely at our fingertips
but like Twitter's faster, Twitter's like easier
let's just go there, that'll be like more
you know fast results
to my brain stimulus
I just hate scrolling down, not in like a physical way
like I just don't want to scroll
but it just makes me feel like
I'm a fucking soulless automaton
well look, I hear you
I still think there are good things
for example, shout out to
Ukrainiansagok at black
s-e-a-a-m-s
something like that, I just posted a link
to a thing, Ukrainian, yeah
look at the disgusting gross audio links
just look at this one tweet, just says enormous
and it's an old school anime
robot guy just oozing power
this is what I like to see
this falls into my anime cat robot group
it's just lovely old anime
images that he posts screencaps of all the time
and it just brings me a little bit of joy to see
this is what I like Twitter for
to see shit like this
he posts stuff like that
in the discords that
I'm in, that he's in
so like
I don't know, I mean it's good for me
it means I don't need to follow him on Twitter
I can ask him, like hey
send me some funny things and he'll do it
I just, I just
I'm just over here saying
I started first, I'm just over here
I want to quickly say I'm just over here
I'm going, I'm going
yeah I have to, I have to, I'm sorry
I need to go, it's okay though
just sorry for
pay docked, you gotta pay
understood, say why
why you gotta go, what the fuck
I gotta go, I did say in it
I don't mind not getting paid, it's fine
it's okay, have fun guys
later
is it private, you can just go, okay
alright
do we bully her too much, I'm so sorry
I don't think so, I hope not
I hope not
well whatever
triggered by Twitter
well I guess, you know
Twitter is lame, art is lame
I hate images, I hate going on Twitter
and seeing images that I like
I am having a great time
I'm having a great time
going on there
saying an opinion
and having people be
and having an outpouring of yes
I agree with this and I hate you
you're an idiot for thinking this
that is stimulating to me
maybe I'm just weak, but I don't get much joy out of that
I don't know
I don't think it's like a strength to enjoy
indulging in stupid
shit
it's not stupid shit, it's about
saving the world
one tweet at a time
just manipulate people with your comics
that's the best way to do it
I do think that's the best way to do it
to package an ideology in some
consumable media, I think is pretty effective
alright, that's fair
I'm scrolling down and it's literally all in Japanese
and all the images that I like and I'm still unhappy
well that's why I'm bummed
that's why I'm bummed that you've muted me
because now that I am drawing comic pages again
and every time I finish a page
I tweet like, hey it's on the Patreon
new page up early
for patrons at patreon.com
that's true
I don't know, I'm sure I'll get you back
frankly you're one of my favorite people to follow
historically, but I don't know
I pretty much like all your shit
as has been, I've been pretty vocal on
but whatever, I mean you're not like some of these other people
who have just always been annoying
shout out to my boy
what's his name? Econ
an eternal mute
if there ever was one
but uh
I like
I know, but I have muted him historically
a couple times because he will go on some
tears, he will go on some
tweets, he will go on some tweet rampages
indeed, from time to time
what, Munchy?
number one
what do I call myself as a
binhead patreon bin saint fan?
I think a saint head
I think bin head rolls off the tongue better
I think saint head
I like the sound of it better
personally
I'm a clergy member, that's more thematic and funny
as opposed to saint head
what about a victim of
pre-sexual molestation
I don't know
also totally unsubstantiated
also, by the way
so
as a saint head
I always see
vapor's pages
posted and emailed to me
I could update from patreon and be like
hey, here's a new page and I always check them out
but I have to wonder
why aren't you putting them on your website
so normal people can see them
and you get bigger
let me speak
for the voices of the non-patrons
I've never patroned anyone in my life, I speak for the normos here
and
it's true, but I see you post
all the time, or maybe more in the past
but whatever, I see you post like, hey, new page on my patreon
become a patron
totally understandable but
that does nothing for me as a non-patron
I think you're possibly
somewhat handicapping your reach
by giving some preview
to people in some way
I don't know exactly what would be the best way to do it
the way you do it, that's what
it's like, you post a page on patreon
then maybe like a week later you post it publicly
so like, if you're a patron
you still get that bonus of it being like
oh, I got this on the inside, like I'm up to date with the bin saint lore
I know what's going on
that's reasonable, I suppose
you got your eternal stingy fucks like me
who just will never pony up the dollar
that's why you make it public
so that you can still have benefit
no one can market to you then
well, you'll never get my money
but you will get my
support and my spreading of the content
so that's something that you can leverage
you can get, I'm not a patron to Ben
but I did buy
the vapor's kickstarter book
that's the sort of thing
I'll put money down for
rather than a recurring payment
buy a cool thing
so if people know about
and like your comic and more people are fans
that's just better
the biggest currency
someone in your position has to trade in Ben
is awareness
yeah, attention, exactly
so putting that first
my rationale
maybe it's good, maybe it's bad
but I like
and I want the
well, like
you know
when I work for a long time
and I release a full comic
like Vapors 3, done
one of these days I'm gonna say
guys, this Friday
Vapors 3, it's coming out this Friday
and then on Friday, bam, Vapors 3, it's out
it's sort of an event
and I've looked at my
website analytics or whatever
and on those days
I get a big spike
and sometimes
my viewership stays
a little elevated after that spike
and I don't know
I'm sure there's an argument to me
that maybe if I spread that out
there'd be a lot of smaller spikes
and maybe viewership would grow
over the long term, I don't know
good or bad in terms of that business model
I know I would do something similarly
because I feel so
I want my videos
and my artistic creations or whatever
to be released in the way that I want them
to appreciate in that way
so with patrons, that's one thing
but I sympathize
when I first started doing the whole
comics thing, I thought
I don't really like reading
one page at a time
you've championed that
I like reading something in one big chunk
the whole story is one story
I want to consume the whole thing in one
blast because that's really how it's meant to be consumed
not one page every week
here's a thought
and I was just going to say on top of that
also, releasing
an early two patrons
is something that I do for my patrons
I would think it's good to offer
something
and then that's one of the things
just to confirm
none of Vapor Chapter 3
is on your website, none of it, correct?
that's right and there is
not an unsubstantial amount
of pages that you've released to patrons
so imagine you're a Ben St. fan
who likes your comics, likes the Vapers
but maybe you aren't as initiated
as
maybe some other St. Heads
or maybe you just don't want to patron someone
from their perspective, Ben St.
has not released a comic page
since the champion
since the champion ended
well, I mean
there was nuts the beginning
if you want to count that
okay, sure
then yeah, you're right
so I think
again, there's a middle ground here
I think it would be
I don't know if there is a middle ground on this
I don't think it's necessarily a bad thing
that it just comes randomly
at some point because like
with animators on YouTube
that used to be like they would do nothing
and then suddenly there was a new video
and you're like, oh cool
it wasn't like a detriment
some people would get mad
that somebody didn't upload
like Egoraptor didn't upload enough animations
and they left
and I never understood that mindset
but I guess some people are like that
where if they don't get a constant feed of information
they're just going to be upset
I mean I don't think people will be too upset
at someone like with Ben's release model
because I think they're relatively used to
like the long delays between stuff
so it's a different-ish sort of thing
but I mean on the subject of
something of a compromise
here's a thought
I think it is something of a problem
even George R.R. Martin
has released like sample chapters
of Winds of Winter and I think that's
helps him
here's a thought
maybe either like releasing a page as a tease
to give some general maybe something like that would work
or perhaps
when you tweet
when I see those tweets that are like hey
new page is available to my patrons
and I have the idea of having like a
just like a screen cap not of the whole thing
but of like one little highlight
of the page to be like a tease almost
to be like hey you could see this
and so much more
if you're on board with this shit
that I think would do a lot for me because I have not seen
new Ben comic
for I don't know what a year or something
now and I would love to
I'm very excited to see more
so something like that might both drum up
I mean it could persuade me I mean potentially
think about it like this
or just to pay more attention
I would wager to say
that blank
that blank Patreon link is not very appealing
indeed
I would wager to say that a lot of people
do not think of you
as primarily a comics
artist in a lot of ways
that's true and it's partially my fault
because your other work is
so much more visible
and so
much more frequent
Ben St. is far more
of a streamer or a
video essayist than he is
comics and I don't even think that's
because it's wildly that you produce
these things more though you do obviously
but just that they're so much
easier to get to people
than your comics because they're just
behind the Patreon wall
and not as many people
see it as
probably want to see it
I mean some of this is inevitable
I mean a lot of people would want to see it more
than just our Patreon too
I mean it's a platform
problem right
my Twitch streams
are on Twitch
and you know people are on Twitch
I got like a thousand and some change
followers on Twitch there they get notifications
my Youtube videos
are on Youtube
that's where people are
it's definitely part of that
are on my website which does not have a subscribe feature I think it's definitely
something to be said that if you release more on there there will be more
traction I haven't I haven't released I've been releasing my old pages on
line webtoon I'm trying to get online webtoon and when I start releasing
Vapors 3 I'm gonna be releasing them on Topastic again which I do I always
forget I have like I have like six thousand five or six thousand followers
on Topastic that I just forget about yeah it's not bad I don't even think about
their existence ever I was thinking about like in terms of like websites and
retention and people going to your website I was I was thinking about like I
want forums back I want I want to bring a forum I want to make a forum on APS
adventures dot site where I like I do like most of my notifications and
stuff and maybe even I mean like I have a community on Discord but they are
mostly just chat about nothing like if I had them to like if there was a
reason for people to go to my site just for no reason just to hang out then it
would be better for me in every way when I made my website peep like like like
webs like how-to sites on the internet as well as like individual people that I
talked to about it like I heard a lot like you got to have a comment section
like you got to put a comment section under your pages so you can see so people
can discuss and shit and I thought about that and you know I have I wouldn't say
I have a huge readership even right now and you know back then it was much
smaller and I just I just thought about well two things one I thought about all
the all the shit that we say about like the comment section under a YouTube
video being a part of the experience it's a part it becomes a part of the art
if you put it there right and apart and it's a part that I don't have control
over and no I don't want that I want your site is very clean and well I I totally
value you know the utility of comments I it is it would you know it would mess
with the aesthetic of the site which I would mess with the aesthetic of the
site of the site of the site it would affect the message of what I'm trying
to put there would affect the experience I'm trying to give the reader or
whatever and I don't like that furthermore I just thought back to all of the
like modestly known web comics that I've ever seen and unless you're huge you go
to a website for a comic and you look at down at the comments and it's like zero
comments on bait if you like if you got one if you got one on every page even if
you're a popular web comment you'll have just zero comments and it's just a bad
look and embarrassing Frank yeah I even though it happens to like everyone it
looks bad and I don't want to look bad yeah it makes you it makes you feel it
makes you look like nobody is reading and therefore it's like going into a shop
where there's nothing on the shelves yeah even if people are reading it's like
well why would you post a comment on like every page like maybe you'll have a
bunch of comments on like the last page or the first well Ben clearly you don't
get over to my and visit my friends on I don't know what it like dojin moe no
that's not it like an ex hentai.com where you'll see just some some some real
troopers commenting on every page oh yes I would also like to do this to my
sexual partner ah yes that that also was the good sex right there.
If I had one.
Oh us gamers am I right?
I completely empathize with like wanting to have things be a big block you just drop
and it has a huge impact but I just don't think that that's valuable.
I mean Munchie might just be right that like no matter how you want to do it I
mean I get that like there's no reason for me to make like big videos that take
a long time it's just a mistake but I'm going to keep doing it anyway because I
want to so I mean on YouTube the algorithm specifically rewards frequent
content I think well I think the algorithm rewards that because that is it
kind of ties into human nature like people get hype for for regular we
Aguas yeah that's true and when you know I mean you leave a little trailer for
the last one that you did the Kingdom Hearts one I think like that was yeah
like that build-up hype people are waiting for it but it's it's only like
they were expecting it because you used to post it weekly and that that's in the
name and it's kind of a joke that it hasn't been weekly but playing the hype
is a dangerous thing to do because it risks the the the the possibility of the
bubble bursting that's true you can build a pipe for a while and if you pay it off
well the rewards are sweet but you run the risk of very easily waiting too long
and then no one cares that's why that's one of the many reasons why you don't
talk about what you're doing until it's like done yeah like you don't you don't
promise a thing until it's like beyond a shadow of a doubt that it is going to be
delivered yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah cuz if you know I should say yeah if you
if you hype yeah hype you know it's that thing about like investigator like
any day now guys I'm sure just like I'm pretty sure I oh well no that's not yeah
okay you know when you when you I mean there's the thing it's like when you
talk about what you're working on you get that emotional release as though you
had shown it to someone as though it were done which kills your motivation to do
it and also the fact that yeah if you don't end up doing it so so it makes you
less likely to finish it and then if you don't finish it it is emotionally it is
damaging to the people that were hyped and are now disappointed and it's like
emotionally damaging to you I don't know about you guys I mean I'm sure you
get this as well but like I love I to a to a what's the word I supposed to a
problematic degree probably I love keeping my projects completely under wraps
or as much as possible and then just complete like t-bap resurrection for
example look took a look like we sure we were not working on it the entire time
you know steadily but like little bit of time really talk about it we I mean I
avoided discussing any details basically tension and I'd like to be cryptic and
not give any like exact dates as to like when we expect I've done that before
it's a mistake I still do it occasionally I like that too I think that
vapors 3 is going to be I think people really will really like it and I have
been saying that I'm doing it for a while but I haven't I mean I might have
spoken a little bit about it on a stream here or there to like that's a pretty
small chunk of the people that will end up reading it when it comes out so I'm
yeah I get it it's cool it's cool to be cryptic and I think when people read it
they'll be surprised and I think there's value in that and yeah so I just look at
how great t-bap resurrection turned out with all the all the I mean the dope-ass
intro that we were so hard to make and then like the ending with our multiple
Mr. X like new characters showing up for the ending with a risky business and
then our live-action segment at the end it was just a real layer cake of
deliciousness and to have spoiled any of like that the image of Ben and me
looking at the camera your two fathers caught you masturbating you know that
look yeah it's a great it's a great image I see people using it it showed up in
the dating sim it sure did it instantly became a little bit iconic it
absolutely did and like I wanted to tweet like like when I was first editing
like six seven eight months ago I wanted to just do something with that image but
I mean it was not hard for me to say no no no I must wait I must wait there will
be a time when this you know pays off I'm I'm glad the conversation has gone in
this sort of artistic direction because the thing I wanted to talk about today
was some data on on Andrew Hussie and the comics he's written compared to mine I
went and looked at the the dates that his comics were published well pages were
published and of Homestuck of all of it all of the things I got the numbers
how to break it down so jailbreak is first little one 134 pages drawn across
two days so that was that 134 pages and no not not hippo Hussie yeah I know but
wait he drew 134 pages well yeah I mean jailbreak is very simple this very much
stick figures that's pretty impressive that's still that's still a lot yeah it
is yeah it's pretty good problem sleuth 1,700 pages a lot of them in very
impressive gifts drawn in one year exactly mm-hmm 1,700 that's like three
yeah three days the two yeah something like that and yeah a lot of them are
huge yeah projects in and of themselves okay that's when he really got into his
style of like the what we see later of Homestuck where he has his character
assets and will like move them around and it becomes easier to produce fast I
mean I just that's good he did that that's yeah yeah cool and then all right
I've made a little graph for Homestuck because we all know the Homestuck
declined in speed at least indeed the first year was 1,668 pages the second
year 2,048 the third year 1,005 1,014 1417 I can't read numbers for the fourth
year and then it was like yeah 5,600 with year 5 yeah act 6 happened at the big
like somewhere in year 3 so like the first two are you fucking kidding me
that's when act 6 started oh yeah yeah disaster so like x6 was you know this
took a long time like what's the word epic exponential growth meme are you
guys laughing yet are you laughing for these last five years yeah I mean it was
very impressive especially since you know act 5 he adds so much color and it's
the feature all of the things get so good but that's the year he does most of
his work like the speed is at the highest like cascade is in year 3 so yeah
imagine we just gotten like two extra not bail james but problem sleuths
instead of all of act 6 what a great lifetime that would be pretty sick that
would be the brightest time line and then and then I went over to my to my
images because I hadn't been like well I'll just say that the numbers first
a canon story my first thing 141 pages so very similar to jailbreak and that
took like two hours to draw that in a stream and maybe one day to like write
all the texts so that's pretty good jail bail jpe which is the big one that I've
been working on is only like 367 pages one of which is a video game so that's
pretty cool indeed but it was started according to when the first image was
created around the 8th of February 2018 so it's been more than a year almost a
year it's been yeah that's barely that's barely a page a day you hack I know it's
well I mean for first part of that it was me trying to juggle that and
hypocrite videos and then also I have other things going on but I really I
was looking at all these numbers I'm like bail jpe is so small it's such a
tiny little thing I really gotta do bigger faster work but I don't feel too
bad because unlike a hussey in in bail jpe I I got tired of like copy pasting
the it's strange to say but like copy pasting like images and on layers was
more of a hassle than just drawing a new layer for each panel so I just drew
them all in uniquely individually and then I'm finishing it off with kind of
an overblown animation it's not like beyond my capabilities but it will take
a few few weeks sure sure but yeah art I was so fast he was too fucking fast yeah
I faster his own good I think a lot of this is not being focused like you said
you for a lot of that you were you know you had hypocritical and even now
there's something to be said that when you are in the sort of work that we are
and you had the sort of disparate projects that we do it's very easy for
you to be paralyzed by indecision and for you to have a lot of little things
that just sort of feel like they're bigger deals than they are for instance
if you're been you might have been for a while maybe you didn't have necessarily
anything on your plate they had to do that day but you always had ten paces
and draw over your head thinking oh maybe I should do that today or maybe I
should do papers three today there's so many things you were keybabs and whatnot
or tea or tea bath yeah stuff like that just a ton of things that you could do
and that makes it so it's hard to do any one of them because you're just thinking
what am I gonna do well maybe I will watch this YouTube video maybe that's
what I'm gonna maybe I'll just play enter the gungeon for 12 hours yeah maybe
we'll just do that it's easy for you if you haven't clearly defined what work
you're going to do what kind of stuff you're gonna accomplish each day it's
very very easy to just sort of fall into a routine of doing a whole lot of
nothing but still feeling overwhelmed I felt this a lot even recently yeah where
there wasn't a lot of like stuff that I was even doing but it was so easy to
feel overwhelmed like there was so much on my plate just because there was so
much stuff being unfinished because they're all just at the same time stuff
I know I have to do and just I felt that way for a long long time and and now
that my you know now that teabab and and ten paces are done I'm really not
eager to start anything new I really am so relieved I've kind of I kind of quit
the poo videos I don't know if I'll go back and finish yeah I don't know if I'll
go back and finish season one I had like maybe two more episodes of that that I
might make but I kind of don't want to think about it right now I just I'm
really happy that like the first three is the only thing that I have on my plate
and but speaking I'm totally with you but actually this circles back to hey
remember how it was discussion at the beginning of the episode I said I put a
pin in something that I wanted to say but I had not said it but I did in fact
write it down and I just want to talk about very briefly just in you know as
Ben was saying just now that yes when you're trying to come up with a project
and like when you're trying to schedule and plan what comes next that's the
hardest thing to do but I feel such a euphoric freedom when I simply have
intelligently or not committed to the project I'm doing and said I don't care
a meteor could fall outside my house could be burning around me I don't care
I have my project I am free I just need to work on this one thing nothing else
matters right now it is kind of my favorite feeling in the world and as soon
as the project's released that feeling lasts a few minutes and that's like
shit think about my next fucking video now damn it feels good it feels good for
a moment and that's like oh but it's that's why I'm that's why I like it
feels so good to be out of the YouTube rat race the the the no more chasing the
algorithm the fact that you have to be consistent to I mean production algorithm
right of like I mean I just mean as soon as like any projects done it's time to
move on to the next project just in life right I suppose I mean I'm kind of
excited about bail jpeg being done so that I can move on to the next thing
rather than you know well I mean it's not like doing the animation is boring or
I hate it I like it it's just also the idea I mean I was reading like looking
at the the time in between problem sleuth and Homestuck it was just like a
couple days just like you finished you finished the the problem sleuth and he
did some epilogue pages and introduced the midnight crew in one of them and
then he was just like yeah I'll just start Homestuck I had this idea for a
while and they started it and it you know it just kept going like every day
there'll be like five six images and you know the first year it got all the way
up to Jack ascend like imagine that right I'd non-stop not a single day was
messed I checked every day there was at least an image a page that's like hey
yeah that's I want to do that I would I would yeah I would love to be I would
love to be like that hey I'm just curious does anyone know was was Hussie
like able to successfully like live off his work specifically during not bail
jpeg but but during problem sleuth is he like full time at that point he had an
audience yeah but I I mean but was it monetized like I like live he had ads
yeah I assume he was making his money through ads and I mean this was I mean I
think ads were worth more back then I mean he had enough clout by the end of
problem sleuth to start making books didn't he's my real question I don't
think I don't think he made books until Homestuck was well oh well maybe this
this may or may not be the case what I'm really asking is like was he having to
like do a day job in addition to doing this I think you must not have he must
not have had a day job if he could have uploaded every no I feel like not I you
know maybe you're remembering wrong but I remember something about him like living
like kind of low budget like all he needs is a computer and his tablet and
he can just do anything he's just like me he's just like me indeed yeah here's my
message just to the people on that subject though I mean Hussie had to work
his way up I haven't followed his career extensively in his early days but I mean
for me it's very much if you want to be an artist guy I mean we all feel this all
the time just that we wish we had more time wish you had more hours in the day
to do stuff I mean I have basically you know whatever I've been doing YouTube
like part-time essentially for the last four or five years whatever and it's just
I feel such a desire to just be able to throw all my you know force into it I
feel like I can just explode and do all these great things once I've made the
time and I'm just like but that's on me I gotta figure out a way to get there
that you know will let me continue to live and frankly you know I'm not like
Ben I don't want like I need a decent amount of money to have a decent ish
life not that whatever I'm not even joking about bed like I'm just I'm
simply saying my I want a little more that's fair although more money would
help of course patreon.com spent I feel I sometimes I worry that maybe this meme
that I am a that there's not even untrue meme that I am that I am like a low rent
like like you know what do you call it scowl ag something like yeah it makes
makes makes people feel like oh well he doesn't he doesn't need any money so I
don't support not true I do need money of course not a ridiculous amount but
more than I currently have would be really nice okay that's fair yeah okay
patron.com is not a joke ladies and gentlemen this is not this isn't your
dad is in fact deadly serious this is life and death yeah yeah I find extremely
useful and I have just just a few days ago when I was organizing my my schedule
as I mentioned previously I think it's very helpful to literally write things
down to very absolutely just completely black and white what am I doing what
projects am I currently producing right now and I do that with my whiteboard I
not to belabor the point not to belabor the point I also want to say that this
past month my pay is a couple of big patrons reduced pledges and my rent
went up for unrelated reasons fair enough save me help please okay well I'm
still paying shit room rent because I still have the shit room but one of the
guys who was living here left and we did not find a replacement so I've mentioned
it to him I don't know if he could afford what we would charge for a room but
he didn't put the he didn't close down the possibility but I mean he doesn't
need a room right now he don't think he'll need one for a little while so
that maybe we'll see yeah I don't know fair enough I don't know okay sorry to
interrupt oh god I think it's good to because most of the time when you feel
overwhelmed and you think oh god there's just so much I have to do in
actuality there's not and it's not that you're you're stupid it's just that it's
easy for the human brain to get overwhelmed by uncertainty so in order
to be certain just write down the projects that you are working on and when
you can remove some of the boats some of the stuff that you don't have to do and
just kind of focus on those things it becomes so much easier for you to focus
on oh actually there's nothing I can do if I just allocate time here and there
oh wow look at that I've accomplished my goals you just have to be certain on
what you're working on you just have to remove uncertainty you know you can move
in decisiveness this isn't exactly the same thing but as just so this isn't
about exactly managing tasks that lie before you but actually what I did the
other day was just out of the blue I decided to make a list of all my total
life goals and this was spurned on by I watched PewDiePie's video that was it
was like another googling himself and I'm surprised about how frankly he talks
about like how much money he has and I mean he was just like I mean it's not
secret or anything it's not really a secret I mean the the figures are like
wrong but he was like yeah I think my net worth you know like those like what I
probably like 20 million or something and I was like well shit there you go I
guess these are the facts yeah and I've actually learned a lot I actually from
PewDiePie I learned about CPM or whatever like cent per meal or whatever
it's like a European thing like per meal as in per thousand right yeah that's
right that's right yeah and actually just incidentally I don't know if this is
true for everybody but I make the most money from Australian views so for every
like thousand views from Australians who watch ads on YouTube you make the most
per capita or you make the most total well I mean per capita not not total
because like it's I've like 59% of my viewers are from the US and like Australia
is a I'm just saying if everyone moved to Australia that would increase my income
so I really appreciate that if you would do that for for bin technique PCP HQ
Australia Sydney I know we don't want to move to what we want other people to
move to Australia because like right we want them to be exchanging their
currency with us at a favorable rate and some and maybe we would get new
Australian fans you hear about you hear about the Prime Minister did today I
hate them anyway I just I made a list of all my total life goals that the one
that spurred it on was actually that PewDiePie just said one of his life goals
is to own a house in Japan and I was like me too motherfucker me too so so that
became generally one of mine and I've just I've got a total of 14 yeah I mean
what of my what are my goals here I'm honestly shocked that he can't do that
right now the reason he can't is not money it's due to like like immigration
and visa issues I think specifically I mean which I'm sure in time he could
probably I'm sure he doesn't have 20 million dollars available right now well
you know what he said the issue was actually this was interesting he said
and yes he'd probably need to liquidate like at something I don't know also I'm
surprised I'm kind of surprised it's only 20 million I would guess me to me too
a little more than that but whatever but what he said the the real issue was
was that when it comes to getting a visa like claiming your you like you have to
state like your job and your intentions when you travel internationally and
stuff yeah and so like when he puts down his his employment he's a youtuber and
he said that first of all like youtuber isn't a real career in like in the eyes
of Japan particularly and also the Logan Paul shenanigans have given
youtubers a really bad okay so actually affected immigration issues wow in his
eyes I mean maybe that's not a hundred percent accurate but that's you know
that's what I mean it doesn't that's not inconceivable that's not I mean I've
heard of Japan's serious immigration at one point I was thinking maybe I'll move
to the to the US yeah but it's the same sort of problem like I can't get in
because I'm a youtuber I don't mean no immigrants my dude we've had enough of
those although you know soon I can now say that I'm a writer instead cuz that's
true that's true income like I mean couldn't you could call yourself a
freelancer I mean as long as you report your income wouldn't that be Japan is
very strict I mean Japan regulates its population pretty strictly when it comes
to immigration and stuff so like maybe who knows like exactly what their
process entails they maybe they want like an interview and they want to know
like what who you are what you do and like significant detail I don't know I
don't know boy okay I understand that but surely
Japan must realize who PewDiePie is on some level not as in like the
immigration officer like watches PewDiePie but surely he's like he's the
most famous person on he's like famous famous well are you guys aware that not
only was PewDiePie passed by T-Series recently so he is no longer number one
I saw that he released a video a celebration music video today called
congratulations to T-Series where he snidely congratulates them in hopes that
they're decadent you know giant corporation that somehow managed to
defeat one Swedish boy that they're myriad corruption scandals and me too
if she's happening to not tragically wouldn't that just be so sad pretty
funny I got I got me too by T-Series
I got me too the other day what a fucking what a nightmare what a life
yeah indeed indeed but but you know just to back to the point making a list of
life goals was good and helpful it's I'm pretty good at making task lists I do
it not every single day but frequently when I have like 20 things to get done
in a day and they're not even big the only way I can do it is to make a list
and then I like if they're fast and easy I will burn through those motherfuckers
tell me tell me if this is relatable to anyone or am I a freak my if I think if
I wrote down my list of life goals every single thing on the list would be a
thing I want to make and nothing else mine or more about well I mean I don't
know like my number one rule my number one life goal is to like be morally
upright and I put when in doubt adhere to the golden rule so like that's the sort
of goal I'm keeping in mind just like a way to live in general okay but a lot of
a lot of my like big dream thoughts is to be someone who's like you know
obviously I like doing the art that I do but but in the back of my mind I'm
like ah if I was a good enough artist I could like be friends with Andrew Hussie
oh I could I could talk to them and be like cool and like I'll be I'll be one
of those those you know the mysterious elite artists who talk to each other I
assume yeah you know okay now that you say that that I also aspire to that to
be to not just be cool and glorious myself but to like but to travel in
circles you know what I almost tweeted the other day I whatever I was like
busy and didn't but I was this is my tree I was gonna tweet like for some
happiness is like I don't know like a walk on the beach whatever blah blah blah
but I say happiness is measured by the number of secret backroom executive
boardroom meetings you are in over the course of your life relative to the rest
of the population to me that's happiness that's you know that's true okay it
feels cool to have like a secret meeting that people will not know about
indeed indeed by the way but here's their here's your visual people the visual is
the the meeting in godfather number one when you know Vito Corleone meets with
all the heads the five families at the tail end of the film that is what I
aspire to in my life I want to be there oh yeah things things of that nature
like every time I have like a meeting in about like the movie I'm making and
there's like an important person there and like a producer is like oh you know
this is this is like something's happening right here things are being
things are being said you talked to somebody pretty big the other day I
forget who maybe you don't want to say was that a Mike Cooper he's a feature
director feature animation guy at Ardman he was as is that the wall he was a
Wallace and Gromit guy right am I not the Wallace and Gromit guy he was also
called Mike but you know one of the big guys old guy was given info feedback on
the script and we we talked about stuff he looked at your script and gave you
feedback on it that's pretty dope dude and and then we had dinner later and it was
like that was like a business trip I went on a business trip to Scotland that was
like the coolest thing that's dope dude that's so that's so romantic and sexy
hippo totally yeah you should you should shag a Scottish last like the
Pokemon Sword and Moon yeah cloud cloud and hopper what the fuck it's called
did you what's what's the hat uh yeah cloud and hopper that's what I said
getting that fucking goo goo machine like all the Scottish yeah but she's got
she's got that sex she's got that cute Shalely on her head yeah yeah yeah that
that hijab yeah yeah gotcha okay uh yeah it's excellent I'm glad we're all on a
on a projectivity mindset today I'm glad we're sure about this I've been thinking
about constantly I just made this is just a small thing but like I've I really
have committed I'm a little bit late on my new we Agua but I have after after
what else is new I know after the power creep arc is indeed over it's true like
I've got a we Agua in the editing bay just needs a you know a day or two left of editing
and it will be out and I've also got the next one already not feeling like ready to go
knowing what I'm doing you gotta commit to we Agua I I'm effectively committing to we Agua
and I'm sure I'll reference that in some way so it is it is what is happening so uh
another logo coming up I say you know tightening my own chains around my own neck
it's a totally new show we Agua's dead long live we Agua totally new original idea I just came
up with I want to go back to when we were talking about Ben's comics I just want to say oh sure let's
do that uh that I was on st comics whenever we're talking about something like PCP I I just look at
it like pictures of whatever we're talking about on the internet I don't know why I do it
add to the show notes of course and and and I I clicked on the the vapors number one and I had
such like a visceral reaction like an emotional reaction to seeing the like first like title
screen title page cover page of the vapors by Ben saying and right it was almost like
this is so iconic I can't believe I'm talking to the person that made it in a weird way I don't
I don't want to turn this into a dick-sucking thing but like the vapors is like a real thing
that is so I don't even know what I describe it other than like like yeah like iconic it like
influential and like but it's not influencing anyone it just feels like legendary it feels it
feels mythical it feels like a legendary well I think what you're describing is that it feels
like a real big project with all the pop and circumstance that comes with that and yeah yeah
and it look at this page I have this page on my shelf right now like I have the physical version
of this comic thing I still want to copy I don't know the copy of the vapors well I can't believe
that it's it's real well fortunately when chapter three is done the Kickstarter for chapter two
will begin and in the Kickstarter for chapter two you will be able to buy bundles that include
the first book if you missed it the first time oh that does sound good uh yes I gotta start thinking
about that um I got I got I gotta start uh this is something you know I've been I've been chugging
along doing new pages and that feels good but in the back of my mind I've got that oh I need to do
some more shit I gotta I gotta think of I gotta write scripts for bonus uh vaporettes I want like
at least three probably more because chapter chapter two is shorter than chapter one and
I want to make up some of that length uh somehow wait is chapter three shorter than chapter two
or well it's not done I think it might be slightly longer than chapter two but not as long as chapter
one yeah okay I think uh we'll see something like that okay cool cool yeah right yeah yeah well I
think we're all in agreement that we all look forward to it very much uh yes um I feel like I
need to make my site more epic it feels pretty juvenile I my my site is so I'm you know I just
I made that thing with like such a basic understanding of like html and css it is
it's a I went back and revamped some of it it's it's functional and it looks decent
but the editing like like okay I know there are ways where I could have like automated the upload
process but one it is so inconvenient to update because like okay what what I need to do to it
is to make is to like enclose all the elements like the okay like the button bars for a long time
to change a button on the website I had to go through every page of the website and
manually update the button I change that for most things there are still a few things that are like
that I think and I could and I will fix those probably before I start uploading any more okay
I gotta up before chapter three comes out I'm gonna upload the um the um actually I should
do make these a patron exclusive I should make these like an early patron thing is the the the
vaporettes from the first book they gotta go on the website and I gotta and I gotta go through
the whole fucking thing and going through page by page and putting in the like when I put up a
new page I have to manually put in for example the numbers you gotta make some sort of database
indexing system or something that that's easier like put it like is each page has to link to the
previous page and the next page and the last page of the chapter and the first page of the
chapter and I gotta put those all in one by one and it's oh god it takes like it it's sometimes
it takes a day or two for the big update it'll take like an entire day or two just to put it on
the website um which you know could be improved some some to work on indeed yes indeed on the
subject of character specific interactions hippo I also want to ask you something about your comic
do you intend to always be the dude who makes homestuck like comics
no but I like I like it so I mean bell good place to start I suppose bell jpew is like
supposed to be that obviously with the name as well but I do have other types of comics
that I want to make so you're you're not intending to carve as much space underneath
Andrew hussey shadow as possible is what I'm trying to say no okay look at our boy toby fox
he's he's he's broken out and uh he's he's the role model here I'd say I don't want to underestimate
or underplay how much I love jailbabe and just even the way that it's produced I also want to
empathize the fact that I I too find the homestuck style very appealing and very much something I
would want to emulate for like like just the way that I work I feel it gels with me quite a bit
however I feel like there's something to be said that it just is no matter what it will almost
always feel and teeter on fan art jailbabe is not related to homestuck in any way but you can't
divorce from homestuck no matter what sure can't read it and not think about homestuck no matter
is it on is it on mspfa no okay I think somebody wanted to make a mirror of it
the I don't know what how I feel about that I am like I made a I made nuts the beginning
and I put that on mspfa not because it is particularly homestuck like but just because I
found that a convenient way to do the um the uh like timeline split yeah to have like multiple
endings I think there's like complete valid way in like the structure of homesuck I don't think
it's an inherently a wrong thing to do to have like you know you know not just like have it be a
text command parody but in the sense that you can have multiple pages and split paths and choose
your adventure like elements in there it's just I mean specifically with jailbabe I mean it's
literally on a website that's supposed to look like homesuck and it's called like APS adventures
or something to that effect it's literally called it's so similar I'm gonna you feel me probably a
good time to say that like I think when vapors three is done I'm gonna go back and I'm gonna go back
and finish beast capades which is um a much something that oh yes I'm very excited for that
yeah I was really excited about beast capades too the thing that excites me the most about beast
capades is that I don't think I don't think it was apparent like I don't think that the amount
of it that I did communicated where the story was going I don't think anyone probably could
guess where the story is going but the thing about beast capades is that it has an ending it has a
specific like ending in mind and I know mostly how it gets there and I am just really excited to
you know is this is this tell a story with a definitive ending and then you finish it and
you're like yes wow that story went places hey is this too much you know what I mean in terms of
like I'm curious I know these things always change but like if you had to guess what percentage of it
would you say like is complete now of beast that's a dangerous question to ask it is a dangerous
question to answer and I'm gonna preface it by saying I'm probably wrong okay like whatever I say
will probably be wrong but I think maybe 25% okay that's good that's good what you know locked and
loaded written down right now I mean it's definitely well it's definitely not halfway done yeah but a
big chunk of it is done so somewhere in that region so I'm just gonna ballpark it at 25% okay
I've been thinking about like the the whole like Homestuck Hussie's Shadow thing because like I kind
of do regret naming my website APS Adventures even though you know I don't really mean I mean hail
MS Paint Adventures is dead it's homestuck.com now so it is dead but the things that are called MSPA
still why did you say hail did I say hail yeah you said hail I think I meant I meant say like
hell I guess I just said I think you meant to say hell but you said hail I apologize to the audience
to the commander I was I was going to say I was going like hail okay sorry hail not yeah okay that
makes sense sorry I really like to be pedantic and point out when people pronounce things wrong
appreciate it appreciate point of order I'm like I'm like a game of order I'm so smart that I pointed
out that you said less instead of fewer relate to me audience point of order hypocrite I will be
hurt yeah I'm fucking I think I've lost the train of my thought what was I saying oh you're
regretting that you named it APS Adventures a little bit kind of oh yeah yeah I like um
I could you know quite easily just make a new site it would be a hassle and yeah I just call it
something else change the name of it I guess I could just change the name of it big floppy
dongs.com I'll be there I had a completely other point but I just I've lost it oh sorry we fucked up
guys yeah I mean I have the memory of a goldfish I have a cool thought but I can't write the yeah
whatever well let's talk about well let's talk about capitalism and it's many anyway back to the
vapors by me you know I do I do want to just quickly say I want to hurt all your feelings
real quick yeah and just this is we're getting a little hug boxy so I just want to retort with
all your efforts mean nothing if you can't survive off them I mean you can you can play in the sand
you can be a little sandbox baby who you know works like a normal job and then supports your
art on the back of that but until you go and you're you're a real boy a real survivalist
off of your art are you even a real boy are you even a real boy Gibb is because Gibb is a real
artistic job now but yeah for the rest of us we we've we've got some work all right I don't care
about that I've remembered what it was I agree with that okay atreon.com slash Ben saying to make me
a real boy the whole thing about staying in the house and yeah and stuff when I started it I copied
like the the arrow going forward and the text commands as if you were the characters just
because that's what he did and I thought it was funny but you know more recently I've been thinking
that is because he played games that were like that and I didn't do that I am doing that because
I'm ripping off Homestack not because I'm ripping off text-based adventures and it's the same thing
with like Hussie knows a lot of code and if I were to try and make coding jokes I wouldn't know what
I was doing yeah so like it would it would be like wrong so like going forward the things I'm
gonna base I mean I've already written a few stories that could be like novels rather than
comics anyway they're just like stories that work but the the way I'm going to approach them
regardless of what I whatever the site's called or like whether it's just one panel per page
because I just like that in general is that I'm going to base things off of things that I
grew up with and know about more so than you know good like um text commands specifically like the
idea of commanding the the person reading the adventure is uh uh commanding the character to
do stuff that's only because um the characters actually were being controlled by the viewers
with uh the prompts that the people were giving and I hadn't I hadn't done that and so it was really
just like very hollow very like um copying for no reason sort of thing so if if I ever copy anything
from Homestuck in the future it'll be because um not you know I will consider the usage or like the
reason Hussie did it in the first place right right including the fact that he made so many pages
and he had his characters uh you know reuse the assets because the reason he had that in the first
place was not because he can't draw like me it's because he wanted to have the fan interaction be
like a major part of the comic and the faster he can make the images in response to the prompts
the the more intense it would feel and that's why he wanted to to make it like that I feel like
Hussie you know if he makes a new thing he's not going to do the the command the prompts from the
viewers because he's done that to death and his art will be like completely different
from Homestuck which is probably why he's like apprehensive maybe to to do anything because
damn it you need to go go Toby Fox Hussie isn't he still well isn't he still working on um
Hype Swap he well I suppose he is yeah but that's almost sad to me I I feel like that's like
bolderline cancel Hype Swap yeah uh Hype Swap is in like I like it's so
long and so just I I I honestly see it being like a failed kickstart and I don't think it will be
finished it's it's so a dude whatever I think about the first chapter already came out and people
generally liked I mean I haven't played it and I feel honestly guilty about that but but why haven't
you played it Ben could it be because you just don't care anymore well I was kind of over it
and also or two not yeah like the fact that it's only the first chapter I'm like I'd rather
play the whole thing except the delta rune chapter one was hype as shit and was the
fucking dopest thing in the last several years I I can't help but when I think of Hussie I compare
him on every level to Toby Fox Hussie like did a huge kickstarter got complete he just fucked it up
financially stopped hurting Hussie's feelings I won't Toby Toby made like 50 grand made like the
biggest game of all fucking time as a first-time game developer fucking he went on but he's already
made his sequel thing and he's working on it sure it recycled some assets but it's fresh it's new
it's beautiful I love it I can't wait for more it makes me want to piss so badly yeah I have to
I don't know I don't know I know I'm getting a little bit over the top on Hussie I but it's just
that he hasn't the last thing I heard from Hussie was him making a game that I'm not interested in
and you know like kind of fucking up his legacy a little bit with like getting rid of msp a.com
and change it that's not a huge deal but then he just hasn't made anything new for me so I'm just
here like well I really liked Hussie but what do I got to I mean I imagine he's working in the
I mean he did that like kickstarted thing with drill like he and drill made you know that's true
that's maybe uh the the sweet bro and hello Jeff book which I wanted to buy I just I just didn't
I meant yeah same yeah same I got it I got you got it is a great spoon inside is it cool
um I like it but it the things that you you may have seen from uh like the previews of the art
yeah uh doesn't exactly look like the sweet bro and hello Jeff earliest comics it's more like the
later sweet bro and hello Jeff comics and we all love your comics yeah and and the whole thing is
pretty funny so I you know I feel and I got the fidget spinner you know I feel like it's worth it
did it come with a fidget spinner yeah I got the fidget spinner edition it's got like it's
got like the holographic film and and the angle at the angel of the book itself is like um
it's not at 90 degrees there's just sort of like on one of the corners it's like
an acute angle so it just sort of goes off in a weird direction it's hard to fit on the shelf
it's really funny I have I have a fidget spinner actually our our our mutual friend econ gave it
to me uh it's a sweet it's a sweet metal yin yang fidget spinner nice fucking sick and I just want
to let everyone know what a cool guy that was such a legendary piss I'm honestly mad that it
wasn't on the episode I'm honestly I didn't just take the bullet and do it on the it was I did it
for like it was insane it was insane was it just quantity was it the power behind it I mean both
it was it was a total package it was a total package was it one that was just like continuous
force the whole time yes ends abruptly yeah yeah doesn't just travel off trail off yeah yeah cool
all right should we go to voicemails do you think oh yeah no no no before we yeah before we go to
voicemails we should shout out the the pcp dating sim thing that came out yes okay okay thing about
that and I think this is just a me issue I am having trouble getting it to run I got it to run
every time I opened it it opens up this window it's a gray window that just says j s dot n w or
something like that yeah yeah and one time I got it to open and I played it for a while I did a
bunch of branches it was very amusing but then I I think I hit a bug or something or I got to a
something or the text wouldn't load some if the game it I got to a point where I seemed to not be
able to progress anymore so I closed it and then I couldn't open it again and that's and I'm very
upset that's too bad it was pretty cool and funny well let's okay let's start from the top here
people if you're not aware yesterday today's the 31st on the 30th at pcp dating sim that's them
they came in and they undercut at pcp dating who was making the initial pcp dating sim will be releasing
their demo tomorrow indeed tomorrow that's coming out by the time you're listening to by the time
you're listening to this you can play both and compare and contrast yourself indeed and it's
kind of erotically so so uh at pcp dating sim made theirs legendary they beat the other guys
epic joke and uh so it was made by no need bra and lumia stargazer so big shout out to those guys
they were I'm deeply impressed they they actually got this thing out and so I played it too so I
played it a bunch yesterday and I had a great time exploring all the different paths I mean it's
basically a game where you but we will absolutely put a link in the show notes to where you can get
this so go click on that download it um it's it's fun as fuck and uh uh you basically you
got to avoid the landmine deaths as you go through uh and you can make it all the way to the end
but what I did not discover uh until I was playing it again with Michelle later and we were trying to
do even more options there's actually some choices you can make early in the game that affect what
your ending is way later independently I won't spoil anybody I have a guess I have a guess about
what one of those might be okay but at I mean I only discovered we only discovered one when we
were playing but like at the end we we you discover uh let's just say an arch nemesis of all pcp dome
and uh uh that that encounter can be changed uh depending on uh uh you know what uh what's done
as you go through the game and uh it's super funny and hilarious and don't want to fucking beat it
I really want to play have the full experience shekels for heckles stream it pcb dating sim
dude that's not that's let's fucking do it's not a terrible it uh there's there's some hard
n words in there but you know I think we can survive that okay well we just we won't read them
aloud fair fair um it's not our fault we didn't know we didn't know I disavow I disavow we're disavowing
so hard guys throw the holy water I disavow but uh I mean it's great I mean I don't even I don't
even give a shit it's fucking hilarious every word of it is priceless and and it it's just it's
just such a legendary shitpost and the opening movie that these guys made at the very beginning
the anime intro is that like an incredible Gundam it's I think it's the original Gundam uh I think
or Gundam Z or I don't know I have no idea it seemed I couldn't make out the logo and I'm not a Gundam
boy uh anyway it was hilarious and dope play it every pcp member shows up um good good good and
it's there it's great yeah some of them are hard to find though so you gotta you gotta put in the
work to find them and uh the ending is truly hilarious um when you discover the greatest
podcast of all time but I'll leave that up to the viewers to discover so I don't spoil it for them
oh boy that's oh man this is there's more mysteries here than I realized yeah yeah I I gotta figure it
out I gotta figure out how to play this fucking game uh the rest of the way one time I don't know
what the fuck I don't know what I did the one time that made it work I yeah I don't know dude
I mean maybe just download it again would be fine maybe maybe have you given uh Munchie have you
guys played through have you done it yet no I I don't know I've seen screenshots though I know about
it yep I've played through I haven't got like multiple endings uh you die a lot uh there's a lot
of wrong decisions to make yes you do save often people save often uh I definitely encountered
some bugs hey here's a shout out to one bug to those guys it's probably too late to do anything
but when you talk to mage on the staircase uh as you leave Digi's classroom I think uh that's the
one that's that's why I had to restart the game that I just yeah the text just didn't load it just
doesn't load so uh yeah so I guess that's just a dead end probably probably okay well whatever
anyway the rest of it people go play it's legitimately hilarious and fun uh highly recommended
highly recommended yeah um and shout fucking the next p at pcp dating dropping tomorrow for us in
the past for you let's see maybe it'll be a joke it's April 1st what could that imply I don't know
we'll see I I don't know I talked I talked to it's supposed to be real I talked I talked to
Levent Hart who assures me with all possible sincerity yeah that it is not a joke that's what
they say and and that the April 1st release date is not meant as a troll and I mean we'll see about
that that's not really in doubt like if it I feel like I'll believe I'll believe it when I see it
I mean I feel like it would be very like stupid to to have a fake game on the April 1st I mean
yeah something will happen something will happen I think I said last time but I don't know what
something will definitely happen I think but I said last time that like we've talked about previously
in like April Fools I know at a million years ago on a piece of yeah I said we said like
the best April Fools jokes are when it's actually something like expansive and like actually fun
that no one expected and it is surprising and funny and perhaps foolhardy but it just like
is a real project that you can play and enjoy that's a real project not necessarily what you
expect yeah I mean if it would just turn out to be I don't know I mean fighting game honestly
if I were betting if I were putting my bets out I mean I think they're just going to release
an actual demo of the actual dating I agree I think that's the most likely that I think yeah
and by the way we have maybe a little bit insider information I mean some people on
I don't actually know who was on the team doing any of this I know only like one or two people
but like in the at the end of the pcp dating sim the the meme one that just came out those guys
go on to like it actually it's actually really sweet spoiler is this a spoiler no it's not really
a spoiler it's just that at the end they say like like they're like we're excited too for the bigger
pcp dating sim so like it's like an advertisement almost to hype up the big release of like the
demo or something and it's that that was so sweet that they that they put that in there
and uh I those guys might have insider knowledge I don't know I don't know don't know we'll find
out tomorrow and you people will know yeah all right I'm very I'm very excited I'm very you'll
definitely be able to find we'll retweet anything on the pcp at TP Krasnayers Twitter so go check
that if you're you know if you're looking for updates um okay we don't have to spend a lot of
time on this but I feel the need to respond to all the people calling me a fascist in the comments
last week uh okay for what purpose for what reason uh for because I was supposedly anti-free market
and more and anti mostly was an anti-free speech people people okay this would piss me off people
in the comments respond they weren't even generally making an argument like Ben what you are saying
is anti-free speech sure they were just sort of taking it as an assumption it's just like
so so Ben's anti-free speech and here's why I'm against that and and like like it's just the
base assumption and I just want to say that I fucking hate all of you because okay what we were
talking about everyone just fucking jumped in logic they made a huge fucking logical leap
we were talking about tom getting kicked off mastodon yeah we were talking about platforms
mastodon is a privately owned platform that people are in charge of and have the ability to curate
I'm I'm not talking about like making it illegal to be to to say the n-word or whatever but I'm just
like okay did you made all those rants he made all these videos he's talked so much in the past
about how you know it's his plat his youtube channel is his platform and it is within he
does not have to let you into his house and and give you a platform to say whatever shit if he
doesn't like it you know and that's true for all of us like if it's your platform you are not obligated
to let some what to let people say whatever they want to say even stuff that you disagree with
stuff you don't want propagated you're not obligated to give people a platform you know
with the tom example so I hear what you're saying and that's not a crazy point or anything
well let me let me let me just finish so the like the logical and I absolutely agree with that logic
and it's the the logical extension of that is that if someone makes a platform it's their platform
mastodon or twitter or whatever and you might not like it you might not agree with their decision
but they are not obligated to let people say stuff and if they believe that something is you know
a bad ideology to spread I do I think they are not obligated to let you spread it I think they
have every right to be like I don't like what this person is saying I don't like that they're
saying it on my platform get out go say it somewhere else I mean if I'm not mistaken with
that's not a legal thing that's not me talking about criminalizing or censoring like on a legal
bait that would be totally different well I totally fucking different I hear what you're
saying man uh so with the tom thing I think that with mastodon like with tom he was kicked out of
a group made by users and I you know I think those guys probably like it'd be hard pressed to say
are you not allowed to kick a friend out of your friend group or something I mean that's a little
you know that's not exactly their group so that's not even being kicked off the platform as I mean
maybe I missed something but I think that's it although okay maybe I misunderstood yeah I mean
the point still stands but whatever the thing about I'm fucking mad I hear you but the thing about
getting kicked off Twitter is like I mean so yeah so so Twitter's definitely a private platform and
the the thing people bring up about this is that like okay um it's fine that you know we've got
private businesses they can do what they want and all that they they don't have to platform users
they don't want to or whatever um but I suppose you have to think about like what the goal is so
like Twitter claims to be just for example a platform where like they want everyone to come
together and speak but and yet at the same time they go beyond that and they enforce policies
that favor some ideological groups you know over others and they say like okay but some
speech simply isn't allowed here so really what they're saying is that they actually aren't truly
going to welcome every type of speech here they actually have an ideological lean and like again
if you're talking about like a small group like this is like 10 people and they have their little
you know let's just say communist club or whatever and like you got a free market and
arco cap he's like I like this they're like get out you're not one of us like obviously that's
fine but when it becomes an issue I guess with the like the idea that this is the new open marketplace
and the Twitter claims to be a place for everyone to come and speak well here well here's a problem
and I think this is a problem that arises because capitalism sure and that is the fact that this
platform that is you know supposed to be a free marketplace of ideas or whatever is privately owned
they own it they made it they own it they get to say I don't think this type of speech is good and
I don't want it on my platform yeah I that's a fair point and it seems like the only real
ways around this are like I mean at a certain point you gotta ask like what's best for the
civilization and like this is what a government's for to keep things like getting crazy and out of
control so you know I'm not actually but let me go on let me go one step further and make
the argument that I think people last week thought I was making which I wasn't okay let me just go
right ahead and make it you're not allowed to run into a theater and yell fire we all heard this
example because that is a that's a harmful action that is false and deliberately harmful speech it
causes harm through you know it's it's engineered falsehood to create damage yeah that's true what
about someone going on the internet and spreading like bullshit statistics about like about like
white genocide and the great replacement or whatever and inciting like we need oh we need a
we need a piece we need a peaceful relocation of the jews I think that would probably help with this
issue look okay first of all then is that not is that not false harmful speech okay well you've
got to make a distinction I think it's disingenuous to say that those two claims are exactly equivalent
and I mean you'd probably agree with that I mean they're not the same act but I think they both they
have the same the same descriptors could apply to one versus the other that would qualify them as
you know not protect look legit like if you've got just I mean you know to try to you know
delocalize it from the hot button issues if you've got like let's just say I think this is a
politically incorrect word but whatever you know what I mean like the eskimo population
let's just say that they though like there's a there's an identity I think you're I think
Inuit oh yeah okay let's say you've got whatever I frankly I don't give a shit but whatever I
got you got you got the Inuit population and like among those people they've decided um like we
don't like let's say there was some Scottish people whatever they move they're like we are gonna we
believe that our society should be us and we do not like the Scottish influence that's coming in
and so we are going to enact a peaceful like you know like not again like because there's
there's various discussions about like what white identitarians or white nationalist want
or they want like buyout policies or like relocate like whatever it's just that like you
that the policy and the ideas by themselves like people are going to have these ideas in their
head and banning them from somewhere doesn't get rid of the idea so I think at a certain point you
need to think about is it actually a good thing to do to ban these people from the platforms is are
we doing any good to deradicalize and is is like them being present doing direct harm in the same
way that yelling fire in a crowded theater is and are you actually doing more harm than good I
I this is it's a tough thing and I think you have to balance all the elements in a conversation like
that and I again I'm no expert I'm a dunce about this shit I'm no policy genius there was a you
know there was a time there was a time when being on the internet yeah and being edgy and making jokes
about gassing the Jews was you know it was funny because of how audacious it was and it's like well
no one's actually going to do it so it's funny to say it yeah how ridiculous and then now here we
are in the year of our lord 2019 and you got you got open fucking rallies you got open white
nationalist rallies you got literal you got literal neo-nazis collecting in public and espousing an
ideology of genocide and I don't know that doesn't feel like it should be protected speech you know
I don't I don't think that's cool I think we are at a slightly different place I think you get to that
point and suddenly you gotta you gotta be like okay but are you allowed to advocate should you be
allowed to advocate for anything really so just to be clear you are in fact coming out to advocate
that some speech needs to be repressed and you're you seem to be making that claim I think I think
when your speech is we should we should do something about these Jews I yeah I don't know if I don't
know if I think that should be protected speech why is it better to force these people to not speak
publicly why is that a better solution they will that will not change their beliefs it will not
change their beliefs but are you saying because it won't spread the ideas yeah that like like
giving these people a platform spreads their ideologies and like they're advocating to like
hurt people but like that out there saying we should fucking hurt these people are you are you
allowed and listen your pretend what um conspiracy to commit murder is not protected speech why is
advocacy for genocide it's basically the same well okay roundabout way I think that you are
conflating a couple of things like I don't think that genocide look if you like if you're a serious
white nationalist for example and you want a buyout policy to buy out all minorities so
they will leave your country that is not genocide that is a white nationalism that is a different
thing who's talking about a buyout I've heard a Richard Spencer make that case for one okay well
I don't know well that's I mean I don't think that's what most of these people are talking about but
I mean I think that there's a lot of conflation going on and I think that the danger is when people
I and I think that you're a little guilty of this you're you're look yes there's absolutely
violence and you know identity and bad stuff that I am totally opposed but when you just I
feel like there's a grouping together of a lot of ideas here and saying that it all needs to go away
and it's all dangerous to even be allowed on the airwaves I just think that that enacting policies
to suppress that will do more harm than good and maybe I'm wrong and maybe I'm wrong about that
but that is my well you know what maybe maybe there's something to what you're saying can we
okay let's just okay what would you agree with me if what was being advocated for was just open
genocide you know okay that gets way closer to where I'm more likely to agree the only thing is
that like I don't know if it's really a great idea to govern based on specifically like beliefs as
opposed to action and so that I guess I kind of would like to I don't really know for sure
what I believe on that I can't say for sure I think it's a good idea to always ban it
because I I don't know it seems like that will definitely that still would lead to the same
problem that I'm talking about but maybe it's kind of worth it in that position I understand where
you're coming from yeah I understand the idea that like you know you know free marketplace of ideas
these people should be allowed to say what they're saying so purely pragmatically forget the
marketplace so that we can hear it and be like well that's bad but that's sure that's not that's not
always what's happening that's not always what happens I mean you're right but like that's the
thing these are these are like percentage cases right so it's about I think you end up in a game
of like if which choice does the least damage and like does the most good you have to like really
figure out the majority if if the overton window shifts like like if if these ideas get out there
and they get more popular and the overton window shifts more and more to the right and the majority
opinion the centrist opinion ends up being yeah we should get rid of these guys will we then be
saying boy I sure am glad I'm sure I'm glad that we let the marketplace of ideas decide what was
right for us because here we are we've accepted that that X group X ethnic group is bad and we
fucking got rid of them you know but I we fucking ended them I hear your point great I would make
two points one thought is that I think I'm glad we were so egalitarian about this uh okay I hear
your point and again that does make sense as well it's not unreasonable it's that that on the one
point I would make the case that I think that we are a long way away from something like that
but I understand people think that it's going to increment more and more so I get that yeah I mean
I don't think this is around the corner right yet but it's fair to say that like it's more
tax happened it's too close for comfort okay I mean I think that's you know whatever people
might feel differently about that but fair enough the other thing is I think that a large difference
between sort of more leftist and rightist thinking is about the emphasis being on
targeting a specific goal and then kind of advocating any policy to get there I think that's
kind of more like leftist thinking whereas I think more right thinking is about
implementing a system and again I don't mean to like load this more with moral stuff but like
implementing a principled system with the belief that like it will not you know lead to a bad
outcome and if you see that trying to correct the system when those such things occur and I
definitely sort of lean more towards that model of well let's let's let's let's implement let's
let's not let's just implement a system that will you know engender the jews getting the
fuck out of here you know we won't actually do it but I really think that's a pretty fringe
belief I and I get it it is a fringe it is a fringe belief but it's growing and it's there
it's there in the alt right but we'll it's undeniable it is undeniable will it ever go away
though is my question like will our struggles seem like it was away it seemed like it was gone it
was a joke and it's becoming less and less of a joke due to what I'm scared well look like I got
you Ben I I don't know I think we've we've covered decent ground I think that you and I are kind of
I don't know at the one point I don't love talking politics like this but the thing I think when Ben
and I discuss it hopefully the viewers agree we give each other charity in our arguments and
hopefully people see that and think that it's good uh and see that there's there's decent
points to be made on either side and like maybe I'm wrong but I like to think I'm approaching
good faith um and uh I feel the same about you so I mean I think you're a reasonable guy and I
don't you know yeah I I want to I want to like I want to actually engage yeah with your ideas on
this yeah I don't I don't want to just I don't want to throw anything out uh out of offhand
or whatever you know okay I think I think I've made my point about the people calling me a fascist
in the in the comments yeah isn't isn't May a fucking wanker I can't wait for her to resign
they're talking about Digi's fiance yeah which is gonna resign from that position of fiance wait who
are you talking about Theresa May Theresa May our department minister that fucking speech she made
about how it's oh I'm on your side you know it's all the MPs where are we gonna get Paul
them into a side what a fucking bitch she knows that she's at least responsible for like half of
the problems in the stands still are you she's a real fuck this is a this is a left turn I think
he's talking about her position on brexit uh she said she was for it but he's been dragging her
Theresa May the prime minister of the UK indeed that's really funny sorry sorry guy tbbb ap two
best brothers bitch about politics yeah there it is it's alive but well here on the pcp everybody
thanks for fucking oh we gotta do voice we gotta do voicemails I was gonna be like and thanks for
watching tbap okay there's still we gotta do voicemails we have to do the format indeed we have
to do this mandatory court sentence uh I mean it's funny you know shut up munchie the voicemails are
good yeah I like him munchies bad attitude don't be an idiot don't be a don't I don't I don't dislike
the voicemails well great because we got a couple of them coming up for you buddy yes all right um
now okay before we get to the real voicemails um guys I I did some digging I made I made an
underground contact with someone okay this is unconfirmed he claims to be the pizza party
podcast this man has made this claim so he is he has he has he been has he returned from his
from his exile it's I don't know I you know I was has he has he been found like Jimmy Hawthorne
I was handled I was handed this this mp3 file physically just the file itself not on any device
of any kind uh and I've smuggled it here across the border to try to find out did it look like did
it look like in Fullmetal Alchemist when Scar like pulls all the the words off of that page of that
book and holds it in like an orb like an orb of letters like floating around his hand did it look
like yeah I was it was a little bit more digital kind of like you're grabbing like a glowy effect
kind of thing but that's what it was but okay let's let's hear what pizza party podcast has to say
go congratulations you have dived into all the layers of the deep web you have uh crawled
out the dungeons and have found the witch made prize the secret anion of the pizza party podcast
you're now listening to pizza party podcast I'm your host it's a body podcast uh we have your
guests uh coming to San Diego uh Waldo from Wraith Waldo
we found uh a zombie lighting the bin line okay that would be hidden in the original
shear cartoons we have uh what um I don't think something's wrong returning guests um
the the brown is it I don't think this is it this is a this is a forgery god damn I did not
understand any I don't know there's a deep there's a deep all right you know what fuck you dude
fuck this deep fake you're canceled stop there's a deep fake there's a deep it's everyone's trying
to be the pizza party podcast but you can't you can't you can't fake the original and it's and you
can't find it either I think I think that may have been a pcp fan and not actually a podcast
damn it's they're trying to stand there I don't think there are any of those actually it's it's
it's kind of funny how the pcp fans are either like you can't understand them or they're like
american children yeah that's true yeah yeah yeah yeah I like that too uh well that was disappointing
maybe one day we'll we'll get a real contact going uh okay moving on uh actual voicemails okay
here's a lovely call um you know what I'm not even gonna read this name uh it's all in the subject
matter and you're about to hear it let's get to it go a munchie wears killing code huh oh that's it
hey that's the whole okay actually that was a good voice that that that was a good voice I actually
thought that was munchie for a second I was I thought about this the other day about how I have no
desire to finish that series because first of all Tom's like like dead uh something like that Tom
like he's doing better everybody he's doing better he's still he's still on it I am games
uh that's true but also why would I continue killing code when I'm coding every day for endless war
the reason why I was doing killing is to motivate myself to do code but why would I need a show for
that when I already do it just in my daily life sure I understand that for you to live vicariously
through me and not actually do your work and to be just be like I like to see progress made I like
my favorite TV characters to have arcs and I want this to be spoon for me I want to feel like I'm
accomplishing something by watching killing code and not actually doing what I understand this might
be disappointing for you but from my perspective I've accomplished everything that I want to and
I'm living my ideal life right now and I code all the time and it's just well munchie I I want to
say I don't know whether to blame you or the fans for this but like um uh the people people in the
comments being like hashtag where's the podcast killing code and stuff and people like people
commenting on tbapp and 10 pays like where is killing code is that is that accurate there are
some there is some of it and I hate it and I hate them and I hate you why have you done much you
you need to make killing code finale already it needs to yes you need to make the killing you need to
kill you need to like do like the the we have killed the code we have killed the code the video
release you need to do the till that I'm not opposed to continue but I just see no no reason
for my perspective well hey as long as people no no no don't don't continue it if you don't want to
but please just just slip a dagger into its ribs put it out of its misery that's that's fair that's
fair I mean obviously the reason people say that is because the very first episode it's like we're
going to do this every week and if we don't you must attack us verbally and mentally yeah that's
true yeah I think that's the same height backlash you were talking about I mean I'm getting roasted
quite a bit for we ag was being late you know totally fair totally fair but it's because I
sent myself embrace we ag a boy okay okay indeed I just want to say yeah the difference between this
and reagawa is even though they're both supposed to be weekly or whatever you know we agawa was you
know like like it's it's good content for your channel you must survive yeah to make videos and
stuff like that killing code had a purpose and the purpose was not to be a show it was not to be
like well much I can't I can't let you off the hook on this surely you would admit it is not the
viewers who are at fault for believing your promise of a weekly show that that's not at all what I'm
saying that's not what all I'm saying I'm not saying that they were wrong to suspect this or
even wrong to want it or continue to want it after I mean you're explaining why you're not
going to do it which is fine which I totally get but exactly yeah that's that's all I'm trying to
say is that there's no like I'm I'm doing everything I wanted to do this was a man killing code was a
massive success in my opinion fair enough all right so so canonically killing code kill is it
killed it's yeah I haven't talked to Tom Tom might want to still do it yeah maybe Tom's Tom's
like hey I'm waiting and then he's too busy he's too busy creating 3d modeling that's doing a
different show he's making a game though you know what this will be interesting I wonder I wonder
what's Tom's done with with with all this this Cody knowledge these so I wonder he should let us know
we should let us know well that well that killing code finale that's where you get into that start
up killing code season two what did we do with killing code season one no no I think the finale
would just be like Tom and munchie in a call and say so what do you do I'll do endless war what do
you do I do this other thing and it's like all right now the end you know you could embed that
in a piece of the episode that could just be in one yeah I mean it's in this one well but I hear
fortunately I speak for Tom I killed the code Tom what's the deal with 3d models why do they
gotta look like that yeah what what's the polygon I'm asking you Tom Tom who's in the call right
now come on as the official you would say yeah you've been here the whole time Tom
uh classic classic Tom 3d models
wow really nice move Tom really impressive response to that question what what's something Tom would
say um yeah I don't know it's just like oh my oh my bones my bones that's what Tom would say
just stop that sad I don't want to think about just go back from the gym he's gonna have a Q&A
what's up guys it's me Tom Oliver time for the little Q&A uh oh no my my sciatic nerves
all my nerves are exploding uh okay let's um pathetic god brutal he's gotta he's gotta lift
those nerves uh okay anyway um let's let's move on to our next call all right how many more do we
how many do we have uh I think there are seven more I think there's seven more we have a proposition
from the zoom tomb uh all right go
why have I called you up here today well pcp this is here's the thing you're all old as dicks
you'll die right like soon look at Tom that motherfucker looks like a skeleton got HPV and
spaghettios in a soup kitchen
you might be saying well munchie he's a kid well no he's fucking not this comes to boomer at best
so what's my proposition the zoomer titans the next pcp when y'all are dead as a dick some
will need to continue the podcast who's that someone me motherfuckers me and my legal extraordinarily
gay gentleman the teens to zoom to the zoom team fucking me fucking me sex with the young
I'll carry on your motherfucking legacy who's with me this is so fucking bullshit I can't
believe I've been demoted to your work this is now you're an adult yeah yeah yeah you're over
the damn it you lost your privilege dude it's over this is so unfair it's not hey dudes time
time passes dude yeah that means no it's and and it's past it's over why no you're doing the
over I would have been on your side I would have joined you zoom to zoom to my would have been
on your side like you did he could I want to be just just let me come in please I beg you let me
you would have been the perfect in you would have been the perfect sleeper agent for their
cause to assassinate the rest of the teen cp I mean you could have been even alienated what's the
word cp you could have been uh fucking like they could have kid I guess I guess they kid next door
rule fight it and you're officially like over the bar so they had to like wipe your memories and
kick you out you're no longer eligible although there is hope because later on and like some of
the movies of kid next door remember remember how some adults like never got the treatment and like
there's still kids on the inside yeah they fought against it oh my god I think Nigel Uno's dad
agent zero was agent zero the most legendary kids next door agent of all time they wipe his adult
memory or rather they like they revive his childish thoughts and he teams up with Nigel Uno
that's emotionally gripping shit it's it is it's so good it's so good next door fucking rules
I kind of want the audio for that for that voicemail so that I can animate Dirk Strider saying it
you got it dude not Dirk Dave Strider sorry yeah excuse me excuse my exits
uh okay moving on how how crazy is it that I am literally a hundred times as old as the characters
in Homestuck is that crazy right where does the time go yeah feel old yet um okay next call is from
some crazy dude all right some pink otter uh is calling it let's let's see what they have to say
dear denizens of the pcp podcast and any potential celebrity guests I've been listening to the
podcast long enough for my brain to rot and to believe that following my passions might actually
be a good idea so a little over half a year ago I began writing in my spare time oh good what I have
now is the first draft of a method I would simultaneously like to edit and release over
some unspecified amount of time however I was left with a conundrum where in the world do I post
this piece of garbage after talking to my stupid friends they suggested Wattpan but I don't particularly
like the idea of being on the same website as Naruto has a sister Sasuke love story
as stupid yet more experienced internet creators yeah I was intrigued about your opinions on the
matter should Wattpan indeed be avoided like the plague or am I just a fucking fan fiction figure
okay first of all what's Wattpan what is he saying I I don't know what what what what pad is a
it's a wait what what's the name of it what is it Wattpad like WATT yeah yeah is it a is it a fan
fiction site or is it just a fiction site that a lot of fan artists post on it's it's it's a fiction
site that oh it's most fan I mean none of us have ever done like long-form prose Tom kind of did
with a certain iteration of sorceress loss I feel like you might know more about I mean did you
wrote like uh his light novel I don't know what he released that on though I think he just made
a google doc yeah oh yeah like the thing with the thing with writing I mean I don't know either
because I don't I usually write for things that I end up drawing right um but uh I suppose
being on a platform doesn't necessarily mean that you are associated with the people on that
platform but people people will like think certain things if they know the you know like if Wattpad
seems like a place that everyone goes when they hear it then maybe not put it there well it's
it's also like if you're on a platform then people who are also on that platform will see you so
yeah fans might consist of I mean I mean there's nothing there's nothing stopping you from posting
on multiple platforms I was gonna say that's the solution even if it's just a personal thing for
you to make you feel better then you'd be like it's available on all these platforms like oh are
you on that Naruto one no no you don't understand I'm on everything I'm just I'm playing the game
baby I'm going everywhere I'm multi-plat and and I mean people will turn their nose up at any given
platform right like no platform is perfect or completely respectable uh I mean I would suggest
maybe maybe make your own website or maybe even just like a wordpress or something I mean he's just
trying to get a seat right right so and then just you know make your make your twitter profile
whatever put the description like author of you know whatever the title of your thing is make that
part of your thing you know talk to other talk to other amateur writers and stuff and you know build
a little personal brand around it I guess and while you work while you work on your next one um
I mean I yeah post that that's the answer posted to every every platform yep every don't feel boxed
and even like even if that put it on lulu put it on amazon have it like do like print on demand
sir you can do this you can have it like you can have like print on demand books yeah is it is
it self-publishing is it vanity publishing maybe but it's not completely illegitimate so fucking do
it whatever publications going to be like that anyway so you know and I mean you won't it's your
first book you know it won't first of all it might suck he's gonna keep working on it he said two
it's like he sounds like it's still being okay yeah okay but um let me just say it might suck
that's fine whether it sucks or not it won't sell that's fine this is your this is your base
this is your like this is the thing that I made and like this is what you you're about and you
work on your next one and and it's just you know don't worry about don't worry about the money don't
worry about making sales worry about building a this sounds kind of dirty when I like I see it as
but it's your fear for early shit is like you building your brand yeah right yeah absolutely I
totally agree I mean who out right out of the gate like is super successful very rarely are people
successful immediately like a I don't know like an undertale was his first time making a game
really but he was a modder so I guess even that wasn't his first like you know well I mean yeah
I'd feel like a lot of the success of undertale is down to Toby's uh proficiency with making really
catchy good songs for sure for sure so and he had a lot of practice in that already I didn't I mean
he also had he also had connections like Hussey promoted yeah he had he had lots of lots of help
with that um yeah yeah so I mean so the short answer to your question yeah fucking release it on there
and like don't well what are you gonna let like let the fact there's lots of fanfiction on the site
stop you from spreading your shit and hustling and getting that green my dude I don't think so get
out there post it there and then just be and then yeah like if that makes you feel bad post it everywhere
put it in a google doc that you can just link to people if they just want to read it you know
free of whatever else if you care about that but I say who gives a shit man that's um that's what I
think maybe maybe commission someone to draw you like a like a cover yeah spend the 20 bucks to
get funny effectively function as a cover art or something yeah hell yeah hell yeah and don't
don't do if you can't draw don't do it yourself there's nothing worse than like an embarrassingly
bad uh like piece of art piece of promotional art drawn by someone who obviously you know I always
thought I you know I enjoyed mumke's uh the triflers and all that but I always thought he
should have gotten a cover made I just know I never finished it I got like halfway through it
and then I forgot to finish I mean we had our podcast big fan loved it a lot really enjoyed it
maybe super pissed but I mean that's because it's supposed to so there you go right all right well
there you go there's your answer moving on he would he would know ask him he's I mean that
that sounds like a higher level though that was like actual releasing it for sale which I don't
think this dude's going for yet but I mean you can always ask him he might have well I'm saying
yeah I mean you can buy the triflers on like it's on Lulu and stuff yeah yeah Amazon books may I
don't know but like there's nothing stopping you amateur author from doing oh I mean that's
totally true yeah like why limit yourself if you don't have to you might as well just make
it available you might as well you might as well yeah so go for it dude yeah okay anyway okay next
yeah that there's your answer moving on okay this call is from a little guy you know him you love
him his name Nate foreplay go oh welcome to a never before found recording of Nate behind the scenes
yeah I recorded between a Nate fan and Nate himself
Nate let me let me let me drink your beans okay but only if you talk dirty to me yeah fine
uh uh kino hearts
final fantasy yeah very good you need to eat your greens
thank you my son the shocking revelation that it was indeed his son the whole time
I was definitely not ready for thank you and have a good day thank you man
you too this has been another episode of Nate foreplay what a nice what a nice man yeah
he's a good man uh please call back give us more um all right oh okay we've got a very special so so
um so I just gotta say I am I am I'm just wait I'm just waiting for riddle my ass oh it's it's
coming it's coming you know it's coming uh but before that we've got uh so we've actually got
some robots calling in um so first we've got the pcp generator 0.0 0.3 gang gang 2020 yeah that's
fair we have to fight against them I got my got my yang shirt fuck the robot but we gotta know our
enemy so let's hear what this version uh of the alpha generator has to say okay uh go welcome to
the pcp version 153.6 edition four beta got the right lesson this program was carefully crafted by
the best scientists the world had to offer for your listening pleasure Ben sainte is here
so his best guy ever also made jopen brackets who does not talk close brackets laugh she left
what about yang gang best guy ever ah yes the yang gang is quite delightful I agree
Ben but I also hate that the laborers of the world are oppressed by the capitalist overlords
best guy ever best guy ever but they take money for work which was agreed upon beforehand
you are stupid come on guys I will get mad so I will talk about pokemon and all its derivatives
in length it's okay we're talking about pokemon I will join the conversation now because I know
something about pokemon which is not the case for politics which is why I have abstained from
contributing during that time mage insert nothing of value here thank you for listening to our
professional podcast and please donate your hard-earned money on patreon which contributes to
the abstract idea of making more of this podcast which we will do anyway and a possible gathering
at a later date yeah fair all good there it is okay you know is that it pretty good yep though
that was it so that was good I appreciate that okay so the good news is okay so first of all
I'm actually getting a little worried we've got another bot calling in uh and it's already evolving
because uh I mean maybe maybe yang was on to something because we podcasters are being
deposed by these robots that are just better in every way did you hear that last call that was
better than anything we've ever recorded on this podcast over 50% of the american population is
currently working in the podcast sector and every single one of those jobs is automatable god damn
he's right by by 2020 there will be no podcast we cannot compete with that level of quality therefore
we need to ban the technology it's the only fair thing to do okay but I believe in knowing
thy enemy so let's see what uh pcp ai bought version 208-03-30 uh oh wait no that's the date
it's version 208 okay okay here we go uh commence all right let's get into this urban
dictionary's definition for procedillary generated podcast is the procrastinators podcast
i don't think that's right good or can't be made by our machine i kind of agree
we're not at the level with that sort of thing what if there was a machine that let you turn
whatever you were thinking of dream about a god lost i mean everything's every day that's why
capitalism works that is keto it's not fair that people have money pay for leon dot com slash
then say we need to get everyone building themselves up that's how we get the star fleet people real
problem with procedurally regenerated art is that at some point it starts making a mess and
you have to clean it up is that really i don't like it it's not good i don't know why i am just
thinking okay press one one one one one one one one one one one one one that's okay that was those
two real algorithm they have evolved since that first robot it's already advanced this much maybe
maybe that interrupting each other maybe we should lean into this i mean we have now had yeah two
entire effectively two entire pcp episodes within this pcp that's true because we've had
two basically four it's like the the equivalent of like you know in uh in uh willy wonka they got
the pill that's like the full three course meal like that's what these are these are these are an
entire an entire pcp experience just the pure joy condensed into this few seconds this 45 second
podcast uh that's really all you need i really like that the topic was a podcast made by ai and
they actually discussed that as the thing they evolved so much dude i'm they're getting smarter
uh i'm okay so you know so uh the thing about yang i don't just agree with is that like if i can
be on top if we can be controlling the robots to just do our jobs for us so we do zero work
we reap the benefit while the rest of society stagnates and is destroyed but we can suck the
the wealth and the resources from them while that's happening that sounds great that sounds like
what i want to i mean that's what i mean that's what automation should do that's that's what i
believe in yeah the robot shouldn't lead to people being miserable it should lead to oh the work
is done for us well we can just relax we can chill out we can do some cool although you know i mean
okay that's true and i don't want to get too much into this but like why are we doing this again
look just just okay this one question i just have one it's like no if no question if you were i want
to hear it if you were the roboticist and like you knew that like if you made this robot that
it's just an omni robot it can do everything it'll replace every job on the planet and you know
that like your but you will not earn all the money it's gonna be taken and you're like fuck it
i'm just not gonna make the robot you know why is everyone else gonna benefit disproportionately
to my work shut up you fuckers uh what's your what's your word to that scientist who feels that
his work isn't going to be fairly rewarded that he should just do it for the benefit of humanity
is that you know uh i mean why wouldn't he be people i mean people are gonna have to buy his
robots right uh i suppose i suppose maybe the robots will build themselves and then they'll
you know they're smart enough to do that well here's what i would say i would say that okay
maybe it's bad maybe it's a shame that he won't be compensated however by creating this robot he
will create a utopia in which he doesn't need money i suppose he doesn't need rewards because
everything will be solved um yeah yeah so i would still say okay i'm gonna make i'm gonna make
they'll say it'll a partially controversial statement that i think you'll totally disagree with
and lots of people will but it's just that like if you're let's say you're a rich man on the top
of the hierarchy and you have the ability to make like to give everyone infinite wealth like with
these robots or whatever and you choose not to because you like your privileged position at
the top of the hierarchy here at my stance is i think that's you're like well if everyone's if
everyone's equal if everyone's equally provided for then i won't be above exactly i think it is
your right to make that choice and i i think it is your right to make the choice but you are a
fucking monster that may be a fair case you are a fucking demon who should be swell all right
okay good news people were passed that it's time to check in with riddle my ass batman he's here
finally god i know just what we needed okay i've been hyped so i think so far ben and i have been
saved if i remember correctly um okay let's let's okay let's hear who who are we gonna who's in
this exciting i'm so excited of this barely intelligible man to speak some more he's probably
gonna get mad at me for calling his riddles not great probably gonna so so so i basically just
ruined my chance of having a actual real little my ass is just gonna be like him specifically
calling that out so i just ruined my my entire batman's probably gonna be so pissed that he just
deliberately failed yeah okay we don't want dick eating all right let's find out okay here we go
really upset honestly so batman what do you say we raise the stakes a little bit you know what is
great little we have people's eyes just take care of all the games of our middle name batman
release the testicular tenderizing tuna oh no so now where do i ask batman who doubts my riddling
skills says nigger just for thrill yeah yes yes there we go what should i pose to you who asked to
analyze smurf's too i'm gonna press one for munchie one one one one one yeah good job batman
release them yeah thank you
don't scratch the car though well tenderizing tuna may release but tenderizing tuna
we get to many members of the pcb put it next time to find out the same pcb time same pcb channel
okay that was that was great you know what real last time and you just did the best of both worlds
it was one of many i love the fact that you're such a munch head that you that you remembered uh
analyze smurf's too dude this guy knows it all real fan this guy this guy's a this guy's a true
believer this i'm gonna give this guy we're gonna have like a pcb medal of honor yeah we have a pcb
award yeah a hall of fame a hall of fame for voicemails or something that's that's a really funny idea
you know what first member of the pcb fan hall of fame first member riddle my ass batman yeah
welcome to the club you're doing it now don't we're all we're all honorary we're all honorary
members of the hall of fame by the way right of course of the fans of the fans of the fan okay wait
okay okay there's a little juma argumentated that i should be in the pcb fan hall of fame
why is that oh i hear your point i i i want to say that because you were elevated before the
institution was founded you're disqualified okay that's fair i get your point but it's like yeah
you're like you're like a horse cuss a horseshoe crew fan yeah i mean that's true yeah that makes
sense was i officially in the cmc for that or was or was i not the there was an official cmc for
past analysis was there i remember that oh yeah he was wasn't i don't i have no idea i can't remember
but you never had a pony ocea so i want to say no i want to say that you are a gyno see
yep so he did he had an mlp didn't well time okay yeah strawberry milk i wasn't sure how long ago
that was made but okay if you say so if you say so charlotte milk's an institution oh i can't
can't believe that that guy's going to brony con and not me what a fucking bitch yeah what an asshole
he i can't believe he didn't take you along that's a shame dude that's a shame uh how exciting
brony con august what 30 30th something right no no first first the fourth august first to fourth
holy shit oh god it's coming up oh god it's barreling down all right yeah yeah in five months
months yeah like four months it's right around the corner that's like that's like nothing to me
yesterday i blinked in five months ago okay we've got uh one last voicemail for the day uh and that
is going to be another definitely i think we can say safely this is a member of the uh fan hollow
fame we got another call from them snakes ladies and gentlemen oh yeah oh god oh he's back oh no
i hope he's not gonna demand let's hear what he has to say go dear fans saint i write you
for what might be the final time what after the defeat of munchie i find that there is little
purpose for me to stay here in this realm now i depart into the wasteland in search of a new
character arc but before i go there are a few things that i need to get off my chest
know this then i am eggborn you are just an egghead at the end of the day you are simply
a shallow imitator to my glory but i have no reason to fight with you anymore thank you
for being my bro thanks i'll see you in another place in another time
it is already out go and play with you fucking worthless human scum before i destroy
pcb dating simulator at now hopefully i assume that's true so we'll go check the twitter it'll be
them we'll do all kinds of stuff them snakes love to link it them snakes now he's gone what a
fucking emotional gut wrenching voicemail that was yeah but i just want to official member of the
of the hall of fame oh yeah yeah you know what he's in a better place out in the wild
he's on twitter at tp at tpc dating or whatever pcb dating at pcb dating by eggborn was that
reference to your egg status after the nuzlocke or uh just an egghead you know i don't know i mean i
i mean he's okay we know what he is yeah let's not overthink it people we let's just end on a
end on a high note uh at no wait wait that was legendary uh thank you so much for calling them
snakes uh riddle my ass batman you know you know even though i had a meticulous you know i had i
got to read the script of the past encounter with him and you know it was all a planned you know
well thought out like strategically maneuvered character arc that we mean that we specifically
engineered uh i think i remember something like that maybe and even though you know it was always
in the plan for me to be defeated and i understood what was happening at the time very well yeah
maybe yeah it could be for all i know sorry i'm really intoxicated right now uh even though all
that's true i i just want to say that mr snake you're a good snake you know you're one of the
good ones that's all i have to say one of the good ones yeah yeah it's nice it's nice to get
closure it's nice to get close on onto onto a new onto a new adventure fucked up how uh there are
no more humans and they've been replaced with snakes and like every single day the snake population
just grows and grows and humans are getting you know uh less and less uh part of the percentage
of majority that's pretty fucked up human bodies are becoming on average 25 more snake and it's just
it's just skewing more and more in that direction and uh and he went on to have many grand adventures
all right that what a what a bro what a people ladies and gentlemen thanks for listening and
continue to support the nebulous idea of more content both on this podcast and in future
meetups at patreon.com slash the procrastinators five dollars for the bonus episodes there will
also be a new bonus episode out right now and i can tell you what it is because it's out sunshine
and rainbows edited by our one and only lethal aurora mage this is the first time she edited
something no she's done it before no she she did a previous bonus episode and at least one
yeah she's a good drawer and go see the fresh aren't you go look at them there'll be a thumbnail
around you can look at that for a preview uh and she teased me before she said like or you know she
was like oh did you see the thing in the episode i was like no i was like oh shit i guess i better
go back and check where can i look at where can i look at this you can go to at the procrastinators
on patreon that's where and also wait no no it's not at the procrastinate no wait it's patreon.com
slash the procrastinators five dollars for 24 that's two years of solid bonus episodes now
goddamn excellent work everyone and uh one dollar you'll be in the patreon lounge won't that be fun
ladies and gentlemen follow us on twitter at tpcrastinators for updates about the dating
simulator and other stuff all kinds of great things happening and by the way someone sent a picture
of him wearing and i retweet on the procrastinators the i'm the reason people are dying shirt
keep it up people and buy a fucking beautiful i mean my preference is for the the the the the
the group piss that's my aesthetic reference but it's all gravy sold uh we've sold a few of those
it's pretty cool it's pretty cool i'd like to see those on twitter if you got it send us picks people
show it show us you're rocking your pcp threads indeed show us rocking your pct
your pct oh god and um i'm using i guess that's it so we'll see you next time stay tuned same
pcb time same pcb channel bye