Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
This is Gibbontake and we've got Simsie. Today is with us. Simsie at Simsie Fart on Twitter is a self-described artist who likes drawing lips and boobs and flanged.
I bought into the meme. I bought into the cryptocurrency.
It's a great meme and I'm honestly a little sad that nobody else made a flange sonar for themselves. Only is.
Well, I think it's because your octopus hermit is the only one.
The fucking profile picture on Twitter is hideous.
It's so terrifying.
That's what's cool about it, you fucking idiot.
It's so abrasively vile that it's put everybody off of contributing to this fucking meme.
Is that what being flanged means? I don't know, man.
Yeah, you saw the monkey. You know what it means to be flanged and yet it's simply the most desirable state.
I don't understand.
Well, you have to be a man. You have to be a male to be flanged.
If you're a fucking unflanged...
You males can't have flanges.
That's what you think.
If you're an unflanged human, then yeah, of course you fucking see a flange. You're like, ew.
But that's just the sign of the unflanged is that you don't fucking appreciate it.
The sign of the unflanged.
Oh my god.
It's the mark of the beast. The mark of the beast is being unflanged.
It's the mark of either an imbecile or the unflanged.
The sign of the unflanged is like an Anamorph's book title.
I don't even read those. It just feels like the sort of thing.
I retweeted that meme from the Anamorph in Time Twitter of the cover of an Anamorph's book, but it's Rick turning into Pickle Rick.
No.
Oh, that one fucking did me. That one did me a chuckle.
That one really got me.
I haven't even thought about Rick and Morty in such a long time.
Rick and Morty has just been absent from my cultural perception for like a year now.
It's not about Rick and Morty. It was about, I'm there for the Anamorph's content.
And there I see the cover of an Anamorph's book and I'm like, ah, yes, this is what I'm interested in.
But the twist is what if it were Rick and Morty and then I remember, oh, Rick and Morty.
What a time in the zeitgeist that was.
What a blunder.
Did you see that Justin Roiland was bullied for making a Rick and Morty NFT?
And then he was like, ah, geez, guys, ah, geez.
Oh, geez.
He was like, legitimately, ah, geez.
I saw that he was making an NFT.
Okay, but did he get bullied out of it?
I don't know whether he got bullied out of it, but he was bullied and he made a sad tweet about it.
He should be bullied.
It's like, I can't, I can't, this is why I can't deal with Twitter, you guys.
And then I don't know what he did after that.
Oh, I saw that.
I saw that fucking weak shit, the fucking weak pussy cow or that piece of shit.
I hope he fucking dies.
Fuck that guy.
Nah, fuck him and his NFP.
He's rich! Who cares what he thinks?
Yeah, exactly.
I think, I think you're agreeing with me.
I'm not sure.
A little bit.
There's some truth in my statements.
Fuck him.
Oh, deny it.
Oh, I'm just in Rowland.
He's just in fucking Rowland.
What does he need to make an NFT for?
Oh, I scream.
Nothing.
I really think it's like, it's just, he had no idea somehow.
I don't know how.
I don't know how he had no idea.
He feels like he would be more connected to the internet.
Maybe he's been deliberately distancing himself from it.
And thus does not know how bad NFTs are and was surprised.
Well, I can believe him not knowing, but if he's going to do it, he should.
I mean, he should have researched it ahead of time and he should know.
Before you do one, you should know what it is and know why it's bad.
All that I care about is that he didn't do it.
He was pulled out of it.
I've got to make a confession here.
When I first heard of NFTs and I didn't know any of the concerns around it, I was like,
I'm going to make one of those.
And I didn't.
Well, we're all born knowing nothing.
Right.
Yeah, I don't.
I don't like blame people.
Like, I don't, I don't blame him.
I don't blame him as long as he didn't go through with it.
As long as he didn't fucking make that devil's bargain.
I don't blame him for doing a bad thing.
As long as he didn't do the bad thing, then everything's fine.
I don't.
Well, I don't.
I mean, I say I don't care that he was going to do it.
I wouldn't care if he was going to do it as long as he changed his mind and did the right thing.
That's, that's all I'm saying.
But, but, but you know what?
But on the other hand, what, what drives, you're, you're just in Royland.
You have like TV shows on like networks.
You are like, you are like a rich, famous person who's like well connected in the industry.
You've, you've, you've literally got it all.
What drives you at that point to be like, I should make an NFT?
I think.
What, what's the, what's the point?
Most likely it's a PR person saying, hey, NFTs are a thing that's going around now.
You should make one.
We've got the thing set up and he's like, oh, okay, cool.
Ah, geez.
And then he tweets about it, not like, I feel like he wouldn't have, if he had found about it,
found out about it himself, he probably wouldn't have like promoted it.
I feel like it's just one of those things.
Because a lot of people who don't know what they're talking about have things called jobs
in the real world, in offices, and they wear suits and then they don't know anything.
And then they tell people to do stuff.
I feel like one of those people told him to make an NFT.
It's definitely more of a publicity thing than like a money thing.
Like he doesn't need the money.
It's just this concept is popular at the moment.
It's an extra boost.
Does it generate publicity that you made an NFT?
Generally have no idea.
Does it do that?
I don't understand the mindset of people.
I think it's just like, oh, it's the hot new fad thing.
Exactly, yeah.
Do you see the guy, the Oscars, the guy's golden head?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, the guy who played Bozeman.
Chadwick Boseman.
Chad Boseman.
Real Chad.
See, that one's actively disgusting.
That's one of the most loyal things that has come out of this whole NFT thing.
That one was pretty hideous.
It is.
Say what you like about NFTs, but that one's not in good taste.
I saw that it was just like, it was like a stock, like 3D model that like the NFT,
the guy who made the NFT, just like he bought the model and then he just like applied a gold texture to it.
He didn't even make the model.
I don't know.
I'm an multimedia artist.
I take the tools and use them to my fullest extent and make thousands upon thousands of dollars of selling an NFT of it.
I love my book.
And fuck you.
If some PR suit told him, like, NFTs are hot, it'll be a big thing if you do one right now.
People will think it's cool and he was like, okay, I guess.
And he did it, like, I mean, fair enough, I guess.
But I mean, if not, like the alternative is that like...
There's no reason to defend it.
Oh, him.
The alternative is that he thought it was cool.
The bullying him into not doing it is a good thing.
Yeah, it's a force for good.
I just wonder, I just wonder, like, did he think it was cool?
That's what it means.
Like, what does it say?
What should I infer about you that you were gonna, that you were like on board with this?
I don't know.
Because it's so lame.
It's so shit and lame and bad.
It's bad in so many ways.
Even if it didn't destroy the environment, I would still hate it, honestly.
Is NFT more like not fucking tasty?
Because we can't eat it.
Yeah, true.
Not flanged.
It's flat.
Not at all.
It's the opposite of being flanged, guys.
New vile, fresh teat.
Gross.
No, wow.
I don't think new vile is the right word to use there.
Gross.
But that's what it stands for now.
What does new vile mean?
Hey, guys, welcome to the new vile means that you're capable of, new vile means that you
are capable of childbirth, right?
That's what new vile means.
Oh, no.
Well, you know.
I mean, stranger things have happened.
I guess so.
Speaking of teats, Simsie.
Jesus.
That's me.
Hello.
You draw the ladies a lot.
Teats.
You draw the ladies.
Yes.
Teats on the ladies, on the teats.
And there they are.
Links in the description.
You are very good at what you do.
Thank you.
I make baseless thoughtless art with the sole purpose of titillation.
You do the cash grab fan art, pick a popular character, cash in on their existing fan base,
draw them looking sexy, rinse, repeat.
You've done me there.
You're right.
It's true.
I mean, I see you do it.
And I know what you're doing.
And it's fine.
I get it.
But yeah, you're a guy.
You like to draw.
It says right in your body.
You like to draw tits and lips.
Why not draw them on, you know, Nico Robin or, I don't know, Tubi or like whoever is fucking trending right now.
Or Goku or whatever.
Or whatever.
Yeah.
It's so easy.
It's like cheating.
It's not fair.
It really is.
And that's why you've got like 10 times as many Twitter followers.
What do you mean like 40k?
I used to hate that.
Like people who would just do whatever is popular and make bank off of it and usually tits are involved.
I'm like, damn it.
I don't want to do that.
But if I did want to do that, I'd be jealous.
Realizing that I don't actually care to do that art.
It means that it's fine.
People are just making money.
I'm under the impression that you're just kind of just genuinely like doing it.
Yes.
And you're not like suffering through the process.
I'm just doing this cynically to fool them all.
No, no, no.
I would still be drawing tits if like commissions were not a concept in this universe.
I would still just be like drawing tits in person online.
Like it's not purely for the money.
The followers of the fame.
I just really like doing it.
I never disliked it because it was like a cynical thing.
I was just sort of like, oh, damn it.
People make money from things they draw that I am not drawing.
That sucks.
I wish that sucks when people do that.
When people go to Google.com, they type in their favorite character, Big Booby, and they would find my art instead.
But they don't do that.
That is one of the most satisfying things about.
I think I am a little bit of an egomaniac, to be honest.
Like seeing my numbers go up is very satisfying.
Like typing in a character like Google.
Yeah, typing in a character on Google and seeing my own art on there.
Just like on Google.
That's really weird.
The couple times that I...
Yeah, I had them...
I've done a couple pieces of fan art.
I've never done number one result or anything.
But I have a couple of old fan arts that I did.
Like if you Google Lisa and you scroll down a little ways on the...
It doesn't take you that far to find the one like Lisa fan art that I did.
Yeah.
I think that's pretty cool.
Where she became president in 2020?
Yes, where Lisa Simpson became president in 2020.
No, the one with the game, with the guy.
With Brad.
Darling House?
No!
No.
Greg of Art, he'll come back.
Yes, yes.
Speaking of the Simpsons, have you guys heard Dr. Hibbert's new voice?
There's a voice?
Yeah, Dr. Hibbert.
No, I heard that he has one.
I haven't heard it.
They recast Carl and Dr. Hibbert and all the other recurring black characters because, you know...
White people can't play with people.
Okay.
I'm fine with that, but the voice for... they're not good voices.
I...
That is the...
I don't know.
The concern sometimes.
I mean, who cares, really?
It is the Simpsons.
If it ruins the jokes, then that's the problem, I guess.
I mean, if it's just unfamiliar, then people can get used to it.
Yeah, I guess who cares, really.
It's pretty weird.
It's like a quasi-impression of the old one, but like much deeper and like...
Of course.
Squishy-squishier sounding.
He's got that like, whoa, thing going on with his voice, you know what I mean?
That's like a weird way of putting it, but...
He's... what?
He's got the what?
Like, like...
He sounds a bit like Mr. Bean, but like an American man.
I was gonna say, Mr. Bean.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, exactly.
Like, he's got big jowls on his face.
Yeah.
I get... I think that the Appu thing makes more sense,
because Appu is like a specific ethnic group,
and he's from a country, and he has a linguistic accent.
Dr. Hippard and Carl are just like American dudes.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know about that one.
The thing with him is the aspect of the character matching...
Like, the voice actor matching the ethnicity of the character being portrayed.
That doesn't matter, because voice actors are talented.
The actual issue that was like...
Nobody really understood, because the surface level of,
oh, it's a brown character played by a white person.
That's bad.
Like, that's fine.
It's just that there's less minorities in the industry,
or able to get into the industry as work tech.
I mean, is that...
All characters could be black voice actors,
if there's no reason some of them have to be white,
because they're played by white characters all the other way around.
It's just like, there should be, you know...
It's not really... that's the reason, Ben.
It's not really that's the reason.
The show is 30 years old, and made it a time when you just hire people.
Yeah.
I think it's probably good.
It's good if people of every stripe can get a fucking job doing their shit.
That's all fine and good.
We should have...
We should have the white characters.
They should have replaced white characters with black voice actors.
I just wanted to say, the voices do sound really bad.
It's just my point.
Well, I don't know.
What are you going to say?
If people are trying to do an impression of a character that has existed for 30 years,
it's definitely going to feel weird.
Yeah.
Because it's not the same.
No, yeah.
I just watched the real gyms did a...
You know him? The Simpsons? The Simps... The Simptuber?
Yeah, he did a character history video on Dr. Hebrou.
Maybe that was why he picked him or something.
Oh, maybe.
There's not that much to talk about, really.
Dr. Hebrou is not like Edna Krabapal or someone who has a arc that's carried throughout the show.
Dr. Hebrou has been the same fucking guy every single time he's appeared.
He's never had an episode dedicated to him, ever.
Wasn't there that one time there was a mayoral race and Mr. Burns was running,
and he had his League of Evil politician people?
Or maybe it was just some other evil organization.
And there was Mr. Burns there, for one.
But Hebert was there.
Are you talking about when Cytro Bob was running for the Republican Party?
That's what it was. Cytro Bob.
And Hebert was there.
Yeah, that was weird.
I don't know why he...
That was a very secret Republican.
Is that some weird statement on hospitals being secretly owned by political parties or something like that?
Like bias towards them? I don't know.
I think they probably just picked a bunch of kind of upper crusty springfieldians
and were like, we'll make them the secret Republican cabal.
And you know, you pick a doctor, you pick a lawyer, you pick the rich Texan guy.
You would think Dr. Nick more so, wouldn't you?
Dr. Nick.
No, I think...
No, I can totally see Dr. Herbert being a Republican.
He wears fucking Argyle sweaters.
He's got his wife...
No, his wife wears the fucking shoulder pad suits.
He's well to do.
That's kind of his joke, isn't it?
His joke is that he always says something totally horrible.
But laughs afterwards.
And so it's like silly how he's laughing about it.
Maybe he's a really nice diva.
Can't do his voice at all.
Yeah, that's much better.
I'm so bad at voices. I used to be okay, but now I just don't even try.
Oh, the Palestinian-Israeli conflict? It's complicated.
I'm gonna get fired.
Israel deserves to exist, Bart.
Do we want to get into that?
Worse fucking hybrid impression.
We could. I'm flabbergasted.
That was a really awful hybrid impression.
Let me try again. He sounds like...
There's a couple of injections into the spine.
Oh, God, I don't remember. I don't remember what he sounds like.
He goes, no, let's get along with your COVID-19 vaccination.
That's better than mine.
Right, there's war. There's war happening now.
It was kind of like Israel-Lamao.
Israel-Lamao. A week ago, when it was Monday, I think, everything kicked off.
When there was the attack on that mosque and those people praying.
It was the Islamic religious holiday.
And then Hamas retaliated by firing rockets and then Israel jumped in and shot back.
It was like, okay, it's a big old thing.
Is that what inside of the Hamas rockets, the mosque attack?
I missed that part. I forgot.
I think that was the initial spark.
The first thing I saw was there were people praying in Arab.
Is it Muslim?
Yes, it's the word.
During a religious holiday, one of the three most important places for Islam.
It was tear-gassed by Israeli police at the time for seemingly no reason.
I didn't know what was going on.
I still don't really know.
But tensions between Jews and Arabs in the area have been high and up and down for generations.
Ramadan ended May 12.
The basic gist is, from what I understand, the Israeli Prime Minister.
I forget his name.
Netanyahu.
He's a far-right ethno-nationalist who is very anti-Arab.
Right now, him attacking in such force is good for his party.
Because Hamas is firing rockets, he can get to say,
you need to keep me in power because I'm defending you, citizens.
These terrorists are destroying us.
And if we don't blow them to fucking Kingdom come, they'll come and get you.
Vote for me in the next election, lol.
Nice, nice.
It sounds about right.
It's pretty bad.
I didn't know much about the Israel-Palestine conflict other than what I'd heard from bits and bobs
in my entire life that it's complicated.
I guess it's too complicated.
I don't want to know.
That's what bugs me.
I was raised as a kid.
I was told that that whole Israel-Palestine thing,
it's an ancient battle that's been fought.
It's like the blood war.
It's like the blood war between demons and devils.
It's raged since time immemorial.
It's an intractable conflict that can never be solved.
It will outlast all of us and it began before anyone living today.
Israel is like 50 years old.
It was made within living memory.
It's like a new country.
It was made at the end of the First World War.
I looked into the origin of all of it.
And it's basically Britain's fault.
Because that land was occupied by Turkey.
During the First World War, Turkey stayed neutral for a while,
but then due to some shenanigans,
because they were upset at the Ottoman Empire shrinking.
The Balkan Wars previously were like,
they lost territory and they're like,
damn it, we got to make the Empire great again.
So they joined Germany.
And so in order to fight off the Turks,
the British enlisted the help of some Arabs
who were trying to, from Arabs in the area,
they wanted a unified Middle East, a singular nation.
And they said, we'll help you fight the Turks, Britain,
if you help us and recognize our right to this land.
And the Britons said, okay.
And then they fought together in the war.
And then Britain was like, and lol, no, actually,
we're just going to carve out the land to our own benefit.
Against the Turks of the Ottoman Empire, right?
Am I following you?
The Turks were defeated.
The Ottoman Empire was pushed back.
And that land that was going to be like a united Arab era,
I can't think of the word to describe.
It was agreements.
There was stuff on Wikipedia about it that I read.
It's basically all I did.
I just looked at Wikipedia for like three hours.
But then Britain and France secretly had been talking,
all right, so we're not actually going to recognize their state.
We're just going to take...
Radcon 5 Gibbon takes lecture on the Israeli Palestine.
Yeah, this is brilliant.
It's just Wikipedia.
It's so easy to find.
I could fucking do a lecture on it.
It'd be funny.
Do it.
So like Britain and France, it was just like,
let's cut up the land.
We're going to make Jordan here.
We're going to make Lebanon.
We're going to make Palestine cut the land into these sections.
And those are the countries in that area now.
For their own benefit to like for trade or something,
colonies, I don't remember exactly what the reason for cutting it up.
Obviously it was beneficial for them.
They just said, we're not going to honor the promise to you Arabs.
And I think that carried over into a different separate agreement
that was made by Zionists and the British government at the time
to make a safe haven for Jews in Palestine after the First World War
because the Jews were going to help fight in the war if they agreed to that
and they made an agreement.
I thought...
And the agreement was extremely vague
and did not consider the Palestinian people who lived there or the Arabs
and at last it was just sort of between Jews and the British government.
We want a place to live and we want it to be in our homeland
and this Holy Land area give us this.
And they said, okay, we won the war.
Turkey is smaller and this area is now occupied by the Britain.
We're going to give you this land in Palestine
and we're just going to leave the rules very vague
and you can have a land in Palestine, quote, in Palestine.
It doesn't say how much of Palestine.
And then they just left and everything was fucked from there
because the Palestinians were like, you didn't tell us...
You first of all fucking betrayed us.
You said this whole area was going to be like an Arab.
You lied, you bastard.
And also you're giving this land to the Jews
and I don't know whether they were on good terms back then.
I don't know religious history that much.
But they obviously were persecuted up to that point, the Jewish people.
So I guess it was not welcome and they started fighting almost immediately
and it wasn't so bad for a while.
I don't know, that was where my reading stopped.
But basically Britain fucked everything up.
You sound like you've read up more on it than I have,
but I thought that the Israel that exists today,
I thought that it came into being after World War II and the Holocaust.
What happened with that is that the Holocaust had...
Obviously Germany at that time was doing a lot of bad stuff to Jews.
They had to run away.
Lots of them ran to Israel and they grew Israel
because there's more Jews there and people would come in all the time
and it would grow and they would use the excuse that
there's more people here, we need more land.
Hey Palestinians, we're going to take more of your land now
and you're just going to give it to us
and there's nothing you can do about it because we have the backing of the West
because current day the US backs Israel a lot
specifically because it is a good jumping off point
as a good jumping off point to bully other places in the Middle East with military power.
This is a very powerful place.
Have you seen that old clip of like somewhat younger,
weirdly balder Joe Biden ranting about Israel?
There's a several minute clip of him.
He's like banging his fist and he's shouting
and he comes off as extremely aggressive and thuggish almost
and he's like, if we didn't have an Israel,
America would have to invent an Israel to protect our interest in the region
and stuff like that.
It's like, oh boy, now here's a guy who really likes Israel.
Our interest in the region meaning quick and easy access to bullying Arabs out of their oil.
I don't think it's entirely about oil.
It's about foreign policy relationships.
It's about foreign policy, but ultimately foreign policy is dictated by resources
that the US and the UK to some extent.
I don't know exactly what they're...
They have not like...
What was that thing?
There's like a call for a ceasefire, the UN,
but the US didn't back it.
Everyone else did, including the UK.
So I don't know exactly what the UK's relationship is.
But yeah, it's a foreign policy thing,
but a lot of it is dictated by resources, oil, other things, uranium that you can mine.
Are you still learning Arabic, by the way?
Capitalism is the problem.
True.
If I can...
I did stop.
I just fell off.
I like it.
It's a cool language.
I want to learn how to write it, like calligraphy style.
It looks so cool.
It's a really cool looking language, written...
I do remember a lot of the little quirks of writing the letters,
where there's a shape that is like one way when it's the first letter in a word,
and then another way when it's like the middle letter in a word,
and you can recognize the similar swerve of the ink,
and it's like, ah, that's a zh sound.
That's a zh, and if you put a dot about it, it's a zh sound.
Stuff like that.
How are you feeling by the way?
It's cool.
Feeling?
Have you recovered?
Oh no, I feel terrible right now.
Nice.
I was going to talk about it, but I need to pee,
so I'll be back in a second.
Ah yes.
Okay, Simsie.
Let's talk about what a fucking nerd give is,
for doing research and reading up on history and shit.
She knows things I don't.
I have nothing to contribute.
Yeah, I didn't go that in depth with it.
I'm just a basic bitch.
I'm just your basic bitch.
I see some fucking ethnic cleansing on my Twitter timeline.
I say, I don't like that.
Exactly.
I saw a headline and I was like, oh that's bad,
and then I haven't seen anything else again.
Wait, I did make that.
I made a, since I was fucking around in Game Maker,
I made a quick and dirty edit to my game
to record a little footage of Phantom Horn destroying Israel.
Oh my god.
That was a bit...
That was great.
I mean, I understand the sentiment is funny.
It's like, yes, Israel is being bad,
but the idea of destroying it with a sword slice...
I was laughing so hard as I uploaded.
Just imagine you sat in your dark room,
hunched over on your keyboard.
It's pretty edgy.
It isn't that edgy.
You click done after importing Israel.png to Game Maker.
I would do the same thing for America.
You think I won't have Phantom Horn slice Israel,
I mean America in half?
I'll do it.
I get it, but I think it's annoying,
but it's true that there's a lot of actual anti-Semites
who just hate Israel for stupid reasons,
and they would want to kill Israel and Israelites and Jews.
And so people get confused a lot.
It's annoying.
There's this very clear difference
of the actions of a prime minister who is a far-right guy
and an entire ethnic group.
I did get one or two people mad at me and their replies,
but it's a country, and countries aren't people,
and countries are bad, states are bad,
and they should be killed.
So, I don't know.
Fuck it.
Insert any fucking country you want in there,
and it's fine.
It's always correct.
It's always moral to kill a country.
Yeah, fucking it.
It's not in Merry Old England.
I do like the design of the flag,
but I will destroy it.
I will kill everyone present.
It's aesthetically pleasing.
Give me, put the England in there,
and I will just, I'll have phantom horn
just neatly slice Northern Ireland right off.
Right off of it.
Freedom.
Northern Ireland is an England ban.
That's not part of England, you fool.
Wait, is that, am I stupid?
I thought Northern Ireland was part of England.
It's part of the United Kingdom.
England is its England.
Oh God, yeah, now you're right.
England and Scotland and Northern Ireland and Wales,
to some extent.
I was just thinking like,
you could do like a whole political series
of phantom horn destroys X,
and it would be like, oh Brexit,
like slicing the UK off from Europe.
From the EU, yeah.
It's like, oh man, commission.
Commission me to have,
you can have phantom horn slice anything
you want in that.
Unironically, could be like a,
like a Patreon reward.
I mean, shit.
$70.
I mean shit.
Yeah, I could, I can,
when the game's done, I can release
a custom version.
Patreon me $100, and I will release a custom version
that just has, I will put
anything you want in there as the final boss.
Well, I don't know about anything you want.
Anything you want.
Anything, it's yours.
It's done.
This could backfire heavily.
No.
I'll just pretend someone else did it.
I'll pretend they hacked the game.
Somebody modded my game.
They modded my game against my will.
Should we go back to Gibbs Health
for a second?
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I sound all right at the moment,
I think.
But last few days,
especially, have been
agonizing.
And I don't like it.
It's, I'm still waiting
one, I've got one week to go
waiting for my fucking
ultrasound that I'm having on my
liver so they can see inside
and see, ooh, there's a gremlin in there.
We mis-stab it and chop it up.
There's a nasty Whittle Galboy.
Just get the harpoon.
Nasty Whittle Galboy in there.
Yeah, I still don't have a diagnosis.
I've been waiting.
They said they'll call me or text me or whatever.
I gave my blood.
What more can I do?
The ultrasound is the only thing left
that is like a test to be done.
So I assume after I get that done,
they'll tell me that I'm going to die
in one minute.
Did you get vaccinated yet?
No.
Vaccines are still like,
you have to be old-ish.
Really?
And they're only now.
Yeah.
You have to be old or sick.
I don't think I'm going to get a vaccine for a while.
Oh, damn.
I guess we're hogging them all.
I was thinking of like seeing
what the accommodation was because I smoke
and seeing if I could get mine a little bit quicker
than all the other-
I've heard that some people have gotten moved up the list
because they smoke, yeah.
Fucking cool as hell.
Yeah, look into that.
Definitely.
Cigarettes are so fucking cool.
No, they're not.
They're so fucking good for you.
No, dude.
I'm so ruthlessly addicted to them.
I literally just like put on my coat,
went out in the rain earlier,
I was smoking.
And I felt like this is nothing.
I'm not even like socially doing it.
I'm just like putting toxins into my body
for no reason.
I mean, yeah.
That's how it is.
But I kind of like it though.
I kind of like it.
Let me just take that nicotine out of there.
I just-
Get some like parsley.
Roll that up.
It would still be toxic to just burn something
and inhale the smoke from it.
I've tried to quit.
It's still bad.
I mean, I've been in the worst situation
because I tried to quit
and I quit for about six months
and like with a vape.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, with a vape.
And then now I just smoke and I vape at the same time.
I smoked less, but I vape a lot.
So now I'm just doing both.
Why didn't you just not buy any more cigarettes
and just vape instead?
That's what I did for six months.
Oh, okay.
And then I went to the pub with my friends
during summer and they were like,
just one, my friend.
And then it happened.
You must kill them.
I have not smoked or vape
like hardly at all for months now.
Occasionally, a friend will offer me a cigarette
and I will smoke it.
But I've been off smoking for long enough
that it doesn't give me the fucking shakes
and I crave it anymore.
I'm just like, I'll smoke one.
And then I'm like, okay.
Well, I think it's literally just a matter
of not being in the habit
of going to the store to buy cigarettes.
Because when I'm in that habit,
then I'll go and I'll buy them
and then I'll have them.
But now I'm out of the habit of buying them
so I never have them.
So it's not even an option.
The price of them keeps going up
and I thought that would stop me.
But also the amount of money I make
has kept going up.
So I just fucking keep buying them.
Well, okay.
You heard it here.
Stop paying Simzi.
You're killing him.
You're killing me.
Pay us.
Customers.
Yeah, yeah.
Pay the PCP.
Donate.
I don't even smoke weed.
No, I don't.
I hate weed.
I've only smoked weed twice
and I had a horrible experience both times.
I smoked a few times
and it's been like okay at best
and pretty fucking terrible at worst.
I was like, I'm violently sick
and then also all of my senses
went backwards and then I passed out.
That sounds like some strange weed.
I've looked it up
and I think I'm just allergic to it
and had like a really violent reaction
or something.
I had one time that I smoked it
that I thought maybe there was some other stuff
in what I smoked
because this one time that I had it
I had like a really intense
like physical body high
that felt like a nightmare
and I wanted to scream.
That's probably just more accurate.
Like that's not normal.
Yeah.
And it hasn't always been like that.
But it's one time it was super bad.
Both times that it's happened
like everyone else who's done it
has been absolutely fine.
So either it's just
I have a really low tolerance for it
and it's fucked me up
and I think that I'm having
a nightmare reaction
and then it happens.
My understanding
it seems like some people
just feel different
when they smoke it
than other people do
and those people
and I think I'm one of them
and maybe you are too.
It just
for us it just feels like shit
and it's like no thanks.
It was a wild bite.
I mean I've
I've had it like
two or three times
and it's only been
when Trixie has given me some
I've probably done it maybe
or maybe a dozen times
maybe a dozen times at most.
We're so lame.
The most it's ever done
is
at Redcon 4 actually.
I had like a pretty mellow cool
walk on the beach at night.
I was like seeing weird
patents in the sand.
So I was like whoa,
that's nice.
And that was it.
That was the most I ever got high.
I've been much more drunk
than I have been high.
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah.
Before I ever smoked weed
the first high I ever got
was fucking
this is so embarrassing
but it was a
Downing Robotessin
because
my girlfriend in college
she in high school
she and her friends I guess
had just fucking down
Robotessin and Robotrip sometimes
and she got me to try it with her
and it was a
I mean it wasn't
it wasn't too horrible.
It was fine
but it's just so embarrassing
to admit it.
Robotripping is not
it's not cool.
Wait.
It's not hip.
What is that?
It's when you just drink Robotessin.
What's Robotessin?
Is it a brand name
or is it?
It's cough syrup.
Oh.
It's DMX I think
is the chemical in it.
It's a
BMX.
Robotessin.
What's the
what's the active chemical
in Robotessin?
It is
cyanide.
Weed.
Dextro.
Dextro metherfan
is the active chemical
that I don't know
makes you fucking
high and I
did that a bunch of times.
So you got absolutely
shot faced on cough syrup
and had a
had a lovely time.
I don't know if I was shit faced.
I mean it's
I mean I don't know.
I was probably I probably acted weird
because you know
I have really visceral memories
of the first time I smoked weed and
just like after after I'd been sick about
six times I went and sat in the garden on a chair
while everyone else was like getting drunk and stuff
and my friend who's got a really thick
Bristolian accent came over
and kneeled next to me and he's like
it's alright bro.
You're just having a bad trip.
It's alright.
Just calm down.
Just don't worry about it.
It happens to everybody.
It happens to the best of us.
And I was just sitting there just like
please leave me alone.
I can't hear a speech now without feeling
worse.
Yeah.
God bless him.
He's trying his best.
The time that I had the worst
reaction to it I remember
I felt um
I was in a room.
I went to a party after I smoked.
This was with that same
girlfriend in college.
We went to a party
and I was like sitting on the floor
and there was a ceiling fan
going.
It was blowing the air in the room
and
I could feel the wind from the ceiling fan
but in my in my high
my weed state I felt
like it was like a
torrent.
It was like a
I was being like blasted
with like dry air from this
ceiling fan that was like drying me out
and killing me.
In my weed form.
Yeah.
And I was like this is the worst feeling
I've ever felt.
It was awful.
Awful awful.
The second time I had it it felt like
the inside of my nose was swelling up
which which is why I think I'm allergic
because it just sounds like it was happening
and then like it sounds like yeah
the position of taste on my
tongue was swapped.
So like if like a piece of chicken
like because I had chicken wings like afterwards
and I was like I'm gonna eat something because I feel weird
and then like food
on the right side of my mouth felt like
it was on the left side
and I've tried looking this up
and I've never heard of anyone having the experience
like this ever again with weed
and all my friends were completely fine
and I think I'm just
How bizarre.
It was very odd.
It was one of the most unusual.
I've never heard of that before either.
No.
I think you I think you just invented
a new a new symptom.
Maybe I'm just like
of the weed overdose.
Maybe I'm just lying to myself.
Maybe it didn't happen.
I don't know.
It was only last year but
I mean you were twisted.
I was twist.
Hello.
Whatever the new one is.
Twist.
Hello.
Cool.
Dude.
That's so base.
We should pay a mural.
Back to hook me up.
Hook me.
Introduce me.
You're going to get those connections.
Oh, do you want a back to the.
The Gib.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sure.
Like is dying corner.
aside from aside from all that's happening a new
Complications happened not related. I assume. I have an ear problem now. I think it's nothing serious
Sorry, sorry, I'm just I'm just so bored listening to other people's problems
Then that's so awfully rude you nasty man. I
Know and yet I can't help it. It's my nature to be a nasty man
Capricious
Continue. So is it just some sort like like ear pain or like you can't hear properly? No, no, no it I
Can't hear low frequencies in one of my ears and I couldn't tell what was wrong for a really long time because
most of what I listen to is like
Fine, but as soon as I speak because it's coming from my you know inside my head
I hear all of the frequencies of my voice including the low-end and it's very clearly not right in one of my ears
I can't hear low frequencies in my left ear. It is
so
Frustrating because I feel like I just need to just to grab something in there and pull it out like as a blockage
but obviously
I'm stupid
There was a bit of earwax there and I was like like scratching at it with my finger trying to get it out apparently
That's the worst thing you could do is try to get it out
Because um, you're just pushing it further in and now I think I have a blockage
And that sucks you should you should watch you ever watch those videos on YouTube of like earwax
Blot like clump extraction. No, please. No
No, no, no, I mean
You there you can see fucking giant fucking like lumps of like condensed earwax be removed from a person's outer ear canal
And I mean it's kind of gross, but it's also kind of like oh
It's nice to see that removed because that was really bad
I think kind of satisfying I mean see it to see it. It's it's satisfying to feel it removed
I don't look at it when I scratch my ear
Hmm
Gross but I feel like the low point of my life is watching weird YouTube videos like that sometimes like
There was a pimple popping. Yeah, it's like worse than that like specifically there was an example
Like I was drunk and I came home from the club with like my friends and like I went upstairs the bed
Because I don't want to talk to these people anymore. I'm spent I'm done
I'm gonna be an introvert and hide in my room and I was I was drunk and eating like crisps and
watching videos of a guy testing like mouse drowning
contraptions and I
It was horrible and I don't know why I did it and I generally consider that one of the lowest points of my life
Well, I wasn't like it entertained. I was watching this guy. So say why why would you do it then?
I don't know. I found it and I was like whoa
What the fuck and I start watching it and I I feel evil for having done that I
Feel I feel like Justin Royland for having done that. I also feel that you are evil
The point is just that it's it's cuz like yesterday I
Was feeling so bad in the morning and the night before
That I could barely like I think it was like
Super dehydrating something going on with my liver is causing me to like dehydrate really easily and very difficult to
Rehydrate so I've been drinking loads of water and it hasn't been going in it's like frustrating and I was so cracked and dry and dusty
I felt like I was gonna turn into dust like that one episode of Angel where that guy turns to dust
Because it's a creature demon goes inside him and sucks all the moisture out of it
Oh, yeah, Harry Potter and the sorcerer's stone Harry Potter and the demon that sucks the moisture out from on the side
The demon that sucks the moisture
It was just like so perfect. I was watching this angel and this guy
He was like possessed by this demon that was forcing him to drink
But he was not getting the water in and he was his face was cracking and there was like some like face makeup to make him look
Like it was cracking like down the side of his face and then he fell over and turned into a pile of dust
And I felt that that was the most visceral feeling what I have ever had
Stone
When when professor quarrel just crumbled to dust and fell and fell and and then Voldemort's
Ghostface went screaming through Harry's torso. I I felt seen
Anyway that that
Coupled with like I was I was trying to survive was trying to like feel better
I think last week. I wasn't on the PCP because I was feeling similar
It was just so like I there's no energy and then today
I well over the last few days this ear thing has come up and I'm like
Just stop getting sick
Yeah, and I want to stab myself in the head with a knife doesn't seem fair
I stabbed myself in a head with a knife to get the ear. It's just not fair like what have you done
that means that
You need to fucking fall apart all of a sudden
Yeah, I haven't released my secret project
Yeah, they were upset that I that I didn't release my secret
That's why I've escaped
Law for you now
So I'll kill you. I'll kill you. Oh, I'll kill you. I'll just kill you. I'll kill you. Oh, yeah
There's nothing special about it, I'm just mentioning it so you know
This is why I'm never doing a secret project because I will collapse
Simsie I was I guess I'm does it bear mentioning that one of the things we've talked about in my
Server is that you were one of you were one of the kuso mega people. Yes
You were on which is for anyone doesn't know that was Trixie's
Light I guess it started as a light novel series, but it was gonna be more than that
Right, it was it was a light novel parody series that was gonna get a physical release
Basically, you she was commissioning like manga pages though, right?
So or were you were you just doing like character art for a light no, there were insert there was lots of different art
There was commissioned there was like a cover there was like a character page
Which is what I worked on like at the beginning of the night light novel where it lists all the characters and descriptions of them
And I did all the basic character designs for that
There was like a ton of like insert pages for key points in the story and things like that and um, yeah
So I was the guy who did like if you open up like a modigatary or some other light novel where they show all the characters at the front and says look
It's her. Wow. Look at it. Look at look at that
I have never read a light novel in my life. It's sort of it's still the same thing
It's like in a manga where you pick up a manga volume and it has like piccolo and he's smiling and stuff
You love it up to a picture you see and then and it makes you smile and you smile
God fucking piccolo rules
Piccolo really does rule we can all agree like triangle shoulders, and that's based
Yeah, Piccolo dresses like Dr. Hibbert's wife
with the big shoulder pads
I
The entire series
Yeah, she has a name. I think oh god. I think her name is like Janine is Vivian from the Fresh Prince of Bel-Air
She does look like she has she has spoken before
occasionally
There are there I
Since I since I watched the real gyms episode. I guess there I guess there are rumors of infidelity
I guess there are rumors. It's dr. Hibbert's been fucking around with his with his
I don't know. What would you call it?
Secretary or whatever?
It's all concubines. Okay, it's catamite, but it's all unsubstantiated
Der
Never had an episode
Never had an episode about him. He's like it. He's like everybody knows dr.
Hibbert never had an epic comic book guy has had an episode dr. Nick's had episodes
Yeah
I guess I guess dr. Hibbert's thing is like Applejack. He's like the doctor that is
He's he's a Republican so he's just like Applejack
He's just like Applejack because because like Applejack
Was the the straight man pony the the one that was not
Stupid and so she would always be the the character that would be like here's the truth you dumb fuck
Dr. Hibbert they always go to dr. Hibbert because he is the the responsible one who knows medicine
Dr. Nick is the one who doesn't and that's his joke dr. Hibbert is the straight man
He just has his joke we laughs at horrible
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, even what you can do like with an episode about a character like that
Wait, Applejack isn't the stupid one. I thought she was a stupid one
Wait, do you actually not know? No, I've never watched my little pony, but I've gotten the impression that she's just she's the one with the hat, right?
Oh, isn't there isn't there like an old quote? Oh my god, please please. Let me say what I want to fucking say
Oh my god, isn't there an old quote from like Gen 2 or whatever where it's like Applejack's a silly pony? I
Feel like that's a thing that is like a line that I've seen
Yes, Applejack is a silly pony. Okay, good. Thank you for confirming
See I was right. She's sorry sound like I'm cutting you off. I think my I'm sorry. Yeah, I know the connections bad
I know there's lag. I know it's not your fault, but I'm like, yeah
I I'm sorry. I flew off the handle a little there. I got a little frustrated feeling like I was being talked over
I know it's not because I'm sorry. I apologize
I brought the whole vibe down my little pony. Oh, please forgive me
Anyway, no, Applejack is the responsible one. She's she's yeah
She's the hard-working
doesn't react like down to earth cuz she's an earth pony
Twilight is like a a like a nerd that gets extremely stressed out about scheduling
Pinkie pie is jumping off the wall all the time Rainbow Dash is like
It's gay
Yeah, you know got their vices, you know, okay, okay
Cool
See, I don't know anything about my little pony. No Apple. No Applejack. Well, you better know
You should you should get into my little pony so that you can humanized versions of Fluttershy with
Humanized Applejack in in the boots Applejack is hard-working and honest and
runs a business and
loves her family and
Responsible and boring
Love's traditional equestrian values
Equester equestrian values from an outsider's perspective. She's definitely the coolest one. She has her
What the fuck no no the outside is perspective
Fucking
What the fuck are you talking about you're crazy where anything they don't look cool. That is very cool
It's it. It's a cowboy. Did she get the hat from it's cool. What do you mean?
She's she's not she get it from they don't have made by a haberdasher from a haberdashery, of course
They don't have fucking haberdashery's in the stable. I bet they fucking do I bet they fucking do actually
Probably made it herself. Yeah
That's cool
Yeah, she's the cool one cuz she has a hat. Yeah, it's fucking crazy. She's like
Twilight Sparkle has a fucking crown
So she does
That's a lie. I've never seen that. You're lying. You're a liar. Well, she's got a tiara
She doesn't she doesn't wear it all the time. Just sometimes lame on special special occasions lame. She's not cowboy. I'm googling
Oh, yeah, that's yeah Applejack's hat is identified as the one that bright Mac gave her
bright Mac being her dad
Just just chicken eggs. I thought that's a red. Where's the hat come from?
Luffy it's it's this emotional value the best character boy for turn up then
She's basically
Except she's nothing like him
Okay, but I'm sure there is a haberda. I'm sure someone in Ponyville runs a haberdashery
Somebody's got to know we can't all get our hats from our dead dads
Okay, no, that's where they spawn they if you have a if you are born with a hat on your head
When you come out of the room that means you're gonna be a dad of Applejack. That's what that means
I I think it's more like, you know, when we die
You know, we all drop loot, but your loot depends on your loot table and and dad's dads are on their own loot table
And dad's just have a very high chance to drop hats
Sentimental hats
Sentimental hats and AXP so you have the experience of your father dying and you level up
And you go yes, and you go all my strength rows
Thanks dad
Ah
The
It could be a funny like thing. Yeah, Kusa mega. Oh
Yeah, what Kusa mega?
What how's about Kusa mega? Well, basically
Well at first I was in the wrong
Because I was about a week late in sending like all the designs and stuff like it took me ages to get them done because I was balancing
Work
Tricks he didn't seem to mind too much. It was just like hey
We got to get this thought we've got to get this project done so we can start the Kickstarter is what she kept saying to me
I was like, okay. Yeah, I'm gonna do that and I gave it to her
And if a few weeks later and we had heard nothing about the Kickstarter and we we never have again
Who's you you and the other you and the other artists you mean? Yeah, exactly
So the the idea was it was stupid deal. I shouldn't have taken it
It was like well below my commission rate for five drawings
And it was like payment only on successful funding of the Kickstarter, which is just the stupid really yeah, exactly
If you if you ever do
Something like this like like like you knock it for someone
Yeah, I didn't sign on for immediate pay. No, there was no guarantee that I would get paid
Did you did you not get paid at all?
No, I did get paid in the end like what what actually happened was the Kickstarter was basically canceled and then she just paid
All the artists out of pocket, but um, yeah
It it took a while and apparently I was the last artist to get paid and um, yeah
So yeah, just like forgot apparently and I'm pretty I'm pretty sure everyone else got paid
It took me making like a
Post on Twitter saying like any other artist for the kusa mega project. Please contact me like that like vague and mysterious
Yeah, I saw yeah, I saw that I saw that and I saw I remember you replied to it and saying what happened
I was curious like I was mad
I was mad because I I saw that and I inferred I just inferred like why would somebody make this tweet?
Somebody didn't get paid for their work and it makes me mad and when it's when it's someone I know I'm like
Don't do that. I mean it was stupid
I was like I was a big fan of Trek see at the time and I was like watching all their videos
And then it was like I'm making a light level and artists can sign up and I was like hey
I do that, but it wasn't even that because I had done the first like light novel chapters that she released on YouTube
It's like an audiobook
I drew like a piece fan out for it and send it and she retweeted it
I was like that's cool, and then like immediately like that like as soon as I was like messaging her
I was like hey, I want to work on the actual physical release project
She was like I was like can I do this page because it was like a big list of all the different parts of the book that you
Could work on like a drawing a specific scene or something like that
And I was I was like hey can I do this one and she was like actually
I want you to do all of the character designs at the beginning of the book and I was like oh Jesus
But yeah, I did them slightly weak slightly lake like a week or two weeks late late. Sorry, and um
That's bad. Don't be late people, but um and then nothing three months, and then project was canned and like
So the reason why I signed on for basically no guarantee of pay was because I was such a big fan of
Trixie at the time, so I was literally doing the
The parasocial fucking. Oh, I like this person. I trust them
So parasocial of you
Cream you got dr. Wolf. Yeah, it's that yeah, you got that
You get you get dr. Wolf. It's so it's he's still
He's I got the money in the end is fine
Yeah, true. Yeah. Um doctor. Dr. Wolf is still at it
I saw a reddit post that someone made being like guys
I think dr. Wolf is stealing our theories for his videos and this is like a recent post like like two weeks ago
People are still like
Upset although, you know, I feel like that's just
That's common practice, right for youtubers to churn out content
They just go to a subreddit and just like regurgitate some shit. They read on a subreddit. Oh, yeah, and make a list of it
Yeah, yeah, so I don't know that's common practice
So I think that guy might be disappointed the the one piece the one piece community on YouTube is a nightmare of just
Regurgitating nonsense in evil bio
It's not good. I'm sure evil bio. I don't watch any of the no
YouTube one piece. Yeah, you're better off. I've watched like a few bits and pieces like and just been told a lot about it
By the other members of the party discord and it's like, yeah
These people just stupid and they just lie and they just make up things and pretend that it's real. I
I
Haven't really watched much one piece content. I don't really get the sense that there is a lot of like
In-depth one piece content going on. It's a lot of like a
lot of very like surface level like just like chapter recaps and like
Just kind of like theory crafting but in like the basically just the sense that you're just like reading shit off the wiki
People who make nonsense bullshit theories and then like other people pick up those theories and take them as facts and then
Regurgitate and make their own theories based on those theories and it's like almost like a big chaotic mess of just misinformation and lies
Yeah, I think I'd watched a bit of some of that theory stuff
And I was only interested because a lot of one piece
It's so big there's so much of it, and I forget a lot of things
So it's so much of it an order like doesn't clarify like things things that brought together
It's like oh, I do remember that happening
And I guess if you stretch it you can make it part of this theory like I never really took the theory too seriously
But I was I don't know. It's just sort of like. Oh, yeah
I guess it's like harm us, but it's embarrassing and like it's enough, but yeah some
people people I
Don't know theories crafting is it's fun. I've defended it before
Yeah
When it when it gets to the point where somebody theory crafts a theory that doesn't end up being true, and then they I
Don't know lash out to the creator
Now it's not always
One piece you just be anything then that's stupid and dangerous and vile like the thing that I think about
With like reddit theory crafting is um
Blade kind eyewear was that poster on the Homestuck subreddit. Oh?
Who had that whole that whole theory about them aspect inversion that like a pretty sizable?
like
Chunk of the of the Homestuck subreddit community like believed in and thought was sort of like a secret
spur of mechanic that
like
At the time kind of sounded
The gist of it was basically that like there is a thing that can happen in spur where you can like if you basically
Like go evil you become like the opposite of your aspect and the basically the only real evidence was this was that Rose
LaLonde was the seer of light, but then when she turned evil for a second
She went dark, so it was like oh did she did she embody her opposite aspect the aspect of void?
Like how what does this mean of a seer the blind?
Can can can the you know can other aspects do this?
Is this like a universal thing and like other quote-unquote evidence was brought forward?
But that was like the only one and like it like really quickly like as the story went on
It was like it never really happened like that again, and it was clear like no. It's just kind of a
Maybe sort of a thematic
Coincidence that like she is the character of light and then she was taken over by this dark thing. I mean it's not like
Yeah
basically, yeah
so
Yeah, but the the the the aspect inversion theory generalizes to like ah, yes, so like under these circumstances
John if he were to undergo such a process he being the air of breath would you know become he would become the
I don't know the the whatever of blood because blood is the aspect of bonds and oaths and and
relations and
Breath is the one of freedom and and non-commitment or whatever
movement
And it was like no
But like so many words so much fucking digital ink spilled
Over this like yeah baseless fucking thing based on like one. It's piece of evidence
It's harmless and then defended until it makes fans like rabidly attack each other over their
Disagreements about whether or not this fan theory is like more accurate or bad or stupid or not I
Like communities are terrible
That theory appealed to me because I'm like I like to imagine because I was really into the the spurb aspect of it
I liked the gamey parts of it and the parts of the homestead that explored spurb the game
So the idea that there was like all these hidden mechanics of the game going on that like we're influencing the plot
I found that really interesting
But the evidence just wasn't there for it
But a lot of people were really committed on an emotional level to defending it as a thesis
Blade kind eyewear would fucking post these like
Pages and pages long posts like every time there was a new update being like here's my new analysis of what's going on in
In in the you know seen through a lens of understanding that includes
Aspect inversion as a game mechanic LeMau
Pretty funny pretty good
pretty based
Homestuck
Homestuck um, I want to complain read homestuck so that you can draw a brisco with big boobies
One of these days one of you should you could just do that anyway
You could just do that anyway. I could just do that anyway
I tried homestuck years ago because I had a crush on a girl and she was like you should check out this comic called homestuck
She was right. It's like
This is stupid. Oh you fucking asshole. You fucking asshole. I was 12 when I was dumb
I've never tried again. Yeah, I was like 12 or something. Why how old are you now? I'm 22
Maybe I wasn't 12. How old was I those that would have been
No, I guess homestuck was around 10 years ago, but that was like I would have been like early homestuck, right?
Maybe I don't know
2013 I
Think oh, whatever cuz attack on time was out. I know that she was obsessed with that
That would have been
2010 then
No, I think I'm talking was like 2013 2014. I think Jesus, okay
Jesus Christ. Yeah
In 2014 wait, no, I don't know how it no in 2014 I would have been 15
Okay
Fucking remember when I tried to read out
I was like one I
In my sleep because it's like Mozart you put you put your baby into the Mozart aka homestuck
Discography and then watch them grow
If you ask me to list homestuck characters
I'd be like John Egbert and I know him because he's the main one and then Drisker and I know him because of you
I know her because of you
That's my greatest contribution to the world is to tell people about risker
Before we move on before we move on from kusa mega, I want to complain
I want to complain about Trixie just for a minute just for a moment
Just for a moment. I want to point out something that has been bothering me and it'd be done
I it can be done. I can I can do it
I haven't mentioned this but it I feel like I want people to know about it because it's really irritating and that is that there was
I've made up tweet a tweet about this yesterday
Um, there was rad content that Trixie had that nobody else had
That she said she was going to give us and she hasn't done it and she has fucking
Obscunded and become a vagrant
And I just I just I feel like it's safe to assume now that she's never going to do it and probably doesn't even have it anymore
And that just makes me really mad that makes me real fucking angry
And I just want to fucking say it confirmation. I tried to this was a footage was like stuff
we had recorded on phones and
Cameras that was supposed to be behind the scenes and also the the footage recorded at the meet-up
I think this is all of the stuff that she was that what it was
Okay, I wasn't even sure like what it was that she had just that she had some rad con stuff and she said
She would give it to us. Yeah
Yeah, okay behind the scenes and meet-up stuff. Okay, cool
I was a in the in the fucking garbage in the fucking garbage because she doesn't give a fuck. Okay. Go on
I yeah, I haven't gotten any confirmation that she's like
Gotten rid of it or she can't give it. I did contact her
Not too long ago before she was she went on that road trip
And she said yeah, she's on it. She's on a permanent road trip now
Yeah, I mean, I don't know there was like before she went on the road trip. She was like packing stuff up
And she's like, oh, yeah, I'm a little busy right now, but I'll get it to you
I was like, okay, please could you because it might be difficult to do it from the road
That was the last I heard and I guess I could ask her again
Like I don't know. I feel like this is just gonna be a continual like yeah, I'll do it for like months years
That's all she ever does you ask all anything you just ask her and she's always says yeah, I'll do it
Yeah, she'll promise anything. She doesn't give a fuck. So like a Kickstarter. She's a big fucking liar
and
I'll tell you what I did when she when she was doing the
The the not the yard sale. Yeah, the yard sale
Someone bought her hard drives and I and I DM'd the person who bought her hard drives to ask them
Hey, if you get those hard drives and they have data on them
Let me know because I feel like I absolutely believe that she would just sell the hard drives that have our fucking rad content on them
I totally think that's something she would do. So I don't know. It's possible
It's possible
That may it would be so it would be hilarious if that were the way that we could recover
That stuff. I'm not holding my breath. I feel like it's an outside shot, but just in case
It would be very funny
It would be such a normal thing to do if you're selling a hard drive to wipe it first
But then again, what does she know about technology? Maybe she just didn't think to do that. Yeah, it could happen
She computers she uses a computer. She might have thought of it. Let's hope she didn't
That's her. I mean, yeah, my I feel like she probably would have my eye
I mean, we can dream we can just say I'm just saying there's a chance
It was whatever whatever. I'm fucking pissed off about it
I'm fucking pissed off and
Disrespected and disgusted and I don't know
Yeah, that sucks. That's another reason to be annoyed. I guess
Okay, well, I guess I guess I guess I could I could go on I could go on but I guess let's continue
You said you were done bad. You said I was done with tricks. Hey, I know
I know
Oh, but yeah, but then they did that interview they did that interview with Oki Oki's weird stories who I'm a fan of and who
For some reason, I don't know what compelled him to do this
But he de-embed me he followed me and he de-embed me to let me know that he had just done that interview with them
And I was like, oh wow cool. Okay looking forward to it. I
Did too it was it was entirely about Trixie's content, which is like
Yeah
If you're a fan of her and you're you know, he's like the the conversation
Boiled down to Trixie your content's different and it's bad and we don't like it and Trixie's like that's okay
I want a new audience and that's the entire video
Um
Well, I don't care about her like career goals. It's like whatever. I just want the rad con stuff
I want the stuff that is
Tight up in and back the stuff. That's the stuff. That's the stuff. That's ours and not hers. Yeah, I would like that too
um, I mean in about that I
Get I
What stood out to me about that interview was how she keeps like pivoting and playing like this weird rhetorical
game
Where she will in the same breath claim to
Not care about money not care about losing the audience
But then at the same time insist like well, I had to post all my music stuff on my main channel because it's the only way
It'll get views. That's the only way I can make money off it. That's the only way I can build an audience for it
It uh, it was a very interesting video because uh, lots of the points that oki brought up were like proofed by her actions during the interview
Like it like it it's almost like
He's calling her out for this stuff and then the video itself is just like a complete
Microcosm of all of those things like giving example
um, he he he briefly brought up her inconsistency on like, um
Like a content and like like void gazes is meant to be like a cooling show like with fans, isn't it?
I don't know sometimes. I don't know
We like
A big point of the the interview was uh him saying we don't know what your new content is even supposed to we don't know
What this channel's for like it's too broad and like
That interview was emblematic of it because it was fitted into the void gazer format
Which is like not that
It should have been its own separate thing. It's even more confusing. You know, you're right. Yeah, I I guess I guess that's true
Uh
I don't know. It's probably most not the most solid criticism, but yeah, why yeah, why I feel like why why is this a void gazer?
I guess I guess I agree with that. It's odd
I don't know. I feel like her answers were were
Like they maybe were confusing but her
Like goal seemed pretty clear
I don't care about appeasing my older audience
I believe somehow
For some reason the what I am doing now will create a bigger and newer audience that will make me money
And I just need to get enough people who just like whatever it is. I do exactly. Yeah, I'm like, yeah, that's okay
That seems pretty clear if you if you believe that
I guess I I see her perspective, but she's wrong. So she is wrong
You can all agree on that
Uh, oh, I hate her. I I fucking hate her. God damn it
Uh, uh, I don't know. I'm so fucking mad. I'm so fucking mad guys
I'm I'm I'm sitting here release the red hands
Hands the red hands on the table hands to God
Heart heart on my sleeve. I just fucking hate her and she's a bad person and she's done wrong
And she's done wrong by me in particular and all of us collectively
And fuck her forever. It makes me feel bad because I keep checking the fucking Kiwi farms
And it makes me feel sick of the ship. Some of the shit people have read writing on there is disgusting and like nasty
I I saw I saw some real racist shit in there
Like pretty recently and I was like, oh
Yeah, that's just that's what these people are. It's like
Yeah, I go I go there to laugh at tricksy making stupid business decisions
All it is is fucking transphobic and racist comments and I don't care about that
They just they just can't help themselves. They can't fucking think they can't fucking see beyond that
Like that's such a fucking blinder to them. They're like, ah
That's it. That's where that's where the buck stops. Oh god. Ah
I like laughing at people but not in that way
No
Jesus
Make make a joke about something funny. Why don't you? Yeah, like how they're literally hobos
You're fucking rubes there
Freelance freelance roadies
Fat hobos
Freelance roadies living in a Prius because I stole their RV because I bend saints stole their RV
And have hidden it in an undisclosed location and will not be returning it until the rad con cut is released
This is a blackmail situation
We must we must have an exchange
Then you can't afford to hide an RV. You can't afford to find a place where you can hide an RV. Come on, man
Not unless you donate to me at patreon.com slash ben saint to fund it boys
Fund my fund my my my uh, my whatever parking space for the RV until until the exchange can be can be coordinated
Oh, man
What were you saying? Are we saying give?
Oh, I don't know. I I forgot that it was the leg was like
Sorry leaving me in the dust. I didn't know what it was happening. You know people, you know, I'm sorry
I'm seething. I know I know it must come across like I'm just fucking coping and seething and you know what I am
I absolutely am and I have been for a while and it's it's peaking. It's peaking and it's not going away
Uh
And maybe I should talk to a doctor or something
Uh, yeah, maybe you should touch some grass. Maybe you should touch touch some weed. Maybe I should touch some
No
No, no, no
if I
I feel like if I smoked weed while I was angry
I would like
Cry I would like like the weed would like affect my judgment and it would like it heighten the emotion
To the point that I would like break down and cry about it because I would like feel it even more strongly
Uh, so no, I don't want to do that
I don't I don't
You know what they say like you got to be in like a good emotional place before you get higher else it like
You can like, you know, that emotion can like spiral out of control or whatever or like it heightens it thumbnail
A thumbnail and title for this video Ben literally cries about Trixie
It's too much coping and seething coping and seething which I am admittedly I am both doing both of those
Well, but no more
That's that's as much as I'll admit to
um
Oh
This is unrelated
But it's sort of related to you being late with the kuso mega drawings. I was also late
Uh with the cover
Which I just finished drawing this morning for the kato and anthology
Which uh, I don't think I don't think it's my fault that the uh kickstarter
Launch was delayed. I hope it wasn't well now
Uh, but anyway, it was it was gonna launch last
Friday
But I think it might be launching this friday or it's launching sometime this week the kickstarter
for that, um
And uh, I don't know link link down in the description
So by the time the episode's out, it's either already started or starting today
They they told I I gave them the cover
I gave them the cover and they told me that by the time this episode is out the kickstarter for that will be launched
Uh, which would be pretty cool
Be pretty cool. If that fucking they've had the fucking sell a bunch of copies
Uh, uh white white lion, uh, uh hd remaster
Actually, I have to I have to go and get that re-scanned. I have to go and get like a better scanner
I should try and make a comic at some point. I mean have you never have you never
No, I've never made anything more than like a page and it was like born
It's nothing all you you
It's funny to me that's like
If i'm gonna draw something
It better be a comic. Yeah
Yeah
I don't know like when you first mentioned the kato thing to show going from point a to point b
Otherwise
That's right. That's right
Like when you first mentioned the kato thing I was like, man, I'd love to do that
But I got commissions and uni work and stuff to do
And I want to sit around and play red dead and waste time. I don't know
Yeah
Yeah, I mean a video video games are a poison on my life and I need to just uninstall steam
I'm me me too. I uh
I I I spent a day I spent like a day and a half drawing the the cover for the anthology
And uh, it was it was tough because there was a lot of detail I had to get in there took me a long time
It was pretty it was it was a it was a
Trying experience it was a lot of work and then I had to decompress with an entire day of noida
And it was terrible. It's like time to get back to work on my game. Oh or
Or I could just play noida for
Like 20 straight hours and that's what I did that
If you do a work thing and then you follow it with another work thing, you're obviously not going to want to do the second one
Yeah, that's what I think that's what I tell myself. That's what I tell myself. I earned this I earned this
I did like three commissions in one day. I don't know about 20 hours straight, but
I did three commissions in one day and then I like turned it off and I was like, okay
And I just sat and played through all of resident evil village in like one sitting and I was like cool
good game
Everyone's everyone's fucking abuzz about resident evil village. It's a very good. It's a good game
It's a triple a game that came out and it's finished and it's good and it it's makes me happy that that's happened
What is on press? What is good?
Never have I heard such a thing. What what's good about it? Um
It's it's got it's it's very broad in terms of its focus like the action is good
It's it's um, it does a good job of making things. Is it an action title? Do you do you shoot?
Do you shoot the big booby lady?
Yeah, you shoot the big booby lady. I don't I don't know about spoilers
I don't know about spoilers because the game is
We don't have to get in the spoiler. You do shoot. They make you shoot the big booby lady
Oh, she's barely in it
Really how many yeah, she's there's five like main bosses and she's one of them
So she's like she's one of the longest sections of the game
I mean, she's only she's only about an hour and a half of content from seeing it on social media
I assume the entire game is about escaping from her fucking crazy haunted house. No, no, that's just the that's the first bit
That's like I see the first section
It's good. Just be horny though
Yeah, they Capcom Capcom were very crafty with the marketing and they were like, hmm
Let's release this trailer with like all these vague images on it
She was in that first trailer and then they just focused entirely on her because they knew that people were obsessed with her
Yeah, I mean
Makes makes sense. I guess I would say I would say most of the best stuff in the game is completely unrelated to her
Which is surprising
considering how focused they were on it
What it's spoiler me. What is the lore for her being so big?
She is uh, basically
Uh, do you have a play resin evil seven?
No, I've never played a video game
Okay, there's evil mold parasites, uh, that like just like a natural thing that makes people weird
um
Okay, there's this other lady who's trying to bring back a daughter who died with by using the mold parasite in some weird way
And she experimented on a bunch of people and she gave it to the big lady and it meant that she just kept growing
And it's now immortal land of empire
It's like a bio fungus thingy nice
present evils nice, so she's it's uh, she's a clicker. She's a
Mushroom she's towed at from yeah, super mario
She's more like uh lichen like a moldy guy
Uh
I see like uh spoilers
She turned like when you fight her she turns into a big dragon monster and she's like sticking out the top of it
and what?
What you mean like um, you mean like uh that fucking demon spider lady from dark souls
Yeah, a little bit like that except she her body's like fucked up as well. But like there's like a giant dragon monster
It's a reasonable game. It's what surprised the villains turned into big monsters at the end. Wow
I've also never played a resident evil. So it happens in every in every single game
Like past the first one the villains turned into a big monster at the end. So
Well now
All right, you thought you could now I know but in fact I am a giant scorpion exactly like it
They were like, oh, it's sexy. Let's turn into a monster and ruin it and make it sad. Well
Yeah
You gotta you gotta you gotta get rid of her somehow
You gotta you gotta have some kind of conclusion to to her arc of having big tits in a big
Why can't the conclusion be why can't the conclusion be
That you save her and then she fucks you and you have
Because easins winters is a good man. He's too busy trying to save his daughter. That's not family friendly. That's evil
What you just described is fucking evil and it's against god's law
You have to fucking turn her into a dragon and blow her fucking face off
Also, also in the beginning of the game you can't solve all your problems by turning them into dragons and blowing them up
It's never failed. It hasn't failed me yet at the very beginning of the game
The main character's wife is like killed in front of him. So it's like, I don't think he'd be up for some sex right now
He's trying to save his daughter
That's it's a it's gonna be the rebound. He's on the rebound
There's now the time within hours. Oh, so he gets his fingers bitten off and she cuts his arm at one point
It's not nice. Never been a better time for a big booby lady to fucking come into your into your life
Yeah, the blessing
I don't I don't actually think she's sexy. I hate her face. Her face. I hate her scary face
She does have like a weird old lady face if you look closer at she's got like crusty dusty skin and looks weird
yeah, yeah, yeah crusty dusty skin
and uh,
Heard big teeth
And I'm like, I don't want that looking at me
And I and I and I get that the appeal
I get that the appeal is like a juxtaposition of like her slightly horrifying
Face and skin unlike her fucking sexy ass milf body
Yeah, but I'd rather just have a sexy ass milf body without a horrifying face
If I'm being honest, you can't put that in resident evil. That doesn't have a place in there. It's gotta be spooky
I guess
I think when I play as like a normal human with big tits
I think the lady who makes the puppets in the game is sexy or anyway, that's a hot take
You don't even get to fucking see her. You see like a painting of her
She's like
I don't even know what they know. Yeah
He's uh, she's just like a pretty girl
Nice. Yeah red. She's pretty girl and like a gothic black dress. She met henson
Yeah
She makes muppets she makes evil muppets not muppets puppets
Oh
Darn
Resident evil with muppets in it
She's the uh, she's the jumping around
She's the cause of the the most horrifying segment I've ever played in a video game
Which is what like her section is and uh, it made me feel the most the most horrifying segment of any video game
Really any video game I've played
Okay, and I've played a fair few horror games and uh that one shattered me up the most
Huh
I I'm just gonna say I don't uh, I don't want to think about babies ever again
Oh gross. Yeah
It's not pleasant
hideous
Sounds like a fucking nightmare
The second half is like a nightmare, but I kind of love it because it turns into resident evil nonsense
Where you shoot things nightmare in like a in in what kind of a way because nightmares seem like in like in like uh
Oh, this this is not totally consistent with anything that's come before in the new continuity
It's just wacky zany. Yeah
You there's a there's a boss boss battle where you ride a mech and shoot a giant monster
Um
Okay, you you play as chris redfield running through a village killing like hundreds of werewolves
Which like took you like three minutes to kill at the beginning of the game
You just kill them with like one shot of a gun and shoot like giant laser beams at a big mold pile and stuff
It's crazy
But I didn't see any of this in the trailer. No, they didn't put any in the trailer
This is all this is all wanton spoilers. Everybody stopped listening. Um
But uh, yeah, and there's like a twist at the end. It's a cool game. I liked it a lot. It made me happy
Ah, yes, I guess if you like video games, I guess if you're into that shit
I know you two don't like care about like triple a games at all. Do you?
No, um, I really don't know not usually
Like I usually get into a game like a hundred years after it was relevant. Yeah, I'm like, wow. Have you ever heard of
Super Mario 64 guys
It's a jump so gross. I have a compulsive issue where backwards long jump up the infinite staircase. It is cool. That is cool
Like I've been playing death stranding
And it's death death stranding look baby in it. I know I know that game's not that new anymore
But to me I I consider it a new game because it's gonna come out like two years ago
Yeah, that game looks kind of cool from what it is interesting
The whole look honestly just just the yeah like the the fact that you got to like fucking navigate
Like the terrain and you got a stack shit on your back and you got to deal with like
A very intricate like carrying capacities
Navigation puzzles just seems neat. It's like it's just like a cool thing to base a game around
It feels like an indie game that was just like remade by a triple-a studio or something
It feels like somebody had this idea
And uh, and it's weird and it's it's got all the stupid kajima shit that's clearly shoved in to be like ha ha wacky kajima
But that's not what's cool about it. It's just satisfying. It's like satisfying busy work. It's one of those games
What what did I watch uh?
It was either joseph anderson or noa called welger vey
I think no noa definitely did do a video on death stranding. I don't know. I don't know if just I've I've definitely seen uh noas
Uh, if joseph anderson did one. I probably watched it as well, but I don't remember matthew matosis did as well
Oh
He was a lot more sure
Yeah, I'm sure I've seen both of those then. Yeah, and uh, super bunny hop. Yeah
Everyone everyone had a thing about everyone's talked about death stranding barry kramer talked about it
And he had baseless criticisms that uh, who cares about that guy? Yeah, I wouldn't have seen that why that's funny
It's a bad video. I guess he made that kingdom hearts video. Yeah, that also like wasn't that good, but no
But everyone watched it because it was extremely topical at the time
He did like a 20 minute video about skyward sword where the the only point I got from the video
It's why is this the sky's yellow and that looks stupid
Oh, okay. Jesus. Why are the clouds yellow? It's extremely. It's it's
Barry's
Analysis videos there. They have good points in them, but yeah, they are bloated
To to such a degree with like goofy speech
I'm just not into it
Yeah, I I love youtubers that just don't waste your time like people who don't try and do jokes
Like if they can slip in the jaw for people who are just making the video and he has what it needs into it
Like I mean matthew metosis is my when yeah, yeah, I was gonna say matthew metosis
He's so like deadpan monotone the entire way and then occasionally he slips in like a joke
Yeah, he lets like he leaves a little bit of
Space for you to chuckle to yourself and then he moves on to the next clip. It's great. Yeah
He's not try it like he doesn't shove it in if he has an idea for it
He'll put it in but he doesn't like try to constantly have something funny happening in his videos
Which is a big problem with a lot of review-based content on the internet. I think this is a problem with my content
Like I go back to like work money. I thought I thought you succeeded pretty well
I I would say I would say yes
That yeah, I was pretty good at being funny
Like I I was annoyed at people like kadikaris who would do the loud talking and never laugh at anything
um
I
But I felt like I was pretty funny, but I felt like some of my videos. I was just doing the loud talking
And some of the earlier ones. I was like, oh god. I don't want to I don't want to go back and listen to this
I want to like scott the was but his videos are
A lot of them are like just loud talking is the joke a little bit and i'm like i'm just not into it
I'm just not you seem like a cool guy
But you're i'm just not into the style of comedy that you're putting on display
There's there's some people who do a good balance like some call me johnny does pretty good videos
I've never heard of them. He's very fairly small. He just does like videos about like resin evens
He just does a series called johnny versus where he talks about stuff
And he's just like uh, he's just like a friendly fat man who talks about video games and makes like decent jokes
I I remember seeing his avatar and thumbnails and I was like that this motherfucking piece of shit
I just didn't like his avatar. It's not a step. Yeah
Wait, who at last time the voicemails recommended that I watch someone and I actually did
Oh my god, it was it was I I know it was um
Oh god, who fucking was it? It was that guy with the purple mask
That guy with the purple mask I actually went and I watched one of his videos and it was like all right
Markiplier
No, he's like a nobody. He's got like 600 subs markiplier with this new luchadorie
Cosplay go be amigos
Viewers go back to last episode listen to whatever it was
Whoever it was that they recommended that I watch a channel of and I watched a video and he's got like
He's like a really loud
He's he's got the same accent as kim justice. It's a very it's not just a british accent. It's a very specific kind of
It's a very specific kind of british accent. Oh, and he like burst into laughter like
like
Sometimes like he'll end a sentence and just like start cackling
um, and uh, it's
kind of funny, I guess
I can't remember what his fucking name was I subbed in everything because it was like this is all right
Check the recent subscriptions if you can I'm looking I'm looking. I can't I can't find isn't there like a thing on the left side
I'm looking wait. No, I'm logged into the I'm logged into the wrong account
I'm logged into into uh
I was logged in I was logged in as the pcp. I was I should have been logged in as myself
I never watched uh, Noah
Cold World Javais until like yesterday and I watched like eight of his videos in a row and I was like, oh my god
There's another one. There's another really good video game guy. I love I love Noah. He's great. You should watch all of his stuff
his fucking
His fucking line reads are so bad. Oh, it's charming though. It's a little charming. I don't even mind it
I really don't
It yeah, they're just
It's it's funny because you you you you listen to him and he's like, oh he messed up that line
But you realize that it doesn't matter because it's it's a youtube video and you don't care
You've never cared and the only reason people have good audio is because they think they need it
What is this genre of youtuber called who'd like smart guys who talk about video games and don't waste your time with jokes like
We need like a name for these people
Yeah
Like
There's no glamour to it, which is what I really like
There's almost like no persona behind it at all. It's just here's here's lots of points
Well constructed and a good argument
Yeah, true. There's there's no ego to it. There's no, you know
It's good and they've all got really nice voices and ways of delivering their stuff, which is great
Which helps a lot. Have you seen I really like I really like his uh his travel logs
Where he just talks about I haven't seen any of those
He I think there's there's like
Two or three of them. There's like one where he like visits a bunch of
Places that are
I found it. Oh, there's one where he visits a bunch of places that are like inspired locations in the fallout games
And then there's like a couple more where he it's literally just like him describing like a road trip that he took
with his wife
Yeah, they're great. They're like three hours long. They're really relaxing
They're awesome. Um the channel I found it was called ray are reviewing
Ray are reviewing this guy with a purple mask. Oh, he has he has like the loudest
most british laugh
Uh, what I watched I watched his latest one about the the rise of youtube the rise of youtube video game critics
where he just talks about like
the the influence
of uh, you know dug walker and and no no mostly uh
Not nostalgia critic angry video game nerd and like the the diaspora of that, uh, you know, uh
He's I don't know. He's loud. It's really funny. It's it's really funny when he laughs
I don't know. I just think it's really funny when he's just like yelling something
And then just starts laughing at whatever he just
said
Yeah, I watched the the running shine video on yiek y2k earlier today
I I watched I love that video. I watched the to snaker
Uh yick video for like the second or third time again yesterday. That's enough those
What is it? What is it? I just
Those videos are so good. These two videos about yick. I'll have to check that one
Because I I was watching the only plays playthrough. They're playing through at the moment
It's like funny. What did you think of? Um, this the running shine?
Oh, very good video
Funny. It's such a good video. Uh, well argued
Correct entirely in every aspect
The to to snaker is not he's not as funny as running shine, but he has
To snaker has like a really interesting like thing where he he goes through the whole game and then at the end he has like
Two competing thesis about like what he thinks
The game is intended to mean and they're both like different from each other
And he and he lays out the case for like each one and why like he's not sure which which he believes
And uh, it's good. Yeah
To snaker, uh, what to snaker. Yeah, okay. Oh look into that
Um, I was on the train
Like a week or two ago. It was I think it was like
When I was on the way home from getting my shot or something or
I was on a train. I was on the subway
And I just like looked at my phone and I saw that running shine was streaming
And he that he was streaming with cybershell
And I was like, oh my god
I gotta get in there. So I just just saw my so just on just on my phone. I jumped into the chat
Just because I was like
I just want cybershell
To see me and I just I just want to say hi to cybershell and see if he'll say hi back
And I just jumped into the chat and made a some fucking stupid observation about how sonic the hedgehog has gone downhill as a franchise or whatever
some asinine nonsense
And uh cybershell noticed me and he was like, oh hi Ben and I was like, yes
Fuck that means running shine. That means running shine has has now noticed me as well
My influence
The notice spreads like a plague in the stream
Yeah, whenever you like stream like do a heckles for shackles and I'm like in the chat and you go, oh, hey, cybsie. I go. Yes. Yes
He knows what you're on
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get that. I get that
But I was like it feels great. I've tried I've tried so many times to be like cool in a germa stream
But there's too many people. Oh, yeah, it's like it's impossible. You have to
I tried to be the one guy would be incredible
I tried to be funny
I tried to be funny in that chat
But I was like on the train and I had to get off in a minute
And I had like 30 seconds to look at the chat and I just like I tried to type a couple messages
But like autocorrect fucked one of them up and I was like dammit
Um, so whatever
Whatever I got what I came for
I got noticed. That's all that's all I wanted
Uh based based as hell
It's worked for me. I got on this fucking podcast by fucking bullying you on your twitch streams
You fucking we just commiserated. We just commiserated about
Being aggrieved about Trixie
Uh
Oh, it's just is that and the fact that uh, you have more twitter followers than me and that means that I I need to uh
I need to steal your cloud. It means you'll get a chubby little retweet from me. So
You scratched my back I scratched yours. If you know what I'm saying, that's the how you play the cloud game, baby
I mean, I like I like no simsie from from the art discords and stuff
And baby we use mummy milkers and it's like yeah simsie's a cool person. Thank you
You're you're both cool people uh, too. I've been a fan of you guys for a few years and I'm
Overjoyed
I get to talk but not but not from the pony days apparently. No, uh, I was I'm a lecture
Bastard I'm the worst kind of pc a pc p fan
Where I came in I came in with the big lectures
The worst child the worst now the worst kind are the are the old digi heads
Oh, I mean I I think I mean I was kind of that
And um, and I'm I'm not why did you come from the uh, the dick show lecture? No the the first thing I
Saw was your sonnet you think because I found out about you from the frederick nukeson video
Which I showed my friend and I was obsessed with it and I was like, I think that's one of fred's
I think that's one of fred's worst videos. Yeah, definitely. I would agree like he's improved so much since then but um,
Yeah, like I watched your sonnet you video. I was like, oh, this is cool. Hang on. There's a king hearts one
Hey, is that digi bro in the background and then
I'd listen to podcasts that went into all your solo stuff and watch lots of gipsy videos
It's not it's not my new it's not my new and and more sour grapes talking when I say that the like the hardcore digi heads
Are though are the worst are the worst faction of the pcp fan fan base? Uh, the lecture the lecture. I mean, that's fine
Uh, no, that's good. That's good. Um, I have gone back and listened to every episode
So I feel somewhat validated
But only the pony only the pony only those who were listening in the horse cast days are the true
The true core audience you can never if you weren't there, you don't understand man
You'll never really get it
Yeah, it really was like a secret
Society that like a lot of people just
You know because bronies were cringe at the time
It's like oh god
You were either in or you were out and if you were out you had no idea what they were doing
But you you just had a vague idea that they were strange if you were in
Uh, it's a it's a whole world
There was solidarity. There's brony solidarity
We all we all had each other's backs, you know, you've you mess with one of us. You mess with all of us spider-man. I mean goblin
Uh, yeah
It's like works though because there's there's so many people connected to your little community
Like like there's so many discord servers and offshoots of the pcp and like pcp adjacent things
They don't even know us anymore. There's like no
There's people there's people that like play rfck now that like don't even know
Yeah, I was I was on endless war the other day and like some like some guy was like, hey, are you doing?
Yeah, and he was like, do you want to go fishing? I was like, okay, and then he died and then he died
I was just waiting for him
He I was waiting for him at the pier
I was waiting for him at the pier and he was like, hang on. I'm all by over and then I fell asleep
Oh my god
So we had this weird little interaction. He was like, hey, uh, type go to jrp. I was like, okay, and I did it
And then he didn't even DM me. I said, I died lol
I was like, okay, cool
You know what?
Endless war is like a great like physical location online
Like if you wanted like set up a secret meeting with another person and then another internet person you go to endless war
You go to a specific street and meet you at this time
And it's yeah, you would you would never find it
Like it would be so hard to find like a record of what was said there
You would have to know like what what town what town in endless war
Do you need to navigate to and then like check the history and yeah to find those records?
So what i'm saying is if any if you want to do it, but endless war is funnier endless war is yes
DMs are first
If no, it was interesting because I wasn't even typing anything on the server. No wait actually
Oh
Yeah, this would be worse because uh
The other person would have a record of it if you both have a conversation in a place
Neither of you will be able to remember where the fuck it is or to scroll back to it
and then well
Yeah, you got to go and do your shady dealings in endless war and then get yourself banned from the server
You both got to get banned from the server so you can't find it again. It's the only way
I
True cyber security. That's the only way to make your nfts secure
I've been money laundering through endless war for years. I should just I should just I should just sell an nft of endless war
No, just of the game. No, no, no make make an nft of like a sly moid
No
I because I don't have to do anything like if I just sell I don't need to make like a model or like a picture
No, fuck it. Like just sell an nft of the game. It doesn't mean they own the game
It doesn't mean anything. It's just the nft represents the game and you own the nft
And uh, you know, I've burned down like 20 acres of forest to make this happen
I'm I'm gonna
What if what if it was an aft like an automatically fungible fungible token like no matter what you did
Someone else would have it you couldn't have the rights to it
It would be impossible to have the unique article. Isn't that just like a computer virus?
Yeah
I'll make I'll make a like a I don't know
The image of frisker as a aft and then she would infect the internet and she would be everywhere
Would you dances or something?
And she would eat bitcoin if she stays on your computer
It's just a little desktop friend that eats all your bitcoin
She she people are mining bitcoin and she would grief the miners. She would like poor lava on them
Dude bitcoin is down bitcoin is fucking dying
Bitcoin has been dying for a little while. Yeah. Oh, it's no it's it's down even more
It's down even more now like it like just today. It's having another like big crash today. It's down to 44. Holy shit
I don't know what I got. This is tinged. It's tinged for me though
It's who the who the fuck just left the call. It was craig
Craig you
It was a old friend craig. He's a fucking dog. Shit craig just fucking hates when we talk about bitcoin. You can't stand
Yeah, he's like he's like I don't want to hear this. He's like, no, I've got so much invested. I'm like
I don't want to hear this right now about it. Um, I'll have to get him back into record. I guess but uh,
I feel
Tinge of this because I want to celebrate when I see bitcoin go down because I sold
Uh near the top not quite at the top, but I sold like pretty high
You know, I made back like some of the money I lost on gme
So I was like pretty happy with that and now it's going down. I'm like, haha. Fuck it. Fuck you
um, but it's going down at least partially because elan musk said like
It's bad for the environment and like we're not going to trade in it until like it's less bad for the environment and I'm like
That's kind of a good reason for it to go down though. Damn it. Fuck
He took this. I can't I can't I can't be 100 happy about this anymore
I wanted to go down because it sucks
You want people to lose faith in it. You mean I wanted to go down because it sucks
Not because like someone is like doing like the right thing with it
You're just a very bitter man, aren't you?
Shut up
No, um
I I I I feel like it would be easier to feel happy that it is going down
It'd be nice setting a precedent
The that it might actually get green energy. It would feel better to be happy involved. No, I wanted to go down
because people see like oh
It's like it's stupid. It's stupid and it's and it's bad. Oh, bitcoin's bad. So
Let's not use it. Right. That's what I wanted. It is but instead it's like, oh, they're gonna. There's a problem with bitcoin
Okay, we need to address it and fix that problem so that we can re-adopt and I'm like, no
This like this is I don't want I don't what I don't want to see is like short-term
losses for bitcoin in the name of like, you know
Greenifying it or like, you know pretending to greenify or you know greenifying it enough that like people will stop complaining
Whatever only for that to like then become long-term gains. I don't want long-term games. I wanted to die
I feel like unfortunately it is too established to actually die
I mean
I mean, you never know
I mean, who knows? It'll go down. Obviously. It'll it'll have crashes, but it'll always be there as a thing
I'm too stupid. Maybe some of the less known coins
Will die out but bitcoin is
I mean, maybe maybe it'll like change hands. Which one is the most impressive? Bitcoin could be overtaken by a number
Another coin. Yeah, but I feel like that becomes more widely adopted
I think
I don't know. I don't think I don't think it's a foregone conclusion that crypto is just gonna be a thing that like people use in daily life
Why I don't think that I don't think that's inevitable
I think um that the uh
The trading investing and then buying low settling high all of that crap
That's short term in like interest
People will be like hype about making a quick easy money
uh, but eventually I think
it'll have to or
It'll have to become more usable in the real world for like just selling stuff
Well, yeah, that's buying stuff. But in order to do that it would need to like
Level out and not be as volatile
Yeah, so I'm like, I guess if if it can like if the investment hype
Can stick around long enough for it to mellow out and then I think it'll stay for I don't know
Well, it needs
It needs like wide adoption in the way that like everyone has access to getting it and like every and like
You know lots and lots of vendors, you know, accept it as payment and there's a convenient way of doing those transactions
And if that happens, I think then that will drive its value further up because now it will be more useful as a currency and therefore more valuable
So if one I think there's a lot of companies like investing into crypto
because of it's not being like
Regulated exactly. So there's there's an incentive for companies to get their hands on the sorts this sort of currency
Which I think is because it's like, um
Oh, I don't know much about finance, but I in my head I'm thinking like, oh, yeah offshore bank accounts like they don't have to pay tax
They're doing shady things all the time. Cryptocurrency is very easy to do shady things with that might be part of it, of course
They're gonna want it that might be part of it
um, I mean, I think it's also the idea that
It has not reached its peak value yet because
It has seen like some adoption lately, but it still hasn't seen like truly like universal adoption like if that
if it were to happen like tomorrow that like
Amazon accepts bitcoin and then like, you know mom and pop retailers all install a fucking scanner that lets you
You know pay for your fucking groceries in bitcoin
Then like it would fucking shoot up to 100k because that would like suddenly it's something that like everybody wants and it's not like
It's it's it's less niche now than it was before but it's it's still a niche thing
Um, yeah to to and to an extent
um
Yeah
So I think that's the like speculative part of it that like people are betting on
It eventually becoming more widely adopted which
Will make it more valuable which makes the value go up which makes getting in on the ground floor, you know
An investment that will pay dividends in the future
Uh, although it's the market seems to be looking a little bearish a little bearish for the moment, but uh, maybe just in the short term
Who knows
who fucking
knows
Yeah, no one you guys okay. Yeah
wowy
Man being being on the pcp is just save as listening to it. I zone out whenever benton. I was talking about
No, no zone out and starting muffins
It's time it's time to zone out even harder because I feel like we're at a point where maybe it's time to move on
To voicemails. Yeah
Yeah
By the way, ben we're at two hours right now. I don't want to be here for five hours
So no no smells go on for too long. I will kill my I
I'm still thinking I'm thinking we can
Hustle through these in an hour
We go quick. If we just don't react to them at all. We just play them in a string
I do try that's the strat. We go. I can try to keep it under three hours. I feel like that's a good
guideline
Yeah, let's see. Where do I where did I save this?
shit
Looking at speak pipe. Okay, the first voicemail
is from
It's called bleach fan 17 exposes the retards
So, uh, sorry. I'm I'm I'm pulling it up. Okay. I think this is
Dischord please
Okay, posting it in the general chat right there
Bleach fan 17 exposes the retards three two one go
Today instead of regaling you with the scripture
That is tight Kubo's bleach palms tight Kubo. I will be reading to you something a little bit different
Let me begin
Bleach is trash
Compare it to something like vagabond and tell me the characters have
Compare it to hunter hunter and tell me it has plot
It compare it to one piece and tell me it has world building
You're fucking delusional if you honestly believe bleach is good comparatively to any of those series
She got asked for a reason
Only series that big to be asked so far in
Literally never happened before or since but i'm sure you die hard idiots actually believe
When jump when they see you
I don't care. Uh, next one is called no anime analysis. No watch
Uploading it there
three two one go
I thought this was supposed to be digi bro's anime podcast. What the fuck aren't you talking about anime? Not anymore
baby, uh
Bro, we've cast off the yoke art
Bleach has good art in it. I like the drawings sometimes
This is no longer that uh, the anime podcast. Duh, thanks. Thanks for the
Cryptocurrency and trouble in israel
Yes, yes, yes, we're moving in a bold new direction. Uh, uh, uh, we don't know what our content is but we're gonna
We're gonna start color coding. Yeah, we got we're gonna have a blue and white border for israel palestinian
Conflict videos and we're gonna have yellow for bitcoin related videos
It's gonna be great. You're gonna love it. I have all the colors
For gib is dying corner
That's that's every video that's every video
Next next one is uh, no no next one is called motivation. There it is
three two one go
Hey pcb monotone jones here. No relation
I recently finished my first semester at uni and I'm pretty happy because now I have more free time to work on art and stuff
Nice. The issue is that I never have any motivation to do so. This is specifically withdrawing too
I never have any problem with making myself write my silly little books
I don't know if i'm adhd or what but I really do love making stuff
So there shouldn't be any reason that I can't force myself to work
You guys have some of the best worth work ethics i've ever seen and I don't know if it's because that's not true
Not if you could share some tips on how y'all stay motivated. I would appreciate it
Ben congrats on your game. I hope you feel better soon and tom. You'll never die
um, okay
Yeah, I mean if you if you love doing it then why can't you motivate yourself to do it would be my question like why
A lot of the time with um motivation like if you're thinking of something to do
uh
You might be thinking too big and that is like paralyzing you
A lot of the time you you end up like having a thing you do on the side just for fun and that becomes
Your main thing because you you're doing it more and the thing that you want to do
Uh that you keep thinking about doing and you're not doing it. It's because you're thinking too much about it
You just gotta yeah
Draw some stupid crap
It will suck
And then draw some more it sounds to me like he's just got art block and he just needs to wait
And keep trying until suddenly it goes. Oh, I can I can work again. Keep trying and wait. Yeah. Yeah
Keep trying and wait. That's the best way to put it try for like 20 20 minutes at most and then if it's uh,
Oh, oh, I can if it's not if it's not coming. Just yeah try again tomorrow. Yeah, exactly
Yeah, it happens that happens to me fucking on a monthly basis. We'll just be like an entire week where I'm
I'm my job. I'm not gonna do it
Just can't I mean you're you're quite quick with the the art and it's you are quality
So it's it's I think you can uh, you can afford yourself a few moments like that. Yeah
I mean
People just don't there's always an upper limit. There's always an upper limit to how unbelievably
Um, uh, productive a person can be and it's impossible to like be the most
You just do what you can. Yeah
Everyone works at a different rate and stuff
Uh
I I feel
I don't know. I sometimes I have the same thought as this guy like why can't I focus on the thing I want to do
I want to be working on this thing and yet I'm continually
Finding myself doing something else. Do I have a problem? Do I have ADHD? Should I get diagnosed?
I have that thought a lot. I think Ben. Well, I think it's it's it's like what you want
Is maybe the thing to be completed and the doing it is not the thing you want to do
Ben you're like I want to have the game be made. I don't want to make the game
Ben your show is called The Procrastinator's podcast. I know I think you forgot
It's a it's a big problem. It's a big problem. Uh, yeah, uh, I just I just uh, I don't know
Sometimes I wonder sometimes I wonder like am I
Am I operating and like am I am I am I operating irregularly?
Do I have like is there something like is there some issue?
Is the could be chemically resolved for me that would make me a more efficient at the things I want to do
Do you never think that am I crazy?
I mean if well, I guess I guess I do but I feel like if somebody says
Yes, you actually do have a ghc. Oh, yes, you do actually have autism
I I don't know what I would do. I guess I would just continue the way I was because well, no, I would
You're missing the point the point is if that happened and they were like, oh, yes
The reason why you don't uh work as efficiently as you wish you did is because you have ADHD
And we have you know, uh treatments. We have medication that is you know
Can treat some of the symptoms of ADHD and then what if I was like, oh, okay cool
And then I took some and then I found like oh wow
I'm way more able to focus on the things I want to do and I get a lot more done
I it's possible. I don't think I have
A medical issue though. I feel like I'm just most of the time. I don't have good discipline
I do but then every now and then I'm like discipline up when I was younger
But every now and then I'm like I'm procrastinating even though I really want to be
Getting that thing done and it's yes, it's it's clearly irrational. I'm clearly pursuing an irrational course of action. Why?
you know
I guess I guess that's human
I mean
It just comes down to like what are the things you could do playing video games or doing the other thing and that you
Choose the video games because you find more short-term pleasure in it and it's very easy to go to those sorts of things
Oh, I don't think it's indicative of you
It's just it's just how how things are so
Good and satisfying and video games. They give me that dopamine
So engaging
Yeah, I mean, it's true. I could be making money
Not really though
Not really because I don't get paid for anything in particular
Yeah
I just have I just have a vague sense of obligation that I need to be putting things out into
The world and I hope
That I will be correspondingly met with appreciation which in some cases might
congeal itself into money, but I have no guarantee
Uh
Just a kind of
Just a kind of vague sense that maybe sums up the artist experience
Yeah
Uh next voicemail
is called uh
Gibbs pancreas
3 2 1 go
This is a message from Gibbs pancreas
Hey, Gib. I'm real hurt man
I've been making yo insulin for over 20 years and you go and credit all my hard effort to the kidneys
I'm ashamed of you Gib. I'm actually so so mad
You know what?
How about I stop how about I stop making your insulin bitch? Yeah, take that you diabetic now
Sorry, not sorry savage, but well-deserved
Damn, it doesn't sound as evil and vile anymore without funny boys. It's small
It's a small little thing. Yeah, it's so small so insignificant. You understand that I'm bigger than you pancreas mine
Okay, I could beat the you up
Keep in line
I'm going to beat up my own pancreas
You should do it just to teach him a lesson. You can't you can't you can't let him get uppity
You gotta keep him in their place. You got a squash rebellion when it starts to form
Who put a microphone to my pancreas? Hey, that's what I want to know
I didn't notice next next voicemail is called uh
Oh, it's jean s. Uh, it's from jean s three two one go
What do you think is the biggest problem in the universe?
Capitalism
Uh, um scarcity, uh, I mean, I don't understand capitalism is probably
So I'm gonna let decay think bigger. Yeah, you know universal entropy universal entropy
Um
Biggest problem for the existence of the universe, but I don't care about it. I'll be dead
Well, when you when you when you can feel your toes touching each other in your shoes, that's the biggest problem in the universe
Um the biggest problem in the universe is just uh
Is just uh the the the finitude the finitude of of existence of of a discrete uh being
Just the the yawning the yawning gulf of void
Uh, uh that extends in every direction. I like that up down left right forward back and front and back and that inspires cool
Things that I see that I watch. Oh, I fucking hate you. I hate that shit. I hate that shit
Oh, you know, actually if you didn't have the abyss you wouldn't have dark souls more more talent
You wouldn't have dark souls if you didn't if you weren't all gonna die. We wouldn't have dark souls
That's yeah, the notorious best you'll see happened. You gotta fucking you gotta accept that then
Uh, it's mortality is good because it makes us sad and that makes us make video games to cope
like dark souls
Jesus fucking christ. I didn't say that I just said that like the the concept of thinking about the abyss
Gives you the thought to like, hey, what if I should put it out in a video game?
Yeah, I just
I
You sure now you're right. Yeah, it's true. I'd like to submit an argument
Uh, the biggest problem in the universe is when my uh drawing tablet pen disconnects
I have to move it a few centimeters away and then back again, and then it works again
That's the biggest problem in the universe. The biggest problem in the universe is when
Uh, sometimes my tablet does a thing where
For no, I I don't know why it will just
I'm not pressing any buttons, but I will I will hover my my mouse over
Like something and like over like a slider and the slider will just creep up
And like and like like a like the volume on a youtube video will just creep up to the max
Or like if I hover over like my my pens my pen tip size in like manga studio
The size will just creep up and I don't know why it's like my fucking mouse wheel is like
Nudged in a direction or something
And I have had times when I have had that for like weeks and I have like I've tried disconnecting my mouse and I've tried
Like fucking reinstalling my mouse drivers and stuff and like
I don't know. I think I think a broken mouse is the problem back then, but I got it again the other day
I was like, oh my god. This is gonna be a weeks long problem. I'm doomed
But no, I just like
Un I just unplugged my mouse dongle and re-plugged it in and fortunately that fixed again, but it was the scariest
I was so scared of having to deal with that because I really threw a wrench into a lot of fucking shit like
Fuck it. Let's destroy Israel
Yeah, yeah, you're right. Israel is the biggest problem in the universe
Israel, you know what? It's really it's a pretty big problem. No
America is the America is worse
If Israel is a problem, it's only because America is empowering them to do their shit
So I guess America is the big supposed to just all comes back to capitalism
Yeah, cool. Come on. You know what capitalism it all comes back to capitalism
Again, I was right the first time money
Money money dough
But me like money
I do like money
I like money a lot. It's really great. You should try having some
Sometimes what are you fucking poor? Are you fucking poor? I don't like poor people. I like you live in a Prius. Come on
No, I got an RV. I stole it
Next voicemail. Let's move on. We're done. Yeah, next one. Next voicemail is uh
2021 Ben
Wait
There we go 2021 Ben three two one go
Ben insanely transphobic saint
Oh
Nice meme
Round of applause
Ben it's like not true. Where's my reparations? Where give me bitcoin ben
I sold them my bitcoins stupid buy some more
Okay, all right
Oh, I can pay you in satoshi. I give you one satoshi
Per whatever. Yeah, okay
I'll get right on it. Ben. Ben. You don't go on the kiwi farms anymore. You're not you're not transphobic
I look at them. I look at them. I saw on there though
I saw I've never posted on there. I would never I would never fucking do that. I'd like
God um
Uh, oh next one is called
What the fucking number are we on next one is called cross. Don't worry Ben
Okay, three two one go
I just got my second vaccination yesterday and I am totally fine
My arm was a little bit sore when I woke up this morning had some general flu symptoms
But took some tile at all. I'm feeling totally fine now. So yeah, don't worry ben
Some some people say it makes them feel pretty pretty out of it and sick for like a day or two
I
After I got my first one
uh, I was like literally nothing happened and then
Like five or six days later
Uh, I suddenly got like a little bruise like a like a bruising around the injection
And I'm like, why would that happen like five days later?
Uh
But like it's fine, uh
I'm pretty I don't know. I'm pretty hearty. I think I think I have like a pretty
Naturally like high constitution score and resistance to disease and illness
So I think I am probably not likely to feel much
From it
So thanks cross. I won't worry vaccine. Good
And if I do get a little sick, well, whatever it doesn't matter
Um
Next one is called vaccine. Good. You know in my opinion in my opinion vaccination
Works
Probably at least I hope so
I hope so
Fuck it. I'll get both shots. Hell. I'll even get a fucking third booster if they want to give me one to fight some
Weird strains or whatever. That's how dedicated I am
All right
Uh, yeah, all right. Next one is called based joker three two one go
You know Batman
They say that one bird in the hand is worse two in the bush
But like, you know, I think that one turd in the hand is worse two in the tush
Ah
It worked
He did it
He fucking did it
I am a big fan of based joker. I got to be honest
He's got some staying power
he
You you don't think you think he's got to be out of material. How long can he keep this up?
He's can't possibly do it again. He's got a full week in between each one to come up with them
No
I like to imagine he sat there with holy quinn just fucking writing notes for 20 hours a day
He's like work shopping it
What if I said something about feet? No, that's not funny
He's showing up to like open mic nights like reading like reading like a huge list of them out and just like
And he only gives us the one that gets the biggest laugh
Look at the cream of the crop
Absolutely
He's like front-lining for snl and then he takes that to us
He says
Did you did you watch the the elon snl?
I watched a clip of
A bit of it. Did he did he say i'm a stupid. Did he say that? I don't think so
I I mean maybe I I literally
Just hearing about it and thinking about it. I saw I saw some people posting clips of the zoomer
What was it hospital? This is the gen z hospital and I
I I saw the thumbnail for the video and I I couldn't even click on it like I I was so embarrassed even
I was so embarrassed even thinking about like what could be in this video that like
I couldn't even bear to start watching it. So I just didn't and I watched a bit the mario
I saw that
And it was it was like cringe, you know, like they
They're just saying things that they've heard zoomers say but like not all of the things and mostly from twitch
They said poggers
um
Bass but it was like I didn't even know what that it was
like surprisingly
I mean it wasn't surprisingly bad. It was obviously bad like
I did it wasn't so bad that I was cringing out of my skin. It was just sort of like
You know
Yeah, I all right. Yeah, maybe I'm back into the retirement home. You go. It's just sort of sad
Hmm, I see
Yeah, but it's also like the biggest comedy show in the world and you gotta you gotta expect something more from that
You have to laugh. You have to laugh. It's the biggest
Well, it's like it's like if if this is if these people aren't delivering something that's fucking funny and impress me then like
What is the then like where am I to go? Where am I to go for amusements?
If you go to the pro crest
You got a patreon.com slash the pro crest and it is five dollars for 50 60 bonus episodes
Uh laughs a plenty you go to youtube.com forward slash resin evil village all movies full hd
Cut scenes and then skip skip about one hour and 10 minutes in and then laugh at the funny bit where the guy says the silly thing
Ah
Time stamp time stamp
Uh, uh next voicemail like the voicemail, uh, okay
I'm gonna throw up
I'm not actually gonna throw up. Oh, I just burped and it tasted like butterscotch. That's pretty cool. That's great
Don't you just love that? What a man you are
Yeah, uh next one is called
Uh spork
Wait, I think I already put it there spork more like dork three two one go
This is in response to spork's voicemail last week, uh bitching and moaning about uh been using gendered pronouns
Whatever, uh, don't say the n word spork. It doesn't matter if you're black. It's not cool. No one should say it
Okay, negga
Uh
Fuck you
I'm tempted to cut that. I don't know. I should I keep it or should I the spork thing from before so
I don't know. Well, the this guy sounds like he's in
spork's voicemail was bad faith spork's voicemail was just uh
don't
I mean, I don't even think she was fucking that's she's not it's not that serious guy
It's not that serious. I don't think she was what a prick. Fuck
Next voice we won't cut it. Just this is fucking
Don't send bad voicemails. The number one rule of voicemails is don't send them if they're bad. They're not funny
Uh
Next one is called, uh based saint. Yes, three two one go
Oh
I don't know man. Well, is it been after the game. I know where it is after the game
Yes, the game after the game's done. Then I'll you need to finish your third finale. This is like been punished, but
Uh, that's only the second one. Oh, it's only the third time's the charm. Yeah, they can finally end and finally die
Uh
Next voicemail is called the three two one go
um just to add on to like the um
weird interactions with dug walker stuff. Um
He was at my local comic con
Uh, like a few years ago and um, I didn't know he was gonna come so I was like damn. This is the guy
Um with the glasses
The guy with the glasses. Oh my god. I like had a dollar and I asked him to sign it. Um, and he was like weirdly
Offended and I could have been misreading his reaction, but
Weirdly, uh, it definitely seemed to me as though he was sort of taken aback by this
And I don't know like is that is it that weird? Um
I I don't think so. Um, but yeah, you defaced the the president. It's like a crime, isn't it?
No, who cares?
Yeah, I know who cares, but like it's a it's a piece of paper. I can see
I can see Doug walker being the kind of guy who would be worried about that sort of thing. You know what you're right
Yeah, I can see him being like, oh, you can't fucking write on united seats currency
I could totally see that maybe that's it. Yeah, or maybe or maybe it's like a
Or maybe it's like an ego thing where it's like this guy's seriously just taking some random junk and like asking me to fucking
Like give him my signature
No, I don't think it would be like that. I feel like I feel like the the him not wanting to
Like anger the american gods
Is is more likely really not I wonder say what you like about Doug walker. He's really not very mean spirited
A lot of the time. No, I don't ever see it. I don't think he's mean spirited
I don't think he's mean spirited, but I do think he's he's pretty conceded
I don't think he's pretty like self-absorbed and seems like kind of a narcissist. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I feel like I don't I'm a convention though. He
Do you think I'm do you think I'm reading him wrong that I think he would be like
He would be like do you gotta wait in line like everyone else for a signature?
I've only heard um good things about him in personal interactions
so
Like by actual people meeting him. I mean regardless of business practices and shitty videos
Yeah, yeah sure
Okay, I'm a huge fan of it
I was a huge fan of him. I don't want to think of him as being mean
Well, sure
Next voicemail is called thought slime. Okay, there it is three two one
Hey, it's me thought slime. Did you know that you're actually sexist and racist?
Uh
Let's know what he sounds like. That's not true. That's uh, that's uh
What that's not you you could say that you could make this
Impret you could do this impression of like anyone you could be like, hey, I'm I'm big Joel
Do you think did you know you're really sexist? Hey, I'm I'm fucking contra points. Did you know you're really sexist?
Like you could say this about fucking anybody terrible insane. Did you know that you don't have an RV?
Uh
Terrible this is awful. This is awful. Sometimes you just don't know what your unconscious biases are and you need them pointed out
You fuck
Sometimes that is true. Sometimes that is true. Give do you think me and ben are racist and sexist?
I definitely am
Uh, I don't know
Who knows it's it's it's everyone's a little bit like biased
Towards their own race just because they grow up around, you know
The same skin color and they're like, huh, what's that? It's someone different
I said I I always manifest in different ways, but like no not everyone is literally like the worst possible
Of anything I heard necessary. I heard a youtuber the other day
Who was a a black british person and I heard his voice and I said
This guy sounds like nino and someone was like it's kind of racist and I was like I thought about I was like, you know
It kind of is
It kind of is and then everybody
But like I mean, I don't know. I'm not I don't like feel bad
It's like, yeah, it is. I just think like like black people in
Well in the london area that have like a voice that white people in the london area do not have
So I could see why they would be like, oh, this is a similar sort of thing
Yeah, yeah
but but it's um
I mean, I don't feel like I did anything wrong, but I think you could probably yeah, it's kind of like a
racist
Thing to be like, oh these these these two people sound the same because they are the same
I don't know maybe I'm the accusation of racist as like
Oh, you're trying to ruin my life. You're a bad person throw me in jail. You're being malicious. You're a bad person in harry
You'll never be good at anything. Yeah. Um, and it's not always that yeah, I mean some people do act like that
And that's your you know what you're right racism is good actually
No, oh no, I've been don't clip that don't clip that
Don't clip out of context cut it out cut it out
All right
Eleazar double down
Put a reverb on it
Eleazar play the guy who said the n word again play that one again. Yeah. Yeah, let's go back to that one. That was my favorite
Next no double censor it censor everything
Next voicemail is called
Uh, wait a second. Hold on. You've pushed it too and we haven't listened to one of them
Oh, I'm stupid. Okay. Do the one that's called 3170. That one is Henlo Corgo
Three two one go
Hey
Ben
Yo, um, what up?
I was just wondering after spending roughly 10 minutes or so in your discord
How like often you hatefully masturbate to the dumb shit that Riley says
And how you compare the quality of those orgasms to normal orgasms
Because I myself have been interested
in
hateful masturbation for some time now
And I'm trying to like get into the craft and was wondering if you had any tips
I have been I have been seething particularly hard
Since the since the oaky interview. I mean, I've been doing it and I've got no investment in this shit
I have I have been thinking of
That guy says shit that really pisses me off. I hate him
I hate I hate her you Riley's you up. He does he really
I admit it. He I
I guess that's I guess that's a win. I guess that's a win for him. He's like a successfully
He makes me mad when he says dumb shit about like making fun of poor people and stuff. I'm like, he's a funny guy
Who isn't funny?
Sad. Yeah
Um, it's like yep. He's success successfully trolled me. I guess. Uh, it's it sucks and yeah, I've been yeah, I'm seething
So to answer your question, uh
I've been
Usually only once a week or so. Um, but this week multiple every day
Next voicemail is called roguelike recommendation three two one go
Hey, Ben. I have a roguelike recommendation for you since you cannot seem to be enjoying that genre a lot
So it's called synthetic
Subtitle is legion arising. I think
It's a top-down tactical shooter
Kind of a roguelike. It's pretty good. It has has like some really solid shooting mechanics
Um, I recently got its final update. So all of the content that will be in the game is in the game now
It's hard as fuck. So, uh, I think I beat it like four or five times and with the final update
They added kind of looks like a twin stick shooter, but I'm not sure not new game plus
But like a final ending after the ending that I got a couple times
Um
Yeah, it's pretty good. If you want to try it out for free. There's the arena version of synthetic
You can like try out just uh, just the mechanics against like hordes of enemies
But that's not the roguelike. Uh
Yeah, also that that's sef guy who made a video on kenji. He also made a video on this. So yeah, check it out. Oh, yeah
Seth Seth Seth seniche that guy
Seth like barlin. Uh, I'll check I'll check this out. I'm gonna check this out. I like video games
Ben when you're gonna play hades
Oh
Hades nuts. I don't think I don't think you would like hades that much, but I really like it
uh, honestly
Yeah, I think
I just heard I started so many people gushing about it, but
Yeah, I mean I talked about this last the isometric gameplay. It doesn't look like
It doesn't look like you're blown away, but I don't know. I'm sure it's fun. I'm sure it's fine. It's very addictive
Um, the character is nice. Music's really good. I really should give it a I really should give it a try
It's just very satisfying to play. It's one of those that's you just sit and
Chill and runs are only like 20 minutes. So it's nice to jump in. That's good
A noida run a successful run is like 16 fucking hours. So
I've never made it past the hasty base in noida. I suck
Oh
You fucking idiot
Fucking dumbass
Here's what you do. Yeah, fuck you. No, here's what you do. No, no, no
You just you all all you gotta do is you go to the mines and you go to the left
And you just you just dip into the you dip into the fungal caverns
Because that's where the good wands are you dip into the fungal caverns and you get a good wand
You look for you look for a high mana regen
Uh, uh, and and you know low low reload time and cast
Castile and reload time
And if you can find all what you gotta do you need you need a mana you need the mana
Rebooster or fuck. What's it called? Um
The the the mana the one that like gives you 30 extra mana. I got your coach. I'm writing this down coach
We're writing it all down if you get that if you get that you're fucking done if you get that it's game over
You just fucking you just stack that you just stack that in the right wand and you just
And that's it. You got a fucking chainsaw wand and of course
And of course I get that all the time because I know what to look for and I still fucking die in the heesey base
because I fucking because I shoot bullets into a
Liquid nitrogen canister that I didn't see under a pile of snow
But if I was being smart and playing more patiently I would never die
Uh, so that's how you do it. Cool. Yeah. Now you know not it is a good game. I just I've barely scratched the surface with it though
So it's so fucking good dog
You got you you haven't been to a pair if you haven't been to a parallel worlds
Forget about it. Okay. Um
Yeah, I haven't
Next next one is called, uh clarity
three two one go
I benched on to clarify a couple things. I wasn't entirely with you about autism last week
I wasn't correcting you on anything. You just sounded kind of unsure the first time you talked about it
So I thought hey, I'm autistic. I'm diagnosed and everything so maybe I can give them some first-hand insights into what it's like
I guess I couldn't uh
Maybe it's fine that it's an increments of a minute and a half at something
Your voice this okay, that's it. Thank you. Nope. Thanks for the voicemail. Uh, sorry your other voicemail wasn't great
Uh, keep them shorter. Thank you. Uh, next one is called
Dolos
Uh, there it is three two one go
So, um, like um, this um question. Um, is maybe um, uh,
Directed uh, um at uh Tommy, but the rest of y'all can answer too. No
Especially because you know, he's not here your roster changes every five seconds on the podcast
Sorry guy. Don't know if he'll even be here. Nope
Uh, Ben said to keep these short. So, you know, uh, how are the kids?
Okay, how's the life?
Uh thoughts on the guilty gear beta though
Cheers. I'm sorry
I've been seeing a lot of guilty gear posts on twitter. I post about yesterday
But I I don't know what to think about them because I don't play. Yeah, I don't play that shit
I think the the girl with the wolf is hot
Um, is she is she now? Yeah, she's like the new character
She's just like a girl in like a like business casual attire and she's got like a cool wolf that she summons. She's nice
Cool. She's the most normal looking guilty character
To me guilty gear is a guilty ignore
Hey, it looks like something cool. I just I just keep ignoring it. I just can't play fighting games
I just can't do it. I can't even play the dragon ball. Yeah, also
Hmm, are you just following for the
Cute girls. Yeah
Just look at the art of the characters and go. Yeah, that's cool. I'm just waiting for the game to come out
So I can watch all the animations on youtube basically. That's fair. All right, that makes sense. They do they do look great
That game looks fucking great. Yeah
Uh, sorry tom wasn't here to answer your question law
um
The next voicemail is called. Where is it here? I?
Oh god, I found it. It is called. Uh
SF2 is base not that one
three two one go
Saka frontier 2 it says obscure ass square soft rpg for the ps1
And it's got these kooky characters brights, but the most gorgeous
Watercolor backgrounds the soundtrack is amazing. It's like the pinnacle of how to speak motif in music
The combat system is pretty fucking wonky
But once you really experiment or research into it, it's really sick
The only blight on the game is that it has these hideous
3d backgrounds when you get into battle
And they are just dot awful
So truly, uh, tom is wrong for once
2d over 3d. Thank you. Thank you very much
Check out this game. If you really like old s rbgs. It is really fucking saga frontier
Oh, I thought he said soccer frontier
I would type that in and I just got soccer
Saga I'm looking at screenshots
Saga
Oh god, I guess they did like a fucking it looks like they did like a hideous chibi remaster of it
Oh, that's what this is
Like one of those fucking uh, like final fantasy the old final fantasy like phone remakes. Yeah, like a psp remake of it
Yeah, oh, yeah, that looks like like it's 2000s mmo
So I I can't tell what's the original game here and what's like some shitty remake
I just don't know was it too. They was talking about
It's I it's a 2d game, but I think it has 3d
backgrounds only which is like a weird
Design choice. This looks really nice. Honestly. I might watch it. Let's do it
Um, I
I don't know some of these
I want to
I don't I don't think I like the look of it very much. There are bits that look okay
Uh, I would have to see it in motion. The one on steam is definitely like a shitty remake of the first one
Yeah, it looks really bad. Yeah
Okay, next one, uh, there you go. It is called. What is it?
Based veggie tails three two one go
Oh
Have I ever told you about the israelite? I know this one. Hmm the israelite
Oh, yeah, I remember those guys weren't they supposed to be god's chosen people? That's what the bible says
Oh, I bet they always followed god's directions. Oh, you'd think so, wouldn't you?
Yeah
You would think so
Jelly beaner posted that in the rad con
In the rad con server and I I really cracked me up
Oh, oh, you'd think so
Is veggie tails a christian show right? Yes. Yes, it is. Yes, it is. Yeah, okay. You've never seen it
I've seen the one where they predicted memes and people like oh, wow, I see the one where they all turned to look at each other
Wait, were they predicted? I saw the one where there was an orange and he yelled. What do you mean? Were they teeth?
What do you mean where they predicted memes?
Uh, it's that clip that keeps going around where they say in the future comedy will be randomly generated and
They have like a like a shit post spot
Wait veggie tails has that
Yeah, it was a clip
Uh, I okay, that's
It's strange. I'll have to look that up later. It's really weird. Okay
Um, why would why would they have that? What? I don't understand. I I no idea. I've never watched it
Next voicemail is called ben read one piece, please three two one go
So I was just watching munchies video he put out
And I just wanted to say that he is a good boy. Yeah, and
I am proud of him even though
He didn't need to do any of this and it really shows
Massive growth on his part to do all that stuff. Um
um
Munchie a good boy
um, I
I think
I think he went
I mean, I would say he went a little overboard. He used some flowery language like and
Said some things that like, you know, I think he's
I think he's correct in what he was doing
But I think definitely what he isn't saying is that he doesn't like the limelight either
So like I just want to not be here anymore
And also things I've said were bad if if he yeah
If he just doesn't want to be online anymore that I mean, I guess fair enough
I don't think it was really necessary to delete
Everything that he deleted and I I think it's a little cringe to delete stuff for no reason and some of that stuff
I feel like was fine
But at the end of the day, it's it's his stuff and he can do what he wants with it
Uh
Yeah
Good good good for him. I saw I saw a few people criticizing him on the podium discord where they were saying like
Oh, it's clear that he's lying about uh, not doing this just because uh,
It all affects his job prospects in the future. I was like, oh, okay. That's none of your fucking business. Who cares?
I uh
I mean
Even if that were true, would that not be a great? Yeah, that that would be a great reason. Yeah, exactly. That would be
That's really weird
Like like that
If you're like, hey, I want to get a maybe fucking get a job in an industry one day
And like if I have videos of me saying the n-word then I won't be able to get it then like
Yeah
Take your fucking videos down
Take note pcp voicemailers you dirty people
Jesus christ. Yeah
Okay, next one is called um
Episode 260 battle scroll scenario explained
Three two one go
Hey, hi, it's your boy Dolos again. Uh, sorry for leaving a second voicemail on the same day. Fuck you ben
but uh
I'm catching up on the podcast and an episode 260 samurai sama calls talking about him and all the boys and mr
T shout out to mr
T
Uh, they're pissed because the the scroll that ben stole from them is battle plans. It's true and ben insinuated and
In fact blatantly stated that the battle plans were for them to fight each other
No, if you would listen to samurai sama shout out to samurai sama read that scroll
He said the battle scroll was for them as enemies to come together and take over japan with mr
T
I see
So, yeah, shout out to mr
T
Fuck you ben tom will never done continuity maintained
Ben does not fear his nemesis so much that he doesn't even listen to his words
I don't really you know, I have a
Yes, it's the thing sun sue said if you have your enemies battle plans just leave it just don't it's just like
It's just like listen. It's just it's just like listening to the pcp. You know when samurai sama starts talking
I just kind of tune out
Disrespect at all costs
Next voicemail is called uh
The two three two one go
Um
By the way, I I was the person that talked about the uh
The weird dug walker interaction
Um, yeah, I'm not sure if I mentioned this but like the one you saw it at like a tech
Uh a booth for like specifically for autographic things. So it's not like I just
Approached him and was like
Signed my dollar like he was he was there to sign things. Okay. Well. Yeah in in that case
It can only be that he had a problem with the dollar
So he must have just been like he didn't want to sign a dollar. Yeah, I can't sign at the holler. That's the greatest in the law
Isn't that illegal and legal tender though? Yeah, that's totally what he needs to use that
Seems like dug seems like dug god bless that sweet sweet man
absolutely
Next voicemail is called ben to-do list three two one go
All right, ben. It's time to get down to the real shoes the real bids. Please. No play isaac
Okay, they added a few new characters and doubled the characters because they all have alternate versions now
As well as tons of new content alternate routes new endings all that shebang
Also, please catch up on one piece. Thanks. Yeah, man
I'll probably check out Isaac again. Hey, Ben. Where where where were you last when you were reading one piece?
I was uh
kind of
Early on in wano like I was a little ways into wano. Okay
I would say wait until you hear that wano's over because it's
We're in the yeah, we're in the thick of it now and captain. It's a little bit like oh fuck reading it
Oh, like like if I caught up now, I would be on a cliffhanger. No, you'd I don't reckon you'd enjoy the week before that
you'd be in
In no, I don't I don't want there's a lot of action happening and not a lot of plot furthering
It is a lot of panels of cool shit happening. But there's only so many
Only so many things you can show in that many pages
We're deep in what is known as clash piece at the moment where it's just every chapter is just the different clash between characters
I mean, I'm I'm really enjoying it. It's cool. But I am if you want to binge it. Maybe after it's finished
Yeah, yeah
Yes, I do want to binge it. I'm not interested in getting back into reading weekly. There's some great stuff in wano. So yeah
Uh, oh, it's incredible
Hmm
I do I wish I was caught up, but I don't want to spend the fucking time
Ben it's got actual trans characters who are actually cool and do things. Isn't that nice? Um
It already had it already had those had the okama. Yeah, but now it's got like a pretty girl one
Well, that's nice. It's it's still I love I love that for her that character is
Trans or is just a man that looks like a she refers to herself as she she gets everyone else to refer to as yeah
I've always seen her in all in all the ways that that matter. It's yeah. It's a trans character. Talk about kiku not Yamato
I don't know who these people are. Yeah, don't worry. They're lame. They're okay
Uh next
Wait
Wait, what?
That was the bend to do oh wait, I uploaded to okay the next one is 3 180
Okay, uh, the this one is why the Ralph thing makes no sense three two one go
The the Ralph video was not uploaded like to start a fight and to get clout
The Ralph video was uploaded out of spite because it's motivated by fucking Trixie not by uh by fox's face
Vizier dickhead, uh, it's motivated by Trixie because it's spite at uh fucking may and Ralph
That's why that video went up. It has nothing to do with fucking money at all. That's just like why can't it be both?
A neat side effect that was completely like a missed opportunity for them to fucking get clout with it
But no that I don't I don't I don't these are all good relationships fight bullshit
That's why it went up on the fucking channel to the fucking piss me off. That's the only reason why I I don't think you're right
I think that might be a reason. I think it's absolutely both
I
Yeah, I think it's both and probably hundreds of all reasons of insanity that we we can't comprehend
Probably yeah, yeah
Sorry sucker, but you're
You fuck you
Sorry, you're a fucker. I rhymed it. Sorry. We've decided that you're wrong with no evidence
clarification
We we know what those guys were thinking. You don't know shit
Oh shit, I posted another one whatever next one is a three one eight one. It is uh the deepest lore
Three two one go
I want to hear the fucking Tobuscus deep lore somebody should figure that shit out because like quentin reviews already did
I don't fucking know who that guy is. He would brag about it on like his channel. Sometimes I don't know anything about
Players and shit like that. So there has to be this some like that guy with the glasses pro jared game
Yes, like style. Yes, like deep lore quentin reviews story about this person
And I've never heard it told from a like reputable source before so it's got to be out there somewhere
Yes, someone figure it out. It'll be funny
If you had type if you had typed that into fucking youtube I think you would have come up if you typed Tobuscus drama
If you took Tobuscus drama or history or something like that, then fucking you'd have it
There's probably more. Yeah, there's probably plenty more videos that I haven't seen. I've just seen the the quentin
I know who I made a funny scorum song whatever and he was a sex pervert
I had only I had only heard the name
I had never heard I isn't tabuscus is the diamond sword sword sword sword is that that guy?
I know that from munchie knowing that song. I had never heard the chicken in a biscuit song
Before I found out
I watched that quentin video and I was like, okay
uh
Yeah
Do you see a sex pet? I don't even I don't even remember I watched that video. I don't remember anything from it
He was like an emotional abuser and sex pest and all that all the easy hard like nasty stuff
Nice nice
Groomer was he a groomer? No, I don't think so. I think it was all over
All right
Well, no, dude that makes him a fucking that makes him a hero in my eyes
Fuck yeah, dude
He's cleared but he's cleared the bar. He's clean. He is so much better than his contemporaries
uh
Next voicemail is called uh taking it too far three two one go
Hey, Ben. Hey, Gib. Hey, uh
God this tome's still alive even
I was wondering what you guys thought about the fact that games journalists like I don't know what you mean
I could talk you are being more supportive of the palestinians in the ongoing genocide against them
Than our own fucking government who barely even spoke out about the fact that the Associated Press was
Hit by a fucking missile
Earlier today
Anyway, uh free Palestine
I
I'm glad I'm glad you liked
I'm glad you liked when I trolled chris with the slime and punishment
uh
I believe I believe that the slime and punishment finale that the game
The game will be the ultimate act of trolling chris
Uh by by making uh mind-blowing mind-blowingly high effort content
Uh
So look look forward to that that that's coming
Uh other than that, I don't know what the fuck you're talking about
You remember you remember in sonnet you 101 when you said that you follow the prime directive when it comes to christian
Ben you said that one thing the one time and you didn't do it
That's not what I sound like. That's not what I sound like in you know, that's what you fucking sound like
Everyone says oh ben ben used to be cool, you know
I want I want so bad for all those racist fucks on kiwi farms to like me
But then they say oh ben said he follows the prime directive, but then he didn't and I and I and I cry I cry
I've lost their esteem
Damn, so what you're saying is you're a liar
I am
I am a liar. Okay. That's right
Yeah, okay
Shit the next one's the last one. Oh really wait. I think so. Yeah. Yep. Okay. This is this is the last one
It's called super sick guy
three two one go
So I noticed that uh, there's a certain number of people left on the pcp that are uh
Very talented artists false
Maybe we could bring back a certain
draw cast
Wink wink kiss kiss
Oh my god
I mean, I guess there's no reason why we couldn't you know, it's funny we
Yeah
That we made that quick draw server because we wanted to branch off from the pcp and
And make it our own thing but munchie. Yeah, mostly spearheading that and now munchie has left that and um, yeah
We can do what we like with it. So we could that was a munch. That was a
Yeah, that was the quick draw saloon was like a munchie thing and then munchie's gone. So
It's whatever. Yeah, and he's been gone. It's a great server still
We have lots of cool artisans. So, you know, I haven't just we could just like have that server and then make the show and put it on
the pcp channel
I guess
I guess you're right. I guess we could we could fucking reclaim that shit the power in the hour
Um, well, that's the last voicemail and we are almost at three hours. So I mean, I guess we're I guess that's it
That works for me
Um, I don't know any any final thoughts about shit
Israel um phantom horn versus coming tuesday free palestine death to israel free palestine death to israel
free palestine death to israel
I don't know about yeah, I think I think they to the states to the states not to the people
All right
Like like like get rid of the prime minister get rid of the fascist government they have
And and press talks god damn it
Uh, yeah, I'm speaking. Yeah, no more no more the usa needs to stop speck in israel
Need to back off need to back off back to their own country. You bros need to
Yeah
You gotta you gotta go back where you came from
America america send your american dollars and your iron dome back across the pond. Why don't you
Why don't you get a dollar in trouble to dig you out of a fucking hole?
Uh, okay
That's that's the show. That's enough
patreon.com slash the procrastinators bonus episodes
Uh speak pep.com slash cheap
Uh, what's our fucking slash pzp voicemail if you want to leave us a voicemail, but keep it short stupid
um
I guess that's it. I guess the
Simzies links. Oh, yeah
Uh, uh twitter.com forward slash simsie fart. Uh, we'll just leave at that simsie fart. Everything's on there. Check out simsie farts
Uh art over there commission him. He's a he's a good boy
He's a good. He's a good boy. Give me money. Keep the capitalist wheels turning boys
Yes
Yes, uh, thank you for having me on folks. Bye
My pleasure end of the episode. Good night. God bless. Yes