This episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast was brought to you by our bonus episode!
Go to patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators and pledge $5 or more to get access to all our bonus monthly episodes.
Last month's episode was Insomnia!
That's Patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators, making you fall asleep every single time.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
This is episode 99 of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever.
We're getting there.
I'm a Digibro.
You've got Tom Oliver.
I am...
Nice one, dude.
I'm not Digibro at all.
I'm a...what's the opposite of digital?
Analogue.
Physical.
I'm an analog bro.
Analogue bro.
When's the lore of analog bro gonna break in there?
Oh, no wait.
Look forward to anal bro.
Look forward to the awesome origin story of analog bro at Radcon 3.
That's right.
All right.
Right off the bat, making false promises that we can't keep right off of that.
Everything's a lie.
Don't believe any of it.
There's a...
Every time anyone mentions anything concerning Radcon 3, there's always little asterisk at
the end that makes a notch in the mind.
Do you sound like a munchie hat?
Munchie hat?
My favorite hat producing content creator in the entire world, known exclusively for
his hat making skills.
I don't think so.
Tom Oliver.
Pretty good.
Known for being black and white.
For affinity user.
Yeah, for affinity user.
Whoa.
That's for a future episode.
It's true.
We've got Hippocrates.
Get ready.
I am ready.
What are you doing?
Get ready.
Get ready for the podcast.
Okay, shut up.
Ben Taint is here.
There he is.
Ah, the crisp, refreshing taste of Diet Mountain Dew Code Red.
There's so many adjectives.
Okay, and what are we talking about today, everybody?
Let's just get to the fucking topic.
Today is the day that we revisit a topic that we had previously attempted, the only failed
PCP episode up to this point, the legendary, much awaited, weird utilitarianism.
What?
Whether there have been failures is debated.
Well, okay.
Any technical failures.
This was ruined by Nate's work, if I remember correctly.
Well, it's true.
My computer had died in the middle of our episode.
We were 45 minutes into it, so we had wanted to put the capper, put the stopper on all
discussions of this weird utilitarianism meme and make it so that there was just a one-stop
shop for all your WU needs.
We wanted to end it once and for all, indeed.
We wanted to slay that dragon.
Fucking fizzled out and died much like Nate's hopes and dreams and his computer, and we
had to restart here today for you.
He's not wrong.
I think he said in the original episode, I think I'm going to come down on your side,
Nate, but also make fun of you.
What better way to start Radcon than to fucking end weird utilitarianism forever?
Never to have it rise again.
I just want to reiterate for everybody.
Yes, indeed.
Radcon is next week from when you're hearing this.
This is episode 99.
There will be the PCP episode 100 spectacular at Radcon.
You guys have been fucking asking about Nate's fucking weird utilitarianism since day fucking
one, and here we go.
We're finally going to be able to put that ghost to rest and suck him up in our fucking
ghost bathroom.
Put that ghost right back in its shell, everybody.
Here we go.
I think the best way to start is to reference Nate yourself.
You are the urban dictionary this time.
So what is weird utilitarianism?
Excellent question.
What does it mean to you?
It's a complicated thing, but as a good starting point.
Does anybody know where the term came from?
Was it from the comments?
Someone in the comments.
I was actually trying to remember who specifically said it, but I couldn't.
That exact phrase came up multiple times.
I don't know if it was inspired by one person, but multiple people would refer to Nate specifically
as weird utilitarianism as your thing.
That's true.
It came a little bit of a meme, and now obviously it's grown a little bit.
Let's start with the word utilitarianism.
So here's your urban dictionary defines it as such.
A philosophy that people should act in order to increase the frequency and longevity of
pleasure throughout the world.
Although the idea acting to increase long term and global pleasure sounds desirable,
utilitarians believe that the pleasure of many outweighs pleasure of a few.
A utilitarian may believe that killing one person in order to increase the pleasure of
any or killing someone and harvesting their organs would be a just action.
Some utilitarians have seen that this can be dangerous.
Many utilitarians, because of this, follow a slightly different ideology.
They should act to increase the frequency and longevity of pleasure throughout the world
by following the best social standards.
Okay, Nate, well it sounds like utilitarianism is already weird,
but what's weird about your utilitarianism?
Well, what's weird about mine, I guess in contrast to this,
we'll flesh it out throughout this entire podcast,
but the definition here, even in here, it is confused on urban dictionary.
It's like bringing multiple interpretations at you.
The weird thing about that definition is the fact that they started off with like,
it's all about bringing the maximum amount of happiness to the maximum amount of people.
I'm like, that's what every philosophy is about.
That's not you need to utilitarianism.
What they feel to define here is that utilitarians think purely in mechanical terms
and in like, there's no soul to be conscious of or thoughts of the afterlife.
It is purely a materialistic view, which is not synonymous with immoral Christians.
So that the utility calculus is every utilitarianism.
Correct, he had the soul of a champion.
Well, okay, I personally, the reason why I like the term weird utilitarianism so much
is because I am 100% against identitarianism in every form.
What's that?
Identitarianism, just the idea of grouping any people together under a label to quantify them,
I find it definitely harmful and mostly immoral.
I hate labels so much.
I'm so glad people have made this label for me.
Well, yeah, but that's the thing because the weird utilitarianism label is a label of one, me, just me,
which is exactly how we should think of people as individuals and that's it.
Like the word, if I tell someone I'm a Democrat, which I'm not,
then like they will immediately pour all these assumptions onto me.
If they say that they're a weird Democrat.
Well, then you got something special going on.
I would say the same thing about me.
If you attach the word weird in front of it, yeah, it helps to diminish some of those.
It's like, yeah, he's kind of like, it's kind of like if you call yourself like a weird feminist,
like nobody wants to be called, or I shouldn't say nobody wants to be called a feminist anymore.
But a lot of people don't want to be called a feminist because of the fact that they're like,
oh, it has too many connotations.
But if you're just a weird feminist, it's like people get that you're on board for women,
but they're not sure why or like what things you're into.
What are his true motives?
There's a lot of people that would look at feminists now and be like,
those are pretty fucking weird people.
Yeah, but if you're a weird feminist, you've got to confuse them so that they're not upset.
I don't want to have to meet a girl and have her say she's a feminist,
and then I just start to project all my bullshit baggage onto her.
I don't want to do that.
And of course, I don't want people to do that to me either.
There could be some old fucking mom from the 70s who doesn't even know what a computer is,
but still calls herself a feminist because that's what she was when she was a little babe.
The biggest problem I see in today's online discussions,
and it's probably been the problem forever, and it's just become clear to me as I get a little more mature and worldly,
the problem across the board is twofold.
People, one, they talk past each other and they don't understand what the other, excuse me, is actually saying.
They're not actually paying attention to what the other person is saying.
They are making assumptions and projecting things onto them from their predetermined biases about what these people think.
That is problem one.
Problem two is that people do not actually comprehend that people believe what they say.
They don't actually understand the difference in foundational worldview that people have.
You can be an atheist and you can go around and be like, oh, Catholics are so evil.
Always preaching about hell.
It's so immoral and I say that because on a base level, I do think it is immoral.
But if you think about it from the perspective of the Catholic,
if they don't force their children through whatever means are necessary to be a good, virtuous Christian,
that is dooming their child to an eternity in hell.
That is so much more significant than any amount of discomfort they will suffer in life,
that it would be super immoral of them to not do whatever was necessary to protect their kid from this perceived danger.
The problem with people, oh, sorry, continue.
No, no, go ahead, go ahead.
The problem with people on, like, fighting just in general, but also on the internet, especially if you can see it,
people's conversation is laid out bare-hair.
People respond to the invisible words.
People may be implying by just being part of the hate effigy that they are assigned to.
So if you just see, not even in the text, if you just see some sort of avatar or name
that could in fact signify that they are a part of some group vaguely,
then you are just going to bring up your hate effigy that you have of that group.
Dude, I for one am sick and tired of people seeing my brony icon
and just making all this shit on the page, just making all these blanket assumptions about.
It's not cool.
I gotta tell you, if you want people to take anything you say seriously ever,
don't make your whole aesthetic memes, because if your whole aesthetic is memes,
that is often the case.
Let's say you go to Drill's Twitter.
Drill's Twitter is a big meme.
That's the joke.
It's a joke Twitter.
His pictures are all goofy.
His name is stupid, but it's great.
Sometimes you see people and their name is cuntlord,
and they've got a picture of a gaping ass as their avatar,
and they're leaving comments like, this video was okay,
but I think if you improved your sound quality or whatever,
am I taking advice from cuntlord with the gaping ass?
The gaping ass is just how you kick cuntlord with the main building.
Consider your brand.
Your brand affects the way that people perceive the things you say.
And even if you're nobody on Twitter, people still are gonna...
It's amazing how often I get responses that I don't understand on Twitter,
because it's like some random guy who I don't know anything about,
and his profile is just so uncomprehensible that I can't even understand the tweet itself.
Even if it's written kind of plainly,
I don't know what perspective they're coming from,
and it's hard to get that in 140 characters,
and with the minimal information that's on somebody's Twitter page.
280 characters, 280.
My phone still is 140. It's annoying.
It's very annoying.
Anyway, right at the back here, we're just describing for the viewers,
just that tribalism is...
Everyone's packed into a label and Nate doesn't like that.
Does anybody disagree with that, that tribalism is bad?
Probably not.
I think we're all on the same page.
Well, they're funny.
I don't think that tribalism is bad.
I do think labels are bad.
I think it's fine to be a part of it.
I think the tribadism is pretty cool.
I think it's fine to be a part of whatever...
What is that, Ben?
I'm trying to talk and you fucking talk it over,
because that's why no one's reacting to your goddamn joke.
What was he saying? What is your thing?
What are you asking?
Tribadism.
What's a tribad?
Shit. It's some kind of lesbian thing.
Thank you, Ben.
I think it's scissoring. I think it's scissoring.
Oh, tribadism. Ignore me.
I pronounce it tribadism, not tribadism.
Well, I guess you'd be the expert.
Wait, wait, wait. I looked it up.
A tribad, according to Urban Dictionary,
is a female with a greatly enlarged clitoris,
thought to be of as a result of hormone imbalance,
especially one of homosexual orientation.
Ben, what cartoon is it?
It looks like I was watching.
Steve from Universe.
Well, in any case, I'm okay with the idea of people
sticking with their groups.
I mean, we are a tribe. That's pretty clear.
Are you telling me you're a white nationalist, did you?
Yeah.
Invisible word.
Absolutely.
I don't think anybody questions that the PCP is a tight-knit group
that's kind of insular,
but we do try to avoid having labels on this group.
There's a lot of podcasts that you can point at
and say that's a libertarian podcast,
or that's a liberal podcast,
or this is a comedy podcast, or this is that.
PCP is like, it is tribal in that it's the PCP,
but there's no other simple way to describe it.
I love...
Yeah, we're just ourselves.
One of my favorite things is insisting that I am a red pill
and a blue pill at all times.
Yeah.
Just it.
Both ends of the spectrum.
And see...
Yeah, that's just...
Pure and simple.
That's fair, but that's just...
Yeah, that's you just rejecting.
Nobody likes to be labeled.
Being labeled is not fun.
People should be judged on their ideas.
Some people really like it.
Some people are all about it.
Some people derive a lot of it.
Okay, well, you know what?
Labeling yourself is a fickle enterprise
that far too many people identify with.
You got your guys like Richard Spencer,
who would just say, like, I'm white.
I care about white people.
I don't care about, like, whatever.
I just want, like, a future for the white race.
And, like, I get why he thinks that way,
the tribal nature of humanity and stuff,
but I think it is a very huge mistake
to just say let your race, like,
should define the group that you hang with.
And, like, you got groups like, I don't know,
like feminists or whatever.
People just push their particular agenda
and increase the amount of, like, fragmentation
by having, like, purity tests over and over.
Like, if you've got, like,
how feminist is feminist enough to be a member of a community?
Or how white is white enough to be in Richard Spencer's country?
Well, I think the big problem with collectivism in general is that,
and we're seeing it happen now,
is that whenever you have, like, a collective ideology,
it kind of, like, turns on itself,
because there's more, like you said,
there's more purity tests that happen over and over again.
And it seems like the inevitable end game of collectivism
is just individualism.
Because, like, eventually, you're going to keep breaking down groups smaller and smaller
until it's just me versus you.
So it's like, why waste, like, a fucking century of, like,
infighting and, like, social unrest
when we already came to the answer?
That's exactly right. That's exactly right.
Hey, we're not really talking about weird utilitarianism.
We're talking about labels generally.
And we're going to continue nonsense because I weren't talking about something that Digi said.
Yeah, and I have to go out and read.
As soon as everybody else is done.
Oh, yeah, it's fine. Digi, I think that it is misguided
that it is good that the PCP is so insular.
Because I don't think that it is.
I think that we should be branching out more as we are with guests.
Oh, I didn't mean to say it's...
I don't mean to say it's good for us to, like, never talk to anybody
and all stuff like that.
I just mean it's nice to have a tribe.
Like, it's good to have people who generally see things the same way you do
and that you can relate to and bounce ideas off of
and, like, get a better understanding of yourself.
Like, I don't think anybody in the PCP would have been as successful
if not for having a bunch of like-minded individuals
they can bounce their ideas off of, you know.
It's usually advantageous to just not be in one particular group.
You know, on that side...
Why limit yourself to just one box?
Yeah, that's right.
Zero artistry and just pick any one you want.
I think it is important to note that humans definitely are tribal.
We definitely are that way, just biologically speaking and psychologically speaking.
We definitely, like, are more comfortable with things that we've, like, grown up with
and then when you go to foreign cultures, like, it feels foreign.
You know, you can't just instantly absorb the culture of, like, a new place immediately.
I actually...
What Munchie was saying about, like, don't limit yourself to one box.
Pick as many different labels as you want.
I like that.
Yeah.
Well, you were joking about it, at least.
I think it's a good idea to...
I think it's funny everybody, like, has, oh, I have this one religion
and this one, like, philosophy.
Like, oh, I'm a...
I'm a fucking, like you said, atheist or zero-astry-anist or whatever.
Like, pick two.
Pick three.
Some of them are mutually exclusive.
Some of them are, but not all of them.
Like, I would consider myself a Taoist
because nothing about it contradicts my own philosophy, you know.
So, like, why not throw it on the pile?
There you go.
You know, be a...
That just cheapens the idea of labels, which we already know.
They should already be cheapened
because they're not worth anything.
Well, it should be super cheap.
Taoism based off of Tao, the greatest devout commenter of all time.
Yeah, exactly.
Shout out to Tao.
I want to go on a...
Okay, well, let's talk more about...
I want to go on a rant here
because this is a perfect opportunity for it
since you're all here and this is all your fault,
which is that I, as a...
This is super relevant.
As a member of being in the PCP,
have been judged to have opinions I don't have
based on other members of the PCP.
Same.
This has happened where...
The biggest way this happened to me
is recently there's a board called TRANS
that exists on Reddit.
It's spelled like that, like a ton of letters.
And it's for, like, trans people making fun of themselves, essentially.
Like, you know, self-effacing humor about trans issues.
So they had a thread called a gender-fluid egg,
something like finding a gender...
The rare gender-fluid egg is what it was called.
And it was just a bunch of quotes of me
from my Crunchyroll interview
talking about how I wanted to be Ranma
and being able to switch between male and female freely.
And people in this thread,
a bunch of people were saying,
like, oh, I always thought Digi was like that
because I watched his videos
and he talks about wanting to be a girl all the time, you know?
And I was like, this thread was a huge revelation for me
because I never thought about it and I'm reading it
and I'm like, oh, my God, these people are right.
Like, I've been ignoring this this whole time.
But then somebody comes in the thread and is like,
Digi can't be...
Digi's probably not gender-fluid
because he's part of a transphobic group
called the PCP,
who all hate trans people and want them...
Is that what people say about us now?
They want them to have no rights and their red pill.
And also, you were considered...
This was considered a...
What's the word I'm looking for?
The...
Hate group?
No, the red one, not the blue one.
But not Republican.
Oh, yeah.
Conservatives?
Yeah.
This was described as a conservative transphobic podcast.
And I was just like, I don't...
Even if there was at least...
This was all based on a discussion of, of course,
Nate and Ben and DeVue, I think,
being, like, aggressively misunderstanding
trans issues or something in some podcast.
But it got attributed to me, and I was just like,
I've been the most pro-trans person that I know
for as long as I've known that it was a thing, you know?
Like, I've always been totally down
for trans rights and everything.
So it was very strange for me to see that.
And I was just like, the PCP is not a conservative podcast
or a transphobic podcast.
If it was, then I wouldn't be on it, you know?
Like, that would...
Because for it to, for the entire podcast to be,
that would mean that everyone on there was that, you know?
But it's not.
It's a multifaceted podcast with a bunch of different personalities
with different worldviews.
That's the problem.
People who feel as though they can actually talk to each other
in spite of the differences in their worldview, you know?
That's right.
It's unfortunate, but this is people...
You know, like, I understand why people make this connection.
Well, first of all, to make the case that, for example,
what I said on the podcast was transphobic,
I said something...
Actually, what I said in this podcast was equally damning
in terms of me being a hater against trans rights.
Because what I said previously in this very podcast
was I am staunchly anti-identitarian.
And that is exactly synonymous with saying
what I said in that podcast was that I don't care about trans people.
Because that's what I mean.
I don't care about these individual issues
that have literally nothing to do with my life.
And I don't care about Republican rights.
I don't care about anyone's rights.
I don't care about black people.
I don't care about white people.
I don't care about any of this shit.
I just care about individual rights as a person to person.
I think every trans person should be 100% free
to do whatever they want.
I completely think you should do that.
But, like, you know, I've got a lot of shit to do.
I don't have a lot of time to worry about everyone's problems.
That's how I feel.
Fight your own battles.
I definitely believe in that.
Say that again?
Oh, fight your own battles.
Like, everybody's always trying to fight for somebody else.
They're always trying to be like...
Every time I get a complaint that I said,
nigga, from a non-black person,
I'm just like, you're...
Why do you care?
You know, like...
Yeah.
And even if it is a black person,
I'm like, why do you care either?
But, like, it's just very strange to me
when I see people fighting,
like, trying to fight for other people.
It's like, fight for your own shit.
I know you've got problems.
You know, I know you've got your own shit.
I don't know.
White guilt or something.
People want to be allies and something.
I don't know what are the ideas there.
I think...
I'm sure that's part of it, Nate.
I'm sure that's a growing culture.
But I think a lot of it is just, like,
people trying to be goody-to-shoes.
Though, I say that in, like, a mean way.
But I'm sure in their heart of hearts,
they want to be a gay person.
See, I completely agree.
Yeah.
I completely agree that these people are actually
being good and being honest with their worldview.
I don't even begrudge them that.
I simply have a different worldview,
and I think that it is not helpful
to just, like, call me evil or hateful
or, like, you know, any of that shit
as opposed to convincing me...
Like, pedantic romantic is trans.
And message me.
And, like, politely explain some areas
where I made basically just complete mistakes.
And I just politely said,
oh, well, thanks.
I wasn't aware of that.
You know, I don't spend a lot of time
thinking about these issues as should be clear.
So, yeah, I was definitely wrong about that.
Thanks for correcting me.
We had a completely civil discussion.
I respected her points, and it was fine.
And that's a civil discourse
that actually gets somewhere.
Yeah, that's it.
But the reason we're all grouped together,
this is the other problem here.
It's that people can think whatever they want
about, like, me and what I've said.
But because I am, like, officially,
I have the label.
I do have a label of member of the PCP.
And, Digi, you also have the label
of member of the PCP.
And people can just latch onto that.
And they can make any connections they want.
They could say that, first of all,
they wrongly perceive me to hate trans people.
They could say, he's in the PCP.
Therefore, the whole PCP is tainted with this idea.
Therefore, Digi is also tainted with this idea.
Or he's, like, encouraging it.
This is a huge part of why we've essentially lost Jesse
and why all of you are responsible
who listened to the show for associating him
with everything we say.
When he does not want to be associated
with a lot of what we say, you know?
But, like, again, like you said,
you get a target on your back just for being,
like, friends with somebody who, you know,
who people don't like.
And it's one thing if it's, like, a criminal,
I'd be, like, yeah, you shouldn't be,
like, if someone's doing something really bad,
even if they're just being an asshole,
like, yeah, you should probably not
openly associate with them.
But, like, this is a podcast.
It's a discussion.
I'm not holding you guys responsible
for the things you say on the PCP,
because it's, first of all, a comedy show.
It's not a fucking...
We're not, like, trying to decide laws.
We're not, like...
This is a whole other rant
that, like, people these days
are constantly holding, like, YouTubers to task
to be right about everything.
It's, like, this podcast is not about
being correct about anything.
It's a fucking comedy podcast.
A bunch of, like, guys in their late 20s
get to sit around...
Well, and munchy.
You know, sit around and just be all whatever
thoughts they happen to have about some topic,
because we're pals.
And if you like listening to it, that's fine.
But, like, every time people are, like,
coming down on us super hard,
because, like, something we said was a little edgy
or, like, offended someone,
I'm just, like, dude, it's a podcast, you know?
Like, don't worry about it.
It's not gonna hurt anybody.
I mean, it's one of those things,
and also none of us were, like,
transphobic in, like, a really bigoted,
like, stupid way.
Right.
Like, we were all just curious
and, like, talking about it, like,
if none of us was.
But that's the thing.
It could not be an ally.
You know?
The problem is to these people,
these are, like, life-or-death questions
in their mind.
So to not be an ally fighting on their side
is to be, at the very least, like,
facilitating harm.
And that is, like...
If you have that kind of mindset,
you need to fuck off.
I mean, yeah, I would agree with that.
I would agree with that.
Like, anyone who doesn't agree with me totally
or isn't, like, fighting, you know,
for my battles and my rights, it's, like,
dude, I got my own shit to worry about.
So you can fuck off, you know?
I mean, that's how I feel.
I'm completely libertarian on this front.
I encourage anyone to do whatever they want
on all of this front.
But to say that, like, we have to be
fighting the same battles as you,
like...
Fuck off.
You can't tell me what to do.
Your particular world view trumps everything else
and has to be respected above all others.
If anyone's being hurt,
if there are people being murdered or, you know,
any of this shit is happening,
let me know so that the...
Well, don't let me know, because I don't care.
But the police care.
The police fucking care.
You know, there was probably a couple murders
in Africa, probably a couple murders in Russia today.
Guess what?
I don't care.
I don't know those people.
I'm sorry.
The police of Russia have to deal with those murders.
It's out of my jurisdiction.
It is outside my fucking jurisdiction.
That's how I feel.
The problem with the PCP and everyone taking all of our
opinions...
I have real trans friends, by the way.
I have real trans friends who I talk to and like.
And we are friends.
But here's the thing.
I like them because they're my friends,
not because they're trans.
That's the thing, guys.
That's what I want.
Everyone to fucking understand.
I have trans friends who are really...
We have not talked about weird utilitarianism at all.
Man, I would have said something
completely else other than weird utilitarianism
right now as well.
Okay.
Go for it.
We'll get to it.
This is going to be side tangents forever.
We're at the very end.
We're going to be like,
what were we talking about at the beginning of this podcast?
Anyway, the problem with the PCP and everyone
taking all of our opinions as whole is
everyone's taking...
Print out each of our icons,
put them in a bowl,
put them in a microwave,
and you've made an opinion soup.
Not only do all of our opinions
get mushed into one,
they're warped opinions.
Just do the nature of the way the internet works.
Everyone will warp your opinion no matter what.
To be a cartoonish, evil, hate, effigy version
of what it originally was.
It's a double...
You will have...
If you close comments on your videos...
It won't be attributed to Hippo or something like that.
It won't even be...
It won't even be your warped opinion.
It'll be someone else's.
Yeah.
And people...
It's like when you close comments on a video
and suddenly you deny all criticism.
That's the kind of logical...
That's how the internet works.
You turned off comments on one video
and now you cannot take criticism at all.
That's how people now take you.
It's funny you mentioned that
because there were a lot of people back
when we did comment rules part two.
The entire PCP is anti-comments.
When half of that episode was a debate
about whether they were good or bad.
People recently who have been criticizing you
for your whatever stance on comments or whatever,
they'll take clips of you
saying these things from a PCP episode.
You can hear me cutting in,
making a counter-argument,
and arguing against that point.
And then they say,
oh, the PCP believes this.
And we just have clearly different opinions.
I'm trying to say mine,
but then they just say the PCP thinks this.
I think this is like...
I don't really blame people for doing this.
It's like intellectual shorthand.
I feel like that's kind of like...
Our brands are designed to do that
because it frees up resources to do other things.
Back in the day,
when you're trying to make sure you don't get mulled
by a saber-toothed tiger,
you don't really have time to noodle
on the nuances of everything going on around you.
Our brands are good at picking out patterns really quickly.
And I think that's what happens in situations like this.
It's easy to just make a flat association
and roll with it,
as opposed to sitting there mumbling over.
I completely agree that it's totally reasonable
that this happens in people's heads.
But I think as soon as they open their mouth,
that's when you need to start thinking about it.
That's right.
We cannot judge people's thoughts,
but we can 100% judge their actions, and we should.
I'm not excusing people.
I'm just saying I understand why it happens.
I think 90% of the time it's not maliciously done.
I think people are just not thinking it through.
When you're tasked with being a trans police officer
and you're on your morning commute to work every day,
you have to scan every podcast to see which one is transphobic.
And you only have five minutes to do so
in which you're eating crunch bars.
You're going to make some mistakes and miss files here and there.
I understand.
We get it, guys.
By the way, I just want to clarify, guys,
it's not like I've said this before,
but I don't like not care about trans people.
It's that your issues are your own, they're not my issues.
That's how I feel.
I think that people can't comprehend the idea of a group
that isn't the same.
We're a group of friends.
Most groups of friends don't go under a group
that is like a brand as well.
So we sit around having meanings deciding
what opinions we're going to have as the PCP.
I feel like some people imagine
that we all sit in the chat going like,
oh, hey, everybody, fuck commenters, right?
And then everyone's like, yeah, yeah.
Then we all rally together and we say a chant.
We're like, fuck comments, fuck comments.
Because that's what's presented on the show
is this weird, frat boy, fun atmosphere.
That is interesting.
That's the podcast.
Yeah, we're all total chads and everyone knows it.
You know what was a fascinating video recently?
Uncle Adams and Anthony Fantano were having
a bit of a tiff recently.
They got together finally and they kind of just,
they had a podcast together.
And what was fascinating about that
was Anthony Fantano is like, he's a big meme guy.
But on this podcast with Uncle Adams,
he opens up and really says like, yeah, you know,
like I present myself as a big meme-er,
but I still get like a lot of like really vicious,
terrible comments.
I mean, of course,
he's got like 1.3 million subs and shit.
So he gets like vicious, terrible things
and he's aware of how terrible his comments are.
And like, and he talked about that for a while.
But to some degree, it's his fault.
But like, what he says is that like,
there's nothing I can do about it.
Because these people, they will just,
they're here to do this stuff.
And Uncle Adams was making all these points
about like how toxic his fans were like,
you know, when Fantano shit on him,
he got all this hatred and stuff.
And Fantano was just like, yeah, man, you know,
it's an unfortunate reality.
But what was interesting was how mature
Uncle Adams really was about this.
He was just like, look, people can shit on me
all they want.
But like, I'm getting death threats calls to my house
and like my family was getting this kind of shit.
And Fantano was just going along with him.
Like this perceived guy who appears to be like a bastion
of how much he, you know, like doesn't give a fuck
and just memes everything.
He actually, like he deliberately goes out of his way
to like not address it because that's what they want
in a situation like that, you know,
going off in a tangent here,
but I just thought it was interesting
and irrelevant to this comment discussion.
Even the most meme-y guys out there
or among the most, they are aware
that comments can be terrible
and that they generally are,
but they allow them to exist
because no good comes from like closing them.
Like you got to just let people do what they want
and that's just how it is.
I don't know if we all agree with that,
that no good comes from it.
Well, it's not that no good comes from it,
but you know, there's a lot of bad that comes with it.
I think in the case of Fantano though,
part of why his comments are so bad
is that he, for the longest time in his videos,
was like, you know, leave a comment
if you have something negative to say to me.
And it's like, well, you're encouraging people
to leave negative comments at that point.
That's true.
And like encouraging the memes to perpetuate themselves
and like every video he makes
is all the comments are just memes now
and it's the same memes, the same stale memes.
And it's like...
Pretty good meme video, Fantano,
but did you have to praise Hitler 50 times?
Exactly.
You know, you see that like every time.
It's always that.
And there are ways to deal with that.
You can just like block some of those people
or delete some of those comments
or favorite comments that are good.
Like it's a huge, huge thing
that you can do for your channel
is if you hit that heart button next to a comment
that you think is thoughtful and good,
that'll make it show up at the top of the fucking comment thing
and then everybody will see that like top comment
is a thoughtful comment, you know?
That's interesting.
Yeah, I like that.
I haven't thought of that.
See, that's a positive way to do these sorts of things.
I really like how the weird utilitarianism podcast
was lost to time
and here we are trying to revive it
and 30, 40 minutes in
we still have not gotten around
to even starting to talk about it.
Yeah, hey Nate,
what is weird utilitarianism mean to you anyway?
Let's get back to it.
Okay, here's the thing guys.
Here's the thing.
I think that was all good.
We're talking about ideologies here
and all this kind of stuff
and like group think and stuff
and weird utilitarianism,
as I've come to understand it,
is the bastion rebelling against all things
identitarian and bad and gay
and fake and not real.
I don't think that's what people mean
when they say weird utilitarianism.
Yeah, I've never thought of it that way.
I think you're confused.
I'm projecting, I'm lying.
I think when people say
you're weird utilitarianism,
they mean your drive
to your belief in bettering humanity
for the greater good
and your weird and frankly insane belief
that you can do it through YouTube.
When did I ever say that I could do it through YouTube?
I've said that I can control it.
Okay, okay.
I actually want to just revisit.
It's been like 40 minutes now,
but if we revisit the definition of utilitarianism,
the thing that I didn't like about that definition
was they talk about this thing of like,
I mean the little example here
is people who believe in utilitarianism
believe that it is all right to kill one person,
take their organs and distribute them to many.
Or like a utilitarian with the trolley cart problem
where you've got a train headed to one person
or headed to five people
and you have the power to flip a switch
so it'll instead run over one person
and you get a net gain of life.
These are the sorts of questions
that are dealt with by this.
You know, I've never understood that real car thing
because it seems like obviously you kill the one.
Like who would choose otherwise?
Well, but then you're responsible for killing the one.
Okay, well you're responsible by an action
for killing four people then.
There's a moral quandary here about action.
The idea, yeah, like the responsibility for the death
is the quandary here.
Is it moral like to kill one person to save a billion?
Like is that moral?
Well, that's your question.
Even I don't necessarily agree.
It seems so obvious to me
because it's obvious to me and that's the way that I think.
Okay, what if you had to torture a person
for a thousand years to save a billion people?
What if you had to do that?
First of all, it's a huge waste of my fucking time.
Yeah, why am I living a thousand years?
Yeah, I'd pay someone else to do it, obviously.
We're using examples here, goddammit.
Are you saying I push a button and it causes somebody
to suffer a thousand years to save a billion people?
Is that what we're talking about?
Basically.
Are all the people I love in that group of a billion people?
Yes, let's say yes.
Okay, then I'm pressing the button.
Okay, what if it's your dad you have to kill to save everyone?
Ooh.
Does the rest of the family die if I don't torture him
for a thousand years?
Let's say you have to kill your family
to save a billion other people.
No.
I don't care about anybody else outside my family.
Okay, well see, that's interesting.
I do.
Which of the PCP would I torture for a thousand years
to save a billion people?
Digi, Tom, Mage, Nate.
This is the question.
This is actually utilitarianism discussion.
This is the good stuff.
It's like making calculations,
trying to figure out how to maximize happiness
and health and human life and intelligence
and everything that comes with humans being alive.
I just want to mention that this problem
Vsauce did as part of his
special YouTube Red series,
but one of the free ones.
Where he set up a situation
with the train thing
and it was like
he actually fooled real people
and one of them
pulled the thing and killed the guy
but it's like this simulation ended
and then they interviewed her
and then everybody else
was just stunned
and frozen, could not
even though they were told
how to press the thing
and it was like
it's a good video.
That sounds fascinating.
And that's exactly the sort of thing.
When you're in the hot seat
and it is you now
let's say forget a button,
what if you have to slow,
the only mechanism is to physically cut
the throat of the person.
You have to reach down with a knife
and save, but see that's the thing.
I agree it is a different story.
How it affects you as a person
is relevant here, but the bigger question
is it's the amount of
suffering that you're calculating here.
Will this person suffer more
than the goodness that will be acquired
through saving
100 people or whatever.
The real difficulty with utilitarianism
and acting it out is because you have to put
your own personal values
and comforts aside.
The discomfort of
cutting someone's throat would override
the utilitarian value
of saving a million people.
This is a great thing.
Sam Harris has an argument
that has been made against him a thousand times
by guys like Glenn Greenwald
and stuff, and it's this.
Sam makes the case in
one of his books, I don't know which one,
for ethical uses of torture
and a lot of people,
a lot of Christians, for example,
that's obviously ridiculous.
No, there's no ethical case for torture.
Funny that the Christians would be the one
bringing that up.
Of all people.
But when you think about it,
let's say you've got a guy,
a Saudi Arabian terrorist
or let's say
what's the one?
A Palestinian terrorist, because Palestine has nukes.
He's part of them.
So you've got him here,
you've got him locked up, and this man
knows the location of a base
where his current,
like Palestinian terrorists,
are preparing a nuke to launch against the United States.
So let's say Los Angeles,
where the technology
is such that we won't be able to stop it.
This man has the information
and he will not talk.
Tell me the moral justification
for not doing what's ever necessary
to get that information out of him
to save millions, if not billions
of people.
That's true.
That is very true. Slippery slope is real.
Setting a precedent or something?
I think it makes a huge difference
if you are guaranteed
to know that he has that information
versus suspect.
Which is what I think is usually the case.
How do we know
until we torture them if they know?
You're not wrong.
You are not wrong.
When the question is,
we're talking about saving millions of people.
It's a reasonable thing to bring up.
How much are you willing to do?
Are you willing to
not give him a cup of coffee
when he asks for one?
Are we willing to torture him on that level?
I'd say people would probably say yes.
Are we willing to,
I don't know,
give him an Indian burn.
One Indian burn, exactly one.
Will we go that far? Where is the line?
Will we do literally nothing to him?
Are we comfortable with putting him down
or are we finally roughing him up
a little bit around the edge?
I think it comes down to what people are comfortable with themselves.
You're putting yourself in that situation.
Some people would be more comfortable
with going places than others.
My thing with utilitarianism
is that
from a raw intellectual perspective
I have a hard time arguing against it
even in its most extreme cases
just because
when it comes down to math
the math adds up.
It's uncomfortable
and unable to do it as I would be
because I'm a sensitive little bitch.
At the end of the day
if someone needed to murder me
to save a million people
I can understand the math
and I have a hard time presenting a rational argument
opposing it.
I feel like a lot of us would be okay
with somebody doing the horrible thing
to save millions, but not us.
I agree
that it's hard to argue against
that making more people happy
is good, even in an extreme case.
Intellectually I want to say that
probably you should kill that
one dude to save that billion.
But it's
the putting it into action
that is like, well, but how do you know?
Sure, you can be like, well in theory
if torturing this one person will save 100 people
utilitarianism would say
that I should do it and probably I should.
You can't know for sure
an outcome like that.
I mean, when you're talking about a math equation
you're assuming that
all the variables in the equation
are accounted for.
Just because we don't have literal mathematical
absolutes doesn't mean that there
couldn't be a case.
What if the one guy who could have got killed
was a future Bill Gates
and was going to save
literally billions with his money
or millions and the others
were worthless.
I feel like that's an interesting thought experiment
but there's no way to account for the future in the present.
I think even with
the fact that this is
even though it's a thought experiment that I understand
this is like a black and white cartoon
situation like press this button
kill one person instantaneously
save a billion others
obviously this is not an everyday case
and when you get out of the minute details
of what would an actual utilitarian
philosophy entail in the real
actual not thought experiment world
it gets more muddy than just
here's why.
This is not really what weird utilitarianism is
I think.
Let me just respond to his one point there
the reason why we have
conversations like this is so that
because laws have to
follow ethics
first you have to have the philosophy in place
and then you build from that in practice
and then you apply that to the real world
and that's why we discuss things
like this so that we can in our
heads understand what is an
inappropriate thing to do in a certain situation
what isn't so that then we can extrapolate
from that.
I'm just saying that like
we're all saying that like intellectually
we would all agree with that
and I'm sure we all would
I'm not saying that this is a bad thing
as a thought experiment I'm just saying that once you
get into the more minute details of everyday life
it starts to become less just like instantaneously
like yeah I cannot
well the thing is like when you talk about
utilitarianism in a crazy thought experiment
it's very easy to like understand
logistically how it would work
but like I don't think utilitarianism holds much value
in everyday practice because it's very
easy to make utilitarian arguments
for everything and like the whole reason we
have like morality
would break down at that point
I feel like morality is just kind of like
a religion that we all kind of inherently
apply to to keep like social structure
in place without like any moral
commonalities
in people like everything would break down
and utilitarianism really doesn't have any morality
other than math and like you can fudge the numbers
based on how you make the argument
no you can't I think that's totally
bullshit but I think
there's wiggle room to determining what constitutes
like creating more happiness
versus taking it away
we need to get into the fact that this is not what weird utilitarianism is
this is what utilitarianism is
weird utilitarianism is where
Nate eats nothing but beans all day
that is weird utilitarianism
I was talking about this
I got to crack open a can
I love
talking about all you guys
because you're all such you're all just like
perfect like encapsulations
of certain ideas you know
and Nate is a
Nate as a man who eats beans all the time
is like a great example
for conversation
like oh yeah like my friend Nate I mean that guy eats nothing
but beans so that's one way you can live
like that's something I say to people
that's one way you can live if you can call that living
that's where we get into the real
because okay I was making fun of you the other day
to my girlfriend
my fiance because of the fact that
you
I was like you know Nate is a big fitness boy
but like
for the last few years he's been like
kind of you know
by your own admittance
by your own admittance you haven't really been
at the gym like everyday
you haven't like kept maintaining
like being perfectly hot
but you're still eating nothing but beans
like even though
you're not like optimizing
the
serious
what you say
the facade has been ruined
I didn't ask for this
okay alright go I can take it I can take it
throw it at me hit me
I want it I want I feel the pain
I'm just saying that
I'm just saying that if you're going to eat
beans all the time
you need to have like all of the weird
utilitarian lifestyle beans are good
have you eaten a bean they're good
I like beans alright I've tried
a lot of beans dark red kidney beans
that's the one that's the one I'm telling you
I mean in fairness I think it's
I think it's fine that you're doing
like something at all times like
you obviously have a good figure
like even if you're not like as cut as you want
to be you're in the gym all the time you look good
and obviously if eating
beans all the time is contributing to that
then that's fine like it's just for me
when I'm like oh I'm going to be on a
workout and diet routine it's like it has to be
everything it has to be like the whole lifestyle
because otherwise it's like I can't
if I'm not
like really going ham into the
bean life then like just eating
beans every day it's really unsatisfying
for an everyday life like how do you reward
yourself after you finish like work
that's that's that's entirely true
I do reward myself
with oranges
I do not okay this is a meme
I don't actually just eat beans all the time
and in fact I went for quite a while
not eating beans for the last I don't know
like a month or something I didn't eat beans for lunch
there was a reason for that it's because like
a girl who did the apartment wasn't accepting
beans as the only meal that she eats
well I generally eat beans at work
like I have a shelf
just full of cans of beans at work
that I just open up and grab a can
but it's like
I left this particular batch in my car
in winter and it had frozen and then thawed
and the thing was then when I had eaten the beans
they were like gross and I didn't
like they were even more unpleasant
than normally they're pretty good
but these were pretty grainy and terrible
they was looking forward to his daily bean treat
but unfortunately he was met with something entirely different
this is the thing this is where utilitarianism
can bite you in the ass because I am a human being
and I think you'll like this
so I just wasn't eating
my beans because
they were like this this particular batch had like frozen
and thawed and was just gross and unpleasant
and so for like a month
I kept telling myself I really gotta eat these beans
for lunch and I'll fuck it I'll just go get fucking McDonald's
or something you should have thrown away those beans
and just got the beans
that is exactly what I did last week
I finally was like you know what the existence
of these beans are literally preventing me from
eating beans I need to destroy them
and start fresh so I did
so I threw them all in the trash and then bought
the whole new batch of beans
and now I'm eating them again and it's much better
but see that's what I'm trying to say
I am a man with many weaknesses
I go out and I like to preach ideas
which I think is valuable but everyone has flaws
and I admit I'm a man of many many flaws
I do not stick
to my plans all the time
I have missed on Monday I didn't work out
and then last week's Monday I missed that as well
so I've only been working out twice a week
for the last couple of weeks and that's terrible
that's a business I've been working out
see I'm an embarrassment I'm an embarrassment
but I know
the right things to do and I'm slowly
gearing myself more in that direction
like my
YouTube success came from
a cold hard analysis of like
okay what's happening now it's not
working out you know marginal success so far
but I'm working on it
what I've been doing up to this point has not been working out
I have to re-evaluate
and figure something out and so I just
made up me a mafia got that idea
in my head just did it it was great
and now it's been re-cajiggered doing we-agwas and stuff
and it's more in line with the formula
I'm still trying to make the big projects
you know whatever
but I wanted to bring up
oh shit I forgot what I wanted to bring up
never mind
fucking you just keep going buddy you just go on all day
I don't know what the fuck I'm talking about
all I'm saying
all I'm saying is that with me
like I said before I like to start with having
the right principles
principles are in place so that then
I personally for my life
can then like work on
quote-unquote laws or just like strategies
that I'm going to employ
it was that you were saying
how you preach a lot and can't
necessarily like you know practice it
perfectly and
I have weaknesses many well you know
we're all here on YouTube being like
we're here on a soapbox like that's what
we're here to do a lot of the times people
make fun of me for the fact that like
they say something in a video and then totally
contradict it later or make another video that
contradicts it and do that all the time
and it's because these are just
like these videos are just thoughts
they're just ideas they're just
here's an idea what if the world's like
this you know like idea channel
have these people not seen Steven Universe
you need to here comes a thought you let it
come and then you let it go they need to
they need to catch up
great great joke Nate good job
I have no idea what to talk about
Stefani here comes a thought
that might alarm you come on
oh fuck you guys none of us understood it
that was the universe
I just didn't care
hope you enjoyed it okay
who else wants to tell me how cool I am
let's tell me more
utilitarianism sucks because human
happiness is worthless
I sort of agree
including weird utilitarianism
okay here's the thing I take a totally
pragmatic view that I think
human happiness is a non-tangible good
and like I don't
actually care about it but what human happiness is important
for is that human beings
are machines that have a happiness gauge
and if that dips they become
less efficient so it is in our best
interest to keep people happy and productive
I think of it like that
to accomplish what ends Nate
now you guys are talking about the whole like
objective like what's the purpose of life
like where are we going what's all about and that's
that's where I can tell you
I'm not asking I just want what do you
want humans for
but it applies the question
and that's totally relevant that's the foundation
of all this like you have to start a bedrock
like where are we going then how
do we get there you know assess human nature
etc etc okay Starfleet
right Starfleet I see
yeah oh boy here we go
Starfleet is the
vision of the future that seems
like a rational place
for human beings to go and I don't think that's necessarily
like the end point
of where humans go like Starfleet Star Trek
is a very transitional phase
for humanity even in the show
it's a period of exploration not a
period of like we're done exploiting
like we found everything let's just work run our shit now
it's a period of trying to pursue
you know the truth that exists
outside of the current human perception
and I think as long as human beings are alive
there will always be things for us to discover
and new stuff I mean just obviously obviously
so
what Starfleet is to me
is an idea of where
humans could go sort of in the short
term this idea of being a multi-planetary
colonizing
you know species shout out to my boy
Elon
having space travel you know
and hopefully developing some sort of space travel
that allows us to go faster in the speed
of light I mean I don't know if that's actually going to
happen or if it's practical but that
you know without that we are kind of trapped
exactly where we are right now in space
so hopefully we'll find something out that allows
us to do that
you know warps and whatnot in Star Trek
so I mean to me and like look at the
ideas of the people of the world
of Star Trek you know there's like the Klingons
who have their civilization there's the Romulans
there's all those guys but the Federation itself
is like the United States and it was made as a
metaphor for the United States it's a
conglomerate of different
allied races of different aliens
and within the Federation
every planet has autonomy over
itself kind of self-governance
and within those states within those
systems like on earth right now
everyone still can just run their shit however
they please the thing that has changed
about civilization in Star Trek
is that want has been eliminated
it is a post-scarcity civilization
so what that means is
if you wake up if you're born on earth
in Starfleet they call it paradise now
it's just a paradise because you're born
of your parents you know you have your
teenage drugs or whatever when you become an adult
and you say oh you know what I want to open
my passion life be a painter
I want to be a painter and devote myself to that
you have infinite resources with which
to make that happen you will not be hungry
you will be able to do this
I mean there's probably limitations on space and stuff
but basically you have everything at your disposal
to pursue whatever kind of life
you want so right now imagine
what would life be like in like the inner city of
Chicago for example which is you know
gang violence all this terrible things are happening
if all of a sudden just everyone
had everything that like they no longer
had to fight for money because there's just
everyone's got food what would there even
what need would there even be for crime
in a civilization like that if you just have what you want
like the only thing at that point is like power
and influence which is real
which is a real thing you have to account for
sociopathy yeah and that kind of stuff
too but like we can address those issues
but the main one is an economic
lever that's been pulled just anything
you want you now can get
for the most part
and with the advance or with the development
of these things called food materializers
I'm forgetting the word but like for example
with that you can just push a button
it makes food out of it it combines
subatomic particles that just exist around
us all the time it assembles
the food let's move away from
Star Trek lore to how it applies
to actual what we're talking about here
wait wait let me give you some deep
on the subject of lore here's some PCP
lore for you some true facts
almost every single episode that I've
been on like in recent
months like clockwork around
the 55 minute mark when Nate will start
ranting about something that I don't think I'm going to have a
response to so I'll just get
up and go to the bathroom and don't say anything
and I do it every show at almost the
exact same time like
55 minutes that's when Nate goes like
bam hardcore off the deep end
and I'm like checking out
we have no way to wrangle him he's
like a fucking bull like
yeah I feel like
there's not much that
we can talk about because you're
the thing with the reason this is like
a tell me why I'm wrong it's not
it's well I mean there's this thing
okay it's not about
what Star Trek
is and why you want it it's the
fact that when it comes up in
a podcast discussion it doesn't make
any sense that's not true
that is bullshit it makes perfect sense
like when it sometimes makes
sense but it's like
you just don't want to hear it
I don't think makes sense is
the right phrase for it
I think it's more that it's weird that he
brings it up in every context
that like there's my world view
god damn it's a found no one else has
to do that with their world view
I don't have to bring up that I'm like
I don't have to bring up like that
everything I do is gonzo and all my
values are revolve around gonzo
like every time I do a podcast
you know oh here we go all right you fucking
cunt this is what you were building up to wasn't it
no what no I said nothing wrong
hashtag Nate did nothing wrong
what the fuck this is bullshit
when this is what I thought this podcast
was supposed to be that's I thought this was
the people versus the last
time the last time we recorded
this podcast yes like hot off
the the the the heels
of you being weird with
utilitarianism recently and
we talked about it in that
I remember we talked about it I don't know
what it was that we talked about and I can't
think of any examples but it's just
the that's the reason it became a meme
and that's the reason it is now a topic
yeah explaining what your world view is
like you know you
want you want the star fleet
to exist it you know
it makes sense I don't really know what
we can tell what we can say about it
beyond I think it's it's because like
it's because Nate Nate wants
wants star fleet to happen you want
you want you what you what you want
is from my understanding
is what you want is you want to better
humanity right humanity has this grand
destiny this grand like
well I mean I think that we
we might we might if we
work at it right that's what you want
you have this vision is
but I I don't mind
your vision I'm perfectly okay
with you having your word utilitarianism
it's just it's funny and it was
vision-shaming me right now
because you bring it up in topics
and situations that seem
weird which is why it's called weird
it's weird you're taking you're taking
minute small compact issues that we
talk about on the PCP and tying them
tangentially into this like whole fate
of humankind in the future and I think
that's where the weird it's alarming
the words what does like what's the
the future of humanity
we're doing like the animals podcast
and it's like so do we think animals
come with us into space when we all leave
earth like that's where the discussion
is going to go you're asking about
the morality of how we treat animals
which is perfect like how do we treat animals
I don't know that's relevant
I think that you're always arguing how do we treat
animals now but how do we treat
animals in zero gravity
well okay here's something that a
DeVu used to give me a lot of shit for
whenever we had like political arguments
which is that I always argue from an idealistic
perspective which means like
whatever I want the world like if we're
going to move the world in the direction that I
think is perfect here's the things we should
do and DeVu would always be like yeah but
the world is not moving in that direction
we need to worry about the issues right now
and like how we deal with them in the moment
and so I do think it's funny that
like I sometimes feel as though
you view every issue from the
perspective of like how will we
feel about this when Starfleet begins
as opposed to like how do we feel about it
right now you know you know
that's I don't even disagree with that
to some degree I would argue that I'm a very
pragmatic person but when
these things come up like yes
well for example um like
I understand the ideas of
movements let's say like like black lives matter
for example or feminism or any
those don't exist in space
they do that right now
I hope not because I hope by then we don't need
them to exist but like here's
like that's the thing this sort of like
identitarianism I think is relevant to this
because like any individual
issue of this kind like
I think we'll no longer matter
if we address the larger issues of
like individualism like if our
core principle as a civilization is
like individualism then it's a complete
waste of time to
focus on like pushing
for you know like quotas
in stuff that may or may not be founded
on science and you know like
women quotas at Google or any of this kind of
shit like what I want to do
is focus on the topics that will really
matter long term and I fully admit
I am less invested in short term ones
that is true that is true
it's just funny
it's just funny how like if a podcast on the
procrastinators goes long enough it will
turn into a discussion about
Starfleet and how all of what
we have been talking about will affect
like the heart of the issue
the kingdom part to me that makes perfect sense
it makes sense to me too
because like I used to have
a gimmick in my writing when I was younger
that like every time I wanted to explain something
I would start from like the beginning of the universe
like I always be like oh the big bang
happened and therefore
eventually this led to humans and because we developed
in this way like this is how we evolved
this is why we
say I'm sorry to each other you know like
okay so
I get coming from that perspective that's why
I like that that happens on the PCP
like but on the other hand
it does kind of make a lot of episodes end up
with Amy where we kind of go down the same road
and like the answer to what
we're going to do when Starfleet happens is often
the same and
I also want to say that
we can call it weird
utilitarianism but Nate is just any
Star Trek next generation fan
because they all talk like this
like if you listen to Mike's The Closet from Red Letter
Media or Neil X
like all these guys who are into TNG
all they do is talk about Starfleet and
what we can do to get there and shit
we're enlightened, we fucking figured it out
you're welcome for our wisdom
the wisdom of watching a television show
the wisdom of watching a children's cartoon
yeah basically
you're all in line by milk
no it's incredible
you're all in line Tom
you're not wrong
hey you know MLP
MLK
Junior
social importance
hey how come there's an MLK
there's no MLP
wait do you think that we're going to
have our whole new enlightenment
when MLP TNG comes back
and we have the pony version
of Captain Picard to Twilight Sparkles
Captain Perk
that's way too easy to imagine
like if the current MLP FAM
is like the original Star Trek
like I could totally imagine them rebooting it
with a next generation
like in a year or two
the next season is the last one
and they're rebooting people were pissed
no way about fucking time
that's all I guess
it has been a decade I think
8 years
alright alright
I think we've discussed what you want
out of weird child feminism
let's discuss like what we gained
around earlier because I think that's
I don't know are we out of things to say about that particularly
I mean you can
go on you can move on to it at the top
what do you want
to get us to Starfleet
what do you want to do
that's the thing people accuse me
people accuse me as well
of being idealistic when it comes to this
but like I really
that's like getting mad at a philosopher
for arguing about philosophy
and like having a focus on philosophy
because like yeah like you can get mad
that I keep going
back to the same thing but I really
approached the world
with these thoughts just you know you can ask my fucking
girlfriend how I go on these like retarded
tangents about like fill out like
why the way I'm doing or addressing
I mean it's because of a philosophical reason like Nate
shut the fuck up I don't care just buy the coffee
I don't care right now
about like the fact that like they might have used like
immoral means to mine the coffee beans
that are going to mine from the earth
coffee you know deep in the chocolate man
let me tell you I made it
very clear when I was buying
an engagement ring that I was like
you know these are all like at the cost
of human suffering right like yeah
diamonds are you know
I mean I'll buy you the diamond because
I don't want to look like a cheapskate but
yeah you know just let you know as long as you
know like a lot of black people had died
to get this on your we're participating in some
fuck like every iPhone every
smartphone is made with minerals that come
from some fucked up situations everybody
so it's good to think about
these things I think this is a real thing
if we're ever just interesting like ha ha
where you want to press do you care about
the suffering of people in like
countries I mean if so then yeah you should
try to be as I don't really
I try to be like mildly conscious
about conscientious about certain
things but it really depends on like
do I want it like
yeah with cigarettes I quit
cigarettes for a while after
John Oliver episode where he was
breaking down just like how fucking evil
the cigarette corporations are they like
Hock this shit two-year-olds in India
and stuff like that and yeah I was
like man that's really bad behavior and I had
a pack of camel cigarettes and that was one of the companies that he
called out of time and I just threw it in the trash
and I was like fuck smoking I'm gonna roll
my own tobacco
quickly realized that like if you
his own well if you the thing is
you go and like buy a pack of tobacco
they're all branded like you just
are buying like camel tobacco
to roll your own cigarettes with unless
well the profit margins lower so you're
doing your part you know so at some
point I was just like okay
like I don't want to support this
corporation but I want cigarettes
and I don't want to have to grow and roll
my own and that's why we let these
corporations exist in the first place
is to rock that's right provide us with
the things that we can't you know farm
ourselves and like if I was
now don't be wrong I would encourage
if anybody could to try
to compete with these companies and sell
some homegrown tobacco and if it was in
my town I'd probably go for that instead
it probably be better you know probably be a
better product and I would encourage
people like shop local and
don't be mind
controlled by the giant
corporations like McDonald's
and fucking Walmart that
just create the same building a thousand
times so you get used to it so you're just like
oh this is what's normal this is what's
right you know I shouldn't go to
that store that looks a little run down
that's in my town even though it's like
locally owned and operated and the food is amazing
and it's been around for 20 years and everybody
like it looks dingy and Walmart's
right there you got to get out of that
mindset because like a lot of the your local
shit is better some of it's bad
some of it I've got a we've got a place
we go to called we call sketchmart
that will just sell you
expired food and
they deserve to probably
get in trouble wait it's actually called
sketchmart no we call it that
okay yeah but like well okay
is fucking everyone who works there looks like
they're in the mob and some of them are like open
guys and sometimes we hear conversations
like oh when did you get out of jail
while we're in there we're like what is
it feels like an Italian mafia
run a store and I wouldn't be surprised
so like just just going back a little bit
like I just want to point out that like
everyone in the world is a utilitarian
when it comes to their smartphone for example
because like there are there are conflict
minerals in your smartphone if you own
one and you definitely do
so you are supporting like
you know like I don't know like
African fucking
people getting fucked up in mines and shit
for rare minerals that we need from those places
in such an infinitesimal
and roundabout way that's hardly
you can't even register it as being
if you support well that's exactly
you are making a calculation that it is
of more value to you to
use this cell phone than it is suffering
for these people who are being taken advantage of
to produce this material you're making that
calculation whether you like it or not you're doing it
so as long as you're aware
I think the main reason to get away with it
is that most people are unaware
and nobody wants to be the one
who breaks the huge story that kills
your advertisers
I'm aware and we're all aware and we are
now guilty of you know
facilitating this and we should keep that in mind
I made a video about why
everyone on YouTube needs to like stop
talking about Netflix because of the fact that
like Netflix owns YouTube
right now like they can put out
whatever they want and everyone on YouTube is going to talk
about it and all the ads on my video
were for fucking Netflix
because Netflix buys out all the ads based on YouTube
I can't even the only way I could have controlled that
is to turn off the ad revenue
but that just means I'm not going to get any ad revenue off this video
yeah so fuck that right
you know how like
that the whole like
products have been
like the kids in Africa
have been killed to make an iPhone
and all that and you look
around at your white privileged life
and you're like well I mean
I guess I've killed hundreds of thousands of people
should I just kill myself
and end all of this suffering
or will it make
so much little difference that is basically
just like who cares
I mean the healthy way to think about it I guess would be
I've consumed all this shit
I've caused
I'm always thinking about like my footprint
on the world not like my carbon
footprint per se but like my
human death toll I guess
like how much of what I've consumed could have
like the excess that I've consumed
rather like not just what's kept me alive
but like all the excess consumption
all the excess stuff I've bought
how many people could have been helped with that
with that money or that food
but then I have to think well okay
whatever I owe the world
that's what I now have to pay forward
like I have to make stuff that's good enough
or I have to help enough people to like
make up for this
like the eight human lives that I've taken
with my YouTube channel
um
at least
618 years
of view time
at least eight human lives have been
spent watching my YouTube videos
that is eight people who have died
who have lived and died their entire lives
just watching my YouTube channel
that's an interesting way to think about it
I'm not sure I would exactly say it works out that way
like people might have just gotten more benefit out of your videos
or like I just want to say that like
yeah like nobody
none of you listening I'm sure
give a fucking shit
about like I don't know maybe there was
people in Ukraine today who got like killed by Russian soldiers
during the occupation of Ukraine that's happening
uh or you know the part of Ukraine
or whatever like do you care
no you definitely don't
and I like I don't know it's got
on shlooshed or whatever the fucking where it is
got absorbed
um so like
so you just get absorbed and nobody's talking about it
no no no it was one piece that had been
like contested between Ukraine and Russia
and it is currently under Russian control like they just took it
and actually the people there kind of wanted it
but not everybody did so it's
it's a complicated but you know aside from that
there's a ton of fucking crazy shit going on in the world
like what about
what about the fact that Saudi Arabia
uh you know like it executes gay people
uh it still is
absolute monarchy in 2018
yeah and it classifies
terrorism as terrorism
that's what it does if you're an atheist in Saudi Arabia
you are considered a terrorist for holding that belief
I don't think
the point I'm getting to here
the point I'm getting to is that the reason
that you don't care viewers
about any of this shit
at least you don't waste any time thinking about it
even though the injustices
are like incalculable
and need to be addressed with
are need to be addressed in like
we would think they need to be addressed
and people were not designed
to live in a global civilization
but we do now and we're aware
of all the fucked up shit that's happening around the world
but we're still tribal
that is like we care about the people
in our immediate vicinity about the shit we see
with our eyes we don't care about the 100,000
people that die that get reported on CNN
and that's because
this is human nature
and human nature is
immoral you cannot fall back on
it's just human nature that's just how we are
there are defects in the system
totally to be addressed
Nate I have a question for you then
and I'm not trying to put you in a gotcha
I'm just kind of curious
is that you're talking about Starfleet
and like you're putting all this value on the future
of humanity why are you so willing to pass
off the present of humanity
because I am a weak tribal human like everybody else
so you're just
you're hoping future people fix your problem
essentially
absolutely not I am aware of the problems that exist in the world
I think that we have to find ways
to address them and
I'm aware that we need magical future
technology to make Starfleet real
that we have no guarantee will ever exist
but we can get closer
by doing things like optimizing
the rate of
production and you know
I think that what Starfleet is
essentially trying to make a human tribe
like that's what the show is about
is that all of humans
even though we're not supposed to
be a global community
we're not genetically
disposed to it
but it would be possible if everyone understood each other
enough and there was no reason for them to fight
you know
so that's like the idea and then there's of course
they're still fighting though because it turns out there's other tribes
out there in the universe
even in Starfleet in Deep Space Nine
there's a big war against these guys called the Maki
they're just humans that settled
in this contested area
and the Kardashians this other alien race
like they're just like oh we're taking this back now
and the Maki
we're just like no like this is ours now
and so like those guys actually started a war
against the Federation and the Kardashians
so like yeah like obviously
these things still happen on like political
and issues in it
do they get fucking destroyed?
well they were really sneaky
they were really really sneaky but I think they still existed
by the end of that series
good old fashioned guerrilla warfare even in space
pretty much
like if they were presented
like not everyone has like a radar
like oh where are people dying right now
there's someone dying in Ukraine right now
well I feel sad now
if someone were to be alerted to like a news article
it wouldn't just be like a blanket
just like oh I don't care just look away now
people I think most people
most people in the comments most people listening
will probably feel a little bit bad about it
but there's just no
practical way that you can
that you can make sure that people
everywhere don't die
well I think it comes down to like a lot of people
like it's just like
everybody says you want to help people
you got to help yourself first
capitalism has done more good for the world
than any form of socialism or collectivism
like even if I said
right now like I want to make a difference
like I can't even keep my shit straight
you know like I'm in no position
to help anybody else because I can barely help myself
and I think the majority of people
have that problem
that is a burden that humankind
should take up
and people try it like it is
a choice here if we could give up
or we could try and we might break under the strain
of doing so and I'm not saying like we should
nanny state it up what we should do is
apply principles across the board
that we think will best facilitate us
to getting to whatever destiny we choose
starting now that's what
you know that's really what I think so it's about
finding the philosophy that makes the most
sense to advance and this is what
people argue all the time this is why we have political
arguments for these exact reasons
I personally think that
it would be best if we left it up to individuals
to flourish on their own and have less state
intervention and stuff and just let people do what
they want but and I'm willing to hear
arguments of all kinds and I do I listen
to political stuff all the time different people's
views on this stuff but I have come to
a conclusion and I think that it's a pretty good
one but I'm willing to evolve it at any
time and this is
not passing things off to the future like
if only we had replicators then
everything would be great so guys we need to make
replicators what are we doing not
investing in a replicator technology
I'm not saying that at all what I'm saying is
like let's continue
to encourage capitalism
because capitalism seems to get
results it's got issues that we should
work on but we should
like continue to champion that because I think
it's like the best way to go and then
yeah go on much you know they just
released a new version of a capital called
Anarcho Cavals I think we should upgrade to that
version so we can get the ball really
there's good things and bad things about it you know
but I've learned I've heard about it I
don't know I've heard about that game I think it's
pretty good that's pretty good
I've been watching the trailers I don't
know like talking about all this I don't
know whether I have
a worldview
like like it just
even like if I sat down sort of thought to
myself well what do I think
it would probably just be blank space
we're like I don't know
I think my views are contradictory to one another
most of the time and I think that the fact that I
am contradictory to myself
and the fact that I think multiple things
is my worldview because
I'm very against
not as a blanket just all the
time but I'm very against generally speaking
tribalism and them
like me versus you
well that's a worldview of a sort
of a sort yeah there's things I
feel
such as emotions that's a worldview of
a sort said Nate snickering
himself
you could say that it's kind of broad
but I don't care if you die
but like I'm thinking
about this and I'm realizing
right now why people
like labels of world they love
they can latch on to because if I
don't I would need to like
like look inside myself and think
about every single thing
to come up with like a what like I have
worldviews on all different types
of things
like I don't have like a blanket worldview
and if there was one that would like
approximate basically
the things I say I would ascribe
myself to that because it's easier than
trying to think of every single individual thing
see that's why
Tumblr culture like the fucking
gloom genders out there and shit you know
like people love
by the way gloom gender if I remember
correctly it was like this is a gender
it is like 50% female
25% like
fucking shadow from
like 50% it was Oscar
and cat it was part cat part
Oscar and mostly gloom as in
depression and sadness
this is the gender of this person
that was a legendary moment
I've never seen this before please
show it to me
I don't know if I could find it but like
me Ben and Nate we're on a way to
like 2014 or whatever and I was just
happened to stumble upon this thing and we
stopped at a rest station and I'm like guys
do you need a mental rest right now do you want to
reset your brain for a quick sec check this out
and we all had a good old chuckle
what a legend by the way I searched
gloom gender on Urban Dictionary it doesn't
even have a definition it's just not
I feel like that
I think gloom gender
was someone's weird utilitarianism
that's exactly what I was gonna say this sound
this is gonna sound a little bit hypocritical
this is gonna
sound a little hypocritical but like what I
these people continue to splinter down
but they take a thing like
gender and they splinter it down
into a little special identity
that they can latch on to and
weird utilitarianism
is actually a meme
that is not a real
thing it doesn't mean anything
I always thought that the gloom gender thing seemed like it was
um
not satirical per se but it's intended
to be kind of funny
the fact that it's like
12% oska is your
gender and 80% gloom
people have lost the plot
the whole tumblr was written
in this very like
childish dialogue that made it hard to
determine if it was sincere or not
I don't think that it's insincere
I just think that it's intentionally funny
like you can
is what we have here like a kid just like playing
with gender is that what's going on here
I think that's what's going on in that particular case
okay but I mean that's the kind of shit
that is literally the kind of shit I would
have done like when I was 14
it just is factually inaccurate
it deserves to be told that they're wrong
I think that's part of the point is that it's fact
like it's just kind of a fuck you
to anybody who says you can't be whatever you want
but you literally can't be
that's not real
no I'm fucking 80% gloom bitch
well it's not that it's not real
because sex and gender are considered
two different things by this
but saying that you're 12%
Oscar as your fucking
gender
doesn't make the point it's a deconstruction
of what gender is because then gender
doesn't really have a clear definition
like according to the
principles that these people are operating under
there's a
strong disconnect between the
concepts of sex and gender
your sex is what gender do I have your genders
how do I see myself sort of
and so I think if this person sees themselves
it's like well if gender
doesn't matter anyways if saying male female
whatever it doesn't actually mean anything
I might as well just make up my own
that communicates how I see myself
to other people
my always weird
okay thought to that
is like why even hijack the term gender
why don't you just like say this is my personality
it's just like postmodern art
you put it in a museum
postmodern art sucks
I have less than no time
to indulge people who want to tell me
and I think this podcast is postmodern art
well I can't be a part of it anymore
I have less
I have less than no time to indulge someone
who wants to tell me that their gender is a fictional
character I have no time for it
it's not worth it
it's a very young person's idea
of how to deconstruct and
subvert this idea
the problem is that serious people take this seriously
and they're like yeah I gotta respect their gender
I don't know if anybody takes
I mean I don't think
it's taking it seriously to say
I respect your decision to call yourself whatever
the fuck you want
it's not that I'm saying I respect your gender
I totally agree that you are
25% oska it's just call yourself whatever
you want what I'm objecting to is the idea
that I would ever have to validate
someone's opinion of themselves in any way
you're still in New York right
isn't like on the books right now there's 40 something
genders in New York and you could be fine
I'm not sure
what if you think you're fucking dope
and I think you're fucking shit
am I oppressing your world view
am I
I wouldn't say you're oppressing their
well okay
it's the same shit I'll say that you are
but it's not a bad thing
everyone's world view should be oppressed
because all of us are fucking wrong about everything
so we all deserve to be horribly
lambasted for our views
in fact realistically
as human beings
we don't even perceive the reality of our
universe we live in and we're probably wrong
about fucking everything
all math probably doesn't even
actually work in like the next
one dimension up none of it makes sense
I could go on a thing about that
then tell us go on your thing
I want to hear it
math works definitionally because we
created it and we
created the axioms that it works on
maybe did you mean like physics?
math is not a thing that we discovered
and it works within our own definitions
I feel like this entire podcast
has just been Tom, Nate, and Digi
talking endlessly and then
Hippo, me, and Ben just being disgruntled
but not really knowing how to express myself
I don't know
this was the intellectuals episode
you guys
I'm shifting it to disgruntled gender
right now
the way to solve that
for me is to bring up the
the previous
lost episode of
utilitarianism that we did record
and I posted my audio on Gibb and Take
you just play
both of those videos at the same time and I'll basically
have the same points
I just realized, Nate
you just gave me a great idea for the term
gender drifting
like if you need to
pull off 5 consecutive
hair point genders
while
blasting running in the 90s
you're like, oh shit, I gotta be like
I gotta be a man, a woman, a gloom
a fucking vile plume
and I gotta be a fucking
a ghost by the end of the night
and the prom is tomorrow
the only way to do it is gender
drifting
you just stop, you just take your foot off
the pedal of the gender
and you just like flow through the conversation
you know
it's funny that you take it that way
because I took it to be the opposite
gender drifting should be like a slower
version of gender fluid
where when you're gender fluid
there are instances where you're not
but when you're gender drifting
it's like a percentage based each time
you run into the same problem I ran into
last time I called something drifting
which is that you're thinking of it in terms of
like drifting along and I'm thinking of it in terms of
Tokyo Drift
hard core Mario Kart DS drifting
you're getting your acceleration
you're building up your charge so you can release that and just burst
forward to the speed
boost forward to the speed of
gender
in the first season of Initial D
there's this gigantic mountain that has five
consecutive hair point turns on it
and so like the whole show is about
how can you tackle this
five consecutive hair point turns and the only way to do it is drifting
is that the one with the Donkey Kong
barrel that shoots you to the top
yes
Mario Kart
that's how we're going to build Starfleet because
the only thing that travels faster than light is gender
we have to build gender
oh my god
for real though I do respect
transgender people
with non-traditional gender identities
that's cool man
I have no hatred in my heart
don't you think it's sad that we have to make that
addendum though
I feel like the reason
everybody has to say that is because he constantly
says that he doesn't care about them at all
because I don't care about any identities
god damn it I'm consistent here
and also for what it's worth there is like a strong
like culture on
YouTube of like conservative people
who do have a problem with trans
people so like I understand why people
are like wary why some
like for the PCP
has like a weirdly large trans audience
which is entirely my fault
it is interesting because I have a really large trans
audience but like
but I do think
that some of those people you know come
here and they're like uncomfortable at first
because they're like I don't know if these guys
would hang out with me if I was
there you know because they're afraid that
like we're going to treat them
I will hang out with you but I will laugh at the fact
that you call yourself gloom gender
I would love to hang out with that gloom gender
I would love to meet them and pick their brain
like the thing with
the PCP is that
we're really really edgy
a lot of the time
we have no problem
we're not the sort of people
who would disassociate with a type
of person because it's kind of funny
what they are to us
that makes me like them more
that they're funny
alright do we want to move to questions
or do we have more to say about weird utilitarianism
I feel like we've
run the gamut here
it has
closing points anyone
anyone on this thing
I don't know what happened
I want to talk briefly
about how have you
come to the point on your life
where you are
or at least you claim to be and I'm sure that you are
consistent in 100 spin of the facets in your life
where everyone can
every one of the choices in your life can be
whittled back to weird utilitarianism
or if it occasionally can't
it is an insane bias
I don't think it's a bias
what it is is a consistent application
of my current world views
that are absolutely subject to change
but that's what it is
it's just for the last, I don't know
maybe like three or four years
I have been like this really seems like the right approach
to me and I'm always on the lookout
for ways that I might be wrong
and in fact I'm hearing some critical
points like to utilitarianism
as a whole like you know there's always the ideas of
like you know when you put too much
like these guys were memeing about like
oh if you're a utilitarianism
you have to murder people and steal their organs
to save more lives, like that is ridiculous
it violates some foundational stuff
it doesn't make sense, totally bullshit point
but I really feel
I strive in all things
to be completely honest
and fair to all ideas
but I do have
opinions and I have experiences in my life
and I have arrived at a place
where I really think that like
utilitarianism has been shown to work
it really works well
but it needs some you know regulation
like the future presented in Star Trek
I think is a
good vision for where human beings should
like keep in mind as a star
as a distant star in our mind
to head towards and I think like
treating things in a utilitarian way
generally speaking is like
the most moral and
to do the most good for the world
and because of all these things like
there's a little silly label on that stuff
for my views of weird utilitarianism
two points on that
first of all what I meant was practically
like have you ever sat down and thought
like I need to change some opinions of mine
or have you warped your philosophy
to set your own personal opinions
and then second of all
if you like you keep
like in a way that like this is like a far off thing
for Starfleet which probably is
but then like
then certainly it shouldn't take up this much
time of the fucking podcast if it's such a far off
distant like pie in the sky thing
um okay to your first point
I am
subject every single day to
examination of my ideas
I mean obviously everyone gets attached
to their world view to some degree I do not
feel I am overly attached to my world view
on on these economic ideas
in some ways like my
like my atheism I am
very very convinced that
I am right on that but I could be corrected
I could absolutely be correct if there was evidence to the contrary
but none is forthcoming
but to your other point of is it a
utilitarian idea to bring up
weird utilitarianism so much in the podcast
are we producing the most wealth for the world
in doing so is that the most useful use of time
I don't know we just
have to react to market forces and let them
dictate whether or not it's the right way to go
um and that's it
I think that I bring it up
when it is occurs to me
when when something comes occurs to me
that's that resonates with my world
view on this stuff I bring it up
because that's just what this
podcast is it's a it's a train of
thought well yeah I
hope that now that we have made
this big uh dump
info on your world view
it will it will happen less often
cannot promise that but
I hope that if it comes up
we can just say I'll just go watch
episode 99 and then skip
skip you you you edit a lot of these episodes
so every time he goes on a weird utilitarianism
and just cut it out just be like
and now go to PCP episode
99 to understand what the fuck the
15 minutes are you saving three hours
of your life instead of doing that instead
of doing that please edit this entire podcast
into that section of that podcast
and play it in its entirety that would be
ever see seven-hour episodes that's the
PCP but every time Nate opens his mouth
we play the entire weird
utilitarianism exactly
exactly someone's gonna do that
and they're gonna be the hero of time
complete with complete with the 40
minutes of not talking about which
every time Nate says right while
someone else is talking
like every time he goes oh right right
you have to also put the entire
podcast
excellent I think I am always right
yeah
guys I think that we're good
we're good on that
let's do it mother fuckers
let's get into some goddamn questions
oh I like this one
from the procrastinators
patreon questions lounge
pledge one dollar at least you can get
this exclusive club secret club
that you can't tell anyone about or you'll be banned
we have
from cappy what is the human
body lacking a built-in gun
I
immediately thought tentacles
like okay
I don't feel I have enough dicks
I feel one is
not enough women have more than one
whole and lots of
like play like okay the reason
tentacle porn is so great is that it's just
like it wraps all around her and fills all the
holes right sure like and I want to be
able to do that I want to be able to wrap
around and fill everything all at once
and not have to like move around and do all that
other shit I just want to be like a monster that
just I'm just too lazy to bank guys like
I don't know what to tell you I don't want to move
I just want to be able to do it you've taken
this wholesome Christian podcast and do it
you
just said
do you do you think
a fucking tentacles should all come
from like your groin area like there's
just an already come from everywhere groin
wait are you
are you asking sorry I wasn't paying attention
because of a fucking famous gay porn
actor just died
Billy Harrison yeah from
all those fucking what's it called
all those Japanese
yeah that guy
wait he died he died he died in a car
crash yesterday I think
no it's true
I have no idea who you're talking about
Billy Harrington I think is his name
I was saying this to my friends he died
100% it's like he was like
I don't know 40 something and he just died in a
car crash that's fucking
I feel legitimately
saddened though I can't believe
he's dead how could I
reserve this news on the fucking PC
probably the person I love that guy
probably the saddest death
of a gay porn star the world will ever
experience besides when you died
did you
anybody else got anything they think the human
oh hey but what were you asking me about the tentacles
before I got distracted by the
it was saying like would they all come
from the groin area or would they be like
all over your body I would
like a forehead dick oh man
I don't know like I would always assume
that like I maybe said watch too much spider
man the tentacles come from like your back
yeah that's not that's a good one
if it's coming I mean I would just prefer to
be like a blob monster made of tentacles
you know like or like a tank a lot of
type creature that can be a raid
did you how much homestuck
fan porn have you seen not much
have you are you aware
of the tenta bulge
no
what oh no
oh is that the that's the that's the homestuck
dicks right that's the troll dick yeah
imagine like a
giant as I'm sure you're doing
but
but the clitoris is a tentacle
oh
and it's all slimy and
and the and the slime colors
based off your of your blood color
of course it's not supposed to be tentacles
that are like a foot long
there's no canon like a troll
dick but yeah that's what the fan
fan them is
the tentacle is like a foot long
because they don't reproduce that way
just for it's just for pleasure
they're built for pleasure not for speed
the the trolls
um built for need
hey can I can I read a let me read a question
wait you gotta answer the fucking
we're missing about
150 extra pounds of lean
body mass just out of the gate
we're missing where you just want us to
be gorillas
that body mass has to come from somewhere
and it's gonna come from our brands and it's
gonna come from our ability to last without constantly
have you have you guys seen that picture of that
that like creature that was
a human being this is what a human being would have to look like
to survive a car crash
that's great that's what we're missing
we're missing a lot of that stuff
look it up right now if you haven't seen that
put it in the show notes
because I'm not looking up right now but I want to see it later
I think what we're missing is
a hand like directly in the center
of our back humans are so
front focused it's fucking disgusting
there's no back representation
in our body and our body mass
we need some sort of limb on our back
so we can better defend ourselves from back stabs
as you all know those are an instant kill
and it takes 12 seconds to respawn
it'd be like a leg
and you can kick people like a donkey
for anybody who might know this
this is him how did we used to sleep
how did humans sleep before beds
like you would just gather around a fire
and then take turns I guess
you get a bunch of leaves and break
and grubbly grubs and you just huddle up
did you lay on your back
on the ground or just like
I don't know
or whoever posted this
what do the breasts add
is surviving the car crash
so you can nurse yourself back to health
with supple milk drinking
oh my god this is like a whole thing
there's like
why is this
I thought this was going to be like a funny scene
human beings would have to be built like
to survive a car crash is the idea
yeah but why the weird nipples
it was originally developed
by a car crash
thing
they published that and it went viral on facebook
and I think there has since been like
further
is it like deliberately disgusting
to prove a point or something
we almost
made it a whole podcast without looking at images
to piss off people
thanks to me
thanks to me everyone
praise me for that
but just in concept it's just this disgusting
like bulbous creature
a lot of padding around the brain obviously
with these big ass thick feet
he looks like the juggernaut but if he had
under his helmet
was shaped like his helmet
basically
anybody else got answers for that question
I have a couple answers actually
I think first of all a tale of some sort
to help with balance because I'm horribly clumsy
yeah
no it's like
we're missing a lot of fur and cat ears
I want to be a neckochon that's what we're missing
I'm missing the neckochon appeal
I realized a great one
but our eyes need to be large
did you would you not want to have real life cat girls
I mean come on
then shut the fuck up
I think we're missing file conversion
in our biological body
it takes too long for me to convert files
I need a body
I'm literally about to say that we need a USB port
like that's a good one
you charged my fucking phone
transhumanism watch that episode
no another thing is
I was just recently found out that the
we only have like 10% of our
or 10 or 20% of our
the cells in our eyes are good for like acute vision
the rest are like really shitty
and if all of the cells were like
the stuff that we could use like acute vision with
our brain would have to be like three times its size
to accommodate all the visual information
so bigger brain or if we could do
like the fucking andolites
and anamorphes have like the high stocks
that can go look behind you
so you can look in multiple directions at the same time
I was gonna say
I wish we could see a greater range of the electromagnetic spectrum
we're so limited
it's pathetic
we can't even sense microwaves
let alone radio waves
do I want to sense microwaves all the fucking time
like I used a microwave
do I want to sense it
do I want to fucking feel my body
like she just sees them
they'd be like a different color
and you'd be like oh neat I see there's some microwaves
I don't want to see more of the spectrum
because I don't want to see in other
qualities how bad my art is
the limited spectrum I see is bad
you know what spectrum I'd love to be able to see
is the autism spectrum
before I talk to somebody
so clever
imagine if like those color codes
that they had it
bad enough about myself I don't need another measure
let me take a step back to explain
we're missing the UI to just our vision
imagine it's fucking Vincent from the Vapors
and every time you walk up to someone you can like
turn to the rank of autism
well remember at BronyCon
they had these for the audience
who wasn't there which is everyone I guess
they had these fucking badges
where you could
they had like a three color system
where it's like if you have green that means
you can talk to me if you have yellow
or hesitate to talk to me
and red means don't talk to me at all
and it was like it was literally a system
for like the unbelievably
large autism population of BronyCon
to you know
communicate whether they wanted to be spoken to or not
or for you to communicate
that to them not that they fucking
work because like
course not but because you just got a glomp
sometimes you just got a glomp my dude
I think we all just need
to glomp every now and again
get out of our system
we build up our glomp receptors
we just need to let them burst
point being I'd love to be able to see those colors on everybody
point being I'd love to glomp
I think we should have big
porphy cheeks like this fish right here
because
it looks funny and you could
you could inhale bigger
and you could exhale
and big face
if anybody whose DTF
should have like a
like a graphic over there
you know the quest markers and
MMOs like the little exclamation point
anybody who's like wants to fuck
should have an exclamation point above their head
oh wait wait wait
that's like
what if when you want
you want to go at it
your skin changes like to be
extremely red and then people like oh I know
I'm sick of accidentally
raping all these women who didn't actually want it
I feel as though a lot of people
like the reason that they're afraid
this is definitely true for me like part of why
I could never cold approach girls is like
I don't know if they want to be spoken to
a lot of people see you have to do it to
find out at all yeah I just want to
so everybody knows here's the right way to
assume they don't want to talk to you once you
know that then your arm you know it's the worst
but still do it anyway
of course yeah anyway that's right
Ben you
you are the creator of science
you've made physics
what would we have to do to the human body
to make it be able to see more colors
I mean
more cones and rods yeah we just have to
have like a greater like
I don't know what would have to change in our cones
and rods they just have to be
you know set up to be sensitive
to more frequencies
just shove a little
bumblebee in there and then he'll
work it out for you yeah
you put bumblebees in your eyes
and they will see different colors
and then they will like type up on the little
computer like okay there's
we might as well get that
and then that gets sent to the brain
what part of the eyeball do you think tastes the best
enough for this shit let's move on to the next question
I want the answer to the eyeball that's probably the best
here's a question from
no there's a question from roo guy
he says have you ever pushed yourself to a point
where you opened your inner strength
what
I feel as though I've done that like almost
every time I do anything physical
because I never believe I can do as much as I can
I climbed the tallest mountain
in Virginia one time with my friends and family
they were all like
workout guys who were swollen like ready
I showed up you know
overweight in pajamas like
but I climbed the fucking mountain
so you know it took
like there's times
in school
years like where we do like
a run round
several blocks for like 10 minutes
it's like a long run
and
when you get to the end or like near the end
you're like I'm gonna die but you gotta
look cool so you have to sprint at the end
and you always kill yourself but
inner strength
you can't do it until you see
the glory that is sprinting over the end
when I was like
when I was like a little kid
I used to wrestle like every single day of my life
with my friends
with my family
with my estranged relatives
I used to wrestle with fucking everyone
and every time I was like pinned to the ground
by you know a woman in her 40s
or my best friend who was 2 years younger than me
I would always think like this is it
this is where I fucking die in this playtime of wrestle
but then I would like channel
my chi and I would like close
my eyes and I would start breathing heavily
and I would overcome the hate
and he would remember that he's a 7 foot 5
juggernaut and this would destroy them
and I would fucking obliterate them completely
and I would like scream
as I like as I come up from my
pin using all of my body force
in the world and all of the g-force
I've been saving up by burning up against my wall
I've been saving my g-force
I can fucking release it all in one punch
and obliterate them even though he said to not punch each other
it was just a wrestling match
I would do it anyway
what a champion
that reminds me of the thing I used to do with my brothers
where like we would get like all the soft
things in the house like all the cushions
all the pillows
all the duvets all the blankets
and then one person
usually me because I was the oldest
would get covered by all of the stuff
and I'd have to like scratch my way out
like punch my way out and they would lay on me
and then I would be like
oh I have no strength left
but like right at the end
I burst forth
and I'm alive now
and now it's your turn to be fucking suffocated until you're dead
dude dude
and what
well here finish your thing
no no I'm done
my friend who used to wrestle with
fucking rocky I'm talking about him
we sports fucking shitter
like literally
we were like the RPG
I was like all attack and all
but I was like super slow
and he was lying on attack but he was super fast
that was literally it
and the way it would work is like once I got him in a pin
on him it would be over
that would be the end of the game
so he had to find ways
to like get jabs at me without
me being able to like grab him because if I grabbed him
I could get into like an infinite combo
and I would like instantly win the set
so like he would have to fucking
evade through me
but I always fucking got him because he was a fucking bitch
fuck you rocky
I found inner strength
while I was working on Mia Maffova
I definitely physically
that was an extremely demanding
time and I
just persevered
there was no one moment of just like
you know unlocking something
but just the physical fortitude required
to get it done despite you know
I found inner strength working
on Brunswick I worked on it like
most of every day all day
for like most days I worked
for most of the day for like an entire month
and I was like the most
focused I've ever been on finishing a thing
it's similar to this
two for one
which are both related to one another
for the past couple of days before I came here
I've been a bit of a boss now hello
before I came here I was
working on finishing up the vape rent for Ben
and I realized two things
like most of the day was just me doing the vape rent
which was great and it felt good to just
like do work all day but I also just
realized that like I can
just stay up forever
like I don't get tired
like I get there's like a dip
in between like I spent
like in the last month in February I had
like eight or nine
twenty per hour days
and it like wasn't hard at all
like there would be a dip where I'd normally go to bed
that would be kind of hard but after I get over that
it's just like really fucking easy
I would get like
kind of tired around
ten p.m. and then I would be fine again
until maybe like four
a.m. or five a.m.
yeah exactly exactly been exactly
like well over
thirty hours for me to like
if there's a crunch time that makes sense
but you got to sleep some time
so it doesn't seem like you're really just making me
miss like being young
because that's what I did when I was your age
was just like not sleep
as much as possible like not even so much
because it was like super easy to do
but just like to me it was
the coolest thing to do is like if you can stay up for
forty eight hours that's the best possible
like night because it just means that you did
shit non-stop for two days without
like any interruption and especially
for me as a kid when I valued
weekends so strongly because like
my cousin would come over and we watch anime
all night and it's like if you pass out you don't
get to watch as much anime you know
if you pass out you don't get to see every show that comes
out it'll swim so you got to be up all night
you know and
yeah so I got used to doing that
but it's a lot harder now
I think one of the best
one of the best times that I
pushed myself physically
and Digi you were there too
the first burning con we hung out
we didn't sleep for like three days straight
yeah well
because we couldn't and because we didn't want to
in that order
yeah that was definitely
almost every con I've been
to I've pushed myself physically because it's just
up until recently
up until the last couple cons I went to
because of the fact that I decided
first of all I'm an adult now
most of the shit at this con is not really exciting
to me I'm not going to try to be anywhere in a
timely fashion I'm going to make sure I get my fucking sleep
in my shower because
you know when I was younger it was like no
sleep no shower ever
always by day three I was like
my voice doesn't work anymore and I look like
shit and I feel like shit I always want to get the
hell out of Baltimore like usually leave
like by noon on
Sunday because I'm like I don't want to fucking be here
anymore but you know
again now that I'm older it's harder to
actually do that and also there's less
incentive because like
I feel like every year sleep
means more to me you know
I understand that's a terrifying development
we really need to get on
I still hate sleep it's still my
enemy I would still never do it
oh I still hate anime hey but
if you guys want to listen to us
talk about sleep for a bunch of hours
you can go look at the procrastination bonus
episode in song yeah five dollars
I thought you were gonna
recommend the sleep podcast
but we want the money one though
please yeah the money
also it's more recent
from fucking where
oh from Zeno
grade in the questions bar
if you could completely get away
with one crime what would it be robbing a bank
that has all the money in the world
um then if you buy anything
they'll catch um rape next question
state enforced homosexuality
that would be well that wouldn't
be a crime oh shit you're right
never mind yeah if I could get
away with one I got master
plan if I could get away with one crime
I would illegally pass legislation to make
all crime legal
oh okay
okay illegally yeah but
again that we're like dealing with like law here
like why not just do that legal
why not legally pass the law to make all crime legal
because
they would say that sounds hard
okay whatever
my crime would
I would somehow make it that
I have
like amnesty from everything
so then I can just do whatever I want
I can like cook the books
so anything I do from that point forward
I can't there's no
legal ramifications for my actions
all you guys are playing fucking like wishing for three more wishes
yeah we are
I will
say my opinion on the internet
oh god
but I'm so fucking scared
that's too far
I'll get away with it though that's the best deal of all time
I would take a giant robot
and destroy a city with it
why
because you get to fucking destroy
a city in a fucking robot
it'd be awesome
I used to have a fantasy I used to think about this all the time
when I was younger that if I ever became like a billionaire
this was my plan
I was gonna own a private island
and I was gonna own like some kind of
mech or giant like some kind of destructive
suit of something I could pilot
and
then just like have a city
built on this island
that I can destroy and then I just keep
rebuilding and destroying the city whenever I feel like it
yeah okay
fantasy of mine as a kid
you just gotta play wretch and plank too
did this tie into the fact that you were a god
um no I was even
probably younger than that when I had this fantasy
before you're a god baby
you were a malevolent billionaire
before I was a whole god
back when I was only a half god
alright here's another question
from OneSpar
he says hey guys it's OneSpar
the one man
who's sparingly on time for questions
what are your go-to excuses
for being late
ah
Ben, you have the floor
um
I just didn't care enough to show up on time
yeah there you go
works every time
they burst into applause
when he trots that one out
yeah I'm owning it
I'm making it look good
my go-to excuse will be
finding something that I was actually doing
that sounds like you're an asshole for making me feel bad about it
that's good
that's pretty much what it comes down to
like I find something that was outside
my control and I project
the excuse onto that
dude there was just so much traffic
what could I do
my friend Matt really got this down to a science
because Matt
Matt Pat
yeah we had
he's a whole game theory about it
he uh
he'd constantly be late for work
and so his way around it
was that if he realized he was going to be late for work
he'd be like I'm just going to be later for work
and he would go get donuts for everybody
and then he'd bring them in
like why are you late? I got everybody donuts
everybody was happy and he never got in trouble
that's a reasonable idea
there should be a podcast
with talking Tom and Matt Pat
can you imagine the disparagey there
the richest man in the world
and the poorest man in the world
there's some knowledge
that can be gleaned from that
that would be good I would love that
that would be literally the most opposite to
tracking the entire thing
the most happy positive man who's ever lived
you know it's just a theory but he claims it's true
and then versus Tom that would be
that would be something
make it happen guys patreon.com
slash me
patreon.com
slash Tom versus Matt Pat
we should get Matt Pat on the PC
it's a good idea
does anyone else find Matt Pat kind of like
kind of adorable
no
yo what's up guys sorry I haven't made a video in a long time
it's the Tom bomb here time for another
game excuse
I don't know he's so like
like he's kind of like overly sincere
but it's kind of in a way like
he doesn't see anything I don't know
I think he's just like
I think he's very authentic
yeah he's really authentic and he's like he's
I don't know it's like
he's so authentic that I search into optimization
sometimes I'm kind of embarrassed for him
but then I'm like oh but
but you know he's having fun with it
I just get
I stop at the embarrassed thing
I love game theories on
five nights of fun
I actually really like them
I do they're so much better than
the game it's the presentation
I just like it's just not for
it's a taste issue it's a taste issue and I just
can't sit do how much fucking how
repetitive his videos are
they could each be half the length
we're fucking you guys we're fucking everything
up we can't say all this shit because we need to
get him on the show okay stop
I apologize Matt Pat I meant none of it
I remember Matt Pat responsible for one of
the greatest childhood tragedies that ever
occurred my entire life what was that
I was using the family computer like in
just like the living room
like like and like the way my house was
positioned like if my mom were to come out of
her bedroom and like look in the living room she could
instantly see it was on my screen and one day
in like in like the the dead of night
aka 10 p.m. she walked
out from her bedroom and saw me
looking at Matt Pat like
like the boobs episode of Game Thea
where he called his video game characters boobs
nooo
and she flew off the handle
how old are you at this point one year old
yeah I was like eleven
boobs involved because that dude puts boobs
in like all his shit
what is it definitely a boobie man
hey
would you like to enter a lightning round of
Radcon 3 hype questions
before we wrap up the podcast
I think that's only fair because the next episode
the 100th episode will be in Radcon
that's right let's do it
alright so here's all the questions we got about
Radcon we got AJ
Shoup who asks who's gonna smell
the worst at the end of Radcon 3
digi
wait wait
hold the fuck
do you
okay
when Ben saint moved out of my house
the room had to be pressure washed
for days before it stopped smelling like
his body odor
my dad literally pressure washed the room twice
like all the walls
I smell great what are you talking about
everything had to be cleaned multiple times
before it's less lost the scent
Ben saint
well there you go
the answer is Ben
but Ben will smell no worse
at the beginning of Radcon than the end
also we will all smell
fucking terrible except for Nate
who will probably wake up at 5 in the morning
and shower at 8
we're in a fucking mansion
we have showers
we're good man
it's a big house
if you want to understand what Radcon 3 will be like
just take the late great
Billy Harrison's
fucking locker room scene
or Harrington
fucking the locker room scene but instead of
there being lockers we are locked inside
and the smell permeates the entire building
that's what it's like
well here's an answer that much he can just say
my name immediately and be correct about
Mr. Tangelo asks
who will get the drunkest at Radcon 3
digi
who else really seriously drinks out of this group
yeah I don't think so
not as much drunk on life
cause that would be me ladies and gentlemen
the question is though in the environment
of Radcon who could be motivated
to drink more perhaps it would begin
I was gonna say hippos the only person
who I could see out drinking me
but it would only be once
it wouldn't be that he drank more overall
it would be that he might at one point get drunker
guys do you want to play staves
Tom could get that too
that's when you
duct tape your beer cans to each other
and the more you drink the longer your wizard staff gets
and whoever has the longest wizard staff
wins the night
oh that's good yes
actually no cause I don't want to die
I will agree before I know what that is
I just told you what it is
I don't get it
you drink your new beer
and you duct tape it to the top of the old beer cans
oh those things
I thought you were talking about duct taping it
to the other person and having to drink it
I do that with orange juice
I want to play the corona
I definitely want to play that beer stacking thing
I've never done that before
but I want to
here's what I have done though
you get two big cans of beers
and you duct tape them to your hands
and you're not allowed to
remove them until you finish
beers duct tape your cans
we did this with a game of
we combined this with a game of 20 questions
every time you got a question wrong
you had to take a drink
because we wanted to be able to use our hands
we just stood there
me and the guy I was doing this with
facing each other and questioning each other
until one of us finished our beers enough
to get our hands free
yeah it's a fun game
I don't mind the idea of
a big drunk party time
because I will not drink
unless pressure
I will have a beer
and I won't go like I'm gonna get drunk
unless that's the point
in my life I have drunk the beers
and the alcohol laws after this point
but recently I like never drink
just because it's not around
and it's just a waste of time
it's the biggest waste of time
here's a really important question
the other day I went out
and we were at dinner
it was like a mango teeny
and I drank it and I felt
swasted after one martini
it was
it hit me
I'm gonna go for alcohol and it's pure
swarm and eat pure pieces of wheat
I'm not the middle man
I have a very important question
if I were to bring weed to Radcon
would anyone smoke with me
I would not
nobody would do it
because I have smoked weed on a number of occasions
and I have never enjoyed the sensation
well that's unfortunate
I have never smoked a weed
so I might try one
I might try it once
but I hate the smell
I know I hate the smell
I mean I don't care if you bring it
for the record
it is totally decriminalized in Massachusetts
so this would not be like a legal
it's all good
but I would have to
drive it
give me that kush
I mean don't be high the whole time
let's talk more about this little shit later
one final
last Radcon related question
from agent MM
to those in a relationship
what does your significant other think of PCP or Radcon
and would they join in
I'll answer first
my fiance
is a huge fan of the PCP
excited about Radcon
to see what's going to come out of it
she has no interest in being a part of the PCP
whatsoever
because the chemistry
of this group is like very
I mean first of all
anyone new joining the PCP
is a terrible fucking idea
no one should ever join this group again
the standards have elevated
astronomically
the point of this
is that it's a long standing group of friends
for years
I mean I could see if say
we all move to Boston and we all
have our girlfriends with us and everybody becomes
best pals I could see them
getting involved in some way in the future
if we're doing
like
if you're doing
do you not want to have anyone around to do set designs
to turn on your cameras to switch your batteries
to manage your data
to do all the things that I pay a secretary
who happens to
be my fiance to do
but what happens if you break up
you got to hire a new guy
but
when you put your relationship in the middle of your business
you're asking for trouble
I have no interest
I think that you're going to run into the same trouble
I actually have a hard opinion on this
and I think if you want to use them as a camera man
I think that's perfectly fine
as a camera man
if you just want to have them be a tech guy
you fucking need those people around
it's like with red letter media
if you actually see a picture
of the whole group
there are other people in red letter media who never show up on camera
like if you look at a picture of all of them
there's people who just run the cameras and stuff
I believe there is a woman
in red letter media
she's never in any of the videos
the one who's been around in a couple episodes back in the day
maybe it might be her
because it was that girl who was in the documentary
I don't know if she's considered a part of the group
or if she was tangentially related
but I'm pretty sure there's someone
there's at least one member of the group
who I don't think ever shows up in videos
well hey, hey, I'll tell you this
I have legitimate nightmares
about girlfriends getting involved in the PCP
legitimate nightmares
like do you actually have them at night
it's the worst case scenario
life has gone to hell because girlfriends
have been involved in PCP work
it is the worst case scenario to me
and let's just say I'm not interested
that's how I feel about it
if May was ever involved
for any reason in the future
it would not be a girlfriend involved
because we're already engaged
same difference
the fact that this even comes up
is a terrible thing for me
this is the wrong questions to be asking
this is the last question that anybody had
and I want to know what everyone's girlfriends think
of the fucking PCP and Radcon
if they would be involved
if you think so
briska thinks you're old
fucking game
I don't know
my girlfriend loves the PCP
is a fan
is a fan of everybody in it
patrons most of us
she has said that she has no interest
in PCP
though to be fair
after knowing how I felt about it
so perhaps her opinion was colored
she has made no bones bad
that she doesn't want
to be involved
it's not her thing
I think that generally
are spouses
of whatever kind
recognize that
this group has already
anything that tampers with it is already a problem
everything we've tried to do
has already been a problem
so let's not make it any worse
Michelle was just telling me about
the super best friends cast
apparently
people were coming them and asking them questions
we see your girlfriends occasionally
why don't you get them involved
the guys were like they're not in the show
the girls themselves
this is coming from Michelle
it's a third party thing
they said themselves
that's their thing
they are doing their thing over there
it has nothing to do with us
if we want to do something with them
we can do another project
if there is going to be a gigantic
hey it's all the PCPs
and their dates and they're doing a fun
whatever like that's fine
but they don't need to be a part of the PCP
you know
I feel like
you organized this
what the hell are you groaning about
well that was just a friendship initiative
except it was all over twitter
it was super publicized
it was used as a PCP group activity
that groan was on relation to you
that groan was in relation to me moving my stomach around
okay sure
not going down hard on the anti-girlfriend side
did you I think it's a funny joke to say
haha I think it's fair for me to say
I am staunchly on the anti-girlfriend side
very very much so
in terms of them getting involved in the PCP
I would agree I'm not a fan of
anyone new being involved in the PCP
but you know what this is kind of an interesting question
I've thought about this more as time's gone on
I think something like what did you did with corrupting your kids
like what he did was he's just
making new content
for people who choose to be involved with it
that way you're not putting any pressure
on like old people to just like
get with the times into your role
the college fund was the same thing
okay there you go
college fund was definitely part of what inspired it
but because it was just
it was pretty immediate it was like Ben moved in
and they immediately had a new channel
that had totally different content
we had been making it like before I moved in
it just didn't get done until after I moved in
I mean it's always important
to keep in mind like if you're an internet content creator
you only have so much time to work on stuff
so like if your workflow if you start
devoting like all your time to this side project
obviously that's something to like watch out for
but it depends on if like at the same time though
I think there's a lot of potential
in like for instance corrupting your kids
for that to end up being a flagship channel
well that's perfectly fine
but you have to recognize that
at the moment you know that's not bringing home
the bacon like a main channel digital video
that's all that's all be practical that's all I'm saying
um yeah
interesting question I've certainly thought about that
quite a bit you know as I have a gf now
and whatnot it's hard not to especially
when you're living with your fucking
significant other and they're like witnessing
all they're sitting there all up in it
they're all up in it like listening
to the pcp right now
while you're performing it
and are every time you record
so sometimes it's weird but other times
it's fine
and incidentally uh like
just the other day with the the new we Agua
had like a thing filmed
uh by Michelle who was just around
as I filmed my little Hillary section
I had a music video that was filmed by
May yesterday the uh fucking
there you go there you go it was great
uh was it that uh uh well okay it wasn't
but I'm just making a joke uh weed hit spot
would you fucking I'm a thang but the weed hit spot
no it's very important everyone knows that it's not
me and me dude the first thing we thought
was like wow did you wow he really did it
he really did it this time anybody doesn't know
there's literally porn
in my youtube in my
uh music video for this song
which didn't look nearly as apparent
when I was editing it like okay
because my monitor is so dark
I thought that this was like really obscured
and like uh May couldn't even see
she was like oh I don't see anything
yeah no when you look at it on a phone it's like
way fucking obvious that it's porn
and I was just like well I posted porn on youtube
now hopefully I don't get my channel
deleted on the subject of that song
me and Michelle roasted it endlessly
for quite a while but but once we just
it really got into our heads
and now we just say to each other weed hit the spot
dude that song is intended to be
here's how you need to listen to it
if you're in the grocery store
and you realize that you are picking up
hot dogs but you didn't get buns
and you need to go back to get buns
and you're gonna haul ass across the whole grocery store
weed hit the spot when you're fucking
in my thang baby weed
I want to time my gigantic
strides as I leap across
the fucking grocery store
it's replaced sabotage by Beastie Boys
as my run across the grocery store
mental song because I used to make a playlist
for that I should make a fucking playlist
I get most of my cardio done at the grocery store
because I forgot hot dog buns
and I've only got hot dogs
and have to move back for more
my diet consists of only hot dogs
no buns cause I keep forgetting
and I can too I don't have enough
music to make it across the store
it takes me like 4 minutes and the strong is like
we need this playlist
what's your hot dog bun song
Detachable Penis
by whoever made that song
I know what you're talking about
guys let's just give a meme shout out
to our boys on the twitter
just to placate them temporarily
okay here we go
djphilis asks how do I get a GF
what's your meme answer for this question
become famous
become rich and famous in hands
rich indoor famous
and get a fucking snapchat
that advice is terrible
just talk to girls
Ben what the fuck
oh wait is this a meme
oh shit you said meme answer
oh I ruined it
I'm cutting this out
now all these guys are gonna actually get GFs
no no god I wasn't paying attention
rape
you did it Ben
you solved it
great save that's a good meme
I would say log on to RuneScape
2007 edition
and just farm for gold until you have enough to buy
the best places
Grand Exchange and Varric
sometimes Faldor but you know
don't go to Lumbridge though
that's where all the them
what do you call it
thoughts
oh excellent
good thank you everyone
I think it's time we shut it down
it's time to power off
this utilitarianism machine we've got here
thank god
we've made so much progress for humanity here today
really gonna be useful
we've really made a difference
whining about topics we don't really understand
on this podcast that no one watches
yeah you're not wrong
that weed has really hit the spot
at this point
that's how I feel
alright we're done
hey patreon.com
bonus episodes
insomnia episodes out there's a total of 12
bonus episodes you just split 5 dollars
you get them all 1 dollar you get into our patreon chat
it's a fun time we're hanging out all the time
we got some merch clicking the links
in the description everything's up on google play
and iTunes for the podcast
tom here's handling that and that's
everything
magical episode of radcon 3
fucking week look out for fucking rad content
it's gonna be on everybody's channels
you're gonna wanna look for the radcon 3 playlist
which I think already exists and has one video
like the um the thing
like I would watch that playlist that's where
everything's going to be
if you could subscribe to a playlist you should but you can't so
watch everybody's channel radcon 3
coming in a week it's kind of it's gonna roll out
over time but there will definitely be some during the con
so let's keep let's prepare ourselves
for that new journey
thanks everybody we'll see you next time
bye
why do we do that
I don't know
you