It's me, it's Future Munchy. It was kind of right here. We have Future Hippocrit, any PCP.
It's me.
Okay, we just want to stress real quick here. We're scared baby cowards. We are good people.
We are the good guys in this situation. We represent wholesome intellectual values,
and we have nothing against people. If you look bad or are ugly, we don't hate you.
Yeah, the things that go on in this podcast will make you cry. It doesn't matter who you are.
So the thoughts and feelings and words said by me and Munchy do not reflect the thoughts,
feelings of me and Munchy. We were joking. It was a robot. It was someone else.
Yeah, it was a clone. It was an evil twin. It was a badass. He was a really cool guy,
and he upstayed just in every way. I believe everything that I said, but I said it in a mean
way, probably. I felt like it was unfair. It's just a trigger warning. Just don't kill me.
Just please don't kill me. I don't want to die. I like you, all of you good guys, all of you
men and women, and all the other ones shout out to those guys. We're on your side. I am the biggest
liberal cuck of anyone to ever exist. Martin Luther King Jr., shit, he's gone. Get rid of him. Bye.
It's me now. I'm on your side just a little bit of intellectual curiosity. Just putting words
out there. Just a little bit of an idea. I'm going to die. I will be dead. I will be dead.
Anyway, enjoy the podcast. Just remember, everyone else is evil, not us. That's why we're doing this.
We are the good guys. Everyone else is bad guys. If everyone's transphobic, I just throw it on
everyone else. We aren't bad. We promise. Don't kill me. Hello, everyone, and welcome to another
episode of the Procrastinators podcast. I am the best guy ever, and this is the PCP. We're a bunch
of internet people get together. We all make stuff here, and here is us talking about it. We're joined
today by Ben St.
Hippocrite is here. Hippocrite, everyone. Sorry, I was saluting the flag of whatever that song was.
What song is that? I don't know. I guess it's probably Scottish, because in my head it's not
played on the bagpipes. It does sound like bagpipes. Okay, Munchy, where's Tiny Hats?
I just got back from Papua New Guinea. I've been spending my entire, the past 10 years with a
native tribe, and they've taught me wisdoms you wouldn't even able to be comprehending with your
dumbass white boy brain. They taught me secrets such as don't look at the sun and also play in dirt.
It's fun. So I'm here to spread these invaluable truths with the population. Did all their lessons
rhyme like that? Oh, they talk exclusively in rhymes. Dr. Seuss is a black aboriginal.
And we're also joined by Tom Oliver. Yeah.
Okay, well, speaking of African places that we just came back from, which is the topic of this
video, I just came back from Nejair. Nejair, that's how I think it's pronounced. Funnily enough,
I actually wrote down for a school test. Am I in trouble now? I wrote down for a school test,
I wrote down nigger instead of Niger on an actual test that I put in. What are they going to do?
What are they going to do? No, they gave me full credit that there's actually no penalty.
They gave you a gold star. You actually get bonus credit, bonus. You're right. Okay. Can I tell my
n-word story? No, no, because we don't know what this topic is. We're lost in the fucking dark.
We need to be guided by African countries that we're not allowed to go to, right? We need a
dictionary of non-rule descent to guide us. Here's what we got. Here's what we got for you,
everybody. The topic for today is things you're not allowed to say. Things kind of like George
Carlin's old skit about the seven words you're not allowed to say on television. It's that sort
of thing. It's a little bit broader here. And it's kind of a broad topic. There's no
one urban dictionary definition that really fits this. I tried searching for a bad word.
That's what I found. There was a definition here. The first one's just a list of swears not supposed
to say, ass fuck bitch, skank slut, asshole, ass wipe, cunt, hoe, whore, bitch, ass, damn. But then
there's a little definition. That was weak. It was very weak. And here's the longer definition.
Words that are said in order to make someone or something look or feel bad, cursing is a type
of bad word usage. Okay. That's like, okay, but we're going broader than just bad words here.
There's no definition here. There's no bad ideas of which Nate is full of.
Of course. But Ben wanted to tell his n-word story. What do you got for us, Ben?
Well, it's, I might have told it before, but I'll tell it again here. When I was like,
I was probably in like fourth grade or something. And remember how our parents used to,
used to cruelly and inhumanely leave us at like an after school program while they were at work?
Oh, of course. That's unfortunate. Yeah, yeah.
Stephen Mullenew would be very upset if he heard this. He would be very upset.
And I remember I had, I had a black friend when I was like in elementary school.
This just gets worse and worse. Yeah, yeah, the problems all started here.
And we had like a little electronic, like digital dictionary. It was like a little like toy thing
where you could look up words in this like little database. And he was like, oh, look up,
look up this word. And he types in n-i-g-e-r. And I'm like, what, and it's like,
doesn't find the word. And I'm like, oh, what's that? And he's like, oh, I guess it doesn't
know the word, but it's a bad word for black people. And I was like, oh, okay. And that's how
I learned about that word. Did you try putting in n-i-g-g-e-r or anything?
I don't, I think he, yeah, I think he then was like, oh, wait, wait, wait. And then he tried it
with two Gs. And it also did not, it also did not return anything because of course it fucking
wouldn't because this was like a fucking toy kids dictionary on a fucking little micro computer.
Dude, I didn't see the guy who programmed that in. Like, I wonder, they got to learn somehow.
Just type that. You know, it's a funny thing though, us like adults policing what kids
shouldn't, shouldn't know as like just, just words that exist. Even it's like, I guess specifically
with like racial slurs, it's like we don't, the concept of the racial slur comes with a lot of
baggage that we just don't want children to have. Like we don't want kids to like differentiate
between racial groups because not a lot of good comes from doing so. So I guess I understand
like not wanting kids to hear that. Like when it comes to words like fuck and shit,
I don't really see the need to keep kids from hearing words like that. Yeah, I don't know. I
never have. I think the kids who do find out about it are then like they use it as currency to become
popular. That's true. And I guess if it wasn't those words, it would be something else.
As have I right now. Kids like hiding things from other kids to be like stupid and stuff.
Here's my Jordan Peterson archetypal moment. Okay, that functions just like the story of
Adam and Eve, the forbidden fruit of knowledge, was actually just some sick ass swear words that
Eve found out from Satan himself. And Adam was like, yo, share that with me, bro. And then when
big daddy God found out, he was super pissed and he grounded them for life, which inspired the show
grounded for life. It was a big daddy God is actually the name of my first.
We found out that that that that Eve had taken by the apple. He wouldn't give them
Cummys anymore for like an entire big ordeal, which is why Adam had to make his own Cummys,
which inspired original sin. Oh my God, we figured it out.
Well, guys. Okay, so what do we this is like the concept of like forbidden knowledge almost
like bad words, like words themselves are simply tools like anything, right? Yes. So where
why do we get this whole idea? Yeah, what do you got? Well, I was gonna say, I have I have a thing
that you're not allowed to say, say like, especially on the internet, especially on a like a red
pill podcast like this. The idea that social justice isn't all that bad. And in fact, some of
them have a point. I have a point where I literally support not freedom of speech in this
scenario. Like like self policing. So well, self policing is very different from the kind of social
justice mob justice, you know, like, like social justice warriors are like stupid people who I
think are very funny. But social justice as like a thing is like, it's not a bad idea. Like,
yeah, I mean, I mean, I mean, on the on the face of it, it sounds pretty good, right?
Okay, I guess you're getting there with like, is that really like the racial slur thing? Or
like how we expect? It's just that the idea that I was bringing forth a thing that you're not allowed
to say on the internet. Okay, okay, that's your point. But like, you know, it's because like,
like the idea of like, policing it is stupid, like making sure like quotas and stuff. No,
you don't need that. But the idea that we got a character, should we have a woman character or
a black character or like a gay character? Like, yeah, yeah, sure. No, not if you want me to read
the correct answer is who cares? Yeah, like, why not? Why not be okay with it? I mean,
the yeah, yeah, it's just it's not really just so much as like the idea of normalizing it is like
completely harmless. Okay, here's here's my here's my quote unquote counter argument, which
isn't really a counter argument. But kind of is the reason I have no when when when these things
happen, there's like the social justice injections of like minorities and other shit into media.
My problem is never the fact that there's more more minority representation. It's always,
I know the reasoning behind it now because they pulled the curtain out way right and that's what
pisses me off because like, I know this wasn't a natural artistic development in the production
of this thing. Someone checked off some boxes. There's nothing wrong with making a character
a non white cis male. But in fact, in fact, I think it's it's nice. I do I like I like
the idea of representation in principle. But when it comes when it comes off as contrived,
then you've you've done I feel like you've done more damage. Yeah, or even if it's not contrived
when it comes off as like it when you feel that like what you're seeing there is not so much
an artistic, you know, expression as so much of like, like, micromanaging of a creator's desire,
like that's that just speaks to like, okay, well, we just want to create a specific example
that I'm going to talk about because I like I went to Germany recently and I was pitching a show.
This was a show I hadn't made. But yeah, a lot of the show characters, you know, are gay or like,
you know, race, many races in this, you know, but like, it's a fantasy. Is that hard to animate,
Gibb? The fact that there's so many races, like that everyone's running all the time.
You know what I'm saying, dude. Okay, yeah. But like, I had no problem because like the way
that the story was written, because I was brought on to write with the story, I didn't write it,
obviously, about the the race and the gender, you know, stuff like it's not a show about
a woman being the main character. It's a show about, you know, cool shit. And a woman just
happens to be the main character. And I made my pitch and stuff. And then I the the person who
came directly after me was the complete wrong, like the opposite of like, you know, they had the
same sort of thing, just all that shit was like the focus. But yeah, they literally like their
whole pitch was like, every single social justice were a buzzword. And nothing about what the story
was or why we should give a shit about this show. Well, that's just that's exactly because it was
basically the same thing on the surface level. But nobody gave a shit, especially me. I was like,
why would you tell me about this show? This is this was the person that was pitching their show
after you. Yeah. Okay. And it was just about, I really wanted to show that, you know, women can
be main characters and represented blacks. I'm just I didn't even mention that in mine because
it was important. And it just annoyed me because that's my point basically entirely is when you
do this for the wrong reasons, like you're you're the integrity of the product isn't there because
there is none. Yeah, like what I would really want to see is like that person to like finish their
show, like at like display it to the public. And then like, if that show like tanks, because nobody
gives a shit about it, because all it does is like, that's kind of what you see with like this,
like right now, Marvel is pushing a lot of diversity in their comics and shit. And yeah,
exactly. And like the comic industry is doing very badly. People are turned off by it in a big
way. And they're being forced to reevaluate their position here. So it's like, the marketplace
does not support just ideological brow beating, you know, through through their comics, you know,
with something like the comics, changing the gender or the race of characters people know
and love is not the way to do it. You make new characters that are just good and that have
We can't have that. We can't make original IPs anymore. The market saturated with them. And we
got to play it safe. Oh, well, we've had too many ideas in the past. We've farmed we've farmed the
future. We've we've stripped mind the future of ideas. And now we've pulled them all out. And
there's no more new ones to be had. We've just got to work with what we've got.
Unfortunate. This was a problem, I guess I had back in the good old days of the Wild West of
Gamergate, where it was hard for me to like, it's hard for me to tell all the time when a like
when a black person is a black person for corporate or for artistic reasons, you know,
that's the issue right there. There's obvious, you know, there's obvious examples of, you know,
a black person never corporate, you know, gain of which I can name exactly zero, but I'm sure
they exist because everyone says that they do. But I it I a lot of time I would imagine if it's
a small like, you know, indie game as it was with a lot of Gamergate people, you know, talking
points, but there's probably just done because they like black people. And I think it's hard to,
you know, I would say that like as a general statement, I would say like, like, I like,
yeah, like Ben said, I like black people, I like seeing them in video games every so often,
pretty good. So I think as a Blake and statement, I want to encourage that. And I, and I don't,
I'm skeptical of the like, how often is there really a border mean of all right, we need like a
couple more black people here, like, I just need it. It's probably more often than any of us would
like to admit like the BBC is on record saying they have like quotas that they have to meet now
and they post jobs all the time where they're like, white people can't apply like straight up.
Like this is my majority job. I want to I want to take I want to take sorry, you can you can go.
No, no, no, it's fine. Okay, well, well, I think this is a good time for me to stake my claim
because I want to put this out there. So everyone knows where I stand on this issue. Oh, no. There
is a well, it's not a big deal. It's stupid. You're all going to be disappointed. There is a
there is a Mr. B tongue video that was controversial and it's about like the one about diversity
and the one about I got I forget what it's called but it's the one where he talks about
CD project and how like their games are different because they come from like a Polish culture,
which is not like a well represented culture and stuff and how like more diversity leads to like
fresher ideas and stuff. And I fucking love that video. And anyone that disagrees with it is stupid.
And well, wait, was he was he making a point that like the buzzwords for the discussion of that was
that there are too many white people in this Polish game. But was he I forget what he was
saying about that was he agreeing that like there should be black people in the winter? No,
no, well, he said that he said that maybe there should be. But was he saying that because the
game was all about Polish like folklore and stuff. And yeah, because CD project is Polish and Polish
people don't make that many games, like that's why CD projects games feel a little different.
And that's what he likes about it. And I think that's great. And I was already kind of I was
already kind of blue pilled. But then I watched that Mr. B tongue video. And then I was fully then
I took my big I took a big vat of blue pills and blue gel capsules and crack them all open to a
swimming pool and just die right now. That's not even really a blue pill point. It's not.
Well, and why did I get in so many bitter arguments about people are the stupidest people
ever. So I'm not I'm not I'm not talking about people on YouTube. I'm talking about people in
this very PCP that we're in people in the PCP fought me to the nail on that issue. Well, then
I could not everybody in this podcast who isn't me is retarded and because that point is totally
fine because it's not I love it. It's not contradictory to anything we were just talking
about because that has nothing to do that. That's the reason that that game feels refreshing isn't
necessarily because it was Polish people's because it was Polish folklore. It was a concept that it
was a it was a well of inspiration that hasn't been tapped on a lot. And while those the Polish
people are in a better position to take those ideas because they're familiar with them, anybody
could have just really said, hey, look at Poland, let's take some ideas from there. And they could
have no I don't think would have been would have been his nuance and authentic, probably not,
but it still would have been different. So it's an intellectual thing that's being brought to the
table. It's ideas that make it refreshing. And yeah, but I think that I think that the thing
here, the idea is that like, people from different backgrounds bring new perspectives and ideas to
things. So like, okay, yeah, I think it's would be over. I think it's oversimplifying to say that,
okay, if we're talking about games, like, yeah, the games industry, it's a lot of white males and
stuff. But like, that's not, I don't know. There's lots of different types of white male. Yeah,
the term is so wide. I think I think it's not important to point out the specifics of like,
oh, it's white cis males that are doing it. That's not the point is that it's a monoculture and
it attracts people of like a like minded culture and societal values and outlooks and similar
and similar ideas and sensibilities. And is it like an exclusive thing that kind of pushes people
away that I do not share that same minds, including, you know, minorities and women and things like
that. So I, yeah, basically, I just really like the idea of inclusive inclusiveness and that
fucking because he says that Mr. Butung says in that video that like, we're not doing them a favor
by letting them make video games. It's more like we're, we're allowing them to do us a favor by
like, bringing their fresh perspective. No one's allowing anybody to do a goddamn favor. They made
their own studio and made their own fucking video games. They built it up themselves. They didn't
need anybody. The end result is that you get something that you wouldn't have otherwise.
And it's not positive for you. And I'm not here. I'm not saying, I'm not talking about like a
conspiracy to keep women out of video games or anything. It's the, like the problem,
how the fuck did I get on fucking women in video games? And this is a fucking game or game.
I'll finish the point and then we can move on. The problem is that the culture is hostile to
outsiders. And that's what key, that's what it's not a hard kind of what cultures are.
Cultures inherently have barriers around them. Well, people who are not within the culture.
Yeah. Well, there's, there's, there's degrees. I don't want to get into this. I'm just gonna
let that point go. Let me just say one point about this. And is that ironically, Ben,
Poland is by far the most red-pilled MGTOW country in Europe by far. That's neither here nor there.
It's still illustrative of the point. But then again, so we're like, so it's like, I mean,
they can't hold a candle to like Islamic country is like fucking, you know, Iran and shit. They're
pretty. But what about Sharia law, Ben? What about Sharia law? What about Sharia law?
Dude, that's a game about Sharia law. But it's just, it's red-pilled as fuck. And yet it's like
loved by like feminists and SJWs. Okay, but whatever. Let's get off this shit. I want to ask for
clarification on that, but I'm scared to. I was very confused that entire time because I didn't
know what side anyone was on. But here's the thing. Imagine like there's like a game where,
or a story where the law is humanity was underground for fucking millions of years.
And they do this. And you're talking about homeless. Yeah. And imagine, imagine that's a show. And
then, you know, everybody's like real white and pasty because they've never had any son. And then
there's a black guy in there for like, for like diversity. I hate stuff like that. It doesn't
make any sense with the law of the world. So get out of here, blackie.
Alternate timeline where Nate watched her in the gamba. You couldn't get past the first episode
because they were all black in this timeline. Oh, that's my, that's, that's real life.
Let me, let me touch on this thing that I sometimes feel weird about. It's that like, okay.
Okay. Okay. Pretty much all my, all in my comics and stuff. Everyone's white, more or less. And
it's not that like, it's not like a deliberate like, everyone's got to be white. It's just.
That's gonna take about a hour in my brain. But we grew up, we grew up around almost exclusively
white people. There was so little diversity. The truth is that we are not racist for just
like that sort of being our vision of like a default human being. There's nothing wrong.
Yeah. Like it's just, it's just the way that it should be. I don't have a lot of like,
I never had a lot of like black friends or anything. And yeah, the way that I see it,
if I made a character and made them black, I would have two options. I could either treat them and
characterize them exactly as I would anyone else, which would be the same way as a white person.
And that would be fine and everything. Or I could like, unless the story is like about
their race, but then it'd be like, well, how would I even fucking write about that? I have no,
I have no footing in that culture. No, I have nothing meaningful to say. This is a whole
interesting point with social justice and how they push this forced diversity shit is that
they, it's a damned if you do, damned if you don't, because if you, if you're just doing white
people and stuff, and that's your characters, they'll be like, well, you need to have diversity.
And then it's like, okay, I guess I'll add a black person. Then it's like, well, this is an
inauthentic representation of X, whatever representation we want in this show. So basically
what it's really about is it's they, what they're, they're saying we need more representation,
but at the end of the day, what they really want, they want you to get the fuck out of their whitey.
That's, that's the end goal. Look, here's what I'm thinking about this. It's like, okay, I,
let's say I make a comic. I, it's all white. They're like, okay, put a black guy in. Okay,
put a black guy in there. Like, okay, you did this all wrong. Like, why is he talking white?
And I'm like, oh, let me fix that. So I make him sound black or something. They're like, well,
why are you being so fucking racist right now? Exactly. Why isn't he acting just like the white
people you fucking racist? Like, is, is race relevant or not? I don't know. Yeah. Take a,
take a side. The problem is, I say no, by the way, I say completely no. It's a complete social
construct. I think there's almost no value in it. And I'd rather just go away. For sure. If, yeah,
like, like, no matter what your race is, you're going to grow up acting like the people around
you. And to go back to a little bit of genetic stuff, to go back to a second to what Ben was
saying about Poland and stuff. The interesting thing is that like, well, the, the, the Poland
example works, like, when people push for diversity and stuff in like America, I kind of don't feel
as, as, as like it has the same thing, because we're, despite the fact that there's a bunch of
different races and sexual orientation stuff here, despite the very like surface level, like
different experiences, we're all growing up in the same culture. So our experiences aren't as
different as someone growing up in an entirely different country with an entire different set
of cultural experiences. So what, when you have something in an American setting, like that's
the whole thing. The reason America worked and now like is kind of falling apart as this whole
like race thing goes crazy is because America was built on a set of values and everybody
regardless who they were, shared those values. And that's why the whole thing works. So when
you start doing all this race shit, it falls apart. This little, this little race kerfuffle
we're involved in. This little race war we're about to start is right. Here's, here's, here's
one example of my intense red pilling. So here I go. I am actually angry about how much I have
to think about trans people, despite them being such a tiny percent of real people in real life.
You know what, I'm mad about that. I kind of am too. I agree. I agree. Why the fuck do I have to
think about trans people so much when I like never ever met one? 99% virtue signaling. Yeah, it
makes me mad. It makes me mad that a thing can be popular for no other reason than because it
references or is somehow relevant to trans people because trans issues are what are trendy on the
internet right now. Just in the fucking marketplace, they should have so little stake. And I get that
we don't want them to be fucking, you know, trampled or discriminated against. I'm with you on that.
Why the fuck do I have to think about your problems all the time? But I got my own problems.
I see a disproportionate with his wicked ideas. Yeah, phantom horn,
angry horse man. There he is. Insanely, Ben insanely transphobic saint. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Insanely. I've never met a more red pill man in my entire life than Vincent.
And you never will. Because if there is one, I'll kill them. Yeah, yeah, I just want to agree that
yeah, I feel like I hear a lot like a disproportionate amount of media is relevant to trans issues.
You know what I'm saying? I'd like to hear more about furry rights. At least they look funny.
I agree. At least they're cool. At least they work really hard. Because my mom grounds me when I say
fuck. It's really, it's really getting to me. My mom says I can't say nigger when I'm at the dinner
table. I want to talk about one time I saw, I don't remember why, but I was, oh, I think it was
when I was practicing for one of the races. You had to really try to get in that way. I was
practicing the black race. It was really going hard. I saw, I think I was looking at some speed
running records and I saw that a couple of records in I forget what game were held by a woman. And I
was like, oh, whoa, well, this is interesting. Like, it's just like a high tier pro speed running
female. Like, well, let's go check her out. Go to her YouTube channel. It's a trans. It's a trans
woman. It's a trans woman. Proving that even men are better women than women. That's what we've
learned here today. It's one of those ones who wears like a pink, fluffy, low-lead dress and like
big, like, big, like blue banana curls. Just does way over the top and does the like ultra,
ultra, like anime girly style of that version of being a woman. I would beseech any legitimate
trans person, I think would have no choice but to completely agree with my points. Like,
for what reason are your issues forced on the like such a huge amount of media relates to your
tiny little niche thing? I don't like why the glasses fetishists of the world, such as myself,
do not consume the massive amount of airwaves that like these other things do. And why is that?
It's because nobody gives a fuck about our problems. They are our own to deal with and no one should
ever care about them. And same should here. Same should here. I'll go ahead and say something
that you can't say. Please do. There's, all right, here's what I think. Here's what I think. If you
are of a mindset where you do not feel okay unless you are dressed, say, as a woman, if you're a
biological male, if your mindset is such that like if you're not dressed as a woman, you're like,
you're not okay. Dressing as a woman is not the solution to that because like the problem is way
deeper, you know. Uh-oh. Insanely transphobic. But it strikes again. And I want to say I'm not
saying that someone who wants to wear a dress shouldn't wear a dress. Not what I'm saying,
but I am saying that the solution is that it's not it's not it's not a solution to be like,
oh, well, I'm just going to wear a dress and everyone has to call me a woman or else I fucking
will be I'll just break down and cry. I'll just break down and cry if someone refers to me as a
man, you know. Since this is just what the podcast is now, I have something to say about the transgender
community. I think a lot of the time the way transgendered people like present the issues
are like are transphobic and like sexist. Yeah. Oh, oh my god. They're so they're so sexist. They're
so sexist. Oh, okay, okay, okay. The way my ideal society would work is Mulan because at the end
of Mulan Mulan has like gone through all these trials and tribulations trying to be a man trying
to act like what she thinks a man is to, you know, do all the shit written into a Disney movie,
but just bear with me. But at the end Mulan does cool things and she is a good person in a dress
and the thing about being a man or being a woman is that it doesn't actually matter. Like you can
be a masculine girl and wear a dress. You it just is a set of actions and ideals that you have like
like it's just super undefined and trying to like act like oh I'm going to be a man that doesn't mean
anything. That isn't actually anything. When they say that gender is performative
and then they're like okay well I'm going to put on a suit and like cut my hair short and like,
you know, take hormone pills so I'm growing a beard. Well this means I'm a man because I'm
performing as one. Well shit, aren't you fucking pigeonholing what men are like? Like not all men
have beards, not all men wear suits, not all men work out or drink beer or whatever. Well you don't
appropriate that culture. The only time it's okay to be like a classically beautiful woman
right now according to you know the current feminist ideology is when you are a trans woman
because then it's okay to adhere to the stereotype and you're not just you know feeding the patriarchy
by giving them what they want. Okay I know this is like an unfair blanket statement and I'm sure
that there are exceptions probably a lot of them but so but so many trans women their idea of what
being a woman is is this is this overblown fucking like china doll like hyper like hyper feminized
yeah and it's like that that's you that's the great thing to say it is no no it is you know what
is it's female blackface it's female fucking blackface is what it is and this isn't to say this
isn't to say that like if you're a man you can't wear a dress or if you're a woman you can't wear
a suit that's what I want no I want you to just wear what you want because it's what you like
if there's some guy who's like okay I just want to look like a woman because that's just what I'm
into I guess then of course but it's like what is there's no problem there I just don't like
when you're saying that all men or all women are a certain way that you try and perform as
like it's a fucking kabuki theater act. There's a real element there's a real element of like
imposing their worldview onto the language of others and demanding that the way that others
speak in a way that conforms to what they believe and it makes me mad okay well here's the thing
it's really makes me mad if we're we're gonna go down this rabbit hole like this is because we just
fucking are apparently this is the thing and I've always had a question about and I haven't been
able to get a good answer I've talked to a couple trans people about it and I never really get a
straight answer at least something I find satisfactory to to satisfy my kind of like cognitive
dissonance with this is that yeah we have this whole like kind of like blue-pilled you know leftist
ideology that talks about all these issues and that's where all these talking points really come
from. By the way Tom I just want to put it in here I am those blue-pilled person in the entire world.
I agree for sure of course. Okay okay. I I may I'm catching up to you much you one day I'll be as
blue-pilled as you are. I aspire to it. Well my point is that we we talk about like or they talk
about I guess I talk about I'm talking about now too about how gender is a social construct right
and there's no difference between men and women men and women are just as capable they're the same
thing it's all about a performance and then you're talking about trans people and how you can be a
man's brain trapped in a woman's body in vice versa and it's like these two statements you can't
have them at the same time right because if you if if gender is just a performance and your trans
you don't need any surgery you don't need anything to kind of correct anything you just start acting
as something else and so I know like a lot of this like social justice stuff I feel is
faces so much I guess pushback from people because they make everything needlessly more
complicated like that point like we've added like 10 billion genders like what we should have done
just like none of this matters there's just there's we shouldn't have any difference in gender there
should be no gender performance you like added you just subtracted instead of adding things
would have made it that point you blah sorry keep going that I'll go for it that that point you just
made about how gen the the performative gender thing it makes me so mad because it literally
means that tomboy's aren't women like they don't like if you if you act masculine then you're not a
woman because you're not performing the gender and holy fucking shit how fucking sexist and like
fucking and fucking like conformed to my world you because what you can you possibly feel like I
feel like acting like a man so I need I must be trans and it's like well okay but if you just feel
like acting like something just act like it like you don't have to make a huge fucking big deal out
I've had this like thought for like a while uh uh because like you know I like boobs
what if I what if I just what if I just had them what if I just got some grafted onto me and then
just stayed the same and say people would say uh so you were trans and I said no I just have boobs
now I just have boobs I just like them why are we getting there there was a chapter of a manga that
I forget the name of it's like miss so and so's uh nurse clinic and it's about monster girls the
main character is a is a Cyclops with massive tits and she is a nurse in a school full of monster
kids and that's cool yeah and one of the chapters is about like a dude who is obsessed with tits
and like in this world whenever a kid like goes through puberty they like develop their like
monster characteristic and they're all they're always different this particular guy who's like
obsessed with tits he himself turns like just into a woman like he just gets tits uh actually
I guess that's probably the only thing that happens I think other than that he's still
got a dick and stuff but he's just like you know what I like how your voice cracked when you said
dick I like how your voice I uh so the the the the ultimate point of the guy is just that like he
he just like because he just owns it like all the guys that he was like encouraging to like be
ledges and look at tits now he's just like well now I just have this so I will just like enjoy it
and be able to look upon myself as like a sexy tit having individual and so he starts dressing up
like a girl and just being that but he's like no like I am the manliest man in the world I just
have this awesome set of tits that I rock and it's fucking fantastic and uh I'm just gonna live
like this forever and it's great so he just even being able is able to appreciate like his own body
as a sexual object uh and it's great and I don't know I'd like that like the way that he just like
accepts what he is like he doesn't feel the need to like chop off his dick I gotta tell you this is
where I have some issues with this I just don't see the solution to any kind of psychological
discomfort to being cutting off body parts what that's just my other psychological come out with
some crazy pictographs nowadays yeah what other psychological condition is the solution that
you make the outside look like the inside like that's not done for anything else like yeah like
it like the solution if you like are depressed and and think you're ugly they don't tell you oh
well you will you better get some plastic surgery then so you can look the way you feel on the inside
well hey let me it's like fucking I get yourself a steam stored it stored let me push back on that
a little bit though but let's bet if there was a magical like wand you could wave to just make
these transformations instantly like would that be a different case um you know like if there was
no no no because I'm not saying that you shouldn't get surgery I'm just saying that like getting
surgery is one is one thing but like the problems that are making you sad are another yeah you know
well gender dysphoria is like an actual mental condition I'm not trying to underline it's been
redefined now it's been redefined it's no longer one it's being redefined and I think that's kind
of dangerous because like if if these people actually have a condition I think it should be treated
as a condition and not as a fad and I feel like it's devolving into well you know I'm sure these
people would say that it really should have never been like a disorder of any kind it should have
always been treated like again to talk more about this weird kind of like SJW hypocrisy isn't it
interesting that people wear depression and like you know the headbates and all these weird conditions
as a disorder as a badge of honor but then when it comes to being trans like it's not a disorder
that's offensive what is the line being drawn there even though I'm with everything said here
I just want to say that I haven't like actually seen any like headmates or like I haven't actually
seen any like absolutely crazy out there um trans people most of the ones I've seen have been like
pretty normal people so you know this is not a comment on trans people this is a comment on the
ideology that's pushing this agenda I think I think that goes without saying but just to say it again
just in general like this is I try not to argue with people I try to argue against ideas because
I feel like this is a philosophy discussion show this is not a listen to me you loser I have known
at least one crazy trans person who was fucking bizarre and she wore she wore goat horns everywhere
she went like giant goat and like a crown and like a crown of flowers is that weird
and um is this like a trans species thing or are you trying to be like yeah yeah she was like a
goat yeah she was a trans goat she talked all the time about getting like real horns transplanted
onto her head did she change changed her name to clover because that's a goat name oh the ultimate
furry the ultimate furry uh like but you know she was actually she she she was actually kind of a
nice guy most of the time so whatever hey hey I just want to state to go back like like like
the general ideas of things I don't know if it's gonna out me as like a beta cuck loser
but I don't know what these people mean when they say like I feel like a man like yeah I don't
know what that feels like that can't possibly mean anything yeah and even if it did how would
you fucking know I think I think what they mean is I feel like the social the societal um like
normative like generic like this is what everyone decides a man is I feel like that guys I feel
like a generic sitcom dad from the 1950s aka a man that like that's what I think a man is I feel
like that like one one time I was talking one time I was talking to a guy um well a trans woman
or trans girl whatever and they were and they were like well I just I feel like a woman in my head
and I was like well how do you know what a woman feels like and and like they they fucking cussed
me the fuck right out I respect your challenge there but on the other I do want to be like how
could we really understand what they feel like like I don't I don't care about how do they understand
like like there's more going on here there's more going on here because yeah they feel how they feel
but then they're translating it and they're saying well I feel like that I feel like that other group
of people and it's like okay do you know okay how do you know how what your feelings compared to
theirs fuck you god damn it get out of there I mean I have never um like seen like a crazy
trans person but on the topic I have like something it's still like a thing you can't really say
because it's kind of like uh insulting um but I feel like a lot of trans people people who call
themselves trans they're not trying hard enough with the gimmick they're not going far enough
things like they say oh I'm this different gender but they don't do anything about it
besides maybe changing the way they dress and sure they take with that like the whole pronoun
thing like all this special like you I don't know whether these people actually have the dysphoria
that others actually really do and they're just sort of along for the ride because trans is a thing
now and you can be a part of a group with it well like there's no well like there's no test right
like there's no there's no test that you can run to tell whether someone is really trans like all
that makes someone trans is just that they say they are which is fine and it like if we're all
agreed when when there's like actual like people who are like really suffering mentally and they
need help and then there's other people who are just sort of like uh yeah I feel like I feel like
wearing jeans I feel like wearing jeans and boots sometimes so I guess I'll be I guess I'll join
it right and and I'll guess I'll join this culture that like gives me a feeling like I'm a part of
something right because it's not just because it's not just about yourself it's about being a part
of a social it's totally about getting social currency yeah that's what all of this is about you
know that that's why it's all done it's like I want to be a part of this group I want to feel
validated I want to feel part of something bigger than myself they they and the trans community is
so welcoming that they will even accept Christian Weston Chandler as one of their own and and like
actually love him and respect him and be his fans even though he is the worst person in the world
and should be shot dead where he stands right now that's that's the final fucking straw for me
I that's how you know that this shit has gone too far on this on on any subject of this nature I
feel completely consistent in that I just I don't care about anyone who isn't useful to me that's
how I completely feel and man are these people not useful to me so I don't care about any of your
problems listeners any people in any of these subjugated communities your problems are your
own they have nothing to do with me and I hope they work out great for you but you know I just
don't care I just do you know where this does become your problem Nate you know how this does
become this is uh the the culture that surrounds these movements of ostracizing and destroying
anyone who disagrees with them that's where the book did you hear about what happened this guy
he was a teacher he's been a teacher for years um and he went up to these two girls who are working
on like they were working diligently in his class he was like oh nice job girls like you're doing
good and one of them's like how dare you misgender me and he got fired oh my god he got fired because
some little girl said decided she was a guy and the parents reported it to the head of the school
and he got fired I mean he should have known she was a guy because she was working hard
oh my god yeah she was she was really performing
you can't say that you can't say those words oh my god that was excellent
oh zing oh there we go that's what you were gonna do you stole my point and ran with it
I mean oh my god I never intended this discussion about trans stuff to like even begin I wanted to
talk about like the concept of how you're not allowed to say certain things which actually is
relevant to what we said but instead we've just spent the entire podcast saying things you're not
allowed to say which I don't like any of my notes whatsoever well we can we can just switch
a web back to what Tom's point we're gonna go into yeah uh where's point sorry go ahead man go
words I can't say uh what's what's to sheer sauce
what's the sheer sauce yeah this is a lunchy life hack right now it's it's what's the
shit like I've heard what's the shit I've heard I've heard what's I've heard what's the sheer and
I've heard what's the sheer like without war chester sauce is that a war chester here
well that war sauce sauce which is just Jew blood mixed with a gold
war chester shire I mean it it is in England and I assume I feel like it's Worcester like like
that's how you're supposed to there there actually is a Worcester Massachusetts as well is that where
is that where you live uh tower caramel yeah bent and ornate have you guys ever had people from
out of new england come into new england and try and pronounce the words and laugh at them because
like they're saying how they should be said and they're all weird because they're normal to me
yeah it's it's it's hilarious it's like war chester English spot just a thanks cube uh you're
well yeah fucking here's a munchie life hack and like like rest here's like a new munchie recipe
for you if you're out of a one sauce I'm gonna teach how to make munchie shaw's which is just
okay you mix ketchup and wishes your sauce together and it's like it's like tangier than
a wonder like it's basically the same but like this is the first episode of the new hit youtube
series munchin with munchie oh my god that's a good one that is banded right now trademarked
don't even that's that's gonna be the future that's coming up well hey that that that point that Tom
got to right at the end of that trans woman that that is okay so we could talk all day about specific
things you're not allowed to say but but what's what's interesting to me is the the consequences
of saying the things that you're not allowed to say yeah and specifically uh like yeah it's like
there it seems to me that the way it goes is you say something I don't know like anyone listens
to this podcast decides that something we said is particularly offensive to them or their community
and would then go time right and then they would go begin to cultivate within that we're gonna get
we're gonna get roasted we're gonna get roasted for this no no for this podcast this is like those
those guys who are those guys who are who are who are shitting on them they're gonna they're gonna
be back I have no doubt that we'll all be called very ignorant which I admit to I'm totally ignorant
around subject although I think that philosophically I have found I have ground to stand I just feel
like when people shit on me for thinking this way they're really like reading a lot more into
my opinion than I'm actually saying like they absolutely like they hear they hear me say
that like you know well well how can gender be performative if like a tomboy is still a girl
and they're like well quit being transphobic man live and let live uh uh why do you hate trans people
the fact that they jump from you just like asking a question or trying to examine it they interpret
as an attack on like this identity in some way it's not even that it's because there's I think
it's worse than that I think they they they see it as an attack but I think it's because this is
such a feelings-based thing that this ideology has no logical defense because you'll they'll
be like you need to educate yourself and it's like okay teach me and you know I don't think it's
even I don't think it's even controversial to say that it is all about feelings like there's
nothing else there that's true and I mean I guess there's some studies I guess there's some studies
but the studies are all about feelings you know my whole thing that I said before about how I don't
give a shit about how anybody feels or anyone's you know feelings or whatever like that's only because
that's not out of like uh malice or anything it's because I don't think you can get to truth by just
listening to the way people saying how they feel about shit because all these other things get
bottled in I just want to examine fucking data that as as objectively as possible categorized
I want people to be as happy as possible including trans people and like I don't know like the suicide
rate is really high for trans people even after operation so yeah it's really necessarily the
best way to go yeah I want the best opportunities for them possible and like and like people's
feelings are valid and like people feel the way that they feel and I would never tell someone no you
don't actually feel the way that you say they feel but you can't make sweeping generalizations about
your your feelings in comparison to others because you can't you can't fucking tell another person
how they feel which I really think a lot of this a lot of this ideology really toes the line towards
doing that's the thing the reason but we value facts over feelings even to begin with because
it's easy it's easier to to have feelings than to get the facts right but the reason the facts are
more important is because they're universal right yeah and that's the whole thing because when you
when we start taking feelings super seriously it inevitably leads to nothing because your
feelings are different than my feelings communicate with each other with and understand what we're
saying it's a it's a it's a it's a shared baseline that we can build things off of whereas if we
start taking feelings in consideration I feel different than Ben then feels different than
Nate that feels different than much and none of us could ever get anywhere I don't know that sounds
like fake news to me I don't know yeah there's no red-pilled enough for this fucking truth
there's no basis there's no basis for comparison when we're talking about feelings you know right
so it just gets really complicated and tricky well here's a feeling for you I love you guys
give gave were you saying something there well I was just gonna say I'm pro-phobic I I love homophobes
and transphobes I love fear I'm a big proponent of fear yeah okay let me just say okay we're
talking about homophobes let me just drop a bomb on this things you can't say okay what let me this
is just me giving an example of something that you cannot say or like it's over for you okay here's
here's this thing that I do not actually believe but here I go feel free to cut this everybody
and pretend this is what I actually think for the rest of time okay it is impossible for the white
race to share a nation-state with other races therefore the white race needs their own ethno
state like what do you there there's a lot of people think compelling right that's that's the
alt-right position it is like okay what if you believe that what happens when you believe that
and say that publicly you are you're fucking you're done you get punched in the face and I mean
sidewalk during an interview I don't know because now you've got a lot of friends that are with you
well that that that is true you've got the alt-right movement with you the real one it's not very big
though it's real it's well it's big enough that it scares me so you know that's my feeling
the estimations I've heard is this maybe 15 000 people in the alt-right well okay but you know
what it's kind of like it's kind of like with like the jihadist movement 100 people that's a lot of
people I mean I have I have personally known people who well I mean I don't know I guess they
didn't come right out and say that they're all right but like they definitely had like leanings
in that direction well it's hard it's hard to be white person and not sympathize to some degree at
this point considering considering considering everything's about race now it's like well I
guess I'm a white person so I guess considering everything that we as a people have been through
well okay here's here's a thought uh uh you know the the white race specifically uh like gets gets
lambasted in a lot of ways these ways these days publicly as uh and it's like totally acceptable
to make sweeping generalizations about specifically that race and no others uh but but here's I think
it's totally useless and extremely harmful because that's punching up right right that's that's
punching up right well there's like a statistic floating around that I heard that like 50 something
percent of white people in america feel that they're being discriminated against now like that's
an insane metric but when you hear about but like yeah they're not actually discriminated against
right but then you all these talking points like you're you're culturally lambasted all the time
like Nate just said and of course of course people notice that we just you're just not allowed
socially to say anything about it so yeah it's it's it's really just I gotta say there's there's
definitely there's definitely a frustration when you're just like okay here's what here's what I
feel I am I consider myself basically above even considering the concept of race and it's like
basically useless to me so so here I am just being like okay I'm a human individual and this is like
the individualistic philosophy of just like everyone run your own shit and just like get ahead do
whatever you can do and everyone should just try and I want the people who are the best to succeed
Nate are you in the galatarian because you're not allowed to say that either
exactly but then like but then like okay but then you see I don't know like the neo-black
panthers or just whatever like the islamics or whatever I don't know any like racial group
is right any other racial services group sure I don't fucking know but any any like racialized
group then says like okay uh no like we're here to root for like uh you know I don't know uh
like Arab people like we're here champion Arab people and then okay if they're they're sort of
weaponizing their racial group and then you're over here saying like okay but I don't identify
with my racial group I'm just an individual operator it's like you can't contest them it's
like they are just they just go unopposed in saying that like we need to advocate and they're
like reinforcing thinking along racial lines you know which is an issue I don't know if I agree with
I'm gonna I'm gonna come out and and say something uh that I don't know if you'll
agree with but like okay white white people because they're the minority sorry because
they're the majority or like culturally the majority at least in our culture um they have
they have the benefit of being the the default and they have they have the privilege and it is a
privilege of they have the privilege of like living without thinking about their race whereas
like people in marginalized groups and people in minority groups don't really have that privilege
and they are kind of forced to confront like the reality of race and I don't argue with that
I don't argue with that yeah so so I get it like I get why marginalized groups need like
yeah like it's do you think okay this is what I'm coming from a position of privilege but I wish
they wouldn't do that and that no one ever would like I wish white people and every group wouldn't
like be racist I mean I wish people would feel the need to inculcate themselves in the racial
identity because I think it's all bad yeah yeah it would be nice it would be it would be nice if
nobody felt the need to do that but like right by being by yeah by being in the minority and
marginalized you know I I I get it I get I get the the reasoning where like we got a band together
and like it's like it's like how I it's like how I see people who are religious and everyone's like
oh but yeah like religion is is a helpful tool okay but like even if you talk to like a lot of
atheists like like Stefan Malinu is an atheist but would say like okay religion like is sort of a
support structure that helps humanity and I'm like okay but it's not true and he's like yeah of course
I'm like okay uh so how do we like fix this he's like what do you mean I don't know uh we just
keep doing it it's like okay we can recognize this this this has a place in the world like it makes
sense why it's here but let's just try to get past it as soon as possible let's let's let's let's
leave the shit behind because it is an old thing that drags us down and we should move past it
eventually and I'm thinking about doing that I want to do that as soon as possible that's where my
focus is uh yeah yeah yeah that's what I think about religion religion is interesting there's a
there's a guy Dennis Prager who makes the argument and he's not the first person to make it without
religion Dennis the menace hardcore you know he kind of looks like an old guy this guy's a big
conservative guy Prager University and shit yeah but but he made the point um I mean he's made it
before but I saw it on the Rubin report he made the point that um without without without religion
there's no uh objective morality society like in a social context right so because without without
one fake thing you can't assume belief in another totally right because the the argument is that I
mean he is religious but even like saying even saying that it's like I don't believe in religion
so but even putting that aside like if if everyone believes in something then the entire social uh
construct like the social contract has a baseline of ethics or value systems to work up from it's
the same thing we're talking before about America right that's kind of what America was it was a
baseline that everybody who came here could agree with and work off of um yeah but the argument is
once you take away religion everything becomes subjective because it's just human interpretation
well because that's the reality because in reality everything is and and while it's it's I I'd agree
it's way more difficult to work in that paradigm of saying everything subjective how do we come
to a consensus I think it's more valuable long term but I think the reason religion has been
around so long is because it's an effective shorthand for that yeah it's like of course all the
Christians work this way so in our in our Christian culture this is the value system and we don't
have to think about it anymore we're on the same page inherently it's like it's like I think it's why
Islam is doing so well too because everybody you know to some degree is on the same page it's like
here it's like here with with this shit with these like idea systems and systems of like belief
that really functions control mechanisms uh for like societies it's like you're playing spore
and everyone's playing I like this the greatest game I've ever made yeah like you're playing
and you're playing like on like on the cell level where you're just like eating cells and like okay
we're we're living on the cell level where we just we understand the rules at play here but at some
point you eat enough cells and you grow big enough where where it does it does the zoom out to like
the next level so now we're aware of this like larger context and like you can still play the
little cell game and like you can see that at a much lower level but we're not aware of all this
truth about the larger universe beyond this and and it's time to we need to slowly adjust from
thinking just on that cellular level to the like small organism level or whatever it is and I think
that that's the way that like understanding more of the truth that the universe has to work like
people are stuck down at this like lower level thinking which is like religious thinking but
then we realize that okay none of this is true we need to expand the way we think about all these
frameworks and adjust our reasoning for that I see what I'm saying you're talking about leveling up
my christ consciousness trying to rev up those murkabahs guys
it's like you know life is like life is like that game life is like uh that that mini game at the
end of a level of Kirby where you gotta time your jump to like see how high and it's like just like
who can who can who can who can ride their murkaba to the highest dimension right of course the winner
the winner gets to eat a tasty tasty higher dimensional spirit yeah it's how blitz is Kirby
gonna be that like the lowest level is the root chakra and then the top level is the crown chakra
and that's and that's that's the amount of chakras you're gonna be fucking living off of hey I have
one other thing just one other like idea I want to touch on that relates to just like things you
can and can't say and it's the idea that like in context some things that you can't say normally
you can say and specifically Kirby is what reminds me of this
it's that like so you can say nigger and Kirby well I mean that well you kind of can uh because
believe in the weeb episode season two episode three just came out and it's everyone should
watch it it's it's very good it's very funny please don't but it's like but it's like our friend
at munchie here like the the conceit of the episode is that munchie is the biggest race
realist uh whoever lived and is is is a big fan of the racial slur and yet I don't think anyone
has has come away from watching that video and thought like anything negative about about munchie
and I mean I can't imagine why you would it's it's just so like within the context of the video
it's so ridiculous and over the top and this is like the comedian effect like comedians can get
away with saying things like your average person cannot you know you know what I'm saying and I
just think that's real interesting I would like to this is a good point I don't want to come back
to but I just want to say for the record about the plea in the weeb uh it was it was at like
six three in the morning I've been up for like an entire day and also a year ago and also I'm sorry
I'm not funny I swear to god that I'm funnier now first rule dude no no it's right I'm so sorry I
will say though that I do think you've you've evolved significantly over the past year uh since
rad con too which is which when was your like first pcp entrance I mean you were probably on
one before that but like you became like a main dude after that sometime the first episode I was on
was memes that need to god need to die but I don't remember what my first like I am a member was yeah
okay well but I don't know you're it was after that anyway yeah yeah uh I'm so excellent about
like the context in which you can say things yeah I exist in like a weird like limbo land I live in
california in a big city and all my fans are all yeah all my all my friends are blue pilled as
fuck but the actual town that like I like go to and interact with on a daily basis is super red
pit like like like like like fucking blue lives matter flags everywhere you know okay you can't
walk down the street without seeing a trumpet but blue lives as opposed to blue pilled lives
get confused a lot right okay okay so no matter what I say if I'm if I'm in this town with my with
my blue with my cuck friends which is San Diego right that's that's the city I'm thinking that's
specifically like a small like suburb it's like oh yeah like it is San Diego but like it's called
Coronado it's like a like a like a jump away but like basically it's in the metro area like like
they're the same city basically uh yeah so like like if I were to say something there then no
matter what I would have someone who hates me and it's just like like you just have to play
the mood constantly in whatever context that you're in you know it like if what I'm gonna say like
here beneficial to me because I'm just gonna come out right here and say it like I censor myself
sometimes like while I like realize the value and meaning and saying nigger I realize that like
you know like this will make this will make my friend sad if I say nigger and like you know
like like like saying like fuck you know a generic swear word is incredible and makes you a better
person on average but like going to a funeral only sometimes it only sometimes experiences yeah yeah
only sometimes can you say fuck and like you know like like it only sometimes improves the experience
but I've been kicked out of far too many morgues to continue my hedonistic lifestyle of going up
to random corpses and screaming obscenities you know like like I like say nigger but I just have to
realize the mood and you know like like I'm fine like like I care about relationship with my blue
blue friends more than I care about saying nigger in this exact moment like like in this context I
don't it just goes to show that like feelings is what dictates whether or not these things are okay
or not it's all an emotional state that defines this stuff yeah here's here's like on that point
is like another thing that you know it's kind of like stupid to say like sometimes censorship is not
even a big deal like it like people are just kind yes because like everything it's like you're not
supposed to to say certain things in certain places and sometimes it doesn't even fucking matter so
you know why not who cares like censorship isn't you know I was just trying to be like like like
extra blue pill like censorship is good sometimes like whoa that's something you don't hear that's
something you're not allowed to say a clickbait thumbnail they click on the video it's like
actually a far more reasonable point I mean like when you go and meet yeah if you go and meet like
you're fucking I don't know like you hang out with like your grandparents or something like
you're not gonna act the same way with your grandparents that you do on like your your red
pill podcast on the internet yeah exactly I act way more red pills with my I could you know maybe
there you were just in Germany probably visiting Hitler's great and saluting extensively I walk up
my grandmother all right guys time for another episode of arm retrieval you know Andrew house he
is a fucking nigger hack and he's like oh that much he's at it again yeah you only record arm
retrieval when they're in the room it doesn't make any sense yeah it just it just all follows apart
well I guess we we've gone through a gamut here so what else what else should we touch on before
we end our discussion I would like to talk about we've talked about like like the controversial
you know we're talking about nigger which by the way I just want to say like we've talked about all
the negatives and positives I love saying nigger as demonstrate the thing about nigger is that it's
the it's the it's the word that makes people the angriest so it's the one that you want to say
to piss people off which is why like nigger is such a common word okay can I can I can I
pose a question before we go for any further yeah me too good yeah yeah yeah okay is it do you
because I feel and maybe this is just me and that's why I want to pose the question see if I'm
like crazy or this is totally a thing are swear words and racial slurs the most fanatically
pleasing things to say yes or is that just me like that that is me as well that is like a lot of
it's some I think that the reason they become used as words meant to hurt people is because
they have a punchy sort of feeling to them like cunt you know you call somebody a cunt it feels great
yeah it's just of the way I don't know it's just all those they feel good to swear words because
I kind of hate that because it not not even just because like it gets you into trouble like racial
services do like you want to say them but just like I say fuck so much is because like it just it
feels good to say it yeah it feels great go to kinesthetics unironically I mean I I would I would
imagine that like racial slurs like like nigger wop kike like they're all they were come up with
like probably by like your smarmy sailor types just like leering over the bar at like those people
they don't fucking care for very much thank you very much uh so by christ he's a fucking gooke
he's a fucking wop you know like fuck that guy well well well well well well wop is the sound
that spadey makes me drop it down to the fucking ground like you're gonna drop a fucking italian's
head down to the fucking ground is that true is that where that fucking comes from I'm I'm I'm
fairly certain yet no that the sound of that greasy lock slapping against the floor tiles
wop is an abbreviation I think it stands I think it stands for without passport because they're like
illegal immigrants or something was the original idea that's what I heard like that that one's not
phonetically even um even kraut like like like the world war two thing right you call the germans
the krauts like that has like a consonants like whatever that word is like it has like a punchiness
like a like a sharpness to it any word like that is useful for for sounding like powerful
and in command and aggressive so any any any words that has ever been used to like hurt people has
had that sort of sound in it can we agree at least on this if nothing else that the the nation state
of knee chair must change its name to make me more comfortable looking at the world map
it's the only thing I it's not really dragging down the rest of us with that shit like how
how are we supposed to operate in this blue pill feminized cuck world that I live in and advocate
for every day on my blue pill podcast the pcp that how can I live knowing there's a country called
nigger how can I live with that I just it it tears me up it's truly too much to bear those
black people are the most racist against black people in the world and it's a big problem for
me we should fucking bomb the fuck out of it destroy wipe it off the map kill all people
there just just forget about it indeed nuclear bomb I the reason like the reason I like nigger
it's funny that you bring up like it's like it is the worst so it's funny to make it is the worst
but I don't I don't actually agree with like I like I don't set out none of my actions are
inherently to make other people upset that is usually actually the opposite of what I want to
do oh of course yeah but it's it's like it's the reason they're fun to say yeah because it's like
you're just you're just a ball of like insane energy and like you're obviously not like when
you go on a rant about how Kirby is your fucking nigger forget who in the world would like ever
be offended by such a thing it would be inconceivable to be like that's like we're talking about
context and that's like so important right the context of that has nothing to do with like a
racial insult you know yeah exactly people get so pissed off when you say those words because of
like the con like the historical kind of usage of them yeah but at the same time like it's when
you when you're saying something like that there's no insulting context like is it really more offensive
for me to go up to a black person be like you fucking nigger than is to go up to a black person
be like the color of your skin disgusts me and makes you feel like you're less of a human being
than i am right right dude you should do a prank video okay here's where i where i drop like a
munchy lower bomb because there's actually a reason i use nigger a lot uh in the context that i do
i almost got through the entire show and not saying it damn it i was so close i um this doesn't
happen always because i've kind of fallen off the bandwagon and it's just it's just too fun to say
nigger and i say in context and i let my discipline down however the original reason i i set out to use
nigger a lot is because one like like the most important thing about it is that it's phonetically
pleasing and it's really punchy and fun to say absolutely it's just like how drawing a swastika
just feels yeah it just feels right it just is good yeah but i i i i realize i like like i am again
a blue-pilled cuck and you know i didn't want to make anyone feel bad that i was using the term
nigger even though i just wanted to in the base of my soul so i tried to remove nigger from its
cultural context as much as possible that's the thing right there in the curbie episode there are
no black people i am not saying this like like this african this this fucking slave here i'm
saying this like this like snail this like gross snail monster is a nigger what does that mean
exactly the answer is that it means absolutely nothing and to remove that from its actual
cultural context just makes it a fun thing to say the only way i think that someone could like take
this in an insulting way is they'd be like okay the fact that you're calling a character a nigger
means that you're saying like oh this person is as lowly as the lowly nigger would be like the thing
they're i want to say i'm with you though like what you're doing is robbing it of its insulting
significance yeah yeah i feel the same way because i okay i like the i like the feeling of like being
like an asshole and throwing out insults and like treating people you know like like like i'm so
fucking great i'll call you some i'll just be like you suck peon but i also hate hurting people's
feelings yes me too i know exactly same so exactly so what i so what i often do my favorite insults
are the ones that mean literally nothing that's why my favorite insult is to call someone a fuck
because what does that mean nothing right yeah there's there's that that insult has no content
to it at all my favorite type of insult and like threat of violence are the ones where there isn't
actually any violence being like conveyed yeah like i'm not actually say i'm not actually
saying like i'm going to hurt you my my favorite insults i'm gonna pick you up i'm gonna i'm gonna
pick you up i'm gonna put you down like like like like like what does that mean what does that
mean exactly carries all the attitude it carries all the attitude of bravado of like a threat without
any actual threat being exactly it's like it's like beyond like swearing it's like a post swear
it's like so yeah sometimes what i like doing is is instead of like doing any of that violent
stuff it's just to to wish like a very mild and non-sonic die like like like i like i hope i hope
you stub your toe and then you know you fall over like like something like that wouldn't hurt but it
would hurt you know like it would just like fuck i'm really annoyed that i still you know i think
we all really like utilizing these very like light you know it's kind of magical about those is that
yeah if you if you say i hope you know fuck you i hope you go die like they're just like you know
whatever but you say fuck you i hope you stub your toe and then later they stub their toes like damn
it they did it to me that's true that's true that that that that kind of that kind of sticks with
you i feel like i feel like this post swearing world's a world i want to live in now yeah get
together everybody i cannot wait for the hashtag post swear to cash on i'm so happy
well guys everyone else i mean i feel like we've done a quiet i'm glad that we got to this point
at the end this is this is where i was immediately thinking that the discussion would go i i just
want to comment before on the overuse the idea of angry video game nerd syndrome as as i've titled
the use of using too many swear words okay i view it a lot like legendary pokemon like the
useless terrible yes it yes almost exactly because okay the reason i like swear words
and i think we all do is because they they are special as even though we will say you know
swear words aren't that bad and you know you should be able to say swear words to kids and you know
scream obscenities at your toddlers and that should be okay at the end of the day it's almost good
that they that they that is that gives them their power if i heard it's what i said at the very
beginning yeah well i'm saying i'm i'm saying it better because i'm not you get okay okay sir
on that topic i think the point you're making i watched a little video by by a man named steve
recently yeah it was just about how legendary i was just about to recite that is our piece of
shit and terrible and how you had to fucking search for mute two and the original birds and
dig in deep down deep inside and catch them uh that was the good shit uh stop giving me legendary
pokemon pokemon your your shit okay they really give you a very straightforward in sudden moment
they just give them to you basically yeah yeah wait yeah you get to the end of the game and then
you get them what you have to catch them and the game will not let you proceed until you catch
them so you you are forced to catch them and they won't even object they immediately go in the ball
if you just throw the ball so i guess look i i guess lucario is not a legendary but they just give
you a lucario well that's bad too i want to earn my black and white i forget all right well pokemon
sucks gen two was the best gen two was the best objectively actually gold and soul silver that
is the peak pokemon experience and if something you're not allowed to say i like gen three that's
the good one nobody likes gen three get that is literally the most popular opinion as i say
nate says no one likes gen three i hate those fucking trumpets i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
go i'm gonna die in that hill oh i'll kill you gen three oh i'll kill you what are you talking about
what are trumpets music and gen three sucked ass those synthesized trumpets it sound like someone
was like farting really high pitch okay they fucking suck that kato what the fuck ever okay
what takes at least six points off the metagame score it does critic score six out of ten too much
trumpets ign reveal anything anything like gen four or later if that's your favorite pokemon
you're a literal baby and you don't matter will you like the day that you're black and white too
black and white too is a great fucking oh you're a baby get the fuck out of here if you're not you
guys into one other how about that gen three is your favorite pokemon game you're you're you're a
literal autistic uh uh uh sixth grader is what i'm gonna say gen four is the best generation
you're objectively no no no i have no respect for you i i'm so fucking elated an option for
favorite gen of pokemon i'm so fucking happy that the the the the big argument was just pokemon
okay we're all on the same page we're all on the same page about trans issues about gamergate
about all of that like that like we've solved that we've solved that we're onto the real problems
now look look all the trans issues and the racist stuff that was the cellular level now we're
moving on to work what does it mean to feel like you're that you like the generation one pokemon
more what does that mean to feel like the discussion about which pokemon gen is is best is so much
more relevant to my life than the trans debates and the trans issues so uh that's why i care about
it to go back what i was saying just to just close this up uh i don't like it when you know
people just say fuck or shit randomly as i demonstrated in the plea of the weeb oh god kill
me the reason that's not cool is because you there is no classroom there's no there's no sense of like
oh god he's saying that word right now he's making me conscious ever to say that now it is important
and it's just yeah like everything you know what i will say if you're if your undertale is like is
is at maximum intensity all the time yeah there will be no peaks and valleys in your undertale
and it'll be a bad undertale so here's i think specifically in media i think that over swearing
had its time like i think i think the angry video game nerd in particular is a great historical
snapshot of how media has evolved with the rise of the internet because if you watch an episode
of south park or something on tv back when the internet like youtube was still a wee babe and
they had like a swearing spree it was just like a bunch of bleeps and it just turned into nothing
whereas you watch like an episode of the angry video game nerd having only been able to watch tv
and youtube being a baby thing all of a sudden this guy's on a screen stringing swears together
that you only hear with your friends like holy shit this is crazy and that was really novel
for a time now it's like past sake because everybody can do it so now we're now we're in the
post swearing uh society makes me feel bad i really i think i think that's true i think that
like i think that like the older generations like are more like baby boomers are really offended
by swear words and like millennials as been saying the ultimate baby boomer you know what's
interesting uh i've actually been getting some comments recently on like unlike my star wars
video for example that i made on my channel um we're like i've distinctly noticed like some older
people you know probably like old school star wars fans like clicked on the video to watch it
where i'm like comparing star trek doesn't matter which i say star wars i meant star trek i meant
star trek um and uh i know i would never talk about star wars grace yeah you cannot say star wars
to me don't say it's all it's all star trek all day uh and i know like i've actually been taking
some notice of this myself how i use the word fuck like a lot all the time just in like my
daily speech and i actually think it's a little bit getting in the way of the message i'm trying
to convey like in my weyagawa videos so i've actually been thinking that i'm trying to actually
reduce it just because i don't like for the for the vehicle that that show is i don't think it
actually like adds to it particularly and i think if it distracts people from the point i'm trying
to make then like i wouldn't want to whereas you know something like uh like but what i will say
is like guys like digi or like i don't know uh like other other youtubers who are just common
like interweaving just the word fuck into the script just you know like once in a while has
become super common and like everybody does it now whereas like older like on tv of course it
would never happen so i i actually like that the words these swear words have been like more
interwoven into everyday usage and to use them sparingly is like not even blinked at people
don't even bat an eye at like just the insertion of the word fuck at like a uh a relatively
appropriate moment and i think that is a very positive way that we're gone i like it i i i
completely agree it yeah i mean swear words they really always have been like um if you want to
be controversial you use them so and now like in the internet you can find all types of different
people you can find you know if i'm in a world on a like a potato cam if i'm in a like a like a
like a place full of red peeled people i'll say something blue peeled to rile them up because
i like doing that i mean it's funny yeah for me it's like in a place full of blue peeled i'll say
it you know maker or whatever it's for me it's like it's like uh it's similar to how i think there
should be a state enforcement to include a certain percentage of like erotic content in all media
i think they should be enforced and the reason is because with increasing control parents have
over their children and how they won't let them go out and just like fuck strangers the way they
used to i think it behooves us to make sure that children are exposed to a certain degree of sexual
content so they know what the fuck's going on this is a literal thing i'm passing legislation in my
state at the moment and we're going to expand it globally soon enough so uh i really like i really
like that's the quotas that people want to see everybody that's what you're going to be saluting
that's the flag you're going to salute in the morning had fucking uh a christmas day everybody
get ready for it what are you gonna do when they start having like uh racial and sexual orientation
quotas in the the the sexual content they expose children to that's just oh no well you know i'm
i'm 100 anti-race mixing i can there could be none of that there could be none of this right okay
yeah that'll be a big problem we'll deal with that when it comes out where are you still here
you'll have a pow wow with richard spencer it doesn't matter it was it was a fucking joke
and i couldn't get in now the time's passed so fuck it oh jeez it poops all of us stub our
toes after this show i hope you stub your fucking dad's toes oh my god he had nothing to do with
this how dare you bring it to me but lay off the dad's you aren't allowed to say that
wow um well guys shall we go to the question now nigger yeah i think he's reached that point yeah
it feels like it okay uh uh everybody oh uh don't forget to uh patron us at patreon.com
slash the procrastinators please please you're in our fan discord please lord for for jesus
lord mercy amen lord knows we're not gonna have monetization on this episode so please make up for
it please oh christ i i just want to shout out that guy uh i don't know who was made like a bingo
card of me and i just want to say briska just so you can cross that out before we move on to
questions i have a i have a question for all you just what you're what's your read on this
okay our opinion on like the whole trans thing are we in the majority or are we in the minority
of what the real majority of like real people right yeah well i don't know i'm like i really am
no i do you know what i think it is i think we're in the majority i just think because of the the uh
the culture uh you're not allowed to say it yeah so it's not presented very off so i guess we've
been punching down pretty hard this episode i would imagine zero point one percent of the
population well they have a loud voice they have a loud ass voice online so i don't feel that bad
i would imagine that like the majority of people who are explicitly against trans people are probably
not as nuanced as we are and while we may be in like the majority of like we're skeptical of this
our exact opinions and formations of our thoughts are probably different i don't know i don't know if
we would be necessarily in the minority i'd like to think i i'm sure i'm sure i'm sure that the
people in the comments aren't going to see it that way it's just i i think literally oh no we
will be dead we are done goodbye i want everyone to be as happy and healthy as possible i simply
do not agree that the methods that these people have selected as the optimum one are necessarily
that and i would like to see more evidence that that's the case i agree that's my position i mean
that's my opinion the reason i overflow with empathy for these people but go on the reason we
would you know reason we were talking about it in in the first place was is because like because
we can't talk about it but that you can't talk about it because they have their claws i mean
not to imply they have claws it's like they're fucking deep monsters but like that's the master
kids who have the claws you just you're just everybody's like like the majority of people can't
speak the the way they want right yeah it's kind of silly but that's right here on the on the pcp
we have an open mic for any ideas all the time well they're they're gonna it's it's gonna be like
those dudes that were fucking around on me on twitter they're gonna say like well you can have
your opinion but you shouldn't say it because it's regressive and because like you're you're like
hurting you're like hurting society by spreading around the way you feel about this issue that
usage of the word regressive really got me that's them just saying like no my opinion is confirmed
the correct one you cannot argue yeah like i said i'm not i said i'm not gonna agree with anything
for the sake of progressivism and then he took that as a as an admission that i was that i was
regressive which it was not oh my god fuck yep i love the the words and that should be another
episode fucking like bullshit semantics that people use i hate that oh god that i couldn't
do an episode on that we got speaking of this but here's a great question i love this one actually
there's a lot going on with this so this is from the twitter everybody we do the thing follow us
at tpcrastinators on saturdays we record so that you see the tweet where we ask for them questions
using the hashtag ask pcp thing we also pull questions from the procrastinators chat so if
you're right of course you get access to the discord server and we'll pull questions from
there more often because you love us and we'll love you back that's how indeed but listen to this one
okay at gabe 11 gabe w underscore 11 asks is it wrong to want to see others not succeed in life
if their career is already heading towards failure oh no there's a lot i think i think that
well i think if i think that's i need a minute to parse that good i think that means you care
about them if you think well exactly if you think that's exceeding at their chosen thing is going
to be bad for them in the long run yeah i think you should i think yeah you should want them to
fail at it yeah that makes sense to me yeah um well i mean i'm trying to think of like an example
where that would not work hey i've got one for you i've got an example of this so there was this
there was this guy who went on the shark tank and he advertised this game and it was called like
boulder ball builder ball it was some like game oh yeah i know i know what you're talking about
yeah like this man had spent like a decade a trying to make this sport an olympic sport
and was like going around had sold his house had had divorced his wife or he like his marriage
had collapsed like his life was in shambles because he was trying so hard and he believed
to a pathological degree you might say that this game was going to be successful and he would not
stop until it became as successful as he wanted to be and like the sharks were like dude you need
to stop this is not going to happen it's not going to work out and it was called bullet ball
i have bullet ball yeah okay bullet ball and uh it was it was a nightmare like he listening to his
story but the amazing thing is ultimately he did find some small success with it in like uh i don't
know exactly how but like he did manage to get a little bit of his toe in the door yeah like it's
i'm seeing that it's it's it's part of the senior olympics now right or it became part of it so
yeah someone somewhere picked it up it didn't become an olympic sport but jesus christ someone
someone maybe he met senior olympics all along it just wasn't saying it i don't i don't know i mean
i'm sure it's a perfectly playable game and i'm sure it's an okay game it's an okay game but like
okay but the question is was it worth it was it fucking worth it did he losing his wife that
depends on the metrics you're measuring like is it personal satisfaction or is it like tangible
asset like i think i think the only reason i think the only reason you should um wish for the
the failure of someone is because if they succeed it will be like actually bad for you in some
tangible way yeah otherwise it shouldn't really be part of you but like i mean if you care about
them and like this is gonna kill them then you know that's that's different but if it's like
they're they're living a worse life but they appear happier like if they're going down a road that
you cut like the sort of drifting apart from you is it really your place to like decide where
their life goes if they like it more i think you have to respect their time like don't interfere
you can hope that if something looks really bad like man i hope that i hope i think it's less
about if it's someone you care about it's less about hoping they fail but hoping they change
directions right you're not right you hope right yeah like if you get some sort of something
improves if you're getting a sadistic pleasure from watching your friends fail like i mean that's
that's not that's you know maybe i guess i shouldn't judge what makes you happy either but like
that's not really like what we want society to be built on so i think that that would be uh
fairly safe to say that's a negative thing to do and you probably wouldn't want to do it um
yeah i think but no i think gibbs right the only time you really want to actively hope for someone
failing is like if you're in for an interview and the person before he's interviewing first
man i hope they fuck it up right right anything like that anything like that that's that's perfectly
reasonable i got a question from the procrastinator's patreon lounge you can donate for just one
dollar uh get in here you can fucking scream as loud as you can and we're all contractually
obligated to hear you yeah it's true um by griffy what is your least favorite i'm gonna
expand this to least favorite and possibly the favorite thing that's happened as a result of
the existence of the pcp uh okay so i mean this friend group or specifically the podcast
i would i would imagine like the podcast i would i would like or the podcast or you know like like
the culture surrounding it as a result of it being a podcast uh i make money my favorite thing
that's the best thing that's true that's not bad yeah the best thing about the pcp is that it
lets me do my other stuff yeah absolutely yeah but i think my favorite thing about it is uh radcon
that was the fun radcon and i mean i mean well i'll take it i mean i do enjoy being on the show
and and hanging out with y'all like i always have fun actually doing the podcast yeah that's my i mean
long before the pcp made money i mean it's no secret that i am the beating heart of the pcp
that keeps this this machine lumbering along and a lot of that i think just came from the
fact that i had moved out to a new city and i didn't like have friends out here or anything i
didn't know anybody and i felt a strong desire to to keep conversation going with these guys online
so like i was always there like let's do it let's fucking do this because like this was my excuse
because like again this was a big thing before the podcast there was like never an excuse to like
getting calls and talk it's true with you guys like you have to be like you guys i'm so sad i
need to fucking talk about i think it's safe to say nate that if you hadn't started the pcp we would
not be nearly as close as we are now i probably would have fallen off the map with a lot of you
just because we don't because we didn't we don't have like a fandom thing to keep us all talking
and stuff like we all kind of went off in our own directions and if we didn't have this to to galvanize
our our group i think it would have would have definitely weakened if not and i it's true i think
some people might be inclined to think i don't know i just want to say like on that point some
people might think that's the mark of like a a weaker bond or a weaker friendship and i just
want to challenge that completely if anyone's thinking that that there is nothing that is that
is the mark of of a group of intellectual gods going to your own thing yeah we're we're i mean
capitalism in general and like the the free market decision to do what you want in life
like allows you to self-select for the kind of people that you want to spend your time with
and interact with and so like like you can't choose your fucking parents you know so like you
should have i don't know i was tweeting about this the other day like you should have standards for
like whether or not you want to continue to even associate with like the people that you had no choice
of being involved in when you were growing up like if your parents are monsters it's perfectly
reasonable to not associate with them and if like you guys were shit i wouldn't hang out with you
but i choose to because they're all my brothers and it's great and i love you all thank you and
like and like even before the pcp made any money or even looked like it might ever make any money
like we were all we were we were like there was never any question of like let's not do this anymore
because yeah i love i love my paycheck from the pcp but i'd do it for free yeah and we did a lot
of us for a long time for a long time yeah well some was part of his question the least favorite
thing yeah as well oh that's true i forgot i want to say my favorite thing was either like like
hippo the rad con too or just recently going out to meet ben that was truly incredible and it was a
great time and it was fun great so it was fucking great uh it was blissful yeah i can't wait to do
it again i mean the worst thing about the pcp as an organization by far is is the kind of issues
that arise just from a group of people working and have clashing ideology sometimes and uh you
know we they may have not have been an incident where someone had to leave you know that wasn't
fun and uh things like that are pretty much stand out as the things you don't want to have to do
for me i think i think we can all agree that this i think i want to say uh i i i i'm sorry monkey
i i i i don't hate you uh but i i feel bad about the whole situation oh yeah it was real it was
real shitty it was real shitty yeah actually i'm mad i was gonna make a joke but then you made it all
serious and yeah i'm just gonna echo that it was you know that oh well here's gib cutting off jokes
how does it like taste in your own medicine i can't even make the joke now because my joke is going
to say the worst part was jeff and i can't even make that it's real got him jeff's career i love
you jeff um yeah the monkey situation make no mistake we were all upset about it awdy and so
none of us were happy about it no no yep yep yep yep it's some of us for different reasons
and others yeah but any of the worst things uh i can't really think of any no i mean that's pretty
great in it yeah everything else is great yeah yeah yeah especially the money yeah i i love every
month this is like it is literally my favorite part of the month to just like calculate the finances
of the pcp and like divvy it up appropriately and make sure and check off my little boxes when
everyone's gotten paid i feel so great about it it is it is a pleasure to do it and uh i just watch
as our financial empire slowly grow and can feel that's my favorite thing it's my favorite you're
always posting like you're always posting graphs of like look at like look at our performance like
look at our revenue yeah look at the upward trend and i gotta say i appreciate it a lot damn right
right it does make me feel like my life is on an upward curve in some way despite everything else
being a dumpster fire it's good to know that there's some glimmer of hope there that's good that's
everyone's saying the generic like oh yeah i i i like money i like money and i do like money
however i want to go with like to the black pilled extreme and say that that that that my favorite
aspect of the pcb that might be my favorite about vanity is seeing people say that they like me and
that i am the best pcp member that's what i striped or yeah whoever someone says that i'm the best pcp
member i know like oh of course that is true thank you very much you're a polarizing figure but you
do get a lot of people saying you're the best and that they're here for you and i will say
social currency is just as fun to collect as the actual currency so you know you're not wrong yeah
i feel like i feel like um i feel like i'm a i'm kind of a dark horse kind of a cult favorite
i feel like i'm not the most popular but i but i feel like there's a like there's a like there's
sizable minority of people that are that are solidly in ben's camp and i appreciate them so much
i feel like i don't know what i'm doing lately but people i've gotten a couple comments who
like oh tom's pretty cool i'm just like yes notice me you know the mysterious satisfaction i need
yeah i i feel like i'm like the the token favorite like everyone has to say they like a hippo because
you know i like you just do anything negative at all like as the the absolute everybody gets
tired of some weird utilitarianism every once in a while or they're you know they
whatever or ben you know like there's only so much trash you can eat out of the dumps before
you take it before but before they just get old but yeah exactly but never you stop the podcast
this episode dead in its tracks twice with like three words great just yeah it was great it was
great so i i certainly agree uh that it's it's great there's a reason you're the one pitching
shows and not us it's because yeah well that's not because i made funny jokes you're like you're
like the the you're like the the blueberries in the blueberry pancakes of the podcast you know
juicy sweet bits that you love it's true you know what i'm saying you know what i'm saying that's
that's what i don't like blueberries oh i don't like you yeah i don't like you berries yeah uh
excellent what was i gonna say oh oh it related to this topic uh there happened to be on four
chan the other day a thread uh it was actually about digi something about mario odyssey i think
or something you know that shit um stupid and within it there a discussion about the pcp emerged
and three individual tier lists were posted as for who were the best i just want to say now this is
four chan which i am a close ally of so it makes sense that they would like me but i was the top
contender on all of them on all of them i was number one so that's not true i was i was the
top contender on a bunch of them i specifically remember that i was a different thread i was
consistently ranked high tier one guy was like liking ben saint and someone else and someone else
came in and shat all over him for his for his deviant opinion who may or may not have been me
you're in every episode it's all it's your show and so and i was going to say though the fact that
i talk so fucking much and i'm still liked is a pretty good indicator that my that the quality
of my average contribution is is good is positive so you know i'm the best we'll see about you're
gonna see about that more than you would like in a few minutes i think you're getting a little too
big for your britches i will say that one time i hosted the show i got a lot of positive comments
and people wanted me to replace you more often so just keep an eye out for that buddy it could just
be that host bump it could be the host it could be the host it could be the host it could be the host
angle for the pcp dictation so hard i'm gonna roll in my communist revolution here you just
yeah oh that was the best part of the pcp no like like saying that tom is a communist and having
everyone agree with me and then being that then him saying like it was what makes you think that
and we're all like oh we don't know we didn't question it was a real strizan effect moment
in the pcp like there was no moment of origin but we were all unanimous that of course this is
the funny thing is i didn't even know it was a thing until we had the the wrestling thing and
everyone's like oh you're a communist like i am why i don't know i don't fucking know it was good
good times all around it was it was um it's because you wear a beret it's like a shake of art you
know that honestly could be a real connection that might be like a real source of the though
that's a tutor cap which is not quite the same but you know it's it's a we don't we don't talk about
the tutor on educated americans they're all the fucking same right right another question from
patreon lounge by the vacuuminator are there any songs you've listened to so much uh at one point
in your life the lyrics have started to inform the way you've lived your life every song every song
from the sponge bob musical um not not lyrics wise but i have listened to a lot of like led
zeppelin songs to the point where i like off of the like off by heart i know exactly how all the
drum solos and guitar solos go and i could play along with them you listen to them on the thing
so much you are the black dog you are the stairway to heaven you are that yes yes i i just hum it to
myself in my brain like every every day like i can i can replay a song a classic rock song in my head
without having to turn on my mpc dude if this were a video game you would be like the designated
npc that like you talk to to begin the bgm playing like a different song in the background after you
collect the item oh my god associated with it that'd be you that's you in real life uh wait what
was exactly the question like have you listened to it so much that you're gay yeah that you turn
into a gay person wait no you talked over to her i didn't actually hear oh that it changes
your life well it informs it informs the way you live your life uh like it changes you and it gives
you new ideas in your old craning there i mean here's i don't know i like i'm hallowing at the
moon a lot these days uh uh like i don't actually know most of the lyrics to like sorairo days the
the garin login main theme but like i know i'm always on about it but like i listen to that song
a lot and it like deeply emotionally moves me every single time i was thinking about like what
my point was going to be that i it's not so much like lyrics of songs yeah like me but just like
the context of songs presented it and kind of just the emotional gravitas of the instrumentation
fucking you're not alone from final fantasy nine is like like that song just evokes such a strong
moment like from that game of like i mean i'm not even going to go into it but it is by far
the most emotionally powerful moment in final fantasy nine and it's devastating i actually have
one you know i do actually have one uh if i can pink floyd's welcome to the machine yeah informed a
lot of uh like like uh coming out of college having to think about looking for work uh not really
knowing what to do and be like yeah now you're in the machine this is what it is all of hybrid
theory informed my my middle school years i'm not gonna lie i bet it was a walking meme at the time
this is a like a little bit of a recent find for me so i i've got to see if it's truly changed my
life but it's uh put in a lot of like like ideas in that i've been cooking in my brain it's like
popped out and you know made me fully understand uh this guy this guy on bandcamp who did like like
homestuck music he's a guy who made the music for s enter he like he's that guy michael bowman
he's a real good singer songwriter guy and he's real is real fancy go listen to him uh
fucking comfortable bugs that's my shit and uh that that's he learned all i love all of his
lyrics and they feel like me there are me has there been a has there been a ceasefire in the
bug wars that allows you to listen to comfortable bugs yes yes yes there has okay and and it's
actually it's it's it's like cultural diversity i'm learning about so many different backgrounds
i'm i'm unsure if this fight is you know good enough to continue oh by the way i just want to add
like on a practical note like that that's serairo days and like like that song in lots of other like
songs that evoke strong emotions in me i actually strategically deploy those songs like during my
runs oh yeah i do as ways to like or like just when lifting to like force my like when i'm like
halfway through a run if i just put on like serairo days like it like the i've been psychologically
tricked it just kicks in in dorphin that just allows me to finish my run like easily so using it
that way to like force my body to just obey its stupid biological impulses uh is very interesting
and uh very fucking funny i do that all the time i like like i only listen to music in context of
would it be cool if like i was in a movie and this song was playing right now to the audience
like what this could be what's happening right now that's the only context i listen to any music
i think i think of all music as like what would what would an s like a home stuck flash look like
with this music yeah yeah what if what if i was having the baby and the baby was you what would
that be what if i was a great arm retrieval right now what would that sound like the baby is you
the baby is you changed my fucking life nothing was ever the same after i heard the baby is you
yeah god it's it's like actually like my favorite album oh and by the way people that that is a
homestuck album made by toby fox yeah it's his greatest fucking contribution to culture you
fucking swine indeed to you got two homes like musically guys check out go do it you fucking
bitch okay how about one more question then we wrap it up okay i i have something far very important
that will you know cut to the core of your very soul and your very being will change after you hear
this it'll be it'll be controversial uh topic like none other by bug fuck no my favorite one
by cuddle to ol in the patreon discord what's the best breakfast i'm gonna go out here and say
that pancakes pancakes without butter specifically or syrup and then and then two eggs is the best
breakfast or alternatively two eggs and a steak i'm gonna bring the breakfast and if you don't
have that then you're doing something wrong i'm gonna bring i'm gonna bring a little class
to this slovenly hole that we all reside in i'm gonna i'm gonna be two my two favorite breakfasts
are as follows one lobster eggs benedict oh my fucking god two i'm gonna knock you down oh the
decadence two uh locks locks bagels with cream cheese tomato onion and capers yeah yeah all right
all right slo mo okay all right buddy that's my name oh wait all of us went to a foreign language
class bed and the best and the best breakfast beverage is two thirds cranberry juice one third
grapefruit juice mixed together with your mix all just ain't you i am fat i'm a breakfast alchemist
is what i would describe my profession uh in stark contrast my favorite breakfast is uh to get a very
small frying pan and put two bits of bacon and two eggs uh just in at the same time and just crush
it around it like crush it and squish it around and then flip it over and it becomes like a
like a like a writhing squidging mess of like a like an omelet pancake like bacon things please
it's like it's like it's like a bacon omelet but it's just really messy and you you end up
like mopping up all the grease wait i've got a problem with that i've got a problem i love that
this sounds great just do it like fry bacon and then halfway through just put in okay i was gonna
say i was gonna say the bacon's gonna take longer to cook so you gotta put that in first but i have
one more there's one more i forgot there's actually a breakfast named after me um named after my real
name uh it's not the ben saint it's the perfect beverage for the chat on the go uh the ben i'm
listening the ben i won't say my last name even though i literally don't care if anyone knows it
uh uh but uh it's coffee coffee with a scoop of chocolate protein powder in it and that is a great
that is a great uh powerful breakfast treat that people people turn their nose up at the ben at
the ben saint guy's last name two two points the wonder you just don't want to say it first first
of all it inspired by that it's a bunch of Polish gobbledygook that's why i don't want to say it
indeed it's a waste of everyone's time inspired by that drink ben i i have made my real name as well
which is just the same thing however it's slightly different and for literal like like kill yourself
you will die of a heart attack uh yes i guess the the toby fox an excellent yes yes an honor as
always to have you here today here's if you want to be awake and also you're a fucking disgusting
fat freak you take a scoop of chocolate ice cream and you put like two shots of espresso in it there
you are going to be awake and also it's delicious i eat it it's a great uh all right all right all
right you idiot it's extremely important about your fucking breakfast extremely important
here's how you eat eggs you crack open the oak so the so the yoke spills out and then you dip
your pancake slash steak into the yoke so it's like a sauce of course that's exactly yeah runny
yokes are central ooh Nate Nate i used to i used to i used to think you were a big fucking weirdo
for liking your your yokes runny but i saw the error in my ways and i would never have many other
way and people if you are cooking your yokes you are just making your life worse just don't do it
you're just wasting eggs they're wasting that flavor don't do it okay uh now everybody shut the
hell up your your suggestions are terrible those are the worst because all that matters is that you
are meeting your nutritional macro goals in your breakfast that's all that matters so here's i'll
give you an option as well uh you have a bowl of oats just fucking steel cut oats you put uh uh you
can put strawberries in the frozen strawberries cook that in that's for flavor if you're a weakling
and need flavor like and that's fine indeed you can put sugar in but that's just extra calories
count those fucking calories you coward uh and then you have a thing of water and chocolate
protein patterns eat that all and i'll give you the option of having black coffee in addition
if you're weak and need that kind of thing to wake up which i i actually do now so uh there you go
that's it that's what you think it's all i have to say on the subject of things you can't say
what about what about what about tom though tom didn't come i'm just i i i actually am starting
to do the oatmeal thing a lot now uh because it's cheap and it's easy and it's fine and i don't care
i want to turn into a machine if i could if i could remove my sense of taste i would do it
it would improve my life dramatically absolutely but when i when i'm a weak boy i'm i'm fan of omelettes
i like making omelettes i make omelettes all the time they're good i need protein because i don't
eat meat because i'm a bitch so that's a good source and that's it protein and beans eat them
i get canned beans all the time it's the best i was doing that before it became a pcp meme
guys i i i would eat beans if you could eat them in an omelette could you do that could you do
like a bean omelette anything in an omelette do you eat burrito yeah no problem no friday burrito
i think they sell those fucking taco bell but beans are just delicious and especially fried or
something they're they're really good it's good shit it's good shit i'm all about the bean life but
i'm lazy and just eat them out of the can because fuck yeah fuck some parents things i don't
know who's got time for that it's like 50 percent of it i just don't want to do dishes later so i'm
like fuck i don't need a dish to get in the dish right here oh yes oh yes i hate no dish life that
no dish life oh dude all right here's the thing you're not allowed to say i like washing dishes
oh my god it's good what even are you i get it i get i can be relaxing it's not the worst thing
in the world and like as chores go it's probably one of my no no no this is where this is where i'm
gonna pull a weird utilitarianism that's wasting your time that's wasting your time doing things that
don't matter he is right oh yeah you're just gonna do it again later it sucks i hate it and dishes
are the worst because i'd still rather just not use a plate i don't think i don't well i i i i like
it because of like the the the therapeutics sort of like i can just sort of like zone out while
doing this it's it's as opposed to just vegging out watching a youtube video like it's it's you
know the same amount of work is getting done in that i'm trying to relax i think you're maximizing
your your happiness levels by watching something you enjoy as opposed to like doing a monday attack
i mean i would i would like to listen to you to watch what i would do well yeah i mean i could do
both i just i just like the the relaxing and the like sort of like standing there like the sound
of water it's it's good it's good for my soul and therefore good for my motivation and productivity
i eat i'll grant you it even though i don't agree i i i like cook soup i like boil the soup
and then i eat it directly out of the pot i will never use a bowl ever because you have to handle
on the pot yes it's true it's more convenient you're making it less convenient by using a bowl
yeah yeah just eat it right out of the fucking crock pot or whatever why not why the fuck yeah
there's no reason not to thank well i don't know america let's let's wrap it up everybody uh
thanks for listening everybody all right patreon slash the procrastinators uh please give us money
five dollars to get the bonus episodes uh what was the last bonus episode about i can't fucking
remember alcohol alcohol alcohol yes we got drunk and by the time you hear this one very much it'll
only be a couple days until the next one's out so get ready for that motherfucker so you want you
want to you want to you want to hint you want you want you want to tease get my head muchy give me
the next the next the next epic battle that that will come into the fucking ring and like like
two will enter only one will leave the most fucking star star spangled banner fight you'll
ever see in your entire life american versus american pure rod blood patriotism it is charlie brown
versus in yasha i came up with this one myself i'm very excited to unveil it and have them fight
to the fucking death i think they're equal in power and raw cultural impact so if you guys want to
hear the awesome battle you have it's five dollars on patreon get access to all the bonus episodes
there's that's right eight of them right now that's correct eight so far so this will be number nine
also you can listen to all these podcasts on itunes and on google play just search the
procrastinators two words because we're going to trademark that shit right and there you go
that's it give us your money give us your time merch we got a little merch you want to buy a piece
of me merch down below click on that shit and follow us on the twitter at tpcrastinators so you
can ask us questions there in addition and get updates and whatnot and of course subscribe to
the channel because there's more than just the podcasts on to your my fam there's lots of shit
so we'll see you in that one on your facebook your personal facebook where your family and friends
will you will see it please let's please show this to your mom especially this episode where
you want a red pill your your buddies this is the episode to post my friends indeed let let us
take the brunt of the blow from your your your your deep racist inclination public service this
episode was you know what you know what can i uh can i make an announcement at the tail end uh the
the champion's done and it's out it's out today let's yeah i've just i've decided well i've decided
right now that i'll fucking publish it the day this episode comes out that's a good thing that'll
maximize your back so excited so if you're listening to this uh go check out saint comics
dot com and read the full fucking chapter one of the champion that i worked on for like 18
thousand years i can't wait for the future when that's happening read read and play it because
you know oh it's a multi-media experience i'm pulling a home stuck i see i'm pulling a little
home stuck i'm making a little undertale you know no big deal all right thanks everybody for listening
we will see you next time bye see you later you yeah yeah
i am an asshole i am a stupid i've got a deadline don't want to do it