I'm going to bless that guy. That son of a bitch.
Hello everyone, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's Ben Saint, it's Gibbontake.
And we've got a robot guest today.
Excuse me, I fucked it up.
I fucked it up and then I also swore in the first five seconds of the video, so the channel's going down.
This is Twitch from Reploid Revo, the Mega Man YouTube channel. Welcome to the show.
Thanks, I'm super happy to be here. Thank you so much.
Thanks for reaching out on Twitter to say you'd like to maybe talk about Mega Man or something sometime.
And yeah, I did. You know, this week, famously, this week I put out...
Twitch, you've got to understand, for the past six weeks or more on this show, I have every episode I've been saying,
I think the video's going to be out this week. This is definitely the week that it's done and I'm putting it out.
So it's finally happened, that's the context.
You know what, I'm guilty of that sort of thing too.
A highly anticipated video on my channel is Time Skimmer Episode 6, where I finally begin talking about stuff that happens after Mega Man X4.
And famously, I was like, yeah, it's going to be coming really soon.
And then it never came. And the reason why is because I wanted to get a set of animatics made for it, depicting the battle between X and Zero.
And I even got it voice acted. I got Lucas Gilbertson, the voice actor for Zero, to come and record lines.
It was a whole big to do. But then it became an entire animation.
And the person working on the animation, granted, it takes a very, very long time.
So it just kept getting pushed back and pushed back and pushed back.
And now the animation has been abandoned. And so I waited several years for this and now there's no animation.
So I'm going to go ahead and go forward with just releasing the episode.
You got to scale it back, yeah.
Yeah, unfortunately. But you know what? It does mean that that blockage is not there anymore and I can finally continue with the rest of the timeline.
I can only do so many. Who exactly is in what exactly is in a row?
Mega Man.
Yeah, Mega Man.
Gib, how many Mega Man's did you play? You said you played the first one.
I played a bit of the first one on the Wii virtual store and it was hard. I couldn't get past anything.
I think I beat Cut Man once.
That's a par for the course for Mega Man 1.
You just got to get the magnet beam.
What could that possibly be?
You just got to, is it not selfish? It's a magnet. That's also a beam.
Yeah.
There's one tool in Mega Man 1 and it's the magnet beam and it just lets you place platforms wherever you want basically.
So it's a big help but it's a little, I think it's in Crash Man's level.
No, it's in Magnet Man. I don't remember where it is.
Crash Man is 2 and Magnet Man is 3 so those are definitely not correct.
Wait, it was Guts Man that's Cut Man.
What the hell am I talking about? Yeah, you're right.
It's in Electman stage? I could be wrong.
I don't know where it is but the bottom line is it does make platforms but it's also very janky.
It's pretty janky.
The way that it works is that it creates a platform for as long as across the screen as you're holding the button down.
So the longer you hold the button down, the longer the platform is.
But as soon as you let go of that button, a timer is ticking down that you can't see.
It only lasts for like, I don't know, like 2 maybe 4 seconds tops and then it just vanishes.
And if you're standing on it when it vanishes, you unceremoniously plummet like a cinder block to the bottom of the screen and die.
Yeah, if you put it, you can shoot one out and then jump on it and then you shoot another one out quickly and then you jump on that
and you shoot another one out quickly and then you jump on it and if you do it quickly, you can cross pretty much any gap.
See, I vaguely remember, maybe I did find that and I used all of the energy points or whatever they're called, the PP for that thing.
And I ran out.
You gotta consider the energy points.
Is that what they're called?
I think they're called weapon energy is to generally agreed upon term.
It's like the secondary meter for the things that are not your health.
If you're reading one of the manuals, it's called a belt buckle for some reason.
What the magnet beam is?
No, just the weapon energy.
What?
Because they look like little buckles?
No, they don't.
I don't know.
Oh, the drops.
The drops kind of do.
Drops?
Yeah, they look like little lemons or like a big lemon sometimes.
I don't know if I have the picture anymore, but there's, I don't know if it's in the English manual or if this was on like a blockbuster pamphlet for renting the game.
But they absolutely were trying to describe the game and a lot of it doesn't make sense.
It says something like press down to crouch and I'm like, you absolutely cannot crouch in any Mega Man game until like the year 2000 or next five.
So that's a lie.
I read some of the translated guides, like the Japanese guides.
And some of them are very different, some of them are very funnily different.
The English ones are just, the English ones are just bad.
They don't explain the game properly.
They call the city Monsteropolis for some reason.
Yeah.
Calls the, calls the robot masters.
Like robotic humanoids or something or no, robot like humanoids.
It calls them.
Yeah.
I know there's a handful of really weird English.
Well, you know, it's funny because in Japan, Dr. Light's robots, the robot masters are not actually called robot masters.
I think they are just called like humanoid robots or something to that effect.
No, in the first one, I know they don't call them humanoid robots, which would be correct.
They call them robot like humanoids, which doesn't make any sense.
Right.
And then in a lot of the English manuals, they were just like, oh, they have human faces.
Therefore they are cyborgs and they just converted everything to cyborgs because I guess it was the 80s and cyborgs were in vogue or something.
Sounds cool.
I saw one.
I really wish I could find it.
But I have like scans of this manual and it's like, you are Mega Man.
Last creation of Dr. Kine after he was murdered by his evil lab assistant, Dr. Wiley, spelled with like an E.
I know they spelled it Dr. Willie.
They spell it Dr. Willie a couple times.
Yeah.
Dr. Wright and Dr. Willie.
I mean that I can, I guess forgive.
But Dr. Kine, I've seen Dr. Kine and I'm like, what are you?
K-I-N-E.
K-Y-N-E.
Very, very strange.
I was telling Gif that she should play two because one is hard and it's kind of bad.
You should play two and just get the metal blades and then the game's easy.
Yes.
That is accurate.
Yeah.
Because two is the best selling Mega Man game of all time up until like a month ago.
Up until a month ago when Eleven just knocked it off.
Don't.
Shocking.
The manual by the way.
Because two is when they actually figured out like how to make, two is when they hit the formula and they made like the first good Mega Man.
I mean one is fine.
I'm not trying to shit on one too hard.
It's janky.
It's competent.
It's smooth.
It's not like polished.
Yeah.
But you can see what was coming.
And then three is kind of just easier in general.
They give you so many health drops in three.
Well, right up until the Doc Robot stages.
Well, yeah.
Three is they give you, they lull you into a false sense of security.
You're like, wow, I might actually be getting good at Mega Man.
And then Doc Robot comes in and he just ruins your day.
The robot, yeah, the robot master levels, the eight normal levels are easy.
And it get, you know, most, most of them get really hard at the end.
But yeah.
Yeah.
I see the belt buckles.
In bulk.
Oh, let me see.
Let me see.
Belt buckles.
Pick up the belt buckles to make your weapon.
The helmet adds an extra man.
Wait, propeller.
Oh, yes.
I forget what it's called.
There's an item in, it's a special item.
It's in Mega Man.
And I think there's only one of them.
It just gives you like a bajillion points.
Yeah.
It's the, it's like, it's a Japanese thing.
It's got a Japanese name.
Yeah.
And it's, and it's a thing.
It's like a Capcom puts this thing in like a lot of their games is like a mystery.
Yeah.
It was a power up or something in, I think in 1941 or 1942, like a Capcom shoot them
up.
And so they've just been putting it as like an Easter egg and other things.
And I know in other games, it's there and it like is like a full life and weapon
restore.
Yes.
But in this one, it just gives you points, which are totally useless.
Yeah.
Well, I'm so glad they dropped the points thing in Mega Man 2.
It's so funny that there's points in the first one.
Yeah.
And what, you know what, I think also makes Mega Man 1 harder because of the points.
That is now a useless pickup that is on the drop table for when you kill enemies.
In most games, when you kill an enemy, it's either health or weapon energy or nothing.
In this, now it's you have two chances for nothing and two chances for weapon energy
or health.
You know what I mean?
How did I forget that they call him Dr. Kine?
Like what the what the?
Well, I don't know if you had seen this particular thing because I think this isn't the
Yeah, what is this?
I don't remember the origin of this off the top of my head.
I know I have it in a video somewhere, but I think this is this might be a blockbuster
insert, like a little pamphlet that came with the game when you rented it.
Okay.
So I think it's not official.
Right.
Like it was one of those things that because blockbuster in place of giving everyone like
a complete inbox copy of a game.
They would often give you a pamphlet because back in the day, certain NES games.
I mean, honestly, we're just you couldn't play them unless you knew what you were doing.
So the manuals would often give you critical information on how to play.
And so to kind of circumvent giving everyone a complete inbox copy of a game, they just
whipped up these like quick little like pamphlets which like skimmed through the manuals.
I think wasn't wasn't there.
I think I've seen I swear I've seen a of a gaming historian video.
You ever watched the gaming historian on YouTube?
Occasionally.
Yeah, there's he has one that's about the lawsuit between Nintendo and blockbuster where
basically Nintendo tried to sue block really they wanted them to stop renting their games
because that that was like, you know, hurting their business model.
But the way but there was no legal way they could do that.
So instead they attack them on the grounds that the game manuals are like copyrighted material
and they're not allowed to to give those out.
And so yeah, I think it would think it might have been because of that lawsuit that blockbuster
issued a lot of like that they wrote up their own like yeah.
Oh yeah, that's that's totally a possibility.
Like that sounds like that lines up perfectly with this.
So mm-hmm.
I have watched like every gaming story and video that's ever been made.
Oh, wasn't wasn't there a Dr. Cain in Mega Man X?
Wasn't that the X guy?
That's Dr. Cain.
Dr. Cain is he's sort of like the Dr. Light replacement in X, but then he kind of just disappears
after X3 and is never heard again.
Well, I actually have a strong idea of actually where he ended up and this is the agreed upon
theory by most people who like care to know.
Okay.
So Dr. Cain forms the Maverick Hunters in response to the first handful of Mavericks
that appear in the X series, right?
Yeah, he like he talks to the council though, which we never see them all mysterious council
and they're like, maybe we should just stop making reploids and like, you know, is that
is that what they call it the council in?
Well, it's in the journal of Dr. Cain.
It's called the council and the interesting is the the journal is only English canon.
It's it was just made up for the English manual and no such thing exists in Japan.
However, I know that much.
Japan later adapted it and changed some of the details.
So it retroactively did come into Canada USA USA USA.
A rare instance of when English canon has actually added something useful because it didn't hurt
anything by adding it there.
So he he's like the council has, you know, met with me today and something something
considered stopping production of all reploids.
But I think that's a step too far.
So then he builds the Maverick Hunters.
So Dr. Cain is actually the leader of the Maverick Hunters.
He's running the organization up until X3, as you said.
And even though we don't see him in X4 in the English manual, which again, this hasn't
officially been adopted, but it says he created repliforce.
I know in the X4 manual in the English manual, it says that he is he was one of the he's
founded repliforce.
So he's not actually in the game.
Yeah, he's not actually in the game.
He's just kind of like mentioned, you can even in the yeah, yeah, yeah.
So so peep this, the official origin for sickness.
Remember, I remember you're talking about him.
He's like the leader of the hunters and he's like, well, he doesn't really do anything.
Well, yeah, it's cause all of his story happens like out of the game.
Yeah.
Apparently, he became leader of the hunters.
And this is exactly rough on paraphrasing, but this is as deep of info as we get.
He became leader of the Maverick Hunters after the previous leader of the Maverick Hunters
resigned out of shame for how the repliforce incident was handled.
So basically, I think it's Dr. Cain.
Where does it where does it say that?
Okay, because because I know that like he's the in five, he's the new leader, which
implies that there was an old leader.
Right.
And he's no longer there, but I don't.
Yeah, if you're going to kill me because I don't have this information on hand, but
I swear, I'm telling you, there's no entire channel of people who will back me up on
it.
I would.
I would love to see it.
I think it came in one of the.
So there's like these guides called like, like the Rockman X Psycho Dysacon guides.
And they've had they've been making them from X one all the way to like X five.
Are they like books?
Yeah, they're like, they're like, excuse me.
Yeah, they're like strategy guides.
Yeah.
They also include like bits of lore.
That's where we got the information for Iris and Colonel, how they used to be like one
Reploid and then they got like split into two because they have like conflicting personality
differences.
Yeah.
That's where we get information about like just like different, like random things.
Like sometimes there's motivations for the for the Maverick Hunters and also for the Mavericks
that you fight.
Like that's where I get the information about like Gravity Beetle and stuff.
Like I was brothers with Boomer Coanger.
I know I've seen some of these before.
What are they called?
Dyso.
I'm probably going to butcher the spelling, but it's Psycho Dysacon.
Yeah, I saw some of these.
Are these all translated?
I don't know if all of them are translated.
I believe most of them have been.
However, the person who did the original translations said that they did a pretty poor job and they're
like, don't trust these translations.
Like I'd like to do them again someday.
So, but, but it does seem to be information that has been like corroborated with like other
sources.
And so it's like not everything is like a hundred percent accurate, but I mean, like
it's the best we've got.
So, yeah.
But, um, yeah.
So the implication is that well, Dr. Cain is running the Maverick Hunters.
He's the only person we see running them up to X3.
It makes perfect.
It makes perfect sense that after, after the Red Play Force Rebellion.
The leader, whoever that is would resign and it makes sense that it would be Dr. Cain,
whether it's Dr. Cain or not, that makes sense.
But if it, who else would it be besides, besides Dr. Cain?
So, yeah, and since he's the only guy that we've seen leading them up to that point.
So he's just like, you know what?
I really handle, I really dropped the ball with Repple Force pretty badly.
That would mean that he was simultaneously leader of the Maverick Hunters and Repple
Force.
And he says no one man should have all that power.
So he resigned because he was a big gay fan.
He was a big gay fan.
He was right.
I can't, that's why, that's why it's all happened.
I just pictured now Dr. Cain listening to like a bunch of old Kanye West albums and he's like,
he's like, yeah, he was a genius.
He was ahead of his time.
But it's light years ahead of anything we have now.
He says, he shakes his head and he says, ah, too bad in 2022.
He went crazy and ran for president and came into submitting.
They call it the fall.
The fall started in 2022 and then, and then the Irish Rebellion of 2024.
Dark times ahead for humanity.
Boy, I would have hated to be alive back in 2022.
Yeah.
Oh goodness.
Sick.
I forget what we were talking about before.
I'm sorry.
I have a tendency to do that.
I just, I'm like a banana in a fruit smoothie when it comes to Megaman.
I'm a little, I'm a little, I'm a little.
Take over everything.
I'm a little abashed because, you know, I made this big video where I explained Megaman.
But like, I think I know in my heart that you probably know more about the subject than
I do.
So, well, I mean, I want to keep you off the subject to avoid embarrassing me.
No.
Listen, I'm going to tell you one thing.
You did a fantastic job and I'm listening, like actively listening.
And I'm like, you haven't said anything like wrong.
Like the only things that like, that I wouldn't agree with or that I wouldn't even call them
wrong, just things where I'm like, I kind of differ are points of, of like, it's kind
of like fuzzy where it's like, well, you could think of it any which way that you want.
Like there's no like solid answer for this thing or not.
You know what I mean?
So, I mean, at that point, it just comes down to like personal preference.
I used to be like way more like, like iron fisted about that sort of thing.
But I've since loosened up because I find that Megaman kind of does as far as established
as its canon and story is.
There are certain areas where it's like, nope, this is just a little fuzzy and you just kind
of have to deal with it.
Like, so a good point that someone brought up shout outs to Zan on my, on my Discord server
in the Lord discussion.
He, he mentioned, he brought up a good point.
He goes, what is the cannon way to play Megaman X five?
Oh, X or zero.
Well, not even that.
Do you collect all of the, do you succeed in collecting all of the enigma cannon parts?
Or do you just fire it and you destroy the, the space station in one shot?
Like, what is the story?
Oh, yeah.
Like in the history books, you know, do they, do they say, you know, matter of fact or X
and zero go and get all the parts and then they fire the cannon and it didn't work.
So then they launched zero at it in a shuttle and then that did work.
Or do they say they just launched both without, you know, without getting anything and it just worked.
Yeah.
Or did it fail?
Because well, it, well it can't have failed because that's true.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know the cannon ending is that zero doesn't go Maverick, but there's two different
ways that that can happen.
I understand.
Yeah.
It raises an interesting point because for once the story actually is determined.
Like in every other game, it's like, yeah, you beat all eight Mavericks and that's it.
But in this game, the Mavericks are literally optional.
So do you beat one Maverick and call it quits?
Do you beat, you know, like all of them?
Do you beat like two or three and then just, you know, launch?
I mean, even in X4, there's differences between the X playthrough and the zero playthrough
that, like, did, like, did X fight general?
Well, like in X's playthrough, yes, but in zero's playthrough, not necessarily.
You have to fight general as a zero.
You actually do need to fight him.
Oh, you do?
Yeah, it's guaranteed.
Damn it.
Okay.
The only thing that happens is in X's playthrough, you fight Colonel twice in place of a cutscene.
So zero gets the prepare yourself cutscene, but X just fights Colonel like for real.
Stop the coop now.
Yeah.
It's not too late.
Never.
I'm not gonna lie.
I didn't have nothing against that voice acting.
I thought they did a pretty decent job for the time, comparatively to, like, if you look
at, like, what they were up against, like, with Resident Evil and, like, some other horrible
games, it's not the worst.
No, you're not wrong.
You're not wrong.
I think, you know, coop is a little silly because it's like, okay, you literally said
the wrong word.
But I didn't have a problem with the voices they chose.
As a matter of fact, I think Shake Man explores the best.
I think if I was a kid, I probably would have just been like, yeah, cool.
Like, yeah.
Like, I didn't know any better.
That's just what they said.
Okay, I will say, I think General's voice is pretty bad.
I think.
Yes.
They picked a very, they picked, like, a reedy voice for a guy, like a 40 foot tall man made
of gold.
They think it should be a little deeper.
I think you should have a slightly more booming voice.
Yeah.
In my opinion.
He absolutely needs to shout, sound like some sort of, like, big shogun or something.
Like, instead of this, he's just, get out of my sight, you know.
We are the repliforce.
We must do this.
Remember, we will not defy the humans.
Yeah, like, I don't know.
He sounded a bit like Steve Urkel.
Gib.
You know, I don't know what their deal was.
Hey, you know, you know, yeah, well, that's just my problem.
In the game, General's voice sounds more like Lenny, even though Homer is the one who's
giant, who's the biggest man in the world and covered in gold.
Hey, Homer.
We're going to fire a space laser.
Hey, guys.
Notice anything different about me?
Hey, Colonel.
Oh, you're the biggest man in the world now and you're covered in gold.
Not a half bad Colonel, gotta say.
Thanks.
I like Sigma the most.
I think the guy, and you know what's funny?
I think the guy that did Sigma is the only one of those people who went on to do, like,
a really serious voice acting career afterwards.
Hmm.
He, how does he sound?
Sigma was chewing up the scenery.
He loved it.
He kind of just sounds like, um, he's sort of like, ugh.
Ugh.
Oh, my Maverick Hunters, what will you do?
You will, yes.
Why do you, why do you do this?
Why don't you kill him?
I forget, I forget any of his lines.
Um, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He sounded fine.
He's, he's, he's getting into it.
I think later on they made his voice a little too, like, not that there's anything wrong
with his voice being deeper in other portrayals, but I almost feel like it, um, it's a little
too breathy for my liking, I think.
I liked him better when, when he was speaking from the back of his throat and like a little
bit more Palpatine, you know what I'm saying?
Hmm.
I like that.
That's just, that's just me though.
Um, Gib.
Hmm.
Hi.
What's up?
Uh, nothing.
I'm just, I'm just, I'm, I'm, I have no way to, like, interact with this conversation.
Don't want to, don't want to exclude you.
Don't want to, don't want to apologize.
I mean, we can talk about the lecture because I have been watching that.
I'm like up to the Mega Man and base part.
Is that, I guess, I don't know if you have, you know, sorry, you know, as I've been saying,
I've been, I've been hyping this video up for, for weeks and weeks on here.
So, um, it's time, it's time to pay that all off.
But, um, I don't know if there's anything, if there was anything that stuck out about
it to you and you wanted to bring up, then that would be something we all would be familiar
with.
Or maybe if there was anything, uh, uh, maybe you could, as to anything you wanted to clarify,
me and, me and Twitch are here with our expertise.
Well, I mean, I feel like I, I feel like I haven't gotten to the really weird fucked up
stuff yet.
Cause I'm not.
Oh, did you not, did you not finish it?
I haven't finished it yet.
Oh.
I haven't had enough time, uh, spare.
Uh, but.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm just finished with like legends, uh, to.
I gotta be, I gotta be honest.
I love legends so much.
I, I love it now.
Uh, Gib, you should play legends.
You'd really like it.
I, I've seen legends.
It looks fun.
Also, just because I've been following this artist for a while.
Um, Arthur Vader has been making like an indie game that is like a Mega Man Legends-esque.
Oh, is that the, um, the Delta Gal thing?
Yes.
They took out Delta Gal.
Arthur Vader.
Big shout out moment.
Big, big appropriate shout out moment for that game.
Yeah.
That game looks fantastic.
Um, it does.
I, that guy follows me on Twitter.
I love the, um, the, the low poly PS one anime aesthetic.
Maybe we should, maybe we should, maybe we should ask him, maybe we should ask him if he wants
to be a guest.
Yeah.
You should.
He'd probably, he'd probably, he'd probably.
Okay.
All right.
Anyway, what were you saying?
But yeah, Mega Man Legends looks fun.
And it's of all the Mega Man games.
I, I like 3D environments.
I'm a big 3D person.
The graph, the graphical style is exactly what you always say you like the best.
Plus it's just a, it's just chill.
It's a chill time.
I think you nailed it when you said in the, in the video you said that, um, Legends 1 is
more charming.
And what did you say about Legends 2?
I said 2 is more, more epic.
Yes.
That's exactly it.
Um, I always, I got that exact same, that exact same feeling.
When I, when I heard you say that, I was like.
Bigger world in a darker tone.
Yes.
When I heard you say that in my head, I'm like, this guy gets it.
Like, that's exactly, that is exactly right.
Cause I always tell people, they're always like, which one is better?
Legends 1 or Legends 2?
And I'm like, guys, you can't make me choose like that.
It's a little bit.
Yeah, I didn't, I think, I hear people say like one better, but I think there's things,
there's things to like about 2 as well.
Well, yeah.
Like, so in Legends 1, like, and this is going to, I'm going to sound like a big, big old
sap here.
I played Legends 1 very recently, and my girlfriend was watching me go through the whole thing
and I cried during the ending.
I got like all emotional and I was like, oh my God, like these are people that not only
did I like figuratively grow up with in the game, but like I literally grew up with these
people in this game as a kid playing this in, what was it, 97, 98 when it came out?
That sounds about right.
Yeah.
And you know, so like you grow attached to them and I was explaining to her, I said,
if you play this game, you're stuck on one island, but you explore every single nook
and cranny of this island and you get to know the people on the island and every single
person has new dialogue when anything happens.
Like, I'm talking like, literally there's events that take like, I don't know, like
20 seconds tops to complete, and they will literally change their dialogue as soon as
that new thing has happened.
And so you're, it's more cozy.
You get to learn about these people's lives, you know, and like you kind of like become
part of the island.
You become part of their little community.
And when he leaves, it is like genuinely like all that when they're all, yeah, let's
talk, let's talk, let's talk spoilers.
But I don't give any spoilers.
Yeah.
When at the end, it's just like, oh, like I get it.
Like even though it's just like it's kind of like typical like sappy cartoony stuff.
Like it's the one time in like any sort of media where I was like, oh, like I feel what
they were going for.
It's not like, it's not like in other cartoons where they're like, you know, we'll see you
again sometime.
You know, and I'm like, they're never going to see those people again.
Like, yeah.
But like this is the one time where they had a scene like that and I'm like, ow, like
that's hitting me like square in my heart.
This actually like hurts.
Like it's like a happy sadness.
I don't know how else to describe it.
But then I play legends too.
And I'm like, this game, like you said, this game was more epic.
It's not bad.
It's not worse than legends one.
In fact, the gameplay is much more improved.
But the presentation is like, it doesn't have it does not.
It definitely doesn't give you like a cozy like, I know these people sort of.
Yeah.
Because you don't get enough time on each island to get to know them.
There's only one island where you get to actually like sort of get to know people.
And that's Kalbania Island with snowy one.
Well, the snowy one too, because you go there quite often.
So there in Kalbania, because on Kalbania Island, it's like that little one that's
like just got like the girl and her two brothers, like the two wild kids.
Oh, yeah.
And you kind of like get to know them a bit because you can talk to them often and
they send you letters back at Yashunka town with the snowy one.
And you go to the post office.
And so like you kind of that's a little bit of that.
But yeah, you're basically it's like a globe trotting adventure.
So you don't really have enough time to like sit there and get to know the people of the island.
Do you?
You know.
Yeah.
Did you ever play a game called Phenotopia?
No, I've never heard of that one.
Okay.
Well, it was a it was a Newgrounds game, but it was like a side scrolling action RPG,
a bit in the vein of Cave Story, but like without like gunplay.
But I played that a long time ago.
And then when I played Legends, I was like, wow, some even though even though this is
like a 3D free roaming adventure and that was like a 2D side scrolling action adventure,
there's something very similar about like the pixelated graphic style and there's something
because because in Phenotopia, you go around, you meet talk to villagers, you like do favors
for them, you find them stuff and trade stuff with them to like upgrade your equipment and
all that.
Mm hmm.
You explore ruins.
There is a sort of like secret science fiction backstory that with dark implications that
you uncover.
It's like this is this is just this is Phenotopia.
I was playing Legends.
I like this is just Phenotopia.
Right.
They Phenotopia just ripped this game off completely and Phenotopia is awesome.
They remade it.
They remade it on the on the switch.
It's on the switch now.
Really?
It's awesome.
I think it's called Phenotopia Awakenings.
I haven't yet.
I haven't played the remake, but like they did like a full like read.
I don't have to look into this.
It's a good child of Newgrounds.
So yeah, it was, um, it was like, uh, like Newgrounds.
It wasn't even just like some random guy posted it to Newgrounds.
I think Newgrounds like funded this guy.
Like they did like a big full page spread on the on the on the main page when it came
out.
Right.
They sort of did like a lot to do a little bit.
Yeah, a little bit.
That's awesome.
It's a good game.
It's a good ass game.
Yeah.
It sounds like a good ass game.
I think anything that lets you, any game that lets you like emotionally connect to a
10 PCs, um, I think it's doing a great job because you do feel more connected and you
feel more like satisfaction and more like, um, I'm not sure what the word is, but like
it's just a bigger deal to you.
Like it has more meaning when you like actually finish quests because not only are you getting
like, oh cool, I got the item to go give to the next person to go do whatever.
You're also getting an emotional payoff.
So like it feels good.
It's, it's Fino.
It's spelled like Phoenix, by the way.
So it's like P H O E N O T O P.
Got it.
Right.
Phonetopia.
Uh, gave you said you made it to the Mega Man Legends part.
I think I got, I think I finished that and then you were talking about Mega Man and base.
I was a little confused because you didn't draw a line was based made by Dr. Wiley.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's sort of a reveal like part way through Mega Man seven, I think.
It's part way through Mega Man seven.
I think I eventually draw that.
I eventually draw that line.
Yeah.
Base was made accidentally by Dr. Wiley.
Well, he, he's, um, oh, I didn't mention this, but like, okay, all the, all the robots have
the serial numbers and base is, base actually has a serial number, but he's not a, a light,
a Dr. Wiley number.
He's like a super Dr. Wiley number.
He's called like special Wiley number.
Yeah.
He's like, he's SW, he's SW.
I'm messing it up.
SWN.
Yes.
SWN zero, zero one or just one or something.
Whereas zero is, is, is DWN infinity.
He's not a special Dr. Wiley number.
He's just a regular Dr. Wiley number, but he's number infinity.
Yeah.
He's supposed to be like the end.
Like there is nothing, you know, there's nothing more than him.
You know what I'm saying?
Like that's.
Yeah.
I think that's kind of cool.
Whereas X, he's not a light number.
He doesn't have a serial number because he's not part of a series.
He's, he's his own person and his name.
A person.
Yeah.
And his name X is like a variable X because he has infinite potential because he can be
whatever he wants to be.
Oh, it's beautiful.
It is.
Like I've always had people ask me, they're like, what's X is a serial number?
I'm like, well, if it had to be anything, it would probably just be X.
But I don't think.
Yeah.
I think that would defeat the purpose of what light is trying to, trying to illustrate.
So I think he would just not give him a number at all.
He would just be like X, you, you aren't.
I said this in one of my videos.
X is not a robot with the ability to think like a person.
He is a person who happens to be a robot or something.
Totally.
What's this?
Sort of like X, if he wanted to, could choose his own name.
Yeah.
And that would be his serial number.
I'm just putting this here because you can see in teeny, teeny, tiny little letters.
It says DWN infinity.
You see where it says like Omega because you're dealing.
Oh, I see.
Bottom right.
It's a doctor dot W dot.
And number, number infinity.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Because this is an emission where I believe you're going to confront Omega or something.
And so the implication is that Omega is DWN infinity because he's inhabiting zero's original
body.
Is this where that comes from that he's DWN number infinity?
No.
Okay.
This is the, this is the first like in game confirmation of that.
But I believe it was another thing that was like confirmed in a, you know, on the back
of a soda can or something like that in Japan.
Yeah.
But it's a thing that's always been known.
Everyone's because I've heard that even since I was a kid, they were like, no, he's DWN
infinity.
I think, I think that was first confirmed around Mega Man X five where like the Wiley zero
connection was like, like right in your face.
There's no escaping it anymore.
I mean, arguably X four, but they don't really delve into it too much.
But that's when they were like really like, look, he's made by Wiley.
This is the connection.
This is what's going on.
So it was confirmed in a book somewhere and it's spread throughout like the, the old
early 2000s Mega Man websites that I used to frequent.
Shout outs to Mega Man Network and Mega Man homepage.
This is like into creates like they into creates loves their references.
So like they were absolutely going to be like, we're going to cram as much references in
here as possible.
That's a good one.
So that that's a good one right there.
And I don't have it handy.
I'm desperately trying to find it.
This is actually cut content.
I think you can find it on the cutting room floor in zeros like opening area where you
like the in-game cut scene where CL walks on screen and he's in his like little capsule
thingy when he's like hanging there with no arms.
Yeah.
So there's like the artwork of him hanging, but there's also like the in-game scene,
like where he's like where he's there.
There's actually a wall that they removed, I guess, so that you can see him better.
And the wall has the words like, like warning virus and a symbol.
And you can't really read that it says virus because it's like broken.
It's like kind of like, like, like messed up.
Yeah.
But the symbol is there.
And it's a symbol that's actually shown in the cut scene where zero is in the warehouse
fighting against Sigma.
There is like these canisters that have this symbol on it.
And then that this thing that says warning virus has the exact same symbol.
So I guess into creates looked at that cut scene.
It was like, that's the symbol to indicate like computer virus or something to that
effect.
Wait, which game was the cut scene in?
X4.
When?
Oh, when the, the anime one, when they're.
Yeah.
When they're fighting.
There's a, there's a spot somewhere either during one of zero's flashbacks or when he's
fighting Sigma, whatever that is.
But there's a group of canisters and they have this little symbol on them.
And like it's just there.
Like there's a background thing.
Like you didn't mean anything.
But then I guess not retroactively.
Yeah.
I guess retroactively.
They, they, they picked that out and they said, Hey, what if this is the symbol for the
virus that was in?
Yeah.
Exactly.
So it's funny because it's cut content.
So you never actually see it, but it does.
It is there.
And so I'm saying like, well, it's cut content, but what was their intention?
You know, so.
Yeah.
Totally.
Oh, that's great.
There's just like little details, you know, there's like way too many of those.
You could get there.
They're like, they're all over, especially in the zero games.
And then I mean, yeah.
Oh, man, I've after I finished at some point, I realized that the in ZX, I think it's in
ZX one or two, like the body of high leg or a buckle is just kind of like buried under
some grass somewhere.
I have one even better for you in the woods.
Yeah.
For the entire, there's a lot of bosses actually.
I don't have screenshots of all of them.
The high leg or a buckle was just one that I in game.
I noticed was like, oh my God, it's high leg.
It's everybody's favorite suitoroid high leg or a buckle.
Yeah.
What's the name?
That's so easy to pronounce and remember.
I mean, it's memorable.
It's a memorable name once you get your head.
Oh, this one.
It's cucumber.
Right.
It's a wire sponge.
Wire sponge.
What the fuck?
So I always thought this was cool that he's like dead, but he's like fused in.
So this is the Tower of Vendir in ZX, which is like or ZX Advent, I should say.
And it's like a giant organic tree thing.
I think I don't know if this is growing out of area zero or if it's like near area zero.
But it's interesting because wire sponge was part of a like a weather control thing.
And there's like these weird gross like organic vines that can like grow out of his stage.
Like there's like things that they drop.
So this looks like if one of those like grew out of control and I guess his body was just like merged with it.
I don't know how he got stuck there because I mean like he got blown up and then you fight him again in the Sigma stages for or I guess the X Hunter stages for X2.
So how did he get here?
I don't understand, but I don't know what the implications of this are, but it's neat to speculate.
That's just news.
Hell.
That's just cool.
They love their references, man.
I'm telling you, it's all over the place for better or for worse.
Yeah.
I'm like appreciating.
I'm like appreciating the screenshots.
Oh my God.
This is so cool.
There's so much implied history here.
Yeah.
Speaking.
Oh, go ahead.
I just want to say I think I think unfortunately I think I got to say that I think the part where in the lecture where I talk about legends is a little bit slow.
I think like I think it was I think that's kind of maybe like the low point energy wise in the lecture because I think.
Yeah, I felt like there was a few moments when you were talking about Legends 2 that I realized I wasn't listening for like four times and I had to go back.
And I'm like, okay, let me actually pay attention.
Like what happened?
Like who?
It's because it's because it's because like that those games, even though they canonically take place in the future.
They're like they're very they feel very disconnected from the rest of it.
So there's not that much in the terms of like like connections to be made.
So there's actually a few that I wanted to mention, which I don't know if you knew these and couldn't fit them in because I know that for for Legends.
I didn't think that it was low energy so much as there wasn't a lot connecting other games, but there's a lot to cover.
So I know you were kind of like going over a lot of it.
Like you're and this is not that it was any less good.
It was just kind of like you have to just kind of speed through it because there's just so much.
I think I was kind of trying to speed through it.
Which makes sense because I mean the story is massive, but here's something that I was surprised that you didn't.
Right.
So there's so much more dialogue in the Legends games.
It's like it's kind of got to kind of got to summarize all this.
So connecting ZX to Legends, I'm surprised you didn't talk too much about this.
Alright.
In Legends, the Master runs Elysium, right?
Yeah.
This big tall blonde man who lives for however many years, 3,000 years or something like that.
The Sage Trinity made up of those three smart guys.
They're also called Masters.
There's Master Thomas, Master Albert, Master Mikai.
That's true.
Yeah.
And on top of that, they are doing, I can't articulate it better than this because it's
not made very clear in the ending, but he's like something, something replates with human
bodies.
And what do you think we did with this and that?
And on top of that, Mega Man, or I should say Rock, Volnut, is called Mega Man Trigger,
right?
There's another Mega Man on Cadillacs Island called Mega Man Juno.
Yeah.
The people who use bio metals are also called Mega Man.
Yes.
It's like now a title.
Even more than that, it's only like brushed over really quickly.
You are not just a Mega Man, you are also named based on which bio metal that you're
using.
So if you're using Bio Metal Model Z, you are Mega Man Zero, you are Mega Man X, you
are Mega Man Thephnir, you are Mega Man Harpuia, Mega Man Phanta, Mega Man Leviathan.
So Mega Man has now become a title.
So there's not too much connecting them, but I mean, you got people called Masters who
are like, they rule over the society of people and kind of control, you know, human-reploid
relations as well as, you know, they have their own like backup of like human bodies
somewhere.
And then there's also the Mega Men who serve the Masters, just like how in Legends, the
Mega Men who work on the islands and things like that also serve the Masters.
So I think there's some sort of connection going on there too.
That's true and you put it like that.
And the kicker, which makes everyone kind of all their, everyone's brains explode, is
the very last thing that Thomas says is this world needs to be reset, which is not unlike
the Carbon Reinitialization Program, which will wipe out everyone on the planet and literally
reset the world.
It is like that.
So what they mean by this, I don't know, but I feel like I'm not saying they're like,
you can draw a straight line from ZX to Legends, but I'm saying that that seems to be laying
the groundwork for something that's going to come.
I think it's, yeah, you can, you could definitely hear that and be like, is, you know, he talks
about like he wants to like reset the world and create the next step in human evolution.
So is it, it's not, it's not that hard to imagine that he's talking about carbons or
the Anthro, uh, the Anthro units or pure humans or, uh, yeah, the stuff that becomes, yeah,
sure.
I found this out in my, uh, I have a series of three videos I did called History of Robotics
and Mega Man.
I watched those.
I watched those, of course.
I had a feeling because I heard you say a few things and I'm like, hey, I remember
I had, I watched a bunch of them and I, and I got enough from that I was like, I can't,
it's plagiarism.
If I just say these things, I have to, I have to shout, I have to shout this channel out
now.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
I was very surprised when I saw that.
I was like, oh, wow, look at that.
I'm hitting the big leagues now.
I was, I was, you know, I was, I was, um, I was looking for like Mega Man videos on YouTube
to get like alternate perspective, like, you know, just to hear what's like, hear what's
in the zeitgeist, hear what's like word on the street.
So I, and I think I found your channel and I watched a bunch of your stuff.
Thank you.
I'm very flattered.
Yeah.
And in the end I was like, well, I got it.
I got some key, I got some keen insights from this, from this guy.
So got to let people know.
Oh, well, I really do appreciate it.
It means a lot to me.
I've been trying to share your video everywhere that I possibly can because it's great.
Thank you.
Um, I got to, I got to celebrate.
I got to celebrate.
I did last night, it did hit the milestone.
It did hit a hundred K views in its first week.
100 K views.
Nice.
That's crazy.
I wasn't sure if it was going to do that.
Uh, I'll say, I was going to, I told myself I was going to be happy if it hit a hundred
K views ever.
Like, I thought it was not going to do as well as my previous ones.
I was, I was going to say in the Mega Man, in the Mega Man circles, your video is getting
everywhere.
I've had like a thousand people be like, have you seen this video?
Is it going to be good?
Check it out.
It's going to be awesome.
So like everyone knows about it.
In the Mega Man community, like everyone does, like, and I'm super happy that they do because
it's amazing.
I don't want to be like the only guy that talks about Mega Man.
Um, some people have even complained they're like, he's the only one that talks about
blah, blah, blah.
I'm like, okay, but that's not my choice.
Like I'm not like, you know, like, like monopolizing it.
Everyone's free to do it.
It's just, I'm the only one who is.
So, um, I'm really happy that there's more people doing it and I'm more than happy to
collab with other YouTubers, you know, who want to talk about stuff.
So.
A lot of people keep, you know, every now and then I get a comment that's like, obviously
a lot of people are like, where's battle network, where's command mission, even though I explained
in the video.
I saw that.
But that, but that's okay.
But that's okay.
I get it.
Nobody read.
Nobody pays attention.
It's fine.
Nobody reads the description and nobody pays attention to your opening statements.
Cause I do videos like who exactly is Mega Man and I give you like a 30 minute video
explaining the origins of Mega Man, his specifications, a buttload of trivia.
And then I still have that one jackass in the comments.
He's like, oh, you didn't talk about Mega Man EXE and I'm like, it's a different character.
Like, come on.
Cut me some slack here.
Hey, wait a second.
I'm sorry.
This is off topic.
I'm looking at that screenshot.
The wire spun screenshot.
Uh huh.
Okay.
You see that pillar.
Rewinding a bit.
You see that pillar in the background under the spike wall.
Yeah.
The angry face.
I'm sorry.
Is that Dr. Doppler?
It looks exactly like Dr. Doppler.
Yeah.
You know, you know what?
We found another reference.
It totally could be.
Like I'm not saying that it is, but I'm not putting it out.
I'm not saying it isn't because he's made up of nano machines and he's merged with everything.
So if anything is Maverick or evil, no, no, no, no, not Dr. Vi, although he does kind of
look like Dr. Vi.
I'm saying, oh, you know what?
You're right.
I think it looks more like him.
I got it mixed up.
You're totally right.
It has to be.
Who else could it be?
Yeah.
It's literally the only thing that makes sense.
It's literally the only rational explanation.
Yeah.
If you deny it.
I used to think Dr. Vi'll, or I always say Vi'll just to make sure that I don't confuse
him with Vi'll, the bad guy robot remix.
Yeah.
I said, I said wheel.
I used to say wheel.
I used to say wheel too.
And then people were like, no, it's supposed to be Vi'll because that's his name in Japanese.
I'm like, I know that's his name in Japanese, but I'm saying while because that's how it
looks like it should be pronounced.
So now I had some people say, I had some people say while now, I had some people say that
in German, it might be, it might be either Vi'll or some have said that it might be
Ville.
Yeah.
And unfortunately it's it's hard.
You can't even reference the original Japanese pronunciation to be like, well, what is it
supposed to be?
Because it's a totally different name.
Yeah.
That's kind of like the whole ballad or belayed.
I always go with ballad because in Japanese, I think his name is like Barado or something
like that.
Like it's got the, it's, it's a, what's the word I'm looking for?
The short a.
Yeah.
So that's why I always say ballad makes, I had a lot of keyboard warriors in the comments
slamming on their keys, like, no, you idiot pronouncing wrong.
I'm like, all right, sorry, dude, I'm too busy knowing everything else about Mega Man.
So remember here to pronounce his name, right?
You just got to pronounce it really wrong because it's going billiards or whatever.
Yeah.
You gotta do Billiards would be a cool name for a robot actually.
Honestly, what would have gotten the video even more views is if I just deliberately
pronounced all the names wrong because people can't help like, like, um, you get so much
interaction.
Welcome to my Megaman lecture.
Megaman, Pokemon, Pokemon YouTubers and like Nuzlocke, like FlygonHG does it all the time.
He like pronounces Pokemon's names wrong on purpose all the time.
Like, uh, uh, uh, like he calls Magnemite, Magnemite, and he calls Ninetales, Nenaytales
and stuff like that.
And I think he's doing it as a joke, but I'm sure it has the side effect of like,
Rattata.
Um, people just can't help but be like, he said, um, he said, uh,
Yeah.
He, why, why did he pronounce it Lucario?
Why did he say it like that?
Yeah.
I, I have to admit, um, I don't think I've ever done anything that egregious, um, but
I have absolutely said things that like, for instance, I saw you, you mentioned this.
There was a theory that saying like the star droids might not actually be aliens.
And don't get me wrong.
I did consider like, you know, maybe that is a possibility, but I purposely didn't double
back to say that, you know, like, no, they probably are aliens.
I think that's, that's what their intention was only because I knew it was going to get
people to comment and be like, they absolutely are aliens.
So it's, it's, it's kind of cheated a little bit, but I got a lot of engagement out of
it.
So I mean, what can I say?
I think, um, I didn't, I didn't set out deliberately to say anything wrong for engagement, but like,
I think the fact that my video is eight hours long and I say so many things, like I'm surely
I'll, I'll leave stuff out or probably get things wrong here and there.
Uh, and I think you did fantastic though.
Like honestly, all things considered, and I'm telling you as someone who I don't want
to say it's my job because I don't do YouTube as a job, but okay, um, as someone who spends
every single day basically looking into and examining Mega Man lore and history, um, you
did a fantastic job and I honestly don't think anyone could fault you given the size and
scope of your video for leaving anything out.
Like I thought you'd agree.
Anything that you left out, I didn't assume it was left out because of, um, like ignorance
and I figured you left it out because of time because honestly, like it's huge.
Well I think it's like you said, even if I did, um, even if I didn't get anything like
straight up wrong, there's always going to be things that like someone else interpreted
something differently or someone else or there, or there's vagueness in the interpretation
and it's like, well, someone's going to think something different.
But as a result of that, um, the video has gotten, it's got like for its view count,
um, it's gotten, it's gotten like a thousand comments, which is a lot, which is a lot for
a hundred K views.
Like I have videos that have like, I have a couple of the other lectures have like two
hundred K views and they don't have two thousand comments.
They have like eight hundred comments, nine hundred comments.
Right.
So I think, I think, uh, this is very, very active comment section on this one, which
supposedly, uh, which is great.
Yeah.
I'm already getting pulled into arguments in your comment section.
I left.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I'm not like actually like.
I have not been looking at my comments.
I know I said I would answer comments in the video and I, and I will go through them at
some point, but there's too many and I haven't like gone through them and like tried to answer
people's, uh, questions except for like one or two here and there.
Right.
It's just like, um, so I referenced, um, in, in one of my comments, I was like something,
Dr. Wilde or, uh, or whatever his name is, uh, love Lava lamp, man, um, he in, in X dive,
they have character bios that they release every once in a while and the character bios
as far as I can tell contain cannon information because I've actually been able to cross reference
it with other sources.
So it's like, oh cool.
So X dive itself, we all know is not cannon because it's, it's, it's literally a game
playing off of your nostalgia.
Like within the opening.
I was so relieved to discover that it's definitely not cannon because I'm like, this seems
like there's like an amount of content and it's, it's clearly just them having fun.
They're just like, Hey, remember when you used to play video games all night and did
this?
I'm like, okay.
So they're acknowledging that Mega Man is just a video game series and like it's not
right.
It isn't the story.
The story of X dive is that you, you basically play yourself, but like going into the computer
to like fix old Mega Man data.
You're fixing, you're fixing data.
You're fixing the memories of Mega Man, which is stored in a giant computer called the deep
log, which is the most unfortunate name for a computer ever log wall.
So it's basically, so it's basically an excuse.
It's basically an excuse to play through a bunch of like, what if like alternate Mega
Man scenarios with the goal of like fixing them.
Yeah.
They're just throwing cannon out the window to have fun crossovers and whatever.
And I'm like, I'm all for it because, you know, it's people are like, it's nostalgia
pandering.
And I'm like, yeah, you're just having fun.
It's not a serious game.
You know, it's not meant to be taken seriously.
Sounds like it might be fun.
I like, you can, you can argue like, oh, it's predatory because it's gotcha or whatever.
I'm like, all right, fine, but like just don't spend your money then.
Yeah.
Like I stopped playing, but even if I stopped playing, I'm still enjoying just looking at
the new character designs and models as they come out.
So like, I mean, I'm loving it, even though I'm not even actively playing in it.
I love the game, but, you know,
all this to just to mention that I mentioned that Dr.
Wild thing and people were slamming me in the responses because they're like, really,
you're going to accept X dive as canon, that that piece of crap game
that's all about milking you for money.
I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, chill, dude.
Like I'm not saying the story of X dive is canon.
I'm just saying that if all their other character bios are canon because I've been
able to reference them with other sources, why would Dr.
Wild's bio not be canon, you know, even though it's giving us new info?
I feel like that makes sense.
I. Yeah.
Because like, why would he be the one exception?
Like all the other bios are canonically accurate and there's sources for them,
except for his like, come on, like really?
I mean, you could maybe you could try to be like, oh, it's a different studio.
But like, Inti Creates is a different studio than the one.
But it's not a different studio anymore.
Or at least I don't think it is.
I think is it not.
It used to be Capcom, Taiwan.
But as I recall, I believe Capcom, Japan resumed development of it.
But so like, I think Capcom, Taiwan is Inti Creates made zero.
And I'm saying that it's not.
Oh, yeah. Inti Creates didn't make X dive.
So I mean, I guess you could say that, but like, that's dumb.
So never mind.
It's it's owned by Capcom.
So, you know what I mean?
Like Capcom owns the IP and even though they gave
Inti Creates the permission to make whatever story they wanted,
ultimately, Capcom still holds the reins so they can change it
to be whatever the hell they want it to be.
So, yeah, you know, so that is just the thing I'm putting out there.
I there was something else I was going to go off on.
I can't remember. But anyway, I just wanted to say, please don't attack me
for using X dive as a source. I'm sorry.
There's a lot of useful information in that game, even though the game itself is not can.
And I feel like that makes perfect sense.
That makes sense to me.
Like I learned another neat fact about X's armors.
Yeah.
So this was something that was only speculated on, but it was recently confirmed.
So everyone's always like, what happens to X's armors between games?
Why does he lose his armors between the games?
So originally, there was a quote from a developer somewhere for X4
where they're like, this isn't canon, this is just our personal idea.
But we think that X doesn't like holding onto weapons of war.
He only uses them when he needs to.
So that's why your weapons go away.
He's like, I don't need these anymore.
I'm going to get rid of them.
But they're still stored somewhere because in X5, he has some on the back.
Yeah, when you fight zero, he uses some of the X4 weapons.
But where did the armors go?
So there's actually another again, it's on the back of a milk carton somewhere.
It's in a newspaper, not newspaper, excuse me, magazine.
I think one of the Dysocon guides where for X2, it says that X found
another light capsule after he had the full armor and he stepped into the capsule
and it unequipped it from him where Dr.
Light then studied the armor and then developed the second armor from it,
which is why the first armor is not actually called the light armor.
That's like a fan name.
It's actually just called the first armor.
Second armor is also not called the Giga armor.
It's actually called the second armor officially.
And so everyone's like, OK, well, that explains that one.
But where's the third armor come from?
So Xdive, when they were doing a showcase of the third armor as a character
when it came out, they mentioned just like previously,
he turned in the second armor to a light capsule.
And then he studied the battle data from that and then developed
the third armor from that, which totally tracks because.
Makes sense.
In X1, you get the dash.
In X2, you get the air dash.
In X3, you get like the vertical dash on top of that.
In X2, you get like the double charge shot.
And then in X3, you get like an even bigger double charge shot.
So like, obviously, it's like an increment of what it's working on.
And then, of course, in X4, there's like, we don't actually know
what he did with the third armor because there's nothing no one said anything.
But it can be presumed that because they're all named first, second,
third, and then finally fourth, that he turned in the armor for the third one.
And like it got developed into the fourth one, which also increments.
I read somewhere that fourth armor was a mistranslation of force armor.
No, it's actually not a mistranslation.
In Japanese, it would be pronounced and spelled the exact same way,
which is why people were saying force.
You could technically translate it as both fourth and force.
But given that the previous three armors are first, second, and third,
fourth is the one that makes sense.
I guess I didn't I didn't realize that
because they don't actually like say they're they don't actually like call them
that anywhere, like they don't they're not really named in X one through three.
They're they don't get them.
Yeah, they don't mention the names of them in game.
The names of them come from other sources, of course.
It's always like a random source.
Another another weird wrench that they threw into it for some reason
is that for X3 for a while, even though it's the third armor,
they kept calling it the Max Armor and it's not the Max Armor.
Because as it turns out, again, I love my because Mac died.
Obviously, you killed Mac.
It's not Mac's armor.
He's dead. You can't just wait to lose his body.
It's stupid. It's ridiculous.
No, but I can't tell if you're joking.
Mac is X's best friend.
X's best friend of many years, his long time friend and compatriot.
Oh, it's great.
How cool of fate this is for to follow you yet.
I think I think I think you I think in you, your video about
like, how would you rewrite the story of X to give to give?
You would give Mac more of a but you would give him more backstory.
So when he betrays you, it actually means something.
I think I think I was riffing on that when in the in the in the lecture.
I make I make I make a joke about.
Oh, yeah, your close personal friend and confidant Mac.
Yeah, I mean, even if even if you weren't riffing on that,
you absolutely hit the nail on the head because that's how everyone feels.
There's been a long running joke between me and my buddy, Colman,
where every time someone mentions Mac, we're like, who?
Like, we just pretend we don't know who he is.
Never, never heard of him, which I'm going to call it.
Before I lose the weight, my train of thought, Max Armor.
Max Armor isn't the name of the armor.
It refers to having all of the armor parts.
And the reason why I know this is because
when they did the Mega Man Bandai Mega Armor series model kits,
the third armor was called Max Armor.
And what they really mean is full armor, because it was the only model kit
of the armor they had at the time.
So Max Armor was referring to the full set of armor.
And then there was other toys, which reference a full set of armor
for the X one and X two armors, and they also call it Max Armor.
So Max Armor refers to all the armor pieces, not understanding.
But everyone just kind of adopted it as like the name.
Do they say it in the game?
Like, like, does it show on a display somewhere that like when you've got all
the pieces, it's called, it says, oh, you've Max, you've Max on it.
OK, it does not.
It's literally just part of like, merchandise material.
It's like on a box, like for the model kit somewhere.
Like, that's it. That's all it is. So that makes sense.
But that's the reason I'm glad I cleared that up.
Because for years, I was like, yeah, the third armor is called the Max Armor
because in X four, it's called the Force Armor.
And then in X five, they got the Falcon and Chet.
But no, it's actually first, second, third, fourth.
And then X five and onwards, they start giving them names.
Yeah, because because they start being more than one in the game
and you got to like switch between them. Yeah, exactly.
So that's that's what was going on with that.
Yeah, uh, where should I apologize?
By the way, I feel like I don't mean to ramble as much as I do.
I have a show for that called Ramblin Reploids.
This is this is but I apologize.
I get passionate about about Mega Man and it just flows out of me.
I'm possessed by the spirit of X, you know.
Uh, I wait, I feel like I was going to say, oh, I was on the subject of the.
Oh, you said you Gibbs, you said you made it to the legends.
And I said the legends is a bit of an energy low point.
I just wanted to say that I think I to me in my opinion, the video picks up
energy around the time I'm getting to X around the time that I go on
like a big rant about how much I hate Repliforce.
I feel like that's I feel like that's kind of when I hit my stride.
I think you.
Yeah, because I think not only that, because like you, like you said,
legends is so disconnected from so many things, unless you know, like, where to look.
But I was really, I was really enjoying how unapologetically against Repliforce you are.
Yeah, I felt like it's more interesting if I like.
I feel like it's more interesting if I take a hard line
and I'm like everyone's very waffly about whether or not Repliforce is.
I mean, and I like you can tell you can tell in the game they were going for
like a sort of morally gray both sides are both sides are sympathetic conflict.
Like so they're so they're they're both they're both right and wrong.
Like so Repliforce is wrong for just being like, hey, man,
all your all of your robots are at the scene of the crime.
Can we like talk about this?
And they're like, how dare you?
I'm afraid we can't talk about this.
Yeah, just launch a full on war.
And then the Maverick Hunters not really X or zero necessarily.
But I guess I guess society is the problem because they're so quick
to label anyone who doesn't fall into lockstep as a Maverick.
So you could argue that Repliforce knows that no matter what's going to happen,
they're just going to be labeled Mavericks anyway.
So maybe they figured like we got no other choice may as well throw a revolution
right now, you know, I guess. Yeah.
Yeah, that's always been my argument is like Repliforce knows.
I guess it didn't really consider it from that angle.
But yeah, Maverick Hunters, if yeah.
They're they're quick to they're quick to call people.
If I guess it is they are the ones who are like, well, we've got to we've got to declare.
I guess they sort of start the conflict by declaring them Mavericks in the first place.
Yeah, I mean, I see that.
Yeah, I mean, X X or zero did their best.
They're like, listen, if you don't cooperate with us, you are going to be labeled as Mavericks,
which, you know, right is not only is it like, yes, that's the logical thing to do
because they're at the scene of a gigantic terrorist attack
and are basically refusing to cooperate with you.
But also it kind of speaks to the fact that like anyone can be labeled a Maverick,
you know, like it kind of does, you know what I mean?
Like I've always had the idea that as time goes on leading up to X for an X five ish,
I guess even all the way into X seven, that the Maverick Hunters are slowly becoming
like the judges from like Judge Dredd, like if someone doesn't obey you
or doesn't does anything to even slightly look at humanity the wrong way, you're a Maverick.
You know, by the I by the I mean by by X, but by zero,
like that's zero is like the logical conclusion of that progression.
Exactly, where the finally the Reploids were never equals.
They just finally it's like the true colors are shown where it's like, OK,
we don't trust Reploids, we're going to subjugate the crap out of them.
And if anyone disagrees with that, you're a Maverick,
whether you're a human or Reploid alike, it doesn't matter.
So it kind of goes to show how like the term Maverick can, you know,
it's not it's not really just it really just means whatever you think it means.
Yeah, it goes from it's not like the word criminal where it's like this person,
you know, committed a crime and they've been like convicted or something like that.
It's more specific than that.
Right. Maverick is just kind of like, hey, buddy, you're acting a little funny
or like, hey, man, you made some anti human remark before.
And I'm not sure I trust you anymore.
And so you can kind of see how it's like a slippery slope.
Once you kind of like start on it, you know, they're so they're they're basically
getting canceled for tweets, yes, human tweets, except instead of getting canceled,
you can blast it in the head.
They send they send the they send the cops.
Yeah, the robot, the robot police as they were almost called.
Yeah, they I mean, they pretty much they pretty much are the robot police.
Yeah, they were almost called that like in early drafts for the game.
They were called the robot police.
Maverick countries is cooler.
It is way cooler.
But I guess it all it kind of comes to the same thing.
Everyone I don't like is a Maverick.
Yeah, that's how it is, though.
That's what that's all this whole deal that really is.
Like, no, you know, Zero's line in Zero's line in Zero Three,
when he tells Vile, like you you sound like the Maverick.
Like, yeah, you're like you're like the king of the humans and like you're
persecuting everyone and then you call them reploids and then have them retired.
But like, you're you're the one that sounds like the Maverick,
like for being such a desperate for being such a such a just a psychopath about it.
I think who's who's the real Maverick here?
What a game. Exactly.
It is. I think I have some problems with indecorates storytelling
because in the games themselves, it's a fantastic quadrilogy of games.
But there's lots of other like minor details, which makes like a lore nut
like me, like lose my mind because certain things just don't add up.
But I won't get into those now because we'll be on.
No, I can think of one. I can think of one or two.
Yeah, there's definitely a handful.
But I do think it is beautiful in that
you can kind of see how the term Maverick gets applied more and more liberally
throughout the series until finally it reaches a point where humans are like,
yeah, we don't trust you, which sucks, because as you mentioned,
there was a point where X was like kind of like ruler of the rest of the world
for a little bit and everything was like cool and sweet and everyone
was like singing Kumbaya and it was awesome. Yeah, definitely.
And then and then Dr.
Dr. Weil is like, how about no?
And he he like actually I don't know if you mentioned it,
but it is part of the story, which, again, is not explicitly stated in the games.
I don't think he manufactured Mavericks to attack places
after X's. So they're OK. Let me know.
I didn't. I don't even remember that.
OK, so this is again, this is this is why I say I don't like
intercreates is storytelling, because there's lots of key details,
which contextualize a lot of things, which are just not in the games.
That's no, that's definitely true.
Like the fact that I had to go and listen and listen and listen to it.
But like there's you have to listen to the audio drama
to know who like where El Piso comes from and why he has the baby elves.
Yes. So this is actually about the baby elves.
Dr. Weil develops the mother elf with
Ciel's great grandmother or whoever the hell she is.
I'm going to I'm just going to call her Alia.
It's Alia. I'm just going to say it.
We're just going to go ahead and say it's Alia.
All right. He's developing the mother elf.
I mean, just because that's what I choose to believe.
I think it. I think it. Yeah.
Why not? Why not? Why not?
They got the same hair. They got the same color eyes.
They're both pink, whatever.
So he develops the mother elf and
wisely, the human government of the time of the world.
We'll just say the world governments are like,
how are you going to use this thing?
So everyone kind of submits their own ideas for how they're going to use
this reality bending digital deity that they've created.
And X says we should use it for its intended purpose
and just remove the sigma virus from the world.
And if any other viruses ever come up,
we'll just use it again to get rid of them.
And that is the only thing we ever use it for.
The moderate position.
Yeah, he's like, that is the only thing we use it for.
It is only it was designed to stop viruses.
We only use it to stop viruses.
And Dr.
Wila was like, well, actually,
Reploids are the cause of literally all the conflict in the world.
And I can't say that he's wrong.
Like he's kind of right.
So he's like, instead of using it to get rid of the viruses,
number one, we get rid of the virus.
And number two, we then use it to mind control all Reploids
and revoke their free will so that we control what they do in the world.
And so there's no way I did read this.
Yeah, this rings a bell.
So he he wants to control all Reploids.
In the end, everyone, you know, is like, I don't know, that sounds kind of evil.
And so so they go with X's plan and they're like, OK, so X,
we're going to go with your plan.
And I forget how they do this exactly because I thought they needed
zero's original body to control the mother elf.
But I don't know if Omega is a thing at this point, but either way,
the point is they do erase the Maverick virus and or Sigma from the world.
And then everything is happy and great and everyone loves it.
So Dr.
Wila's like, well, you know, I don't like that.
I think my plan is the right plan.
So he goes and makes two copies of the mother elf, which are the baby elves.
And then when he has those,
he uses them to start manufacturing Maverick uprisings,
basically mind controlling Reploids to go and commit crimes.
So he's like, see, look, like the giving Reploids their free will.
It doesn't solve anything.
They're going to always rebel against humanity.
It's evil. We got to control them.
And so the government.
I feel like there are parallels to be made to the real world here.
Yeah.
So he's like, see, I've manufactured a crisis, although no one knows that.
And therefore you should give me control of the mother elf.
And I'm going to enact my version of the plan.
And so the human governments are like, and he also it's briefly mentioned,
but he did have conspirators like on the inside that helped him.
And so they were like, OK, we're going to go ahead and give you
Zero's original body to control the mother elf and do whatever it is you want with it.
And that's where Omega comes into play and gets put into Zero's body.
And then also how he controls the mother elf and means.
Yeah, no, no, go on, go on.
So and so basically once he has the mother elf, he's like, Tee he, I'm just kidding.
I'm not going to just control all the Reploids.
I am also going to wage war on the entire planet and just rule it
because I am a power hungry, crazy person inside of a lava lamp.
It makes it makes perfect sense.
If that's where if only it were actually in the game.
Yeah, exactly.
And so that's where the elf wars come in.
And that's why they were so devastating, because they were literally
waging war, not not just with the mother elf, but the other sides were fighting
with their own cyber elves that were developed from the mother elf.
And so each side is lobbying these reality bending super weapons at each other.
You know, and just I mean, that must have been one hell of a battle.
Like there's literally a cyber elf that can turn people into metools.
Like, could you imagine like one day you're just a soldier on the field,
you're shooting at guys, you're dipping and ducking through trenches.
And then all of a sudden you just become a metal.
Well, yeah.
So so that's that's basically what happened.
And then so X is fighting back and he's like, this is ridiculous.
Holy crap, how did you guys let this happen?
And so that's when they wake up zero and put him inside of that copy body.
And then he he fights back with X.
They defeat Dr. Wilde and Omega.
And then that's when everyone's like, OK, X, you were right the first time.
We're really sorry.
You just you rule the world at this point, because we know that you're good
and pure and you're the best little cupcake out there.
And so then he does.
And then everyone is happy and everything's perfect for a little while.
It does make sense.
I think I was a little I was a little fuzzy on some of the details of how it
shook out and it is it's there.
This is this is from like the drama CDs, right?
Yeah, it's like drama CDs, external sources, like the art books.
A lot of this is in official complete works.
A lot of it is also on the now defunct, although I guess still considered canon.
Mega Min zero collection, official timeline website,
the official timeline they had on their thing.
Yeah. So that's basically how that happened.
So yeah, everyone's like, yeah, we screwed up X. We're sorry.
And that's why instead of just killing, yeah, instead of just killing
why, like they should have, they were like, what you have done is so bad
that we're going to punish you harder than just killing you.
We're going to try to make you suffer every single day.
And this will absolutely not bite us in the ass.
I understand the sentiment, but I don't think it was maybe the the optimal play.
Yeah, it was.
And that was the thing that apparently was like kept secret
because like they knew that it was illegal and they shouldn't have been.
They should like it was supposed to be that highly illegal.
So and that's why like when you were saying he comes back and copy X mark,
too, is like, well, it wasn't an illegal exile.
It wasn't illegal exile.
They did it wrong.
They didn't follow the correct procedures.
It's fine, guys.
Like I think he basically like says exactly that.
He's like, yeah, I didn't follow the rules.
No, they did it.
They did it sneaky.
None of that didn't count.
Didn't didn't count.
We give him another chance.
Kiwi Hermans's way.
Yes.
Into power.
Stands up in the town hall.
Yes.
My name is Dr.
Leuve and, you know, like Mr.
Mr. Burns doing that.
I'm I'm Mr.
Snrubb.
He's just like he's got a fake mustache on his lava
length, lava, lava, lava.
Yeah, exactly.
I think I think it was not according to protocol
that Dr.
Vile was exiled.
So we should we should give him another chance.
Exactly.
It was totally and you know what?
I mentioned this.
I have like a meme video I did.
It was like I summarized the entire Mega Man
timeline in like 18 minutes.
It's just me screwing around.
But there's a there's a part where I mentioned
I'm like the four guardians are a bunch of
dumbasses for letting this happen.
And I'm like, yeah, they really are.
Like like I know I was joking, but they really
are dumbasses for because they were they were around.
They were around.
They were around for watching because when
Copy X was made, that's when they were made as well.
So like Copy X and the four guardians were built
around like the same time.
I don't know which ones came first, but the point
is is around the same time.
So they got to watch Copy X rule like a toddler
over all of human civilization.
And he's just like, there's an energy crisis.
Replies use energy.
Replies aren't allowed to get any more energy.
And instead of any of them raising their hand
and being like brilliant, brilliant, sir,
I think there might be a problem with that solution.
They were just like, yes, of course, your highness
and just let it go.
And I'm like, you know, I feel like at any time
they could have stepped in to solve this
if they just used like their brain a little bit.
Like why would you make them perfectly loyal to Copy X?
They said, yes, sir.
Mr. X, sir, you're saving humanity.
You know, I'm so glad you bought Twitter.
You know, you're saving the world.
You know, your self-driving cars are really good.
Copy X is like we're going to put people on Mars
or something like that.
Yeah.
He's building the orbital elevator.
Actually, I was going to mention,
Mega Man Zero does have orbital elevators.
It's not remarked upon, but they are there.
There's lots of orbital elevators
all throughout the Zero series.
As a matter of fact, I think in-
I know in Neo Arcadia, like in one of the endings,
you climb up a big tower.
Yeah, that's where you go and get.
You actually go in one.
No, three.
In Zero One as well.
I think that's area X, where you fight X.
It's you actually fight him.
You go through like a big elevator area.
I have a picture of it.
Hang on.
I do remember climbing a big tower.
I wasn't...
Yeah, you kind of do like sort of end up like in space.
Yeah, you end up in space somewhere.
Or at least like really, really high up
and you can see the...
Yeah, you know, I remember that.
I remember that and they don't really even remark upon it
other than that.
They don't talk about it much.
It's just a really high tower.
But it is there.
Oh, come on, where the hell is it?
I got pictures of it or in here somewhere.
Is it in this one?
I gotta say, before we go on with any more of that,
I just wanna say that I had a happy Thanksgiving
and I hope everybody had a happy Thanksgiving this week.
I had one, it was pretty good.
How was your Thanksgiving, Twitch?
It was good.
I went to go see my family.
Like I always do, we always go to my uncle's place.
We have been going since I was a kid.
Literally, I don't think there's been a single year
where we haven't gone.
So I've been doing that
since I was like single digits old.
So, it's cool.
We did not do like an extended family Thanksgiving.
Pretty much just hung out with my parents and my sister
and my dad's like best friend from a childhood came over
and then you just had dinner and it was good.
We watched a movie.
I think it's, we watched a movie called,
I think it was called Bullet Train and I hated it.
Oh, I've seen a clip from that
and I wanted to watch it based on the premise alone
and how silly it looked.
It looked, I just did not appreciate Brad Pitt's
twee, cutesy little quips and dialogue.
They were so irritating that I just decided
that I hated the movie
and then I couldn't take any of the action seriously.
I don't think it was meant to be taken seriously.
It was meant to be like a big cartoon.
But just annoying, just the twee Joss Whedon-esque dialogue
was really irritating and I just couldn't stand it.
The Whedonisms.
The Whedonism, yeah, yeah.
Ice quip.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for saying that.
Sorry that you had that experience
on Thanksgiving, the most holy of days.
And my dad, my dad is so impossible to watch a movie with
because he will literally, he'll quip
about whatever's on screen, like nonstop,
like every like 30 seconds.
Like he can't stop.
He can't stop making a little quip.
Even if it's just like, the bad guy comes on screen.
My dad would just be like, bad guy.
He'll just like say that.
And then like 15 seconds later,
I don't know, somebody gets shot and he'll go like,
he'll go like, oh, shot or something.
It's like, shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Dude, great quips.
Sometimes he tries to be clever with them,
but sometimes they're just like completely banal,
just like saying what he's seeing.
Why?
I totally understand.
So funny.
Just why are you like this?
It reminds me of, I don't remember.
I think I was watching Hollow Man when that came out.
It was in the movie theater.
And I was but a wee babby.
I don't know, I was like a kid, teenager, whatever.
And I think my mom was with me
because she wanted to see it too.
So we're in the movie and every time anything
remotely spooky or foreboding what happened,
there was this one guy who in a very deep voice
would just go, aw damn.
Like, but like the whole theater could hear him.
And it would always be like, aw damn.
And like, it just kept building and building
until finally something like actual,
I think like there were some boobs on screen.
And he was like, aw damn, like really stupid,
but I kept laughing.
Me when I see boobs, aw damn.
It was really dumb and immature, but I laughed anyway.
Yeah.
I think it's like a relieve the tension for yourself.
It's like you relieve the tension of what's going on screen
by quipping about it or just saying something.
Yeah, probably.
I've noticed, I've noticed I used to do that
when there was something like a romantic scene.
And I'm like, I don't wanna feel like feelings right now.
But what if they farted?
What if I like make gross lip slacking noises
to like undercut the emotional resonance
of the scene I'm watching?
Yeah, I don't do it anymore though.
I try to allow things to affect me because that's better.
I had a moment recently like that
where I was watching the Wachowski Speed Racer movie,
which I love, I love that movie so much.
I saw that when I was younger.
I saw it when it was fairly new
and I remember thinking that it was great
and then I heard that it was really bad.
And I was like, what the fuck are people talking about?
I, I, but, but culture has come around.
Culture has vindicated me.
I think we as a society have decided
that actually it's amazing.
We're now ready for Speed Racer and what it has to say.
It was fun.
It was way fun.
I loved the movie.
I thought it was great.
The visuals were incredible.
Action was well choreographed.
I loved some of the neat stuff they were doing.
I love the scene in the snow
and they're using the snow and the movement of the camera
to generate anime speed lines.
I'm like, that's so clever.
I liked them.
There's a, I remember there's a shot where like,
I think it's when Speed Racer and the girl like kiss
at the end.
That's what he has.
You know, and like, you know,
that's what I was building too.
Yeah. When you unfocus the lens
and the lights in the background like expand into circles.
Well, they do that, but they expand into hearts.
Instead, it looks like a floaty anime background.
And it's just fantastic.
Speaking of that scene, like you said,
commenting so you can kind of like relieve
the tension for yourself or you're like,
oh, I don't want to feel things.
I was, this is the only part of the movie
that I was disappointed in.
I loved Spritle in the movie.
People are like, he's just like a dumb annoying kid.
I'm like, yeah, but he's supposed to be
like a dumb annoying kid.
And he kind of sticks to himself.
He doesn't really interfere with the story much.
But there's one part at the very end,
just like you were saying,
where Speed wins the big race.
I know, shocker spoilers.
And he goes to kiss Trixie.
And the scene freeze frames and Spritle comes on
and along with ChimChim, just as doctors.
And he's like warning, the following scene
may contain gross feelings and cooties
and something, something.
If you have a weak constitution, please look away now.
And I was like, okay, like it is kind of like a funny joke,
but not at the climax of the movie.
But also, yeah.
Like I was waiting for this.
They've been building to it.
And like Spritle like kept interrupting them
before they can like, you know,
get romantic with one another.
But like, I was into it.
I was like, wow, like I feel emotionally connected
to these characters and what they're going through.
And finally, Speed gets like, you know,
his well-deserved first place win
and he's going to go kiss Trixie
like he promised he would do at the beginning of the movie.
And then Spritle comes in and ruins it.
And I'm like, like, I,
I don't, I, yeah.
If you want to break the-
Sounds a little annoying.
If you want to break the tension for yourself,
like you said, by like saying something
or making a fart noise or whatever the heck it is,
you know, fine.
But it annoys me when the movie does it for you
because what if I wanted to be invested in that scene?
Now that I am like,
because now that I'm looking at it as an adult,
I'm like, I think Speed Racer is like a work of art.
I think it's great.
It has great messages.
It's got good, like it's just,
it's just produced really well.
Like everything about it is great.
So then I get to this end scene
and then I'm like, I get slapped on the face for,
you know, almost the perfect movie.
Yeah. That is the one and only like-
So close.
You know, so here's what I'm going to do.
I believe the music cuts as well,
but it resumes where it's supposed to.
I'm just going to go ahead and load up the file
into like Sony Vegas or something.
And I'm just going to cut out that part with Sprytal.
And I'll just have it resume uninterrupted for myself.
The Revo cut.
Yeah.
If I-
Isn't that the thing they do in like,
like some or most like Marvel superhero movies
where they sort of, they're embarrassed to be superheroes?
Like, isn't that like a, like a,
like what sort of power do you have?
Isn't that like stupid?
It was funny.
Like they say that in the text.
They like sort of embarrassed.
It was funny like once, like the first couple of the times
that it happens, like, you know-
Common isn't it isn't it wacky that we have that we are wearing spandex and
Yeah, it's like movies. Like what were you expecting yellow spandex? Oh
I mean
It was funny when you do it like once and I get it
Yeah, and so I give the X-Men a pass that was pretty funny
Like yeah, they would have matching uniforms like they're supposed to because they're like a team
But then the Marvel movies started doing it and like okay, I get it like you know
It's a funny joke, but then they do it in like every single movie like every single time a new hero gets introduced
They have to draw attention to the fact like huh, isn't it silly that I'm wearing this funny costume
And I have these weird patterns like dude. We're living we are now invested so insecure
Yeah, we're now in a universe where a purple alien man with you know
Tire marks for a chin snapped to the entire universe out of existence. I am ready to believe anything
You don't have to like like deflect like it's cool if you're a weird dude who wears a bug costume like I'm
I'm ready for it now. It's I've
I'm cool with it. I am I am I have not seen a Marvel movie since
I don't even know how long I'm I'm free. I'm pure
of its
Malif Lewis influence
The last one I've watched also I can't I can't call them shit because I haven't seen them
I can't complain. I only kept I catch that from like people saying it and also remembering
Like certain scenes where they're just sort of like, you know comic books were from the the 1950s and those were so strange
Huh? Hey modern audience. Don't you find that cringe? Well, enjoy it anyway, but also
Don't don't feel too bad about enjoying it. It's kind of like how
Using speed racer as a great example of this
um
speed racer is
Impinibly campy and silly
But the movie has internal logic to it where they don't acknowledge that things are campy and silly
Yes, that is just their world and the the characters the characters are serious about what's going on
Yeah, and so I'm like, yeah, I'm fully invested in this. I am totally okay with watching
A movie about a guy whose first name is speed and his last name is racer and is
No problem brothers with someone named sprightle, which is not a name. I think I've heard
Ever uh, and they have a pet monkey named chimchim who is also super intelligent like I'm cool
You I'm already sold. You don't have to like
You don't have to be like, haha, isn't it funny that his name is speed like no like I get it. Yes. Yes. Yes. It is
That's why I'm watching the movie. Yeah to be entertained by this
Stop drawing attention to it. Let's let's just take that and run with it. All right. We don't need to wallow
We don't need to wallow in the premise, please. It's kind of like when people engage in like, um self-deprecating humor
Um, but it might be funny once or twice, but once you do it
Too many times it's kind of like bro. Are you okay?
Like are you sure that you're not like actually insecure about yourself? Like, you know, you know what I mean?
And that's how some of these movies come across
So that's why I love speed racer because they just they're unabashedly
Cheesy and silly and campy, but they also treat it with like seriousness and reverence
um internally
And I'm like, yeah, I buy into it. I for
For just an hour and a half
I believe that miracles can happen on the raceway and I am totally
Hell yeah, and I am totally fine. I believe that love can bloom on the battlefield. Yes. Yes
And I he makes art when he races and I am totally fine suspending my disbelief and just
Enjoying that you don't have to
Tell me isn't it silly like I'm not watching a realistic movie. I'm watching a marvel movie
You don't have to sell me on it
Like you stopped being super realistic after like iron man one like and iron man one was great
But they they quickly realized that we're going to continue down this path. We are going to have to get
Consistently more and more silly and cosmic because that's just the nature of Marvel comics and that's fine
But don't draw attention to it. Just shut up. Give it to me. I'm willing to believe it
Just like how Godzilla was Godzilla 2014. Um, they try doing a somewhat realistic one where he fights king kong
Well, I'm getting to that. So the first Godzilla 2014 was the one where he fights the the mutes the
Mutated ultra something whatever organism. I don't know what the hell it stands for
Um, and they did a somewhat serious take on Godzilla where brian cranced in his wife dies and like a mudo escape
All that other crap. So like I'm fine with that. The first outing was like
Kind of serious much like the first Godzilla movie was meant to be taken somewhat seriously
It had it had a lot to say. Um, but then as they continue down the Godzilla rabbit hole
quite literally
They realize. Oh, yeah, these movies are going to have to go in a very silly direction because the nature of Godzilla movies
Get a little silly. Um
So the tone in Godzilla 2014 versus
Godzilla versus king kong is stark contrast to one another
They and I and I'm glad because they don't really draw too much attention to it
They just fully embrace the fact that um, there's a hollow earth that's always been there and there's portals
And there's monsters everywhere and we're just not gonna internally
We're just gonna accept that this is reality and we're not going to like
Wink wink at the audience and be like, isn't it crazy that all those? No, just shut up. Let me enjoy my monster wrestling match. It's fine
It's fine. I'm willing to I'm willing to accept it
I gotta use the bathroom. I'll be back in a minute. No, you're not allowed. No, it's okay. Go ahead. Okay. All right
You're right. No, I'll just if you say I wish
You must answer me my riddles three
All right, I'll be back in one minute
So how are you given I'm glad to be here
Yeah, it's great. I'm glad to have you you don't worry about rambling because that's
That's what people crave. They crave large
Long conversations about I get nervous because uh, I have a tendency to talk way too much
And I I have a tendency to accidentally talk over people and I don't mean to I'm just I'm very passionate about the things
We're discussing and so it's not I'm not trying to be rude. I'm just excited
No, it's great. It's it's don't worry about it. Okay. I um
I I'm good. I I I did zone out a few times where I'm like, okay
So many of these these things being talked about are like I don't even having the faintest idea what it means
But that's okay. I'll I'll watch the lecture. I'll definitely play legends because that looks fun
Legends is a lot of fun. Um, my recommendation for legends
This always helped me some people say they don't like this, but
Everyone's like, oh the controls on legends are like tanky and crappy, but uh, if you go to the options, you can actually switch
Um, because there's dedicated buttons for strafing and there's dedicated buttons for rotating
And so I always set my rotating buttons to just left and right on the d-pad
So that I can navigate with one hand and if I'm going to strafe I use the shoulder buttons for that
Um by default, it's the opposite left and right actually make you
um
Actually make you strafe and then the l and r is what you use to rotate
That just doesn't feel natural to me
And I feel like using your d-pad to run and also rotate and point in the direction that you want to go in
That just feels more
Like normal to me. So that's just the only thing I would recommend. I think that's an easier control scheme
That's just me. Everyone of course is welcome to do whatever
Yeah, that's the one thing I've heard about that is that it's it's early 3d. So that there's no
Consensus on how you do the traversal in 3d and the controls are a bit odd. It's also so early that there wasn't even
Analog sticks. This was like an early PlayStation game. So the the dual shock controller didn't even like come out yet
Pre-ape escape. Yes, exactly. So
um, and here's the thing
Legends 2 did come out
Uh after the dual shock. So it does have analog controls, but it they're not actually analog controls when I played
um
I noticed hey, wait a second
I can set the right joystick to aim like a modern
Third person and or first person shooter game. That sounds amazing
All I need now is like a target reticle in the center of the screen. Um, but it's not
Actually analog what it does is it takes the up down left and right inputs of your joystick and just moves the camera
Like that
Um, it kind of just automates having to like hold down the look button and then pressing the the d-pad buttons
So it's not true analog
But I think that if you took mega man legends and just gave it like a proper
double joystick
movement and or
aiming scheme
Legends would would play like a dream like it actually
Once you've gotten used to the controls like I have
It's it's really fun
Like I know these like little movements to like move him in like a perfect circle
And I know how to get him like like tight circles. Um, so I can like collect all the the refractors really easily
Running and jumping and like grabbing onto a ledge feels so satisfying and then climbing up
So I think if it just had some modern controls on it, I think legends would stand toe to toe with like modern action games
It's just unfortunately
It was kind of ahead of its time and it came out
Before control schemes. Well, I mean, I don't even want to say it had a good controller
Yeah, I was gonna say it's not even a control scheme. There wasn't even a good controller for it
Before the dual shock set the standard for all consoles going forward
I'm trying to imagine
Because like I've played like ratchet and clank with like the strafe lock
So that's like you you're always strafing
Um, and you move you rotate the camera rather than
Like free free walking around that's pretty much how legends works except l1 and r1 is what rotates the camera
Yeah
I'm trying to like visualize like walking around because like um if I use a dual shock with legends
Will it recognize the analog stick as the directional buttons for legends one? It doesn't it just has no dual shock
Input at all because it predates the dual shock
So there's not even a way to have it recognize
Your your analog stick so you have to play it with d-pad
Um legends two you can enable
The dual shock controls, but they're not analog controls and that's the issue
So like the all it really does is let you use your analog sticks as a replacement for up down left right d-pad buttons
That's that's literally all it does at least as far as I can tell other people have told me that's not the case
But when I play, um, it it doesn't feel that way
Um, it feels like when you press
Like anything on the joystick it doesn't move
smoothly, it's just like
It's it's literally just cardinal directions on the on the joystick. Um, so I just play with him
Welcome back. I'm back by the way, but I didn't want to interrupt. Oh, it's all good
We're we're discussing how legends was ahead of its time and no one appreciates it
Yeah, yeah
The um the the tank controls are a little bit they take a little bit of getting used to but once you are used to them
It's it's fine. Yeah
If you do play legends one by the way, um another thing I recommend besides
Um messing with both control schemes
um, I also recommend
Grinding a lot in the early game because there's a very difficult boss rush that they just throw you at
Um
Right at the start of the game. Uh, if you hear them talking about pirates
Um, you've gone too far. Don't proceed back into the city. Please
Get a lot a lot of zenny and and buy power ups
You're talking about against the three dudes
Yeah, they make you fight, um the serve bots and they're the bloom bears and then you fight tron and then after tron you have to
Fight bonbon. Um, it's like a boss rush. It's very difficult for early games
Especially if you're not prepared for it. So save Austin. I do I do remember that
I did get
Yeah, that one did
I lost a bunch of times. Yeah, it definitely, um, it definitely pushed my shit in when I first played it. Um, but I then had the
Uh, the the foresight because I had a memory card, which is new technology to reload my save
Go to the dungeon and just grind for zenny and here's the cool thing about legends. Um
Legends too would change this but legends one once you can buy, um
Your your your health increase like by like one pip same thing for your your energy canteen, which will like refills your health
Um, you can just increase it forever. There's no cap
It'll just keep letting you increase it. Um, and it doesn't block it off based on what part of the game you're in
Um, so if you have the money, you can technically get yourself to like 200 health and the game won't stop you
You gotta you. Yeah, I think I forgot to use my energy canteen. I like forgot that I had it
But like, yeah, you got to be using the energy canteen. You you can't be sleeping on it canteen saves you
Yeah, gatorade. It's I'm just I'm the kind of gamer that I'm just get really focused on what I'm doing
And I forget to like use the I use the items in my inventory for what's there
So I have definitely done that a few times where I was like, ah crap. I forgot I could heal
You know what I used to do as a kid when I when I was fighting Tronbon
Uh, because she would kick my ass so hard. I'd run away from her and then go buy a soda out of the machine
In the middle of a battle in the middle of the battle
You could do that lol
You can you can literally go buy so you you're mashing through that because she's still shooting at you while the dialogue is happening
So I've had I've had times where it's like
It's a vending machine. It costs 100s any to get a soda
Do you want and then like all of a sudden a bomb just blows up the vending machine and like go flying and I'm like dammit
So I quickly run to where the next one is, you know
That is awesome. It's it's hilarious
Uh, I also found out you can just uh, you can kick the vending machines and it'll just give you a soda instantly
So I started doing that during the battle because it was quicker
But I also found that if you kick it too many times the vending machine explodes and then you can't use it anymore
But if you buy a soda from it, I think you can get like three refills out of it and then it runs out
Yeah, so uh, those are just I didn't know you could blow up the vending machines by kicking them. That's so
Yeah, there's so there's a morality system in legends actually
I I know I know about that because I didn't know about it at all in legends one
But I had to use it in legends two in order to get
Yeah, yeah, that were the last weapon which I didn't even use by the way
Yeah, it's it's a whatever weapon. It's not even worth it for it's such a cool secret that like oh, you have to be evil mega man to get it
um
But it's not even worth I mean it depends on the gameplay you're going through because apparently it gets stronger based on how evil you are
Uh, oh like frustration
Yes
so
um
I'm looking at um
Like mega man's mega man legends on pc
Is that is that like a which which is the best way to play so the game?
Uh, I I officially I do not endorse piracy, but in my opinion the best way to play legends
No, uh, is to emulate it and uh increase the resolution and turn on a widescreen hack
Um, I've played it like that. I play legends and legends too at like two to four times resolution and the game looks beautiful
Um, it's really really nice. I mean I found like an
Abandoned where like like an actual like released pc version of it
Just on this abandonware site. I don't think was it actually released in pc?
I thought it was just uh, it was on playstation and then they released it on the n64 as mega man 64
You might be downloading a rom of it, but it definitely was never released for pc
But um, can you send me that link because now i'm curious what the heck you stumbled upon
I am yeah, I just I just typed it in hang on. I did I did emulate it
Uh, I didn't this on a widescreen
Resolution adjustments pretty cool united states. What?
Is this real? I've never heard of this. I'm gonna have to look into this
Is it uh, is it meg? Is it rock man dash a great adventure to save the world? Uh by strawberry soft
Because that is a taiwanese game that was on pc, but not regular mega man legends. I think they might just be calling at this
I'm so confused. What it looks like we find mega man legends
I don't i'm not familiar with this website wait the reception i'm looking at the wiki pd. Yeah, it says it was released in taiwan
So it's uh in the reception but the pc and nintendo 64 version had lower averages. So there was a pc version
What?
I guess I didn't know there was a pc version
Huh pc version received a more negative review game spot gave it a bad three eight point six out of ten damn
Saying the playstation port is better
I've never heard of this
Uh wacky I um I did I did emulate it the only
The only time I like used any like emulator uh things to like do anything to it
Is just when I wanted to grind for zenny against the golden bird into
That
The uh mirak, I believe it's called. Yeah, I I don't know its name, but yeah, um, they're like pokemon
I know some of them not all of them. That's um, that's uh, you know
Even with even with like I played it at like 10 times speed or whatever and I just developed muscle memory to like
Go in the door
Uh go in the door
Shoot the bullet shoot the bullets
I remember exactly how long to hold the button down and then use the vacuum go out the door
Turn around go back in the door and I just had a perfect like a perfect formula for just the order and the and the rate at
Which is the buttons and it still took it still took like a long time even at like
Sped up. Yeah, it's really really they give you
I'm glad they even include a way of getting like a ton as any that way. That's nice of them
It is nice, but it's good for the early game. It's still inconvenient. Like it's not it's not that
I mean without without without that bird like I just probably just wouldn't
I don't even remember what I was saving up for
Probably the shining laser because the shining laser costs like several millions any to upgrade completely. Yeah, I think it probably
I know
I know it's a crazy expensive item to upgrade to begin with and then the final attack upgrade
Costs you a millions any flat just because
I I don't think I upgraded it. I just I just got it
I mean at that point if you're emulating, I mean I did this on on my I mean, I'm playing through legends too right now
I actually I'm near the end of the game
I'm showing my girlfriend the game. So I'm like she loves it. She's fallen in love with Tron Bonn. She thinks she's great
Tron Bonn is great. She is fantastic. Tron Bonn is so cool
She's she's amazing too. She's like just a good-ass character. She's got some nuance to her. She kills cops
She blows up kills children children's in fairness. She becomes friends with the cop and misinventions of Tron Bonn
So that kind of makes up for it. That's what I dislike about it. That's the one black mark on her character
Really? Yeah
She's she's working. She can't she can't stoop to
No, I like she should be full full anarchy
Well in fairness it's not like she doesn't plunder and destroy the island she goes to it's just she just kind of helps this one cop
Who's like like, oh no, everyone's I'm gonna get fired and she's like well, she's like authority of bone
I know I know
But for emulating, uh, I just turned on the the infinite zenny cheat and then turned it off because it instantly jumps your zenny to like
And so I've just been coasting off of that for you know, fair. You know what? I don't want to grind
I want it. I wanted to do it like
Sword I get I mean I kind of cheated but I sort of did it. I sort of did the grind
I've already put in my time. Okay when I was a kid
If I was doing it again, and I had an option to just like can I please just fast forward through
Spending an hour and a half grinding like yeah, I've done it. It's fine. I've done it already
So like I don't have any qualms about cheating to get through that. That's the only thing I cheated at though
Everything else. I'm playing legit
I just don't want to have to sit there and get like billions of zenny for no reason
Although, you know when when you're in the mood for it, there's something to be said for just okay
I gotta grind zenny for an hour, you know, whatever just put on a youtube video. Just just do it
I believe it was it was designed to help to incentivize you to explore
Because it's like well, you need a bunch of zenny. So what are you gonna do?
So the idea is that you were supposed to go and explore because I did this in legends one
I would explore every single look and cranny that I could possibly get to
Um, and then by the time I was done, I've explored
Whatever was available to me and then I come back and I'm like, oh, I have like I'm like several thousands any richer
And I've explored and found more items
Um, yeah, you know, you know
Without a without a guide like because I did I didn't like refer to a guide extensively
But when I was missing something I would look I would look up like where to find a certain item or something like that
With without that. Yeah, all I would have been able to do is like go back through every dungeon and explore everywhere
And if I was doing that like back in the day, then like, yeah, I probably just would have accrued it would have taken me
months to beat the game
But I would have accrued all kinds of zenny just from the exploration and stuff. So yeah
Legends is an interesting balance because you can play it like a traditional mega man game and beat it in like an hour
If you really wanted, um, or yeah, if you if you want to treat it more like an adventure rpg
You can actually spend like days playing this game and getting lost in it. It's all off. Oh, yeah have to do it, you know
I I honestly felt a little bit bad after I looked up some stuff about legends one because
When I went I think I was looking for maybe like the bone or like I had missed the bone or something. Oh, yeah
It's like in a hole somewhere. Yeah, it's just like there's stuff just like in holes in walls
And like when I looked it up and I went and I found it I was like, you know, that wasn't that hard
If you know, I I could have just if I just made a cursory sweep of like
The dungeons I've been to I were like, I could have find this myself like damn
Yeah
It does kind of feel I cheated not only my I cheated not only the game but also myself. I learned nothing
Um, well, you know what?
If you just give it a give it a year and then come back to the game and you'll have forgotten all about it, so
Yeah, probably
Legends 2 helps mitigate some of the grinding to you. I've noticed where um, there are certain dungeons
They're optional dungeons. You need to get like the the dickers license for it
um
Which where the the price at the end is like a giant refractor
Uh, and I looked at it. I'm like, oh cool. Like I remember legends one
We needed these to repair various machines
But in this one, they literally say you could probably sell it for a bunch of money
Yeah, so I'm like, oh, that's cool
Uh, which is ironic because in legends one this always bug me in legends one
You start the game with a large blue refractor because of the opening cutscene where he steals it out of the chamber
um
Right and uh, and you have it for the rest of the game and I'm like, but you don't you don't it's not useful
It's not useful and theoretically you could sell it. Yeah
I remember specifically reading in the manual and even in uh, I think a game pro magazine that reviewed the game
They were like you can go to the bank and you can trade in your refractors for for zenny and I'm like, oh really?
So that's what the blue thing is for uh, but no, it absolutely you cannot it's just there for the rest of the game
Sad sad. So I guess you just have to pretend like in universe. That's what people do. So I'm like, yeah
Aren't zenny aren't zenny just little refractors like isn't that what they are?
so
Yes, and no, I don't think
Legends has reverted back to like
For lack of a better term the gold standard and everyone's keeping around like little bullion in like a sack somewhere
I think the idea is that um, you can trade in refractors for money
Because everyone is so dependent upon them as a power source
So the idea is like different refractors of different sizes and purities
Can be traded in at a bank who appraise the the
The refractor that you have and then they give you money in exchange
So I think they still run off of like a paper and coin money system
So so it's like it's as good as money
But it's like the the refractors that you find are as good as money
But they're not literally the money the zenny that you're right
For instance, I believe there's a side mission in legends one where
The the serve bots steal a bunch of money from a bank and you're supposed to catch them
And it's a it's a briefcase full of dollar bills not
Like refractors. It's not like a super heavy
Jangly box of refractors. It's it's money. I do I do remember that I do remember that
There's actually content in legends that I've never seen because I'm such a pansy and I can't bring myself to
To do it if you let them steal the money like there's three options
There's you can either catch them and return the money catch them and keep the money
Which instantly turns you full evil mega man
Or you can let them get away and if they get away
They buy a plot of land in downtown and build a burger restaurant
I
I've never seen this content for myself because I never let them get away, but
That only happens if they get away because like I think I I didn't let them get away
But I remember that they have a restaurant
In downtown later. Don't you like you have to well, that's why they were stealing the money to fund the restaurant
Maybe I'm thinking of a different thing. There is I did not let them get away
But there is a restaurant in the town later that where the servebots are behind
the
Counter, maybe there's like a different
I don't know if there's another way to trigger it. I don't know how to get that to to work
But I've only ever
I've only ever
Because like they're stealing the money to fund the restaurant
So one would assume logically that if the you let them get away with it
Then they um, they build it. I guess you could also just not trigger that cut scene and maybe they like still build it
Anyway, I don't know. I I I definitely did the the thing
And I I I'm
Swear there's got to be some other way to do it because I went to that restaurant. It's possible
I I don't know what it is though because I have never seen it myself
The only way that I have seen it is I saw someone who had like a like model rips of like the whole thing
And I was able to like see the restaurant like in a 3d viewer. I was like, oh cool. I've never seen this before
base base base
cool, um, I love the servebots
Yeah, I don't know why everyone lets them get away with everything though like, um
They're like they're clearly the pirates that are attacking the city
And yet they just go around and do things and everyone's like a small yellow child came by later came by lately
And he said something funny, but I'm like those are the pirates. Why are you guys okay with it?
Why isn't the whole town collectively running up to them and kicking them?
Because they're so cute. They're so cute and sweet and nice and friendly and who's you know
That's their defense mechanism. They're just and they're just a little guy. They're just a little guy. He's just a little guy
Who can hate a thing like that?
I don't think I didn't oh give I wanted to ask
Have you played any more inscription or have you put that down for the for the moment?
I put it down for the time being
I know everyone's everyone says like oh you're just you're just
You're you're you haven't seen the big reveal
Where something happens and you you'll go. Oh my god. I can't possibly tell this to anyone
I mean, I know that you know that you have not seen the full game, but
Yes, um, okay. Just just curious because we didn't talk about it last week
Uh, twitch. Are you familiar with inscription?
I am not
it's a uh in short
it's kind of a
horror themed
card based deck building games. Oh wait, wait, wait, wait. I think is this one with like the don't spoil it
Don't no no no spoiling. Okay. This is just like the first thing. Isn't there like a weird like swamp man or something?
Yeah, the guy with the eyes the crazy eyes
Yeah, you're in his like swamp cabin or something or yeah, and like you you look around his cabin
You're looking for clues for like, okay. Yes. Yes. I have seen a playthrough of that. I am familiar with it. It's okay. Okay
Uh, yeah, I I got uh, I made gib play it
That it does seem like a really cool game. I like it a lot. Uh
Yeah, that's pretty good
But I can't talk about it because
Gib has
Failed because fails me suck. I suck at the game. No, you don't
No, you don't
There's the only way to fail is not to play and I'm supposed to lose you're supposed to lose a lot of times
It's fine. Yeah, but that just makes me upset. I hate losing lots of times
Just think every time you lose just think great great
Great just think it's great great people have walked this path great great people have failed at this same game
So many times and I follow in their footsteps now
Now it's my turn steps to my grave
Now it's my turn exactly. I'm just I'm just joining a line of losers over here
She was in a bunch damn
Damn can't can't believe all these gamers have like lost this game so many times
Like I'm a much better gamer than them because I just quit. I didn't lose
Yeah, you knew you knew how to leave a losing battle. You're like, you know what? I'm not going to lose again
I'm going to choose to leave
It's valid. I'm going to go like chop down a hundred million trees and runescape. You know what?
There's a quote. I don't know if it's by bruce lee or if it's just people attributing it to bruce lee because people love
Making up quotes on the internet. Uh, what is it? Do you not fear failure for there is glory even in great attempts?
I think yeah, it's probably heard that
I don't know if that's from him, but I know that's a good quote and I like that one. I don't care who it's from
That's me. I don't fear failure. I just don't like me my my face my face when
My face when I'm basking in the glory of my great attempts because I beat a video game. I'm
I'm just resplendent. I'll I'll get around to it
resplendent in my
It's a good word splendor. Yes. Thank you
Oh shit, I'm trying my my dad used a really good 70 cent word over
Over Thanksgiving. I'm trying to remember. What was it? You know, I've heard so many people say
Like for 50 cent word, I I've heard that phrase used but everyone has a different
Denomination of money every time someone says it. I've heard that's a good that's a good five dollar word
It's a good one dollar for me. For me. It's 50 cents. I would not pay more than 50 cents for a word no matter how good
I just I'm just saying I've always a dollar. Yeah, everyone's got a different night. You know what inflation I guess that can
Probably throw it off. Were we saying gibb? Yeah in in joe biden's america a 50 cent word now costs a dollar
Thanks, obama. Well, we thanks obama. Were you saying gibb?
Um, I had a question. I know this is not actually related to the megaman laur at all
But what the heck is mighty number nine?
Oh, what happened? Oh, you got the right person on for this. I haven't played it. So I mean, I know
All I know is that there's a kickstarter
Yeah, there was a kickstarter to make like a megaman thing from a megaman person
And it sucked so wait. Well, okay. So hold on. You got the right person on for this because I am somewhat of a mighty number nine expert
um, hell, yeah, so
Uh, keiji in a fune was like the guy who he was the megaman guy
Uh for 25 years. He was he was known as the megaman guy
He was known as the megaman guy, but I would dare say he is the megaman guy because
Yeah, he was a key to mura who made megaman
Like he basically was like the guy who made it with in a fune
Basically like as his partner like the site like the the next in command so to speak
Uh, and the two of them worked on megaman one, but it megaman was uh, key to mura's baby. Basically, it's he made it
Um, but he dipped at like megaman three and then in a fune took over
So I would say for the majority of the franchise in a fune was the one
You know, he's not megaman. He's not megaman stepdad. He's the dad who stepped up
um
You know what I mean quite clearly he was basically
He might not have been like the guy who like came up with the design initially
But he was sort of in charge of the series for like a long time
Yeah, and he helped shape like the direction of along with his team
He always mentions like everyone always calls him the father of megaman and he himself in every interview where someone's like
You know, mr. Unifune people say that you're the father of megaman and he always the first thing he does is he corrects them and he's like
People call me that. I didn't make megaman. I just kind of took over for it
Megaman is a team effort. It was created by myself or it was created by akira kidamora and myself
But megaman is a team effort. It's made by all the people who work on it because yeah, there's actually a surprising amount of flexibility
I found in the megaman franchise or who gets how much
Say and like what happens in like the series
So it's it's really interesting. I like that. It's always kind of been a team effort
But he is like the figurehead of megaman
Yeah, so I won't go into every single excruciating detail, but
around this time i'm gonna say
I actually met him at
Wow, uh, new york comic con
Uh, does he like speak english?
Very basic english. He had a he had a translator there. So okay, but he was really nice
He was basically revealing the megaman legends three dev room project
Which was basically saying we're going to create a forum. You can go here
We're going to have contests and things you can submit ideas and if the ideas win the contest
We'll put them in the game. It was really great
Um, but then he was like i'm going to be doing autograph signings at two o'clock
So I I like dipped because I was like, okay. I want to stay here for this
But I know that this panel that i'm in right now is being recorded. I can get all this information later
I'm going to run over to the autograph thing and i'm glad I did because I just barely got online
So I met the guy he signed my copy of megaman x1. Um, I got to tell him I was like listen
You inspired me since I was a kid
I want to make video games the same way that you do your creations and your ideas and the megaman franchise means so much to me
And he seemed like really like touched by that
So I have a picture of myself with him. I actually made a megaman x t-shirt like it's a blue t-shirt
But it has like x's like chest plate on it. Uh, and I made myself a blue
Baseball cap that had like x's like helmet stuff on it. Oh, yeah
He he thought it was cool. I thought it was cool. If I still had it. I'd wear it. Um, that's another story
But anyway, he was a very nice guy. Um, he I think he really does
Despite his reputation now
I think he really does care about his fans and I think he really does care about making video games
I just think that he's become very misguided in recent years. But anyway
He announced
Megaman legends 3 he announced megaman universe, which was basically mario maker but for megaman in so many terms
And I got to play a demo of it. It was not half bad. It played like a megaman powered up in in the way that it felt
um
It wasn't half bad, uh, and then
Around this time capcom was like, hey, I know everyone's really excited for this whole legends 3 thing
Um, but we never said that we were gonna make this game and he's like, huh
Uh, and so it turns out they never actually officially greenlit the game
So everyone was like, what the hell you made this dev room? There's all these materials made for it
There's like clearly like a demo being developed. Um, and the demo for the game
Uh, was going to be its own little contained story and just kind of like kind of like what they did with two because in
They had the japanese only um, like demo game
It never got ported to america for some reason. We never got to play roles critical moment
I yeah where she gets tied up and she's in a crate and you can choose to join tronbon in that mission
It's really funny. It sounds it sounds awesome. Yeah, but yeah, so it was going to be its own story
But like literally its own prologue story
Um, we're like if you play legends 3 and you didn't play the demo you're going to be like, huh?
Like it's just legends 3 was just going to pick up as its own thing
And the prologue was going to cover
Um the build up to them launching the rocket and getting him off the moon
So that was just confirmed. Um, there's other story details, which um
I cannot talk about on the podcast because I've been sworn to secrecy about it
And I might actually get someone in trouble if I do wait really
Yes, I wow
I know some things of it. Well now you well now you got to tell well now you got to tell. I'm sorry
You got to tell us that you got to tell us. You got to tell us. You got to spill the beans
You got to spill the beans
All listen, I don't want to have to deal with the bean spillage, but uh, that's gonna be I will tell you one thing. All right. Um,
There was a fan theory based on
The character barrel and Barrett
That people guessed pretty much right away and I'm just going to say that that fan theory
Was on to something and I will say nothing else
So that's that's as much as I can say because I don't want to get someone in trouble
Is who's Barrett?
He's the red haired guy that you were going to play as in the demo
Oh, he was from the next game. He was from three
He was from three where he can like run up the walls and he has like the cool boots
And he does like awesome flying kicks and stuff. He was really awesome. He rides the really sick nasty motorcycle
It's it's cool. Is he on the is he like on the cover art or like the
Yeah, he's there was lots of art of him. Actually. It's really a shame that he didn't you know, yeah
Well, I didn't yeah
But anyway, I'm this is besides the point of how we're supposed to be on mighty number nine
I'm just saying that um legends had a lot of love in it. Keiji Inafune is not a horrible person
Like everyone makes him out to be he really really he did a lot of damage to his reputation with the whole mighty number
He did and so what happened was is capcom was like
um
He this is how this all went down and this is where things start to fall apart for Inafune and everything else
Capcom was like we never said we were going to make legends
Three we never said we were actually going to do that. You just kind of got that in your head
Um, but we we never agreed to it. We never actually said we were going to do that
um
So he's like, okay. Well, I would like to form my own studio
Within capcom because he's like I'm at the top like Inafune. I am telling you was like literally
The top executive at capcom. You could not go any higher
It was him and a bunch of other people who managed the company
But they're like not game developers like he was like where he worked his way up from like, you know, just an artist
um
So he's like I want to make my own game studio. Uh, I want to get back to making games
He's like I'll take a pay cut. I'll demote myself whatever it is. I just want to make games again
I don't want to be at the top here. I can't do anything anymore. Yeah, and capcom basically said no way
We're not giving you your own studio. You're going to stay right where you are and you're going to like it
So he said well in that case I'm going to finish up
All of my currently open projects and I'm going to resign from capcom
He's like I want to finish the projects that I'm on, you know, I don't want to like leave them
You know, he thought he was doing something nice by saying that by saying like well, I started all these projects
I don't want to like just drop them. That would be stupid. Yeah capcom said and I quote
That will not be necessary and then fired him and wow
He was kicked out of capcom people say that he resigned and like yeah, that's true
He was intending to resign
But what really happened is when he had this conversation with capcom
And they denied him the studio to develop game like kind of like how the clover studios was like
A studio that even though they were their own devs, they like worked under capcom
Clover is the one that made a okami, right? Okami beautiful show godhand and then they eventually went on to go
Become platinum games and stuff. Yeah, platinum. Yeah, right
So he kind of wanted the same deal
He wanted his own studio within capcom to make games the way that they did because he wants to get back in like the
You know creative aspect of it, but they basically said no way and he said okay. Well once I finish all of these games
I'm going to
Respectfully resign because I want to make my own game studio where I can develop games how I want
And capcom basically even the boot and they said no
so
Around this time is what mega man fans. I don't think we have a term for it
But this was like the great cancellation of 2011. Yeah, we're basically legends three got canceled mega man universe got canceled
um
And then we've later come to find out that a whole bunch of other on like unannounced mega man games got canceled like star force
four
And that maverick hunter first person shooter game got canceled
It was just they were just cancelling mega man games left right and center. It was really bad. Um, so then a little bit after that
uh
Inafuna founds his own company
that maverick hunter game
I that looks so ridiculous. It's like I actually
It on the one hand it sort of is it leaves a bad taste in my mouth like why would they do that?
But on the other hand, it's just so absurd that like I kind of would have like
Yeah, I what would it what would that have been like?
And you know what?
People again always give unifunny lots of crap for this because they're like, oh, he's a hack
He doesn't know what he's doing and I'm like, no, he's actually kind of ahead of his time
He wanted to do mega man universe and there there is a story by um, it's an article by protodude
uh, brian on twitter who um
He basically, you know spilled the beans about the development of mega man universe and yeah
Inafuna really kind of mishandled it
But he had a great idea that he just didn't know
How to like manage it and so the project fell apart
But it was basically mega man maker like like mario maker before that so the idea
Was brilliant. It's it's not it's not a it's not a terrible idea. Just yeah, and then on top of that
Mega man x maverick hunter whatever the hell it was going to be called first person thing
Yeah, um, if you look at it, it actually plays very similar to doom 2016
Where you run around in the first person mode you're shooting enemies
And then you do what is effectively a glory kill on them and use take their weapon and ammo
Which is exactly how the mechanic works in doom 2016
So i'm not saying that like they copied them or anything, but i'm saying like the idea was there
And it i'm sure if we got to play it it probably would have felt pretty decent to play
It's unfortunately i'm not a chance. I would i would have given i would have given it a fair shake
I really would have yeah, i was against it at first because i'm like this looks stupid
But then i was like well it does look pretty stupid though
But but i was also kind of open to new ideas at the time where i'm like, you know
It's a it's just a new interpretation of mega man like i used to be against battle network
But that grew on me and became one of my favorite series. Um, but anyway again i'm sidetracking here
So i mean that's how i felt it's how i felt about legends too like before i played
Exactly i think everyone should just be open-minded to give everything a fair shake. Yeah, so
Uh, he forms concept after he gets let go from capcom capcom cancels everything he he even admits
He goes it's my he i think in one thing he said
um, it is my biggest regret that i left capcom when i did because
I feel bad for the fans that were expecting these games that will never forget them and he said something kind of charming once he said
um
He's someone asked him something like if you had all the dragon balls
What would your one wish be and he said his one wish would be to release legends 3
Oh god
And i'm like man
Geez because he was he have to understand he was like asked about it for years
When is legends 3 coming when it's legends 3 coming people on his team were just
Taking their time to make demos for like a potential legends 3 proof of concept and he's like it's not in my hands
I can't do anything about it guys like i can't green light the game
So when legends 3 and universe and all that other stuff happened
He basically was kind of throwing around his executive weight because he was at a point now where he could do that
as a matter of fact this
Inafune was kind of infamous for this within capcom internally
where he would
basically
Greenlight a game and dump a ton of budget into it so that capcom couldn't cancel it
Because it would basically it would be like, you know, so like we spent too much on it already
We can't lose that investment. I think so for instance dead rising, right?
He goes he goes to capcom execs and he's like hey listen guys. I want to make a zombie game
I'm paraphrasing but this is more or less what you said
I want to make a zombie game and they said we already have resident evil and he goes no no no not like horror
survival uh game i want to make
Uh a different kind of zombie game
Uh one where and he basically describes dead rising
And they were like no, that's a dumb idea. We already have we already have a flagship zombie game
We're not going to make another one that doesn't make any sense
So he said okay, and then he just started development on dead rising anyway
And then threw a bunch of money behind it and capcom was like listen man
This better be a successful game because you know if it's not you're going to be in a lot of trouble and he goes
Yeah, okay, okay
Well for dead rising games later and I would say that it was a pretty big success everyone loved dead rising when it came out
Yeah, um they just sort of petered off at the end there because they went to different developers
But you know it was still a good it was a success
Um, then he said hey, you know what we don't have any shooter games
And capcom said shooter games are for americans. We're not we're not a western developer. We're not going to make
First person shooters and he goes yeah, I know but I want to make like a japanese
Shooter game like what would a japanese developed shooter game look like because at the time they really weren't any
Yeah, and so he basically pitched lost planet and they were like no no no that's stupid
We're not going to do that just let the western developers do that
So he goes okay, and then he threw a bunch of money behind it and I remember
I don't remember which game came first if it was dead rising or lost planet
But I know the second time he did that capcom said to him if this game is not successful
You were going to be let go. We're going to fire you for wasting all of our money
And of course both games were a success so that didn't happen
Um, so that was you know how how how delightful
So he's pretty ballsy when it comes to that sort of thing
So basically what happened was is third time's the charm
He tries to do that for mega man and he'd green light
I guess not green lights, but he works on all of these mega man projects and capcom basically said all right
That's enough. We don't care for if it's going to waste our money. We're just going to cancel all these games
So that's what they did. They said we got to put a stop to this. He's he's basically throwing around our money
And we don't want to gamble with this money because if mega man doesn't do well
You know we'll have wasted all this money and the same thing with legends 3
The legend series historically has not ever really sold all that well despite the fact that it's very popular
It is a cult series
So um, they were like we're not going to take a chance on legends 3 and they just they cancelled it
So fast forward to mighty number nine. He makes concept. Uh, and he's basically like hey, I just started a brand new company
I don't really have the capital to make anything yet. Um, but I'm going to do Kickstarter
Uh, and the Kickstarter campaign went
Really well at first and it got funded like immediately and everyone was super hype
Uh, and he basically is like I'm going to give people
The mega man that capcom won't give them. I'm going to make a mega. I'm going to make a new mega man game
I'm going to make a new tv show. I'm going to make merchandise. I'm going to make all these different things
Um that I've always wanted to do at capcom, but they would never let me do it
Because they were always like controlling everything
And that's where things start to fall apart in so many words
He basically bit off way more than he could chew and I just don't think he understands how
Like crowdsourcing looks to people it's bad optics when you crowdsource the game
And then you're like not delivering on certain things or you're late on delivering things or things don't come out
The way that you promised
Um, you know for me personally
I think I donated like 80 bucks
Uh, that's all I could afford at the time
I would have donated more at the time and I still would have donated more even today knowing everything that happened
I still really did believe in this project and I looked at it as like a donation
I didn't look at it as like an investment like most people did I was like
I'm going to donate this money to it and I'm like if the game sucks a game sucks
But I love the guy and I'm willing to give him a chance
um, so
I can't even describe the entire
Debacle with the Kickstarter because I know what do I know about it?
I mean, I know that not all of it was his fault, but he did take the fall for a lot of it
So I know that people didn't I feel I guess I feel a bit bad saying that the game sucks. I I haven't played it
That's just what and so that's the thing. I played the game and I love it. It's a great game. It's not perfect
It's got a few things wrong
But it's it sets such a great foundation for what could be an amazing game
I mean mega man one was bad
That's exactly what I said. I'm like mega man one was bad. But you know what we have and I I again, I'm not trying to
Uh to again like glorify Inafune and like lick his asshole over here, but mega man one
Like sucked and capcom just didn't want to release it again. They were like
Mega man's dead franchise. Whatever. It's stupid and Inafune and Keita mora basically put their heads together
And they said no, listen, this could be something really great. This is actually a lot of fun
It's got a lot of potential
and the the success story of mega man is that
Capcom basically told them you can work on making a sequel to mega man as long as you do it in your spare time
And it doesn't cut into this other fantastic game that we're going to be working on
I think it was like a baseball murder mystery game. I don't know something's stupid
Okay
And so they said, all right, cool. And they literally worked on mega man two
Inafune, Keita mora and their team made mega man two in their spare time and it exploded
I've heard uh, I've heard this one. I've heard that the rest is history. You know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
So, you know
I was always of the mindset. Okay. Money number nine is not a perfect game
But neither was mega man one and I'm like just look at what happened when mega man two came out, you know
Um, and so a lot of people
I think were tainted by
How poorly the Kickstarter was handled. There was a lot of things that went wrong with it
Which I'm not even going to make excuses for there's lots of people out there who think that I'm like an Inafune like, you know
Bible thumper or something. Uh-huh like I I'm sorry, but the guy gave me like 25 years of mega man and he definitely
He definitely made some mistakes. You know, he definitely made some mistakes
I'm not going to like say that he didn't but he was also responsible
For a lot of good that
You know helped me
Grow up as a person and like gave me so many years of you like you don't you don't just fail to the top of the company
You know what? I mean, he didn't just
Screw up like not not when you're like creative director and you're like
Yeah, he he did worked his way up from like he was just like a like a concept artist. He was an artist
That's all he did. He just did the art for mega man one as far. I think that's what he started as
It was actually pretty ridiculous that that's like he's he started where he started and then he
Yeah, he was literally at the top. There were no more promotions for him
He could not go any higher in cabcom
Which is why he's just started throwing his weight around to make creative decisions about games and stuff and of course the other
Executives who are not game developers didn't like that, you know
So, you know, that's just how it is. So so he made a lot of mistakes, but mining number nine
I don't think was one of them. I think it's actually a competent game
It plays really well
And I think a lot of the issues that people have with it come from
their their preconceptions about a mega about about it being a successor to mega man and also
A lot of people have a bad taste in their mouth from how badly he botched the kickstarter towards the latter half of things
Um and other decisions that he made which of course I don't agree with and I think were dumb
But I don't think he was acting maliciously
And I think that's the problem is that a lot of people
attribute his his bad decisions to
Like maliciously trying to scam people out of their life. Yeah, he was scamming people or he was like
I'm like, you know deliberately making false promises or something and I'm like, oh, I'm like, wow, you know
Last I checked scams are usually profitable for the person running the scam
He scammed himself right into bankruptcy. So I guess, you know, what a good guide a scam artist who takes himself out
Like what do you you know?
So, um
But mighty number nine itself as a game. I think is a lot of fun. It's very fast-paced
Like I feel like I'm playing mega man x1 or like the super nintendo x games because of how the dash mechanic works
It's very fast very fluid
And I think just too many people don't understand what they were going for the comparison that I make a lot of times is that
mighty number nine's dash mechanic
Is to mega man as the egg throwing mechanic in yoshi's island is to mario
It would be like if you played yoshi's island and you were like, why do I have to throw eggs?
It's a mario game. I just want to jump on people like well, okay
Sure, but you have to kind of learn the mechanics of the game to get the most out of it. Otherwise, you're
Is there something weird about mighty's dash?
Well, the dash itself feels great
But the way that you kill enemies in mighty number nine is you shoot them enough times and then they like destabilize
Like they get stunned and there's like a big blue aura around them
And it has a humongous hitbox and all you have to do is dash in their general direction and you like absorb them
And when you do that it like refills your health or it can give you points or it can give you like power ups
Um, each one does like a different thing
Um, and so that's how you actually defeat enemies
Now if you don't shoot them, which I don't know why you would you can sit there and just leave them alone
And they'll kind of just blow up on their own or if you keep shooting them
They'll eventually blow up because you've shot them too many times
So the idea is to hit them enough times to stun them and then dash through them
And so a perfect screen of mighty number nine would be
Lining up your shots stunning all the enemies on the screen and then dashing through them in like one smooth motion
Like doing a dash on the ground getting a first couple ones doing a dash jump into the air
So that you're lined up with the next ones that were maybe like floating and then doing an air dash through that one
So you do like a nice like s-motion
Through the screen and you've absorbed everyone on the screen. I didn't know any of this. I thought it was just exactly like mega man
No, so it it the way that it works is that you basically
Stun the enemies and then absorb them and when you absorb them they'll often give you like a power up and usually these power ups
Are consistent
So for one you'll like beat a guy and he'll give you like a speed power up or your speed is doubled for like clinics
However, many seconds. I think it's like 30 seconds
And then they'll give you a set of screens
Which you can make it through on your own, but now that you have the speed power up
There's an obvious like pattern like yeah, you ever watch like speed running how people say
Oh, you want to get on like a good cycle and then you can like get through it
Yes, that's how the game is
That's how the game is set up
They want you to get that like when power up and get through the screen on the right cycle
And then if you don't well, you can just get through it, but you're gonna do it slower or do it the hard way
I got you
I got same thing with like a like an attack power up the attack power up lets your shots travel through enemies and deal more
Damage and so you'll get an attack power up on the previous screen
But then on the next one they will purposely set up enemies that are set up
Like three in a row so that you can't hit the ones behind them
But now that you have the attack power up you can hit that entire row in like one shot
And so you can absorb all of them at once and it's it's you know, you're making me curious
You're making you're making me want to give it a try maybe you absolutely should
I think even as just if you're just a mega man fan. I still think you should play mighty number nine
Um, it feels great on pc. I should note on pc is how I would do it
I will not defend the fact that mighty number nine has some
It's only in like a few places. So I guess it's kind of a defense some really random performance issues and like a few very specific
Parts of the game never enough that I felt it was game breaking
But just for no reason the screen will it'll just chug for some reason in like a few
Sparse areas, but on pc. I never ran into that issue. So maybe maybe I could um,
Maybe uh, it's giving me an idea. Maybe if I could get my internet sorted out a little
A little just make sure I wouldn't have it. Maybe I could like stream myself playing uh
I say go into a one bust out the old twitch bust out the old twitch stream
Not you dust it off. Yeah, no no relation and no relation and uh, uh, maybe I could stream mighty number nine
That might be fun. I'll be funny. I think it's worth it. Um, I think
And you know, I don't know what else this is blasphemous for me to say
I think money number nine does certain things better than megaman 11. Oh my god. I know that's horrible, but
So mega man 11 has
And I I know the irony of this when I say it it has very robotic animations for mega man
He moves very like there's a there's a youtube video about the animations of mega man. Have you seen that one?
I've seen that one from eight bits or like 11. He did the whole thing
Yeah, I don't I don't remember what his name is. But yeah, I I have um
Seeing a breakdown of like all the different like the different ways that he's animated across the different games
It was really. Yeah, it was a great video. Yeah
Um, but in mega man 11 your run sprite or your run animation
I should say is the thing that you're going to see the most in the game and it is so
Robotic and like stiff and gross and I'm like, what is this? Um
And also when you shoot
Like the shots are kind of weird like they kind of like hover in place
Like they like they like hover in place or follow your buster or something like that
And the shots don't kind of like come out the way that they're supposed to
Like the muzzle flash and the resulting shot don't line up correctly in mega man 11 somehow
I didn't know why or how they did that
Uh, I probably notice what you're talking about if I went back and I looked for it
Right. Um, but in mighty number nine does there's like no robotic animation the animations for beck. That's the that's mighty number nine
He he moves
So fluidly and so smoothly like when he's running
He's got like a lot of weight to him and it's like very animated
Um, if you jump and like there's lots of like squash and stretch because like their limbs are kind of like a little stretchy like cartoony
Um
When he jumps he kind of stretches out the right way and then he kind of like snaps back up to like the rest of his mass
When he's at like the top of his jump
If you're running forward and you jump and then land he does like a little stumble before getting back to his full run
It doesn't even like affect gameplay
Because like he does like it's only if you're holding forward when you land that he does like the stumble
Um, so if you just let go of forward you can just land
Completely straight like, you know, precisely
Um, the dash feels really good like he turns into this cool like data form and like he stretches out until he's like long blue thingy
It's really it the game just looks and feels so nice. I'm thinking I'm thinking I'm
I'm gonna have to check it out now
I kind of had written it off just based on its reputation, but uh
And that's the thing a lot of people do and I'm like, you know, it's such it's got such a good potential though
um
The animations are leaps and bounds better than mecha. They release that when they release that trailer that said
Something about an anime fan on prom night. I was so personally insulted that I just like
Believe he would say that about me. I think I forgot that was that was that you know what?
I a lot of people were really butthurt about that and I was like, I mean, it's pretty it's pretty cringy joke
Like it's not a funny joke, but like it's it's not that funny. I don't care. I don't care
I but there was actually people who did care and they were like really personally offended and I'm like guys
I'm an anime fan and it's my prom night. Why would you say that?
I'm like you guys would not have survived the advertisement in
for games in uh
In the 90s like I watched
Uh collection
I open up my magazine to see I open up a game informer to see an ad for earthbound
That says this game stinks and I say, how could they say that? How could they say that about a video?
I like video games and they're insulting one
Disgusting. Okay. Okay. So here's an example of some edgy 90s advertisement
And this is for when I watched a collection of uh ps1 commercials
Um, just you know as you do. It's funny like I in the digital age
We all want to avoid advertisements and yet here I am
Watching them on purpose. No, I hear yet ads ads in the 90s were
Really strange and I I hazely remember them like like a dream like a nightmare that I woke up from
So there's one for metal gear solid
I don't even have to tell you the pedigree of this game. Everyone knows how
The the legacy of metal gear solid and how it taught me that love can bloom on the battlefield
Exactly. So you already know the advertisement for it. Uh, I remember
It's it's a soldier and he's doing like push-ups and jumping jacks
and there's like
There's like a drill sergeant and like a higher up in like a business suit or something
And the the drill sergeant is like drop and give me 50. He's like doing all the things or whatever. Um, and um
he's like
The the soldier is like struggling to keep up with the exercises and it's interspliced with um,
You know gameplay footage and this and that or whatever
Um, and then the the higher up the big general guy leans over and he goes
Are you sure this is the right man for the job? And he's like, yes, don't worry about it general
It's a suicide mission anyway
And then the the soldier guy looks at the screen and it zooms in and he's like, huh?
And then it cuts to I don't even know if this is anywhere in the game, but it cuts to snake
There's an explosion and snakes character model flails through the air and like smacks into the camera and i'm like
What the hell am I watching? I don't know what they were
What was the I don't know. Yeah, the wet western marketing for games and that era was just so like it was they
They insulted you for wanting to play the game and then insulted you if you didn't play the game
So you can never quite tell so when I saw the money
I'm feeling this probably just like two guys that are like the result like the reason all advertising was like
Yeah, so it's just sort of like oh somebody had like a success with some weird ad. Let's all copy them
Yeah, let's all be fucked up
So when I saw that advertising campaign for money number nine
I just laughed I was like, haha, I get it like they're they're going for like this is stupid self-referential like edgy humor
You know, so like it was nothing new to me because I grew up with that kind of stuff
So I was like whatever like it's just it's a riff on
Self-deprecating self-referential stuff. Do I think it was the right move?
No, but I also don't think it was as agreed just as people make it out to be
Yeah, it's it's whatever
It's but separate from that. Let's separate
I ask I implore not ask I implore everyone to please give the game
A shot with no preconceptions. Um, it's always on sale for like a few bucks on steam
You know, it's I will buy the game for people who want to play it ben
I will buy you mighty number nine. No fucking way
I will I know
I'm dipping really deep into the maverick hunter reserves right
I will
I will buy you mighty number nine to give it a shot because I think it doesn't worth a shake
That would be uh, cool. I would uh, we can I can add you on steam
Uh, nice. Yeah, you can do that. Um, thank you. Appreciate it. Uh, oh, you know, okay
Not to change the subject but that reminds me, uh, gib you got to tell hgb guy
That I bought him a video game
The other day and he has not accepted it and it's gonna get refunded if he doesn't accept it
Yeah, oh shit. Yeah, fury fury was on sale
And I was like, oh, I've heard of that. It's on sale. I'll buy it and I looked at my
Who who else has it in their wishlist and hgb guy had it in his wishlist. So I bought it for him
Because he
Is cool and uh, but he hasn't seen it yet. I got a notification. It's like hgb guy has not accepted
Your gift. Ah, I'll tell him. I'll tell him. I could let him know but I won't
I like your initiative. That's gib's brother, by the way. That's the reason
Yeah, I could physically shake him and slap him over the head like
Yeah, get him. Make him pay attention. Yeah, get his ass. Nice. That is usually
That that is convenient
Can you have that sort of ability to do so? Um
Well, uh, okay, we've been all right. We've been going for three hours
And
I feel like we should start we should I'm not saying we we don't have to quit right now
But I do feel like we should move towards a resolution
Yes
to put it
Diplomatically and and and then and then 7 20
And then we and then we can um, we can move on to voicemails. So I don't know um
I
Guess I have um, I don't know. Is there anything else you wanted to like
Talk about while you were here on the on the
On our on our stupid little podcast
It's not stupid. It is. It is stupid. You idiot. All right fine. Geez. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much
Um, I don't know I I'm
I'm I'm really bad. I get the sense. I get the sensation that if we if we wanted we could
talk about mega man and mega man accessories for
Any no any length of time and literally I could talk about mega man for days
And I'm not saying like that as an exaggeration
I'm literally saying that the amount of time I could talk about mega man would exceed 24 hours consecutively
I feel like I had enough food and water. I could just keep going. I feel like we've only scratched the surface
Oh, yeah, there's there's a lot more that I would love to discuss with you
You have you have so many little like little examples of like, oh, yeah
I can bring up a very specific like a thing in a reference that was here or like the time they
They oh, they said this in that one time
Oh, yeah, just like like in in mega man legends the the this is just a little taste the z saber item or the zet saber
as they call it
Yeah, um, they say that it is a toy from a tv series called mega man zero
Yes, and that dates the game series mega man zero. So i'm just i'm just saying it's it really it says that
I remember that it's a toy. Yeah, that's so funny. It's it's in the japanese dialogue only. I think okay, okay, okay?
So it's interesting that they they call it. They're referencing a series called mega man zero
Um, like three years before mega man zero one even came out. So
I'm just it's crazy. There's a lot. It's crazy. Okay. There's a lot I can keep going
But I'm just give I'm just letting you know
I'm just flexing the fact that I do have lots of little things that I could go on
I I won't because we've been doing this for three hours. We go. I mean we we often
We've been we've been airing more on the short side lately, but I mean three hours is not
hugely unusual
It's not overly long. Yeah
Sometimes we go for
I don't think we've been a five hour episode yet. No, we no we definitely did we definitely made I think maybe even twice
It's funny because uh me and coalman were supposed to record an episode of our podcast today
I actually don't know what the subject is going to be
Um, but we're always like this will be a short one and then we always drag it out for like an hour or two
Is that on your youtube channel? It's actually on his
I was just called on as a guest and then I've become
The the semi permanent co-host for the show
Um, I just love doing it so much and he was like man, you're great. Let's just keep talking
So like we kind of became friends and like we've been doing it ever since
Wait, wait, wait. His name is was it x coals, uh, coalman x
Coalman x there we go. Uh, and that's his youtube channel. That's his youtube name. Um, I think if you
His youtube url, he's gonna kill me if I don't remember. He's not I'm just just look up rambling reploids and you'll find right there
We go
Awesome
Yeah, you'll find his channel that way that because we've done a lot of episodes of that and so that show up
I was gonna ask if you've been doing it for a while
We have, uh, we've been doing it for a couple years now
Um, we've covered lots of cool topics. He actually has a lot of interviews with
Some interesting people. Oh, wait. He was in he was in my chat
He was in my premiere chat and he mentioned to me. Oh, that was him and he mentioned to me an interview with um
Oh, I said I was gonna check it out. Uh
He he specifically mentioned one interview with
Someone ah darn it. I can't he's done interviews with a lot of people
We've talked to Ian James Corlett who was the original voice for mega man of the ruby spears cartoon. That might um
It was it was a voice actor
He wants to talk to he meant to talk to me. I don't know if we're gonna finally call in this favor
But we want to talk to scott mcneil who voiced protoman and dr. Wiley in the ruby spears cartoon
He's scott mcneil has also done like a bajillion voices. So he's done a lot of things outside of mega man
But we want to talk to him
I'm trying to remember who else he's interviewed because we've done a lot of interviews actually. So oh
um
No, that wasn't him
Shoot, I can't remember but yeah, um, I was gonna say check out our our channel and not not to forcibly
Stick a plug in here. But no, I mean by all he does cool stuff like it's all mega man related. So
um, we always talk about neat mega man related topics
Usually there's like a theme to an episode
Uh, he he himself gets really great interviews. So I recommend checking out the interviews
So it's a lot of fun. I he he mentioned that interview to me
And I thought to myself and I said I was gonna check that out and I wanted to check that out
And thank you for reminding me. I had almost forgotten. But yes, uh, that's so funny. Yeah, I will I will go
I will scope
I can't remember which which interview he he recommended to me, but I was I was gonna go I was gonna go watch it
And now I remember
Yeah, I I wasn't there for the premiere unfortunately. Um, but I mean, I couldn't that's fine sat there further
But you know, I watch it, you know afterwards
But uh, yeah, he was he was even saying, you know, I'm just gonna go ahead and throw it out there
Would you like to be on an episode of rambling reploids one day? You know, you know, I was I didn't know I didn't want to presume by um
Making that suggestion, but uh, yeah, I would I would I would guess
We would we would love to have you on and we could we'll
Much rambling will be had that would be sick. Cool. We could do that. We could do that sometime
Uh, all right, I love it sweet
Well, it's a day. I'll pencil you in. Uh, okay. Uh, wait, what are you doing?
What what are you doing on my youtube channel? Uh, you can't review this game. I already reviewed that game
Um, all right, I called dibs. I licked it. You're not allowed
I think I think we're gonna I think we're gonna move on to voicemails
Yeah, so I'm sorry. I don't mean to kick you out
No, it's all good. You know what? I've been I I've been kicked out before I totally understand it. It's been uh, it's been fun
It's been fun, uh, having you on and I appreciate you being here and check out. Yeah, check out twitch
Uh, check out uh, reploid revo on youtube. I'm trying to think what what video I mean the history of robotics is the one that I
Oh, no, Ben died. It wasn't me. I swear
Ben what happened?
What did you click on can you can you hear me? Yeah, we can hear you. I can hear you
You just you just randomly worth the call. I don't know. I don't I also don't know. Anyway, I was
Plugging me and then you got kicked you got you bumped off. Oh, well, I shouldn't plug. I guess I shouldn't do it
Yeah, just don't do not check out reploid revo on youtube
I was gonna say that the one of your videos that I watched the most was the history of robotics series
Um, I love that one. Definitely my favorites that I've done because because that one has you know, all the like world history and stuff
Uh, what are the other ones that I mean, um
You know the who the who is x the who is zero series are just very like
You know, it's just very very important very important information to understand
um, my
The your iceberg your iceberg video was pretty good the the the combine. I like I like that one
And I like and I and I like that um the one you linked me the other day, which I had seen before the um
I forget what it's called
But the like everything that happens in the whole time skimmer everything is or time skimmer the whole thing
And it was an April actually all the time skimmer videos again. I watched all of those by the way
Well, thank you. I do appreciate it and uh, you know, I can't wait to
Continue on with that series. I think it's gonna be great because I wanted people are always like, why don't you talk about legends?
I want you to talk. It's your legends three. It's your legends three
It is but I'm it's not cancelled. It is coming out. Oh, it's I did complete all the editing for that video like several years ago
But I'll tell you what I'm announcing it here first. I always do like an end of year video, but I'll put it out there
Uh, I'm going to be remastering a lot of pretty much all my content. Um
Be it's not going to be like a crazy undertaking
But there are certain things that like I didn't know how to do
So I'm going to be re re-recording certain things because like my audio quality has now been way improved
Uh, and I'm also going to be fixing a lot of editing mistakes and stuff like that
So, um, I'll be getting to that and uh, I already finished the editing for time skimmer six
Years ago, and I think I'm just this is the perfect time to just start over again on it anyway. So it's coming
It's coming. I promise and I'm not I'm not fooling you radical
radical radical
Hell yeah, all right. It is
All right, it's bodacious. Uh, it's been been great. Uh
Now skidaddle
All right. All right. Take care everyone. Thank you for having me. I'll see you guys next time. Bye. Bye
absolutely
Sweet man, what a cool guy knows a lot about mega man
Sure does Ben. How how emasculated do you feel right now?
Let's not talk about it
somebody somebody in um
Somebody in I think it was either a comment or someone in the chat in the premiere asked me like
Ben, are you the most like do you know the most like does does anyone know as much as you about mega man?
And I I think as she officially said like
Repload Revo might know as much as me he might know as much as me
But I said that knowing full well like he definitely knows more than me
Uh, I mean I I mean I literally played some of the games for the first time ever for the um
Like I'd never I'd never played x5 or x6 uh before
Then I just do it for the video. So like I'm a freaking nerd. I only did one playthrough of x4
I only did the x playthrough. I didn't even do zeros playthrough zeros playthrough is like even more canon
I'm a I'm a baby
You're a fool
How what a what a nerd you are to not have played so much so embarrassing and I can't get a girlfriend because I didn't play
Both playthroughs of x4
Sad uh
Um, do you want to go to voicemails?
Oh, I forgot or I forgot to do my quip. I forgot to do my quip where I say
Where's all the mega woman, huh? But it it's time. There's one there. She's you know, there's one called splash woman
There's one. Oh
What's the difference why is she a woman because that's her name?
I don't know what you want me to say uh
Uh, she's like I'm because I because they're they're robots. They don't procreate or reploids or yeah, like
There's no there's no reason for them to have gender
But they're all I mean, I guess it's kind of like the sounds honestly
I think it's probably like a crystal gem thing like it kind of doesn't matter. They just all are men
Except for splash woman. Well
reploids are
There are more there like reploids are some of them are women like all the nap most of the navigators are women
Uh, what what makes them women? I don't know because they look
girly
uh
And then and then I think in in zero they're like
It's kind of just equal number
Yeah, I don't know all reploids start genderless and then they just pick if they feel like I feel like
I feel I mean, I mean most most of the like bosses are like they don't really look gendered one way or another like
They just look like an animal
But I think they tend to call them he square when they refer to them at all
I think they usually call most of them he I can't think of any that are called she
until like alia
in in five
and then
I don't know why they didn't you know, they they made splash woman
In nine and like she was cool and then they never made they didn't make it anymore. They had two more games and they didn't do any more
Woman and like why?
Why not?
Everybody likes splash woman
Well, we'll never know because uh twitches left they probably would have been able to talk honestly
He might have had more he honestly might have had more insight into that than me. He said he was doing he said he was working on a video
For his channel soon about reploids siblings
Which is
I thought that was an interesting topic because it actually is sort of like a mysterious thing
There are several reploids that have like siblings, but like what does that mean for a reploid?
You know
Uh, and I think it kind of varies case by case
I think some of them were like
Originally supposed to be one robot and then they sort of split into two
Or like the two of them are like linked by like a single, uh server or console or something like that
Uh
Well, um
Before we get to voicemails. I have
It's not really an announcement. It's just sort of a vibe. I've been on it's not really like, uh
I just I'm I I want to hibernate you this this winter hibernate
I'm getting on my hibernation. I'm gonna eat and I'm gonna sleep
But I'm gonna roll up in a blanket and I'm gonna not think
If I've had enough of the world you see, uh, okay
And I would I would encourage everyone also to do that
No more everybody everybody betray you you're fed up with this world
Everybody is too woke you need to get some shut I get some sleepy times
Hibernate just go into your cave
Exactly. It's it's I think it's good. I think it's what I want to do with my time, you know
I'm not like deliberately setting out to do that
But I think I kind of am subconsciously doing that because I really for like a week or more now
I've really needed
Almond milk
And it's literally like a 10 minute walk down the street to Trader Joe's to get some
But it's just a little bit cold out. It's just a little bit moderately chilly out and that's just
Ah, I just can't
I just can't do it
So yeah hibernate hibernation mode
Yeah, I think is the vibe just stack up just let's get all fat
Roll up and then you don't even need to leave your room
You don't need to leave the blanket a cave is low. You're just burn off at all low key goaded when hibernation is the vibe
I
You should tweet that I'll you know what
Fuck I guess I will if you
If you insist a cave is
Oh god, the caps lock was on. I can't I'm so embarrassing myself
Yeah, it wasn't really like the episode to talk about hibernating and there's not really much to talk about but
Uh, that's my that's my should I thing I'm going on. That's that's that's what I'm getting cranked on right now
So hibernation that's totally
Yeah, of course that totally totally normal totally reasonable thing to say and think
I I have no follow-up questions
Um, I feel like this phrase it needs an adjective
It needs to be not just a cave is it needs to be like a something cave
Maybe like a winter cave or like a forest cave or something. Um
Because greater specificity a bear hole bear hole
um
arboreal
Isn't would it would it be too obscure to say call it an arboreal cave?
Yeah, it might be I think it'll yeah, maybe a little bit. I know arboreal is a word that I've heard before
Yeah, maybe just winter. Maybe maybe wintery a wintery cave mystical cave
Uh
All right, I'm there we go a wintery cave is low key go to when hibernation and this is the vibe banger banger banger alert
banger alert
Okay, um
Well, all right, that's good a voice. I had I litter you know what I'm glad
nice nice
Have twitch on to take up so much airtime because other than the fact that like
The video came out and I had Thanksgiving
I didn't do anything. I don't have anything else to talk about
There's nothing else I have to bring up. Yeah. Oh, I guess on the podcast briefly
I I found this website or I was told about this website called itaku
um, which I am going to be using as
Oh someone
Showed me that I don't know what it is. It's a website
Uh similar ish to twitter but mostly sort of like an art
gallery thing
It's very easy to upload many images
And you tag you you have to tag each image at least five times to make sure that the tags are being used
and
um, it's good because it allows not safe for work. It's very
Very furry heavy. There's loads of furries on here
Which means, uh, it's probably like the best website ever
Because furries are insane and they they care about their their own they they care about
Preserving look out for their own. Yeah, they're not worried about advertisers or like stuff like that. They got a donation page
and I'm like twitter could go or
Could become like untenable
And I don't have any real place to host all of my art
Especially my not safe work art. So I'm putting it on itaku
I'll have a little okay
For any of those freaks who like that shit
Do you want to link it? I'm linking it right here
There we go
There's like a thing like um
I have a safer work profile and then a not safe for work profile which changes my avatar
And if you're like logged on you can switch between them
And so all of the things that are not safe work are tagged properly
Not tagged that there's like a setting and so you can't see not safe work things unless
You are you have the thing turned on so it's all good
And it's great and it's nice
And I feel safe. I don't feel safe posting it anything on tumblr or deviant art or fucking anywhere
So I'm glad this website has been
It exists
That's it uh
Cool. Good. Hang on. Replayed sent me twitch sent me a message and I just need to respond real quick
All right, let's do let's do voicemails. Um
You got them. All right. I think the first one is called do more
three two one go
Um, excuse me ben saint. I think you forgot to add the line between professor
Just getting pretty good video mega man is as bad as I thought
Okay, yeah, good. I'm glad I could help. Yeah, did you forget to draw the line between
Wily and zero
Yeah, I forgot to draw the line from wily to zero. Uh, but visual stimulus is the only way I learned
Even though like literally the entire plot
of x is
Did you know wily made zero actually like?
Ah, I just forgot
I just forgot
It's fine
The next voicemail is a tweet. What is this? I don't I
Is this a real?
Hey, Billy, I believe at young based god g at real donald trump
Your dad gives good brain
damn
Okay, that's a message from young based god. He's quoting it to him. Yeah, he just says it's called genes
Well, I mean I get it. I get the joke. Yeah
I was giving good brain like a like giving good head
Is that is that what that means?
Sure, whatever sex sexual. Okay
Uh, next one is called wait. No
Well, there's um, it's an imager link
Okay, but there there is a voicemail attached. So let's listen to that real quick. Uh, three two one go
You guys always complain about twitter, but I actually love it. It's really easy. Okay. I also love it
I'm sad about it going
I say it going when it's still here, but you know, I don't I don't know if I
I don't know if I really
Love it, but I mean sure I appreciate the value that it has even though it sucks a lot of the time
Okay, so this image is um, this should have been obvious
But this is how to make twitter a good experience for you
Okay
Follow accounts worthy of your time
Never enter the recommended. Yeah, never browse the timeline
Enable this on which you like sends to you a timeline which only your belled accounts
Yeah, I mean, I agree. This is basically what I do
Honestly, I mean, I'm on twitter to see shitty political takes and get mad at them
Like I understand that I understand why someone wouldn't do that. But like
I think I would just get I would get bored of twitter if I was just like looking at art
I got a look at that. Look at that. Who's that? Who is she? It's bonnet with the with the the with the
I don't care
I don't care who she is
She can just be herself on her own damn time. No need to drag me into it
Bonus goth ben bigger
Nose piercings. Oh the the line around your eye is bigger because yeah because eyeshadow
mascara
Cool cool goth ben
Should make a comeback. I think
Yeah, um, there's a there's a youtuber whose thing is
Calls himself like a goth gamer
Honestly, he doesn't really seem very goth other than that his logo is a little bit gothy and like his
And then he's called he's
Fuck what's his name? Um
Um grim beard his name is grim beard
I've enjoyed a couple of his videos
Seems pretty good
I don't really get the goth thing, but whatever. Maybe if I saw him in real life, I would get it
Okay. Anyway, next one is the voicemail. It's called
Discuss
The the voicemail attached is just a a pained moan. So whatever. It's a types of pasta
types of pasta
He got spaghetti lasagna, vermicelli, macaroni. I've not heard of big olie. That's funny. It's just sort of thick spaghetti
Big ol I never heard of that. I saw a I saw a tweet
I think it was a comic. I think it was from
I don't remember
What it was some big ish comic account and they were like
It was a comic that was like a dad was trying to get his kid to eat pasta
And the pasta was like the kid the kid was like, I don't want spaghetti. I want macaroni and the dad said it's the same thing in a different shape
And then the italian police busted down his door and held him down
They were gonna beat the shit out of him, you know, I've you know, you know how it goes
I've eaten a lot of these I really like conch shagley
The conch one
Looks like a shell. It's quite big. Yeah. Yeah, and it's sort of the only thing that's bad about them
Is that they can sometimes get stuck within one of the others
And so you have to sort of separate them to get the sauce in but they're really nice
Well, let me see
I'm gonna I'm gonna mark all the ones that I have not eaten
Yeah, let me I'll also do that. I'm what the hell is I mean, okay
Some of these look similar enough like
Feel like I should be able to say I've eaten even though I technically have not
um
Well, the whole point is the they're the same thing, but they just have a different texture. So
I would say like what is the difference
What exactly is the difference between ditalini and rigatoni?
Um, that one's got ridges ditalini
What am I where is it where the hell's ditalini
Ditalini is on the bottom row
Oh, that's like a hula hoop
Yeah, you know, I don't know. I guess the rate on me is like the brigade they look the same except one's just got ridges on
Wait, is that a shortened rigatoni? I don't think usually longer than that. Was that penne?
No, I think that's z z d or z d or penne
All right, I haven't had but I've been that they're the same
Crosetti, it looks like a medallion. That looks interesting
Like what like what how would I know?
How would I know the difference between if I was eating stringotsi versus fettuccine?
I feel it's fucking same
The fucking same
Uh, because fettuccine is like flat stringotsi is so much different
It I mean, it just looks like fettuccine, but a little bit thinner
No, fettuccine is similar to tagliatelle, but they're also different. I've had both
You don't have enough pasta then you're you're I've actually you need more I actually think I've
I actually think I've
Wait a minute. I think I've had orzo. I've had orzo, but only in the context of
Um rice pilaf. Is that what that is?
Hang on. I think so. I think it
Yes, I think rice pilaf. It has the rice and it has the little pieces of pasta and I think that's orzo
Okay, so I can say I technically have had that one. I think I yeah, same
I feel like I'm just gonna go the pepper
In like a freaking airplane meal
You know what? I think I actually have had
most of these
Here's my here's my list
Pavette if it'll freaking load. Pavette. I
I'm not sure that I've had
I really like gemili. It's like fusilli, but it's chewier. I guess. I don't know why I don't know how it does that
Maybe I just cooked it albente or something
I made my own ravioli one time
It was quite difficult
Yes
I've never bothered trying to make a pasta myself. I guess ravioli is the
You don't need a pasta machine
kind of
What do you
You sort of like hand squish it
Okay, I think this is
I know I know I've seen some of these before I'm assuming that any of these that like look similar to something I've eaten
That that I've eaten them
Like I don't know if I've specifically had barbina before
But like I look at it like I get it
I'm like pretty pretty sure I've had something very similar to that Italian police are coming. They're knocking on your door right now
Yeah, I think so
Ah filesia or how have you say these things? I like that. I know I've had that before
Well, they got in in asia. They just got rice
They don't they can't turn their rice into funny shapes get out of here
Uh
No more
No more italian. No more
Next one is called mega man one exclamation point one one
exclamation point exclamation point three two one go
I cannot believe that then seen
Forgot to draw the one line
That's so important
Which connects the fact that spoiler alert
Dr. Wiley did in fact create zero
What a that's another line line hater
I don't know what I was thinking. I don't I don't know what what's even the point of the board if I'm not going to draw
The line from wiley to zero
It really ruins everything you should start over it really did it literally ruins everything literally it just invalidates the entire concept
Yeah
It's so stupid. Did I mention last week that I was thinking I should try to raffle off the uh
Yeah, yeah, you could mention it. What if I tried to sell the um the the the paper on ebay
That'd be really funny
Oh, but then they'd be they'd be mad that the line isn't written
But you can't like edit it because it wouldn't be in the video you'd invalidate it. Well, I could
Yeah, I would ask I mean if they wanted me to draw the line on it
I would happily do that if they wanted it as
As it was in the video that would be okay too
Actually, but I might have I might have drawn the line on after the fact. I'm not I don't
Did I dream that I don't know
Having a dream like you got the comment you realized you you forgot the line and then in your dreams you have to fix the problem
I I specifically call attention to the fact that I didn't draw the line in the video. So I
That's why people are commenting about it. It's because I said, please don't make fun of me for it
But they didn't listen
Uh, next one is called. Where was I?
Uh, el piezo from mega man at reploids on the web.gov three two one go
So I have just listened to the new mega man lecture by ben saint and I thoroughly enjoyed it
However, I cannot believe that people would simply paint el piezo as a pure villain with no good ideas
Because like the absolute naivete involved in saying on the other hand like oh, no
We'll just give them the new energy source and then everything will be hunky dory like bro
the inherent racism and like
Dehumanization involved in in the first place thinking of reploids is completely disposable in the phase of an energy crisis
Is like not going to go away if you offer them exactly what they want and need like
That's just going to make you seem like even more of a fucking tool like a complete cuck
That is just going to get rolled over and the next time there's an emergency
El piezo was fucking right
I think yeah
El piezo is the villain of that game, but he's not really a villain until the baby elves drive him insane
So I would I I agree
El piezo had a point even though it didn't work out and his efforts failed. Yeah, I'm see I'm team el piezo
El piezo sounds like a pastor
It does
I think it's greek or I think it's derived from a greek word
um
the
What else was going to say about that?
I mean, I guess maybe maybe under copy x if there was no if there was no energy crisis
I mean, maybe the worst of the
robot apartheid
would have abated
I mean, obviously once vile was back there was no
There was no fixing that situation
I it definitely would have maybe there was a time when it might have
somewhat improved the situation to give them the seal system, but
By the time they actually had at that time was definitely passed
um
Next one
Actually, I get actually
Get actually in in in zero two
Harpuya is the head of the government
So like our and harpuya is a good guy. He's like a reasonable guy. Maybe harpuya could have been reasoned with
Hmm. So at the time when operation right district was happening
Maybe cl that was like the time when it was like most likely that cl would have been right
so
in that
light
Maybe okay
Okay, anyway, uh next one is called uh x 000 x 3 2 1 go
If nate were in this episode, what would the title and thumbnail be?
I don't fucking know what the fuck kind of question is that
It'll be uh the same but with the word nate somewhere in the title
I I don't I already I don't even know what the title is going to be
As it is ellie is our comes up with those later. So
mega mega man
maratham
Uh discussion. No, that sucks. It would be called losing our virginity
With mega
Losing our minds
Yeah, that's just the show. Okay next one is called
Ben's weekly reminder play delta room chapter two. Okay, Ben's weekly reminder to keep up to date with one piece
Okay, there wasn't a new episode or there wasn't a new chapter this week
No, well or there was but I don't I think it was last week. Yeah, we did it last week. I think
Yeah, I can't find another one
On the website that I was looking at last week the one that we reviewed last week came out like
That morning or the night before the episode. So
Yeah, this week between then and now there was not a new one that dropped. Otherwise we would discuss it
Um, it's probably out by the time you're listening to this which is probably that's just how it's gonna be
Don't they usually drop in like the middle of the week? I don't yeah, I think it's
Generally been Wednesday, but like I I don't know like what's the official
Thing the official thing on vis is different from how
Quickly some of the scanners can get the scans early. So it's like
Generally been Wednesday, but I don't actually know
Maybe there was like an early leak of the last chapter or something perhaps
Um
But anyway, yeah, I'm up to date. I'm staying up to date
Next one is called i o I a a i o you
I guess i o three two one go
Uh, I need to know your
Opinion on tapas.io is a comic website
Tapas I was pretending to open my shit on it in
years, I don't know
But did you never mention it because it is cringe or you'll never heard of it? Should I keep it? I I've um
I don't like it. I've never I've never I've never had any success posting there
Neither have I it's just it's fine. I think it's just sort of like not really a site I go to
to read things
um
I don't know. It's nothing too much to complain about. I just got like tired
Like posting a chapter of a thing on one like webtoon
and my what my website and tapas
And I'm like, oh fuck it
It's too many things
I'd rather do nothing at all
Post to my website and then link that in social media and that
works fine
I never I never got any like views
posting stuff that I drew to tapas or to
webtoon mary like says
mary loves webtoon
But I mean mary I don't know for whatever reason mary gets like a billion views on webtoon and like I post my shit and it gets like
it gets like
Eight eight views and maybe a comment if I'm if I'm really lucky. It's so like, yeah, I don't know
Which it doesn't feel I never get anything out of it. I feel like the webtoon
crowd
Similar and enough to the tapas crowd is just the sort of thing that mary withers comics
fit very nicely into there's a lot of anime stuff
There's a lot of emotional
I think I think he likes it because I think he likes it because it's easier to monetize than like posting on twitter
So I think like for him, it's like a moneymaker, but for me, it's not so
Yeah, yeah
Uh, that's how I feel about webtoon
Next and and tapas next one is called billionaire man
Uh, let's say vocaru link. So let me um
Get that
three two one go
billionaire man with briefcase walks down the street
He slips in a communist puddle
He drops briefcase all the money flitters out
He screams. Oh no
My billions
Reduced to millions
He tries to grab up the money. He screams
He is so busy. He does not see little girl walking down the street
She slips in a communist puddle and falls into the street
A communist car is on the beat
Save me billionaire man screams the girl, but he does not listen
I'm sorry. I cannot save you little girl. I am too busy saving money
It's so sad
Are you crying right now if only there was anything anyone could have done
It's just I get it though, you know, he worked really hard for that money
It's funny how like even with all of the voice stuff I can easily tell it's oblivion for
Yeah
I know his voice too much
Yeah, I'm pretty bad at identifying voices, but I could you know, I feel like I don't think there was
There's much attempt to hide it
But uh, I mean it was just gas. Oh oblivion fall you
I believe in fall you rascal check the next
Voice metal. I think it is a visual image of this this one we just listened to
Oh
All right, let's um
Let's see about that
No
There's that me
It's I'm the I'm the communist car. You're in the communist car. Oh my god
Ah
What are all these trucks? I they just
I I mean I could imagine that it's a a reference to the truck punchline
from germa and star videos
But I have no idea about that
It's it's a thing where germa and star would play gta 4 and they would make videos star star is a
A
Like a video person funny gamer youtuber. They used to make tf2 stuff now. They stream a lot
um, they do dnd stuff now, but like um
They had a truck punchline. He would spawn in
So many trucks that it would crash the game or it would make things run really slow
And the the the joke wasn't that the trucks were funny
It was that he would always ruin like a setup that germa was trying to do for a different joke
And then he would just like spawn in a bunch of trucks. It's like no not the fucking trunk the truck punchline again
You're always doing that. You're ruining this fucking video. No
And I'm not sure I'm not sure if that's what this is. I can't really tell
I mean what why else is there trucks coming down?
I think maybe it's just because like there was one crash and then there was just like crash after crash after crash
It's like a bunch more trucks just come smash from the sky. I guess communist trucks from the communist sky
I
You're a woke sky
Under your wokes these communist trucks are your woke sky. They're they're delivering pronouns
Nate seems to be having a good time tripping over all his money
No, my billions reduced to millions
Sad it's a lot of billions
That you're you're losing if it was reduced to millions
Yeah, it's almost that's almost all of it. Yeah, it's almost all of it
sad
Uh, unless you mean unless it was like reduced from
2 billion to like 900 million
It's possible. It's technically possible within the
definitions we've
Received next one is called should I from sorry it's long at pcp.drugs
Uh, let me just get that downloading. Okay, three two one go
Hello, Ben. Hello Gib. Hello as someone who has known your names and uh
Just heard your voice
and
Somewhat know you through the video
this internet
Internet presence that you have proved for yourself
Should I
root for you
to gmi in the internet space
Or should I root for your downfall so you get real industry jobs?
and
Make bigger money
in danger of your
potentially
From what that we from what I gather somewhat
unsustainable lifestyle
That probably all kind of applies. I actually just
Should I should I should I hope for your internet career to succeed or should I should I just
you know
Jill you
So the question is
Should he knows it?
Yeah, should he root for our
Downfall or for our internet career to succeed?
the downfall being like
Implying that if we lose our internet career
Then we'd be forced to get a real job which would give us more money
hypothetically
I mean, um
I'm not opposed to like a real job
But I wouldn't really want it to come on the heels of like well my internet career failed
So I guess I better go
Bark up a new tree
I would maybe want to be I would maybe hope to be like well my internet career is doing
Okay, but like there are other avenues. I can maybe be pursuing
at the same time
Including but not limited to
You know more traditional work
yeah, I
I feel like um
Personally
I don't really mind as long as I can sustain myself
Um like a bit like I don't need like a huge house
It'll be all right if I can get something like some some some building of my own, uh, but that's like
I don't know
I don't want to live
Like a really boring life that I hate with a job that sucks
I'd rather be like a like a minorly
Successful artist online if it means that I get enough money to do what I like doing
Generally speaking obviously it's good to have money. Yeah, and it's good to be able to afford things, but like I wouldn't
I mean it's the reason I stuck with art
so far is because
You know, it's not that good for making money. It actually sucks a lot
You have to be extremely lucky to be in the art field and be making it big
Making money
in the industry
It's not like I could guarantee that an industry job in the arts would be good for me
financially
Maybe just as bad and I'd be more upset
so I don't know
Please don't root for my downfall. I'd rather be
Having a encouragement
I'm assuming that this guy
I'm I'm
Maybe I'm assuming too much, but I assume that this guy
Likes us and he and he's wants the best outcome for us and he is asking what is a better outcome success as an internet creator or a
failure that leads to
more traditional
employment, uh
I mean
Yeah, I guess
I guess it's possible. It's it's conceivable that like someone attempts to
You know make a career online fails and then ends up finding more traditional employment in a in a field that is
You know, maybe ends up being better for them
Uh, that's possible. I mean, I guess I would say
viewer
That if you're hoping for the best outcome for us, I don't know like
What do I think is the best outcome for me?
I mean, I mean
I guess what do you think is the best outcome or if you I mean if you think that I would do better
to quit the internet
And and uh, you know get a job
Like if you think that would be a better outcome for me then you then I guess you should hope for that
If if what you want is the best outcome
But I mean, I don't necessarily think
That's the case
So, I mean
Yeah, you might disagree
Like I think the fact is that I know
With what I can do
And the opportunities I have
That I'm gonna be all right in the creative space. I'm not like
Like seconds away from starving to death
I I'm doing all right despite being so like small and insignificant
um
It it obviously isn't that but isn't that just the human condition though? Yeah, I yeah
Like with my skill set like I know that even if I lose
Uh
All of the subscribers and patreon people I can build something
up
And like do some good work. I know how to make good videos. I'm a good writer. I'm a good artist
I can make enough with what I have I would I will I may never make it big
Um, but I don't need to really
And so I feel comfortable. I guess
In the situation I'm in and I'm only gonna get better at the art that I do when I do more of it
So like I don't even know what a downfall would look like unless I don't enjoy doing these things anymore
Yeah, I mean I guess in this context a downfall is
Is
You suffer a precipitous decline in
A viewer's attention
Whatever patreon
revenue
Uh
Like if if all of my if all of my savings are gone and I have to make money immediately
And uh, all of my subscribers are gone. I have no like it's probably a bad idea
To do that. I would have to get a little job to build up like
A a being a live fund so that I could maybe get back into it
Mm-hmm, like my skills don't deteriorate that quickly as long as I'm still enjoying it. It'll be easy to keep going
Um, you know, I guess I think
I feel like you know, I have a skill set I have some things that I'm good at
I get nervous sometimes. I don't know because I don't feel like I can I don't feel like I have
Can confidently say like oh, yeah, I'll be okay. Like I could get a job
Wherever I don't know if that's true. Well, I don't know I could get a job
I'm saying I could make art and post it online and gain
followers again if I lose them all because I'm good at stuff
Honestly, I don't know. I think um, I think I've said this before
I think I might like to try at some point maybe in the not too distant future
to see if I can get some sort of like
work on like like more traditional work on some kind of
Some kind of team or studio or project or something
um
Just be part of like a creative team doing something. I think that would be pretty cool
I don't know what it would be
But I'm nervous and the thought makes me nervous because like what if I try to do that and it's just like
Well, you're just you're just a complete hack. Like you have no you have no skills. You have no skills. It could be
You you overestimate
What people in regular jobs have as skill levels
But I don't want a regular job. I want a creative job. Well, I mean even regular creative jobs like people
My brother knows this because he went to uni for game development with a lot of people
Who are like dumb as shit and the only thing they're good at is talking themselves into business opportunities
They don't know how to code even though they purport to do that
They don't know that that like they have no creative bone in the body
But they're like a creative director for some studio and something is like they just walk their way in they talk their way in
and they suck
You don't need unlike my brother
Charlie is like very very talented, but he didn't have that sort of social like
uh, yeah, I'm just gonna walk in like I own the place and so he's more
Stuck to like indie stuff rather than getting an industry job
which sucks because
people in the industry need him because he's really talented but like
Being in the into it being in the industry doesn't mean that you're like necessarily good at anything
So you would have no problem with the skill set you have getting a job at a creative like
Industry profession thing because I mean it's it's it's not as like that's true
It's not as like cutthroat everywhere as you may imagine
Yeah, well, I hope so. I don't know. Uh, I thought about it a lot. I still have no idea like
Uh, what I what uh, what that's actually gonna look like if I even try to try to do it. Uh,
Uh, I just want to be part of a team. I want to be part of a club. I want to be part of a little
A little a little a little a little crew
You know, I'm not like rule. Yeah a little motley crew doing a doing work on a thing and
making a thing
That's the that's the dream
Um, but um
Okay, I think we've answered that question thoroughly. Yes, uh, next one is called king cringis bingis
viewer discretion advice three two one go
What's a pcb? It's a me cringis bingis the third version
Uh, uh this week I I watched the inside job
I banged it actually it was real good
I hope it doesn't get canceled. Uh, and I crinked at uh, Ben's videos
Kind of me meager viewership. No, I hope it gets better
By cringis bingis
sailing out
I I mean
You sent this email yesterday. You sent this voicemail yesterday. I have like 18 by yesterday
I was hitting like I was hitting like 75 80k views
It's not bad. That's not meager. That's not meager
It's it's doing a lot better than I thought it would like I feel I I definitely underestimated the mega man
fan clamoring for something like this
I did not I was not counting on it to be like
An immediate hit an immediately thing that people in the mega man fandom were talking about that is
Something I hoped for but I didn't like expect
Uh, yeah, I I kind of expected that would like underperform compared to my previous videos because I didn't have
you know
uh
Because I didn't have like, you know dumb shits with a bunch of dumb shit followers
like Trixie to be like
Duh, this thing is good and a bunch of morons go like I guess it's genius. It's genius
Uh, I didn't have that. So, you know, I knew it was going to be a huge failure. Um, wrong. It's fine actually
Yeah, it's outperforming. I this is I mean, it's good. It's getting like it's
I mean, I don't know if this is going to continue, but it's getting about like 20k views a day
So does a view count if I come back to it like a day later to continue watching does that count as a second view?
I I don't
Think so. I'm actually not sure
I'm actually not sure about that because I know that you can watch a video multiple times and it counts as multiple views
But no, who does it?
Yeah, like but if you like but if you like it it saves your place and then you pick it back up
Does it count as multiple? I I'm not sure
Because I'm sure about that either like if I can it was a gangnam style
Just gets replayed and replayed and it became like the first billion view video
Right
it's not like
One billion people clicked on that link people have seen it. Yeah, even though I'm pretty sure billion people did hear it
But from like radio, but not personally they didn't personally go to youtube to listen to it. They just know about it
right um
Yeah, I don't I don't know
um, but I mean
Yeah, I told myself
When I launched it I was like as long as as long as it doesn't get less than if it gets less than 100k
Then I'll be embarrassed. I'll consider it a failure
Uh, but it's like ever and now you're not allowed to be embarrassed about it
No, I feel okay. I mean, I mean, I'm embarrassed about embarrassed that I didn't draw the line
I'm embarrassed that everyone keeps saying oh, he's doing the tim rogers thing
Oh, oh, he's acting like tim rogers like no, I'm not not really
Just because I did that gay little thing with my voice a couple of times doesn't mean that I'm tim roger
um
What else am I embarrassed what else am I embarrassed about um, I'm embarrassed about how my hair looks at many points
But that's that's fine
Oh, yeah, I forgot you shaved. I keep seeing the video of you talking about mega man. I'm like that's ben currently
But no no not anymore
That ben is dead that ben died before he even
Before he even got a chance
That get that that ben died before he even lived
That ben is like that ben is like the light of a distant star who's you know light from
From from millennia ago is only now
You know reaching the earth to be seen in our telescopes. It's it's exactly like that
um
But anyway the video is doing yeah, it is
When it when it started
It was doing better it it was doing not as well as the chris chan 102 because chris chan 102
Came out like right when chris chan was like making the news because like oh god the shit's gone down
Yeah, fucking sexual assault incest charges. She's going to jail like this is the most fucked up thing
Uh, so that was big so chris chan 102 got a big a big bump right at the start and then uh
Uh
Kokoro wish had a pretty slow start
But actually kokoro wish has actually had more sustained viewership and actually kokoro wish has more viewers now than
chris chan 102 did
Which is nice because I think that's a better light. It's my favorite lecture is the kokoro wish one
um
and then
Yeah, this one was performing a little bit better than kokoro wish did on launch but worse than the um
uh
chris chan and I was like, okay, that's a good sign. It's definitely gonna it's definitely gonna hit 100k
It's not gonna be a problem. You know, maybe in a month or two it'll hit 100k
And then it started to pick up around like day three and now it's a it's at almost 110
Because it just keeps it's getting like a thousand views an hour or something for the last couple days
So I think it might be starting to
Not like go down, but like it's not increasing as fast. So
I think it might be starting to peak
in terms of momentum
But we'll see
Anyway, I'm very happy with it. It's it's definitely outperformed my expectations
um
I've gotten a few new patrons not like a huge deluge of them, but I mean I'm hoping that a lot more people will see it
And maybe some more will pledge so that's nice
If I can get if I can get the if I can get my goal of getting 100 patrons
that will be
I will not be quite at the pledge amount that I was back in like 2017 when my patreon was as highest
But it'll be like close that'll probably bring me to like 400 dollars a month, which is like close to what I was when I was
When I was uh peaking so that's my goal for the moment
Uh, yeah, okay next voicemail, uh
It's from prince isolation and it looks like it's two images
Is a voodoo in the voicemail as well. Oh, yeah, you're right. Let's listen to that. Okay, three two one go
How I predict finis comic will end
It's so emotional guys. I swear to god
It's so fucking
Oh the culmination of things
So it's the images is a view and me
and Vinnie's comic
culmination of things
culmination of things. Oh my god. I never wanted it to end like this Ben. I'm crying. I got my guitar
Oh, that's a princess princess such a good uh
artist
Yeah, a big old red man
Given the amazing red man stand if you need a music reference just call him big iron
Are the these are just single images, right? These aren't full albums. Yeah. Yeah, just a single. Okay, and it's you
What's what's been going on like this
You know, I never I never fat. Uh, hey, I'm sure you didn't
So cool, why why am I crying about this and you're the one getting beaten up? Am I killing you? Why am I killing you?
I think we're fighting each other
I think the implication is that we have to fight each other. Oh, no
I got my
You knocked my tooth out and not your tooth out. Just like aqueous
What the fuck? Why would you do that gib?
Well, I mean, what how could you do it?
I how could you do this to me? Why would you just hit you with my guitar really hard? That's how I could do it
Yeah, you know, actually that makes a lot of sense
That is how it would happen, isn't it?
Um
Uh, what was I was I saying?
Oh, I was saying I never found I tried to find the enemy sprites from clash of demon head because there were the little like red
Like red man faces walking around and I couldn't find them
No, I couldn't find no, I could not find enemy sprites from that game. I googled around looking at like sprite
Sheets and I didn't they might be out there somewhere
But I wasn't able to find them eat very easily and I eventually I eventually gave up
I don't know
I guess it's just a funny game
It's just a funny little red little like little like smiley face little red oval man on little feet
It's like a little baby red man
Like he like butted off and do a little head that walks around
um
Oh the next one the next two I think are the same images
But it's like yeah at justincasehotmail.com. Oh, maybe he thought that they would get cut off. Yeah. Yeah
We saw and then the next next one is called btw's and it's also from prince isolation. Okay, three two one go
By the way, I just want to say I really do appreciate venice comics. I'm having so they're cool
Yeah in their own way
and I
like listening to you guys
Read out the comics in your individual voices and reacting to it. It's a fun. It's a fun segment of the podcast
and
I hope viny keeps doing it
Okay, bye
Yeah, I like this segment. I like the viny comics
Uh, I I also hope uh, I enjoy I enjoy uh these every week
It's it's it's you know, it's impressive that there's uh, there's more every week
It's been such a consistent segment for uh this long and you know, I'm I'm I enjoy it
Yeah, I enjoy it. Definitely. All right, uh
I saw a funny at ben and that's sonic imgir album last week. Okay, three two one go
Yeah, I don't know if you know this one that imgir album with the vats of slime and sonic
There were links in the description of some of those images that
Of like different vats and there's some really funny and the very last one
Um
A funny at ben
I don't know what yeah, I don't really understand what he means, but um, all right. I'm scrolling back
Okay
Oh, yeah, I see there is a little there is a link
Here under the desert slime. There's a link to
Oh, wait, wait, we didn't see that slime in the sky
Oh, and then under that there's a link to cave slime vats
I mean, I remember my dream about the slime cave. Do you remember that episode where I talked about my slime cave dream?
No
He really don't
Didn't someone and there was a song and my dream had a song in it. Oh, I sang I forget what you talked about
But yeah, I remember there was a funny dream
I dreamed about being in a slime cave like a cave that just had slime in it with a bunch of like
People like villagers or just like random people from around and we were all like trying to solve puzzles together
Yeah, that's right
Oh, he says if you want it back ben saying you'll have to outspeed sonic the hedgehog with your wits
Until next time Sayonara
What sonic has fished around the scroll always holding a scroll
BS the pre-order gift is those brown glove and boots you can customize the way
What you wear the game has been playing and it's actually a good sonic game as far as the gameplay feels. Okay
So it's not like he he fished up the scroll got the Kawasaki scroll
Those those like black those leather boots do not suit him at all. No
No, no, but they they do suit like the photo realistic fish
That's fish. I don't see fish
Oh, well, haven't you seen the screenshots from sonic frontiers of him fishing up like photo realistic fish?
No, I yeah, that's just he fishes up fish that look like way too realistic
for him
Sonic's the name fish is my game. That's
true
um
Okay, I have the uh, I have the viny comic loaded now. All right viny comic
Okay, so they're they're kissing they're making out they're made out
What oh, no, it's you. It's you
Um, why?
Um, oh what no fucking I wasn't done
She's turning into
Turning into water fizzling to nothingness
Good job defeating vriska give and take your fortitude is strong
But can the same be said of ben saint tron bonn get him
I didn't draw it, but I wait there's a little text underneath. I didn't draw it
But I imagine give and take really just frenching vriska like back to the throat deep
That was yes. That was that was quite clear from the
Hello, ben saint. It's I your reploid wife. We try okay. First of all, she's a carbon
It's not even close to the same thing
Come here ben saint and screw me. Excuse me. I need you. Oh, oh the lol. Okay. Hi
Excuse me. I need you to screw my plate back on. Oh, okay
Your crotch plate that is right. Uh-huh. I need your hands on me. All right
That's so what I would say
Uh, I love this I have this one screwdriver of mine. I used to fix up my vape mod when I need to
Oh, look at you ben saint come. Look. She's so evil
Why why and why is her hand purple?
I think she's a glove. Oh, yeah, purple glove. Look at that fucking gum the teeth. She's so evil. Oh god dang it
It's so small. Oh, you're a tiny little screwdriver. It's tiny little screwdriver. Hey here. I come
Hey, here I come my heart sweet. Oh, yeah, my heart. Ha ha ha step step step step step step
You're getting further away. No, I'm just taken aback by you ben saint
Uh, kiss kiss smooch smooch
Wow, he's staying. Jeez
No, I'm supposed to fuck ben saint, but he's so robust
Fizz pop boing boing boop boop boop boop boop boop boop
Oh, it's like a mega man like robot robot master died death explosion. Oh, I get it
That's fine. I didn't want to smooch an enemy stand replica of tron bond. Anyway, he got a little tear
Oh, I see you're crying. I'm crying herk. Good job defeating tron bond ben saint
Listen to me. You son of a bitch. You had that that risk of stan thing and if you told me sooner
To do battle oh
Told me sooner to do battle. I would have if I knew kissing her would have killed her. I
I'd have avoid
Yeah, I think he's saying I have avoided I had avoided kissing her to kill her and I mean that's true
I'm very I'm very sad that she's died in me. Oh my god. What's happening now? Uh, and then
drops to knee
What mega man charging sound effect?
Am I doing a mega man charge slap on the ring? Do a mega man charge slap on the butt
Over over my knee is like like I'm I'm spanking here
That's like here to punish her for having brisket die immediately. I mean, this is true. This is what I would do
In response a reverberated slap and anime girl. Wow sound. You know the one
Falia defeated
So that your hand in the slap position. Oh, hey, yeah
So oblivion fall does this thing where he sends women at me to mess with me and this was just that again
Briska. Yeah, sorry Gib. Uh, maybe he'll send another one
The cinematic the PCP cinematic universe the the Vinnie the Vinnie PCP verse. I don't know how you would say it
It's just such an absurd concept of oblivion for sending women to mess with Ben St
And it happens often
Wait, wait, it's two. Oh my god. It's two already. It's time for me to take it's time for me to drink my coffee
It's time for me to drink more coffee. I'm I'm losing it
My mind
Okay, this is another page
Ben right
Yeah, if I see oblivion fall or another girl he sends I won't hold back on it
You held back. Jeez. All right
Let's go
Is he holding back? He's immediately just
Okay, so we're walking into the darkness. Look at you. You just look like pinkie pie
I do
I like the strides some good strides here
Enter the darkness of ben sains dwelling here
And here we are Casa de la Ben St. Yeah, that's what I call it
Your home is made of cardboard boxes
Yeah, uh, my landlord is a cheap ass instead of just ordering siding
She bought a handful of things on amazon just to keep the boxes and packaging for what you see here
She saved money this way
bizarre
Oh, no that
Upsets me because it reminds me that I got texted by my land x landlord yesterday
And she wants me to pay a bunch of fees that don't make any sense
I gotta fight her about it
But I'll worry about you to fight. She wants you to to to pay fees fees
She wants my fee fee. She wants me to pay two hundred and fifty dollars for damages that I didn't do
She wants me to pay a cleaning bill which seems like bullshit to me. That's that one's like debatable
and then uh, she wants me to pay five hundred dollars in late fees
for paying rent late which like
a late fee is not
Like an egregious thing like technically she's allowed to charge a late fee, but you can't charge that's like that's like half
That's like most of my rent and that's how that's that's outlandish
Um, so I don't know. Anyway, I have to fucking argue with her about that later
Now I'm now now i'm dreading looking at my phone because I know i'm gonna have a text back from her
Dang because I sent her messages telling her to
Fuck off with that shit and she's probably gonna send me a bunch of crap, but I'm not gonna think I'm not gonna think about it
I'm not
Going to think about it
um
Anyway, think about the comic instead. Yes last page
Hey there, this is my last stop of the day
I was waiting here for somebody to sign for this package
Oh wait first I said oh my fucking god. I'm a resident. Oh say us ups driver
Yeah
Great the package is for a bowling ball saint
It's been saint, but yeah, okay sign here on the electronic pad. Oh fucking k
It wasn't as cohesive as I'd like but the idea comes through well enough
I hope a delivery truck is waiting in the darkness and gives Ben yet another thing to deal with
I'm so sad to receive this bowling ball
What is this bowling ball for it's a just such a burden
Yeah, I'm sort of like looking sheepishly over your shoulder
uh
It's just like this is just like um
Just like in albuquerque
when
Weird owl was in that plane crash and then he had to drag along his big leather suitcase in his garment bag
in his 12 pound bowling ball
And his lucky lucky autographed glow in the dark snorkel and I think I might have missed a thing on that list
But you get the idea
the bowling ball
um
Damn what will happen next tune in next time this is next time. This is really
Involved. This is really like like a big project. It's really involved. It's a big project and I it's just uh, it's remarkable
I'd like how much it's grown. It's remarkable and it's commendable that there's more of these every single week. It's uh, it's crazy
Like the the scratchy is sort of like darkness around your house is so cool
Vinny, I think you should get
I think you should invest in like a drawing tablet of some kind
And I think you should try drawing digitally because I used to scribble stuff on like a notepad
And you know
It sucked
uh
And I improved my my my pieces improved a lot when I just had a freaking
canvas in manga studio or whatever
To draw on and I had layers to work with
Uh, I think you should do that. I think you would not regret it
Uh, yeah, the the fucking the slap and then me just
Sombrily with my hand in the position. It's just really funny. It's for some reason
In the next panel like so serious
Yeah, yeah the head down
eyes eyes shrouded
And I'm just walking just like oh, yeah. Yeah, you know this happens all the time
Wait, you have a guitar and I have a guitar on my back. I think it oh
Yeah, why do I have a guitar?
I'm holding a guitar
at the beginning
I think you did you just have two and you gave me one perhaps was one of them like a ukulele
Yeah, I think that's it. All right. All right next one is called uh, where was I?
Lingering mega man questions lingering mega man questions. Okay, three two one go
Now that ben's experienced all the relevant mega man games. I want to know who is your favorite boss character
What is your favorite music and what game overall is your favorite game?
For me, I like cyber peacock from mega man x4
I like the music from x's intro stage in mega man x4 and overall I like uh mega man x4
Yep, it's it's me the new fan favorite pcp voicemail character guy who likes mega man x4
Guy who likes mega man x4
uh
Damn, I mean it's really hard. This is there's so many of them. Um
Uh
I think strike man is pretty cool. I think ring man is pretty cool
Uh, I'm trying to think at mavericks. Um, my favorite mavericks would probably have to be
Oh, there's so many of them
I like uh cut man because of kung fu cut man
Uh
Is that from like the cartoon? Yeah, he says let's say see how you do against kung fu cut man
I like uh
You know, uh off beat choice. I think pegasol to eclair from mega man x4 is pretty cool. I like him a lot
Um
Phoenix magnion is very cool. These are zero four. These are zero picks on zero two. Um
My favorite my favorite game would probably have to be zero three
Zero three or four probably zero. I mean, I think three is better. Um
Yeah, I could spend all yeah, I mean there's way too many bosses across the whole series to even think about um
Yeah, let's see zero three and pegasol to eclair. Those are the first ones that jumped to mine. I think there's a
I think he's awesome. Okay, uh next one is called
Well, it's an imager. Okay, let's see
All right, I don't think we can show this one
Oh
Okay
Well, I think the next one it's the fuck
Would we get in trouble for showing for showing that?
I don't know
I think it would
Be fine probably. Um, okay the next one
It's the purse son of
If the previous picture gets your channel demonetized use this instead smiley face
Why is the Kirby shirt still desaturated?
Oh, I didn't I didn't scroll
I didn't scroll all the way to the side to see that it's the fucking black. Okay. Okay. Oh, is it
I missed that part. It was yeah, I was too zoomed in. Okay
It's the person of color and the the kumar the kumar smile kumar smile and the flowers. I don't know why the hat
Is that
Is that like the queen's hat?
Queen had many hats
The only person like a royal sort of
Yeah, fancy hat the only person I can think of I've ever seen where a hat like that is queen elizabeth
In in like modern real life
um
Okay, next one, huh?
Duh, well, okay. Thanks for getting our channel demonetized. Lol. Next one is called. Well, it's a it's a vocaru link
three two one go
Ben and get
Happy