1, 2, 3, Sink!
And one more time. 1, 2, 3, Sink!
Okay, dope. I'll do the intro. Here we go.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever, and we've got a full house, ladies and gentlemen.
We're joined by such kooky characters as Ben Saint.
When you walk away, you don't hear me say, please, oh baby, don't go.
We've got Digibro. I'm still alive. Why?
That can be remedied. We've got Endless Jess here.
Hey, it's me, Bored James, and when I'm bored, I like to play some board games.
We've got Munchy wearing his tiny hats.
Guys, I don't want to alarm you, but I just found this book called The Bible,
and I think that it's got some crazy shit in it that we haven't considered up until this point.
And I think we deserved, you know, old classics given the Faraday.
It's not the best graphics, but I think it's got some real wicked truths in it.
How's the game feel? How's the game feel on that Bible?
Not very good. It's a hippocrit.
Damn it, hippocrit.
Uh, hi. It's me.
Uh, good. Oh, there's Tom Oliver. He's popping in and out.
You there, buddy? Tom?
Tom? Yes, it's me.
Okay, he's having issues.
Tom!
We'll see how it goes with him.
And we're today, guys, for the first time in a million years.
We're joined by an actual guest, Mr. Zen Huxtable.
I actually came here because I wanted to spite the three fans of the PCP who don't like me.
Give us their names.
I don't know their names because I...
Give us the names.
Stop hiding, though.
We're a chunt.
Y'all get down on that old-fashioned witch hunt over here.
I just have their names plastered all over my walls.
It motivates me to get out of the house.
I mean, that's what I do with my enemy's names.
I made those dolls out of them so I can stab them.
That's good.
If you put a commenter's name in, like, a voodoo doll,
is that as effective as, like, you know, DNA material or, you know...
Imagine, like, a commenter voodoo doll with just, like, a body pillow
with, like, a square screenshot of a YouTube comment on it?
It only works if the comment says first.
Tom, are you there, buddy?
I think... No.
No, we don't leave you.
Before he dropped out the first time, I heard his voice for, like...
Yeah, me, too.
I heard him mumbling about trying to figure it out.
Oh, shit.
Is this his scheme?
To get on those PC pennies without doing any work,
technically being on the episode?
Possibly.
I bet he'll pop up in, like, an hour as a ghostly whale,
and we'll, you know, just deal with that as it comes.
Okay, but anyway, people, let's get on to things
that are happening with us and fun times going on with us.
I got you, Nate.
It's got stuff. Yeah, okay.
This is what I've been doing all month, is I've been...
All three days of it?
Well, fair point. Yes.
But also, for the previous month,
is sitting around on the YouTube suggested page
and obsessively hitting Not Interested on everything
and, like, on, you know, blocking different channels,
because, like, I don't usually use the suggested page.
I usually am, like, solely in my subscriptions.
Um, but, like, it's just... there's just not enough.
There's just not enough shit to watch.
So I've been camping suggested, and, like, I will literally go in
and have, like, four rounds of reloading the page,
hitting Not Interested on absolutely everything,
reloading until I find the one video that I kind of want to watch.
And I got to say, it's a nightmare.
Yeah, I was gonna ask that.
Did you think that it would work out in your favor?
No, it did. It did work.
Does it even work?
It's also a nightmare.
I don't understand what the goal is.
So if the thing is, if you go into the suggested tab
and you hit Not Interested on a video,
it will never show up again.
Right.
And if you say Tell Us Why,
and then you say I don't want to watch videos from this channel,
that channel won't show up anymore.
So it used to be that my suggested was almost exclusively channels
I was already subbed to and videos I had already watched.
I have a couple of channels I'd like to hit that for.
Right, so I was just sitting there and I just...
Like all of them.
It doesn't fucking work for me.
Really?
I pressed Not Interested and it pops up like two days later.
Yeah, I was gonna ask.
Maybe it comes back.
I literally don't know what this feature is.
I've never gone into a suggested page.
It's like pressing the button on the crosswalk.
It doesn't do a damn thing.
It just makes you feel...
It gives you the illusion of power.
Yeah, I believe that.
The home page?
Because I'm just talking about the home page on you.
Okay, all right.
Okay, I understand now.
I'm on the same page.
Yeah, just the suggested videos section on the home page.
And there's just like a little three dots.
You can click on next to a video and click Not Interested.
But like...
Oh, no shit, huh?
Yeah, if you do that enough,
eventually, I mean, I killed anything I was subscribed to,
anything I'd already seen, you know, any stuff like that.
So eventually it started recommending me, you know,
exclusively stuff I've never heard of before.
However, here's the problem.
Is that YouTube also only recommends you shit related
to things that you have seen.
And therefore, let's say you watch a video like,
Endless Jess's New Video is a perfect example of this,
where he was talking about the Kingdom Hearts.
Like how there's like 90 videos explaining Kingdom Hearts.
So as soon as you click on one of them,
all of your recommendations are other videos
explaining Kingdom Hearts.
And it's like, I already watched a video.
That was my plan all along.
In that case, all of those had already been in my suggested
before I watched yours because of Nate's video.
So like, and that's the best part about this feature
is that when you click Not Interested and it asks you why,
and there are four options that can appear.
The first one is I've already seen it.
The second one is I don't like it.
The third one is I'm not interested in this channel.
And the fourth one is I'm not interested in recommendations
based on this video.
And it'll tell you what video it recommended you shit based on.
What the fuck button are you pressing where you got these options?
I see not interested.
Save to watch later.
Save to playlist and report.
You have to click on not interested and then it gives you a prompt.
Yeah. When you click not interested,
Oh shit.
things come up.
So tell us why.
Yeah.
Tell us why.
Oh, this is perfect.
Okay, cool.
I would never have even known that this was possible.
People have been telling me this for a while
because I always complained about YouTube recommendations being shit
and people were like, oh, well, you can filter them.
And I was like, that sounds really time consuming.
And it is really time consuming.
However, I've been doing it.
So eventually it will kill off all the shit you've already seen.
But like, again, the biggest problem is that it just recommends you other shit
that's like what you've seen before.
So if I watch like world's biggest hamburger,
it's like now I've got nothing but videos about possibly the same hamburger.
Like not even like another food item, but like just more on that.
Okay.
I hope you're going to tell me a success story here
because it just seems like you're saying like,
guys, did you know that YouTube isn't good in a certain way?
Like, yeah, it's terrible.
I expected more of you guys to have done this
because like so like literally every time I've complained about this people
like about the suggestions.
Everyone's like, oh, you can just like it works super well
if you just delete all the stuff.
I'll tell you, I subbed like I made my subscriptions my homepage
and I have never looked at that's what I've always done.
It does jack shit for me.
Yeah.
I get those suggestions days later.
I'll tell you, I did sub like six channels through this method.
So it's I saw you.
You linked that inner standing video or channel before.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
That was something that just came up in the recommendations
and it's like another like spirit science type of thing.
But it's like a guy who he's part of a group.
What was it called?
They were called like the energy group or something like that.
It was just like all the elemental masters.
I believe was their name.
Hey, I want to come back to that later.
Yeah, I know.
There's a whole bunch of channels like that.
There's a whole bunch of those weird spirit.
Like it's like a spirituality general channel.
Like they have like the binaural beats,
but then they'll have vlogs by this guy and then other stuff.
And like the video I linked you guys was just him like explaining all the big things
in the future for their company and stuff.
And it's like I like how it's it's inner standing as opposed to its opposite.
Yes.
Under standing or outer standing out.
Well, yeah, maybe Ben, let's just jump under the shit that you were.
Did you literally just in the middle of saying something or are you done?
I was done.
I don't know that.
I got the point.
I think that topic hinge on the function that we have a lot more to talk about.
Well, I guess what I was hoping to get you guys to talk about is like,
I figure you all see a lot of suggest.
I know hippo watches a lot of suggested videos.
I know.
Yeah, obviously the fact that Jesse put in his kingdom hearts video would suggest
that he also sees that shit.
I'm just wondering what you guys think about like suggested videos in general because
like that's the biggest way that you grow your channel is by appearing in the suggested tab.
For sure.
Kind of like I use them.
I kind of hate them.
I don't know if I feel like going and like curating them super.
I'm with you, Ben, but I have a slightly less like adverse reaction.
I use them.
I'm not like particularly like I want to seek them out like I would never do what you're
doing, did you?
Like I don't really want to like seek out new videos.
I have no reason to.
I'm sort of the middle between Ben and hippo where it's like,
I don't like the fact that I spend as much time as I do on YouTube,
but I don't dislike it either.
Okay, well, let me ask you this.
I'm not out here to hunt for more.
How the hell are you occupying your time?
I'm doing other things.
Like what?
You have an amazing.
It's always seemed to me, did you that you seem to have an amazingly large amount of free time
that I don't understand?
Cause I seem to have, I don't know.
I mean, for me, it's social interaction.
I talk to people a lot.
The difference between you and I is that your videos take a week in total time to make and
my videos take 10 minutes in total time to make.
So that's why I have so much free time.
This even seemed to add like the height of the content machine era.
It still seemed like you miraculously had tons of time despite producing.
Yeah.
I guess we're pretty easy to make.
It was mostly vlogs.
Yeah.
If I make a vlog or a podcast, I just like, you know, all I gotta do is hit record and
rant for that amount of time, throw it into Vegas, cut a little bit off the beginning
and a little bit off the end, render it, takes less time than it takes to record the video,
upload it, and it's done.
That's like 15 minutes, you know?
I mean, I guess you're right.
You know, you could cut out a step by just uploading as is and then editing it in YouTube.
That takes, it sucks so much.
The YouTube editor is terrible.
The YouTube editor is terrible and it takes a while to update.
Yeah, it takes longer than rendering a video, what I think.
Yeah.
Seems that way.
Especially with all my fucking cores and my processor, dude.
All right.
Like the whole thing with like recommended videos, I had watched, like I, you know, the
part of the reason I am now currently not watching YouTube is because I was one of those
people who would just watch all sorts of recommended things all the time because I would usually
just watch YouTube on my phone in bed.
So like I would, there would be like Wendover Productions who does like videos explaining
how flying works, like flights and the whole system of airplanes.
I know about him.
I'm all over there.
Yeah, those sort of things are cool and like anything about like, you know, a lot of YouTube
is just Wikipedia, but as a video.
That's the biggest thing I've been fucking running into and it's driving me insane because so
many of them are regurgitated.
First of all, if any video says 1001 as the time code, don't fucking watch that video.
That's fair.
Any video that's 10 minutes on the dot or just over, don't watch it because it's always
going to be insanely stretched out.
Like every video I click on has to like, you watch a video about like some specific food
and first they explain the concept of food, then they explain the whole history of the
city where the food comes from.
But like, you know, the cursory version and then like maybe at one point there'll be like
a sentence of unique information in the video and then like, so I've gotten to the point
where sometimes I see, sometimes I just see the thumbnail and it tells me enough of the
story.
There was one that was like opening a condom in a wind tunnel and like the picture is this
condom all inflated in a wind tunnel and I went, well, all right.
I don't need just a few minutes of that, you know.
I want to see it in motion.
I'm so sick of that shit.
I'm sick of videos that just do not have any kind of unique perspective at all that are
just regurgitating.
Like there's like, there's a channel called What Culture Wrestling where like, like five
times a day they'll post a video about some like wrestling goss or some shit and it's
just stuff from the wrestling subreddit that everyone's on.
Like you can, you can set your watch to it.
Like there'll be a popular post and within like an hour there'll be a video that is just
regitating the post on the subreddit.
I hate them.
I want them to burn and die.
I kind of feel that way.
I'm conflicted about it when it comes to Hippo.
You watch or you used to watch Trainer Tips, right?
The Pokemon Girl guy.
He, I mean, I like him more or less.
You know, I watch his videos.
That guy actually puts effort into his videos, right?
He does.
Trainer Tips is like the Casey Neistat of Pokemon Go.
He is exactly that.
He is like, he's that on purpose.
But like most of the information that he gives about the game, which is like half the reason
why I watch his stuff, probably three quarters.
I mean, he just gets it from subreddits.
Like he's not the one like doing the data mining or anything.
And sometimes I feel like, is this guy, is this, is it fair?
Is it fair that he's like, you know, he's, I mean, I know he's curating the information.
Yeah, it's not like he's not doing anything.
It's like the TLDR corner of YouTube.
All the reason why I watch his videos is because I like him.
You know?
I mean, I like him fine.
Uh, if it were just, if it didn't have anything to do with Pokemon Go, I wouldn't watch it.
Wait, was that Ghostly Voice Tom?
Is he alive?
I live.
I live in Brazil.
Oh, okay, okay.
There you go.
All right.
We were having issues.
Okay.
I don't try and get down recommended holes too often.
But what I do do, which is extremely adverse to my health.
And I actually, many times in front of the show, is I go on the trending feed every single
day.
Every single fucking day of my life.
Listen!
I want to talk about Good Mythical Morning and then fucking, uh, uh, Philip DeFranco.
That's so zoomercore.
That's the zoomercore thing you've ever said in your entire life.
Anyway, I see, I see these videos.
Zoomercore.
And they're like what you're describing.
They're just like, huh, what if we fucking deep fried a thing that was already deep fried?
What's up guys?
It's Good Mythical Morning.
Like, like, I don't, I can imagine it would be gross.
Like most of what I'm getting, I guess this is because of the type of stuff that I have
clicked on.
But almost all I get is like informational videos with like very standard editing.
Like stuff that's like, if you took one of my videos and took a sentence from it and extrapolated
it to 10 minutes, that's what I get recommended.
Like, and it's a lot of it is like NBC and shit like that, you know, or like, uh, god
one of the worst is like this, what's called munchies or something.
Yeah, I fucking hate that guy.
It was just some, uh, no it was, it was mashed, that's what it's called.
Mashed is like a food channel.
I think I've seen that.
Yeah, it's mega big, but like the videos will literally be like literally one sentence
of information surrounded by eight and a half minutes of video.
And then you're sitting there watching it.
It's not the channel that does like, really talk about like such and such a restaurant
is really bad for you or something.
Just anything.
They put out videos constantly.
You know, speaking of channels that are really massively big and also completely worthless,
I saw a video the other day.
I didn't try to, it wasn't on purpose, but I, I ended up seeing a video by I hate everything.
No, I'm sorry for your loss.
Has there ever been a more worthless form of content than I hate everything's entire
channel?
There is like, you could like just watch an entire video of this, any video, it doesn't
matter which one there, you will not find a single unique thought anywhere.
Jesse, please describe to me what the content was in general because I don't know anymore.
It's been years.
Well, it's just like, I mean, it's like the one I watched was I hate our gaming the subreddit.
And first of all, right away, I see exactly what you're fucking doing.
I see through you.
You're just, you're making a video about hating the subreddit so that it will get big on that
subreddit.
You fucking phony, but sure, sure, but that's just moral outrage has nothing to do with
why I actually hate the channel.
It's just like, he says it's not even like a human being with an actual perspective.
It's just like a chronicling of how people feel about this certain topic because everything
he says is everything that everyone says.
He never says anything unique and he's not even like a good writer.
Like nothing he says is even funny.
There's never a sentence that's put together in an interesting way.
It's just the most fucking, it's like, it's like, I would call it vanilla, but even vanilla
is a flavor.
It's like, it's like the flavor of gray, like gray paste through a, through a, through a
tube in my mouth.
Like when you click on his videos, I feel like you're expecting it to be like an angry
vitriolic rant, but it's just like a regular ass analysis video with very bland editing
everything just slides into place.
There's not even any like passion in the delivery.
Like I don't get why it's called, I hate everything.
I mean, I know why it's called that.
It's a great gimmick.
It's a perfect name.
That name has probably elevated him more than his actual content because he has the gimmick
to be able to say, I hate blank on every video.
But like, and you know, there's tons of videos about guys who rant about things angrily and
you know, they're all fine.
They're fine because they're actually, you know, ranting angrily, but like the, oh, I
hate them.
There's just no, he's not a person.
He's like just, he takes things that everyone is saying and then he just repeats them in
this monotone.
He just is the algorithm.
He is the algorithm.
That's exactly it.
He's in like, his videos exist purely, I believe, so that trillions of years from now on a satellite
in a hard drive.
There can just be like a chronicling of like how people felt about a certain thing at a
certain time.
Because beyond that, beyond, beyond a purely historical perspective, there is no work for
that.
You've described exactly how to succeed is say, say things everyone agrees with.
No, that's the funny thing about it is like, that's something that I've been criticized
for not doing before that like, like Glass Reflection, who was the first big anime reviewer
on YouTube, like he literally like went out of his way to do that, to like try to have
the perspective that was like the most agreed upon, like to, because he thought of himself
as writing an objective review.
So like, you know, which obviously that's the correct way to do it because that's what
works.
None of us are fucking successful.
Like I know that like, I'm not trying to come off like bitter, but like I know that
that that's what works.
But personally, I find it repugnant and I like, I can't, I don't understand who would
watch it.
Like who is that channel for nobody?
It's for everybody.
So when you say like objective review, are you talking about like he, he, he basically
surveys what everyone thought and they like finds the middle ground into that or what?
It's not so much the middle ground is that like, let's say it's just like all the most
stated things.
So like generally people say that this show has really good animation, but a really weak
story.
Like he's just going to say like, oh yeah, the show, you know, like you're in Logan,
for example.
Right.
And like, if, if enough, as he famously said, not to say that I don't think he agrees with
the things that he's saying necessarily and like, but he got into huge trouble one time
when he just wrote a review where his perspective was different from the majority.
Like, because he wrote about, uh, no, yeah, he wrote about no sake and he didn't really
like it.
And like just the way that he complained about it, like he got a ton of dislikes and
all these people were on his ass and then like, he kind of switched gears and started
doing like more, you know, like less of that style.
Just because of that, you know, like realizing, because it was also not working.
His channel was dying.
Right.
Um, like, I'm not even mad at the person behind the channels because like, I get why
they do it.
Cause it works.
I'm more, I'm more frustrated with the people, the audience that keeps like swallowing this
like, why, why does anyone like it?
I don't understand what's entertaining about it.
The reason they like it is that they want to have that timeless chronicle of what everyone
thought.
Like that's how they're thinking of it.
Or they just want like noise to fill the void in their, in their cars.
I don't think that, I don't think that they're that prudent.
They don't want that.
And I mentioned like, there's a lot of, there's a big market for just, you know, like who's
going to fucking remember like what some seasonal anime or whatever it's, people want to hear,
Oh, there's a good anime that I can like watch this video of and feel good about being an
anime fan and identifying as one because even if, even if they're not even specifically
validating this person's experience of the show, they want to hear that like good things
are happening in anime so I can feel like a helpful, good, you know, member of the human
race.
You know what's fucked?
I want that feeling, but I can't get it cause they're all liars and or wrong or dumb.
You're too, you digi.
I mean, this is your whole thing.
The fact that this, this is something I definitely admire about you.
You will not just accept that you, you do your whole finish or fail thing.
You will, you have to go see it for yourself or it'll just let someone tell you it was
like good or bad.
I mean, that's the thing.
Like I think the reason people can appreciate these videos is that they just have basic
taste and like what it comes down to is like, if you haven't seen enough shit, everything
is more impressive.
You know, like the first time you ever see like a kind of cool, like death scene in
an anime, you're like, Oh my God, anime is so fucking cool.
I want to watch more violent shit.
But like, you know, it could be just some basic ass, you know, regular show that anyone
who really cares about the medium wouldn't care about because they're like, Oh, you
can get so much better violence from this show and this show and this one's got great
action scenes.
And then it's like, when you've been through all that, then you can't take the other stuff
seriously anymore.
These people just haven't.
And like, I've seen too much to be placated and that's why I have to be someone on the
speaking end.
But then it's, it's like, you don't have to have seen that much to be on the speaking
end and nobody's going to check you for it, you know, and you don't try to talk about
shit like this though.
You just like watch a show and then you say how that show like what was interesting about
it to you.
There's no, you're never like, Oh, 2018, great year for anime, you know, right?
That's not my wheelhouse.
No, like in, I hate, hate when people do shit like that, when they haven't seen everything.
You know, it's like, how can you make a statement like 2018 is one of the best years of anime
if you haven't watched every show from every year?
Like, I like that.
I don't like his reviews, but I like that YMS will release his list like that like years
later so he can see everything.
That's the biggest thing that I love.
I love YMS is like old like year roundups years later.
I have like, I never watched movies like the rare times that I like of my own volition
watch a movie.
It's because he recommended one in like a best of like 2014.
Those are what inspired Finisher failed in the first place by the way.
Because his taste is so different from mine that anything he's negative about, I usually
want to strangle him because he's a fucking idiot, but like, but I like hearing him talk
about the things that he likes.
So those are the videos.
I just like that his taste is very consistent.
So you know, like if he gives a movie a super high recommendation, like, I don't assume
that it's going to be good for me, but I know exactly what it's going to be like.
You know?
Yeah, it's weird because like, I'm not even necessarily that interested in the videos.
I'm just interested in like the idea that someone is that interested in the medium that
they will watch everything from like a certain year and then like catalog what their favorites
were.
Yeah, that's crazy to me.
And then we get to reap the benefits of their, you know, like sorting out the cream from
like they spent the time and we got mixed.
You mixed your mind.
Thank you.
I maybe I did bad.
I did.
You're you're being real chaffed to me right now.
Everyone knows the chaff rises to the top of the cream.
So I'm what we know when you when you're when you're when you're threshing your milk in
the old milk mill.
What all this looking at YouTube has made me think about is the fact that like the reason
this is happening is that YouTube is replacing TV and people don't have enough to watch.
And that's why they're going to.
I don't think that people necessarily would prefer to watch these types of videos over
something legitimately good, but that they just are trying to fill as much time as possible.
And usually it's just going to keep recommending them the same type of shit, you know, that's
definitely true.
So you just get kind of trapped in a loophole of it.
And I do think there's a growing amount of like, like the audiences don't seem satisfied
by this.
Like it doesn't seem like people are happy with it.
But I know how to solve this problem.
It's not easy, but it's going to require a big push from people like me who have already
been pushing for this, but we need more people pushing for just broadening people's tastes.
Because if you like, let's say that you sub like 10 daily vloggers and like that's, that's
enough content to keep you occupied throughout each day, but it's all low effort, like basic
ass content.
Well, what if you follow like 500 channels that all post once a month and everything
they do is great?
Well, you'd be in, you know, everything you'd be watching is great and you'd have enough
to fill your day.
But like because I feel like there was a time when you could have done that.
And because of the fact that everyone's incentivized to try to be by themselves enough content
to fill someone's whole fucking day, that's no longer viable as an individual, you know,
like, so I think that if we could get the audiences to just care about a broader range
of things and to be more, you know, to just know more and maybe this, maybe this period
will help that happen when everyone becomes desensitized to this information when like
everyone fucking knows everything.
That's how I felt about our day I learned.
Everybody's got to go watch the stupid character rumble.
The only video that's good.
That's a perfect example of a great video that most people are never going to find.
But like, we need more people talking about what's the best stuff out there, you know,
you know, it's just speaking of the best stuff out there.
Let me talk about, you mentioned it before, a little book called Legend of the Ten Elemental
Masters.
Do you guys know about this book?
You've talked about it before.
Have I?
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, well.
I've read it at because you own a copy.
In fact.
Oh, right.
Did I lend you my copy?
Right.
Oh, I didn't mean to.
Well, I was...
Well, for the...
All right.
So for the last maybe six months or so, I've been using it as like a...
It's been under one of the legs of my table propping my table up.
I've seen the way that your desk works.
But I recently actually purchased some table risers.
So I got all my great literature out from under my table legs.
So I had my copy free again and I was thumbing through it on the toilet, you know, like I
do.
And I was like, man, what a great unique piece of literature.
It's like nothing else that's ever been written or so I thought, but more on that later.
And I had reached out to Oolulilia, the guy who wrote it like months ago about like, what
if I recorded an audiobook of this and he never responded.
And then on a whim, I was like, I'm going to do it again.
So I contact him again and this time he responds.
And over the next like day, I negotiate an exclusive rights deal for the audiobook rights
to produce the audiobook.
And I'm doing it.
Whoa.
Yes.
And it's going to be...
You are incredible.
You got to let the people know because people who don't know about this guy will just think,
okay, just some, I don't know, indie author or something.
Please let them know.
This is not just someone.
I think we've talked about Oolulilia on the show before about his website with his list
of ones.
There's a lot.
I could go...
You know, there's a lot to say.
You have the Clip Notes version.
Clip Notes version at least.
I mean, he's like a super OCD guy.
He's spent like, he used to be known for...
He did these extremely like hyper detailed sort of let's play like walkthroughs of like
Ultima and like Bubsy 3D and stuff and he's very strange and he was working for a long
time on this game called Platform Masters in which like seemingly the most important feature
was the extremely accurate parallax scrolling of the backgrounds as your character moved
at high velocities.
I would describe him as like a likable low cow.
Like he's somebody...
Yeah, yeah.
He would have a Down the Rabbit hole video made about him but he is not...
He's never done anything shitty as far as I know.
Yeah, nobody hates him.
He's not an asshole.
Yeah.
He's not an...
He's in no way an asshole.
He's just created really bizarre things.
Like for instance, in this book that Ben is talking about, every time an object is described,
the hexadecimal color, like the hex code for whatever color that object is is placed
in the text and is that color?
Like it is colored that way.
So like you got hex codes constantly.
The power systems are like extremely detailed.
There's like a whole infographic about how flight works.
Yeah, like it's like how characters move their arms, it's like how does a character
move their arms and like what does a different arm motion mean?
Like in terms of like pitch and yaw of like the angle of their flight and stuff.
And like he'll describe time stopping Final Fantasy style for an extended like spell animation
to play out and then he'll describe like a green, like a red like damage number with
like in scientific notation like popping out and he'll say like the number bounces three
times like a ball.
The number is in the Tahoma font, but narrower.
It is size 168 and half an inch thick or whatever.
And fuck, I forgot what I was going to say because that was too funny.
It's really fucking weird.
It's unique all right.
So I did, I recorded one take, okay.
He gave me, he authorized me to release.
If you get into bed with this man, considering the level of OCD he has, what kind of demands
are going to be made on you to meet his very particular, you know, style or requests?
You know, funny and he actually told me that he doesn't really care that much about Legend
of the Ten Elemental Masters anymore because he's actually got a new book that I don't
think anyone's heard of.
He's got a new book called Secret in the Basement.
And one of the ways that I cajoled him into letting me like Jesse.
And it's written by R.L.
Stein.
It is also, I don't know much about it.
It's also an RPG based book, so I'm sure it's very interesting in that way.
I ordered a copy, but I haven't read it yet.
It's still being shipped to me.
Oh, so it's actually out?
Well shit.
It is.
Yeah, yeah, and nobody knows about it.
And I told him like, Hey, you know, if I do this, like this audio book, like I will
plug your new book in it and like, I don't think a lot of people know about it.
So like, you know, people who like the first one, they'll find out about this new one.
Maybe this is patronizing and I don't mean to insult the man by saying this, but like
ever since maybe this is like underestimating him.
But like ever since I heard you, you tell me about him initially and like, he sounded
like a weird freak, like an OCD guy who would just be a burden on his parents and everyone
around him.
But then like you told me that like there was a time in his life where he decided he
needed to like pull his own weight and like not burden his parents.
So he wrote Legend of the Ten Ella Masters like to sell to help like support his family.
And I was like, now I like this guy officially.
Yeah, the reason the reason he published the book at all was like to, you know, pay his
parents back like some rent.
Good man.
So he could like, yeah, because like he couldn't live on his own because he's pretty messed
up or he wasn't.
I think he's better now.
I think he's gotten over a lot of his hyper OCD tendencies.
That's good.
He published it to make money to like to help support his parents or whatever.
Anyway, God's being a superhero.
It doesn't sound like like a long cow.
He sounds like the next step in human evolution.
His fucking website.
I love his phobias, by the way.
My favorite thing about you on there is fears.
Yeah, you find his website fears.
A lot of those are outdated, but at the time he was like the list of like his fears of
all his the best pages, all his dreams page, because the life page, it literally ranks
them by like how capable he is, how much he wants to do it, why he like wants to do
it, and what like how likely he thinks it is that he could do it.
And like, there's some stuff in there that he doesn't even want to do.
Like there's stuff that his yeah, wanting to do it ranking is like not at all, but he
has it on his bucket list because I guess he just thinks he should.
Yeah.
And it'll be stuff that he learned about on travel shows and stuff or like become like
like do a boxing match.
And it's like, I have no desire to do this.
And I don't think I'm capable.
It'll probably never happen.
But here it is on my bucket list.
He cataloged like thousands of his dreams.
He had a he had like a long D dream diary that I never read.
I think the website's down, but like I'm sure it's archived somewhere.
And he's he will like update how he like conquered some of those fears where like he had a fear
of open water, but he spent like years conquering it.
Yeah, that's great.
He's he's got a job now.
Yeah, he works at Walmart.
They're good.
Great.
Yeah, one.
OK, I guess the last thing about that is that so I recorded a take.
OK, he authorized me to put to do the first two acts and put them on YouTube.
So the first two acts of the audiobook are going to be on my channel.
And then he didn't want the rest of it released for free.
But he said we talked about like recording the full audiobook and like releasing it
through like Audible or something like that.
So that's the plan.
The first two acts are going to be on my channel and really, really stoked.
I recorded the I did a take yesterday, but I didn't like it.
I rerecorded it and I included the hex codes.
The first god didn't.
Yeah, the first take did not include the hex codes.
And I was like, no, fuck it.
I need to preserve the author's vision.
So I included the hex codes, doing all the voices.
It's really fun.
And you are I have I have the whole audio for the first two acts done.
And I was editing it until this podcast start.
I'm going to go back to ten tangentially related.
But I actually made an audio book a few days ago of a sideways stories
from wayside school. Oh, dude.
A book that I love for my childhood.
I think was I telling you about that munchie?
Was I talking to you about sideways stories by Lewis Sacker?
If you did, it was in one ear at the other.
I was talking about that to someone.
Yeah, that's a shame, because it's a great book.
It's a great series. It's awesome.
It is. Did you ever read?
Did you ever read the, like, math puzzles, like side series?
No, I didn't know.
I wasn't even aware that was a thing there.
Yeah, I had a couple as a kid.
They're like, um, it's it's it's, you know, it's like the teacher.
God, I forget the teacher's name.
Miss Jules, I know that kind of just read it.
Yeah, like it's like Miss Jules, like, OK, she'll write like a math thing
on the blackboard and be like, who can solve this math puzzle?
But it's not actually a math puzzle.
It's actually like a like a hidden letter.
Like you have to, like, decode the letters in the math and like or something.
I don't know. I'm apprehensive.
But is this like a game or is it a book?
It's like a puzzle book. Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Zen, yeah.
Yeah, why did you post that on your side channel instead of your main channel?
Do you want me to post on my main channel?
I'll do it. I'm just curious.
I'm curious about the logic.
I'm curious. Why did you record an audio book of sideways stories?
Well, obviously, I want to clutter up his illustrious channel
with such masterpieces like why victorious is a hidden gem and whatnot.
Yeah, exactly.
Why Dan Schneider is my idol and my guide, you know, such other pop.
I love. Yeah.
No, Zen, what what made you what made you record this?
What what what could possibly possess you?
I think it literally just popped up in my mind.
So I was like, OK, let me just look it up on Google and see if there's a PDF.
And there was. So I was like, people need to know about this.
But apparently not enough people to put it on my main channel for some reason.
So well, maybe I will know.
I'm curious about the logic because, like, for me, the logic has begun.
Do you have the rights to do that?
Well, well, I'm not monetizing it.
Is that OK? That's probably fine.
I would imagine. Maybe.
Question mark. I think I suppose theoretically they might object on the grounds
that like you've made that information of that book available without purchase.
But they can't. I don't know.
You know, I'm not worried about.
I knew like I knew that I could, you know, do Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters.
Like I could record it and put it on my channel and get away with it.
Like I knew the guy wasn't going to sue me or anything.
Well, but I just I just wanted I just I just wanted his like I wanted to be able
to say like, yeah, this is official.
This is like endorsed by the creator.
This is this is the real shit.
Well, plus now it's not it's not as though you're just doing it of your own accord.
Now it sounds like there's a deal be brokered here.
Now now you are in bed with them and now you are best friends.
Ben is really you.
I would you're best friends.
Yes, you're carving yourself out, Ben.
A fascinating niche as like internet cryptid connoisseur.
This was this was always kind of my thing.
Like I always love. Yes, you always love.
I loved I had that book by like, oh God, caffeine killed my family.
Yes, by what's her face?
I don't remember her name.
It was like it was like caffeine killed my family.
The best free cure since Jesus Christ himself.
It's like and it's like it's a little paperback book.
And half of it is like weird anecdotes about how people die if they drink coffee.
And then the rest, the other half of the book is just a list of food items
and how much caffeine is in them.
And it's full, it's full of stories like, so my grandfather drank a coffee a day
and he died at 60.
My father drank two coffees a day and he drew and he died at 30.
So, you know, because he drank twice as much coffee, he died twice as early.
That's why you know that coffee is going to kill you.
You know, I feel I feel for this guy's troubled life.
Funny, because it was a woman.
The guy who died at 30 was run over by a car.
That's how he died.
Yeah, nothing to do with the coffee, but wasn't it though?
Are we sure about that?
No, maybe it's like a sin leader or something.
The most interesting parts of this group's daily life are the parts
that aren't talked about in the podcast a lot, where, Ben, you are in league
with many, many people that I would just find that we could discuss like an entire episode about.
Like, I really like that, because when I see a channel that's done something
that I would have done, I'm just like, oh, man, well, I guess back to the drawing board.
And Ben's like, I got to contact that guy and collaborate.
Like, sometimes, like I like I made I made friends with low art, and I'm on a I'm on a podcast with him now.
That'll probably be out by the time this video is out.
You know, a long run podcast, like a series?
Well, I know I was I was the first guest on his new movie podcast, The Low Cast.
Low Art is a guy, I think he's at like 40 K subs.
He did his break, he did one with Full Metal Alchemist.
But his breakout hit was like a full series overview of Teen Titans,
where he went through like episode by episode being it was called is Teen Titans
2006 as good as we remember.
I remember that. Yeah. Yeah.
It was pretty much the inspiration for my my Poo series.
I was going to ask. Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. More overall.
Thank God. I was worried. I hope I watched the I watched the whole Teen
Titan series because I love Teen Titans as a as a youth.
And it seems like, yeah, it holds up.
Yeah, I remember it being really well.
Yeah, show. Oh, it has a cliffhanger ending.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ending that never gets solved because that stupid terror episode right at the end.
And yeah. Yeah. Right.
Where she remembers. It'll get resolved, though.
I mean, it'll they'll make they'll bring back Teen Titans.
You think they'll bring it back?
I know the question is because even if they bring it back, it will be about that.
Yeah. But will we be happy with what they think the story
about that because they tease it at the end of the Teen Titans go movie.
Yeah. I saw it in theaters.
I didn't try. I mean, that was that was always my thing
because people were always, you know, people have been whining for years and years
about Teen Titans go and I've been saying for years, you idiots.
Teen Titans go is going to bring back the original series.
Just be patient, you fucking morons.
It's a hugely popular show.
It's making the characters popular again.
Yeah. But but if it's more popular than the old one,
doesn't that mean that, like, don't go back to the old one?
Well, you got to remember, you can get into two different wallets this way
because like the kids who want the original, the people complaining about it
only prove that there's a huge audience for the old shit.
Like, I always knew they'd bring it back and I was right.
I'm always right. It's just a curse.
I never thought I'd like Teen Titans go fine.
I don't hate it or anything.
But I would never have thought that they would bring the old one back.
But if they do, I'll be I would really like it.
I want to know what the fuck's up with Tara.
Was she Tara? Was she a look alike?
Was she brainwashed? Was she just pretending?
Was she in the witness protection program?
We just don't know.
I think she was pretending.
I'm going to that's my that's what I does it.
Does it even matter?
Like, frankly, who cares what happened to Tara?
She's, you know, clearly she's alive.
And does it like all that matters is the emotional stakes of Beast Boy,
which I did kind of care about, admittedly.
I'm just in it for the shipping.
I want Beast Boy to get over Tara.
I want Raven to get that sweet green dick.
I want to see it.
It's I've been waiting for it for 20 years.
Nate, I don't I don't understand how you can say that.
It's so weird and mysterious the way that she's just there
and acts like she doesn't know him.
And like, don't you want to know why?
OK, because like because like going on, I think she's so traumatized
that she's just she wants to be done with it.
So she's just telling him, hey, man, I mean, I'd like to know.
I'd like to know the answer.
I guess I guess I don't know.
I'd take more. I'd take more.
Yeah, sure.
I don't think anyone's opposed to having more Teen Titans, right?
I will be very critical, though,
if like they're bringing like new people to make it.
Because, you know, lower.
Lowered is doing a new series about young justice,
but I never watched young justice.
So it's not as good.
I'm sure that like every comment on every video
he made about Teen Titans was, do no young justice next.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Relatively the spiritual successor, I suppose.
I'm always blown aback by how many cartoon shows
people have seen before in their lives.
I don't know if I talked about this before,
but there was a period where I banned cartoons for my life
and an attempt to become an adult, which were too great.
Yeah, yeah, that's when you that's when you look at him now.
Yeah, that's why he that's why he became huge.
That's why he was like six foot eight at 13 years old
because he stopped watching cartoons.
Ironically worked.
But anyway, I always feel like there's been like a real depth
or dearth, I think is the right word of like traditional TV shows
that I've consumed and like traditional
dearth means a lack of, by the way.
Yes, I know.
Yes, it is the right word.
I thought it was the opposite of that, but OK.
No.
So there's not a lot of things that I've seen.
So I haven't like seen, you know, 20 fucking television shows.
Watch the Sopranos.
I can remember like Flapjack.
I can remember Chowder and, you know,
you asked me to name five more and I can't do it.
Like I don't remember.
I feel the opposite.
Holy shit.
How early on did you put this ban on cartoons as soon as I knew
when an adult was fucking hilarious because I have the exact
opposite experience of I have never had any interest in anything
that wasn't a cartoon.
So like, but I also like, I am more inclined to.
It's not that I had anything against cartoons.
It just was that they were kids shit and I had.
Doesn't Homestuck count?
Well, that's why I mean, that's a huge part.
Well, no, I saw I saw live action shows as like four adults.
So I didn't watch them.
And then when I grew up, I realized that they were just shitty
and that I was right all along.
I never drew like a hard line between cartoons
and live action stuff.
But Digi, I was I was way more in your said, like, I as a kid,
I was not like, oh, I want to be an adult.
Like I wanted to stay a kid.
I fucking resented the idea that I would ever be an adult.
I was like, yeah, people used to tell me like, oh, one day
you're not going to like toys anymore.
And I'd be like, fuck you.
I'm fucking hoarding all my toys.
I don't give a shit about toys anymore.
So I also ended up liking girls, which I said I wouldn't.
But that's too bad.
Oh, fuck.
I had the same reaction to you, but only because I
was already an adult.
I said, what do you mean I'm going to grow up and not like it?
Because I'm already grown up.
What do you mean?
I already know.
I feel like the opposite of the same stuff.
They're not saying that I've not cartooned specifically.
It's all media for my childhood.
I'm not connected to it in the same way
that people can point it.
Like, oh, remember Fillmore?
Remember Disney Channel's Fillmore?
And like, what the fuck is the Disney Channel?
Yeah, it's weird because I somehow miss Fillmore.
Didn't we talk about Fillmore last episode?
Yes, you did.
It's like a thing that I saw one episode.
It's about a black guy.
I don't know, but I caught like one episode of it ever.
And I thought it was the coolest shit.
And then I never saw it on TV again.
And I was like, what the fuck was that show?
It's been making the rounds on YouTube
because there's just one quote where this girl is like.
The chicken, right?
Or the turkey?
Yeah, the girl's trying to swindle him.
And then he sees past it.
And then he's like, and by the way, Penny,
that chicken was dry, real dry.
That's right, I know about this show
because I started watching Black YouTube.
And I have two actually, we can bond over that.
Yeah, well, did you see it?
Because there was a video that was a how to black.
Yep, I watched an exact same video maybe three hours ago.
Maybe that's why Fillmore is making the rounds.
It's pretty entertaining.
Is that a video?
I need to get to watching that video
because I don't know how to black.
The funny thing about it, then, is that it's stylistically
very similar to your videos.
Unironically, it feels like a Zenhux-table video almost.
It reminded me of Fillmore and reminded me
that I had always wanted to see more Fillmore.
But I just, because this was like, I didn't have like,
I wasn't internet savvy when I was a little kid
and I saw it on TV.
To clarify, by the way, for Zen,
it's not about how to be black.
It's about how to write black characters in the video.
Yeah, I know.
That was a joke.
Yeah, Zen, you need a fucking lesson.
I don't even know what it's like.
I got a white splay here.
You don't know what it's like to be a black man.
I'm like, it's name only.
I mean, one more, this is one more account
of how YouTube just gives me the same shit.
Because as soon as I watched that, it was like all,
like, I got tons of black YouTube and like, tons of,
just like, because of your videos,
I keep getting these fucking Steven Universe analysis
and I'm like, stop.
Oh, I only made one.
That's terrible.
I made one.
Don't go down that.
I thought that I had been right.
I have the reputation of being like,
ooh, Steven, you character design suck.
I made one fucking video on it.
Jesus Christ.
Well, my recommendations are because of your video.
No, it's not.
So I thought that I had been recommended How to Black
because I watched that guy, Jack St.
And he had a couple of videos that were like,
it was like looking, okay.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
FYI, I searched ZenHuxdable in YouTube.
The second result is ZenHuxdable Steven Universe,
I swear to God, just saying.
Susan Wojcicki, she fucking hates me.
Is that, no, I'm thinking of Sarah Z.
And by the way, the name of the video
is Stop Making Excuses for the Visual Inconsistencies
of Steven Universe.
So I think I get.
That's not the one I was getting recommendations though.
It's because of his Lily Pete response thing.
Ah, okay, that's the one.
My boy Lily Pete, yeah.
Still kicking it.
You can't say that, you can't, be careful.
I didn't mean to do that, guys.
Okay, look, this is fair, there's a lot of Pete.
You're just cool, there's gonna be a two hour video
on us now.
I just wanna fuck this.
I mean, let's be frank, it would be easier to preserve
the idea of Lily Pete as a woman in your mind
if you don't watch the videos
and hear a male-sounding voice coming at you
for hours and hours and hours, you know?
Oh, let's not, let's not.
Yeah, no, I just stood in front of the mirror.
There's people like, what the what, for example,
who have a girl avatar, who definitely,
I'm pretty sure they're not trans or whatever,
but they just have a girl avatar.
That's the same thing Lily Pete does,
only I guess Lily Pete is legitimately trans or something.
How am I supposed to know the difference?
I just had this picture of Lily Pete on my wall
and I just kept on repeating girl, girl, girl, girl, girl,
girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl.
Your enemy's on your wall, just like me, I knew it.
You're more like fucking silly Pete.
Stephen, your personality isn't fear-aided,
it makes me so mad because every single video
is either like, there's no normal porridge,
there's no just right video, it's all just like,
I see, I hear what you're saying,
and I think I agree with you,
but you're just so fucking rude and stupid and gay.
I made one, I made multiple.
Yeah, I was gonna say, I like Jesse's,
I remember liking Jesse's.
I don't remember, but.
Here's the, here's the.
I made the one, I made the one Steven Universe video
that was a parody of all the shit.
Yes, yes, and it was so spot on, it was so spot on.
Even before that, I made a video about one of the seasons,
a serialized video, in fact, if anyone remembers that old
series, it did like a real review on the season of Steven Universe.
I wanna know what Hippo was gonna say
because he had the chance to speak at all.
Oh yeah.
Oh no, I had nothing to say, I was just trying to fit
a zinger in there.
Oh no.
Well no, Gib was right, the only review
that you need to make is that Steven Universe is good,
and I basically agree.
Yes, I've wished.
Season one recently, and the beginning of season two,
season one is perfect.
For anyone not privy to my content,
I just wanna establish that I don't hate Steven Universe.
Okay.
You just hate women, lesbians, gay people.
Absolutely, thank you.
Thank you for the elaboration.
I bet if you did that, I bet if you just,
I bet if you just made a video called Steven Universe is good,
and you just said like, the reasons the show is good,
and didn't even mention the reasons anyone hates it,
you would get massive thumbs down,
you would be like downvoted to oblivion,
people would come, we're gating the video,
calling you a piece of shit in a cock
and a libtard propagandist.
That's an experiment that I wanna run.
There's something that's going on around the viewer.
I'm gonna make that video.
Steven Universe is good, the video.
I have a video from way back in the day
about Steven Universe, where it was universally popular.
I mean we just did episode.
I don't remember any huge blowback from it,
but maybe it's because it was before the storm.
I think the worm has turned.
I think the worm has turned on Steven Universe
and it's become popular to shit on it.
It's really funny that he said that, Jesse,
because the people who are shitting on the show
the most right now are SJWs.
Like, they are shitting on the show
because they're insisting that it's like,
I've said, I've said for a long time
that Steven Universe is not gay enough.
Well, no, it's not that, they're saying that it's like,
oh fuck, does that mean you can explain this better
than I can? They're not biologically female,
they are fucking light holograms, they don't even fuck.
Okay. Well, everyone's an SJW.
I mean, most of the videos I see are by alt-right SJWs.
Well, that's true.
Saying the show's too gay.
Basically, the gripe that people were having
with the show is that the messaging was like,
this is a fascist like the diamonds.
And basically, the gripe that people had
was that the text in the show was
that they were being forgiving to fascists.
Ah, okay. I think so, fucking man.
God, I hate people who care about shit.
I just fucking, I'm so sick of people thinking
that their opinion matters on anything.
Hey, guys, Kingdom Hearts 3 has a lot of cool stuff.
I really like it.
Oh, wait, before we go on that, I wanted to say something.
I wanted to say that the reason I thought
I got recommended How To Black
was because I had been watching this guy, Jack St,
who did a, he did two videos.
Well, that's for the bonus episode,
we'll talk about that maybe.
But Jack St, he did these two videos looking at like,
black.com is unique quality content.
90s, like gender, like trans representation,
or like, or no, gay in stuff representation
in 90s media, because the feeling,
like the sentiment is that the 90s was full of cartoons
and stuff that had lots of like gay representation.
So he went back and he looked through it.
And basically the conclusion was like,
with only a couple of exceptions,
like yeah, there are characters who are like coded gay,
but they're all, like almost all of them
are like the butt of a joke.
And it's not really, yeah, like it's not really,
it's not really as progressive as people tend to remember.
They're in the show, but like,
how are they being portrayed?
People think they were gay characters in 90s cartoons.
I don't remember that ever, in my case.
To be fair though, when they say that,
they mean like him from Powerpuff Girls.
Okay, sure, when you're on the mark.
Who is literally Satan also.
I'm pretty sure that him is just supposed to,
him is just like supposed to be the Rocky Horror character.
Yeah, he's Tim Curry, he's just Tim Curry or whatever.
Well, yeah, he's like a combination of.
How much more fucking coded gay can you get?
That's not coded gay though.
That's just a sweet transvestite from trans fucking Fabania.
He's like a bisexual or something.
It's not coded at all, it's right there.
I mean, it's all in the same melange.
Well, I'm just trying to say that like.
Fuck that boy pussy.
The point of it is not that he's like gay
and that's why he's evil.
I think he's just a combination of Tim Curry's Labyrinth
and Rocky Horror characters, you know?
You mean, it wasn't Tim Curry in Labyrinth, it was,
was it Bowie?
David Bowie was Bowie, yeah.
Tim Curry plays the devil in that, doesn't he?
It's not Labyrinth,
but I know you're talking about it, something.
Is it Labyrinth?
Okay, whatever.
I know there is another movie where Tim Curry plays.
Wait, wait, wait.
He's got like crazy makeup.
Is this like, look, I mean, is it, wow,
newsflash before a thing was like socially acceptable
on a widespread degree, people like were critical of it.
Oh my God, what a shocker.
No, no, but like a lot of people have this idea
that cartoons in the 90s were like,
we're like pushing a gay agenda.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, so it's, okay.
I thought the, I thought you were saying.
Yeah, by including things like him.
I thought you were saying that people had the impression
that cartoons from the 90s were like positively pushing.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, they do.
Yeah, yeah, I've never heard that.
Okay, I guess what I'm saying is that I thought
that the people who thought that were the other people.
You know what I mean?
Oh God, I'm fucking lost.
I thought you were trying to say
that people were praising 90s cartoons
for having more gay representation.
No, that's why I was confused.
If you tell me that it's conservative people saying like,
oh yeah, cartoons back then really pushed the gay agenda.
That's the case, there was no need for a video about that
because those people are obviously fucking wrong.
And like, no one remembers it that way.
There were a couple, there were a couple of examples
like Robot Jones had an episode
that was like actually about the issue
and not treating it as a joke.
Nobody watched fucking whatever happened to Robot Jones.
I certainly did not watch whatever
I had ever watched.
Oh, okay, yeah.
I fucking watched it.
Did ever happen.
That's why I was interested.
That's why it was interesting
because I'd never fucking heard of this shit.
Whatever happened to Robot Jones,
I've not heard that name in many years.
The name was a hell of a bill of prostitutes.
That was like one of the first cartoon cartoon shows, I think.
Yeah.
The show famous because it had gay.
I don't know about pushing the gay agenda,
but I'm certainly pulling the gay agenda.
Like hand jobs, if you know what I'm saying.
We'll talk about that on the bonus episode.
My mic is phallic.
Can you guess what I'm doing?
Listen, we can be gay coded all you want,
but unless I'm sucking your dick, you're not gay enough.
That's all I'm trying to say.
Yeah, for sure.
Speaking of gay.
Well, about that Kingdom Hearts 3.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Kingdom Hearts 3 pushed the gay agenda.
I sure hope so.
You know what?
I haven't beaten it and I don't think Gibb has either.
Is that accurate?
Final Fantasy has way too many like fucking anime people
I just want to see Donald and Mickey.
You know, the funny thing about that is.
You see Donald and Mickey and Goofy.
Do you?
Oh, yes.
It's funny you say that.
You could have loved Mickey actually.
I played Kingdom Hearts and Kingdom Hearts 3.
I don't know anything about it.
I played those games in spite of Donald and Goofy.
I just wanted to say that I like Mickey Mouse.
I have no opinion on Kingdom Hearts.
It's a great series.
I love it.
As a person who did not grow up with Kingdom Hearts,
I have not been waiting for it for like a decade.
I played the Kingdom Hearts 1 and 2 kind of recently
and I always thought it was stupid
because it was combining Disney and Final Fantasy
and also has edgy stuff.
It's a fair assessment.
That was correct.
Upon playing them, I have discovered that it is stupid
but it is also really funny and I love it.
If every time Mickey Mouse talks about the world of darkness,
it means it's really like Mickey Mouse voice
with his like dark hood over him.
It's the funniest, coolest stuff of all time.
I think that Kingdom Hearts,
I wouldn't even have had ever had any problem with it
or assumed anything bad about it or negative
or thought it was dumb if not for the fucking trench coats
of the Organization 13,
which are the worst design I've ever seen.
I agree.
They look cool on the Organization guys.
No, they don't.
They look so bad.
Those trench coats are the ugliest trench coats
I've ever seen.
They're not the ugliest trench coats.
They're real edgy.
They're very hot topic but they don't look good.
They're beyond hot topic guys.
They're really badness.
They don't.
Yeah, I mean they're like,
they're like goth wave clothes.
No, I want to hear it.
Did you, what do you think was bad?
I'm with didgy on this.
I hate those fucking guys.
They look ridiculous.
As a guy who-
I don't, I listen.
I love them.
I know, I know.
But the thing is,
I don't believe that you actually think that.
What?
What do you mean?
Because it doesn't make any fucking sense.
Let me clarify.
I am a guy who wore a trench coat through all of high school.
I am a trench coat enthusiast.
Oh, so this makes you cringe.
I don't like that.
Just thinking back to it, that's why.
Hold on, I'm trying to look at-
You're not getting proper representation
in your media and you're upset about it.
I'm gonna give you a full breakdown.
I gotta look at a picture of it.
Okay, oh my god.
I know there's lots of weird zippers and layers and stuff.
First of all, I hate the weird, overly closed hood.
I hate the whole look of the chest is ugly.
I hate that they go all the way down
and then they have a zipper coming up from the bottom.
That's stupid.
There's a bunch of different versions of this Google search.
Just Google Xemnas, you'll see him
in the full thing like floating
and you get a good look at the whole thing.
Google Organization 13, there's one of a generic.
I don't know.
You can't see his face.
I've just always found them really ugly.
In fact, when I used to go to anime conventions,
it would be fucking everywhere.
It's like giant groups of people wearing the trench coats
and the hair looks bad enough in the games,
does not translate to reality at all.
First of all, it looks absolutely fantastic in the games.
It's anime hair.
Anime hair doesn't look good in reality.
Like the one you just posted in the chat of Xenohort,
I really dislike.
Why?
This is one of the best designs of all time.
Did you consistently say Xenohort and it's Xehanort?
Xehanort?
Even Xehanort.
This is Xemnas, god damn it.
His name is Xemnas.
He's the nobody in Xehanort.
Have you possessed Terra's body, god damn it?
The problem here is that Digi is realizing something
that he doesn't have the courage to fully articulate,
which is that anime sucks and is gay.
The entire anime aesthetic is just wrong and bad.
I think there's something to what you're saying, Jesse.
Anime is bad.
I don't know any anime that looks like this, though.
Like, I don't know any fucking line.
I don't know Bleach.
They don't wear-
This is clearly anime stuff.
This is why the trench coat looks bad.
Like, I understand looking at this.
It's the fact that the sleeves are, like, flared
and also that the material is not, like, leather.
It's sort of like a plasticky, shiny, weird thing.
No, it's heavy leather, god damn it.
It looks sick.
It does not look like leather.
It looks like, like-
I'm really into this image that Xen just linked.
This is my favorite.
I hate it.
I think the main thing about it-
Leave Jiren to me, Goku.
Who the fuck is Jiren?
He's fucking the alimau from Dragon Ball 2.
Is he the cat?
No, he's the super jacked gray alien.
Okay, I figured out who's the best character.
I figured out everything I hate about this trench coat.
First of all, the biggest problem really is that it's so tight
in the midsection.
Oh, he wants to do-
To emphasize his manly figure, god damn it.
He looks awesome.
He's a fucking stupid fucking Jiren.
He's a big buff baby boy.
He's a vital boss.
He's really terrible.
Jiren is awesome.
He's a tough-toothed baby who can dance like a man.
Ew.
This isn't-
Wait, is this a new Dragon Ball?
The cat thing was weird-looking, but in a good way.
You fucking dance on your corpse.
This isn't a bad way.
No, Jiren is good-
Okay, first of all, please be aware.
This is literally-
He's fucking Star Trek, look.
Yeah, he is.
He is literally Captain Picard.
This is the most powerful entity in all of Dragon Ball.
This alimau, gray muscle alien piece of shit.
Wait, I thought the strongest entity
was like the little old man or whatever, or like-
Well, yeah, that's God.
Did they-
Oh, that was a red herring.
Okay, that's Lord of the Rings.
How many times are they gonna introduce
the new strongest beings?
No, no.
God damn it, I actually watched the series.
I know the answer.
As long as the series goes on,
they're gonna keep doing that.
Jesse knows.
That's the show.
The guy that Digi's talking about, Lord Zeno, is God.
There is none higher than him.
But like, there are multiple universes.
Although they did make the second Lord of the Universe.
There's like 12 universes.
There were two of them?
And Jiren is the most powerful dude
in one of the universes.
I don't think he's as powerful as the little boy.
Oh my God.
Lord Zeno is so cool.
Yeah, I just-
What are you talking about?
No, I love Lord Zeno.
Lord Zeno is the shit.
He's the coolest.
I fucking love him.
He's so cute.
Yeah, he's rad.
These are all the show notes, people.
Lord Zeno looks like shit.
No, shut the hell up and get out of here.
There's fucking Final Fantasy,
there's fucking Kingdom Hearts,
heaven let your light shine down.
A hoodie looks really funny.
This color scheme is so close
of the supporting trans rights.
I don't understand it.
Lord Zeno is a character that I invented.
I respect him.
I like Lord Zeno.
I'm not a fan of the other guy.
I'm not a fan of the G.
Okay, Digi, I still don't understand
why you don't like the Kingdom Hearts 13 or trans guys.
Well, I changed it to mine.
Step by step.
Okay, I want to hear.
I do want to hear.
All right, first of all,
the fact that it hugs so tight
in the midsection looks really uncomfortable.
That's why it looks cool.
That's, I'm not a fan of that.
Second of all.
No, that's just effeminate.
It's fashion.
I really hate that they unzip from the bottom up.
Like, what?
That's stupid.
Oh yeah, that's a little weird.
That is weird.
Have you never seen a double zipper?
It can unzip from both sides.
But it goes all the way to the top.
So we'd have to lean all the way down.
You're assuming they would unzip off.
It's not all the way zipped down.
It's fashion number one.
I'm just wondering, like, when I look at it,
I can't help but think, like, which way does he go
to take it off?
Does he just go up and like...
He pulls up, goddammit.
I think he's designed to be over from the top.
It's a double-sided zipper.
He only has it pulled down as far as his hand
can comfortably reach.
It's style and functionality.
If you think of the power of the Organization 13,
they could probably use telepathy to move a zip
without having to bend over.
They'd just do their little hand motions, like...
Axl can just, like, shoot fire at it
and make it, like, you know, move with that or something.
You just blast it with, like, flour.
I'm also just not a fan of this, like, all flat black aesthetic,
like, nothing.
It's matte black, and it looks dope.
Matte black is for technology.
It's not for clothes.
I disagree.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
OK, I just Googled Organization 13.
Are all these characters, like, real?
Like, are they actually in the game?
They're in the game.
No matter what the question is, yes.
OK.
Whatever you want.
It's such a bad series.
It's so terrible in every way.
Look, look, we all know it's dead,
but they've just released the last one.
None of us have beaten it yet.
Like, it's getting put to bed, like, today.
You know, I bought it, like, this weekend.
I bought Kingdom Hearts, like, thinking that I wanted it,
because, you know, I grew up playing the original games
back in the day.
Did you play the sequels to two, all those other ones?
I played one and two when it came out.
And so, you know, I bought my Kingdom Hearts 3
and I took it home.
And then I looked at it and, like, I don't want this.
I don't even want to fucking put it in.
You'd like it.
This is Kingdom Hearts is fucking stupid.
Like, I just realized all at once.
You would love running around with it.
I just suddenly realized.
I suddenly realized.
And having great Toy Story adventures looking for Andy.
I suddenly realized that I've always hated the series
and just I never, I never knew.
I wouldn't admit it until I had the game in my possession.
This is why I mentioned earlier
that I had not grown up with Kingdom Hearts,
because, like, I bought it as soon as it was available.
And I have been having a lot of fun with it,
because it is a new PS2 game in 2019.
I've been waiting for a long time
to be able to play another PS2 game.
It plays exactly like Kingdom Hearts 2,
little different, you know, with, like, more stuff in it.
But, like, it's colorful.
It's got, like, crazy cartoony characters
that are stupid and funny and cool.
And the story is, like, it's for babies,
and I really like it.
I mean, it's not, like, a shit game.
I have heard something.
The guttons are unwatchable in the first three years.
Most of them are.
Some of them, like, are surprisingly, like, oh,
that feels like it was, like, directed or, like,
was taken from, like, like that, they, like, I don't know.
I'll just say that, uh...
Looked at a human being, like, I have a conversation
and, like, animated it like it was a person.
It's like, that was okay, but a lot of it is, like, awful.
You know what I was wondering?
I just, I don't know what...
Is there some mandate?
Is there some reason why they had to make every,
like, every conversation and every, like, cutscene,
like, paste so awkwardly with weird pauses between speech?
That's why there's stuff on the board.
Like, is this a thing where, like,
because they translate from Japanese to English,
there's, like, tons of dead space left?
I, like, why did they do that?
I would imagine so.
Yeah, but, like...
Yeah, but there's so many, there's so many dubs out there
that are good and localized really well.
Exactly, that's what I'm saying, right.
You can edit any cutscene down, you can just cut bits.
You're playing, like, background music.
There's no audio, like, to worry about.
Yeah, I know you mean.
I have no patience for that weird,
stilted Asian anime bullshit.
So is it, like, is it...
So is it just, like, directed like that
from the get-go or something or what?
It has always been like that, yes, absolutely.
And I don't know why.
Like, I guess it does feel more video game-y,
AKA shit.
Like, I should be pushing X-men right now.
It's not a good thing to have those parts, yeah.
But yeah, it's just bad though.
And, like, they could fix this.
You could just cut out these little chunks of waiting.
I don't know, it's baffling to me.
Why the fuck did it?
I don't know, I like it.
I mean, I don't like it, I don't think it's good,
but, like, it just feels fun.
Like, it feels just, like, it feels like it should
as a Kingdom Hearts game.
And I already know what I was getting myself
to do when I bought it.
I don't know, like, I know what I did.
I'm sure people can play the game.
I've been informed of something in my comments
that has greatly disturbed me
and made me even less excited to play the game
than I already was, which is that
there are no Final Fantasy characters in this one at all.
Is that true?
That's what I have heard, that's what I have heard.
What is the point of the series then?
It's all, it's, what the fuck, why?
Look, the presence of Final Fantasy,
look, obviously, it leads with Disney.
The presence of Final Fantasy-
Nothing would be in it.
I, me too.
The presence of Final Fantasy has always been
kind of a more thematic press.
I mean, it's always been bad.
They've always done the Final Fantasy stuff badly,
but it's like the whole genesis of the series.
It's part of it.
You guys gotta understand, this is the new Square Enix.
You're gonna have to download the Final Fantasy 7 DLC pack
to get the ex-
I, unironically, think that's, look,
I haven't beaten the game yet.
I've heard this from people that, like, DLC and, like,
like, end game content is, like, zilch,
and that it will be, like, patched or it'll be DLC
or maybe, like, they'll make a Final Mix version of the game.
I hear something like that is coming.
I can't confirm it yet.
But, like, yo, the, like, at the very least,
Leon, Yuffie, Eris, and even Cloud and Sephiroth
have been in every game as actual characters
that we care about in Kingdom Hearts Lore.
Why in God's name would we not, like,
address those characters in Kingdom Hearts 3
unless they just, like, ran out of dev time?
And besides that-
The best part of every game is the Sephiroth fight.
You go find him, he's hanging out on a cliff somewhere
and you go, I'm gonna fight ya and he's gonna go,
well, I'm gonna suck Cloud's dick once you kick my ass
and so then you fight him and it's hard and it's fun.
I'm mad. It's fun, though.
It's just good.
I mean, sure, the story is terrible.
It's just, like, where's Cloud?
I don't know.
Fight me. Okay.
Beat him. Get Cloud.
Okay.
That's how it goes every single time.
But it, like, it's just, it's,
the thing about Kingdom Hearts 3,
this is my observation.
It's that it is bizarrely, like, in depth
and bizarrely large amounts of effort
were put into some aspects.
If you get to, like, the Toy Story world,
there's, like, a whole fucking-
They, like, made a second game within Kingdom Hearts 3
that's, like, clearly a parody of Final Fantasy-style games
like Final Fantasy XV that, like, exists within,
within the Kingdom Hearts universe,
within the Toy Story universe, exists this universe.
It's bizarre, but it's dope.
But, like, so that had insane amounts of effort
and energy put into it.
Like, but where the fuck are my Final Fantasy characters?
Why is that just, like, not here at all?
At all?
I don't understand the weird lopsidedness
of the, like, emphasis of the development.
Is it because they're gonna fill it out later?
Is this more Final Fantasy XV syndrome
of they just didn't finish the game that they wanted to?
Because the fact that we don't see Leon
and those other boys that have been in every game
as, like, vital buddies of ours is bizarre.
What if it's because they want you to think,
well, shit, if I want to see all the Final Fantasy characters
interact, I'm gonna have to buy Dissidia?
I mean, that's true, except there's no story
in the new Dissidia, none.
You'd have to play the PSP games from 10 years ago.
So you got nothing.
They're not giving us what we need.
We're in expense.
Sounds like hate and all.
Okay, most fucking games.
Most important questions.
What another fucking thing?
Why the hell hasn't Donald Duck
who's turned my voicemails?
Why the fuck does Donald Duck
give these up both?
And he's gonna have to respond
to all the various emails I sent him.
I want to collab with you, Donald Duck.
I want to know what's in your mind.
I want to be on my interview show.
Donald Duck, why do you not think it's okay
for you to just ignore me?
Like all the other people that you just fucking then kill
and stuff in a dead ditch in Africa.
Why do you think you can treat me like the way
you treat all your horrors and your hookers?
I've known that Donald Duck is not
in Tales Get Strolled, Munchie, for the last time.
And another thing, why the fuck is there not
a goof troupe level and a DuckTales level
in Kingdom Hearts?
There really should be.
Goofy and Donald kind of got the shaft
in terms of their development.
I mean, I'm glad Scrooge is in it.
I love Scrooge.
Scrooge is there, yeah.
He's good.
He's a good guy.
I don't know the thing.
What's the deal with that Kingdom Hearts story?
It's so weird.
Why is it so convoluted?
And how come the games are all on one?
They have such weird names.
There's decimals in there and numbers and fractions
and the names of the games.
I don't know how to read it.
I don't understand.
OK.
How do you even pronounce Xenor?
That's my new character.
Guy who doesn't understand Kingdom Hearts lore.
But the best, every most important question,
who's the best organization 13?
Answer, Seix, Dunn.
Xemnas, it's Xemnas.
Mark Xen, you freaks, you fools, you gays.
But there are keyblades, and then there
are, get ready for it, keyblades.
Keyblades.
No, I won't let you mock that.
That's an actual hilarious joke from our lecture
that we all made together.
And I won't let you soil it.
That's culture.
People now do that.
They go, keyblade.
Keyblade, yep.
I don't do it.
I mean, has your, I gotta imagine.
You were there, Jesse.
What?
Has your video, how the views of your video,
have they spiked?
Have they spiked with the release of three?
Yes, they have spiked.
It's still sitting at around something like
three, two, four hundred, like thousand views.
Which like for a video that,
I mean, I'm not trying to toot my own horn,
but for a video that's like fairly well known,
such as that, those are relatively low numbers.
It's not like it's surging about like
hundreds of thousands, like every month or whatever.
But like, people are coming back to it,
they're watching again, and it's certainly,
like, again, not to suck my own dick too hard,
but like, it was the primordial,
let's explain the crazy Kingdom Hearts lore video
that many people are copying right now.
And by the way, I was gonna say this before,
but let me say it now.
So Barry Kramer, former editor of Game Grumps,
made a video.
I saw this on your stream.
I was watching your stream.
Really, really quick tangent.
Ross follows me on Instagram, that's it.
Oh, dope.
That's cool, that's cool.
I fucking hate Ross.
Oh, well, there you go.
It's fine, because he's fucking,
I don't know, he's just, he's annoying.
But he's outside of the context of him
trying to be funny on Game Grumps.
When he's talking about animation and stuff, he's,
he's really good.
He's still annoying.
I don't like the stuff he makes.
He's annoying.
Everyone ever involved with the Game Grumps,
they're all cool, please give me a job.
Deliver me from the procrastinators
and give me a real job.
But, Hating Ross made it really satisfying
when he was straight up the villain
of that World of Warcraft series they did.
That was a really great series.
Wasn't he the one trying to like,
help everybody have fun and, you know.
Well, sort of, but he does a terrible job
and is an idiot and ruins it for everyone.
Okay, well let me, let me finish my point about Barry.
It's, it's just that,
so Barry is one of these pretenders to the throne.
These, these princes, biting it by kingly heels.
You know, who made like a, it was like,
it was like a good enough summary of Kingdom Hearts.
And I appreciate, it's like animated.
I'm sure he did a good job.
I have not actually watched it.
Great, but I heard from one,
he says like the beginning of the video,
someone in my stream yesterday told me,
Nate, did you know Barry has only played Kingdom Hearts I
and half of Kingdom Hearts II
and yet this man, Danes,
to make a fucking story summary of every,
talk about reading Wikipedia and making videos out of it.
Wouldn't you fucking finish the,
if you're making a video about the story.
He didn't even finish two a good game.
Okay, well for what is it a good game?
You know what's even worse than that though?
What?
I love this man to death,
but AVGN made a whole 10 minute video about Kingdom Hearts
without having played any of them.
That's, that's.
Or I think he was playing his way through them,
but like he didn't know anything about that.
He literally just made a video that's like,
what's up with all the titles?
Whoa.
And I was like, what are you doing?
You know, that was, that was a video.
I liked that video.
I gave it a pass because it's AVGN.
But I would have preferred like an AVGN video
about any of the Kingdom Hearts games.
Like if he did.
Imagine if AVGN did a real video
reviewing Kingdom Hearts one or something.
Or like all the Crafty Spinoff games.
Yeah.
That would be.
Yeah, yeah.
Making them faces.
Saying, oh this is not.
This is the shit load of fuck right here.
That's what I come to see.
That's what I like.
That's why it feels like a cheap like paycheck cash grab.
Like need a video for this month.
You know.
Kingdom Hearts is hot.
Not going to play the game.
I don't even know.
Just going to read Wikipedia.
I'm not saying this is,
I'm not saying this is any better,
but like I wouldn't be surprised
from the way that he framed it at the start of the video
that like people were just requesting him
to talk about it a lot.
That like everyone wanted him to do Kingdom Hearts
that he didn't know anything about it.
So he just made a video being like,
hey, I don't know anything about it
and it seems confusing.
So, you know, but like the way he presented it though,
it's like, it's simultaneously as that.
But it's like, yeah, but the title and thumbnail implies
that you're actually going to say something
about Kingdom Hearts and you're not.
So it ended up feeling like clickbait.
It felt like some.
I think this meme.
I think that honestly, I swear to God,
I mean, I've been V for like a fucking decade
and longer talking about Kingdom Hearts and shit
and like discussing Lauren whatnot.
And I really think the meme that this story
is too complicated to figure out has deeply set in,
despite the, like there's many infographics
and like meme posts about like,
it's really not that hard guys.
You just have to think a little bit.
It's like, I had like, like going through it
for like, you know, one and two.
Just after the lecture, I was like, yeah, I'll play it.
I think I was already playing at the time.
But like, I wanted to know how complex it was
because I like complex things.
Like the parts of the Caribbean three,
the people say, oh, that's such a convoluted plot.
I love how convoluted it is.
I love trying to follow along.
And so I was like, Kingdom Hearts
is probably going to be something I love.
And it's not even that complex.
It's just like a combination of a few things.
It's edgy and stupid a lot of the time.
It has a few, like a lot of the games in the series
have silly names, like titles that you would,
like very unconventional titles.
And like side games have lore that comes up
in the main series.
That's really the only three things
that make it sort of confusing a little bit.
But beyond that, it's not that much.
You just need to know.
There are convenience in it more than it's complicated.
It's the real thing.
The problem is that there's actual nonsensical lore
that does not make sense and like is hard to recognize
as you play through.
Like what bothers me about this with Kingdom Hearts,
like Jesse just said, it's more that it's inconvenient.
It's more that it's broken up into too many places.
It's too hard to follow all that.
But like, I think that also a lot of this
is just people are fucking stupid.
And like, there's so many people who are just like,
like going by what I heard people say
about Final Fantasy VII online,
I thought it would be literally incomprehensible.
Like the way people talk about that game is like,
it's so confusing and so weird.
It makes you think so hard.
It's got so many crazy mysteries.
These people haven't played the game in 20 years.
Or like Evangelion or something where they're like,
oh, it's like, it's such a head fuck.
And it's just like, it's like,
if you've never had exposure to any complicated story,
then yes, you know.
I hear that shit and it's like,
well, I followed it perfectly fine at nine years old.
You fucking retard.
So, whoa, did you, whoa, this story's got like themes.
And like, it's trying to like say something.
It's like, it's more about like just that sometimes
you have to fill in the gaps of what was going on.
And like, the show gives you the tools to do it
or the game gives you the tools to do it.
And those people just don't know how to use those tools.
You know?
That's exactly right.
And I think that then when you go read a Wikipedia entry,
and it's true, these holes are there
and you haven't actually put in the effort
to play the fucking game that gives you the resources
to make obvious inferences like that, then-
Final Fantasy VII tells you-
Yeah, you're high and dry,
because you didn't play the game or whatever.
Everything in the lore is in the game.
You can find like houses and like documents.
You could read about Genova and like Professor Gast
and where like the Shinra Corporation came from.
They don't want to do that.
They want to read what you read.
But it's all there.
There's like the fucking glossary and stuff
and like character bios that are in Kingdom Hearts III.
After you meet a character,
you can go read about them.
If you have a little trouble, like who was that again?
You can find all the information
in all three of the Kingdom Hearts main games.
I mean, this was-
I go and read that because like most other games
that have things like that, I don't need to read it.
But like in Kingdom Hearts I do.
And that's really the only difference.
Once I have read it, I get it.
You gotta remember we're dealing with a gaming pop culture
where like the last of us is the greatest depth
and cinematic achievement imaginable in media.
Like fucking, you know.
Or God of War with like people are saying like God of War
has the best story in a video game.
Every fucking day of my life for the last year,
every fucking day I wake up and I see,
this video was good until you called Joel boring.
How dare you be smirks the name of Joel.
Why are people so defensive about the last of us?
I don't understand.
It's like just a-
It's a mediocre fucking story.
It's not, it's fine.
I didn't even say it was bad.
It's just fine.
Why do people care so much about that fucking game?
They need their golden idol to show people as like,
this is why you need to take my dumb ass opinion seriously
on video games matter.
I didn't waste my time playing these hundreds and hundreds
of hours of meaningless games that do nothing but fill a void
that is the lack of accomplishment in my life
that I make up for by playing these vicarious hero characters.
No, no, no.
This is important in like making me a good person.
I like am Joel and shit.
And I like did save the princess or whatever.
That's not you guys.
Oh God, stop Nate.
You're gonna make me fucking,
you're gonna make me fucking cry, all right?
You should.
Someone needs to call a witch doctor
because I'm seeing several new colors right now.
I wanna make a statement that seems obvious
because it is and everyone's already said it before.
But I have not spiritually resonated with this
until just now.
I Google search Kingdom Hearts 3 full game movie
and I'm watching it.
And the first thing is this bizarre wizard man
telling Anna Mayman that he needs to go on an adventure
for whatever reason.
Is it Merlin?
Maybe, I have no idea.
Anyway, I'm like, okay, yeah, Kingdom Hearts,
gotcha, understand, goofy Donald there, okay, I understand.
Then they go to Hercules or land
and I can like easily in my mind think,
okay, Final Fantasy, Disney, Donald, Goofy
and stuff like that.
But for some reason, now they're in a Disney renaissance movie
and then they approach Hades.
And I hear James Woods.
I think Munchie might be a little behind
on his Kingdom Hearts.
I hear James Woods giving the same fucking voice
he's been giving for 20 years now.
Old and disheveled, like fucking choking up
in the middle of recording,
doesn't he wanna do another take
and then he's gonna die too soon
and then actually be able to get the same amount of shots.
He loves Joe Ladies.
And I just hear him say, huh, fucking Hercules,
more like Jercules, huh, get it?
And I'm like, are you fucking joking me?
Like Kingdom Hearts and Disney are the same game?
What?
They're fucking, that's so weird, dude.
I can't believe that fucking Final Fantasy Disney
are in the same game.
Like I didn't believe it.
Like I knew, okay, Donald Goofy got it.
Like I didn't actually believe that Disney movies
and Q's of Final Fantasy were actually together.
I didn't believe that it couldn't be true.
Okay, the weird thing about that observation, Munchie,
is that I also had that same revelation
as I was playing Kingdom Hearts 3
because I've just been studying lore.
I've been hitting the books about Heartless
and No Ways in the Dark and Keyblades and I'm like,
man, that's where I've been for 13 years.
I finally play Kingdom Hearts 3 and I'm like,
whoa, it's fucking Mike Wazowski, Motherfucker!
Jesus Christ!
You think about all this lore stuff,
but the actual like moment to moment experience
of playing Kingdom Hearts is like 90% only.
Yeah, it is 90% Disney shit.
I fucking like Kingdom Hearts, I was sick.
Oh my God, it's Hercules!
It looks like Hercules!
Oh my God!
Hercules!
The funny thing about talking about the plot
of Kingdom Hearts at all is that it's not the forefront
of why people care about Kingdom Hearts.
Like, I don't think that many people play it for the show.
It's not what the games are about.
The first game is just about a kid
trying to get back to his little girlfriend
and that's really relatable.
Like, it's not really, that's why everyone loves the series
in spite of the fact that everyone hates the lore
because it's not about the lore at all.
The games are about Rapunzel's fucking sexy feet
and you want to come on those feats,
you want her to jack you off those feet
and so you go to the Rapunzel world
and you get what you came for.
Like, they're also about sweet boss battles.
I have a disease, an exotic disease,
there's no way to cure it.
I'm on my deathbed.
Make a wish foundation comes to me
and they say, what do you want?
We'll give you anything.
And I just say to him, make all the Final Fantasy III cutscenes
real and they're happening to me.
I want Hercules to talk to me.
I want Hades to talk to me.
I'm sorry, I'm getting reactivated pissed off
about all the Kingdom Hearts lectures
that are out there now
because I'm really thinking about how the joke
with Nate's video was that nobody cares.
Like, that's the point of-
I did repeat that many times.
Like, the main point of all of the lectures
for the most part is usually that it's-
The climactic moment at the end was like,
they're like, Nate, are these games worth playing?
And I say triumphantly, okay, well, first of all,
if you're playing for the story, stop.
That was the thesis statement of the whole lecture.
That's the thing.
So if that's the case,
like when all these people are making these videos
that are like, whoa, explaining the crazy story of Kingdom,
nobody cared in the first place.
Like, why do we-
We don't need an explanation leading into the new game
because we're not playing it for the story.
We don't need to know what happened.
Just put it on, look at the flashy lights
and fight, you know, Disney villains.
Like, that's the point.
My favorite thing to do in Kingdom Hearts 3
is to run up walls.
There's so many walls you can just run up.
You just walk up to the wall and you press forward
and you just start running.
And then you can do, you can press square
and you can kick off the wall
and then you can jump and you can double jump
and then you can do an air dash.
You can just be really high up
and then you fall down and you smash things.
I think because I haven't like seen-
You can explain the story of Kingdom Hearts.
You can explain the story of Kingdom Hearts in one sentence.
It's a fun anime game with Disney shit.
Woo!
That should be all the videos.
I think because Mickey Mouse and Donald Look
are just like icons, right?
Like, I haven't like seen any shorts of them.
I don't know anything about them as characters, really.
But when I see Hercules,
a film that I've seen many times before
and like I have like an emotional connection
to Hercules, the Disney movie.
And I see him looking at bad evil hoodie.
Heaven, let your lights shine down.
Whoa!
I see him looking at him menacingly.
I just am fucking, like I'm seeing too many colors right now.
I understand what it's like to be fucking colorblind
and I'm saying I'm seeing way too many colors.
The best part of the game by far.
To clarify what I was trying to say before
is that like why I was upset thinking back on it
is the fact that these people making these videos
don't get that.
Like they don't get that that's the, like your lecture-
That's the appeal.
Your lecture was making fun of the story.
You're like, hey, I am explaining this whole story
because I happen to be such a huge fan of Kingdom Hearts 2.
Incidentally, I'm telling you-
Okay, I gotta be that guy.
I gotta be that guy.
So it's like, is that like an in-joke then?
Like why does the story have to be so convoluted?
Okay, even in the games,
Nomura clearly takes this very seriously.
I was gonna say like, yeah, you can say that
you don't play for the story, but like someone cares.
Look, I just wanna say-
I just wanna say, look, the butt of the joke I feel
in the Kingdom Hearts lecture is that look,
I am the joke because I care when I should not.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Is that like the whole point is that like
these games are looked down on for having
like a dumb premise and a dumb story.
And you're like, yeah, they do, but I played them anyways
and I obsessed over them and I learned it all
because that's the way I am.
Anything I consume, I learn everything about it
because that's you, that's your personality.
And so like for you to make this lecture,
yeah, you are the butt of the joke.
Like, hey, I'm a 27-year-old man
talking about Kingdom Hearts,
but like the whole time you're presenting it as,
this is, I'm explaining this because it's funny
and stupid and doesn't matter and you don't need to know it.
I'm like, that's kind of the point of the lectures
is that for the most part again,
we talk about things that like we have
this insane knowledge of that no one else cares about.
Like that's kind of the joke.
That's the premise of the lectures to begin with, right?
That's what I'm saying.
That they are a joke.
So like, so then you get to these other people
who are making videos about this
and it's like they haven't even played the games
and they're like trying to sincerely explain the story
as if like that really matters.
And it's like, no, the whole point was
that it doesn't really matter, you know?
I haven't seen any of these like other explanation videos,
but I can pretty much imagine what they are.
And like they probably come at it from the angle
that they're doing some kind of weird
like consumer advocacy thing.
Like they are providing you a service.
Like now you don't, like now you know.
Like now you're up to, I'm getting you up to speed.
Like you need to know this information.
This is why you should watch my video.
So you will know the things that you must know
before you get into Kingdom Hearts 3.
Yeah, yeah.
Here's my advice for if you want to play Kingdom Hearts 3.
It's if you do, if you care about the story,
then if you plan to watch all the cut scenes,
just go play the other games first.
If you don't, then just skip the cut scenes.
Like there's no reason to watch a YouTube video
explaining it all and then play the new game
and expect to like the story.
It's like, if you were going to like the story,
you would go play the other ones.
Why jump in now?
Why come in late like this?
But they want to be on the new thing, did you?
They want to be talking about it.
I don't even think it's working
because it doesn't seem like many people actually care
about Kingdom Hearts 3 now that it's happening.
They want to be able to say, oh, Kingdom Hearts,
Kingdom Hearts was my childhood.
Yeah, that's cool.
Because they don't even say that half of them are like,
I haven't even played the goddamn games.
I haven't played one and a half.
They want to be able to talk like that anyway.
I happily wear the hat of Elitist on this subject.
If nothing else, I happily adopted.
And yes, on just that level,
I feel comfortable shit talking people
who are going to try to talk about these games
without doing as much effort as I put into play them.
Whether or not, you know, I just did it for fun,
but it became my full-time job later in life.
And so, you know, I'm the expert.
Who the fuck is Barry Kramer?
Who hasn't even, honestly,
that makes me more angry than AVGN.
Like that he gave up on Kingdom Hearts 2.
Like, God, like if you're making this video,
go back and finish the game.
Yes.
Or you should feel bad.
It's got to be relevant to the SEO optimization, bro.
And you know what?
This ties back to that thing
at the very beginning of our talk today.
It's like, when you are a YouTuber,
the pressure is now on you.
Produce content.
Don't worry about research.
Okay, well, let's not blame.
I know that's the nature of the game.
But still.
I don't think you can blame that on Barry.
Because Barry puts out a video once.
No, no.
Yes, you fucking can.
If Barry wanted to make a Kingdom Hearts video
and SEO optimized,
then he should have gone back before the game.
But he knew the game was coming out.
He had fucking time.
It's not like it snuck up on him.
No, no, that's all fair.
I know he tried to get it out in time for the game,
but that was not for SEO purposes.
He did that because it's sexy
to get something out about a game
right before it comes out.
Like, everybody wants to have that experience.
But like, don't do it
if it's not something you actually care about.
Like, I have every season,
like season three of Attack on Titan or something
will come out.
And I'm like, I'm not going to write a video about that
because I'm not going to watch Attack on Titan
seasons one and two
so that I can have an opinion on this, you know?
But Barry's like, I'm not going to play those games.
He wasn't even successful financially.
It was a failed movie.
It wasn't even like the most popular thing.
So why is anime man talking to him?
Why was he talking about the main game?
Hercules world is in every single Kingdom Hearts.
It's relevant to the Kingdom Hearts main game.
What?
He's a recurring character.
You go to it each time.
I mean, the first two games,
the first two games you go to like-
Monty, didn't you watch Barry Cramer's seminal video
explaining the story?
Oh, and by the way-
They're talking like they're friends.
Hercules and anime man are talking as if they are friends.
Like, they know each other like they're like,
oh hey dude, what the fuck, welcome to ancient Greece.
The-
No.
The Hercules world.
This is impossible.
In Kingdom Hearts one and Kingdom Hearts two
was host to the dope Colosseum thing
where you fight like series of battles
and unlock epic dope shit at the towards the end of the game
and you can go through and it gets, it's awesome stuff.
You can refight battles with bosses over and over there.
Not in Kingdom Hearts three.
Just not there, just not there.
That's just a small point.
Well, whatever.
I just wanna say, I don't besmirch Barry Cramer
for making a video relevant to a thing.
I, you know, whatever, I respect the hustle.
People, you know, you wanna grow your channel,
you gotta do stuff like that.
I just don't think that that video will ever be looked on
as anything like particularly good by anyone.
And it was-
There was nothing-
That he has spent his time on it.
There was nothing stopping him
from just finishing the fucking game.
He just didn't want to.
Even if he did finish the game,
the video would have been like from a perspective
of a person who just sort of kind of-
Well, in fairness, let's be fair.
I haven't played any Kingdom Hearts games
since the second one like 15 years ago
and I made my video about it in less than a day.
Yeah.
That sounds about right.
Your video has like, like the point of it
is obviously different from the point of those videos.
Like, again, like what I was praising Nate's video for
is the fact that he's taking the piss out of it
and admitting this doesn't matter.
Well, I just mean, let's not,
let's not pull out the torches and pitchforks
for Barry Cramer for not finishing the second game
when-
No, yeah, but your video isn't,
I'm explaining the plot of Kingdom Hearts.
That's what makes it annoying is that it's like
you didn't experience the plot of Kingdom Hearts.
How can you talk about it with any kind of like,
how can you capture the essence of it in any way?
You know-
So we're just inter-thieves.
You want to buy a sundial?
That is true.
Remember that guy?
Remember?
Hey, you want to buy a sundial?
Remember that guy?
Well, I am an elitist.
I don't want to actually act like no one's allowed
to make a video unless they have like more information
or like experience than me.
Okay, that's fair.
I suppose what it really is is a more of like,
it's more of like, why will I care about your video?
Like, you know, will it last the test of time?
It's all like quality concerns
as opposed to like permission to make a video.
It's where none of us have watched this video either.
So we're all just like,
just getting angry at the mere thought and idea.
But just the fact that I know
he didn't beat Kingdom Hearts fucking too.
Right.
Why would you-
Insulting.
It hurts my soul, but that's okay.
I'm going to beat his heart into the ground.
Even the lowly hypocrite beat Kingdom Hearts too.
Yeah, the furtive hypocrite.
You know what's funny is,
it's so easily overlooked.
I'm realizing I did a video just like Nate's Kingdom,
not Nate's, Jesse's Kingdom Hearts video
about Fate's Stay Night Unlimited Blade Works
back when that came out.
Where it was basically just like,
hey, fate's coming out.
Here's all the things I do know about fate,
which is not very much, but I'm excited, you know?
Like, why not?
And how did that go?
Went really well.
Well, all right, there you go, I guess.
Very did nothing wrong.
Well, there's a price for unjudgment.
I mean, it's worth noting that my completely terrible
and utterly worthless rambling Kingdom Hearts video
already has surpassed in views the epic and amazing
stupid characterable video
that I've wanted to make forever.
No!
And put a lot of my heart and soul into it.
Yeah, that says a lot.
We all know, we know how this works.
I put out the world over album
at the last day of last year.
I think it has less than 10,000 views still.
I spent all year working on it, you know?
In the background, all year.
The next day, I put out a vlog
called Like It's Okay to Hate Anime
that I just had the idea for on the spur of the moment,
recorded in like five minutes,
didn't even really agree with it, watching it back,
and posted it anyway, and it's got like 50,000 views.
Like, we know how it works.
We'll never surprise me, but it will always make me sad.
It will always disappoint.
As content boys on YouTube and otherwise,
I mean, the purpose of what I'm doing
with like my Weagawa approach is like,
I'm making my ones for them,
so I just have the freedom to make the ones for me.
And, you know, that's gonna be my way forward.
Which is the name of a Keyblade, but anyway.
I remember Oath Taker.
That's actually the Oath Keeper.
Isn't it Oath Keeper?
Oath Keeper, there you go.
That's a base fest.
Which George R.R. Martin would famously rip off.
Oh yeah.
Am I thinking of the Weight of the Dawn?
Okay, whatever.
No, there's definitely an Oath Keeper.
No, no, I meant Weight Forward.
Oh, Weight Forward is the game that made Shantae.
Okay, yeah, never mind.
I was thinking of the Weight of the Dawn.
But Oath Keeper is also,
when the Stark sword is melted down,
it's forged into two swords,
and Bran gets one of them.
Right, Tyrion Lannister naming it
after his favorite video game, Kingdom Hearts One,
where Sora gets that Keyblade from Kyrie.
Tyrion has really patrician taste in anime.
When are they gonna make a cross between DreamWorks
and what's the other one?
Get out, Miss Swamp!
There it is.
Yeah, I wanna play PS4 Shrek meets anime.
Oh, so you mean you want like Dragon Quest
meets DreamWorks, right?
Dragon Quest meets DreamWorks.
Now we're talking.
I wanna go to Eldorado.
I wanna do all the cool shit.
I wanna be the Prince of Egypt.
We can go to Eldorado and see that
unusually fit Mayan girl.
The studio that made like Coraline and Kubo,
you could do them with, yeah,
Leica with Atlas then, for the persona.
What about that one, Rango, Dango,
with Johnny Depp as that lizard?
Jango.
Rango.
That was a Jango.
Not Jango.
Oh, I wanna go to the Jango world in Kingdom Hearts,
and you know.
Yeah, you know, Quentin Tarantino plus Steven Universe.
You know that?
I wanna be Sora in there, in that saloon
in the snowstorm with the hateful ape,
with Samuel L. Jackson telling me about
how he whipped out his big black cock
and fuckin' mouth break to dude
cause he was a slaver's son or something.
You know.
Call him.
We got him.
We need the series.
Yes, it does happen.
There's a long monologue about making this white dude
suck his big black cock and it was pretty sick.
We need the Kingdom Hearts to grow with its audience.
Hmm.
He said pretend it's not.
Disney absorbs the Tarantino library,
and then now they can do that.
I mean, they got Star Wars?
They got, there was something else.
When's Iron Man gonna show up in Kingdom Hearts 3?
I assume any one of these days.
I assume fuckin' that they didn't make a Star Wars world
in Kingdom Hearts,
but I really would've liked to see that.
I don't know why they did that.
I mean, okay.
Because the game's been in development
before they got the rights to
it.
Probably.
So it can't have it in there.
Well, the end of this saga,
maybe with the next saga they'll be like,
okay it's kind of a fresh start time,
let's get fuckin' Marvel and Star Wars involved.
Oh, shit.
So it's not the end?
No, it's not the end.
No, it is not.
Oh, cool.
Why?
I can't wait.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're the only one I have ever experienced 3 so far
because me and Digi only played it
for a couple hours on the Ryan game stream so far,
is I sat down,
I booted up the game for the first time.
It was like, oh man.
Kingdom Hearts 3. This game is real. This is pretty crazy. I can't believe after all
this time it actually physically exists and is in my possession. And I'm just, you know,
going along, going through the opening, listening to the babble that passes for cutscenes in
Kingdom Hearts. I'm like, yeah, yeah, I've played a few of these. I've been here before.
And then it fades out and all of a sudden a title comes in. Kingdom Hearts 2.9. I'm
like, oh, my fucking god. No, the box, the box lied to me. What is happening? How is
this possible? I made a joke about this on Twitter a year ago and now it happened. It
was a joke. The meaning, yeah, I get it. Okay. The only meaning of that is that that cutscene
and that the beginning of the game is like of what Sora and Kairi and Riku and whatever
we're doing. That was actually part of the Kingdom Hearts 2.8 package. It was the secret
ending that you unlock where it shows, it literally shows up everything right up to,
like it overlaps with the beginning of Kingdom Hearts 3 as Sora heads off to Olympus Colosseum.
All of that was Kingdom Hearts 2.9 in Kingdom Hearts 3.
Do you guys have stupid that sentence?
If you do.
So Kingdom Hearts 2. So Kingdom Hearts 3. Kingdom Hearts 3 is actually Kingdom Hearts
3 though, right?
Yeah.
Later, the Kingdom Hearts 3 logo comes in today.
I'll add to Tom's impressions after the first four hours. Game seems not fun at all from
watching Tom has had no fun so far, pretty much.
No.
Are you still Olympus?
He's still Olympus.
We just finished Twilight Town.
Well, it's Square, so you know the fun starts at around 38 hours in.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's correct.
The thing I hate the most is that in regards to the running up walls like Hippo was saying,
I hate how everything that you can action with has like that white line going up it.
It looks so bad.
They turned the entire world shiny because you can run on everything and it looks like
shit.
I hate it.
I know they did it.
It also makes it...
You fucking negative man.
It makes you feel even worse about the stuff you can't climb up because like in Traverse
Town you can climb up like the buildings but then there's a wall around the town that
you can't climb and so you're just like, oh, okay.
So I understand why they did it so you could distinguish what you can and can't climb.
But you can climb most things and it's just like there's other aesthetics they could have
used that would have done the same thing, not so annoying.
But I do think the reason for that and the game is known for being very easy and also
for the stupid long pauses in the cutscenes is probably just because it's a baby game.
Like the long pauses are kids can watch it and take it all in, I think.
I'm sure that...
I mean, I absolutely feel this is a game made for the masses, absolutely.
It is not made for like hardcore, Kingdom Hearts Final Mix, speedrun level one players,
although there is a level one option that you can choose, at least on pride mode that
I'm playing on.
So maybe I should have fucking done that and then the game would actually be hard.
I think that's in every mode or at least I can see it in mine.
I was just playing normal mode.
By the way, Gib, the other reason that I have such strong negative emotions about the flow
motion stuff is because the flow motion stuff is very much like it was in Dream Drop Distance.
The whole structure...
I'm going to talk about this in my wee Agua, but the whole structure of the game is such
a way to give you cool flow motion stuff that has completely removed any like platforming
challenges.
They are gone from the game.
Nate, platforming was always the worst thing about the game.
Correct.
I always liked it.
Absolutely.
I missed it.
You guys are wrong and I won't admit it.
Specifically Kingdom Hearts One was like dreadful.
Kingdom Hearts Two was okay.
It just wasn't very interesting.
It was just like, I can see a thing up there.
How do I jump?
I guess I need to come back when I have another thing.
Well, fine.
Okay.
Platforming was kind of frustrating in Kingdom Hearts One, just the way to do it.
Even if you guys talk about it, can't you fly in those games?
But that's the thing, Jesse.
You eventually in Kingdom Hearts One, you eventually unlock movement abilities one by
one and it's satisfying and gives you access to new areas and it feels great.
That was completely removed.
Yeah, but like certain things that you have to do before you get those powers are like
platforming segments, which are terrible.
People always bring up Wonderland, it was really frustrating the first time you do it, which
is true.
Yeah, and Tarzan and like all of them.
All of them are bad until you get flying and then it's sort of okay.
But I like when a game starts shit and then turns good.
I like it.
Yeah, I think I'm with you.
I like when games are good and get better.
We got to stop talking about Kingdom Hearts.
When you get gliding, it feels great.
Yeah, you go God mode.
Gliding in Kingdom Hearts feels so good.
Dare we give up that euphoria of finally getting good movement mechanics, even though we have
to suffer through 40 hours of shit movement mechanics.
I say no.
I mean, at this point we've waited 15 years for them, so they might as well put them
at the beginning of the game.
I'm very happy they put Dodger back in the same thing and not something you have to unlock.
Tease me just a little more, please.
No, please.
Daddy, no more.
No more Kingdom Hearts.
We've been talking about this for 15.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess.
Zen, huckstable.
Hey, what's up?
Oh, yeah.
Just to close it out, I'm definitely hooked on Kingdom Hearts and I'm going to play every
single game now.
Good.
Amazing.
Kingdom Hearts 1.
Great game.
They're not super long as far as RPGs go.
Zen, have you thought of anything to talk about in this long 45 minutes that we've been
talking about Kingdom Hearts?
I haven't thought of a thing.
Nate came to me yesterday and he was like, oh, you think of a topic or two or three and
I was like, I can think of zero and here we are.
Fair enough.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the podcast.
No, we're all the same.
We're all fucking calm, empty handed.
Hey, I brought something.
I brought something.
How the hell do you do it?
Well.
It's for your fucking self, bitch.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
We're actually clearly divided along lines of those who put an effort and those who
don't.
And you know, it's pretty clear who's who.
No, I didn't put an effort, but it's-
The problem is-
No, I fucking brought a topic.
Oh, did you?
I brought a thing to talk about.
Don't you remember?
It was less than an hour ago.
Oh, I forgot, that was good.
The thing that I always make the exact same mistake every single time I write that note
for the PCP, where I make notes that are like, I want to like pace myself and like explain
like a thought that I'm having, which is not at all like the way to make notes for the
PCP.
No, this is not a conductive environment to explaining things.
Exactly.
Exactly, Jesse.
Like, it's not about like making thoughts happen and explaining yourself.
It's just about screaming and about fucking playing video games with Hercules from Disney's
Hercules on them.
That's all this is about.
Here's my pre-show process for the PCP is that it's usually like 1258 and I see an
at everyone notification and I go, oh my God, it's Sunday already?
And then-
I need to praise the Lord right now.
Yeah.
I go, fuck, I'll be on.
And then while I'm setting up my mic, I think, is there anything I could possibly talk about?
And usually I just based on whatever I've been doing and like what I could, like, you
know, the whole YouTube thing, like that's all I've been fucking doing is-
Well, I'm reading Hentai right now.
So like, you want to talk about that?
I'm down.
Right now?
Hell yeah.
Yeah, right now.
Yeah, what do you got?
Back it up and push it.
Well, if you follow Zenhuxtable on Twitter and you use mobile where it shows you people's
liked tweets, expect to be flooded with porn.
I mean, you hear that, huh?
He's not the king.
There's more.
There's more prolific porn likers out there.
Yeah.
But he is guilty.
It's a tough one to find.
Hippo's a huge porn liker.
Tough to find someone who likes it more.
Yeah.
Biggest porn liker I know, maybe.
Hippo's fucking horny.
Horny on man.
He's just very clandestine about it.
I've never seen him.
When did it become okay to like porn?
That's what I want to fucking know.
When did it become okay to just openly say, like, yeah, I have sex.
Yeah, especially on Sunday.
Let's go back.
I know no one will agree with me.
I know that everyone thinks that sex is cool now for whatever fucking reason you've got
in your head.
But I just want everyone to go back to the time where everyone was fucking ashamed of themselves.
I miss it so fucking much every day of my life.
I sort of agree.
Look, I don't know.
I'm one of these guys who's open about liking hentai and porn and stuff, and I think that's
generally good.
But I don't want to hear a damn word about your actual sex life.
I don't want to hear anything about that.
I find that mega weird, Nate.
Honestly.
I find that mega weird.
I don't know why.
It's so different for me.
I've compartmentalized them completely, and they feel like totally different.
No.
I understand what you're saying, because, like, you know, like, that side of me is a filthy
fucking animal.
I don't want anyone else to see that, and fucking, I don't want to see anyone else's filthy animal.
I know you've got one inside you.
I don't want to see it.
It all depends on how you think about sex and the sex that you have.
Because, like, I mean, to me, that's like saying, like, oh, I don't want to think about it.
I don't want to talk about it.
It's too powerful.
No, go.
Go on.
To me, it's like, if you were to say, like, oh, I can't stand when people talk about this
video game.
Like, I never want to hear anybody talk about that game.
Like, it's just a thing you do that you have things to say about, just like anything else.
That's no...
Okay.
Well, this is...
Yeah, you just got it.
What could you have to say about the sex that you have that, like, needs to be brought
to, like, public attention?
Well, I mean, okay, there's a difference between it's not talking in the room and going, like,
hey, everybody, I just fucking...
Fuck the bitch doggy style.
Like, that's annoying.
But, like, having a conversation about sex that you have, like, it's just like having
a conversation about cooking.
Okay, hang on, hang on.
Okay.
I'll train techniques and ideas.
Tell them I'm sorry.
No.
I am not training techniques with any of you fucks.
Get out of here.
You can't wait for me.
Here's one thing that comes to mind.
Okay, one thing that comes to mind immediately about this subject is, like, okay, sex, presumably
with another human being, is an intrinsically private act between those two individuals.
No, it's not intrinsically private.
Of course it is.
No, it's socially private.
What are you talking about?
What makes it intrinsically private?
Well, okay, I mean...
Yeah.
Okay, let's just...
Like, is it fair for me to, like, expose deep...
Because I wouldn't want someone to do this to me.
Expose deep nuts.
My sexual performance at, you know, whatever.
Ask permission.
Well, yeah, no, like, yeah, you shouldn't divulge.
What am I going to do with that?
The only thing that makes it quote-unquote intrinsically private is that there's another person that
you have to ask in order to, like...
Well, okay.
Very early into my relationship, I was like, hey, is it okay if I talk about sex that we've
had on our...
On my show?
You know, like...
I guess it's just that the...
My answer to that question is no.
I don't want anyone to know.
Okay, yeah.
So it's different from person to person.
The weirdest part about what you said was the word intrinsic.
Like, there's...
It's not even slightly intrinsic, because if you have a sexually open culture, nobody
would question it if you talked about sex.
Like, there's nothing intrinsic.
It's entirely...
Okay, well, I...
I'm talking about something slightly different.
There's a feeling of vulnerability here, I guess, that I just don't care for personally.
Right.
That's just you, though.
Like, I don't feel vulnerable talking about sex.
It's not just him.
I get that.
Okay.
I think it would be great about talking about my sex life, because I have good sex, and
I want to brag about it.
Enough!
No!
It's not about having good sex.
Case important.
There we go.
That's not what this is about.
Why not?
If you...
Okay.
Nobody wants to talk about the food they make if they eat shitty food.
Like, if you make...
If you do something well and you enjoy doing it, you want to talk about it.
Look, I do agree...
That's true for everything.
I agree that society should be more naturalist and everybody should be fucking like animals
in the streets.
I agree with that.
I just don't want to hear about it or talk about it.
That's it.
That's fine.
I don't want to say that.
I'm just imagining...
I'm just imagining a world where people are fucking in the streets and you just pass them
by and make sure they don't talk about it.
It's called the Polinic Girls Attack, and that is the plot.
That's the world that I want.
Wait, wait...
I prefer that one where they just legalized rape.
That's my favorite one.
Have any of you seen the Polinic Girls Attack, which is one of the best Hentai OVA?
No.
No, no, I don't.
It's a show where pollen is personified as naked girls who fuck people randomly.
So if you are allergic to pollen, it just means you're constantly getting fucked by these
hot girls.
And so all over the city, just everyone is just like fucking in the streets or on buses.
You're constantly seeing sex, but everyone's trying to pretend it's not happening and go
about their normal day.
That's hilarious.
That's really cool.
It's really embarrassing for them and stuff.
There'll be people like...
There's a girl in episode either one or two.
But they can't help it.
There's a girl who's on the bus and this boy who she likes sits next to her and she's
like really nervous, but then she has allergies.
So she starts getting fucked in front of him, but it's like by other girl pollen.
So then she's all embarrassed about it, but he's like, no, I understand.
You've got allergies.
He's clearly embarrassed, but he's trying to be strong about it.
It's adorable.
It's a great fucking OVA.
Wait, wait, what's going on?
Is this the thing you wrote?
Sounds like a thing you wrote.
No, it's a really good anime OVA.
Go watch it.
The Polinic Girls Attack.
I don't believe it.
I don't believe this is a good anime OVA.
It's like my favorite porn anime.
I've never heard you talk about it.
What started this in my mind is not like people talking about their sex lives.
What I'm talking about is like a discord channel for posting porn and like being like,
wow, I love that fucking big kiss on that girl.
Like a bunch of guys just all getting around and be like, oh man, look at the vagina on
that one.
Ah, yeah, dude.
Wait, wait, quick question.
How many of you have an NSFW board on your server?
I have two.
I figured you have to have one or else people complain about the lack of it.
People demanded of me and I refuse outright.
Yeah, that's fine.
Oh my God.
No, it's completely normal.
People come in and they see and they're like, okay, cool.
I'm not against it, but yeah, I wouldn't participate in a discussion like that.
For sure.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm not trying to say that it's like morally wrong.
It just grosses me out and I hate you if you do.
Honestly, it's funny.
Don't look at the channel.
You know what's funny?
I don't need to be in part in a community of people posting the porn that they just
nutted to and it's like, oh, maybe there's some good shit in there.
I can find the good shit on my own.
Thank you very much.
It's more about the fact that I just hate people and don't like talking about them.
The purpose of talking about sex is to get sex.
And if I'm not trying to get sex, I don't want to fucking talk to your ass.
Get the fuck away from me.
I basically agree.
More or less.
I don't go out of my way to talk to anybody about sex.
But if sex comes up in conversation.
Right.
Just comes up naturally.
Exactly.
And among certain people, it does if everyone's comfortable.
It's not unusual.
It really comes down to the individual how you feel about it because tons of people are...
I mean, that's true of anything, really.
Any discussion topic.
Some people don't want you to talk about politics in front of them at all.
And some people are eager and not even going to get mad and are just going to have a good
time talking about it.
Same goes for this.
But it's a lot easier to talk about porn than sex because, you know, you can't share your
sexual experiences with someone else directly unless you fuck them too, I guess.
And it won't be the same.
But like, you know, you can always share porn and it's really interesting to...
I like getting porn recommendations.
Like me and my...
Yeah, exactly.
Me and my previous group of friends used to talk about porn at the same time.
It just established the fact that, yeah, we jack off.
And it's like, here's a person that I think people would enjoy.
So you just link that shit into your servers.
Yeah, I'm over that.
That's all it is to me.
In general, I feel.
I mean, I could easily, like, if I saw...
I think I just watched a porn, like, last night that I literally thought Ben would like this.
A porn.
Because it was, you know, some gothy, like, you know, Avril Lavigne looking chic.
And I was just like, yeah, that's a Ben slide if I've ever seen one.
Ben slide allergies.
I don't...
I don't know if I...
I don't like that in porn.
I don't have any particular feeling about that aesthetic in porn.
To me, it's just weird when there's a channel.
And it's like in a friend group of, like, people who I know and I've spoken to,
and I know them on, like, a personal basis.
And I don't know.
I just think it's weird when they're talking about all the people they want to have sex with
and all the things they've had sex with.
I just don't want to hear it.
I just don't think it's cool when I hear it.
You know, like, for me...
Yeah, okay, go ahead.
In my channel, there is no talking.
It's just a slew of pictures.
That's all it is.
That's how it is.
It's way different for me.
For me, it's like when I post a link and then they're like,
oh, fucking love vaginas, dude.
Haha, yeah, dude, me too.
It's like the comments under an ex-hentai, like, individual page of like,
yeah, boy, I also nutted.
I love reading those comments.
I always go to the comments.
It's those comments, but the people who I know,
the people who I know made them.
I don't know.
What has to happen in your life
for you to end up leaving comments on porn videos?
That's a good question.
Some of them have a ton of comments.
It's great, you know, because like,
the assumption is that, you know, they jacked off
and then they somehow weren't ashamed of what they did after they jacked off.
I guess the better question is what has to not happen in your life
for you to end up like that?
Okay, that's exactly what I was going to say, Jesse,
because I, like, the kind of the way I think about it is,
I think about sex this way in general,
when I want sex, like, it consumes my thoughts
and that's what needs to be done.
Once it's done, I become a true philosopher
and it's time to do everything else that matters in life.
And like, when I see people spending time
in like an NSF work chat or whatever,
I'm like, okay, guys, just nut, then you can get on with your day
and you can go like do stuff.
Yeah, it's kind of like, honestly, I think I'm doing a public service.
When at long last I get off, I feel liberated.
I'm like, thank God, I'm free.
Yeah, when you see someone in their everyday life
talking about sex that they're not currently having,
it's like if you saw Superman typing an article
for the Daily Planet in his Superman clothes,
like, what are you doing?
Go out there and save some people and do Superman stuff.
I couldn't deal more.
Get it out of here.
Honestly, like, not only will I,
I will literally stop doing things to go jack off
and go make myself hard to do that, to have fun.
I do that, but I don't feel good about it.
Why not? You're doing it.
Like, why would you do something and then guilt yourself over it?
You already fucking did it.
Well, I only feel guilty because it's like
I could have been doing something better.
I could have not wasted that time, but I did.
You can feel that way about literally every second you spend on this.
Okay, sure.
Every second that you are not genuinely wasting your time.
That's a particularly useless way to spend time.
The whole idea of, like, pornography or, like,
jacking it as it is, being, like, a time-wasting,
it is a time-waster in the sense that you're not making anything,
you're not being productive,
unless you're literally producing life.
Indeed, indeed.
Yes, yes.
But, like, anything, any other thing,
like entertainment in general, is also that.
True.
You're not getting anything out of it necessarily.
No, it's different.
But you need it. You need to entertain yourself.
No, you're clearing your mind. It's better.
Watching a show or something.
At least you can learn something.
At least you're having a new experience.
No, this is fucking, this is a really fucked weird conversation.
And I don't know how to insert myself into it
because I have to talk about sex and nobody wants that.
Insert myself?
No!
I get as much out of having sex as I do out of, like, eating.
Like, you, it's-
Yeah, very little, almost not.
I don't get anything out of eating.
Except that you gotta do it.
Never mind, I forgot, none of you wants to be human at all.
You just want to-
No, whoa, whoa, whoa, Digi!
Do not let me with these fucking vile creatures.
I'm the most human-core person on earth.
Do not say that about me.
Listen, Digi, you're a freak.
You don't like the Organization 13 hoodie,
and you think you get something edifying out of eating a meal.
What do you get out of eating a meal?
Eating a meal is fucking great.
It fulfills you on the same thing.
I'm like a body level.
I'm like a literal physical level.
Eating a meal is only slightly less of a waste of time than jacking off.
If I did have to eat food, I wouldn't do it.
Jacking off is a hurdle in life.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
I mean, sex is an experience.
Sex is a valuable experience.
Jacking off is a hurdle.
Like, I wake up every day of my life and I go,
oh my god, I gotta-
Eating food is a hurdle too.
I gotta eat twice today.
I gotta cum five times.
I gotta shit who knows how many fucking times.
I probably gotta pay some bills.
I spend my whole day waiting for when I get to eat or fuck.
That's all I think about.
Like, all day I'm like, oh, I already ate like three hours ago.
If I eat right now, I'll get fat.
I gotta wait three more hours.
I spend my whole day waiting for the windows between those hurdles
when I can actually do something.
Yeah, I mean, I think that's there for the mindset right there
because I feel like I'm in Jesse's camp there.
Eating, eating is a chore.
I feel exactly the same about eating
as I feel about doing the laundry or buying groceries.
Oh my god.
It makes me sick that like 70% of my day at least
is like coming and eating and shitting.
It's not-
I wish I could just cut it down somehow.
It's not that I don't-
It's not that I don't enjoy the things I eat.
Like, I cook.
Like, I don't just like eat-
I'm not Nate.
I don't just eat beans out of a can.
Like, I do cook something that tastes pretty good
and I like it.
And like, I do enjoy it to a certain extent.
But like I said, if I could not do it, I wouldn't.
Let me introduce a totally different perspective.
And I was talking to Nate about this a little bit yesterday
about how I heavily compartmentalize my life
and I schedule it very heavily.
So what happens for me is that I'm working on stuff
that I feel are conducive to my future, right?
A positive future for me all the time.
And then when I'm not doing that, I'm eating
and I'm watching shit.
So that part of my day is like, that's the unwinding.
That's like a necessary part of my day.
I need it.
So it's like, I don't view eating or like-
Well, what happens when you want to jack off
while you're in your time zone of work time?
What happens then?
What is that?
Like, if you feel like jacking off, as happens to me
while working all the time,
but you're in work time,
do you continue to work and suppress that urge?
Or do you deviate from your schedule to alleviate that issue?
I do it like in the morning, twice a week.
Okay, okay.
Twice a week?
Yeah.
Oh my god, you're a genius.
Nate, I think you make your secret gene.
I have a schedule.
It's like a circadian rhythm.
Wait, in the morning, twice a week.
Oh my god.
I'm so jealous.
I'm so fucking jealous.
I need to give you a piece of advice.
It's going to sound like I'm being insincere,
but I'm completely serious.
If you have an erection and you want to get rid of it,
backhand slap your dick.
I do this all the time.
If I have an unwanted bone or I just slap the shit out of my cock
and it withers up.
All of my bones are unwanted, so maybe I'll try that.
You got to hit it with the knuckles on the back of your hand.
You know what my curse is?
My curse is that I have no heat, so I'm always freezing.
So I always have my hands under my dick where it's warm.
And so from always touching my dick,
it gets hard like 10,000 times a day and I'm like,
oh Jesus, I got to take care of this fucking shit now.
Jesse, do you not have an electric heater?
They're like $60.
What's that?
You go to Walmart and you get a little tower.
No, I have had space heaters and electric heaters.
I can't because the floor is always wet
and flooding up from the tiles.
So if I had a heater, it would be an electrical hazard
and my house would burn down with me in it,
which might be a good thing.
How much flooding is there?
Guys, you don't understand.
I live in a cave.
I live in a bad place.
This is the moral of all of my stories and all of my anecdotes.
Are you wet?
Jesse's basement pretty much floods every single day.
Right, no.
I watched a video where you're playing with the toys
and that is like, is it larger than...?
No, that's a whole different kind.
There are multiple...
No, that's a different kind of flood.
There are multiple kinds of flooding where I live.
There are multiple genres of it.
There's like rainwater and snow water up from the tiles
flooding, which is like all over the room constantly
for like, you know, pretty much all the time.
Pretty much 365.
Then every once in a while there's like the drain.
There's like the drain backs up and like this weird, filthy, smelly sewer water
like comes out in this huge ocean that I don't even notice
because I'm in bed until I smell it and I get up and I go,
oh my god, what the fuck?
And that happens at least around like eight or nine times a year.
Have you considered...?
But there's also the leaky pipes in the ceiling.
There's also the fucking...
What the fuck? If I considered leaving,
what the fuck did you think my catchphrase was?
Help, let me out for you dumbass!
I say that at the end of every video.
Help, I've been saying it for...
I've been saying it for three years.
Help, let me out!
I just...
I just don't know why you're still there.
Because it costs money.
Everything in life costs money.
A lot of fucking money and it's impossible.
Okay, fair enough.
Um...
No, no, no, but I'm just trying to understand from like a logistical standpoint
because like, how many inches were like even...
Well, not feet, but like how many inches is it?
Because like, you could just get a stand and put the electric heater on top of that, right?
What? I...
What? I don't want to talk about this anymore.
I feel exposed. I feel fucking...
I don't like this.
Fair enough.
I don't like where this is going.
Hey, I got a funny story.
I just wanted to recommend an electric heater because I also have no heat,
no central heat in my head.
I was just trying to make a funny joke about my hand being in my pants all day.
Okay, listen to my funny story everybody.
Here it comes, okay.
This is the joke, the funny story.
So this is a story Michelle told me.
Okay, Munchy, let's perk up those fat fucking ears and listen to this goddamn tale.
I'm not going to like this.
This is what I'm going to make you say.
You're going to like it.
Okay, so Michelle's been going on and on about how her hot coworker is so damn hot.
Her new coworker, female coworker incidentally.
Michelle is gay, definitely.
And so basically, she was stalking her Instagram as she often does
and she scrolls down and she's like, yeah, looking good.
Looking good.
I'm like, yeah, that's fine.
And then all of a sudden, she spies something that looks a little strange.
What is this?
This hot, tall, model-shaped coworker of hers.
Why is her skin gray in this one picture?
What's happening in this particular, what's going on?
Oh, fuck yes.
And then she scrolls a little bit more.
Are those horns on her head?
What's happening here?
That's so glorious.
And she scrolls down even more.
Okay, glasses, a big blue arrow on her chest.
It's Equious Cosplay by dude.
Homestuck.
She's a homestuck freak.
Her weird hot coworker.
Is she single?
Wait, I have a very question.
Could Michelle get her number maybe?
Is she muscular?
I mean, maybe for a girl kind of, but not really.
No.
It's not a one-to-one accurate cosplay, tragically.
That's really cool.
She also did karate.
And it's really funny, and you know, good job, I guess.
I mean...
I laughed.
It was, of all the trolls, Equious was the first one,
the only good homestuck character,
and that's all I have to say about that.
I'm glad, you know, I'm glad.
I feel like, you know, Equious needs love.
He does.
Equious needs love.
He's underappreciated, but the only good character.
Oh my God.
Shout out to Econ for saying that homestuck,
everything after Act 4 is bad.
Shout out to him for ruining my life.
Appreciate that, Econ.
Way to go.
Thanks for ruining Munch's life, Econ.
Here's another fun fact.
I did 100 pull-ups yesterday over a 12-hour span.
That was hard, and my body was giving out...
How many in a row?
I've been doing in batches of 10.
Batches of 10.
So, you know, nothing crazy.
I think this is the perfect time.
Nate, I quite literally cannot do 10 push-ups.
What should I do?
10 push-ups, you say.
I did 10 push-ups the other day.
They were really wide, too.
I did 10 push-ups really wide.
You're supposed to do them tight to your shoulders.
Wide is way harder.
Well, I mean, it's just a different exercise to do them wide.
Okay, so like...
How do I get up to a level break?
My arms are sore the next day.
I feel really good.
10 out of 10.
My arms feel immediately sore.
Okay, no problem.
We just have to do it every single day,
and it will be easier every day, and you can do more.
Yeah, that's all I'm going to say.
Yeah, I know.
I watch BoJack Horseman.
Let's just say your goal is do 10 push-ups in a row,
okay, or 100, or whatever, whatever the goal is.
Okay, like however many you can do in a row,
do that, then rest, then do it again,
and like wait another...
And I'd say like do like three sets or whatever.
I don't know, do like 10 sets, whatever you want to do.
Although I guess I'd say don't even go to failure,
because you want to be able to do it like every day
so that you are recovering every day.
So like, I don't know, maybe you can do five.
Do five in a row.
Maybe five is too much.
Just as many as you can basically.
Chain them together.
So what's the wait time between like...
Well, like at the gym, I wait about one minute
or a minute and 30 seconds between sets.
So that seems pretty reasonable, I'd say.
Just to speak on push-ups in particular,
because every time I've tried to get into working out,
I always start with push-ups,
and I start by doing like 10 the first day,
trying to do another set,
and then it's like, oh, I can't do more.
But then the next day, I can...
The growth is so fast in the ability to do push-ups
that usually by like day three,
I can easily do three sets of 10.
After a week, I could probably do close to 100.
It's almost as though it's just your muscles
getting used to the motion more so than actually bulking out.
It is.
This is like when people start working out,
I remember when I was reading starting strength and stuff,
like a starting lifter, like squats.
Their squat increases like a huge amount really early on,
and it's not because they're getting super strong
and getting huge muscle growth,
it's just because their body is learning how to do it.
I honestly feel like I've become an expert in starting strength
because of the fact that I've only ever had starting strength,
and then I just let it go, deteriorate.
So I work out for like a couple months,
and I get that nice,
oh yeah, things are going great,
and then you hit the slump of,
oh well, now you're no longer in the starting,
it's no longer fast, and then I go,
oh well, I'm not noticing progress anymore.
By the way, the reason I brought this story-
The master of being adequate.
The story was not to actually salute myself
because actually I was attempting to hit 150 yesterday total,
but I simply hit the wall, and it was weird.
It was different than like when you're at the gym
and you're doing like, you're going to failure over like three sets,
and you're, I don't know, benching, I don't know,
like a couple plates or whatever,
whatever, I'm not that strong or anything.
Like 180 pounds or something.
And like you do that, and like you hit the wall
after like 10 reps, and you just can't go more.
This was very different.
This was like, every time I came back to it,
like my baseline strength was much diminished,
which was different from like feeling strong at the beginning,
and then getting weaker.
I've like never worked out this way,
and I'm honestly doing it as a meme, as a joke.
It's not optimal, but I just felt like fucking doing it.
Because yeah, I was thinking, my goal one day
is to do a hundred pull-ups in a row
like level one Zell from Final Fantasy VIII,
as I've said.
That is my goal.
And if I do a hundred in a day,
really all I have to do is slowly narrow the window
between those sets until it's nothing at all, right?
So, maybe that'll be my approach.
And David Goggins.
Is that a thing humans can do as a hundred pull-ups?
People have absolutely done more than a hundred pull-ups.
A friend of mine used to drive out
to Mount Shashmore back in Virginia Beach
just to use their pull-up bar to do a hundred pull-ups.
So he would do it in a row?
I don't think he did them in a row, but he would do...
He would do it in like twenty minutes or so.
Okay, well that's already pretty impressive to do it in that short of a time.
He would just do sets of ten, rest a minute, do another set of ten.
But he had huge fucking arms, you know?
Sure, sure.
Like I've said, when I was in middle school, my record was fifty.
So I know this is attainable.
You know, I was like a skinny guy, but I was like a little exercise boy.
My record was seven, like last year when we had...
When Ben and...
That's already way better than most people.
Yeah, well we had a pull-up bar set up in the middle of the house,
in the passage from the kitchen to the living room.
So every time you pass it, you're just tempted to do a pull-up anyway.
The only problem with pull-ups is that unlike push-ups,
it takes way longer to recover from doing a set...
like a day of pull-ups.
You can't just do it every single day.
It involves more muscles probably.
I'll do one pull-up one day, and then the next day I can't even lift myself.
You know what's the weirdest thing though?
After yesterday, it's not my arms that hurt, it's my abs.
My abs are wrecked, because I never do ab exercises, because I'm an idiot, but you know.
Oh, it hurts. Anyway, enough of that shit.
I just thought that was cool and funny.
I'll get back to you folks when I am a Final Fantasy character.
How do you know that Zell did them contiguously, consecutively?
You know, I suppose I should double-check that, because I remember thinking that.
They said that, quote, something like, Zell jumped up and did 100 pull-ups,
but I suppose they never said he didn't come down in between, or like shake a break.
I don't really remember. Don't you just kind of like come into the scene,
and he's going like 98, 99, 100. Yeah, 100 pull-ups.
Maybe. I can't remember.
What I remember is it being a scene where they shake.
Yeah, like the implication in that kind of thing is always that they do it continuously.
Yeah, I would. And I know humans have done it and can do it, so, you know.
Alright, fair. Man.
Yeah, the reason I just, yeah, it was just like one more thing.
The reason that I started wanting to do push-ups is that my brother, he's fucking jacked.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, and we're pretty much opposites.
Like, he's jacked in short. I'm skinny and tall.
So I'm just like, well, I want to be tall and muscular to some extent.
Good idea.
You know?
It's a good combo.
Yeah, just so I can hold it over my brother, because he can't get taller.
He's older than me.
That is cool.
No, let him have this. Let him have this.
Is he older or younger?
He's older.
Both of my younger brothers are taller and in better shape than me.
What do?
Exercise. That's all I mean. That's all you got.
I want to do a marathon.
We're heels like Tom Cruise.
Yeah.
Base Tom.
He's my god, my icon.
I mean, I'm out of shit to say people.
I mean, we could do more or we could go to questions.
Wait, wait, wait.
I got one thing to say.
For the benefit of the viewers.
Zen Hoxtable, who are you?
I am a guy.
Well, a lot of people, for people who haven't heard this already,
a lot of people said I'm an anti-Tuber.
I wouldn't really identify as an anti-Tuber.
I don't think you're an anti-Tuber.
Yeah, I'm not really an anti-Tuber.
I make videos on animation because just for sake of clarification,
I'm in college for animation right now.
I'm just very interested in that kind of thing.
So it's not just animation videos.
I also do music theory because I played the piano for about,
I think, 12 years now.
So I just know about a lot of that stuff.
And I think that's a valuable thing to a lot of people.
I mostly know you from your drawings on Twitter.
Yes, I need to start posting more of those.
I'm a really big fan of them.
You have a really great, you have a lot of motion.
They're very, very kinetic.
They have a lot of motion to them.
Thank you.
I know basically nothing about you career-wise.
Yeah, I've heard that you have a comic.
I haven't checked it out yet.
Yeah, I did this comic for Inktober.
That was a lot of fun.
Zen is a bit of a human content machine type of guy.
Yeah, just not explicitly YouTubers, whatever I can.
Oh my god, this is beautiful.
Hey, I know nothing about you career-wise.
I'm sure that you have great opinions about Doug.
I'm sure everyone knows you and you're a great cartoon person.
That's not the way Zen Huxable is not that guy.
His videos are totally different from anyone else on YouTube.
Okay, okay.
All I'm saying is that I'm sure your videos are nice and great
and you're a good person.
But all I know is that I've hung out with you a couple of times
before in Boston and you're funny and cool.
And the thing that strikes me most is that you're happy
and you enjoy doing things.
Which is the best thing in a person.
None of my friends are happy.
No one in this call is happy.
No one's happy.
They're all fucking mean and mean.
I'm a ray of sunshine.
I feel like I'm happier than Zen overall in terms of,
like maybe I don't portray the...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, probably in like quality of life and just like, you know,
having your needs fulfilled, you're probably happier than I am.
I think, sure.
Zen is just extremely personal.
Like, Zen is a...
Zen's just like, he likes people a lot.
That's probably what I'd use to be happy.
Yeah, that's what I think you're connecting with there.
Because I think I'm happier than anyone I know.
But...
Probably, yeah.
And I still have to be happy and miserable all the time.
I have to ask the question that I'm sure is on everyone's minds
and everyone's too scared to ask you.
Who is the sexy lady in your YouTube...
Oh my God, thank you for asking.
Wow, there we go.
Oh, it's Tycho Nuki.
This is...
Yeah, Tycho Nuki.
She's my favorite artist.
I don't know.
She's a...
Okay.
Oh, fantastic.
It's all over...
It's not plastic love.
That's Maria Takayuchi.
Oh, I just thought it was the same person this whole time.
No, it's not.
It's not, no.
Well, that explains why she looks like nothing like her.
But...
Yeah, she looks nothing like her.
That was the one gap in the theory.
Well, they sound fairly similar.
I would say...
Not really, actually.
Tycho Nuki has a...
She played me one of her albums at my house, right?
Yeah, I did.
I think I played Sunshine Hour.
That's Tycho Nuki's first solo album because she's...
Okay, now we're getting into this shit.
Okay, so...
I can't believe I just stuck in the same person this whole time.
Yeah.
Remember when I went to your house and we were talking about how Japanese artists released
a lot of music?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
So there was this music movement in the mid-70s to late-80s.
It was called City Pop.
And there were a bunch of artists that spanned from it.
It was like a Kiko Yano type sort of in my life.
This is just like for the people in the comments, just for gratification, like hearing the names
on the podcast.
It's like all these types of people that make like fantastic pop music that was really inventive
at the same time.
Like, they were experiencing...
They were experimenting with just different musical cultures as well.
And yeah, it's like if you like City Pop, you're pretty much set for music for the next
10 years, at least, because there's just so much of it.
They're like 30 artists that are fucking fantastic and they all have like 12 albums.
So it's just great stuff.
Beautiful.
And Taiko Nuki's my favorite because her voice is fantastic.
Okay, but that...
She made 4AM if you're familiar with that.
Plastic Love is a City Pop song.
Yeah, it's a City Pop song.
Okay.
I'm really off base saying that they are similar.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's like instrumentally and sonically, there's not really a unifying signifier of
City Pop.
So it's like, it's sort of a stupid term other than it's like, oh, there are these artists.
It's more of a movement.
Well, John, that's what you say.
That's John is for you, I guess.
Right.
That's like, it's even more nebulous for City Pop, that's the thing.
I'm reading some of your comic right now.
And your art style strikes a very specific chord in my brain.
Your art style is artists from like 5 or 6 years ago that used to be good, but now is
shit, but like you have the art style of the old good one.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay.
I know what you're saying.
So you go to fucking ask Leon, the best Homestuck ask blog, and the art so scribbly and ridiculous
and funny and cool.
And then you go to their new shit.
Like clean and crisp and fucking ah, you went to art school and now your life's ruined.
But now you got scribbly shit.
It's messy, but super aesthetic and great.
I would tell you that.
So you have like all, you have all like earlys to 2010s art style.
Please never get better.
Zen's art style is indicative of his content on the whole.
It's all very unkempt, very like lightly edited, very like rambling and.
I'm not a polished guy.
Yeah.
Like Zen will like stumble into a video, like literally stumble into the frame in a video,
like rambling, popping his mic and just like going, going insane.
And like you, a lot of the times you're not even, if it weren't for the title of the video,
you'd have no idea what the fuck this video is about until you get real into it.
I love it.
It reminds me.
It's in the same way of what you were just saying.
It reminds me of like older YouTube.
It reminds me of like before everybody was trying to be the most polished.
And the thing is, I don't think you need to do all that extra shit that they do now.
No, absolutely not.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Like there's a core that people resonate with.
And it's like, just leave all the window dressing and like leave the essential.
Yeah.
It's almost like.
I think that's a good approach to just art in general.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
It's almost like the level of polish in certain things like YouTube is like a mark of this
person doesn't know what they're talking about.
They're just doing everything that they're supposed to do.
Because how can you have time to actually research a subject if you have to put out
three videos a week that are fully like animated?
You know, like these people are doing like full editing animations.
It's like, dude, I know that you didn't research this thing.
Unless like, because it used to be that you'd get one of those, like it used to be such
an event to get a 30 minute video from a YouTuber because they were going to put as much effort
into that 30 minutes as they would have put into like a two minute animation, you know?
And so it would be like a six month process where they did all the research and they made
it fucking entertaining from start to finish.
And then like, I don't mind that there's now a culture of like 30 minute analysis videos
that don't have all that extra shit that are just like set to video game footage and it's
just a guy talking.
That's fine with me, but I feel like we've like that other thing is like disappearing
like the extremely well made video in favor of like chopping that up into pieces, making
it look as fancy as possible while having as little content as possible.
Just like putting as many...
When you're talking about those old videos, I'm assuming you're like referring to Sequelitis
and shit, right?
You cut out when you said a name.
I said when you, yeah, Sequelitis.
Yes, like the Sequelitis style, which was, which kind of like kicked off that, you know,
on YouTube, like especially in the gaming sphere doing like longer form videos.
And it used to be that because in early YouTube, the wisdom was you can't make long videos.
It was always that you had to make short stuff because people are mostly watching it on like
their phone during a lunch break or something.
And like, nobody would click on your video if it was more than like 15 minutes.
And so it was like, if you were doing more than that, then you really needed to make it
worth their time by putting more effort.
But now...
Right.
Yeah, like the original Plinket videos are releasing like seven parts.
So, like, I like that it has, that we have normalized longer content and that there's more
of it coming out.
But I just, I feel as though the way that YouTube is structured right now, it's so disincentivized
to ever make a like big epic video that no one's going to fucking do it anymore unless
they're doing it in the background like Nate and it takes twice as long as it even would
have before because he has to make Wiago and shit, you know.
Right, for sure.
Viewers, please open up the show notes so that this audio section makes sense.
How do you go from this to this?
Oh, that's what you're talking about.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Yeah, it's, it's...
I mean, the second one's not bad.
It's not bad, but it's way different and not as cool.
The background and the character art, it just doesn't match.
Yeah, not at all.
Yeah, the background looks great.
It looks almost like weird filters on it, like a weird, bizarre bloom.
Yeah.
It's muddy.
It's a muddy image.
No, it's just like, I feel like they're in like this sort of metamorphosis where they're
getting the handle on that sort of background thing.
But look at this old shit.
It's so colorful and beautiful and sketchy and energetic.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I think people just get like, they don't want to be complacent.
It's like, yeah, they got bored with this style because they were just doing it so much.
I would never say this art's bad because I don't even think it's bad.
I'm just saying it's different.
No, I get what you're saying.
I get what you're saying.
It's like, they're just leaving something that they were comfortable with for something
that's, you know, different.
Give, give, give.
Trample on him.
Trample on him, give.
Just say your thing.
Just crush him.
Nah, go for it.
No, crush.
I pretty much finished my thought.
Don't worry.
Okay, good.
I was waiting for it.
The other day, relating to this, I uploaded an image of a character I designed called
Clarissa Gunsmoke.
Yeah.
On Twitter.
That was cool.
Yeah, and everyone loves it.
And it was like, oh, wow, cool.
And the reason it's interesting to me, because it's like a really sketchy drawing, but it's
like, she's got a big hat that covers her face and she's got a little smile and she's
got a gun.
And she's got big red hair, big poofy red hair.
She's cool.
She's got long legs.
She's got long legs, too.
A big horse.
Yes, yes.
For a while, I was...
It's got big hair.
Yes.
And for a while, I was like, man, I want to be good.
I want to be like, after my current comic is done, which is basically a comic that involves
a stick figure with a pumpkin face, I want to draw real arms and legs and stuff.
I want to have proper good art.
I want to be getting better at art by making art.
And a lot of the time, I get stuck thinking about the wrong sort of things.
I was trying to design this cowgirl character to have eyes and eyelashes and pupils with
the shines in the pupils.
And then I was like, I don't know how to make this look good.
I'll just hide her face, because I can't fucking draw.
And then everybody loves it.
Yeah, maybe...
Yeah, that's what you do.
That's what great art is.
Great art is like, the artist works within whatever limitations they have.
Have you seen that video, Ben?
That's been circulating around Twitter.
It's about this guy.
He's like a character designer for anime.
He was like...
The...
I've seen that.
Yeah, the anime designers these days are being so ornate.
Just draw a hat over the eyes if you can't draw eyes in size.
No, I haven't.
I haven't seen this.
I just want to say real quick that what makes Hippo's design so good is that you can tell
that character's personality instantly.
Like the second you look at her, you're like, I could fucking write a story about this character.
I know her so well.
There's so much conveyed in the...
It's like a very specific brand of cool.
And even for me, the context of knowing Hippo drew it adds a lot as well, because it's
clearly his type of character.
And I can imagine how he would write her in a story.
So it's like, I think that all that contributes a lot.
And looking at these ones that Munchie had posted earlier, it's like the first one has
these very instantly readable, likable expressions that you immediately know what's going on.
And then this other one...
You can click on it and there are more images than you're still in the preview, but go ahead.
But the other one, it has a great facial expression, but you wouldn't...
You don't notice that because you're too busy looking at all this other shit going on.
And I just think that putting the emotion to the forefront is always going to be the
best.
Any good drawing, it's always going to be like, can we capture the feeling of this?
I feel like the images much more close to the art equivalent of what we've been talking
about with YouTube.
There's all that extra production put into the second image, where the core of the first
one is right there.
Yeah, I think that's the context in which he brought it up.
Yeah.
Okay, what I'm about to say feels wrong.
And I value technical skill.
I don't want to be the guy who just says, oh, just fucking draw cartoons because it's
all you need to know.
No, I...
Technical skill and anatomy and all that is extremely important.
However, there's been a thought in my mind that's hard for me to argue with myself, despite
how much I want to.
And that's if someone can understand, literally get what you're drawing.
Why would you spend more time doing it?
The only purpose of technical skill is so that you can convey more difficult things.
Like, there's some things that you just...
If I'm trying to draw a fight scene, for instance, a lot of people have noted about
One Punch Man that the original webcomic, in spite of looking like shit, is great because
the layouts are so good.
And the guy has such a good knack for...
It's basically a storyboard of a better comic, but the storyboards are good.
There are panels of official Hunter Hunter printed in Shonen Jump that are worse than
the web novel and drawings of One's Eye.
Fair.
But yeah, those drawings resonated with people, and it's obvious that the reason they had
to turn it into something that was better drawn was just so that more people would show
it respect and appreciate it, it would be more saleable because nobody's going to take
a risk on something that looks like that.
But it's just, I think, a general lack of understanding of what even is a good art.
What does it mean for something to be good?
I'm planning to actually make a video about this soon called Bad Looking Anime or something
like that and just explain how all these people get jizzed about Sakuga these days,
but there's so many times where you guys never heard that one, but...
No, I've never heard that one.
PCP Episode 145, get in jizz.
Oh, yes, that's great.
People get jizzed over Sakuga's face.
There he goes again!
I saw it regularly, I'm surprised you never heard me.
I think the word you're looking for is jazzed, but whatever.
No, jizz.
You're jizzing over it.
I've had friends say this all the time.
Maybe it's a Virginia thing.
I have no idea.
I think it's a huge thing.
It could be that I made it up.
My friends said it back in high school, but anyway, yeah, I think they get so excited
about seeing something moving a whole lot and they're like, oh, it has great animation.
I'm like, no, it's just moving a lot.
There's no emotion being conveyed or it's a confusing emotion or the weight is wrong
or it's floaty.
There's a fight scene in Episode 3 of Boogie Pop, which the whole show looks fucking terrible,
but there's a scene where they put all this super animated segment, but it looks awful.
Everything's moving, but none of it looks good.
I've seen shows where they're just parallaxing backgrounds and it looks amazing.
Just moving three different background layers to reveal something and I'm like, that's better
animation to me than this is.
Oh, I'm sort of related in the sense that it's a good looking anime.
I was recently watching Penning Socking again.
I was rewatching it and it is like the best anime ever made.
It looks beautiful.
Have you seen Dead Leaves yet?
Are you watching the dub or the sub?
Well, here's my experience with it.
I'm watching it with Kazzy and I had originally watched it sub, but she's a dub person, so
I tried to watch the dub and I couldn't do it.
I was gonna say, I thought you would hate the dub.
Yeah.
Munchy.
Are you aware of Dead Leaves?
Here's a quick take.
No, no.
I'm aware of it.
I know what it is, but I had not.
It's only 30 minutes.
Go watch it.
It's the most aesthetically pleasing thing I've ever seen.
If it's only 30 minutes, I will do it after the show.
Dead?
All right.
Oh, actually the puppy ball is after this.
Imagine if Candy and Stocking had been like overclocked highest possible quality the
whole way through.
Basically.
Hmm.
I like that.
I like that a lot.
I thought it was a show.
I was mistaken.
Here's a quick take.
See if you agree with me.
Ideally, Solider should have looked like Dead Leaves.
Of course.
Solider, huh?
I mean, the Solider manga has the coolest aesthetic ever.
Aside from the early chat, it takes a while for him to get his faces looking good.
But yeah, I fucking love Solider.
I've never read the manga for Solider.
Oh, dude.
It's way better than the anime.
The unfortunate thing about the anime is they did the coloring really well in the show,
but just in general, the way that they adapted, it really suffers from moving manga problems
where there's a lot of stuff that in the manga is just really tiny side dialogue that
...
Oh, I know all about that.
Actually, I made a video about this.
My video ...
You did.
I watched it.
What the fuck was it called?
I don't remember.
Was it the ...
It was the difference between anime and manga pacing.
I know the one.
Yeah.
Well, I used Solider as the example in that, where I was talking about how in the first
chapter, there's these parts where Shinigami is chopping the dad or whatever and costing
him.
In the manga, it's this tiny-ass panel that's in between the action happening, so you just
kind of gloss over it.
You don't really pay attention.
But in the anime, they have to make that a full-screen, fully-voiced, animated thing
that takes 10 seconds.
Right.
And it feels way more ...
Yeah.
I don't know.
Cheesy.
It totally takes away from the tone of the episode.
The anime gets better as it goes, but the manga ... The thing about the anime is that
it stops right before the arachnophobia arc, which is by far the best arc of the manga.
Shit, man.
I gotta read this thing.
It's one of the things I've ever seen in a manga series.
I wonder if there's a YouTube video that is about Solider and two people discuss it.
Hippo, take it away.
You didn't like it.
That's cool.
Go watch Chibibacca's on this channel.
Solider, where is it?
Where is it?
The anime Chibibacca's on this channel.
Welcome to Bored, James.
We're the Chibibaccas, and we're James Rolf.
Get ready to play Chibibaccas.
You like Karakano, and that's all that matters.
I can't remember if I've ever said this before, but I watch all of Chibibaccas, and I love
it, particularly because Hippo almost always feels exactly how I would, and describes it
how I would.
Hippo, I think just through sheer force of having mostly known about anime through my
content over the years, is the most satisfying person to listen to talk about anime.
The only experience I have with anime are your videos.
That's literally the only part of anime too.
Yeah, but I feel like Hippo takes my videos, I feel like he agrees with them more, or takes
it to heart.
When I hear him talk about a show, and he's talking about the visuals, and what makes
the visuals good, I'm like, yeah, that's how I have talked about what makes visuals
good in anime.
No one else talks about it that way, because most people are fucking bad.
I guess it's half that, and half the fact that I just like being, like, analysis having
a point in general, so like any analysis video that, like, Mathematosis is really good, but
Joseph Anderson is just sort of slob, and it's okay, because he doesn't really have
a reason for making the videos other than make it for views, and Mathematosis is like
the things coming out of his mouth are things that he needs to express.
He wants to explain these things, and it just, like, I like that approach.
I say it every day, Joseph Anderson is a poor man, is a poor man's Mathematosis.
I mean, Mathematosis is probably one of the best YouTubers of all time.
Period.
I'd put him in my top 20.
And yet I still watch Joseph Anderson, so you know what I'm saying.
Well I hate ChibiBakas, because you guys didn't like Eskrayed, and you were wrong, you were
wrong about that robot.
That was an interesting one.
That was a legendary discussion.
There is not enough, there is a severe lack of long, boring, dry analysis about video
games and shit, like Joseph Anderson and Mathematosis, because those are the best channels, the best
kind of content to watch ever.
Wait, Jesse, do you actually mean that there's a severe lack, because there's a shitload
of it now?
There's not enough.
There is a shitload, but it's not enough, because I've seen all of them, I've watched
all of them.
There's not enough.
You know what it is?
It's still not enough.
Look, I don't know what it is.
There's some ineffable quality that Joseph Anderson and Mathematosis and Mr. B-Tongue
have that like snowball gaming or whatever.
It's just something about a guy who's not trying to be funny, and not trying to impress
me, just kind of talking forever and ever and ever about every little detail in a game.
But the problem is that, like, there's technically a lot.
But they're all, everyone's talking about fallout and oblivion, and that's it.
Those are the only two games everyone talks about.
I want a video like that about every game ever.
Yeah, another fallout game.
Yeah, the new fallout.
The thing is, I watched Angry Joseph, I know what he's going to say.
I feel like a guy like Mathematosis is aware, and is like, everyone's going to say the things
I'm going to talk about, like fucking up his roller and fly.
If you're like me, and you're looking for this shit, and you type into the search bar
on YouTube, like, long boring guy talks about video games, you will just get like an endless
sea of fallout, and oblivion, and Skyrim and shit, and it's like, enough!
There are more games.
Long boring guy sounds like a hippo kid.
Long boring guy is my favorite genre of YouTube.
Jesse, I'm really glad that you clarified that, because I feel the same way you do.
I love super long form, dry analysis, and like, Mathematosis is by far the best.
Nova Caldwell, Gervais, Watchable sometimes, Joseph Anderson just below Watchable for me.
But like, a big part of it is that, yeah, like, every time it's like, seven hour analysis
of fallout, 76, or Mass Effect, Andromeda, or blah blah, and I'm just like, man, can
we like, like, I know you guys are just talking about these games, because you know that like,
a lot of people care, but that doesn't mean that it's a game worth talking for seven
hours about.
You know?
Like, when Matthew Matosis put out his God of War video that was 30 minutes long, I felt
like that was so comprehensive, I was like, how could you possibly have anything to add?
And then Joseph Anderson made the three hour one, and I was like, I'm not watching that,
because I already know, I've already gotten the full experience, I feel like I played
the game after watching Matthew Matosis' video.
That's fair.
You know that one Omega Ruby video or whatever that's like eight hours long?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Shane May.
I still want to watch that.
It is a good video.
I've watched some of it, but like, I feel like it's just the length which is drawing
people to it.
It didn't need, it probably didn't need to be seven hours.
It could have been trimmed, but I don't think it ever is like, pointless.
I don't think that like, I don't think any of it is like a complete waste of time.
It's so comfy and homey and he's so funny, it's just nice and like you can listen to it in chunks
Like because we listen to it over the course of like almost a week
Like just throwing it on when there was nothing else to do and like at first
I wasn't that interested like at first it kind of felt like a dry analysis video
But like there's so many times that he just like breaks away to tell little stories or joke around or just like and yeah
Somehow it feels unscripted at times like it almost feels like he's like kind of like Ben's poo videos
I would say it's comparable to those. Yeah, in fact, that's exactly what it's like is Ben's poo videos
But but one that lasts seven hours
I mean if you think about it
It's really just that he made a series of videos but put them all into one video and rendered it as a seven hour
Yeah, that's true. You could look at it. I mean the thing is that the guy had come back from like a four-year hiatus
What he did that or something so it's like it wasn't like he just regularly does long-ass videos
He did like a bunch of sonic videos way the fuck back
He did a bunch that are like clearly trying to be sequel it is while also like responding to sequel is and like
I think he used to comment on me back then because I found out about him from him somehow at the time
But then he like disappeared off the map for a long period and then he came back and he did like to
Consecutive like he did like a 30-minute video defending Metroid 2
And then like immediately afterwards a like seven-hour Pokemon Ruby video that he clearly had made them both in the
Yo, I don't know if this is just me or or something
But I type Omega Ruby into you into into Google auto-complete it completes seven hour immediately afterwards
Like he made he's probably needs to relax for a year
I liked I like to believe that he's working on another seven hour review of like a different fucking hard goal
Tell me about my heart golds the greatest game ever
Oh
9.3,000 subs. Yeah, that's a thing. He's not he's not a youtuber
He's just he's just a guy. I was really passionate about Pokemon Omega Ruby, you know like that's that's what I would have thought
He would have had before this video. I know right he would have gotten at least into like the 10k
Some of guys not sure I'm shocked. I'm shocked. I'm shocked to that he is he has on under 10k
No, fuck how many views this is video. This has 280,000
280 so less than I would have expected honestly, but yeah, I thought it would be well, you know
The length of how many of those are that it's not at like yeah most probably
You know this is a fascinating thing to me
I feel like so I listen to a lot of ASMR and what did it like when I'm listening to ASMR it like
It's like I'm embarking in a ship on a sea of like comfiness
And I'm like surrounded by like a comforting presence
I feel like being in the depths of a seven-hour analysis video is like a similar sort of thing
You're just you're floating along in this comfortable world and like I don't know does anyone else
You start to feel like
If you have an insight into his like life in my life, it's like you're you're watching a let's play
Yeah, cuz he doesn't like every detail of the game. He goes like city by city
I mean you could I mean you could beat Omega Ruby in less than seven. I well, maybe I well not easy if you're really
Yeah, another thing I like about it. Sorry, Ben
Another thing I like about it is that he doesn't take anything for granted in this video
Like there's parts where he just explains like the basic conceit of how Pokmon even functions as a game
Like it's not just about Omega Ruby. It's like it's like he's he's he's like hey
I'm telling you about like what's unique about this game
But like let's take a step back and actually just explain how Pokmon even works and functions and why it's even enjoyable
And I love that stuff cuz it's like nobody does that nobody like takes that step back and like explains the mechanics and just like
Why they're fun cuz it's like we've all been playing Pokmon since we were children
But to actually have it spelled out was like, yeah, I guess it is like that, you know
It was cool. Sometimes it do be like that
One thing I think a thing that makes it especially
Comfy listening is like he goes on digressions and he talks about different aspects of the game
But most of them end up kind of being
Tributaries off of this this river that he's on but they all kind of flow back into the same sort of theme like he kind of
He sort of returns to the same I general idea about like what he's saying about the game kind of like like all the things
He talked about kind of lead back into it
So you can kind of like zone out for a while and come back later and like he'll see he's talking about a different aspect
But he's kind of making the same like general sort of
thesis statements with them
So, you know, it's relaxing. You don't have to pay too close attention. Yeah, that's cool. That's cool
The guy's Scottish. Oh, that's right. He's
Oh
Watch cuz he's got such a yeah, that's why I like my well, it's not the only reason why I like it's a nice thing
It's just not him atosis is I read. Yeah, but he's not Scottish
Yeah, when I heard he's like really Irish. Yeah, when I heard about the seven-hour analysis of Pokemon
I had no interest because I thought it would be some boring dry shit
And then as soon as I heard his voice and heard the accent I was like I can watch that
It is a plus. She is really
Colloquialism, so there's a few parts where he just becomes unintelligible on purpose
Yeah
I'll have my I'll have my mate Sheamus to boot you with a claw hammer
All right, all right, we've been talking for a million fucking years
I feel like we should go to the best PCP episode because I didn't get mad at anyone
No point did I think wow, I fucking sure hate you. I'm fucking mad that did you doesn't like the organization 13?
Happened to something they tap into something inevitable
I'll tell you right now iconic for a reason. I've always hated them
However, I will say that there is a high likelihood. This has a lot to do with just like
trauma and
general
this day for people cuz like all the goth kids
I knew in high school who I couldn't stand we're all like
Someone who would wear one and then commit a school shooting
Organization 13 coats and wear it brony con because did you won't be there to uh?
To give us shit for it
No, we didn't all right
But by the way about brony kind should mention that for the past four hours before recording this
I've been sample and I created the the architect
Recurring the blueprints of a road trip a fucking 18-day road trip
I'm gonna go on and any of it will be brony con. All right
Well, they're they're paying for our admission and stuff, right?
No, no, we haven't gotten anything back been is that no we haven't come down yet. Oh, okay. Well, all right
It's
Okay, I at least expected them to say like if they didn't want to do it
They would be like hey, no, we aren't gonna
Like they haven't said anything which almost makes me like it's such like an unbelievable
You that they wouldn't have at least said something that I almost believe that they didn't get it somehow. Yeah, maybe yeah
I think maybe they just missed it or something
I don't know try them again. There's no way because there's no way
All right, but well anyway. All right, let's let's let's see the voice. Yeah. All right. Here we go people
Let's unless anyone's got any blast shit. No, no one's even allowed
All right fucking speak pipe, you know the link just down below send us your own boy
How many we got I have eight there is eight today. So less than less than you
Merciful, okay, first one is from to go a message from to go link
What's I don't like that guy it's got to be a scam
Hey guys, sorry, I haven't made a voicemail in a while
I just wanted to talk about the whole college thing and why my god
No, interrupt this program to bring you a special message from our sponsors
Dix are so cute. Oh
When you hold one in your hand, then it starts twitching like a
Ah
This voicemail is sponsored by
Can we can we get to the ink as the next guess
Let's get it. I really love I really really love
Distortion dope. Yeah
The way to get your voicemail heard on the PCB is just to have a voice
That's like the only requirement
Every single person that downloads a voice modulator just gets in automatic. We actually vet these
Yeah, yeah, I cut a bunch of bullshit and you know what speaking of what do we do?
We we get probably like 20 every week to go through that's something like that a lot
Yeah, it's a lot and I appreciate it and people just so you know
I hear what you're submitting if it's not on it wasn't good enough so work on it
That's a fact. Do you get a lot of repeats? Do you get repeats?
You know, I've actually I think today was the only time I ever got clearly someone like retrying like a bad
Something that they didn't want to do. It's pretty rare honestly
Hmm cuz like they don't get a chance to like nothing back
They have to like commit or I don't know what whatever. Oh, by the way
I was gonna do the next one from the sky Filipino who's doing like a Filipino lesson the audio quality is too shit
So I think I'm gonna skip it. So work on that buddy and try again next time
Okay, but here we go fucking play next one. This is from Peter computer Peter
computer go
Hello members of the PCP
My name is Peter the computer and I love your show more than I love interpreting binary data
But I'm beginning to wonder if you're all just a figment of my imagination
Endless just representing my deep anger and loathing
Munchie my inner child as well as my sense of responsibility
Digi my true nature of pure and honest degeneracy
Along with me best man and Ben sainte representing my split political views and negative feelings
And whatever mage might indicate I don't want to think about it
so thoughts
Do you guys have any proof you actually exist? That's hot. No, literally none
Oh
Robot voice and murder of the universe by King gives it in the lizard wizard. Oh, yeah
Listen, I can I I exist I exist in your heart and you know, you know, that's you know
You can feel my heart teaches us that it literally doesn't matter if you're real or not
You have a heart no matter what and we also have a heart as long as long as you literally believe
That's what matters. So I'm going
This is the son of the computer from the Rayman one review on
If you believe well, hang on if you believe if you believe that you have a heart then you know as Descartes
Descartes cogito ergo some says, you know, I think there I think that something course you must therefore it is true
I thought no
Like a quote about like Descartes talking about Kingdom Hearts
No, like, you know, if you if you if you think that you're real
Listen listen, I had to listen. I gotta do something with my fucking philosophy
Asking if he's real he's asking if we are real which we can't prove to oh
Yeah, but I was you said you got it. It's goddamn voicemail. Yeah, next one. Here we go
Kingdom day card. Yeah, this is from
Harlock as Nibble is calling in with a message. Let's go. Yes
listen
This is Harlock as Nibble
I just want to let you all know that you were all wrong and I was wrong
Not only is there a God
But he's the greatest God. He might be the best God ever and
He hates and and podcasts that have people on it
He also hates YouTube and he definitely hates the liberal politics
His cult as one might call it that he operates in the RFC K
So as I am now a true blue Christian boy once again
Drinking that good red blood and
Voting that good red party. I can no longer associate with the pure degeneracy
PCP podcast this certainly isn't no
Something I have to do only for my parents
I'm not I'm not doing this. So they won't kick me out of the house. This is actually how I feel I
Would never lie at you because that is one of the many sins
It might be one of the seven sinister ones
Or maybe it's not we got it, but it doesn't matter
Please all accept the Lord into your heart
Goodbye
Okay, I got good news for you
Yeah, all I ever wanted with RFC K was for it to become a leftist cult. So I think I I think I did my job
You guys know, you know the cop killers over there in their dark dank
Cathedral just full of darkness and shadows practicing their their liberal politics
They're far left at bullshit the cop killers are just cut way too fucking hard and they need to stop skint
rewatching 90s cartoons scanning for pro for
Progressive progressive gay gay presentation representation every day. That's just what we do over there
There's good news though for this individual. It's that luckily while, you know
The the the alt left Ben sainte may be deterring you from entrance to the procrastiners podcast
The the strong alt right leader of the PCP Nate bestman is open with patron pledges to a patreon.com
Slash best ever every damn day. So that's where you need to turn your attention to for sure my dude
You're welcome. There's also
identity politics
Patreon
More black pills by
Dot com slash did you bro?
Letter of recommendation for my college application
I did in order for me for the college to accept that I had to register you as a
Recommender and when I do that they had they asked you, you know, like was this person's relation to you, right?
And there are stuff like, you know teacher counselor political alignment lawyer
There's an employer which I wouldn't with ultimately, but there also was mentor which which I which I thought of
You went past mentor to a lawyer
saving that one for me, so
Yeah, they're enough. Okay next call. We got one. This is from a little well-known character to all of us named
Sunstone is actually fucking good and great. So let's see
Yeah
No Steven Universe
Okay, it had a glitch the new character. Yeah from fucking she's the cool
Listen here, I am legitimately angry that you guys don't hashtag love and appreciate Sunstone
Sunstone is not only
Sick design Ben is right the first time ever
Just something is a sick design the hair is just incredible. That's point two point two is the hair is also really good and
Hashtag tears flowing from my face as I'm being addressed directly by this cartoon character
Telling me the woes and evils of bullying. I'm frankly appalled and I'm hashtag unsubscribing
From a podcast who hates literal joy and fantastic things such as Sunstone, you know what good bye
All right, crazy. Yeah, it's crazy. I I didn't watch the episode
I just looked it up and saw a picture and was like wow
Because so it's on something is that it looks cool. Yeah, remember you should talk to a while on the Steven Universe
What the fuck is Steven Universe?
You know looking back on it. I just I've just been like annoyed
Mostly because like people are pointing out all over all over the place in the comments of all sorts of things
I've been seeing it everywhere like don't the PCP know that it's a throwback to 90s cartoons
Yes, we know but it was fucking gay in the episode. We know it was bad and it wasn't done
Well, it was a badly told joke. It was rushed and I didn't get it. It's not that I didn't get it
I got it. It was stupid and you're all stupid for liking it. I'm sick of being nice
I'm sick of being mr. Nice guy and diplomatic about these things. I'm right and everyone's wrong. It was bad
Zen. Did you see that? Did you see that? Did you see the Sunstone episode? I I saw the special
What would you what do you what's your take on Sunstone?
On Sunstone, um, I actually like rainbow quartz 2.0 the best. Oh, yeah
I don't even know what that is deep into a series
You probably are of the opinion like you know like no matter how bad it gets I gotta finish it, right?
Like you know like go back to Kingdom Hearts like you played the first ones and they were good
And then you're like, well, I gotta just fucking finish it got again
It's just an obligation. Yep, but Steven Universe weirdly is like I love season one with all my heart
I think it's a perfect show that resonates with me specifically very much so but like it's just gotten bad to the point
Where like I just don't want to watch it
Do you want to preserve do you want to preserve the memory of like that pristine memory of what it's just that I don't care because I
Know that it won't make me happy. I agree. I mean as the series has gone on as it's gotten into the later seasons
I mean, I agree. It was a perfect show with like no filler
But as it's gone on there's just been more and more episodes constantly that I just do do not give a fuck about anything and
Just roll my eyes and it just
Fuck it. It's bad. The whole show is bad
That that one Steven bomb about Steven and Connie breaking up. That was so bad
differently
So I feel weirdly like I like the show even as it is now more than you guys and that really surprises me because I really like it
I I still like the show, but like I was looking through the list of episodes
It's just because it's been so like the upload schedule is so weird and like I
Remember like clumps because that's how they were released. Yeah, but like looking at the episode list
I'm like, okay season one good good good good good all of it's good season two pretty good
You know it starts off great this that season two is like a peridot is around and we're trying to find out and Lapis is also here and
Stuff. Oh, no, she's not here. She's underwater
season three
They start to get a few like who cares episodes sure season four
Who cares episodes season five is like entirely who gives a flying fuck right up until the end where there's like a Steven bomb of like homework
Yeah, I mean I suppose so like season five felt like awful
Maybe I just don't remember because of how much how much of it was like. Oh another onion episode. I really
This is like a weird feeling that I am probably not articulating the best I possibly can
But to me Steven Universe doesn't even like feel real
Like I look at clips of it
I'm like, there's no way that's like actually happening like Steven Mears feels like Mars being like
Was a weird space captain guy or something and this is like fan-made content
This is like there's no way like the story is actually progressed in this way
And then I'll watch like a new episode. I don't just think like this is just
So far removed from what I wanted the show to be like or what to happen
Like it's so completely different from what I expected or what I wanted. It like isn't even faze me
It does not even phase me like I can't like yeah, what did you want?
You just hit white male piece of shit. What did you want the show to be?
It's it's hard to explain. Yeah, I just I
We can have a whole I mean I
I'm well known for hating the gaze and hating the trans and hating everyone
You know, I'm singing my theme song every day hide it lie did lie did Lee get me a rope and find me a tree
But nonetheless, I I'm still enjoying
This I was never a lore fag
I was never like I want them to explore home world and more depth, but even yeah, yeah
I don't like you know, I did I did want all those things, but in hindsight. I think I was wrong
I cared about Steven as a character. I care about the gyms as characters. Yeah, like they have been besmirched
Yeah, I mean it really felt like in the beginning they they definitely fell to the wayside in the in the face of like
Oh, no, the world's gonna explode. Oh, no
Straight up. I fucking everyone who will try to get the seniors will say Steven's annoying
I've loved Steven from episode one and I thought that his arcs were incredible and I love them so much
Steven like was literally me and I love him growing like a mature
Responsible person who's level-headed and he loves people because he's like a boy and he's fatty like likes people and it makes me happy
It makes me really happy, but it's now
About weird bizarre fucking
In the beginning they really season first episode the Steven weight loss arc
Begins
He has to love himself he has to be body positive forever. He has to get fatter fatter forever
Do you remember that episode where he turned into cats and he's yeah, that was a freakish and nightmarish, but also really good
That was a you know
I've been tossing around my head for a while because the way I feel about Steven universe is the same way I used to feel about
Homestuck we're like I know that I don't like it and like it's it's just in the tip of my tongue
But I can't fully express it and I feel like it's been too long since I watched it
Like when it started everything was like
Clarified homesick for me so much. I did the same thing with Steven universe to people to Steven universe soon good idea
There was a lot of mystery at first or was like oh man
I can't wait to see what the other gems are like and what home world is like and what everything's like and now we have those answers
And it's like oh, it's all gay bullshit
Yes
Right now sure sure
Wait a second. I said I'm feeling very vindicated about not having kept up with Steven universe. It's like season 2 episode 6. I
Mean yeah, you're not
The show dropped the ball
I mean that's true. I very much felt like like Steven universe the creators
They weren't like in the right place to make like a globe like universe spanning
I still thought all of you guys
Just assumed all of you guys still loved this show since you were all still watching it. I mean I still
Well, I watch it. I
Like it is just watch it for the same reason. I still read okay
Like just despite season 5 generally being a lot of filler the bits that aren't filler. I'd still do like I did like
Liking and loving like back
Podcasts years ago, we were like oh, this is like
And now you guys are all like I'm like wow like people were giving me so much shit over the years for not keeping up with the show
Did I hear that cryptic tom trying to break the ghostly whale?
I
Steven universe as it stands right now is very similar to kind of how I felt about MLP a lot
Yeah, where that it's it's it's biggest strengths was was its abilities to
Yeah, to have really cool characters and stuff because like this the scope of like the network
It was on and like this the length of the show and stuff
It really lent itself to like quick little character-centric episodes, but now they're increasing the scope
They're going kind of outside their wheelhouse, and it doesn't it doesn't can't support that the the um, yeah
That's true. That's true. You know with them with MLP
Everyone said that like you know this the finales and stuff and like the adventure episodes are the worst ones and the ones
everyone liked were like the character ones like art of the dress and whatever and
Now Steven Steven universe is now about like its overarching story is about the like adventure epic
Indeed, which has never been even though it has the same strength, which was its its character
It's about the right blend with Steven universe, but but yeah still I get the point
Yeah, it's not all bad like I was interested like the whole the whole lap is I like was dope as hell
And I think everybody loved that but the truth
I mean sad you know sad to say I liked the I liked the diamonds a lot more before yeah
Yeah
Meh, what can you do on the other hand?
Adventure time was perfect all the way to the end and everyone who says otherwise is a coward and a phony and a fraud and a jerk
But it didn't push my precious gay agenda enough although it did a little bit
Every character to get double
People who are like oh I stopped watching when it became more about the plot and the lore like what is wrong with you cowards
The show was perfect all the way to the end
Adventure time is actually is actually gays Steven. You're I still it's like fake games gems are not fucking human
They don't fuck they don't it doesn't
Fuck a vampire girl. They don't there aren't even any men for them like okay
Well, so like it was big deal. Don't you dare say
Tell me that pearl doesn't fuck. I refuse to believe it. I have to have hope princess bubble gum and and Marceline
They they cut Finn and chose each other and that's dedication. They gave they gave they actually gave up the dick
They they made a choice. That's true. It mean it now they didn't give it up
They're both grooming him in tandem when he fucking grows that big beard in the future. They're gonna be all over
Okay, hang on maybe I hope I mean I hope so hey
Yeah, we got we got three more people we got three more. Let's let's continue shall we?
Here we go, boom
Wait, is it not playing? I can't hey PCP this this is Steven universe fan
This is a question for Jesse
Since he seems to be the poop the poop man
How do you think pearl poops?
Thank you, it's like a shiny
An answer quickly would be nice. I really need it for my
First of all, I hate you and second of all, I didn't hear the question because everyone is laughing too hard
Even say how does Pearl shit? How does she shit?
What's her shits like are they little pearly shits are they big stinking logs?
That's what he said. Oh, no
I mean, she's obvious she she makes reference to the fact that she hates digesting and hates eating
So obviously her shits in the past have been very slimy very hard to wipe. They never wipe all the way
They take forever. She's on the toilet for hours. Just like why is there so much shit? Why do they never wipe?
She's got that she's got that problem. She's got a never white problem here. She's too much poop. It's too slimy
It's too fucking filthy. She's always got filthy rancid, you know
The few times that she has put herself through the the the traumatic experience of eating and digesting food
It's been a bad experience every time so that's why so there you go. Her poops are bad
Poops are shit on average I as short as possible because it's bad
I spend a lot of time in the toilet just because it's the only place
Where I feel safe where no one is gonna fucking bother me
Honestly, I'm at that age. Sure. That's understandable. I don't push too much, but I take my time
I want me out in in under five minutes. That's a success. That is during a shit
I always do the sitting on the on the seat thing to to maximize a speed
Oh like putting your you know aerodynamic
Yeah
Squad over the fucking toilet it makes it come out squad over the sink
Until I do that, but uh when I was younger it used to always take me like 30 minutes to shit
Like once a day or so and like yeah, I've known a lot of people who take long shits
It's both something that you get better at as you age
Like for some reason you can shit faster as you age
Also, like apparently having like difficulty shitting and taking too long to shit is a sign of autism
So
It's a sign of
It's true, I don't know
Every speed up put your feet up put your feet up on every story that did you tell me you might be surprised
All has the same punch line and then later in life. I find out it's a sign of autism
It's true. Every story
What happens when you so it happens when you grow up obviously autistic and nobody notices until you notice later
Because you read all the stuff about it and you go oh all of this was true about me
But yeah, no, I did read that
I don't I don't remember if it was actually autism or something something like that
But yeah, I've had friends who would spend like literally up to two hours like with a laptop like what my my
cousin boyd used to fucking watch full movies in my fucking toilet and just
Damning up the bathroom for a fucking hour. So I have to go downstairs
I have my own bathroom because I have dain to share it my room with my cousin
He's taking two hours shit. It was really annoying, but then he started like actively trying to cut his shit time
Work because he would have the shit all the time and everywhere like he would take long ass shits like twice a day
Like these fucking chapters
I mean, you know, there's something to be said like I'm sure you guys have like had your phone out
You go to the toilet and then you just like get busy doing stuff while you're shitting and you're like
Like I used to I do I used to consistently read manga while I was shitting and yes
Like if it takes me like if I'm reading the first chapter of a new book and it's like 60 pages long
I might be in there for like 20 minutes, but
These days. I don't even read on the shit
I just try to get in and out as fast as possible because I just don't want to be there all day
Yeah, it's especially cuz fucking cold. I mean if you take it if it's if it's taking you two hours shit
I mean, I think the obvious solution is get in there shit what you can quick finish leave come back two hours later
And deal with the rest. There is nothing more unsatisfying than feeling I have not completely
Dude, I will hold it in until I until I feel that I cannot do it all in one go
Fair enough I guess but I do that in the morning character. I will literally wait
Because I started having stomach problems recently and like I could never shit when I first woke up
But if I wait a few hours until you've like, you know walked around and like yeah, all right
Maybe had comes out way easier and also like something
I'll do is just while taking your shit like get up and like pace around the bathroom to hope like jostle some of it loose
You know sure
Gracie grimy bloody fucking muddy shit poopy shitty fucking bung holes
Spraying out fecal matter all over the fucking walls fucking shitty all over people's fucking face
Smelly poopy bloody shits and someone's mouth. I don't even fucking give a shit fucking kill me someone end my life
Poopy poopy poopy. All right, let's go on next call
Next call people is from our old friend paradox crocs. So let's see what he's
Good go top of the morning D gamers. It's me. No
So I got an email from official procrastinators at gmail.com saying that I was gonna be the newest addition to the PCP
Something about how much he's basically 30 now
So you need some fresh blood to secure the zoomer appeal
But I entered in my credit card information and I still haven't received an invite to the PCP discord I
Was wondering if you forgot to send it or if you changed your minds
I mean, I can show you my medical records if you want proof
I have enough mental disabilities to fit the joining criteria if that's the issue
Anyways, it'd be cool if you could get back to me on that as always don't forget to like comment subscribe at paradox crocs.com
Slash paradox crocs and enter in the promo code big iron. See you in the next voicemail
I regret adopting so fucking much every single day
I regret I regret making you my first adopted son and second son overall paradox
You keep crawling back somehow, I don't know how you do it, but what I'll figure out how to ban you for good
This is a great question. We get it all the time. There's lots of people in this situation
The answer we always give is uh, uh, do keep watching your email for our response
Do not check your bank records. No, no, no
Continue because it won't be why wish your time
Yeah, it'll happen by the way. I forgot some people saying they've checked their bank records
Do not be like those people those people were banned. They were removed from the running and from life
You ever wonder what happened? Kevin checked his bank records and look where he is now
Rant ranted about on did you bro and ruin the full name of this via email?
I was over this message from paradox crocs PCB member number 13 lucky number 13. So that was yeah
Good good keeping track. All right, 13 organization 13
Oh boy, what is it?
I don't even is that might be true. I don't know something like that. I don't know
Okay, we got one more. We got one more voicemail. Okay, and this one is from a hen
Zuckstable, so we'll see what this is from. Let's let's get into it. Go more like hen sucks to bowl. Oh, got him
Wolf
Hello, yes, hello is is is this thing on?
Hi, I won't waste your time. Good. I just want to talk to Xenox will real quick. Oh, yeah, that's me. Hey, what's up?
Yeah, it's me your agent. I was just wondering how much longer this podcast is gonna take
It's like another 30 minutes or something. Hi. Well, what's up? Yeah?
Well, I just wanted to remind you that you're gonna be on this the superior pizza party of podcast
Oh
Yeah, okay, and one more thing
What would you say that the chances are that this gag flop because of input like um, you know, I wouldn't be surprised
That's the issue with you know talking to people online. You sometimes like end up talking over each other and like becomes a whole Lord deal
I
Don't know the audience will appreciate the fact that Xen was actually responding to himself in that call
Yeah, I don't know
That is
It'll uh people will know because the audio quality will be
Impossible it was hard to tell the difference
Over the call. Yeah, I couldn't I couldn't I mean I knew what you were doing because I could see your little right
That was submitted by the way like 10 minutes before the start of the podcast
I thought you know, I thought maybe you had like submitted that like while we were in the call
Because we've gone on for like three and a half
I mean, he certainly would not have made the pizza party podcast if that was
If that is a legitimate hey tell those hey tell those pizza party fucks we got a bone
Deliver
Okay, no, I've literally never listened to it. Damn it. Yeah. Well, I
Like we actually should do that let's start shit with the pizza party. Oh my fucking god. No
No, guys really let's actually fire bomb their house
Let's actually kidnap their children in a no hold a ransom in an abs in an abstract sort of intellectual way
I think it would be really funny if we had beef
That mean Ben please break down the abstract
Intellectual hate that you have to say that how the idea of us having it is great
But the actual practice of doing it sounds like work and a pain and it would be bad
Yeah, that's that's what I mean. Yeah, I just like allocate like ten minutes each. I'm so just I don't know anything about them
I've never watched
We said we were gonna add jingles jingles proceeding segments
We should have a shitting on the pizza party
Someone write a song someone write a song and submit it and we'll play it on the thing and it'll be a jingle about
It's time to start talking about how shit the pizza party pie
Listen to it at all so we will just I will say
That's true. I have I have no integrity. I will
I will tell
I don't even know who's fucking on it and I'm gonna start
They're all gay some
Pushing their alt-right and then simultaneously SJW agenda
Alt-right SJW fucks on the pizza party podcast
Purple pill mother fuckers
Thanks for listening to this episode of the pro crass naysayers
Watch the puppy bowl do you watch the puppy bowl a week ago when you hear this this is
There's just this is one little thing we got to do
There's just one little thing we got to talk about before we wrap up this episode. Um, I am that thing
We are announcing the PCP editor contest to find a long-term
Permanent editor for the PCP
Contest starts today link in the description
Look down there
There's a link there to a document that contains all the instructions you need to know about one what we're looking for as the actual
Editor of the PCP and to what you need to do to be entered in the contest
I'm gonna break it down for you real short. We have provided for you
I think it's like five audio tracks that we would normally use to make a PCP episode
It's like 15 minutes long you take those you edit them together with the audio and visual assets
You don't have to use the visual they don't have to stick to our style do whatever you want visually to make that into an example
PCP episode send that to us on Twitter using the hashtag PCP editor contest
It's all in the document. Make sure you send a video file an mp3
fucking
Thumbnail image for the video on YouTube and a text file with the description title tags
Etc. It's a show notes for that episode. It's all in the document also tell us how long it took you to do it
Also, what tell us how long it took you to do it. Oh
Yeah, that's important cuz cuz read the document people. I put all the details in there
You need to know a rather rather we will be judging based on like if because yeah
It's cuz you the main thing that you haven't mentioned is that this is a permanent paid position as editor of the PCP
This is not just like you can edit
That's what I'm doing with this episode
indeed indeed
Well, but that's how it's gonna be people
It's like it's like if you're doing like you need to you know
Submit something that you think you could do for an entire podcast like every wreck like don't you know don't spend like two weeks
Editing this like ten minute mini episode or whatever and get it back to us like yeah, and then you can't you can't do
Yeah, if you want to provide I mean we will be scrutinizing to be like okay
This guy did a full fucking animation that's way too much that probably means he's not the man for the job
So do not go overboard. We're looking for a podcast format. The emphasis is on audio editing
This is an audio show so like hey
I mean it's all in the document, but if you want to fucking scroll down to the part that's like checking your fucking levels
Checking your levels like we you know Tom me and Gib and Ben
Alden our own little like visual syncing with the audio things look if you want to do that great
We're happy to have it, but do not overburden yourself and make it a big deal
It's supposed to be a small thing make it slightly more pleasing the emphasis is on the audio
So keep that in mind people yeah that in mind
But that said we're gonna pick the best one whoever makes the best stuff that's sustainable wants to get paid
It wants to be a part of the fucking team
And that's it. That's really everything you need to know I think so it's in the description click that document
It's got everything you need to know if you got questions
We probably should also like clarify using the same hashtag PCP editor contest
I think we might need to be like ages 16 and up or something for labor law purposes because we
That you have to be legal to work. I don't know what age I assume it's like 18 plus or something
Might might depend on what might depend on what country yeah, it could depend on that
So I guess that's up to you folks if you're 16, and you don't know do us a favor and Google it
If you're legal to fucking work and do this shit
Yeah, I mean, I don't know or over 18 then it should be fine
I think or I mean just fake your information really convincingly because then it's not our oh, that's fair. I would think
Get excited people this is your chance to be a member of the your favorite podcast
Remember
Well, that's what I mean I'm on the team
I'm but I'm excited but I'm excited to see like I don't know
Maybe someone will come up with like a really neat visual look and I'll be really cool
And it'll be like hey, I really want this. I don't know. I'm excited to see what right make me and again just to clarify that remember
This is a paid slave indentured servant position
You are not a member of the PCP by winning this you are a lowly if you employ you rag them up and fuck
If we start to get the impression you're trying to bury Kramer your way on to the show we're gonna cut you right out
So don't even try so have no
You will be a friend or respected by us in any capacity
That's that's what you need to know people
Don't waste our fucking time if your shit just skip it only do it and and also you will be laid off at a moment's notice
If any of us need extra money for editing at any point
Indeed indeed, of course, of course
We'll try to have general job security here, but like you know, maybe one day someone's gonna want to be like
Hey, I want to do a Delta room thing. That's really cool
We're gonna try to do this rarely to take it away and do the editing
We want this to be you this you I'm talking to you future winner of this contest
What are we paying to be you week to week doing this shit?
We are it's in the document everything you need to know and by the way part of the test here is reading the document
Understanding it because that shows professionalism that shows your ability
Don't give them all the hints
That's that's too much already you've got everything you need to do this like the hunt. I have just received word
I have missed the people that this episode when I don't fucking longer. I miss the puppy bull
It happens before the fucking Super Bowl every year what it's it's the only good thing about the Super Bowl wait
Today Patriots are in the go fucking game versus the ramp. That's really funny that we've gone this whole this whole day
This whole thing we didn't talk about the Super Bowl. I didn't know what's happening
But I did hear but I did hear the recording this before the Super Bowl, so it's like indeed
Because that's a pretty important thing we glossed over my favorite football team
Is the Miami Dolphins and also the Dallas Cowboys and other teams that I know
Don't want to do I just I just think John from needs, you know, he needs to be redeemed
I