Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever. And shuffling my deck, shuffling my deck, here's your card. Ooh, that's a loser.
Gibbontake.
What did I do to deserve this?
Oh, you were a bum knee. Welcome, Tom Oliver.
Time to crack open a new can of PCP. It's gonna be a good day.
Indeed.
I thought that was the sound of your bones cracking.
Or did I cut out there? Oh no, oh no. Wait, I'm sorry. I'm Ben Saint, and I'm having
headphone troubles back with you in a hot sec.
It's the Joker, baby. There he is. You drew the Joker and you lose.
Only the most professional. Probably putting the pro in the Pro Crastinators Podcast today,
everybody.
Little dud. Sorry, everybody. Pokémon, politics, who knows what we'll get up to this episode.
Band. Band from this discussion for life.
No. Hey, I've got, yeah, you got something to get me.
Well, there's the big issue of the copper, the copper field, the Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act.
Oh yeah, that guy.
That Big Bejesus that's going on.
I don't know many facts. I don't know many facts.
I saw a lot of scares.
I saw Innuendo Studio, no, not Innuendo Studio. I saw Folding Ideas video about it. Basically,
YouTube is a liar and claims that users are more responsible than they actually are, but
it's still a problem because YouTube will probably impose penalties on users.
Well, hang on. Isn't that, isn't the idea that it's not YouTube, but it's, it's like
outside of YouTube, like the state of California.
That's the lie.
Wait, what about California?
Well, I just thought the copper was like a California state law.
No, it's a federal law from the FTC.
Yeah, it applies to all things.
It's been on the book since 1998, and they refresh it every 10 years or so, but I guess
due to like public outcry, due to some shit with YouTube, they're doing it early.
All right, here's, I watched a couple videos on it. I watched some guy who I don't know
who said he's a lawyer. He seemed very lawyer-y.
He talked about the legal side of it.
I also watched Matt Petz.
Was it legal, legal? Sponsored by Indochino?
I don't think it was. I think it was a different one.
He would be sponsored by Indochino, that dapper fuck.
There's a whole like social media lawyer segment of YouTube now.
Indeed.
Yeah.
But yeah, there was the guy talking about law, and also I watched Matt Petz cry video
about it, where he almost cried.
Wait, really?
Really?
No, fuck.
What a fucking bitch.
That's despicable.
It's not like, it's not like he doesn't do that.
I hate a man who cries.
It's not like he doesn't do that usually.
Like he's got a little bit of glistening in his eyes.
When his editor died, it was called for.
Yes.
When fucking Kyla's coming out, he'd fuck you.
Well, I'm not really...
I kind of like mixed the other video less respectful in going there.
Well, it wasn't like weeping. It was just like, I could see glistening in his eyes.
Like he had been like tear-y or something.
Oh, his eyes are always glistening.
I assume that he feels this way because he feels his work is like potentially in jeopardy.
Yes.
It may, you know, okay.
All right, so from what I gather, the copper had turned a blind eye to YouTube for the
most part, because this is the funniest part, so I'll start with that.
I'm ready to laugh.
YouTube has the thing where you have to be 13 years or over in order to use the site,
and that has been part of the YouTube terms of services, and that's all that jazz says,
and that is copper compliant.
So YouTube was actually doing the right thing.
The thing is copper or the FTC rather clued into the fact that YouTube was knowingly targeting
children because they were bragging about it in media events with shareholders and business
people.
It's like YouTube is the number one place for people 6 to 12.
Little babies with a child brain.
So YouTube basically fucked themselves and everyone else over by bragging about how much
money they were making off of these child viewers that they weren't supposed to be allowed.
YouTube was just fucking these children.
The problem is data collection, right?
The specific problem is the collection of data from kids under 13.
The collection of data of children under 13 is for various reasons like not good, and
the advertising relies on that data so that they can show targeted ads which are much
more CPM, click through, whatever thing.
Can I cut in for a moment?
Yeah, that's what I understood the main issue to be.
So when I saw this, I immediately went in.
I went to all my channels.
I set them to not for kids.
And I am aware that I personally do no data collection of any kind.
So my wonder is just like, am I really in any danger considering I have not?
No, not from the law, but maybe from YouTube.
The thing was, this is where the lawyer guy explained it, and he had an update video where
he allegedly got a call from someone in YouTube who couldn't divulge his name for fear of
retribution.
John YouTube himself.
John YouTube, the whistleblower.
Called in to explain secret facts.
The basic gist is that the law has, in the FTC, it explains that if something is for
adults, geared towards adults, it has adult themes, that is nothing to do with copper.
But if it's aimed at children, and it's for children, and it's all of that stuff, then
your video, if it is collecting data, i.e. monetized, you are liable to get, I don't
know the terminology, but you could get fined $42,000 at least per video, per infringement.
That's what YouTube is telling everyone.
It's either for adults or it's for kids.
There's everybody who is upset and concerned, like Matt Pat, like Arlo, who have child-friendly
aspects to their videos, but aren't entirely child-based.
They are not talking to children, they are talking to people.
They are talking to everyone who would be interested.
Adults like Matt Pat, like myself, I enjoy those videos, they're silly, you could say
what you like about them, but they are very much also a huge kid demographic thing.
They're all ages, all ages, which includes kids.
YouTube did not divulge that in the FTC there is a case for both, there is a middle ground
in the FTC rules that says if you're targeting a general audience and it happens to appeal
to kids, you're not actually infringing.
You're not targeting kids.
You're not targeting kids, you're not doing a frozen Elsa Funko Pop unboxing video.
You're not trying to prey upon the easy clicks of children who don't know what they're doing.
You are making videos that children may or may not enjoy.
So if you're like, you swear sometimes, but you also make fun videos that anyone can enjoy,
you're not actually at risk in terms of the FTC, but the thing is YouTube didn't tell people that
because allegedly, because of this secret phone man, that I mean, I don't know, maybe it's true.
Seems true because YouTube is a company and they don't want to let this information out,
is that it would be bad for them monetarily to allow people to not, like they make it black and white.
It's either for adults or it's for kids and they want people, I guess, to set it for kids just in case.
Because the kid market seems so lucrative and I know that the most profitable channel on YouTube is this.
Nobody will get money from kids' content going forward.
If you are a Spider-Man Elsa video channel man, you going forward will not get money.
That is just how it is.
Sorry, don't you get ads, but it's just not targeted ads anymore?
Yeah, but it's like 2% of the income is targeted ads.
YouTube is the one collecting data, not users.
YouTube is basically trying to pass the responsibility for this onto content creators, which is just stupid.
It's just them shamelessly trying not to suffer consequences for things they did wrong.
And want to continue to do wrong.
They've already paid $170 million in fines.
They've paid a huge big lawsuit settlement fine thing already.
They've given money, but it is in their best interest to make sure that this could not ever possibly happen again.
So they are making it black and white in order to confuse creators and make them scared so that they will set their channel to kids
so that they'll lose out on monetization, but they will guarantee that they won't get fined for thousands of dollars suddenly out of nowhere.
Supposedly, even if you set your channel to my content is not for kids, the algorithm might decide that that's just wrong.
The algorithm might theoretically pick up on song keywords and images and stuff and be like, this is kid entertainment.
This is unacceptable for targeted advertisement.
On the one hand, I don't know if YouTube has any intention of making sure...
YouTube doesn't really care about all this.
If they can get away with not doing anything, they will.
The FTC is the one who's going to be scouring through YouTube to find offending videos and they are working with YouTube to make it happen.
But YouTube has no reason, aside from general compliance, to make a bot and AI that finds all of the kid videos and gets them fined for thousands of dollars because that's just bad PR.
I believe that they did do that. They're not looking to find themselves, but they're looking to mark content as kid content and de-target ads from it.
Or something.
There's lots of stuff we don't know because it's YouTube and they're not going to tell us anything.
I'm looking at my analytics right now on the YouTube studio thing.
We all know that every kid lies to get onto YouTube and just says their age is older than it actually is or whatever.
My audience is 80% 18-34 and the 13-17 is just under 7% and I set my challenge to adult and I know that the content is not catered to kids.
Theoretically, you could potentially make an argument that anime is inherently childish and I'm probably going to make a video about Pokemon and other things.
I could see an argument, but I think I could win that argument.
I personally feel very little danger for something like this.
I saw the internet historian, he made a tweet thread basically saying this isn't something to worry about for most people who aren't on the borderline.
But I do feel for people like Arlo and MatPat to a degree who are forced into this uncomfortable position of forcing to choose.
They're only forced into that position because YouTube wanted to do that. They aren't actually in violation of anything.
No.
To be slightly fair to YouTube, it's like YouTube set up this system.
We should at least examine the other side of the argument, which is just that YouTube set up a system where these creators do benefit.
If YouTube's able to milk more money out of these kids, people with a kid audience to any degree have been benefiting from that.
It literally doesn't matter because it's not about who benefits, it's about the collection of data, which only YouTube does.
That data is used to serve ads which makes more money, right?
Yes, by YouTube. And they could choose not to do that, but they won't.
They're just going to pass the buck onto creators and say that it's their problem, whether the data they're collecting is from kids or not.
There has been some benefit to the creators from this.
It literally isn't unrelated to the question at hand.
I don't think, I mean, they have in fact gained more money through this system.
That makes, that is not what the question is.
Well, okay, if you want to talk about something else, fair enough.
I want to talk about Kappa, which is not about who's getting money, it's about collection of data.
I mean, I agree.
What Nate's trying to say, I think, is that because YouTube for so long has not been in compliance with Kappa,
there's an entire market that's sprung up around making money off of children.
And even if someone like Arlo has been benefiting from that indirectly because these children...
I don't know if that's true. I don't think Arlo's videos are not the kind of thing we're talking about.
I have the mind of a child. And when I see Arlo, I go buck wild.
It's just what it is.
Arlo is a...
Well, of course.
Arlo's done nothing wrong.
But it's just that Arlo can attract a younger audience because of the nature of his content.
Okay, but Arlo's not who we're talking about.
We're talking about Spider-Man and Elsa pregnancy videos.
Right, no, that's the problem.
But I'm just saying there's some crossover, right?
Maybe, but what's the what?
That's just saying that he's probably going to lose some money from this.
Presumably.
I mean, maybe, I guess, yeah.
But not because the law says he ought to, but because YouTube...
No, because YouTube's system has allowed this wrong thing to happen.
And there are people who ride the line like Arlo, who are probably making some extra money
because of that data collection those targeted ads to younger users.
Yeah, and I'm not saying he's at fault or anything.
It's just an unfortunate side effect of YouTube's continued lack of integrity.
Which is a long story history.
The thing is, is this lawyer thing with this third like middle ground option in the law
that says you're exempt if, basically says you're exempt if it's a general audience,
means that people like Arlo and MatPat should not be affected at all,
but they have no option to do the middle ground thing.
Yes, yes.
Which is annoying and shady and that sucks.
But I feel like generally this means that most people who are not Spider-Man Elsa will be okay.
And furthermore, getting to the point where the fines would go out,
it's going to be...
That is not going to be a YouTube...
YouTube might use bots and AI to flag the videos as infringing on kids, whatever.
Like it's kids, but it's not listed as for kids.
They've decided that it's for kids.
And then the FTC gets a list of these things and they go out and then they look at them with people
because they're going to have to make actual fines to actual people.
And they can't, it's going to be expensive if they lose.
Like if this goes to court and they lose because they trusted Google YouTube AI to tell them the truth.
They have to, they should.
Gabe, is this the video by the way?
I'm pretty sure that only YouTube itself and no, I don't think any individual creators are liable for anything.
No, but like the FTC, in the situation where there is a YouTuber who is profiting off of data collected from children,
the FTC has decided that the channel owner is liable for some reason.
Like I assume it's like part of the YouTube settlement, like YouTube passed the buck over.
We'll give you this money.
I don't think FTC decided that, I think YouTube decided that.
YouTube decided, yeah, it was like part of whatever happened.
I don't actually know having looked into that.
And it's basically like extra legal is the idea that either creators are responsible and should be the ones to report themselves.
If you are not targeting kids specifically, you'll be fine, I think.
Because the likelihood that you will actually get hit by a fine is so low if you have ground to stand on, which most people do.
I almost hope I get sued because then I'll get some of that sweet like GoFundMe internet drama money, you know,
and everyone will care about my channel and all those things will happen.
And I know I'll win. I know I will win if I'm sued for this.
Well, yeah, I mean the thing is you know you'll win, which is why you won't get sued because the FTC is the one who has to do the suing.
Unfortunately for me, that's the real discrimination. Maybe I want to get sued. That would be nice.
Good life experience right there.
I think the problem that started this entire thing, because like this is going through the traditional like YouTube drama life cycle of like
really fucking crazy fear mongering, everyone's terrified, radical changes, everyone with their hot takes,
and then all of a sudden like, oh, it's not that bad, you know, the typical way these things go.
But like the reason this one I think was like reacted to so harshly so quickly is that there's just like a video like of the head of the FTC,
like he did like some sort of like meeting about this and just straight up said,
That guy looks like a primo boomer.
Yeah, like the typical boomer of just being like, we're coming for you guys.
We have the technology. We're going to take down as many as possible.
He just wishes he was like in the CIA talking about terrorism, but he's not.
Instead of like everyone on YouTube imagining that this could possibly happen,
like the dude in charge was saying it was going to happen.
So it was kind of a weird thing to do, I guess, because it definitely alarmed a lot of myself.
Well, this is pretty fucked.
This is concerning for some people. I get it.
When any new thing appears to present, it's not actually new, but like when a new thing appears
and could potentially threaten your entire existence as like a creator, like I'm sure MatPat feels obviously that's scary.
But I feel like, I mean, maybe I've just been desensitized, but like how many of these fucking issues happen
that ultimately just peter out and like nothing important comes of them?
Well, I mean, MatPat's not fucking over anybody. He'll probably be fine.
I mean, there's, again, like really convinced that there is literally zero liability on any creator's account here,
and it's all YouTube or whatever.
I mean, I believe that, but it just seems, yeah.
I don't think anyone's going to be hurt.
I mean, there's going to be people who get their shit demonetized.
I was a little like worried at one point because, you know, my Give and Take channel has pony videos on them.
Not all of them are, some of them are analysis, and that's, you know, that's obvious.
Like, children aren't supposed to understand this sort of depth talking about fucking show.
Yeah, but I've seen a couple of documentaries that reveal that the true audience is adult men.
I think we all know that.
Have you heard about this My Little Pony thing?
It's not just for little girls anymore.
No, no, sir. No, no.
No, in fact, it is manly, and I'm a man, you see.
No, but like also, I've made those pony compilations earlier than that,
which are just like a series of clips from the show.
They've all been demonetized recently.
Some of them had survived up to this point, but then they finally got God by Hasbro.
But those are like, you could argue that those are just for kids.
I didn't intend for that.
It seems to me like Arlo-esque in that, incidentally, I could definitely see kids enjoying them,
but they're not specifically targeting kids.
But they're not like, I mean, they were specifically targeting bronies.
That's what my defense would be, and it's like, what's a bronie?
I'd have to explain that in court, like, oh my God, oh my God.
I've got a documentary to show you.
You know, my point before about how I suspect no one will be harmed.
So the one way that I think that might not be true is, okay, occasionally with YouTube,
things don't go exactly as they're intended to.
And this reminds me of how just recently, actually, like a few minutes before this very podcast began,
a new video was uploaded to one CGP Gray's channel, and I think I have it right here,
where CGP Gray was fucking locked out of his main channel for allegedly impersonating Dun Dun Dun himself,
is what YouTube thought was happening.
They were like, you're not CGP Gray.
You're like a spammer or like a bot account or something.
And he had to like fight to get it back.
And he won, which is why there's this new video and the other one, which is probably delayed,
until this issue was resolved.
It took him like over the weekend or something.
But so the issue is, things don't always work like exactly as they were supposed to.
Sometimes a couple of things fall through the cracks, and that's not so good.
And the algorithm ain't perfect.
I know, imagine that.
So in that sense, perhaps there are things to be at least like aware of and concerned is,
we're going to institute new restrictions, new demotization criteria,
and they don't have the best track record of applying that shit exactly where and when it should be.
So on that basis, perhaps it's a more urgent concern.
That's understandable.
The whole thing, I was wearing into like, at first I was like,
there's no way that people are actually going to get fines that big.
And then I looked into it and I was a little scared for a second.
Then I looked into it more and it was fine.
But I kind of wish, like deep down, I kind of wish that it was like the YouTube ending disaster
that is everyone on January 1st, everyone gets a million fines.
So they have to turn off all their channels and everyone leaves.
You guys are just in a black pill mode.
Just wants it all to burn.
I kind of would have, like it would have been the saving grace of the whole thing,
is the knowledge that YouTube is finally fucking killed.
Fuck you.
And you know what that reminds me?
The kind of the other point of CGPK's video was that like guys at any moment,
YouTube can ban us, can deal with, like this guy's got four million subscribers.
At any moment, YouTube can just decide arbitrarily,
they add more and more clauses when they can just decide
if they don't want you anymore and whatnot.
He's like, but you know what still fucking works?
Email lists, baby.
Email lists are the way to go to make sure.
I know you've got your email list, Gib.
I just now went to my monetization settings and I clicked it.
I never upload content for kids settings.
Woo!
Lives saved.
But Ben, you talked about Winnie the Pooh.
Well, not to you.
If you're 13 or under, you stupid jerk.
Get off my internet.
Boomers, rise up.
Imagine a future.
This is just some anti-zoomer propagandas that this is.
Yeah, that's true.
We Zoomers deserved have ads served to us, catered to our specific needs.
It's fucked up, but they'll take that away from us.
That's how we exist.
Yeah, well, good luck to everybody out there.
It's a jungle out there.
Everybody should make their own website and email list anyway,
because it's just better.
But the effort, ooh, the more than zero effort that requires.
Ooh, Ungabunga, Ungabunga.
Oh, man.
Think about my email.
Never, never, never.
Speaking of websites that I own,
which is my website, apsadventures.site,
the name sucks.
I've been trying to think of a better name for months, for years.
Gibbentake.com, Hippocrite.com.
I guess Gibbentake.com might do it.
It hurt to have both.
We did it, guys. We figured it out.
Fine, I guess that wasn't...
I'd say it's the most well-known branding name of you, perhaps,
except maybe Hippocrite, but slightly different thing there.
Yeah, the only thing I was thinking about with Gibbentake...
Did you buy content.com, which redirects to our YouTube,
for like 20 bucks for a year, so that, you know, not too expensive.
Oh, no, no, it's not the expense that I'm thinking of.
It's just like the name. I wanted a name.
20 bucks for a year, that's a fucking deal.
Yeah, I mean, how many people wanted...
It cost me like $10 a month.
How many people wanted can-tent, I guess, spelled fucked up.
Wait, no, no, wait, I'm paying for hosting,
so that's different.
Never mind.
I wanted something...
I was trying to think of something that was,
one, unique and interesting and cool and stuff.
Two, sort of explains what the hell it is before you click on it.
Like, St. Comics, okay, it's a comic website about angels, I guess,
you know, from the name.
A good Catholic website, thank God.
Yeah, and something that you couldn't actually misspell.
Like, if you heard someone say it, there would be no way you could misspell it.
Like, St. Comics, those are words.
You know how to spell those.
They're not comics with a CK and an X, as I recall, which was wise.
But fucking give and take, it's a pun, it's a play on words, it's give and take.
If you say that to someone, they're not immediately going to understand it's the monkey
and the act of taking something as a word.
So I was like, that might not be perfect.
I mean, phonetically, give and take.
I mean, people hear the joke, but I mean, the B's are very distinct.
I think it's a pretty decent one for recognizability of how to write it.
But then again, I've known you so long, maybe I'm a little biased in that.
Yeah, Hippocrates similarly, like, the whole joke, not the whole joke,
but part of the joke is that it's like how people often misspell Hippocrite.
Names are hard, guys.
Marketing and shmarketing.
I've been putting it off for a million years.
And also, I don't like the idea of like, porting over Bale-Japes in its entirety to a whole other website.
Or, you know, whatever I would need to do to change the name.
Couldn't you just copy the code?
Like, just copy paste the whole thing.
You're using Google Sites, right?
No, no, I'm using WordPress's thing.
Not free WordPress, the other one.
The real big boy WordPress.org?
The real WordPress, yes.
That's what the PCP website uses as well.
I've been uploading, so I've started uploading to Webtoon and Tapas.
I'm kind of pushing Webtoon more because I feel like the audience is bigger there.
But at some point, I'll put Slime and Punishment up on St. Comics, just like as an archive.
But I've been putting it on Webtoon just because I feel like, not a lot of people,
but like some people will see it there and like, you know...
Possibly the most dedicated fans, perhaps, if they're there?
Maybe.
Yeah, like, just because it's a public, it's like YouTube.
It's like YouTube for Web Comics.
And go visit my fucking site.
Go search Bansain on webtoons.com.
Subscribe, like all my shit.
It just passed a thousand likes on Slime and Punishment,
which means that now, when it's displayed, when you see a new update
on the little fucking new updates page, it doesn't just...
It actually tells you how...
It says like, this guy's actually got some fucking likes on his shit.
Oh, that's nice.
Like, oh yeah, I'm cool.
What's the... Is the currency devalued?
What's like a large number of likes or whatever to have on tabs?
I mean, if you're really big, you might have millions.
Okay, fair enough.
Fair enough.
Homestuck?
No.
Two likes.
Nobody likes.
No, like...
Zero likes and homestuck.
Or, um...
I don't know.
God, I wish that were me.
Yeah, I wish everyone was using Notify.me,
because it is the best thing in the world that nobody...
Explain that, Tom.
I don't understand.
Okay, so Notify.me is a website...
Is a website slash app slash service,
and what you do is you can make an account on Notify.me,
and you can plug in any source you want,
and people can subscribe to you on Notify.me,
and every time you upload anything anywhere,
it sends your subscribers a notification.
So instead of having to be like,
Oh, I have to be on YouTube,
because that's where everybody is.
If everybody just used Notify.me,
you could just post on your website,
a notification that you posted something on your website,
on their Notify app,
and then they could see it there.
Oh, so they have to download Notify.
Correct.
It's a platform specifically just to have notifications.
It's basically pulling the notifications out of an app,
out of individual apps,
like, oh, I gotta get my YouTube notifications
and my Twitter notifications.
It's putting them all in one thing.
So you get notifications of people, not of services.
I mean, I would love it if everything was kind of on there,
and it kind of reminds me a little bit of, like,
Dick's Masterson made New Project 2,
which is just Patreon with no...
It actually takes zero fees from what I understand,
so it actually would be preferable.
It takes a small transaction fee for the bank.
For bank fees.
I mean, yeah, that's understandable,
but I mean, Patreon takes, I believe, a 5% cut.
Slightly more, if I remember.
I think it's like 9%.
Is it? I haven't checked in a while.
90%.
No, maybe it's not 9%.
I know they changed their terms.
I think it used to be 5, and then they changed their terms.
But, like, we have an old Patreon,
so it got grandfathered into the, like,
we keep the 5% or something.
I don't fucking know.
But, like, that...
Patreon has all these facsimiles of, like,
vestigial social media stuff
that doesn't matter, and who cares,
and I just want a bank transaction on a place
that won't kick me off,
which I am not convinced Patreon will never do to us,
or any of us individually.
So just a neutral platform
that just does nothing would be nice.
Yeah, like one of these generic...
As generic as possible, please.
No coming down on any side of any issue.
Just transact.
That would be my preference, but...
Hey, what you gonna do?
I mean, I love minimalist,
like, no bells and whistles,
no distraction bullshit on websites,
which is why most social media websites are annoying.
They've always got things they want you to look at,
and advertisements, and clickity-clackity things
all over the place.
And then every normal website
that is owned by some company has, you know,
100,000 things you have to click on
before you can see anything,
and then you also have to turn your ad blocker off,
and it's just, like, this is unsatisfying.
I hate the internet. It's not good anymore.
I just want a blank page with text on it that I can read.
You know, I think that this kind of, I don't know,
this, like, social media-esque bubble,
I think it will eventually burst,
and I think that we will see a return
to rote functionality one day,
where people will be like, it's just a basic shit.
I don't think it will ever return to anything.
I think what's gonna happen is that the social media bubble
is going to become an entirely normie thing,
and then everyone who's cool
will be not doing it anymore.
Like, they'll have to log on to Twitter for work.
Yeah.
God, I can't wait for the, what is it,
the social credit score.
Please, I want my tweets to be evaluated
for their affiliation to the one-party system
that we have. Oh, God, please.
I want to rake up the points.
Imagine if we made social, oh, God,
my peach fucking amiibo just fell,
but that's all right.
Speaking of social credit,
what was I fucking saying?
I want to gamify political ranking in the country
because I will then win.
I will then get the high score.
But right now, it's just some bullshit about it.
Wait, gamify in what way?
What would you suggest?
If there's a number value attached
to how many things I'm allowed to do socially,
like in China, if you do certain things
and you have a loan of social credit score,
I could be off about this, but as I understood it,
you can't take the train
to travel between cities or something.
You just aren't allowed to do that.
And I don't know what mechanisms you have to change it.
Maybe you can go give yourself 100 lashes
or go right on the chalkboard.
I believe in the state,
something like that over and over.
I want that. I'll be in there every day,
scribbling on my chalkboard.
You can go kill Hong Kong protesters
and you get points for everyone you take down.
Headshots count for extra 50 points.
Oh, my God, this is it.
It's like death race.
I was going to say, they let you log into a video game,
but it's like a drone control video game
and you log in to go mow down Hong Kong protesters
to up your credit score.
Now, that's the kind of shit I'm talking about.
It's like that thing in standalone complex, I think.
I think I saw a Digi video where they made a video game
and it controls a robot that goes and kills people
and the kids don't realize that's what's happening.
I don't remember that in standalone comics.
Wait, was it Psycho Pass Season 2?
It was something bad.
I would guess that Psycho Pass.
Yeah, that is Psycho Pass.
That's funny because I was totally afraid.
I was almost revealed as a ghost on the shelf fraud just now.
That was a close one.
I've never seen that fucking show.
I only know it because of Digi talking about that show,
but I thought I had seen it.
I was like, oh yeah, that was totally standalone complex.
I remember the whole thing.
The thing is, Nate, if this comes to pass
and it will be just like anything else
YouTube slash the internet does,
where the rules will be an algorithm
and we will not know what it is.
So we'll have to reverse engineer how the fuck
we even got our social credit score
and how to make it better and it'll be a nightmare.
It reminds me of how Matt Pat was so convinced early on
because Matt Pat originally came to YouTube
from like he worked for an MSM
or whatever the fuck they're called
streaming, so he felt he had an understanding
of how things were going to work.
He made a video once about how he was convinced
PewDiePie had gotten so popular,
but PewDiePie has many times come out
and been like, this is complete bullshit
and is not true.
I forget exactly why he was convinced of that,
but I remember thinking that seemed reasonable.
So I don't know which of those two guys are right,
but they definitely don't agree
and one of them's got to be kind of right
more than the other, I'd assume.
Matt Pat talked about how PewDiePie was saying
that it was bullshit and he said,
you know, I did get some things wrong.
I'm not interested in the drama,
but on this point of order, as Tom's saying,
we have to kind of figure out how the systems work
because we are not told deliberately so.
They want to keep things mysterious,
maybe for the illusion of naturality
in the system or something.
I think it's just because if everyone knows
how the algorithm works,
everyone will just game it instead of like,
just make content.
There's this back and forth of just like,
you want to have a platform
that is serving the user,
but without being so transparent
that it's completely
disincentivizing natural content creation.
It's that everyone's just trying to game the system
because then the system is limiting expression
and not helping it, you know?
It's occurred to me recently on that front.
I have just continued making videos
and I recognize about this myself.
I've just basically assumed
that like, if I just keep doing it,
things will work out reasonably well.
Like, I'm probably not being suppressed
in unfortunate ways.
I'm probably not like, totally wasting my time.
It'll probably work out, right?
I don't know that that's true,
but that's how I'm operating.
And I'm aware that like,
continuing to operate is basically assuming
that that is the case.
So like, I have culpability
in that I'm choosing to believe that, basically.
And it may not be true.
I may be making horrible mistakes
and wasting my time day in and day out,
but well, I guess I'll learn that one of these days,
maybe when I'm dead.
And God tells me so.
It's strange in particular,
your channel and its growth
has always, I guess, kind of confused me
because like, the meme has always been,
and we've mentioned it on this show before,
like once you hit 100k,
you get that extra boost.
I'm hoping for that to happen.
And that like, didn't happen for your channel for some reason?
I completely flatlined it, 100,000 basically.
And I don't understand why that is happening,
because it's not like you've stopped making content.
Like, oh, I hit 100k, time to hang up my hat.
You know, it's been very interesting
for me to look at the,
and maybe the videos are just worse,
that's definitely possible,
but like, for a time,
we were getting like, I don't know,
like easily between 30,000 to 50,000,
even over like 100,000 views,
and they're like, relatively lucky to clear 20,000.
And I just wonder,
is it just me, or did something change?
I mean, I'd be happy to
accept responsibility,
if I'm just making a worse product,
that's definitely possible,
but it doesn't seem like that.
I think it would be a mixture,
because I felt like,
your more recent wee aguas in the past
like, few months have been,
you know, like, they're alright.
They feel a little bloated
of talking going on in them,
especially like, the front-loading
upload, like, you talk about
what the thing is for a long time,
and then get to the interesting part,
like, near the middle and the end.
It's just that I don't feel that that's changed much
from how they used to be,
and I mean, that's the curious thing to me.
I'm aware, I'm happy to take any criticisms,
and you know...
I mean, that's just my, like, the back of my head,
like, what am I thinking?
Like, why was I happy about
just sort of, eh, I don't really understand.
Well, you know, I have one other theory that relates to that,
which is just that the format has gotten
stale, kind of in general,
and that could explain it. Like, at first,
maybe the videos were better, maybe they weren't,
they were shorter when they first started,
but now people, like, one, they're bloated,
and two, maybe people are simply like,
eh, I get it, Nate talks about thing, whatever,
which is, you know, again, that could totally be
fair. We're all just still waiting
for the second video of Nate's channel,
Best Anime Ever Goes On The Shell.
It will happen someday. I'm sure
Nate will make a new video eventually.
It's only been, like, two years.
One of these days, one of these days,
we'll see a video from Nate.
Why is he leaving us hanging? He doesn't make any videos.
Oof. I'm doing my best, boys.
One day.
Hey, uh, incidentally, left turn,
I've got an anecdote that I think
you lads will find amusing,
enjoyable, uh, perhaps
hilarious.
Uh, let's, let's, let's, let's see what you think.
So, the other day, I was going to
the P.O. box to pick up my mail
for We Aguas, as it happens,
and I went and got my, got my couple of packages,
and I forget why.
There was, like, an issue with one or something.
Oh, I had to actually, I was paying for a renewal
to my, uh, P.O. box,
because it was, it was running out. Got to get six more months, whatever.
So, I had to go up to the counter to do this,
and so, me and, and Michelle happens to be with me,
because we were, she was driving somewhere, whatever.
And she's wearing her big bear coat.
It's like, uh, she gets compliments on it all the time.
It's, it's cute, it's furry, it's got a big bear face.
It's, uh, everybody loves it.
Right? And she's actually, actually one time
we were in the airport, and
a woman just walked up and said,
hey, excuse me, I love your coat.
Can I just buy it off you?
And Michelle said, I mean, you know,
I'm a kind of cold, and the woman was like,
I'll give you my coat, and I'll pay you for it.
It seemed like a, a well-off individual.
How good is this coat? I haven't seen this.
This really happened. I think she was only willing
to go up to, like, 50 bucks
and she would also trade her coat.
Which is, it's not like this coat is, like,
so, like, valuable,
it just is cute, and I think on a whim
people like it. And she gets compliments all the time.
So, in this case.
If you want to, you want to make a proposition like that,
you gotta have more money to throw around than 50 bucks.
To buy the coat off their back, I mean, yeah,
for sure. We're talking, we're talking, like,
like, 50K, maybe.
I mean, Michelle skinned
this bear herself. She wrestled it,
she defeated it in combat, you know,
it was at least $75.
I'd say so.
So, Michelle's, whatever,
she's wearing this coat, we walk into the counter,
and I'm buying the renewal for the P.O. Box.
And the lady, it's like this nice black lady
I see all the time. She, she just says to us,
she's like, oh, you know, hey, nice to see you again.
I'm like, hey, what's going on? She's like, oh, I,
I love your coat, she says to Michelle.
And she's like, oh, thank you, thank you,
getting one of these compliments. And she's like,
you know what that reminds me of?
My son's, like, my son has.
And we're like, okay, that's interesting.
She's like, yeah, you know,
except his doesn't have the face on it
in that same spot, she had, like, the hood back.
He's like, yeah, his has, like, a tail on it
instead.
Interesting, interesting.
And then she's like, yeah, you know,
he was wearing it at this thing called,
I swear to God, this is true,
Anthrocon, or like, something like that.
And I mean, we're just,
we're just looking at each other.
And we are thinking to ourselves, oh,
oh no. And you know Michelle,
Michelle hates the furries.
She wants the full genocide of the
furries. So Michelle
is not pleased
to be compared to an Anthrocon.
So this whole time, maybe that lady who came
up to buy it was like a furry
and they were looking for that sort of coat.
She was on her way to Anthrocon and she needed
a costume, she forgot hers at home.
So like, as we're leaving, she's like,
yeah, you know, it looks great on you,
but you know, I don't know about my sons,
like it's a little weird for like a 30-year-old man
to be wearing a fuzzy bear outfit,
but hey, he's my son, so I love him.
And we're like, thank you, ma'am,
thank you, ma'am, for this information.
Have a wonderful day. And we
turned 360 degrees and walked out.
And so Michelle
was just reeling from the realization
that maybe Michelle
Tobin is a little closer to the furry
community than she would like to believe.
You know, she's real cozy with Cassie
and she's seeing some red flags
trying to recover from the mental trauma.
So this coat has like a
bare head?
I will have to get a picture and put it in the show notes,
but it's just like a tan
furry-looking coat
and the hood that you can put up over your face
just as kind of like a cutesy sort of
Japanese-looking bear face
on the hood. Is it like the end of Midsommar?
Yes, identical to the ending of Midsommar.
I just watched Midsommar
yesterday or two days ago
because I was supposed to discuss it with
Mumki and Florian on Is It Kino?
And then Mumki just... No, Mumki
just like, he's just like
too busy. I didn't
like one day before
we're supposed to do it,
he just puts in our group chat
like, eh, you know,
I don't have the time to do Is It Kino
or watch any of the movies.
Well, at least he gave you a day warning, I guess,
but still an unfortunate. Well, yeah, the day before.
I had already gone
and watched, like, all the shit.
Was there more than one?
Yeah, there was.
Because I said, I wanted... Mumki, Mumki.
He was like, pick a
pick a thing, pick like an underrated movie
you want to talk about. And I was like,
Turbo Kid, 100%
Turbo Kid. Oh, right, right, yeah, yeah.
And they were like, okay, cool, we'll watch
Turbo Kid. And then, like, later on
in the week, Florian is like
he's like, hey, have you seen
some movie? It was like some
new movie with Christian Bale. And I'm like,
no? And he's like, we're going to talk about that too.
And I'm like, I gotta
go to the theater and watch a movie?
I thought we paid him money too.
Well, I didn't. I skipped out.
And then I was like, and then he's like, okay,
we're also going to talk about the New Rick and Morty
and Midsommar. And I'm like, oh, Jesus Christ.
A lot of things, a lot of things.
I don't want to do any of those, but I did.
I did watch the New Rick and Morty
and I did watch Midsommar just for this.
I didn't get to watch whatever this Christian Bale
film is. And I don't really want to,
but whatever.
Yeah. And then it gets
fucking postponed indefinitely
on my ass.
I can't believe you would come out here
and make a straight-up drama video
against one, Monkey Jones.
It's never been done before, as I understand it.
And you are breaking new ground here
by exposing him as the hack-fraud
canceler of plans. A real Indian giver
of, you know. That full little baby
needs all the defense he can get.
Mmm.
I'm just the guy to give it.
Well, I made that just the way.
Well, I was until now.
I really would have wanted to watch that, though.
I've never seen it. I've never seen
Izakino. It's just never been a thing
I wanted to look at. No. Oh, I watched,
I remember feeling, I was, I will
stent me and Asperger are like
bosom buddies over our love
of law-abiding citizens
starring Russell Crowe.
Yeah, Russell Crowe. Is that true?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Okay. I mean, we never
spoke about it, but he did love that movie
and I also love that movie.
I have never seen law-abiding citizens.
It's based.
Okay. All right. Pretty epic.
That's all there is to it, Ben. It's frankly, it's based.
Okay. Well, I mean, you can't
argue with quality. You know, I mean, it's about
a man. It's about a man going to any
lengths to get revenge for his
significant other, his wife in this case,
being, let's just say,
manhandled a bit negatively, and we all
know how Asperger feels about those things.
He won't have that. Oh boy.
Yeah, okay.
Let's, let's, okay.
Okay.
Nobody knows what you're talking about.
That'll never get old. Should we cut this
part? No, why? That's fine.
I mean, is it not okay to make jokes
about a man who actually, you know,
laid his hands upon another?
It's kind of, all right. All right. Let's move
on. Okay. All right. I'm uncomfortable.
But it's pretty funny.
I'm very comfortable. But anyway. Okay, cool.
That's, did I have another thing? Oh,
you know what? Small baby little anecdote
here. I was just driving to pick up Michelle
from work, and on an overpass I
drove under. Simply the words.
Now, it's just, it's rare for me to see
what, to me, was basically a meme,
but this made it more real in my mind.
Just on this overpass was spray
painted the words, you know, in Cincinnati, Ohio,
out here in the Midwest doing bullshit.
Just the words, Epstein didn't kill himself.
Written on a bridge
in real life. Good, good for that.
Like everyone we've seen. Good for that bridge.
Good job. It's, you know, I mean,
it just makes me reflect on how, like,
oh, this isn't just funny internet memes.
This is things that, like, kind of the real world
probably gives a shit about, which
is totally fair.
Oopsie-doopsy. There we go again.
I found myself, like, I was listening
to the news in the background, and
they were saying something about, there was, like,
Prince Andrew,
son of Prince, not son,
a brother to Prince Charles,
the least, the less
cool Prince
son of the Queen. I thought he was the Queen's favorite, though.
I heard he was her favorite. I don't know if I can read it.
I've never fucking heard of this guy. Prince Charles
is always in the news. Prince Andrew is not.
Prince Andrew has, like,
like,
like a suspiciously close
friendship with Jeffrey Epstein,
and there was an interview where he was
talking about stuff, and he was like,
huh, what's going on?
That was a rough one.
But anyway, they were talking about Jeffrey Epstein
on the news, and they were saying
Epstein, who hung himself in his
Prince style. Oh, come on now, guys.
And I just, like, it was
an unconscious reaction. I was like, no, he didn't.
Like, I just said that.
No, he didn't. Like, it wasn't a meme.
I wasn't trying to be funny. It was like, oh, yeah,
I guess it's true.
I said it without thinking about it.
Oh, you know what I heard about? I heard that
one Steven Crowder, who I'm sure everybody here
loves intensely, is going
to do a show where he's going
to attempt to snap his own
spine in the ways
that it's been reported that Epstein
did, and I don't know,
he says he's doing a live stream or something. He's going to put, like,
a gauge around his neck
and attempt to gauge
how much force is being applied as he, like,
you know, ties himself up and, like, jumps
off a bunk bed that, like, they've constructed
for this. This sounds like a
liberal's wet dream, because, like, on the one
hand, you can either prove that Epstein didn't kill
himself, or Steven Crowder
will die. We could all get
behind this one.
Hmm.
I'm coming around. You know, it does
make me feel warm to see
how everybody is on this
bullshit about how Epstein definitely
didn't. I mean, Epstein just committing
suicide. Woopsie-doopsie is not the full
story. We're all, we're all
seeing it right now. We should cross the aisle and be
bipartisan and just run the corpse of
Jeffrey Epstein for president in 2020.
The one man you can trust
to not kill himself
in office. It's, I mean,
it's still sort of sad, though. Like, it's a
meme, and it can be spread as a
meme, and people can say it and spray paint it
everywhere, but, like,
nobody actually has any information on who
did cover it up. They did
their job correctly. Nobody has any leads.
You didn't kill himself, and we can't
prove who it was. And I'll happily
say, as I always do, like, it is
fear. I think there are conspiracies,
like, I don't know, like, there are versions
of the tale where Epstein was, like,
pressured or convinced to
in some ways, like, kill himself
in some ways.
Kill himself. I mean, I guess
I know what you mean. There are
things that, there are levers that can be pulled to make
someone commit suicide because, like, worse things
will be done to, I don't know, people they love
or they're, like, things like that.
I'm pretty sure if you're forced
to kill yourself, it's not actually suicide
anymore.
You know, that's, legally speaking, you might be right.
You might be right. But,
like, it's just,
I'm just so
disappointed by the
lack of, what's the word,
credulity, or incredulity
by, you know, many people
who just report it as fact. Like, yeah,
it definitely killed himself. I mean, the mainstream
media is obviously just going to step in line
and say what they need to say, and
there's no chance of it. What do they even gain?
But everyone is, like,
this is, we don't believe you.
Well, that's the thing. That's the thing is, like,
the people who orchestrated
his murder,
and who can manipulate the media
into saying for sure that, you know,
not even trying to look into it, like, you can't
report on, you can't, any of your journalists
who want to go nosing around, tell them to stop.
Experiency theorists, madmen,
like, somebody or some group of people
just have the power to do that, and that's
sucks.
I mean, we just, we need our
boy, we need our lord and savior, Alex Jones,
to get involved and really start
getting to the bottom of this mystery.
I want to see
Alex Jones snapping necks and be like, no, it required
more force than it took to do Epstein.
Let me tell you,
have you guys seen that wonderful image of him
on, like, his male vitality
supplement or whatever, where it's before and after
him, with his, like, you know, fat
man, what's the word, like, dad bod,
and then, like, after one month,
and after one month of using it, it's
just him, he looks exactly the same,
but significantly redder.
Like, his whole body
is just glowing with
male vitality.
And he tells that.
I love all those
memes where it's that video
of him, like, pointing someone like, hey, you.
It's like a Pokemon using overheat or something like that.
I love
all those memes where it's, like, the video of
him, like, pointing at someone's like, hey,
you, fuck you, and he starts running towards
them, but it's like, come out and put on
game footage.
Like, there was a Minecraft one where a creeper blew him up.
Yeah, I've seen that one.
Or actually, you know, a better comparison is, like,
it's like Regigigas with, like, slow
start, where for three turns
he's just a normal mortal man, but on
turn four, he's at full capacity
and he's sprinting at you as
Regigigas.
Oh my god, here comes the super
Alex Jones.
I love Pokemon. Let's talk about Pokemon.
That's a great idea.
We can talk about Pokemon and politics through the lens
of Alex Jones.
It all comes together.
Oof, beat the game.
It was good. I had a fun time.
No, no, it was a joke, Nate. We don't actually
know about Pokemon.
Go watch the new content episode, Me and Did You
Produced, where we go into it at length
in a, what's the word, separate but equal
podcast to the PCP.
Just for Pokemon discussion.
Oh, yeah, speaking of.
We have three-fifths of a podcast, I'd say.
You're going to do new Rickstee Minutes?
Oh, that's the next one coming up. Yep, we're definitely
doing new Rickstee Minutes.
Cool. Has there been another Rick and Woody since
the first one came out?
I think three episodes are out now, I believe.
At least two.
I'll give you the short version on episode one,
which is the one I've seen so far.
It was good, bordering on great,
but not amazing.
And I'm looking forward to see if it gets
better or worse or, I don't know.
Well, what to say? I liked it.
It was fun. Yeah, that was good.
It was fun and it was still Rick and Woody, so.
It was. I was not majorly disappointed at all.
Fuck yeah.
I saw premiere and I saw episode two
and I thought the second episode was
pretty mediocre, but the premiere was
pretty good. That's the opposite
of what I was hoping for. I was hoping it would
ramp up as it keeps going.
I've watched any of them. I've just been watching
Beastars and The Mandalorian, which are both
fucking sick.
Oh shit, have you got
Didney Plurps? No, I have
the Leetx.to,
my favorite streaming service.
Everything's there. Leetx?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Leetx.to.
You guys heard about Leetx.to?
Is that legal? Is that legal?
Monkey showed me this app and maybe I shouldn't
talk about it publicly, but here I am.
It's called TTV
and it just gets everything.
That sounds good.
I couldn't find any
rips of Rick and Morty
through Googling
and I'm like, hey monkey, where do I see it?
And he tells me about this app called
tea.tv
and I just get on there and I type
in Rick and Morty season four
and in zero time
there's like, you know, 50 different
file versions of the
new episodes
and he just finds
anything on there for free.
Do you have to torrent him or are they streaming there?
Well, I downloaded it to my phone.
They were streaming but I downloaded it
because it was, you know,
the phone wouldn't sputter or lag or anything
and so I don't know.
That seems pretty cool.
Seems like it worked
as intended.
Fuck the police.
Hear that knock on your door?
That's the police. They're listening
to this podcast right now. They're coming for you.
Oh, you know, the other day
I made a bit of a cheeky tweet
as
like it was a Nintendo put out
a tweet that was like, hey
it's like the 15 year anniversary
of the Nintendo DS.
Name some of your favorite games
and I as an epic meme lord
tweeted out, like I retweeted
that and said, what was it, like
the homebrew channel.
It was an excellent game. Really had a lot of fun
with that one or something.
And full disc, I think actually
I think Keyblade's spirit, that mother fucker
said like, wasn't it actually on the 3DS
the homebrew channel? But you know what the fuck I mean
my R4 card, my Ace card 2Y
I almost said it but I was like
don't let it get out of your skin, Nate.
I won't, damn you Keyblade. Now I'm mad.
Don't play on my DS.
I won't immediately
let you get out of your skin.
Two multiplayer.
I mean I played, I emulated a bunch of stuff
I played a million games
I think I actually played
ironically, I played Mother 3
on my PSP
emulating it on there instead.
But it was a wonderful time and it was a great
PSP was a great concept. They had a great
art app for the DS on DS Homebrew
called Colors. And it was crazy
because the screen on the DS
has pressure sensitivity. So this art
program was basically just turned your DS
into a tiny little Waycom tablet.
I did a bunch of art projects in college
on my DS because I was too lazy
to get up and go to my computer.
I don't blame you.
That's sick. That's sick.
I'll picto chat will always be in my heart
and I'll never forget it. Greatest app of all time.
Press effort DS.
You guys know who Jennifer Diane
writes is? Or maybe Reitz
I think it's Reitz. I don't think so.
She is a lol cow
She is like an old
past meme of a lol cow.
And I've mentioned her one or two times
because coincidentally
I used to post on the same
spore forums as her
in the lead up to the release of Spore
I was on this forum called Gaming Steve
which was
one of the places where
it had one of the most
active spore fan communities
because we were all really hyped
for spore. It was going to be a game changer.
All of the stray.
You were. I remember that.
And there was a poster on there called
Jennifer Diane writes and it turned out
she was kind of a famous lol cow
and I didn't know it at the time
but she was active there
and I went and I read
one of her old webcomics yesterday
it took me like all day
the comic was called
Unicorn Jelly
and it's really funny
it gets kind of good
but it's like
she's lecture worthy
maybe not specifically Unicorn Jelly
but maybe just all of her
comics together
because I mean
Unicorn Jelly is pretty complicated
but it's mostly complicated
and she puts
there's all this lore
there's a whole science
of how that universe works
I feel like the story is almost just a vehicle
for her to come up with weird sci-fi concepts
of how gravity
works through a completely different mechanism
in this world and how
the universe is structured in a completely different way
and it's based on different fundamental
physics laws and stuff
and I don't know
the art style is really funny
because there will be really big
pretty detailed
scenery shots that you can
tell a lot of effort went into
and that actually sometimes looks pretty cool
but then the actual character art
looks like I think
the whole thing was drawn with a mouse
and like the art
the character art is like super bad
sometimes
most of the time
it's like mushy, pseudo, anime
like Dominic Deegan
I like the design, I just googled it
Unicorn Jelly Him Herbs herself
looks cute, it's a cute design
you mean the jelly itself?
yeah sure
which I assume is the main character
basically not at all
okay I mean there are things
that the Unicorn, it's a uni
there are things that uni does
and like uni is in the story
through most of it but like
he, I think it's a he
is definitely not the main character
it's the main characters are basically
his adoptive mother
who is like a witch
who is just like shit at magic
well it's not even that she's shit at magic
and it's a problem
she's a witch but like she literally does
no magic over the course, she just doesn't engage with it
it's like not important
and then
her like adoptive
daughter who is actually like
a human girl who gets in
early on she gets like infected with like a crystal
disease
and like the magic of uni
uni's unicorn magic
like cures her but it doesn't fully cure her
and like the crystals like stay
in her body and they're like in her brain
and they turn her into like a super computer
girl kind of
and it's like it turns into some fucking
like Gurren Lagann like
migrate all of humanity across the cosmos
stuff
and it's website
it's fucking insane
unicornjelly.com
it's very classic it's very 90's
it's so like angel fire
I feel so at home right now
like in this odd sense of calm is
washing over me as I
really live my childhood
with her on website
I like
there's unicornjelly continues
as a film noir side story
that takes place in the same universe
to save her follows an alternate version
KY
and a cast of familiar faces as they seek
a mysterious goal while traveling among many different
alternate versions of the universe
of Tries
Lamastia I can't even pronounce that
yeah Tristle
um yeah
the the saga continues I guess
wait what wait what where's it called
to say it's called to save her
there's a button right below
uh unicornjelly
yeah I clicked on that
oh to say whoa okay
film noir side story what the fuck
okay I didn't even find this
holy shit there's like a lot of it there's like
hundreds of pages more
hooray the adventure continues
damn but you know I like a lot of this sprite art
it looks nice
sometimes it looks good yeah
like okay there are times when like
they do like a close-up
in particular there's like a little girl character
with like big sparkly eyes who's like
eh weh weh
when uh who looks really
bad uh huh
like when you close up
close-ups on faces are really
they can be pretty fucking shit sometimes
oh yeah I just clicked on it
you're right like it's not all bad like there's
yeah yeah there's times when it actually
kinda neat but oh there's like
there's like there's like radio dramas
there's like bits that like
she and her people like like recorded
like radio sort of like
sound clips of like conversations
the characters are having and it's pretty neat
um there's a there's a game
there's like a chess game that exists
in this world called toss in
but I think she made rules for her there's rules
for that there's a card game there's
d&d 3.5
rule sets for all the creatures so you can put them
on their campaigns yeah and all the
all the characters have stat blocks and stuff
this is kind of legit
I know right
but what's uh what's the thing
so how is this a lol cow is it just the comic
just cringe okay well the thing that she
okay well she has a bunch of like
really weird comics like this
like there's there's other ones besides unicorn
do things get way sexy later
no well there's a little bit
of fan service with two
dudes there's like a there's
a there's like a whole page that's like it's called
like the uh the yaoi
like fan service page or something and it's
just kind of like a romantic like kissing
with their shirts off kind of that seems
fine it's funny um
okay the thing that Jennifer is most
known for is the
um Kokoro wish
comment oh that's her
yes Jennifer dyan writes is the
Kokoro wish person
she's also old as fuck she's
gotta be like pushing 60 now
like when she like when she was making
unicorn jelly she was like 43
what some of us bloom a little bit later
than others Ben she's about to hit
her stride and that was in like 2002
so that's like seven yeah she's
like 60 oh
well
I think I don't know if she's online anymore
I think she might have retired from the limelight
damn I couldn't blame her unicorn jelly
I've used up three mice so far
I guess I am pretty hard on mice
the mouse I like is a Microsoft
Intellipoint so she draws
the mouse there's a
whole page there's a whole page about how
unicorn jelly is created and it's just a wall
of text about how she uses a mouse do you
think it'd be possible to like actually
acquire skill at drawing with a mouse
maybe the sensitivity or something
there's there's definitely people who draw
with my houses yeah holy
shit the unicorn jelly forums are
still up
uh the lap okay
any update like every single
one every single like
part of the forum the last
post was in like 2017
except wait there's one post
in the generic all-purpose forum
on October 5th 2019
let's see let's see
what let's see what shivers
have just okay it's in a thread called what do you like
better GTA Xbox 360
or GTA 5
what's the verdict
there is
wait there's dying to know
I'm making an account right now
Ben
there's one reply
and someone named
arex replies GTA 5
on a Sinclair ZX80
PC
gaming master race
okay there you go
anyway I'm going to read more Jennifer
Ryan writes
there's a thread
on 9-11 conspiracy
theories
that was that was updated
in 2018
Ben you have to post in the forums
about Epstein not killing himself
get the fall rolling all over again
how Epstein did 9-11
can I register
yes still up I guess
yeah
okay well here we go
this is my new adventure
Ben what if I made a little uh you know
what's it called uh unicorn jelly
slimeoid you know maybe bringing
the two great series together
the one climactic clash
I mean I think it goes without saying
that unicorn jelly is canon to um
to rfgk
the plot of like
they have to go between like these
like world plates like the world in this
triska triska decophobia
universe
is like
instead of planets like the whole universe
is full of air and there aren't planets
there are these big triangular plates called world
plates that are just like
formed into this big like a serpentski
triangle formation
just like in space
and they have to go from one to another
to escape like a storm that is like destroying
uh plates
and it's gonna fucking wreck their home world
but like but like the native
life on all the non-human
native life on all these other worlds
is like crystal in life
and slimes are a form of
uh crystal crystal light well there's
there's red life which is like living things
that are full of blood green life
which is plants and then there's white life
which is like crystal shit
that is full of this like white like uh goo
I'm hearing slime oids
staydeads and red man
are all
he's the one form of red life that migrated
from triskelion
ooh that's good lore and he's got we gotta
get him we gotta send him back
we gotta build the wall and send him back
over it
crystals in our country no sir
oh my god
otakuworld.com
oh that sounds great
is that related?
yeah there's a she links to it somewhere
I just really
I'd taken it back by the logo
oh wow
it really speaks for itself look at that ladies and gentlemen
uh wait I gotta see I gotta see
is it in the main chat
is it in the main chat though
oh otakuworld
otakuworld
no
oh imagine that you're sailing over otakuworld
oh watch out there's the world eye
and then you actually sail into the world mouth
and fall to the center of the earth
before merryweather made like black hole chan
and earth chan and stuff
otakuworld is is co-run by jennifer
dian writes
and then there's two webmaster people
but is she still active
that's the question
I like this website though this is really funny
boys and girls we can go on all day
about the delights
I could talk about unicorn
stay tuned for more of my hot takes
about jennifer dian writes
his web comics from 2002
did her selfish boyfriend ever agree
to make that full video game
that she would then furnish for art
what is her kokoro wish ever granted
it's a great question
and I don't have an answer for you
I pray every night for an answer
maybe one day I will
I stand for December 30th
that's like 60 or 59
yeah 60
well almost she's going on 60
59 going on 60
you gotta celebrate her birthday
wait wait December what? her birthday is coming up
30th yeah
December 30th
that's like a one month and six days from today
yeah
birthday dian
maybe I'll fucking
put it on
that's not what I meant
but okay
I should do something
grant her kokoro wish
make her a game ben
you gotta make
the version of spore you were all waiting for
back in the day
okay the scene
is the hey arnold christmas special
you've got that
mister win or whatever his name was
is there inside being like
no one ever granted my kokoro wish
I spend christmas alone sad
every year and you ben you
are helga pataki standing outside
sending in your anthropomorphized game
into the house knock on the door
she opens the door it's a game
furnished with everything but art ready to go
it's the most wonderful experience
and you stand outside as helga just saying
merry christmas dian
I can just see this
as the scene from hey arnold
but with like shittily pasted like twitter
cars over the faces
oh god please someone make it happen
someone make that happen
this is a perfect moment for you to get retweeted
by the pcp twitter
account and oh my god
you could put that on your gravestone retweeted
by the pcp patreon
wait no twitter whatever also donate to our patreon
please at patreon.com
slash the progress if you're donating to the patreon
your chances of getting a retweet go way up
they significantly rise
there's no doubt about it
dammit
I know there are other
jdr comics
I can't remember any of them right now
but a lot of them do involve
like slime or jelly
she definitely has
she's got the soul of a slime boy in her heart
she definitely has a certain
affinity for that
I think those crystals that populate her world
they have to be podrans right
oh yes pastel defender heliotrope
that's the other one
which
okay well obviously I have to read it
I think those are the two main ones
is unicorn jelly and pastel defender heliotrope
I'm opening that right now
sounds great report back with results
Ben says nothing for the rest of the podcast
just enamored by this new story
and apparently this one ran for
another like four years after
from 2004 to 2008
so after unicorn jelly
the work output is impressive
especially
she put out a comic like every weekday
and some of them are
like they start out as
just like three panel strips but like some of them
are like big like splash pages
there are some that are like 12 panels
or more
the work effort is admirable
this is the thing I genuinely
have come around a bit on like
christine weston chandler
that is, say what you want
about her and her work
her art skill
you're like her skill level
you can criticize all you want
but she has put out a lot of work
and like she has clearly
there's time put in there
and you have to respect that
there was a video or a vlog I wanted to make
at some point saying christ chan is a better artist
than you because christ chan actually
I like that
that's a really light of fire under somebody
you can be as good as you want
but if you don't produce anything
cause like there was a definition of art
that was on like a youtube video that I found really interesting
this was by simon cynic saying like
if you are a master craftsman
at like your chosen art but you don't share it
with anybody it's not art you're just a crafts person
to be an artist you have to publish something
and in that regard I think
the point is that like christ chan is obviously a better artist
than like 99% of people that don't actually
produce anything
that's super good
and a great take that I will defend
that's a very excellent youtube clickbait title
there's no doubt in my mind
that's been brewing for a few months
in the old noggin
cause I'm waging a silent war against art culture
cause I hate it
as Nate knows
and saw the opening sale
make art culture great again boys
what is art culture
a bunch of whining
entitled babies
for constantly on the internet
being like sorry for themselves
instead of like making their lives better
and I hate it
I'm making things
I'm making things every day
I got really close
to like finishing
the sketches
of this one comic
that I've been working on for a while
and the sketching part
is the hardest part
getting everything laid out
on where the character is
where the speech bubble is going
and how to go from one panel to the next
in a cool way
so that it works
I'm stuck right at the end
cause I didn't write exactly what happens
right at the end
it sucks so much
if there's any lesson to learn here
it's to do
as much pre-production
as possible
and early along as possible
like write down
a description of what you think the panel should look like
even
because then when it comes to drawing
one wrong line or a wrong pose
takes a lot longer than
typing the pose that you want
wait so what
what are you stuck on exactly
let me just make sure I understand exactly what you mean
I'm right at the end of this thing
but the thing is I had a script
I wrote up a script for
what happens in the comic
and this last bit
it doesn't have
there was a complication
I had to add something in
it's just sort of ruining the flow
and I don't know how to reconcile it
I'm only like 3 or 4 pages away from it being done
it's like 80 something pages long
awesome
so it's like
that reminds me
when I'm making
slime and punishment
and slime and punishment
I had a couple of
I guess none of them are
necessarily the ending
but I had a couple of scenes
this will conclude in this way
I had
the big moments in mind
and everything else is about
setting up and building
towards making those conclusions happen
so I kind of know the endings
and I
because then shit happened on twitter
and Christine
responded to stuff
some people on twitter
trolls mostly were saying
Ben don't listen to her
don't do what she wants
this is your comic
it's true
but the thing is that I find it
satisfying and a cool creative
exercise
to build chris's input
for her character into the story
the character should do what she would do
so I find it a cool challenge
and it's
valuable to me
to be like how can I
accommodate this
into the story
the things that are going to happen
are still going to happen
I'm working on a
detour now where phantom horn goes to the alpha timeline
to accomplish
some weird
shit
that chris made up
that she wants to happen in the alpha timeline
and it's really strange and funny
so that's another reason
it would be funny
this is so fucking bizarre
I just want to include it
I know we've talked about this before
but the one thing I'm most disappointed by
with Christine
is her insistence
on the fact that phantom has
obtained his horn
his arc is over
that ruins the character to do that
yes it is a nightmare
it is an absolute fucking nightmare
but you know what
we live in a multiverse
of infinite possibilities
I can't sit here and tell you that such a thing
could never happen
I can't do that
however I can
correct this little
there's nothing to stop
this horn from
rotting or something
corrupting and having to be so sawn off
otherwise he dies
I mean something must be done
something will be done
on earth as it is in heaven
as above so below
by the way
speaking of artistic integrity
I just wanted to say that
for the last bonus pcb episode we did
we did like a game development one
and a lot of us talked about our projects
and stuff and you should definitely go listen to the one
because that was a great episode
$5 patreon.com slash the procrastinators
32 full fucking bonus episodes now
Jesus Christ what a deal
and I wanted to say that
I talked to you guys a bunch
about the game that I've been working on
for years
we worked on it for several months
before I started doing YouTube
and we produced art assets
and I showed a bunch of that stuff
but I didn't have a working demo of the game
but just because I so wanted to
I spent like a full day
opening up my old laptop where I've been working
on that game trying to run the game
trying to get an exportable exe file
that I could share and I couldn't do it
but so I went back
and I fixed some broken things
and made like a working developer
version of the game and was able to
export it so it works as intended
on like window systems
and that's going to be attached to the
episodes so people can play the one
basic ass level that exists without any animations
like the basic functionality
worked pretty cool
and I loved doing it and it made me
be like oh maybe I could like work on this game
again it's like really fun and really good
do it so maybe I
fucking will dude maybe I fucking will
become more than a YouTuber become someone
of actual value
maybe I can do both maybe I can be a value
person and value less person
at the same time I gotta just add a link to my
old vlog uh analysis where creativity
goes to die so it would be inspired
hey you're not wrong I mean that's why
I like red letter media because like all along
they're also like occasionally
just like make a movie right and that's like
money where their mouth is
and I respect that greatly um
but like I loved it so much
I feel I'm gonna keep that exclusive
to the bonus episode but I gotta tell you
I really want to release it to like
the public at large because I like it so much
and I want people to see it so maybe
we'll consider that a limited time restriction
to the bonus episode and then afterward
I'll uh I'll let the boys out there
just force yourself to release it to the public
in a in a further developed
state well sensor every
asset in the game and it's only available
on the bonus episode
I could do that oh it felt so good
programming like like I mean I worked
for years as a programmer and it could
feel satisfying but I mean that was
you know whatever it is that's work it's a job
not that interesting but like you're working on your project
and then you get it working and you get
an exportable exe the first people can
play oh it feels good oh it feels
real good so uh it's
good stuff and I believe I did in fact make
those sprites and I feel real good about them
I love them and uh they're not animated
as there's there's a gift that
Gib produced of the little animation
in the bonus episode so that go look at that
to see what it would look like if
QT base drop
as I've decided to call her from that episode
get Quentin Tarantino
base drop that's her full name Quentin Tarantino
base drop her full name
so it has been decreed um
anyway good good good stuff good stuff go watch
that episode um
uh it was voice mails voice mails
I think I think it's time
well you got something else good well I had
just like a I've been cleaning
out my room no no I think we got it now I think
we're going to have to move along
but the room situation
well just clean out my room and I was
finding uh
stacks upon stacks of lined
paper and and and
yes stacks of of of
paper money that is oh yeah
no uh lined paper and like a scroll
of paper and all of this
unused um you know just
sitting there like blank paper
huge amounts of it um
all these notebooks and stuff and I'm
looking at them and I want to draw
on them but I don't also
want to draw on them because uh
drawing sucks and it's
it's bad have you been drawing a lot in your
in your comic and stuff yeah
it's online it's on the
the on the the internet
super highway the I mean the
tablet right so like
so like I've got all this
paper and I don't know what to do with it like if I fill
it up with stuff if I need to use it anywhere
I'll have to scan it or take a picture and that's
a fucking taking a picture is easy though right
I mean you could you know it's just an extra
little yeah but it's
scanning it in is like if
if I wanted to actually use it for something
I would need to do that when I
did the like because
the first
the first of vapor's chapter I like sketched
in pencil and scanned it in
and it was such a nightmare because I drew
it on big paper and
it was too big for the scanner so
I had to take like four I had to like scan
for like four different angles and then
combine the four scans into
one image and like remove
like imperfections from the scanning yeah
yeah yeah basically it'll
solve all your problems what is that Tom
down what is down with the app your phone
called cam scanner yeah take it open up
it works just like a camera you take
a photo of the page and it detects
the corners of the paper and you can manually
just them if need be and then it
it adjusts the
perspective so it's flat like it was in a camera
like a scanner bed and then does some
post-processing to clean up the image and
then you can save it anywhere and then it's like your phone
scanned it and you don't have to worry about
finangling with a scanner anything it's way faster
it's way easier I found
an incredibly helpful thing because I was
porting I was reformatting
slime and punishment for to plastic and web
tune and it was such a nightmare because
every like it's hundreds of images like
300 something images and
I had to go into each one like
like resize it basically
and like sit and like export right
and and it was really annoying and
someone on some form
or something I found there someone had
just made like a widget online
that you can it specifically
for to plastic and webtoon you can just like
select images and it will just like spit out
a resized version at the correct
and you can do it with whole batches of them
and it saved me hours
overjoyed it was
called crappie
and that's it
do you think it's worth putting bell
jpe through that yes
because why not well the
only thing is there's all the text underneath
the images and also the gifts
and stuff it would be like
yeah they'd take gifts
I don't
okay I know webtoon doesn't
which is why I haven't put
what's I have a beast
be escapades
because be escapades was lots of gifts and I know
web tapas I don't
think so but maybe webtoon
no webtoon will but you have
to be like a featured creator
or like it's some it's some fucking bullshit
class class system
or shit it's bad
yeah so
it's the problem with being interesting
all the rules fair time
that's your answer for everything Tom
it's the right way to go
I mean I agree that
yeah it's good to have a website but there's no pre
existing audience there right so why can't
you can't reach people through your website
like everybody like where all
of us like fucking pleb creators
online right we're all like using
Twitter and we're using YouTube and every time
YouTube or Twitter changes we all
bitch piss and moan about how bad it is and how we're
getting fucked but like if you look
at actual brands like real companies
like businesses that like understand like how
the world works unlike us
none of them do that
all of them use Facebook and
YouTube and Twitter as advertising platforms
to push you to their website
and get you on their email list so they can
stay in contact with you one-on-one and not to compete
with all the noise of social media
that's like good enough for Coca-Cola
it should be the de facto
model we're all just too lazy to put in the work
to actually build a proper platform the way
like regular companies would do it because it is
more effective it's a snow it's a snowflake
no snowflake blames itself for the
Blizzard it's kind of like no snowflake
no individual like Twitter artist or whatever
will want to bear
the full brunt of you know creating a new
thing so there's a lot of inertia there I would imagine
you don't you don't even just just make a website
it's not hard yeah
Squarespace this episode of the
Procrastin's podcast brought to you by Squarespace
Squarespace is the excellent
just go make your website on Squarespace
it fucking should be god damn it
Huell, call me back, sponsor me
for Christ's sake I still get
Huell residuals every now and then it gets
I was saying someone use someone use your code for
Huell here's $15 you gotta
talk about that after I gotta fucking at least
get that shit gone I don't fucking know
yeah all right we'll speak afterward
by the way
Gibb I was gonna say to your point
about like wanting to draw in a notebook
I assume because you like that
tactile I don't know sense or something
I've been what I've been doing the content
episodes with Digi I'll generally
either I'll write notes
on my whiteboard to like visually read so
it's easy to have you know know what I'm gonna say
or I'll write in my in like a physical notebook
I have this nice red notebook for my
old college days and I opened it up and I actually
just like finished filled up the last
available page and I couldn't help but
notice that like this originally was a
Japanese like learning notebook
I was using and it's just filled with page
after page after page of me
doing exercises and like just repeating
kanji and repeating hiragana
and like repeating vocabulary words
because I would just endlessly write those over
and over in the book to learn them
and it it maybe just feel like
I mean this is different from what you were talking about
I was just like ooh I really liked learning Japanese
that's another thing I should you know actively do
day to day which I have
definitely been lazy on most I've done is like follow
a bunch of learn Japanese Twitter accounts
so I'm at least bombarded by a couple
of words every day but it's certainly not
enough one day one day
man I do
like seeing some of these half
filled up books with like
years old like
like this one of
these has like physics
homework things and then like
on another page it's like
um ideas for
a Super Mario World of Warcraft
RPG MMO
where you can you can choose the faction you can
be like a goomba and you can level up and get
goomba equipment and run
around in a field
I thought it was such a sick idea
and and then there's like
like other game things I want to do
and then like spreadsheets I was
trying to write up for
for keeping track of my actual World of
Warcraft crafting
bullshit it's nice looking back
at all these stupid things I was
they cared about
you know just for some reason that just reminds me
of there's a game that came out
relatively recently that
it was a total indie like Kickstarter game
or something and it's it's
literally exactly like Paper Mario
so it's like filling the niche of the
classic Paper Mario and like thousand
year door game it's supposed to be like it's
exactly like them but
it's got the same papercraft design but it's just about
like bugs it's kind of like Hollow Knight
meets uh Paper Mario
and it looks wonderful but I just
haven't investigated whether it's good or not
what's it called you know I cannot
fucking remember I'm gonna Google it now
and see if I can figure it out
but it looks super good
hang on Paper Mario
it's called
Bug Fables that's the one
an exploration RPG full of bugs
on Indiegogo it was funded
man I really hope it doesn't launch with bugs
oh yeah it is just Paper Mario
and you know what
I fucking loved Paper Mario 1
and 2 especially
so I like it's an RPG
it looks great I think like the battle
system in Paper Mario was like one of my
favorites ever so I should
fucking play this game is the is the long and short of it
I'll get back to you if in fact
I do do so
that's what I've got that's my story
neat pretty fucking neat oh
I'm always happy to see like a
little Indie company
like come in to like fill the void of like
man no one makes Castlevania anymore
and like so Ega breaks off from Capcom
makes like Bloodstained and I'm like
yes this scratches my fucking itch
and whenever that happens it's always
a good thing more competition more games
hey the better baby
alright voicemails what do you
say I think it's time I think it's time
yeah anybody else yeah
we've got let's let's play of course
our classic
PCP voicemail
introduction sound clip you all know
and love here it comes baby
here's the voicemails hey everybody
welcome to the voicemails
I'm so glad you made it through the
Pokemon politics Kingdom Hearts
Homestuck Undertale podcast
now this is what you're really here for
right
thank you voicemail god that's that's
it cool that's it you know
you love it man what a what a searing
take that is
yeah I feel scorched I'm roasted
I'm roasted oh by the voicemail god
again called in again I'm not gonna play it
voicemail god's complaining
about how Nate's sending mixed messages
do I send more voicemails do I send less
voicemails just send good voicemails
that's all it's not complicated
why how could it
how could it how could it be like
confused it's never about
I don't know I don't
fucking know maybe because some people
feel they need to I mean voicemail god's the only one
who does this who feels the need to like
it's oh it's like a reggae guy's slow start
like the first three voicemails those are a
throwaway go to metaphor
reggae guys is everything to me this
truly is the Pokemon
Alex Jones podcast and then
did you see the democratic debates it was
basically
tell ya that's Bernie for you in a nutshell
he's slow to go
10 reggae giggas is up on stage
okay now let's let's get serious and I'm
glad you're here for this give because
we've got shadow the hedgehog fan
calling in and presumably
he's got the hottest of takes
let's see what he has to say and
go do you guys
like shadow the hedgehog
from the sonic video game
series
oh right
that's the whole voicemail
yeah the whole answer is no
no it's yes
the game was fucking hilarious
he's like
so cool
he's so cool you see
he has a gun and sick roller skates
I've never played a sonic game in my entire life
really
play shadow the hedgehog as your first
sonic game
it's a little bit of like sonic
and knuckles
let me convince you in one sentence
shadow is absolutely a killer
that's true
that's so true
I mean killer is very much a shadow the hedgehog
I understand the man
can anyone really
understand the man
the hedgehog
you don't understand the man at all
actually I was just watching
I was just watching
a bunch of sonic adventure videos
by a guy called the black hooded gamer
I don't know why
they got recommended to me
I watched a bunch of several hour long videos
he made explaining the appeal of sonic adventure
and sonic adventure 2
I know everything about
sonic adventure
and I don't know why
I played the fucking sonic adventure 2 back in the day
it was sick
I saw a unate play
I played a bit
all I want for Christmas
in my stocking
is the
hypocrite ghost in the shell video
of shadow the hedgehog
that's all I want one day
please let it happen
oh a review of shadow the hedgehog
yes I want the deep lore
I want all the memes
I don't know the deep lore
he's got a gun that's pretty deep
he's the gun girl of shadow the hedgehog
what more do you need
sonic lore would make a good lecture
I mean that's definitely true
but are any of us qualified
you'd have to like
the comic should be their own lecture by itself
there's like a fucking 40 year history
like 40 year canon to that at this point
I mean that's a great idea
but none of us
currently have expertise
just do a shadow the hedgehog lecture
just take the one man
break down his narrative
him making out with that girl
the hedgehog lecture
or his shadow the hedgehog doing a lecture
dressed as a hedgehog
for the lecture please
which is basically just a Ryuko costume
just wear that and
have a gun instead of a sword
that works
okay next voicemail
let me see what do we got this
oh right this was like a weird one
I think this was a Welsh guy
and it was Talys in Ap Gruffind
from McNeilith
or something
I don't know it's some Welsh bullshit
we know how we feel about those
let's give him a chance here
oh yeah we hate them I guess
of course is banning McDonald's
McDonald's is a scourge on health
nationwide and it must be stopped
Clyde Cymru will not rest
until Ronald McDonald himself
is hanging in Penderean Square
for treason
I think we can all agree that this policy
is for the best
number two all education will be done
in the medium of Welsh
English speaking children must be taken
from their biological parents at a young age
and re-homed in state run
parties to revive the original town
of the Britons
half of the course really
number three a plan titled simply
get fucked New Zealand you fucking
rems
this plan is essential for the party's aims
it seeks to rename the town of
planfirepultwingelcogeirachwindrobol
and dsiliogogogog to be
even longer
we only really want to do this because
New Zealand apparently has the longest place
name in the world but I think we can do better
anyway I think I've made myself very clear
and I'm glad to have shown you the light
Diolch yn fawr
the Welsh are not people
I mean let's just say it they just don't qualify
Welsh is a cool language
I have seen
me too
I did see the Plaid Cymru
Cymraeg
a leader give a speech about
Welsh stuff
I do know what he is talking about
unfortunately there is not a Plaid Cymru
you know minister
you'll have to write him in
standing in my constituency
so I wouldn't be able to vote for them
even if I wanted to
join the party and then
just in my okay
the Welsh I mean I like this idea of like
Welsh infiltrators running in like
I mean not just all of England but like
all of Britain rather but in all of
society worldwide
to impose Welsh
cultural hegemony
or hegemony over all of society
as we found the master race
I'm convinced by their silly accent
which is very pleasing to the ear
yeah that's good thanks
guys keep it coming I love the Welsh accent
what can I say oh hey little welcome
I'm a little bit old
just the Blarney stone yeah there you go
tell it to the Blarney stone smash it
into face
of political opponent
alright here we go
next up is oh thank god okay
calling in is allegedly
the first failure of Find Purpose
November who somebody bought a shirt
at least one person so
they say that this is them
I haven't checked if anyone else has bought some
I know at least one so this could be them
so let's hear their story
okay go
I'm here to claim my title as the first
failure of Find Purpose November
I'm like 90% sure
that was the first person to buy the shirt
so it's only right
that I can also claim the title
so here's reason number one
why I'm the first failure
of Find Purpose November
it's over
it's so fucking over
you know what I do instead of like
going outside or going to school
or like working I stay inside
all day playing
motherfucking cookie clicker
and it's a good game
it's like a decent game it's like autistic
there's a ton of tiff and I'm playing
free fucking save files
because that's how I am
instead of like talking to people or like making connections
I'm just clicking those fucking
cookies
so this not voice mail is long enough
I'm gonna check back in with the other reasons
why I'm the first
failure of fucking Find
fucking Purpose November
I'm already convinced
I have a question
it sounds like they have a very clear and defined purpose
like destroy cookie clicker
like become the greatest at it
they're working every day at it
no there's no way to become the greatest
everyone who plays cookie clicker for an extended period of time
is the loser of cookie clicker
it's an endless skinner box
alright I just want to post an image
your purpose has been defined
their purpose is to play cookie clicker
it's not like they're aimless they're not wondering what to do
they know exactly what to do
counterpoint I think that this person
aspires to do better things
than cookie clicker and they feel guilt
at playing cookie clicker
so they don't consider it their purpose
they consider it a failure
now if they has given up on everything else
and only wanted to play cookie clicker
that would be perhaps a different story
but they feel avoid
I had a bit of a cookie meltdown
a few months ago
where I was just doing that
and I wasn't feeling anything
feeling depressed
but I managed to rage quit
I'm going to post an image
she will understand what this means
and that thing right there
is what caused me
like I had tried to do this three times
and this was the third failure
to get the prestige level
and I just got so mad
it unlocks
some special upgrades
that you can buy that increase
golden cookie bullshit
and if you miss it you have to restart
if you miss it you need to go for the next
10 times more
so it was like
I was so mad
I missed it by one
I was so careful
but I think
damn
I was waiting it was going to take 20 minutes
so I clicked the cookie once
like I didn't need to call
my cookie making
I clicked it once
and I think it was like a reindeer jumped in front of my click
and I got a billion cookie
well
way more than that
tiny amount
it was so upsetting
that I luckily
using the ability of gamer rage
I broke the curse
and I never want to go back
I would say that it's a bad thing
to get mad at video games
I think not
try getting mad
try failing
maybe this is the way to break the spell
well ok next voicemail
we've got a couple more here
oh ok here we go
we've got a business idea for Ben
let's hear what he has
alright this will be great
hello PCP
welcome to quick business ideas
I'm your host Jeremy Zuma
and today I've got the idea for Ben
so just put two ad spaces
on the side of samecomics.com
and put a little note on the bottom
be like
please disable that ad block
if you want to support me with my
comic disc comics
that's all
see you in the next one
great
what do you think Ben? I think he's got big ideas
just do that
stick some ads in there
and tell them to turn off ad block
what a winning proposition
let me see
how many people
I don't actively promote
stcomics.com
I've been doing stuff on webtoon
trying to build a following on webtoon
I don't know why
why not
let me see
exactly how many people
actually go to stcomics.com
200,000
that'd be nice
what's the
what's the fucking service? it's not ad sense
google analytics
google analytics that's it
when was the last time I even
google analytics
am I signed in
yes
here we go
this is
I want to look at that
I want to look at stcomics.com
on the edge of my seat
I'm dying
no this is going to be good
with anticipation I mean
oh
okay
it looks like it's getting
where do they come from
but it's getting like 20
ish users a day
okay
that's way more than I expected
holy shit
maybe people are coming back checking for updates
oh my god
in the last 28 days
exactly 420 users bro
oh shit
here we go
time to change the color of the website
to be white and green
or black and green
I'm very shocked
I kind of expected it to be like 4
um
yeah
I know for a fact
I just
I just visited bell jpe the other day
because I wanted to watch the
the finale again
because I
because I'm kind of thinking about
I'm kind of working on a
little project
is there going to be a fucking
shut the fuck up
you shut the fuck up
you were the one who made the connection
I was just asking a question
yes the answer is yes there is going to be
a dot dot dot
yeah I'm going to make a little
I'm going to make a little thing
I wanted to draw some inspiration
oh shit
and again I was
I was like oh my god this is so much work
it won't
it will not
I won't put that much work into it
no
the quality of it
is lessened by the
length and stuff
the amount of stuff I tried to put into that
I wanted it to be even longer
it's not that it's too long
I had just forgotten how many frames
there are
a lot of it is like animated animated
instead of just like
I plan on using all the shortcuts I can
and just using tweens
really that's the smart thing to do
that's what you should do
really yeah
it doesn't make much of a difference
for it to be like animated
I just I don't really
understand like flash
or like
tweens and stuff and I could learn but I just
I know how to draw frame by frame stuff
be like me and animate in Sony Vegas
and import all your images
one at a time you know move to the next frame
drop in the new clip
easy peasy
it's the best frame by frame
you still need to draw them if they're drawn
no you can stretch and skew
on the screen
yes you just rotate it
that's the way
rotation solves everything
okay let's cover our tracks
let's get out of here and no one follow
to these mysterious things we're discussing
and go to
here's a voicemail called
don't say stupid shit about VR
this episode okay
we'll see if that happens
I don't know when you guys record but I'm hoping
I can get this before you record for next week
because the new Half-Life game was just
announced
but I wanted to clear up some misconceptions
about VR in the new game
before you guys say any stupid
uninformed bullshit
first VR is not
expensive anymore you can get a windows mix
reality headset which can play the game
for under $200
it comes with motion controllers
and it's a full room scale
experience with little compromise
it does not require
high-end hardware anymore
you can play VR games
on low to mid-range hardware
now and the new Half-Life game
does require 12 gigabytes of RAM
but you can play it on a GTX
1060 or an RX 5
alright
the new game VR only is
not arbitrary and it's not
meant to sell index headsets because
as I said you can play it with windows mix reality
and there are many
many things in VR
which cannot be translated to a mouse
and keyboard and people may be
disappointed but urban environments
like in city 17 would be much better
than outdoor wide environments
than the Arctic which Half-Life 3
would take place in
don't say anything stupid or I'm gonna die
I like it
I apologize for all the stupid things I meant to say
here's my fucking hot take
Half-Life's gay and it sucks
all games are gay
wait the new one
sorry this is dumb the new game
is not Half-Life 3
it's Half-Life something
something
Half-Life's Alex is a VR
I can't remember I think I never beat
episode 2 because the last thing
that you have to do
is like a tower defense game
kind of where there's the big striders
coming and you go to drive around
in your buggy and get these bombs
and shoot the bombs up so they stick on the stride
and then shoot the bombs on the stride
the so and so device
I lost once
and I was like this is never gonna fucking
happen
you played through the entirety of
Half-Life 2
episode 1 and episode 2 and then you got to the
final boss and we're like
too hard that happens sometimes
I don't
really like first person shooters
but Half-Life is a big game
I only played it like the other
like last year
I never beat any of them
I played it when it was
not new but like
I played it in the days of the orange box
I think I played it then too
yeah
the thing that came out
is like
I haven't really seen
much of people's reactions to it
aside from Jim Sterling talking about it
and saying he has trouble
with VR a lot
so that's a problem for him accessibility
or whatever
yo let me
it's a game I don't know
this is the thing about VR games
first of all investing $200
to get into VR in general
I mean that's less than a console
it is less than a console that's true
but the reason why I'm skeptical isn't really
that I don't think I could potentially get
my money's worth in terms of
VR games
the thing is that I'm extremely suspicious
of VR games
as games that are worth my time
in general
I'm looking at this game
are games actually good
there are some games that are good
my brother has bought a VR headset
for use in developing VR games
and I've tried it
and it is
the gimmick
of being in a real place
when you come down and there you are
I played this game
which is basically just like
a
hang out
like a quest
it's very cute
and you're just sort of in a place
where there's cute animals
and you move around and you pick up things
and you can craft items
and it's very chill
normally a game like that
I would turn on
but
the fact that it is there
in front of you
you can pick up the bird that's tweeting
and you can rotate it around your hand
these controllers he has
I think it's the new Vive
it is so satisfying
just to experience
being in the 3D world
I feel like
they don't have to impress you
as much as other games do
in order to be as impressive
you know I do know what you mean
you're absolutely right
there's definitely some unique strengths that VR has
for this very trailer
that is in the description for Half-Life Alex
at 55 seconds
there's a little clip where
the guy leans over, he looks through an area
he sees a couple combine soldiers
and then what happens
the problem is I don't believe that this is going to be the game
or it's going to be as intense as it looks
he sees the soldiers
he leans over to a bookshelf
of items aside to reveal there are bullets behind it
he then like picks them up
like clearly using a VR handy
reaches over, grabs it
opens the gun, puts the bullet
in the gun, then lowers the thing
cocks it and then turns around
and shoots a combine who has just noticed him
I do not believe
that the game is
like going to
in a high-paced, satisfying way
expect you to do all those things
in such rapid succession
I think they're presenting
basically a falsehood in this trailer
because I do not believe
I saw that as well, I didn't think that
because I've used these sorts of controllers
a little bit
they're kind of bulky
and they sort of wrap around your hand
if you were trying to do that with your actual hands
you'd knock the controllers against each other
I feel like some of that must have been like an animation
like the reloading and the cocking
was just probably him pressing a button
to get it loaded
see, I felt a little bit manipulated
maybe you're right, but because it's VR
I feel like at least this trailer
is giving false hope
for the things you can do
it's this intellectual cap
of functionality
that I'm thinking about lately
I know that things are only going to get so complex
and there's a shot right after that
where a bunch of combined soldiers come up to you
and there's an animation
of these two hands going up like you're surrendering
and when I first watched that
I thought to myself like
is the game trying to make me believe
that soldiers will respond to you
but if you put your hands up in VR
they'll know you're surrendering and they won't shoot you
I feel like that's what it's like hinting
but there's no way
there's no way
there's not no way but
I don't believe that the complexity is there
the behavior patterns are going to be that
it's got to be a cutscene
the complexity, that is possible to do
but I feel like
I just don't think we're there yet
I feel like that
a thing like that is something that will happen
like 80% of the time
and sometimes you put your hands up and they don't respond
that's going to 80% failure
80% success rate
like any motion control thing
the thing is though
I'm in the position where I could
buy the game because I already have
the access to a headset
it's a pretty good headset and controllers
but I'm not interested
really in the conclusion to the Half-Life saga
because
I don't really give a shit
but
I don't think
your reservations
if you're interested in
playing this game
for learning about what happens next in Half-Life
then I don't think it's going to be a massive disappointment
like you're imagining
most trailers
show up the best bits
of all the games they're from
typically trusted to be exactly this way
or exactly that
and there's no way for you to
truly experience what it will feel like
because you don't have a headset
by watching
but by watching
like a 2D version of the thing
it won't feel the same if you watch a trailer
or if you watch someone's Let's Play
so like there's always
a bit of like gamble
in buying a VR game in that sense
I mean it looks
pretty good
I mean what's the best VR game ever made
I would bet it's significantly less complex
than what's being showed off in this trailer
people really like Superhot
that's a pretty Superhot game
and that game is way less complex than the one
reloading animation that you do
in this very trailer
and maybe it's a button but it's clearly designed
in this trailer to make it look like you're doing this stuff
in VR
at least for that reloading section
I mean is that going to
like
if the reloading is like
not as complex as you would like
are you going to like throw your controller down
like fuck this shit storm out
what I will be is mad that they did
basically false advertising
because it clearly looks like that's
I mean I know it's complicated
it's hard to tell what is being promised and what isn't
but like looking at this
my instincts first told me
that's what's being presented here
and I'm relatively savvy on these things
but I don't think it's going to be easy
to think that this is kind of an intentional sequence
maybe it's just a fucking cutscene
I guess
but then like this is a VR game
why are we showing off cutscenes
alright
you're making a lot of assumptions
I'm not saying it's definitely like this
I understand your reservations
but like I don't think
I don't think they're
like if you think that this could be
like bullshit
you're not over your eyes
you are able to be like more cynical about it
and then
I'd say realistic
you're arguing from
no no no I'm arguing like
I'm saying that you're arguing
that the trailer is false advertising
even though you've
like quote unquote seen through it
so it doesn't affect you specifically
it is like a thing saying how dare they do
false advertising
but for you you see for what it truly is
your purchasing decision is not like
you're not being manipulated
because you saw through it
there's a grey area here
like I'm aware that
they didn't like specifically say
these are the exact things that you will physically do
with your hands in the game
they simply showed off some scenes
and we can draw our own conclusions from that
does it look good to you?
I think some people
here's what I fear
I think some people will see that
and they'll think to themselves
wow I'm gonna be able to do that in VR
like look how technical and complex that is
VR sure has advanced
and I think that they will be disappointed
if they expect that
what exactly is the thing that is like supposed to be
like too complex
look at 55 seconds in this trailer here
and there's just a little animation of a guy
like doing a reload that involves several steps
of him like finding ammo
behind a thing
like shooting out the old casing
like sticking it in the gun
lowering the hammer or the barrel or whatever
and then cocking it and then turning around
and shooting a guy
like that to me looks like it's supposed to be gameplay
but I don't believe that the game
is actually going to expect to do those things
I mean it looks like it could just be an animation playing
um
I mean yeah it could be
but I don't know why is the game like
like playing itself like finding ammo for you
in a cutscene
I don't know
a container
was there a button that loots item, reloads gun
and shoots enemy for you
it doesn't claim that there is or isn't
well yeah
I just think it's a stretch to like
go straight to the false advertising thing
like you can say you want to learn
do not say that Nate is putting the big red stamp
false advertising how clear do I have to be
there is a fucking gray area
that I've been saying repeatedly
is what I'm trying to establish here
and I think we're somewhere in there
that's like no position of Nate
what do you
what do you think
I don't know what's the problem
I wish that they put at the bottom of the scene
if it's a cutscene this is a cutscene
not gameplay
I don't think it is a cutscene
I suspect I'm not wrong
about this
it just looks like a canned animation
would be
no no in terms of what I need to say
it looks like
you know when you're playing a video game
like a first person shooter you're running around
shooting and then you hit X and it does
a canned animation of reloading the gun
this is such a context specific
thing where he turns around
to a bookshelf sweeps aside items
discovers bullets
reloads gun
there might be a context specific animation
for different places
and why don't they have the context specific thing
visible on screen as we know it will be in the final game
because they always turn off UIs during gameplay
reveals and that is fucking
giving people false hope that it's going to be more
complicated and impressive than it actually
is they should present it as it's going
to be in the real game
Nate you're so close right now
to coming to a realization
about why capitalism is bad
you are like on the cusp but I know
you are you are right about
to pivot and go right in the opposite direction
but I want you to come back
I have no time for this point yet again Ben
let's move on and go over
and go over that cliff
and join me
perhaps one day
alright I mean
the thing looks like it's just well rehearsed
like a guy played
the game he pushed the things the boxes
to the side so you're saying
it is gameplay it's like high level gameplay
I'm saying it's a mixture of gameplay
like when he opens the gun
and he puts the bullets in
like him holding the gun
that looks like it's still like shaky
it's being held by somebody
and that's the gun opening
and you know
there are buttons on the controllers
so what I'm assuming happens
is that he's actually using his hand
to push the boxes out of the way
because you can just that simple physics calculation
of like you know something impacting
then when the bullets show up he probably hits
a button and it plays a canned animation
of picking up the bullets and reloading the gun
he's still holding the gun in game
but instead of like because you can't do that
with the controllers it's just a button prompt
and they animate it just like they would
any other canned reloading animation
it's literally at the other game
why in a VR I mean okay
you think that like the picking up of the bullet
and all that stuff is part of a canned animation
because like
not the picking up the bullet but the reloading the gun
I mean parts of it could be
but I mean we see how fast and smooth
he like picks up the bullet
I mean that seems a little
not what you're gonna get
he has the bullet grasped in his
fingers which is just seems like he's holding down the hold button
even the reaching out could be
a part of the animation like they could
he could just be looking at the object
and then
you hit a button and the character reaches grabs the object
and we don't know but like there's definitely
like part of it
as a canned animation but it's still technically
gameplay because it's
happening in the game when you're playing it it's just the
the prescripted animation
takes over at that point and like that's probably
a good thing because if you're in the middle of a game
even a VR game you probably
like reloading manually
one bullet at a time would be annoying
and would take a lot of your focus away from the game
like there's a level of abstraction
a level of abstraction in games is
important
this is all why I feel this is going to be disappointing
you know okay let's
we can disagree on this all day
well I mean of course it will be disappointing
because every game trailer is designed
to make the game look good
and the real game is never
looks quite like the trailer
I mean it doesn't
it never happens
perhaps we just disagree on how much
lower I think it's going to be vastly
below what's being depicted here
in terms of
I have some faith in this game
like maybe not being
incredibly amazing or living up to the
Half-Life pedigree but doing something to
move VR forward to some degree
is there some way we can put stakes on this
because I would love to bet you guys
I would love to do that
I agree that it won't be
like the trailer but I don't see why
this one in particular is going to be
particularly disappointing when
just standard procedure is to polish up
and show the best version of the thing
and the game never lives up
games never live up to their trailers
what's different about this to me
is that this seems to be marketed as
an epic real big VR game
and I'm definitely still
skeptical of those
what do you expect that to be
I expect this to be just like
a standard
Half-Life campaign
with VR controls
I mean VR controls don't even have
like good movement from what I understand
they have like weird teleporting controls
in like the latest stuff I've seen
where you have to kind of like point your guy and then you work
to a new spot
maybe that's changed I don't know
no no there's options for that
people get motion sickness from
from having the character
move like with an analog stick
so there's options
for like zipping
zapping all over the place it's also
much easier to program like that
sure
but like it's definitely
possible to have like a
you have the two controllers in your hands
and you imagine like a wee
nunchuck like your thumb has
the analog stick
and then your other fingers are free to click buttons
and rotate the stuff
so like you can move
with your left hand and hold the gun
with your right and I can see it being possible
I noticed that we don't actually see the player character
moving anywhere in the game
well we do in that thing that I've been playing
over and over where he runs over to the shelf
to get the bullets that's why I feel it's a canned animation
that's the only time there's like movement
and
my issue with this scene is that it
it felt to me like it's presented and even you guys
have said it seems like part of it seems canned
but maybe not all of it which makes me a little suspicious
of but what's wrong with a canned animation
that's just normal this is the normal
video game what's different about it is that
this is VR and that
it's I feel like there could be false
conclusions drawn which is I mean
when I first watch this I was like wow look at all the
this is literally my experience look at the amazing
thing you push over away the
stuff you pick up the bullet you load it then I was
beginning to think like wait there's
no way it's going to expect you to do these
things there has to be something else going
on so I mean I felt like I myself
am an example of
exactly the thing consumer not aware
of the limitations of hardware
yeah so here I am spreading
so how would you got how what's the complaint
here I am just stating what everyone should
know right it shouldn't be
as don't be impressed don't be impressed
like every okay
it's not
it's not going to have one for one
hand move obviously like that's
impossible nobody can do that at this point
I just
if you if your opinion of
this trailer is that wow everything I
just watch was a one-to-one interaction
in VR like
I guess that's understandable but that's
also like a complete like
fault of your interpretation because the trailer
is not implying that like you
can argue that like the medium of VR
promises that and so
you can interpret it incorrectly that way
but I don't think that that was
implicitly the idea I think it was just
hey you know Tom that's fair
it's my goal as always
my goal as always is just to keep
people with with reasonable expectation
so perhaps I've done too much on that
front but that that is my goal
for people to not be disappointed because
I'm a little suspicious of this of this project
specifically in terms of gameplay and nothing
else I don't care about the story or anything at all
well glad
I feel like do exactly what it was
warning us against doing
yeah I would never have talked about it
otherwise I just
I am a little like confused
about what
like
I generally
can't remember if the goalposts
switched a couple times
in that argument
like I feel like I agree
with your point now that you've made it at the end
but I wasn't agreeing
with it earlier the conclusion
that it is not one-to-one hand movement
is true probably
I remain in my initial position
I feel like you're advocating for a consumer
that doesn't exist someone who would
look at this and think that this is like
like perfect one-to-one
well I mean some people are gonna be gonna be
like wow
it's gonna be way worse than that
we I know this I know it's gonna be
like it's so polished in the trailer
like one-to-one we all know is impossible
but is is I don't know 50%
there even possible doubt it
what do you mean one-to-one in what
it's just the gameplay shown here
is so
like polished and good looking
and I doubt it will get even a fucking
like a tenth of the way to how things look
in this trailer I don't understand
I'm so mad like okay
are you are you just talking about the reload animation
I'm talking about we've been over this and we know
we understand that it is a canned animation
I mean I
every every fight in the game
every thing every piece of
I mean you the character doesn't
move at all so don't don't expect that
I you know if they would have shown that
if that's something that happens in the game
the the hands up don't shoot thing obviously
that's gonna be a canned animation so like how much
impressive stuff really was there why are people excited
for this I don't know it just looks like the same
show I've seen a million times in a million VR games
it's a fucking half-life game and it's in VR
like what why wouldn't if you like
half-life and or VR why wouldn't you
like this as long as we can all agree
that nothing impressive has happened here
I think we could all agree
it just looks like a fucking VR game
I mean with a lot of money I'm genuinely
confused like I feel like
the goalposts have moved like 20 times
like what are you
I can't I can't
my head around what your point is
because every time
any of us say anything you come up
with a different thing that I
I can't people in the comments
people in the comics please explain
like what was Nate initially
saying and why am I confused now
hopefully they will be
able to elucidate these things
alright well whatever let's go to the next voicemail
here we go
got like three more I think
alright this one's from
oh it's our old friend calling in it's riddle my
ass Batman with silly
songs with riddle my ass Batman
let's here we go
well this will be fun of course
go
Zack you see that new pokemon game that came
out yeah but I still need to find
a job I think to myself how
the relationship topics
Zack what do you want to be he instantly
understands I want to be the very
best like like no one ever
was what's your test they
catch them and your cause
the train them where will you travel
across the lab where you
search far and wide because
because these employers will understand
the power that's
inside
employment gotta find some
soon so true
my courage will hold me through
we'll teach you Zack you'll
teach me and I'll teach you
employment
gotta find some
soon gotta find some
soon employment
that's
there you go clock ticking
hurry
running out of social credits better earn some more
well that was a
palette cleanser when there was a
there was a follow-up message from from riddle my ass
Batman let's uh let's hear him out here we go
happy Thanksgiving everybody riddle my
ass Batman here thank you did you enjoy my
singing I know you didn't
that's why he's joking with you anyway
now I was debating on what to get you
for Christmas this year at first I thought
I'd get to a gym membership
but then I realized you'll never use
it then I thought I'd get to a girlfriend
and I realized you don't know how to use that
so instead I decided on something simple
I get to
a new voicemail series
that's right coming this Christmas a new
300 part voicemail series
wait I found the budget
a new 10 part
voicemail series
with only voicemails per episode of the
PCP for 10 weeks straight
oh my god now you have a reason to watch the
PCP again
see you Christmas everybody
same PCP time same PCP channel
that's like a PCP
or a Peter Griffin Christmas
album with riddle my ass Batman
you know
I hope it's good
he sent in another one that was too long
and not great so I didn't play it
riddle my ass Batman
so maybe just pick the best
of each of them and we can maybe pair this down a bit
I think three voicemails
of a song each time is a bit much
maybe we can do
one a week or something I don't know
but there it is
I'm looking forward to it nonetheless
these songs always bring delay
leave us wanting more
keep us wanting more riddle my ass Batman
oh incidentally we've got
one last voicemail and this is from
thems tapes
number one thems tapes
let's hear it
mysterious
it's hot
why is it so hot
I've been stuck in this desert for
months and I still can't figure
out why there is so much
sand I'm so
thirsty but no matter where I
look I can't find a single drop
of bloge to quench my
thirst how did it come
to this wow is my life
like this things were
supposed to be different after we killed
munchy but it's only gotten
worse I've been stranded
out here for months and no one has
come to help me I can't
rely on them anymore
of all of my own
but
there's one who could
help me to answer my
questions my burning snake
questions however
he is split in two
one half in prison one
half in goo what shall
I do how can he
uncover the secrets without
access to the tapes
the tapes
surely one holds the secret
to releasing his other half
from prison and making
him whole once again
this is my mission this
is my new character
hooray
them's tapes
the lost tape archive
perhaps is that
well he said one half in prison
the other half in goo
hmm how mysterious what does that mean
I don't know what that means
probably but I don't
uh
slime stuff obviously
is it goo is it Luigi
does he hold the secrets
I don't know I don't
shit someone remind me about
our own lore
maybe them's tapes number two we'll call
it next time and elucidate things for us
but otherwise
you know I'm glad
you know I'm glad he's doing good
out in the desert I'm glad he's
fine without me
a big bundle of snakes just rolling
rolling rolling along
good luck good luck out there
all alone in their many
all alone in their multitude
what's
what's a sentient
what's a sentient cluster
of hive minded snakes got to do
to find the little romance around here
a little companionship
one day good luck
alright that's it we're done with voicemails
speak pipe link people down below
leave us more voicemails they're lovely
love hearing them and
thank you appreciate that
what else we got going on
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
support the show five dollars
for all the millions of bonus episodes
including the new one game development
which many of us know
game devs dev boys
lots of lots of good stuff
and what else at tpcrastinators on twitter
updates you know the drill stuff
send things there fan art
et cetera sounds like a blast
and that's it that's the end of
this episode of the pro
procrastinators poop cast
I guess we'll see you next week and that'll
won't that be fun that be fun forever
feel the burn 2020
you heard him dev
bye
die
you