Take me to the channel for the PCP, listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream, I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
I've got CeCe, the Tails gets trolled, Brand Manager, and Tectonic Improv, YouTube, boy.
That's right, hello, I'm back, finally. All the negative is over, I've returned.
Yeah, I'm just looking at your channel right now because I've never seen it.
Oh yeah, you should check out the lecture on The Linkara, or by the top of the 4th wall is worth checking out. Other stuff too.
Play Donkey Kong 94, yeah, I agree with that.
Yeah, it's a great game.
Man, those other games that came out after, like the Mario vs Donkey Kong shit, that shit sucks.
I know that the first Mario vs Donkey Kong is a lot more like Donkey Kong 94, but I know they do like the mini, they like spun it off into its own like other gameplay style, like the mini stuff.
I only played one of those, I didn't hate it, but yeah, it's a, it's a cry.
Even when the first one, like the whole aesthetic is like messed up, like the music is like really bad, it's like MIDI, it sounds like a 1994 MIDI.
That was a coincidence, I picked a random year and it just happened to be 1994. That wasn't intentional.
I believe it.
I just mean like a Windows 95, Windows 3.0 MIDI.
Yeah, yeah.
What about Windows, what about Windows 3.11 for work groups?
Oh, what?
Windows ME?
Nobody knows about Windows 3.11 for work groups, that was what my computer had on it as a kid.
Rare, it was a rare Windows.
Actually, the first Windows my family had was Windows 3.1.
Well, mine was better by exactly .01 for work groups.
Yeah.
Yeah, those are the days.
Before we get, before we get into anything else, I want to make an announcement about the RADCON, the Road to RADCON books.
I put out the message like a week or two ago that we need, that we're sending this apple, we need people who have changed their address to update their addresses.
I'm making a deadline this weekend, the weekend that this episode comes out is going to be the deadline.
If you have not updated your address on the Kickstarter by sending us a Kickstarter message about your new address, I'm just going to send it to the old address.
So just, just don't fucking wait on that if you still got to do it.
Any other good news is those will be going out in the mail hopefully next week.
So that'll be, that'll be fun and get those fucking, get those sent out.
But speaking of physically released books and media, CC, I asked you if you wanted to be on this episode to talk about how you, in collaboration with Laserbot, just released the, the, the, I think the first volume of the official Tales Gets Trolled print edition, right?
That's big news this week.
Yeah, speaking of, I'm just, I'm going to continue talking about Tiktok improv right now and then I'll talk about that.
Yeah, I'm a side Laserbot. Okay, there's a new hotness in town. CC's going to be my brand manager from now on.
We're going to get all of my videos published on Amazon.com featuring Kindle variants.
Yeah, we'll, we'll put them on Blu-ray. But anyway, apparently I was already subscribed to you, which is perfect.
Yeah, I guess I watched, I watched some of your videos before, though I don't remember which ones.
There's a couple videos that got kind of big that could have, that could have conceivably, you could have found me.
Very funny how we were talking about, we were talking about the duck universe that one week and then like, like that, like that very week you put out that the fuck, what's the character?
No, no, it, I, I didn't put that.
I was older than that?
Yeah, it was like over a year old. I just, when you guys were talking about Maui Mallard and like couldn't figure out his name, I was like at work being like, these simpletons, they don't even know about Maui Mallard in cold shadow?
Nobody, nobody knows about Maui Mallard.
Uh, yeah, kinda. But they should.
Does he, does he even, does he even exist in like other duck stuff?
I don't think he does. I think they were like trying to set something up with that sort of character.
Like, cause like, um, cause you know, Donald Duck has like a lot, they, they always like give him like different identities.
Yeah.
And I guess Maui Mallard was this one that never really stuck, cause it's only the game.
And in um, well is it, in like other regions it's called Donald in Maui Mallard, which makes it even more confusing.
Cause he's like, it's Donald like playing the character of like an action star in a movie that is Maui Mallard.
Yeah, cause, cause like Disney would, Disney would do that stuff all the time back in the day.
Like it would be like, well, cause they've done like stuff like the Mouse Keteers and stuff, right?
So it's Mickey Mouse playing a character.
I guess it's not that crazy.
Yeah, like um, the old uh, the old um, Disney shorts where like they had Jack and the Beanstalk with like Mickey Mouse and shit.
Yeah, it's exactly like that.
Although it's a little, it's a little weird because there's more layers to it because it's Donald Duck playing a guy, a duck called Maui Mallard,
who disguises himself as a character called Cold Shadow.
So it's like, it's two, it's, it's layers upon layers of this.
So I can see why people would be confused, including myself back in the day.
I guess probably like cartoon, like animation studios like Disney or whatever,
they would make shorts where they put their characters in these like, you know, public domain, iconic roles, Jack and the Beanstalk or whatever.
And then probably at some point someone had this very meta idea of be like,
hey, what if we like kind of break the fourth wall and call attention to it and sort of establish that like, yeah, these characters are like,
they are performers that work for Disney that like they, they are, they kind of do acting sort of like they're, they're consciously acting these roles in these things.
And then that's probably why like the Muppets are like that too.
There's sort of like a parody of that kind of thing.
I don't know.
I believe, oh sorry.
The first time they made Mickey Mouse be Jack and the Beanstalk, they probably didn't even think at all about it.
But then by the time in the modern era, I think they were like, we have to, we, I don't know, there was like,
I remember when I was a kid, there was something called House of Mouse,
which was sort of like a Muppets style thing where it's like all the Disney characters hanging out at like a club and they're like,
oh, we're putting on a show or whatever.
Yeah.
So meta.
I remember that, yeah.
What I like, well, first of all, like the game, watch my review everyone.
But the game is like kind of clunky, but overall, I think it's really, it has, it has a lot of charm, like the graphics are really good.
And the music is like excellent.
And it's by a, what was it, Michael Chiquino did the soundtrack to the game and he like went on to do the fucking Lost soundtrack.
All like a lot of Pixar films.
Lost like the show?
Yeah.
Like the TV show Lost.
Mali Mallard was one of his like first things that he ever did, which is really weird.
So he moved on to bigger and better things because we all know video games are for children.
That's right.
He seems like kind of still, there's not a lot of like interviews talking about him about the game.
But you know, I think there's one where he like kind of brings it up and he seems like he's pretty proud of it.
So that's cool.
Yeah.
But please enough about me.
I want to hear about Tails gets trolled physical.
For I want, I want, I have a quick question.
You see, he wants to talk about anything other than the tails gets trolled.
This is going really.
Yeah, that's right.
It's kind of like how you, how when you're like eating dinner, you kind of want to save like the main course for later.
Sure.
Well, it's partly that, but also like people know me as the tails gets troll guy.
But you know, I'm kind of tired of talking about tails gets trolled.
Oh, sure.
Sure.
Yeah.
I could see, you know, getting kind of pigeonhole.
Well, I mean, I still, I still like tails gets trolled, but you know,
um, but it's, it's, this is a really quick question though.
But you guys were, you guys were talking about a Mali mallard on like the podcast where he had like six people, right?
I think so.
It was like Cybershell, Gamers Tavern, Tom and because I actually remember that I didn't listen to the whole thing.
Just part of it.
And I remember when you said duck stuff, it kind of sounded like you said butt stuff.
I'm sorry.
I didn't.
But yeah, I'm sorry to disappoint you.
That's a, that's the bonus episode.
That's the bonus.
Yeah.
I was going to, I was going to say something else, but I don't remember what it was.
So speaking, speaking of bonus episodes, speaking of bonus episodes, the, oh yeah, the other, the other news item is I finally got around to releasing the bonus episode, the two behind the scenes episodes and then the one other behind the scenes episode, the post show
goss talk, the one where I have been, have been talking about for like a month and a half where I ran at Cybershell for like hours.
That was, that was an epic episode.
About Trixie.
It was, it was, it's finally out.
And also I updated the Patreon, the model.
It's no, the people, people just had the playlist.
Like nobody needed to subscribe to get the playlist.
It was, it was just out there floating around.
So I killed the playlist.
The playlist is dead.
Now the way to get the bonus episodes is you have to be a patron.
You have to look at the Patreon page.
You have a master post that lists all links to all the bonus episodes are there.
It's the only way.
So I don't know whether it was one thing like that I released this bonus episode that I had hyped up, the, the, the goss one.
Or that I had, or that I finally got around to updating the, you know, the, the distribution model or whatever.
But these two things in combination, our Patreon like exploded a little bit.
When I, it jumped up like $160 or something in like, in like three days.
Which is like, that's pretty, that's pretty good.
That's pretty good.
Oh yeah, I get a couple of bucks.
So I'm excited about that.
I guess I wanted to.
So, so become a patreon.com slash the procrastinators if you want to get that stuff, like everyone does.
It's the hot new thing on the market.
It's pretty good.
They, they, they talk hot goss on it.
There is, there is hot goss.
Although it's not, I remember it as the episode where I did like four hours of just Trixie talk.
It's actually, we kind of like move back and forth.
It's probably maybe half, maybe half an hour.
I think it was longer than the actual episode.
It's close because it's, it's long.
It's long.
I was actually there and I didn't really have, I didn't really have much to say because I don't know anything about Trixie besides before she, you know,
before she, like I, like I watched her videos before she like went, did the stuff.
Went.
You know, you know what I mean.
Sure.
Yes.
So I didn't really have much to contribute, but I think part of the reason you got so much money from the patreon after you announced that is,
it kind of reminded me of how like Kiwi Farms only pays attention to you because like you're associated with Trixie,
which is kind of, kind of weird.
Right.
She's got a thread.
Yeah.
Because she's got a thread and so, she's got a thread and she doesn't like do anything anymore.
She's like almost completely retreated like from posting almost anywhere.
So they've like, there's like so starved for things to talk about that's like, they just, they talk about the PCP sometimes.
Yeah.
Because, because what else are they going to say?
They're going to talk about how Jews are going to kill all the white people.
In a different thread.
Yeah.
That's the, does Ethan Ralph have his own thread?
He must.
Ethan, Ethan Ralph not only has his own thread, he's got his whole like subforum.
He's like the biggest fucking thing on there right now.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah.
It's, I don't really get it.
But like, yeah, his thread got so big that they made, they made an entire subforum for like mini threat.
I don't know why he's so big.
He's just like some podcaster, but.
Well, he's a very large man.
So I guess he does.
I guess he is a pretty large.
They like, they like drama and I'm guessing Ethan has a lot of drama.
I don't know.
I mean, he was like, I guess there's drama guy.
And he's also like, so we're like a thousand other people.
I don't know.
I don't see.
I don't see what's so uniquely interesting about him, but you could say that about like
like everyone they obsess over.
Like I never even, I was never even like a big Chris Chan follower.
Hmm.
Right.
But I'm proud.
This is one of a kind.
Well, I'm a minority in that, obviously.
Hmm.
But anyway, I guess we can talk about the tails gets told now.
Yeah, I'm just curious, like, how did that, how did, how did getting it made go and how
has the response been?
Well, I think we talk link in the description, by the way, link in the description, Amazon
link to where you can buy the book.
Can you like it right now?
Actually, I haven't gotten around to buying one.
I'll do that right now.
Live.
I actually also have not bought one, but I am going to.
Yeah.
Give us the link.
It sold way more than I thought it would.
Oh, that's great.
Let me let me check.
Let me check how many right now.
Hold on.
It was, it was over a hundred last I checked.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
And people have been like sending me pictures of their copy and stuff.
I saw one, I saw one person posting theirs.
That's, that's good shit.
Yeah.
That's good for the hype train.
And me and laser bought are getting the money, which is good because we both have like really
shitty jobs.
Yeah.
So we need it.
I mean, I mean the thing that the nice thing about that is that like, I mean, I imagine
it will have a bunch of sales right at the beginning, but it will like, it will continue
to be around and hopefully it will continue like people will continue to, to buy it and
like it will maybe continue to like, you know, generate some sales as going on.
Like it's not like, it's not like one and done, you know, it's like people in the future
can will be able to find it and be like, Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Now I've discovered tales get trolled.
Guess I should buy the book and buy the book.
Maybe.
Yeah.
And more, more volumes are coming out.
I don't know when, but laser bought already do the covers for them.
Yeah.
He, he, he, he's really excited.
Eleazar show the cover.
Eleazar show the cover of the first episode, the first volume on the, on the screen there.
Even though laser.
There it is.
Even though laser bought left tails gets told he was really excited about the physical
edition.
Cool.
Yeah.
You got that.
From what I remember from the interview, he seemed kind of a, he seemed pretty excited
about it.
Yeah.
Oh, I changed, I changed the title on the, I think it was in, in like after an episode
we were just talking and cyber shell said that he thought that the title of the episode
was kind of bad.
Like for getting clicks and also the thumbnail is kind of like, the thumbnail is really busy
and it's hard to read.
So I changed the title.
I think I called it like laser bought speaks, but I think I changed it to like interview
with tails gets trolled creator laser bought because, because more people will know what
that means.
Yeah.
I'm probably going to change the thumbnail to be like, it's like a crowd shot, but it's
kind of hard to tell what it is.
I'm probably just, I'm probably just going to put the fucking tails face on it.
You know, that's what people want.
Yeah.
People are crazy about that tails face.
That's what, that's what you said.
I mean, that's what you did for the first one where you talked about tails gets told coming
back.
I did.
And I was like, oh, I can't do it again.
But like, no, I can totally just do it again.
Well, you mean the first one was CC because that's the, no, the first one was a cyber
show.
Yeah.
I just use it again.
PCP fans will know.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
PCP.
PCP fans are the dumbest rubes.
They're the biggest suckers on the internet.
No name.
Watch.
Yeah.
Of course.
I like it, but I don't know if it really works as a, as a YouTube thumbnail.
And it's such a shame at low resolution.
Yeah.
Classic tails gets told are, you know, this is kind of tangentially related, but I, I
love the extra artworks that laser bot did for the comic that weren't like actual pages,
but they were like just stuff that was related to tails gets told that he drew.
Let me try to find an example.
There's a bunch of them like right here.
Are you, are you saying, are you saying that there's like, there's like exclusive bonus
content in the book?
Oh, not, not in the book.
It's on the website.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, there is like one or there's like one or two bonuses in the book, but that's not
what I'm talking about here.
I'm talking about like these pictures like he drew, um, this one, this is one of my favorites.
Let me paste it in real quick.
The best challenge for a troll is troll another.
What the f...
It's a remember Kermit's backstory where he tells tales about him in the Muppets destroyed
each other by trolling each other.
I completely forgot about that, but thank you.
Now I, now I get it.
Now I understand what I'm looking at.
Yeah.
That's what the, uh, it was, they, they fell into a troll spiral.
A troll, a troll battle.
Never, never got out.
Never got out.
Many such cases.
Yeah.
Sad.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
Uh, I'm glad to hear, I'm glad to hear that it's, uh, that's moving.
That's moving copies.
Oh yeah.
There is a, that's pretty good.
Um, 32 have been, uh, shipped so far.
Oh, that's almost 200.
So then more or less than the vapors.
Um, ooh, wait, uh, vapors, one Kickstarter.
How many pledges was that?
That was, first one was, fuckin' 212 backers, but not all of them, not all of them bought
Some of them were like five dollar backers second Vapors two was three hundred and twenty nine
But I mean the price the price point of that was fifteen dollars
Whereas this is like what twenty twenty six dollars twenty nine dollars. Yeah, then twenty nine
So you so you know you you got a you got a you got to account for that
You got to account for for for total volume you got to multiply the rate at which money
They've exchanged his hands to do the total the total size of the economy
You know that's that's DOS capital right there. It's a velocity
It's all about that money velocity and soon money will be worthless. So you might as well spend it right now
Oh, I saw a great video from the Gravel Institute about how Bitcoin is a scam
Oh, I was I was gravel like Mike Gravel. I believe it's I believe it's pronounced Gravel
Yeah, it is. I think he's Mike Mike Gravel. Yeah, it is Gravel, but gravel sounds cooler and
He also knew a kid. I knew a kid in my like elementary school
I went to school through high school with a kid who was named Mike Gravel
Not not Gravel but Gravel
Wow, he's a he's
He's obsolete. Well, that's a politician. Isn't that we're like, yeah, Mike Mike Gravel was the Mike Gravel was a
I think he was a senator from Alaska
Yeah, he was like he was extremely base. Sorry if that sounds like Bernie brochure
But yeah, he was extremely, but he like just died like this year. Oh, yeah
That's right
I was gonna mention Mike Gravel or Mike Gravel also sounds better for him because he made that um
He made that ad where he like throws a rock in the water. I
Haven't seen that one. Oh that one is so fucking good. Let me try to find it
That's that haven't it just seems like he such a
Such a what Alaskan ad. I don't know something about I think this is it. This is one ad. Oh
Throw it Mike Gravel. Mike Gravel rock
I'm sure I'm I can't find the oh here we go. I found it. Okay. What is that? What is the point?
He's just staring at the camera. Yeah
What is the point? I don't know
It's a
It's a avant-garde it's postmodern shit post it sure is I'm gonna go back. Yeah, but I go for him
But he was like he was like the um the most left
Presidential candidate in 2008
Yeah, he he he ran as um
The thing they say always he ran as a gadfly to just like
Be there to like put pressure on the other like centrist candidates to be like, hey, how come you suck on all these issues?
Yeah, how come you how come you're bad and you don't want to do good things. Yeah, and of course, of course
I never heard of him two years later
Yeah
The media he really did it again in in 20s in 2020 20, right? He was there for a bit
Yeah, but he didn't he didn't get into any of the debates
Like like he did with the first time didn't he get in the one I think I think he was in no
I'm pretty sure he was in like one of the early dem dem primary only only in 2008
No, I remember like in 2020. I followed that very closely
Unfortunately, maybe wait, maybe I am thinking of old clips that I just saw this year or last year. Yeah, yeah
He was shedding he shouldn't he shed on Biden in that one too because Biden ran for president 2008
But Obama and Hillary were also there. Oh
Yeah, yeah, I think I'm thinking of like he was he was gonna run this year
But like you could because like they changed the debate rules and like he was one of the people that like didn't get to like
Be on stage or whatever. Yeah, boo
But yeah, the Grevelling since you just put out a video about how Bitcoin is a scam and that just reminds me I
sold I sold my Bitcoin
Like a like like a week or two ago and I was thinking like and then it went up a bunch and I was like damn
I missed out
I could have made I could have made a little bit of money and then like a week ago
The like the president of El Salvador declares Bitcoin like an official currency of El Salvador
He buys like 500 Bitcoin and then and for some reason that makes the price tank by like 15%
And and now it's down. I mean, it's it's up a little bit from there, but it's still down from where I bought it
So I guess I won
I guess I won in the end. Yeah, unless it goes to a hundred and then I'll lose
It's kind of a scam, but it's also like mostly just like gambling
It's it's both. It's both. Yeah, it's both of those things. Scambling. You will scam scambling
Well, I know it's a scam. Well, but it's but some people can make money on it
Oh, yeah, Crip as so crypto mining and stupid motherfucker bullshit, whatever
Yeah, it's um
You know, it's basically a Ponzi scheme where like a few a few people get rich early on and then everyone is like
Oh, I can get rich doing this and then they all jump in and then they're they're the ones that are left
Holding the bag as they say when it never actually goes anywhere. Yeah
That's that's how they try to get you. That's how they try to
Mm-hmm, and they do and it works sometimes. Yeah
Oh
You know, I was probably thinking of oh
You're gonna love this. I was thinking of fucking Tom Steyer. I was thinking of Tom Steyer and it's Steyer buyers. I'm a Steyer buyer
Yeah, the billionaire guy. I think I was thinking of him not Mike gravel
That I think was what they were trying to raise money. So Mike gravel could be in a yes
In a yeah, and that's why they had all the they had all these weird like they had all these viral tweets
Cuz his campaign was being run by a bunch of like
Yes, yeah, that was it and I think the zoomers helped found the Gravel Institute also
Yeah, yeah, I saw them like in an interview or something about it. They just like
It's Gravel Institute is awesome. It's so cool. I wish it were bigger
But I mean, you know, it'll maybe you'll get there one of their one of their videos with them
Where they talk about how America's shit that got over a million views, but that's I think that's the only that's the only one that
Got a lot of traction. I I have more views than the than the Gravel
I mean, they've got like 300k subscribers, which is like a fairly new channel. I mean, they're still growing. I hope
You know, they want to be like the leftist answer to the Prager you which you know is it is a tall order
But you know, they're they're they're making progress
Top that channel even yeah, sure
Can I say something really quick? And I'm sorry if this sounds like a bunch of like liberal cock bullshit
But okay, like even like ignoring like political views like I don't understand how anyone can take Prager you seriously
like
It's just it's it's literally it's literally just that like people
They people that already agree with them just like like like to hear it repeated
It doesn't it doesn't matter if the charts don't make any sense or that the experts are all like have like fake degrees and whatever
It's like it's it's that's that's irrelevant
And also it's just Prager or people say people say thing I agree with
Dennis Dennis Prager is also like a old-ass
like
Conserve oil Baron or something. No, he's like an old-ass. Well, he's funded by old oil Barons
But he's like an old-ass
conservative talk old-ass conservative talk radio guy from like the like the 90s and
It's like he just has all the partisan Republican
Like
Opinions like I don't know. It's just stupid
This this town is run by
Spendocrat Diamond Joe Quimby and all his hippie friends who would rather would rather play hecky sack
Lock up the homeless. That's another funny thing like oh Joe Biden is a fucking communist like oh, okay
Well, he is yeah, he's he's he's forcing vaccine mandates. He's gonna force feminizes
Any anything to the left of Ronald Reagan is a communist
Yeah, even Reagan cow pushing it. Yeah, even Reagan was a little bit
Yeah, he wanted to give I'm trying to give it. He wanted to give amnesty to illegal immigrants
That's like some fucking open borders communist shit. That's pushing it. Yeah
Obama also said he was like a
Ronald Reagan, which I agree with and of course Obama was a socialist that makes Ronald Reagan a socialist, you know, I
Guess I guess that yeah sound logic. I can't argue with it
So for a while, I thought I thought Dennis Prager was dead. Is he not dead? I
Think I wish
No, I think his brother died or something or no, there was um, they know who were like the fracking coke brothers
The coke brothers one of the yeah, one of the one of the coke brothers died
And I think I was confused for a while that like
The Prager that like Prager was one of the coke brothers, but he's not
I mean his middle name is it's his full name Dennis coke Prager. I can understand you might be confused
Wait, is that true?
Okay, it's one of those one of those lies I tell it's like
Patented tectonic improv
It's like how in the Super Mario Brothers movie their names were Mario Mario and Luigi Mario
Right Dennis Prager Luigi Prager Dennis
Coke Coke and Pepsi Prager Dennis Dennis Coke Prager and
whatever the
Coke brothers names were I forgot?
Did you know that did you know that the coke brothers ran as libertarians in the 80s? I thought that was interesting
That sounds about right. Yeah, I can't say that shocks me too much
But I don't even know anything about those. I don't know what they look like or whatever. I just know that they're bad
Yeah, bad and I don't like P one of them is dead and that's and that's funny people always said that um
The coke brothers are like the leftist boo boogeyman kind of like George source source is like a boogeyman for good service
But like I was I was looking the other day and I heard that um George source was really concerned about the profits of black rock
You know that company that was like buying like real estate and shit. I
Don't know if you
He sounds familiar sounds familiar. Yeah, and like if he's if he is black rock not like a private military contractor
No, that's black water. Oh
Okay, okay
PMC black rock is like a real estate and they're like responsible for like driving up like real estate prices and shit and
Apparently George George source was like really concerned about their profits, and I'm like that doesn't really sound like a leftist
But you know, well, he's a billionaire after I mean all has been said and done. Yeah
Exactly I'm saying what they say. Yeah, he's also Jewish. So I mean every I mean I
Mean everyone who makes everyone who has a lot of money is really concerned with who else is making a lot of money
I know it seems it seems all how is it even relevant? It seems obvious to me
But all the conservators of like oh George source is trying to he's trying to make us all like
Cucks and shit. I don't know
Sure. Well, obviously
That's what I would do if I was probably probably cuz he's so he's probably just socially liberal and
That that's what that's the only thing they care about because of it's a stupid culture. Well shit
I really hate politics. I'm gonna stop talking about it. The socially liberal financially conservative person
I was thinking about that term the other day and how I'd never hear I always hear I hear that a lot
I never hear the the financially liberal socially conservative. What would that look like?
Yeah, I
Nobody does it if that would be if that would be if you're like
If you're just like believing like traditional values, you know, you know who that would be that would be like Caleb Moppin. I
Don't know who that is
If he's like a he's sort of like a tanky guy. He's like a he's like a communist. He's fucking on Twitter
Did you look him up?
He's like a he's like a communist, but he's all
Him and like Peter Coffin are sort of friends and they are they have this stick going where they're like
They're appealing to like traditional American values the like the the the the what he called the new the nuclear family
you know
You know, they're doing this like appeal to like traditional values and their argument is like, yeah
Capitalism has like, you know has eroded our values
Capitalism is what has destroyed our culture, you know, which are returned to traditional values is possible, you know
Through to it through the adoption of socialism, right? I like I think that's what it looks like to be socially conservative and and
Ufiscally liberal. That's that's a unique people. That's a unique perspective because most people who are like pro capitalism are like dumbass boomers who just
Like had Cold War propaganda when they were like five years old. So they're all like, oh communist communism is evil
And I mean to know the to be fair a calming like
USSR and China and shit is like stupid. I don't like tank. He's either but yeah
This guy is so funny. He wrote like a bunch of a
Bunch of like a punch a bunch of people who one might consider bread tubers like all
Made fun of him. So he wrote he wrote it
So he wrote a whole book called bread tube serves imperialism
And he and he published it and it's basically just a rundown of like people in bread tube
Who he doesn't like and like why they suck?
Yeah
He wanted he wrote there were a couple bits he wrote that like Vosh has many skeletons in his closet including a lack of charisma
Um
He implied that thought slime has probably led trans kids to suicide by like having them like question their gender too much or something
Yeah, it's pretty bad. That's weird. That's weird that you like
Yeah, I spend time writing a book publishing it about you do internet people. He doesn't like
This is all in line with like the whole when Peter Coffin had their like public freak out and like banned everyone that they considered
To be bread to be including like Jenny Nicholson
This is like just totally a political people
Has Jenny Nicholson ever said anything about politics?
No, she's she's she's occasionally alluded to like some maybe vaguely culturally progressive things
But she's not like political, you know, I think she she thinks that like racism is bad
You know like if that's if that's that sounds like some global homo Jewish shit
True true true
Um, anyway, oh
Speaking of which did you hear about the controversy? Well, it's not really controversy except for 4chan dumbasses
The game no more heroes 3. There's a you can get a sweatshirt that says fuck fuck racism
Yes, and no people on 4chan got really we can't have that shit
Yeah, we can't have that shit in a video game, you know cuz really cuz really it says fuck racism
Yeah, okay, and you know
anti-racism is the code word for anti-white
This this is I see this is um, this is just like when when the quartering was like
What did he someone said like fuck Hitler?
He was like hey, and the good you want to know the quarter was like. Oh, it was like some it was Michael Chiquino
You're shitting. I'm not joking. It was Michael. You're shitting me. I'm not joking. He's here. I'm not joking
I don't know who that is. It's that's the guy who did the Maui Mallard. It's Maui Mallard guy. Oh my god
That can't be true. Oh my god, 100% true 100% true
Holy fun the tweet shit find the tweet
Yeah, when someone was like Hitler was bad and and the quartering was like, oh really this is there and this now
Yeah, there we have it. I mean to play devil's advocate. This is this is the Chiquino cast
This is the Chiquino cast. I mean to play to play devil's advocate. Maybe
quartering meant why no, he didn't really mean this but
Maybe yikes, maybe he meant like oh you're saying Hitler is bad
Well, obviously like Hitler is bad. You're just virtual signaling or something
But I was a big fan of his music, but I yikes didn't realize he wasn't he didn't like Hitler. Sorry about that everyone
No, I know I know I know what he means. I know he's like
This is just virtue signaling, but like that's fucking stupid all on its own, right? Yeah, that's an it's an idiot opinion for idiots
Yeah, sure Michael Chiquino's Jewish also also if uh if Michael said like fuck Stalin or something the quartering would be like
Oh my god, based a hundred Gorillian dead
it
true the
It's that that meme of the the soy face that is like
place
Unimpressed place Japan soy face. Oh
You know, yeah that one he gets excited. Yeah, it would be that meme
Oh, never mind. Hey guys. I got a great idea. Oh, by the way, let's draw the quartering as a soy face
Let's draw him as soy by the way that I'll show that place. Japan meme is unironically me
I'm not a shame to admit it
Yeah, yeah, that's why it came in yeah it is
True this there was a nugget of truth in there and it spoke to people
They saw themselves in it like a mirror. Yeah
That's why I resonate. Is that how you is that how you say this name Chiquino Chiquino. Yeah, ju-ju-ju-ju-quino
I guess that makes sense. Yeah, I'm I'm pretty sure that's how you say it
I remember looking it up. Is he is he really Jewish because that sounds Italian or something? No, he's not he's not Jewish
He's telling okay. I was gonna say I mean, I guess I guess you could be both. Yeah
There are there are black Jews and
European Jews and I know that there are black Jews because I've seen because I've seen the the rabbi's cat and
And I know all that move that in it in that movie
They go to they travel into the deepest part of Africa to find the share home of the shared
Homeland of all blacks and Jews and the people that live there are like 12 feet tall and they're like so dark that they're like blue
And there's these judge these these black giants that just have you know, what's the word a bar mitzvahs and stuff and
The cat tries to get bar mitzvah to become a
Real boy, but they won't do it
Because the talking cat is is is some witchcraft or something
Are you talking about are you talking about an avatar because you mentioned like tall blue people
No, I'm talking about the rabbi's cat. It's like a Belgian movie
Is it like live I think live action
No, it's animated. Yeah, I think I think YMS recommended it in one of his like like best of some year
Ronda, I think then talked about on the body only the only it has like a weird. I probably did
Huh, doesn't it have like a really weird ending? Yeah, it's what I just said they go to the shared
Homeland of all blacks and Jews and they find they get chased out by these giants who are like no no fucking no fucking foreigners allowed get out
Yeah, I always imagine this looked like the thief in the collar, but I actually don't know a little bit
Kind of rest
Rest in peace. It has that it has that it has that Lynn Claire like sort of tin tin. Yeah, like a
sort of
What's that like a Le Lascar kind of like French? Oh my god look about it. I never knew this is from 2012
I thought this was like from the 80s
Hmm
No, it's I mean it if it was one of YMS's yearly picks so it couldn't have been that yeah
Yeah, he's only done those as far back as like 2007. Okay. Yeah, I'm glad I'm glad I'm glad people are still making true art in the
in the medium of animation I
Wish I was something once in a while. I wish animation was more respected
I
Think it's a little too respected. Yeah, I think I think the pendulum has swung too hard in the other direction
Yeah, well depending on the
Depending on the target I'm kind of a centrist about animation
I'm kind of a centrist about animation
I kind of think both sides are bad the people that think it's a valid art form and the people that think it don't I think we should compromise
Yeah, you're right
You've yeah, you've convinced me
True
What were we talking about tails get strolled the Mike Jews Mike Shiano being Jewish, okay
What did I say Geano, I think Mike Geano sure
What's so what else is up I should have I
No, I would have talked last time about how I moved into my new apartment and how it sucks and my landlies sucks
And I hate this fucking place and I've been ripped off. I've been fucking I've been fucking scammed
Oh, no for this place. It's dog shit. Yeah, it's fucking dog shit first months rent and last month's rent and a full month's security
Rent security deposit and a $200 like application fee just to get in here and the place is fucking dog shit
Yeah kitchen is foul
Kitchen is gross. There's the cabinet just has like a boiler in it
The cabinet is just a boiler. They can't even put shit in there
Floor is dirty crack paints peeling windows are fucking shit
There's like iron bars over my windows that I had to get like them the product that the property manager to take off
So that I could put my my air conditioner in the window
Oh, I guess I'm not gonna need that for much longer because it's September now. It's fine
Conditioner out today fucking
Rats in the parking lot. I hear I hear rats squeaking out in the parking lot right out my window all the time
I mean, I guess that's not the worst thing, but it's just emblematic. It's just emblematic of the kind
I usually have a location. Oh, sorry the location amazing the location amazing everything else about the place dog shit
Maybe and I'm maybe yearly and large to get a real job
I
Want to fucking I want to say hey, I'm gonna leave and I'm gonna like hey give me my fight
I'll never get my security deposit back. I'm down like a fat
I've down like a thousand dollars because I'm definitely losing that security deposit
And I'm definitely losing that and that $200 that fucking it was just desperate
It was because I left my house hundreds for the last minute and I was desperate and I was like well
I need something so I took the deal. I was like fine $200 the application fee
I guess I got to pay it here. You go and now I've paid it and it's all gone and
And what I'm when what do I have left?
nothing
I'm ruined
I'm truly sorry. Yeah, I
Hate it. I hate it. Are you living but I mean
Well, I mean it's a unit with other rooms that other people live in okay
So I mean technically no, but like I don't I don't like interact with them that much. Yeah
Yeah, so, you know, I got my own room. I usually I usually have cats in my
Parking lot rather than rats. Oh
I would try I'd like to trade please and it's like it doesn't even matter where I lived
I lived in both California and Arizona and there was always cats in the
parking lot for some reason
No, just just rats just rats
Yeah, maybe you can give then one of the cats and leave it outside and the rat problem
Yeah, kind of take care of itself. All we need is one cat and it'll catch two mice and then it will multiply into two cats
Yeah, and then
That's that's how ecology works. Yeah
Uh
Fucking some fucking like frat house like right across right across the parking lot behind me
They're they're blast in there. They're blast in their tunes
Oh, you not even just on week not even just on weekends. Just whenever they feel like you should go and hang you should go and hang out with them. I
They'll never they'd never accept me. I'm too square. Yeah, I
Am much too square for that. I feel like I can't relate to the zoomers
They weren't even alive. They weren't even alive when 9-11 happened. Oh, by the way, happy 9-11
Happy 9-11. Yeah as of yesterday. Yeah, the last episode was late because we wanted to delay to release on 9-11
by the way to commemorate and we like brave
Mujahideen fighters
I didn't say that
We could get into a whole thing about 9-11. I have so many thoughts about it
Um
About I'm not gonna I'm not I'm not gonna go into it. I'll just go into the short version, which is
You know, everything has gotten worse since then
And uh, the world is going to shit and we're all gonna be fucked
That's all I'm gonna say about it
Sure
Thank you
What was I talking about um my fucking all these fucking kids these fucking kids in my in my parking lot with their rap music
And they're and they're and do a dance in the cha-cha or whatever sick. There should be a law against it
Uh, you need to show you need to show fans of rap music real music like anime openings
Yeah, video game music. Yeah, they have these. Yeah, they have these like giant parties and they're in their fenced off backyard
It sounds like there's like a hundred people back there just like yelling
Don't knock knock. Excuse me neighbors. I couldn't help but notice you were listening to uh some quite deplorable tunes
Perhaps you'd like to listen to the delta room chapter one soundtrack
I wonder I wonder if I went over there and I was just like, hey, let me come in
I wonder if they'd be like, okay, or if they'd be like, no, or if it'd be like, yeah pay like $15 you can come in
Describe like a six pack and then fill you in. Yeah, maybe you know, I don't know
There was a back before covid um
Someone in my work parking lot after work was blasting um megalovania from their car
Oh, I played I was playing I was playing dance not actually dance sense revolution, but a knockoff dance sense revolution
I went to cracks house
Yesterday and we played dance dance revolution
And he had a pack that had megalovania in it, but we didn't play it. I didn't play because it was too embarrassing
It might have been step mania. I don't even remember it's funny
I went to I went to a store yesterday and they actually had one of those like metal ddr mats for sale
Like I think it was like a hundred bucks or something. It was used
I was like pretty good. I don't know who brought that in and you know, that would be cool and all
But I I don't have the room for that and I don't play the game
So I just ignored it crack just had crack had the soft pad
But he had it like he had it like screwed into like a piece of plywood
And then he he had like holds in his floor for screwing the plywood to the floor like bolt it down
He sounds like a really dedicated ddr fan
And yet he rolled by one of those metal mats with the with the handle that you hold on to
Yeah, I guess why not why not just go all the way?
He's a little DIY. I guess they're heavy. You might as well buy a whole ass arcade machine
If you're gonna go that far
Yeah, true
No, I went to his uh, I went to the house that he's been uh renovating and posting the twitter thread about place is crazy
Place is awesome. The house rules. He had we had him on a few weeks ago to talk about home ownership
Crack's house is fucking sick. It's like one of the coolest houses. I've ever been in. I've seen the pictures
Crack is uh
So if you don't know crack if you don't know crack then
dev of uh endless war
Yes, yes
and friend of friend of the show and and the
Basically the guy who made endless war
Originally, yeah, he's cool. Cool guy. Yeah. Yeah, this house seems pretty cool apart from the leaky roof
Does he wasn't leaking when I was there? Does he does he actually own the house?
Yeah, he likes well, he's got him. Well, he's got a mortgage. He's got a mortgage, but yeah, he he he owns it
Yeah, in that sort of way
He's got uh, he's got like he works for like microsoft or some shit
He does he does. I I sort of work for microsoft
I work for a company that contracts with microsoft
Hmm
Do you do software stuff? Yeah
Hmm, okay
quality assurance
Yeah, I think I think I've known I think I've known at least one other person who did who had quality assurance with some
Some software company
Yeah, what a what a
What a what a fields
Um, you know, what's weird? I was talking about this
Uh, munchy another
Former member friend of the show. I'm sorry. Who's that? I I I remember him from the uh
Tgt lecture. Sure. What would you would you say tech? Who's that?
Who's that? Nobody. Nobody nobody at all. Uh, but he's doing he's doing um
He was doing art school. He was going to art school, but he's shifted gears and he's doing a computer science this year
He switched schools switched majors and now he's doing computer science
That's crazy
Kind of surprising
Good luck to him. Yeah, good luck to him. Yeah, I heard he I heard he left the internet to focus on that
He left the internet something else and as and as we all know you can't you can't go to school and be on the internet
Well, he he left the fandom of the internet and uh, yeah, who knows who knows if uh, if the fandom the internet will ever go back, you know
He he would have to he would have to beg forgiveness at this point. He would have to grovel
You know, you have to mic grovel
And it it might be harder nowadays, but I've actually known people who have left the internet
It might be yeah, it might be harder. Like I said these days
Go off the grid. I mean, I guess you can do it
I guess you you can it's probably easier if you just never uh join the internet to begin with like, uh
Like bill water. Yeah, you have to whatever
You have to go through the initiation process to join the internet
Uh, I mean the internet is like it's where you get fucking it's where information is. I don't know. I mean
You you if you if you're okay with just being like completely disconnected with from society then sure you can do it anything you want
You can just completely unplug and not read newspapers and not talk to anyone and then sure. Yeah
No problem, but like
Sucks. I don't know who wants to do that. I love I love when the internet was like first coming out or whatever
um
They
Had all those like videos explaining it that were like really corny and they called it like the information super highway and shit like that
I love the information super highway. That's such a good name and remember remember when commercials had aol keywords in them
I remember um, yeah, I was never clear on what those did
me neither
But they they would they would say the url and they would also say the aol keyword. I'm like, what the fuck is that?
I remember the no nobody even knows what aol is anymore for like Netscape and net zero
But this wasn't like when they were brand new
This was when they were trying to rebrand and be cool
Because you know, I'm I was born in 97. So I don't have I don't I don't know a lot of 90 shit
I know like early 2000s crap. I remember
Like I just like one of these ads for I think it was net zero where there's like a bunch of these cool
yuppies just hanging out on their uh in their new york apartment
Like uh and like a skyscraper just talking about how fucking sick net zero is and how they're like drinking champagne
It's like you need to be a part of this
and uh
Yeah, you know, what's really sad
What's that?
I don't even think like when like I used to think of people born in like the late 90s as little kids
But I don't even think that anymore in 24 because we've already we've already got the generation alpha generation alpha is already being born
Yeah, exactly, but also because most
Most people online that I come across are like born in like 2002 and like that's really like little kid shit. Yeah
is that like in the in
I mean like I mean, I guess probably most of the people that I see on twitter are like, you know
They're people that follow the pcp. So maybe they're probably like mid
Mid 20s at the oldest to down to like, you know late teens
At the youngest mostly wasn't there someone who called a few weeks ago that was like 14
Yeah, yeah, I was talking to I was talking to kazzie about it and they were like they were like
14 or something when they started watching like uh, uh, the the horse the horse cast or whatever
Oh, that's weird. So they're
Yeah, at least at least maybe 16. I don't know at least they were in the target audience for my little pony
The target demographic. Yeah, I guess so well
Even even like 14 to 16 would be a little too old
But I mean, of course, there's the whole brony thing. So
That's like an exception
One time uh
The only my little pony I know about is like the one my sister watched when she was a kid
I like the eight from like the 80s. So I said the
Oh, sorry go ahead. No, no, I you can finish. I have an unrelated point
Oh, so, um one time in your discord. I said the original my little pony is better than friendship is magic and it was really controversial
um, okay, I got a comment on my
uh, the the the
It was one of the two lectures the other day the the the chris chan lectures and someone was like, uh, you said that chris wasn't into
Uh, uh, my little pony and that chris got into my little pony late
But actually chris was drawing my little pony even back in the pre sonichu era in the pre timeskik era
Because megan, you know, I actually remember that I actually remember that I wrote okay
I remember it too
But I hate this person because they're deliberately misunderstanding me because I was specifically talking about the brony fandom
Which is not pre gen four mlp old mlp fans are not bronies
It's a gen four fandom is the and chris was like really late to get into brony
Yes, she liked the old my little pony for a bit because megan liked it, but that doesn't count
That wasn't what I was talking about. I was furious. I'm gonna be furious of this individual
I'm gonna side with you on this one because I get a lot of comments that are uh
Where people will people will say things that I obviously know about if you've seen the video
Maybe I don't say them outright
But just like the way I talk about something should at least imply that yes, I know don't worry ever
I know
Yeah, you don't have to tell me I know the first the first sonichu lecture
The thing that everyone wanted to correct me on was that I said chris worked at burger king when in fact
Everyone knows everybody knows she worked at wendy's and she got fired from wendy's
For doing a donald duck impression
Yeah, well, that's funny. That's pretty that's pretty awesome
Everyone comments to tell me i'm wrong about that and fair enough
So I corrected that one in the first the first few minutes of this of the second one
But then in this one the one that I got wrong that everyone tells me is that I was not aware
That the reason chris threw that chapter about rosa chu getting fat was because like some girl that chris was talking to
Had like a fat fetish and so she wrote this like this fat
Plotline in to like please that girlfriend
I I I had heard about that, but I had completely forgotten about it. So like that one's true
That's like, yeah fair criticism. I didn't mention that one
But other than that other than that, I think I was pretty good and I definitely
Was not wrong about the brony thing
She was not drawing. She was not like drawing pony stuff until like
After the peak
Until after t-bap was already over
What's t-bap?
How does one explain how does one even begin to explain t-bap?
Uh fencing and best guy ever used to have a pony show where they reviewed uh episodes of my little pony together among other things
t-bap
t-bap is more to the point t-bap
Half of t-bap is the protagonist of the up-and-coming video game masterpiece
uh phantoms revenge
Now now ben is uh, is phantoms revenge being done with zero crunch by its uh, its employees working on it?
I it is it is doing done with 100% crunch
What I am only crunching
Uh, uh, uh, man, I was uh, I picked out music
I picked out I picked out music for the game. I'm stealing music from front mission
Front mission gun hazard. I'm going with the soundtrack to that because it has like a sci-fi
I think it's pretty cool sort of aesthetic too. That's I never is that is that the one for for snes or
Yes, was it one of the later ones? I played no, it's it's an snes one
I played front mission three on the playstation when I was young. Uh, I'd never played the front mission gun hazard
It was on this nest
It could play for the gun hazard like a little bit on an emulator
The first few didn't come out in the us from what I remember. Yeah. Yeah
I mean, it's not a game that I like hear anyone talk about so I'm kind of like
Oh, people aren't even going to recognize these these these tracks. Is it um, you know, is it is front mission gun hazard?
It's like a side scrolling game
You're like you control a mech and you can like level up its stats and stuff to to be honest
I don't even know what kind of game it is. I haven't seen any gameplay front mission three is a like
Tactical rpg like a grid-based tactics game. Yeah, I think I played this most
Yeah, most of most of the ones in the series are like that
Yeah, which was my favorite kind of game when I was in like high school
I played like every single one like get my hands on like find
Final fantasy tactics
Like final fantasy tactics of van van van garden
Was it me vandal hearts? No vandal hearts is the one I'm thinking of uh, uh
Oh van van and vanguard bandits another one about piloting a mech. Um, the tactics ogre
Let us clean together
Huh tactics ogre let us clean together. I think that's what the subtitle is for that one
You know, I never I didn't actually play tactics ogre. I just know it's another part of that of that genre genre
genre
What was I talking about? Um, oh fandoms revenge
Oh, I've been I've been putting I've been putting a lot of finishing touches on it lately
I've been making a lot of like I've been trying. I've been beautifying it
I've been making lots of like fancy game objects that have like little effects that have like bubbling effects and little little motion effects
And I've been making like background details to make
Every room in the game look like a little different and distinct and stuff and I'm and I'm just kind of
Uh, uh, I've been I've been working. I've been going really hard lately
Like it feels like I'm in the final stretch and now I'm like
I'm focused. I'm laser focusing in on it. It's it's coming together. It's already a masterpiece
It's not even done, but it's already a masterpiece even if it's current state by the time it's finished
It'll be the greatest thing ever made by a human
Uh, I'm I'm very proud of you my son. It's so cool
I you can I can play I can basically play through
most of the game currently it just needs like
It just needs it needs it needs bug squashed and it needs um, and it needs like, you know
Polish and it needs like backgrounds fixed and like and a little more variety
In in the environments and and and the final boss needs to be finished
How how long how long is it going to be?
I think uh
Well as you're uh as as one of your um as one of your
Uh benefactors you will release this game. Uh before quarter four earnings are uh
Are up so
Make sure to get that out before then uh do whatever you need to do time to crunch time to crunch time
Time to crunch. We got it. We got to hit our we got to hit our quarterly goals
Uh, uh, just make sure make sure you don't get a job at Activision
A playthrough
I think
I think my goal will be that you can probably beat it in maybe like a couple hours
Of like trial and error and like oh, maybe like two hours of like
Of trial and error figuring it out. I mean
The the
Like if you know if you know exactly what you're doing, I think you could probably beat it in like five minutes
um, but you know the the real game is like figuring out how to
survive and and win I mean the
The first game I made when I was like 16 was kind of like that
The alpha version that I put out on patreon a few months ago was
Very very hard. I think it was too hard only like six people beat it
And those people took like five hours to beat it or or longer because it was just so much like trial and error
They had to find like the exact right combination of of of moves that like would not would result in in not death
And they were like there was like zero room for error at all
So I've I've made it a little I've added some more like commands and some more like options that make it a little less punishing and a little more like
You can you have you have ways to like sort of
You have moments in the game where you can kind of like take a breather and sort of set yourself up for what you want to do next
It's not like
The in the alpha version you would beat a level and it would immediately put you into the next level
And if you weren't like set up if you haven't like planned on exactly what state you wanted your game to be in
You would get there and you'd be like it's already too late. I've already fucked up
It's like uh like those old sierra adventure games where you can make like yeah, I was I was good. I was I was gonna fuck you six hours in
Yeah, I was gonna I was gonna mention those. It's like you need to know the exact thing to do
Like in those old adventure games. Yeah, the the alpha version is you you literally to the way that you
Could beat it is first you had to figure out like okay
What do I need to do to survive and then you would eventually figure out? Ah, okay
This is the goal and then you'd be like, okay, but to actually accomplish that goal
Okay, I I have to basically I just have to like
Trial and error over and over again and just try like slightly different strategies until I happen to find the one
That works and and means and and you have to and you have to execute it perfectly
And if you miss click any button at any point your strategy will be thrown off
You'll take damage that you can't afford to have taken and you'll be like well, there's no way I can win now
I gotta start over
Uh, very funny. I played another I played another game like that recently a few months ago
It's a wonder boy in monster lands
There is uh, no, I'm thinking of a boy in his blob
Yeah, this is okay. What's that?
This is like a this is like an arcade game
But they tried to do like rpg elements in it, but it's also like level level based
So like if you miss an upgrade like for example, I missed a sword upgrade
So once I got to a certain level it was like real impossible to beat the boss
So it's like I well by fucked up. So I guess I have to start the game over and get the sword
I'm adding I added a
okay because um
I added a command to phantom's revenge called scout
Which lets you look before you go to the next room you can use the scout command and it will tell you
How many enemies are at are like are going to be waiting for you in the next room
So like if you know what you're doing you can use that information and be like, oh, okay
Then I should I should I should set up like this
I should I should make sure that like this thing is is doing this thing before I go otherwise. I'll I'll die
uh
And that's me being very generous. I'm a generous developer
Uh, I'm I'm making dark souls here. You can beat it on your first try. You just have to pay attention to your environment
You know you just have to you just have to be aware of your surroundings
And you never have to take any damage. That's not true
Yeah, uh
the
Okay
Enough of me gushing about my own video game
Uh
It's gonna be it's gonna be great though. It's gonna be so get excited everyone. Yeah, it's so fucking good. It's so fucking hype
Are you gonna release on like itch and steam or whatever? I will put it on. Well, I don't think I'm gonna put it on steam
Okay, I wasn't I don't even know if you can put it on steam
I wasn't planning to sell it for money. I was just gonna put it on. I mean I'm gonna put it on my website
I'm gonna put it on itch. I guess I'll probably put it on new grounds because why not
Yeah, I've never had pretty well on new grounds
What can you Tom's game? Oh, yeah, Tom's yeah, I I've never uploaded anything to new grounds
So I don't even know how it works, but uh, yeah, I guess can you actually like
Export like a game maker games to html
Yeah, yeah, that's exactly what you do. Oh, wow
I made I made one before I made a much simpler one for the champion my other comic a few years ago
And yeah, it's just it's an html
It's just goes it's just embedded in my in a page of my website
Man, I was uh, I was more active on new grounds in the old days when all you had was flash
Yeah, you could you could only make flash games
I saw
I was
That's just oh, I think
I mentioned this because this was you told me about this the interview the the the thing where laser bot was on the
Was on the the panel and he barely fucking got in at all until the very end. I was so
The fact that it was it was the clock gang the clock gang from like the old new grounds days
It's like I can't I can't believe the clock gang is still a thing even at the time
I remember when it was contemporary. I remember like being like baffled like what is the deal with this clock?
Like what is the point? What are these people thinking? Why are they doing this?
I think I I think it started with strawberry clock. He made a movie called B
And it was just a red B on a white background and like people like ironically liked it
I see
and
I don't know like the whole history of it, but it started, you know, I guess I guess I'm jealous
I guess I'm jealous that they were a bunch of like internet content creators
Who formed who formed a tight-knit click?
And then they fucking they web they weathered the storm together
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, they didn't they didn't crack under pressure
And I'll and I'll turn on one another
And I'll quit and I'll rage quit the podcast and become and become bitter enemies
Yeah, like like kermit and the muppets didn't like it. Yes, like that's who I was thinking of. Yes, like kermit and the muppets
Nobody else
No just kermit and the muppets
The the the the great tragedy of the hubris everything that's ever happened in real life is also applicable
details gets trolled so
That's how it goes
That is how it goes
I would I would have to agree. I would have to agree with you on that
Uh
I gotta say, um
I'm I'm really impressed with what gibb did because
She actually had to like print out the books herself and like send them out manually
Which is probably yeah, you did that too and I did that too
Yeah, you did that too. Hey, I'm right. Hey, praise me
No, no, I just I you're impressed with me. I've done that like three times. I'm way better. I'm way better than that
No, okay. No, you're not. Anyway, um
Uh, I just I just mentioned gibb because we were talking about the Kickstarter earlier. Yeah, but um
Yeah, it's a lot harder than what I did
Basically, all you have to do is just upload the um pdf and they like print it out
for you
Yeah, I've never done a um, I've never done a uh an amazon
The the the the downside is that they take like part of the money
Obviously, of course
Well, I guess you would have to do if you printed it yourself too, you'd have to pay for a printing cost
I'm yeah, I I'm sure I'm sure that it's cheaper and more efficient to like to print yourself in like large batches
Because you know
Amazon they're they're print on demand. So they don't they don't have like
Backlog, right? You don't have to pay upfront to have to have like, you know, 500 copies produced to be sold later
But you know with that with that I'm sure it comes an increase like, you know percentage that they take
Yeah for that serve for that service, right, which is which is part of the reason it's 30 dollars because uh,
sure
um
We wanted to make a profit from it. So we had to increase the price
Yeah, I mean absolutely
um, and if you combine the shipping costs and the um
If you combine the shipping cost and the amount that amazon takes we couldn't sell it for like cheaper than like 20 dollars
That's like that's like the the profit line
Yeah, that's like the minimum we could sell it for
Oh, yeah
Yeah, and they wanted me to use like the like I wanted to make the book as big as possible
But they if you do that they also like make you like use the more expensive paper
Which also increased the price. So, yeah
I see I see. Yeah, it's
I mean, I'm sure amazon is
a bitch and uh, you know
It's set up to extract as much surplus value as they possibly can
Yeah, thanks. Jeff. Thanks. Jeff Bezos, but uh, thanks
Some some people some people complained about the price, but I made a poll asking
Would you rather have a a smaller book with worse quality that's cheaper or a more expensive book that's better quality
And most people said the latter. So I was like, oh, okay, whatever. Yeah, I think I would agree with that
What are the dimensions of the book?
Yeah
Like, uh, what's the how big is it?
Hang on. Let me see if it says it's it says on the amazon. It's like
Going from memory. It's like, oh
Eight eight eight eight and a half by about like 11 and a half. That's pretty big
Yeah, that is pretty big. That's bigger. I was picturing like a
Like a digest like a paper bag. Yeah. Yeah, I was I was picturing like digest size. Okay. That's pretty that's bigger than I thought then
Yeah
That's the biggest I could make it and if if I made it smaller
I'd have to like cut up the panels and like rearrange them
Oh, yeah
Because because they're like because the original tales gets told pages are like vertically long
Sure. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah
I um, I was thinking, um, wait
Fuck uh, fuck. Oh, no. What was I thinking?
What were we just talking about? Oh, no
No, uh
Book sizes book sizes book sizes
book sizes
Book sizes printing page page sizes
rearrange
money
Amazon it's gone. It's gone
What a shame
It was gonna be really good
Oh, yeah, and people are gonna criticize or
probably nobody
Oh, what what is it? I I remembered I remembered I was I was gonna say that like no matter what price point you price that
Somebody's gonna complain about like, oh, it's too expensive. But oh, yeah. Well, I don't I don't care about that
You got you got it, you know, you got to price it how you got to price it and like it's largely not up to you
How much it costs to get something made, right? Like it is what it is
I know that's all I was gonna say. I was also gonna say if like, uh
Uh, right wing people would probably say to me. Oh, you're you're like you're like on the left
But like you use amazon. Isn't that like hypocritical?
And they're right. Yeah, it is but I don't care
I have to I have to make a deal with the devil to make tales get told become a reality
That's what I have. No, but if you do that, then you won't get angel deals later in the run
I don't care
Yeah, you die now. Why are you doing it's a it's a it's a trap. It's a trap angel deals better
You want those soul hearts the angel deals are better now ever since uh repentance or whatever
Angel deals were good even back in the day. They were good, but they weren't good enough, you know
Like it's it's better because devil deal items were just so good
Yeah
I think I just liked them better. I just I like I thought they were cooler
I I think they're cooler too because you know, you got to wait a little longer for them and
A lot of like the higher tier items like godhead and sacred heart are just they're just cooler to me than brimstone and like
Yeah, it might just be that I'm more more familiar with the devil items. So I'm coming up brimstone. Ah, I get it
It's like I get I think I get what this item's all about
Oh
Yeah, I I totally agree with whatever you said
We're talking about binding of isaac. Yeah. Oh, I I think I figured it was something like that
I think I I
I figured you were referencing some like that was the only like video game
I could think of would like heaven and hell shit. So I was like, yeah, they're probably well. What about uh guilty gear
Heaven or hell let's rock. Yeah
Yeah, but but you don't buy items in that
That's true. You buy the one thing. It's missing characters
for dlc
Do you I don't know. No
I hope not. I know there's a season pass. There's always a season pass is the fighting game
I don't even know what that means
You know, it's like post launch like the game comes out and they add new characters and you paid for them
Oh and season pass is like you get whatever they release for the season. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, yeah, we uh life is hell
Uh, yeah, it's the common. It's the common state of games these days. Whatever
It's what it is
Well, well darn, so uh, what will what post launch content will uh will phantoms revenge have been?
Uh
Fucking hell. I'll add a I'll add a you should give them a Santa hat wait
Wait, what if I added what what if I added skins where you could where you could swap phantoms is different ponies like you could play as keg
Ooh, like you could play as that should be like honestly. This would be like honestly
It wouldn't even be that hard
I could I could probably add that in like a day if I wanted to like care. Yeah, like a hard mode character select
Yeah keg mode
You know what?
It wouldn't even be hard. It wouldn't even be hard
There you go. Oh, you heard your first books
Is this is this a brony game? It is no
It's it's a brony game. That's why it's that's why it's not a brony game grounds people are gonna get mad at him
tbap is like tbap is like a pony show for anti-bronies
What's an anti-brony I'm like a fallen brony like I'm like I took the devil deal. I'm like a black
Yes, I'm like a blaggard. I'm like I'm like I'm like a I'm like a a blaggard to the bronies paladin
Yeah, well, you that's how you say yeah, it is actually I only found out recently that you're supposed to pronounce black
When I know that like the actual english word is pronounced blaggard
But the I'm not sure if the d&d class is meant to be pronounced like the word or if it's
If it's distinct enough as its own thing that you're just supposed to say black guard
I think you can do either or but I know that in fifth edition are technically isn't a black guard or a blaggard
They're actually called like the uh the oath breaker
And I mean tomato tomorrow. Yeah, it's it's all the same difference
It's technically not even supposed to be a player class because it's in the dmg, but you know people still play it
I mean same with same with third edition. Yeah
Yeah, they still want people playing dark knights or whatever you want to call them. No
No, we can't have that
Yeah, we can't we can't have that
That sounds like a very bad idea. What are we talking about? Um, oh
Kegmo
Honestly the the the the like all my assets are like
Like swapping out sprites is like the easiest part
Making making sprites and swapping them out is the easiest part of development. It's not hard. What's hard
Is just fucking is just having a bug and hunting for it for like six hours. I yeah
That's that's the the part that's difficult. Everything else is cake
That's that's always that always seems like something that isn't very hard to implement in the game
but it's still like nice to have like uh
Well as a cave story has a mode
And like the re-releases where you can play as curly brace and all it does is change like
Just changes the character spray and like she talks sometimes and that's it
But it's fun because you know, I would like curly brace
I would simply I would simply have to create a a palette swapped set of sprites
and then just add like a little a little script into
The the the game object that is because phantom horn is is an is an
He's his own object in the game that has his own like behaviors
so I would simply have to like and he has a set of of of um sprites sort of built into him that are like
This is his normal sprite. This is his running sprite. This is guarding attacking
all these various
Things I would just have to add like another like a flag to be like if keg mode true
Then use this set of sprites instead of these set of sprites. Yeah, and that would be it. It would that would just do it
um
Lamal
Well, fuck. Hey, don't uh fucking ellias are cut all that
Cut all that uh because I don't want anyone to know
That should be a secret that feels like a secret that I just spoiled before I even thought to do it
Now and now I don't know if I can even resist the temptation. Hey mom's the word. I won't say anything. I won't say nothing
But I can't do it. I just want to credit him until
Okay, okay
But I can't but I can't do it. Okay. Here's the thing. I might tonic improv
Here's what I'm gonna do. I might do it
But I I won't let myself do it until the game is done
There you go. And then once once it's done then maybe as a treat. Maybe I will be like, okay. I guess I can add keg mode
Uh
Perfect, it's one obviously it's once you beat it. You have to unlock it
Anyway
What forget forget everyone forget everyone forget I said all that don't tell anyone about that
That's the secret. No problem listener. That's just between that's just between you and me
Mwah
You mentioning cave story, which is one of my favorite games. It made me think like how much of the um
content from
The um later versions was actually made by uh, uh
uh
So I actually know quite a bit about this
because uh
because of reasons but um
I know a lot of the uh the side like the extra content that nicholas added in the ports
Isn't made by him, but a surprising amount is like a the wind fortress level
Yeah, that's the one I knew about he made that that was just like a cut level from the game. Um,
I know he did
Uh, I he did the redrawn sprites that like, you know, they're higher res
I think he if he didn't do them personally
I know he supervised them or was like he gave the go ahead on them
But uh, yeah, that's that's what that's one of the few things I like from the newer versions because they're they're
They're in the same style and everything just I like them higher resolution. Yeah, I like them
but I also think the original sprites have their own charm, but um
Yeah, uh, all the other challenge modes all the other challenge maps are actually all fan fan creations
That uh that nicholas like yes, uh offered to put into the game people accepted like uh
And some of them I believe like some of the creators of the challenge maps actually got jobs at nicholas for some time
Uh through through that, but yeah, most of the most of the side stuff. Uh, it wasn't made by pixel
Well, I was I was wondering about the um
The curly brace mode because I doubt he wrote the dialogue for that, but I'm not sure. No, I'm actually yeah
I'm not sure either. He doesn't she doesn't really say anything too substantial
But yeah, well, I remember it because I played it for like 10 minutes. Yeah, and I know she I know she does say stuff, but
It's uh, it's cool nonetheless. Like I said, it's just a small little thing. They added that's like, uh, that's cool
I'll play I'll play curly this time instead of uh
step quote
on honestly, I would uh
Maybe I could give cave story a replay. I've played it before I've I've beaten
I've beaten it all the way through even the secret ending which I beat. Yeah, I've beaten the secret ending which version
On the pc the old old pc release. Okay, like the original freeware one
Yeah, yes. Yeah
um
But it's it's so good. I could I could I could it's been long enough that I could maybe give it another you could definitely beat it in a day
Yeah, it wouldn't be that hard. You could probably even do like a stream of it
Oh, it's a good ass video game. It's really good. It's one of my favorites as well
Yeah
Man, I I know it's like really controversial, but I just
The nicolas thing just leaves a bad taste in my mouth. Yeah
It's it's definitely. Oh, wait, you made a video about I did. Yeah, I made a video about it last year
So because that was um, there was yeah, I watched there was a lot of
Have you seen that cc?
Um, if I have I don't remember it
But that's one reason why I brought cave story up because I wanted to talk about that. Yeah
Yeah, sure go ahead go be my guest, but uh, yeah, I made a video talking about like the whole nicolas
uh
Thing in relation to cave story because there's a lot
nicolas is obviously not a very good company
Uh, since that was a since jason shrier like uploaded that upload he published that expose on kotaku a while ago
It's like tyrone order again that shitty ceo and all that jazz like the word culture sucks
Uh, and that that is bad. Yes, it sucks
But but uh alongside that just like it became more popular
To to say that nicolas stole cave story from pixel when there's really nothing
That proves that that even that
happened at all
It's yeah, I've I've I don't I don't remember if I watched your video enough or not
But I've done a lot of research on it myself and yeah, I came to the same conclusion like
It's not really clear like what the status is on that
It but I can understand why people think that because nicolas acts like they made cave story when they actually didn't
yeah, and you know, they're
They're within their right to you know, like talk about the game
And it too and they did do cave story plus that was all them
For the most part, you know with with like oversight by pixel obviously, but yeah, it's it
It just it's really
It's really hard to to say they didn't
Uh steel cave story when there's evidence of like other companies having terrible work relations with nicolas
but like
We we know you know that
Uh, tyrone and pixel they still follow each other on twitter. So they're obviously on good terms. There's
Pixel will always like talk about the game whenever whenever it's brought up by nicolas
there's
Really nothing
Nothing to really go on a lot of people like to point to the um, have you ever played carol blaster either of you? Yes?
Yes, I have
It's a I have also played carol blaster is actually a really good game
I I held off on playing it for a long time because I didn't because uh because I thought it wouldn't really like live up to cave story
And it's not I mean not it it is no cave story. It's it's a it's yeah, it's it's going for a different thing
It's not like yeah
It's not in the same vein of cave story and like the this it's it's it's a it's a side scrolling like action shooter
It's not like a a a metroidvania like yeah, it's exploration like story game, but uh
Uh, it is a really good game and I like it a lot and a lot of people will point to like the plot of carol blaster being about like
There's just like one tweet by this guy who's like if you ever
I know exactly what you're talking about. Yeah. Yeah, or basically like he he just
He equated the plot of carol blaster to real life experiences that may have happened between pixel and tyrone rodriguez the the CEO of uh
But it's just but it really is just speculation and and it it's interesting how people come up with their own conspiracy theories like
Oh, uh pixel put tyrone in the in the credits as special things, but he was being sarcastic
Yeah, yeah, and he actually and he actually hates him. It's or whatever
It's really strange because I feel because he's only he's only they're only following each other on platter
So he's only following him on twitter to be polite or whatever. I that's another I really I really don't know what the make of
everything because like
Because like before I played carol blaster
I just uh and like before I looked into the whole cave story stuff
I really just did assume that they probably did take cave story because it's a really easy thing to believe but
You know when I saw that he was thanked when tyrone was thanked in the
In the game itself that kind of made me like raise an eyebrow a bit and kind of want to research it and um
Well, I there's this um, there's this guy his name super something zero who can who really did a lot of the research
And we wait super what zero super something zero
Yeah, but what oh very funny so funny
Yeah, he he's really the one responsible for a lot of the research for that video
Uh, he has like a he has like a master thread. He posted on twitter like a little while ago that um
That kind of chronicles like all the evidence for and against the the whole cave story nicolas thing and it
It really just reads to me that that uh, I don't think I don't think uh pixel
I don't think pixel got the game stolen from him
Uh, maybe maybe nicolas has some sort of like rights agreement to exclusively publish it
but um
But that's not really the same thing as it being as the ip it's wholesale being stolen from the man
I don't know. It's it's this whole snafu
And not that said I don't think that like I don't think nicolas is a good company. I think they I think they suck
But yeah, they they do suck and you should probably just buy carol blaster instead of getting like cave story plus or whatever on steam
Yeah, you if you play cave story get the a free version
Yeah, because there's a lot of mods you can find for the free version that that kind of spruced it up a bit
If you if you're interested in that but if you want like the uh
Original experience. It's always it's always still there. It's always on the the fan site
Hmm. Uh, I did I did talk to someone on twitter who uh, I don't remember if it was super something zero, but um
I did talk to someone who emailed a pixel and they said something like
Caves uh nicolas um got the
they have like the um
Similar to what used to like the publishing rights or something like they um have uh
Uh, they're like allowed to use the characters. I know that because they uh because they show up in a bunch of nicolas's other games
Yeah, I'm trying to find exactly what he said
But uh, they're allowed to use what what quote and curly yeah quote curly brace the doctor ballos, whatever
Whoever whoever really they like the the characters from the games. They're ballos. Is that the that's the that's the secret villain of the game spoilers everyone
Oh, oh, yeah. Yeah, I thought I thought you were talking about ball rock. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, no, they're definitely not allowed to use ball
He's the only one they didn't get in the in the divorce
Wait, okay. Yeah, you're telling you're telling you're telling one of those patented lies again
One of those patented tectonic problem. I can't help myself
I'm just so unaccustomed such trickery
I thought you were serious at first. No, no, I think I think ball rock even is in someone like this
Uh, like spinoff games that they made like the good listen. I'll give you I'll trade you
I'll trade you all the other characters. Just give me ball rock. No deal. I can never have ball rock in the um
In the physical version of cave story plus they released on switch like years ago. They came with uh, they came with like a bunch of goodies
Uh, one of them was like a keychain that would be it would be uh, it was either
Quote curly brace or bow rock and I got a little bow rock keychain. I still have it
I wanted the curly brace one. That's pretty good. But uh, bow rocks pretty cool, too
Yeah, I agreed. Did you play the original v version of cave story because I was like really bad
That's how uh, that's how I first ever played the game. And yeah, I like released in a pretty rough state
But I think they fixed it up in some way
Yeah, a little bit
actually
That's sort of what happened to me. I heard the I heard the we version was coming out and
I was like, oh, I should play the original first
I so I I I played it at the same time as the we version, but I didn't play the we version
I think I thought but I did I did later and it sucked
I think I've played every every version of cave story
Uh, that's that's been released in some regard like I played the free war one. I played the we were one
I played the the steam port
Uh, I did you play it? Did you play the one on psp?
Yeah, no, because that was that was that was a fan one, right?
I know there's yeah, there's a fan one on the psp
And I want which version I really want to play is the fucking someone ported it to the Sega Genesis
So I really want to play that one
Oh, I played I played some of that actually
That's that's really cool. I'd love I love it if someone could port it could port it to the the SNES
Yeah, I actually played it on my uh, Genesis mini
I have I have a SNES now my old roommate gave me his his super nintendo. I just gave you one
He just yeah, he just didn't want it anymore or he he he was trying to pack light
And he was just like anyone want my super nintendo. He only had like three games for a thing
He had like super mario kart. Not bad, which I don't like
It's definitely the first mario kart
Kirby Kirby superstar, which is a plus. Oh, that's that's an amazing game
Yeah, yeah, so that's a winner and actually I think it might have just been those two
So I was a little I was you know, pretty disappointing, but I mean he had one good game. So, you know, all right
Yeah, I'll take all all for free. That's a pretty good deal
My friend my my friend did that with his dream cast. He just sent me his dream cast because he doesn't play it anymore
Well, one of my friends was offloading his like Genesis games
And he gave me like all three sonic games like a spider-man game and like a quack shot the donald duck game actually and uh
And some other like playing game. It was like
It's like, oh, oh, wow. Thanks. And they're all in like the cases. He's like, it's like how much you want for him
He's like, oh 20 books
It's like, oh word. Thanks. I still have those line around somewhere. Make it 19. Make it 19. All right
You drive a hard bargain there. Yeah, pretty cool
Yeah, I still have my uh, super nintendo from when I was a kid
I I have it. I have it packed away. I bought a um, I bought a super nt
like a few years ago, which is basically just like a
It's it's like a console that emulates the hardware to like a very fine level
That uh, that like upscales at the 1080p. It's very it plays like original cards. It's really cool. It's a really cool piece of tech
And uh, yeah, I've and I got a I got a flash cart a little while ago too
So I really don't have a need for my old
SNES carts
But you know, I like to keep them around because a lot of them I've had for a really long time
I
So I fucking I
I think I sold my I know I sold my NES
Yeah, which was really fucking stew. I sold the fucking game stop
Yeah, I was
I wasn't idiot stop
I wanted to buy like PlayStation games or something. So I sold my NES and a bunch of my
Old cartridges. I even I sold Kid Icarus, which was a kind of rare game. I think they gave me like eight dollars for it
So that was stupid. Yeah, they gave me like bullshit for that. I might have sold my super my old super nintendo 2
Uh, I don't even remember. I don't think I have it anymore
Uh, I didn't have that many games. Anyway, I have like mario rpg
Sue secretive mana. Those are probably not that rare. It's not rare, but they're definitely expensive
Yeah, fuck
You're uh, wait, if you if you don't mind biting the bullet, you could definitely look into getting like a secretive mana and mario rpg
Looking into getting away. Look into getting like a flash cart or something
They uh, oh man secretive mana on the super nintendo
50 60 bucks 60 bucks for one of those. Yeah, a lot of the the square games are pretty expensive
Um
Or everyone knows how expensive earthbound mario rpg is a hundred is over a hundred. It's like a hundred to a hundred fifty
I think chrono triggers around that same price too. It might be even more. Yeah
No
It's a mix of nostalgia and covet covet spiked a lot of game prices
Well, it's um, have you seen have you seen the I think carl yobbs just put out a video about like the like the
The the the bubble right then that company from wada. Yeah. Yeah, I was um, I watch uh
Pathy nes punks like podcast say does with uh with his friend ian and they've been talking about this stuff for years
But it seems like it's finally getting mainstream, which is uh, which is good because it is a it's a racket
For those unaware watch the video. It's a great vid
Yeah, I was I was pissed off because there were so many articles about oh this copy of super mario
Told for two billion dollars and i'm like, okay, I don't fucking yeah
It's just the it's just the same three people like buying and selling it back to each other to try and like
Create a market that didn't exist. It's the same thing that happened to like comic books and stuff. They're just finally moving on to games
Yeah, it's it's uh, it's nuts. I wish it wouldn't um
Because you know, they're sealed games and uh
And most people don't have like sealed box copies of mario 64, but that's not gonna think that's not gonna
Stop people from thinking that they're sitting on gold
On their like nhl 95 or whatever
Yeah, yeah, my my normie my normie six. Oh, sorry my normie sister texted me and was like
Oh, this guy sold super mario 64 for a billion dollars. We still have that game and i'm like, yeah, but
It's like not sealed and
That shit soup and also the scam thing which I didn't know about but I was still like suspicious
Wow, yeah a SNES a SNES sells for like 200 bucks. So pretty good for pretty good pickup on that. Yeah, that what's if
You can really like go
Like super nerd into it because there's like different types of super nintendo's like like uh on the inside
there's ones there's ones that um
There's ones that like really hardcore
Retro people really are out looking for it's called like a one chip SNES, which basically it
Outputs the the colors a little better. I think
Uh, yeah, it was like a later model, but it's still like the fat SNES
And then there's the uh the smaller like more compact version. I don't know which one you have but uh
I don't know either
What did I miss
Hey, give Gibbs here
The old the old the old one is more angular and square
And the new one is like rounded
Yeah, we've just having a jet button
And like in the middle you pushing it lets the game pop up if if so that was mine
That was mine in in when I was a kid that had the middle. Yeah
We've talked about any things
All right, I'll get it out of the box. Go find it right now
What is this button from uh, it says super nintendo or uh, uh
I almost called it. I was like as as the brits would know what a super famicom by the voice is called in the super nintendo over there
Yeah, wait, I think the only difference is the the controller has color. Yes buttons
Yeah, you guys got the colorful you got the colored buttons, which I never had a super nintendo
But a friend of mine did and I was like, oh
That's not like the angry video game nerve. The fuck is that?
It a lot of people really prefer the colored buttons on the uh on the super nintendo looks really nice here
I I like the colors a lot, but I really I really like the lavender
Colors they went with on the uh on the american version and I like that half of the color half of the buttons are concave
This this button. Yeah, this one does have this one does have the centrally jack button
Yeah, so is that good or bad that that means it's it's like a model one
It could be a one chip. I highly doubt it is one because they're like a later version or whatever
I don't know. I don't know if mine is a one shipper not, but it's the old uh box model
And yeah, I do think the concave buttons are better
Hmm true
Yeah, you'd have to you'd have to like open your you'd have to open the super nintendo to
To even like know if you had a one chip
It's it's really this is stuff that like really doesn't matter because you know
You're gonna be you're gonna be hooking up your super nintendo through like composite through like a crt. So it's not really gonna
It's not really gonna
I actually have a s video cable for my super nintendo, which is better than yeah, but not as good as
Uh rgb. Yeah, I think uh out of the box s video is probably the best
I think it's the best the super nintendo can do without like modding now. We're getting really heady
And I I think I think some models of the super nintendo have rgb built in
Maybe some of the later ones don't
Maybe yeah, maybe I don't know and uh back back to cave story. I was looking for the um
The guy I talked on twitter with and he posted this email because he emailed pixel
Yeah, I I still distribute if you were cave stories from my site. This is a con
This is a continuation with the special permission of nicholas
Yeah, it
Like like I remember this because this was um
This I think this uh this got passed around when uh when nicholas did like a cease and desist on some sort of like fan
Uh like decompiler mod for cave story, which sucks that they see indeed that's like it's shitty and they suck
But it doesn't like it doesn't prove they stole cave story or anything
I don't know. Yeah, who stole it. I know carol blaster
Uh cool the guy who made carol blaster also made cave story, right?
Have you played carol blaster kid but not cave story?
No, but I have seen
An analysis video about it
Oh, that small youtuber
And it was really looked pretty cool tectonic improv
Did you watch the matthew metosis video on carol blaster? I think that also
My favorite my favorite matthew metosis video is when he uh did a video on
The sonic james collection. Oh my god. That's such a great video
And he uh, he he talks one part is where he talks about
The character come character is coming out of rouge the bat bats vagina
But he says he says like no nonchalant. Yes that it's like hilarious
Or when he's talking about tails taking a stinky poo poo in his diaper. It's
It's probably it's it's it's it's as funny as video
By far
Yeah, uh, I should give it a rewatch. I haven't seen it. You should oh, there's uh
Has he made anything recently?
You mean the the last one he made was eight months ago. So no, I think I've have you heard what's going on with him
No, no. Oh, uh, yeah that well after he released the meta micro videos
video
He he announced on his like patreon that he's gonna he he's gonna like stop making videos
To uh, why he's making a game
Okay, I've seen some of those streams
I didn't really click on I clicked on one of them and he was like
Working with like a castlevania thing and he was talking through his process of figuring out movement
Yeah, he he wants to focus. He wants to focus on like game dev for a bit
And like uh, like maybe I'll go back to making videos at some point, but I'm not interested right now one of those like
It's probably a long time
Yeah
Yeah, I I always got the feeling like the fact that his videos were so slow. I got the feeling that he was maybe like
Thinking about others and he's he's talked in some videos about how he wanted to like write for video games before
And I was like, maybe he's
I guess I wondered like if he would ever like try to do like dev stuff
So I guess that's not a huge surprise. Yeah, good for him. Yeah, I'm excited to see what the sort of thing because like
Uh
If anyone is behind the design of a video game someone like him
You know presuming, you know, the game is the sort of game I would like it would be very well made it would be very considered
I disagree you disagree critics critic critics good critics don't make good artists all the time
Sometimes sometimes it just doesn't that's the that's the fear. Uh, maybe
Maybe I would I would think that his his approach is very thoughtful like he wants everything to have a purpose
I'm it could I'm not saying that he definitely won't make a good game, but I'm not
I don't I mean, oh, there's others just have to see
It's not I don't know many other like examples of critics making games. I know yatsi did but I haven't
I haven't really looked at that. Yeah, that that's that's actually the first thing I thought of when you mentioned that
about critics making their own games
Uh
I've only played the one yatsi game and it was really good. He's definitely aware of the uh of of that idea ben
When he's like when he's like, I'm didn't say
He wasn't I'm not saying I'm not saying you weren't not aware, but okay
I'm not saying that you weren't saying that I was saying
That he doesn't know I'm not saying anything about that. I'm on a podcast. Okay. Well, I mean well me either Ben
You've like critiqued certain things before
And then you're making a game
Really, and you know tom is also making a game and he critiqued my little pony. I've never
I've never criticized anything. I've never criticized anything
In plus I have only ever been criticized anything
Uh, remember in the that was the whole thing with my little pony was that I only said it was good
And I never said it was bad because that's what everyone wanted to hear
Uh, and and if you said that it was yeah
If you said that all you got to do is make a little pony ose and have her say this episode
Is really good and here are some things I liked about it and everyone goes yay
Eleazar Eleazar go back go back show is real go back Eleazar watch the entirety of t-bap
Clip out like a clip show of every time ben said yeah, I don't like it
Or excuse me every time phantom horn said I didn't like it
If you don't do that Eleazar it will just prove that I never said that damn it if you don't include
If you don't include any clips like that it will just mean that there were none
I don't like my little pony because it's for children
I don't like you because you're for children. I don't really like the process. What does that be podcast because it's you know
It's for children. It's not really. I don't I don't I don't I don't really like myself either
Oh, I want to say one I want to all want to see the fuck. I can't talk. I want to say one last thing about cave story
Okay, is that regardless of whether Nicholas stole it from him or not is
It's still like a way worse deal that he got for that than caro blaster because
For caro blaster. I think play is unpublished it. But like like, um
He still like owns all the rights to it
And gets money from it. Where whereas with Nicholas, it's like
people think like
Like tyrone tricked him or something into signing a bad contract. I don't know if that's true, but
it might be because it feels like
they
Are more involved with it than they should be
Which I think everyone already knows but yeah
Possibly, but you know, it might just be that he's not really interested in like working with cave story anymore because
I mean, I think I think that is like 15 years old
I think that's more likely because
Another thing like people come up with conspiracies conspiracy theories about is like
Oh, uh pixel wants to make a sequel to cave story, but Nicholas won't let him. I don't think that's true
That's that's out of I've heard that before and out of all the things that people say about about this controversy
That is probably the dumbest thing I've ever heard because yeah
Out of out of anything
Everything that could possibly happen with that game. Nicholas would love if there was a cave story too
Because that that should just sells
That's that's yeah, you know that they obviously don't want to make it themselves and pixel
Probably doesn't want to do it either. So
They're milking the original
Yeah, and the game is already finished. It's
Find the way it is. Yeah. Oh, did you ever put did you ever play the 3d version because I didn't dude?
I did play minecraft. I played it
I've also played minecraft. It's a 3d version of caves stories caves stories
that you apparently
Apparently pixel also helped with that one. I don't know
It just that that that is what you just said about how Nicholas would love to make a cave story
Sequel that's kind of what they did with the 3d one. They're like, oh, we want to make this
But I doubt pixel like actually cared like he was probably like, oh, this is a stupid idea
But they're they want me to help with it. So I guess I'll help now. Did Nicholas make it or did oh, okay
Sorry, I thought nippon Ichi made it, but I think they just published it. I think
Yeah, you're right. I have no idea what any of this is about and I want to talk about minecraft now
Why well it's it's time for minecraft. I'm looking at I'm late. I'm looking at brown bridge
I'm looking at I'm looking at the matthew mitosis stream. He's playing as like simon belmont and he's just like jumping around
on a plane
Okay, maybe this is too early. Maybe it's too early to say this
I'm not impressed with what I'm seeing. Yeah, the stream isn't much
I think he's just talking to the viewer about like so I'm trying to think about how to
You know do movement and and collision with platforming
And he's he's doing all that like walking through so it's it's not visually interesting
Here's here's what I want to know. Does he have a night? Does he have
Okay, first impressions and maybe I'm totally off base. This does not fill me with confidence not because like oh, there's not many graphics or anything
it's because
It he's he's fucking around with mechanics. Like how do I build a state machine? It looks like he
Is experimenting with like mechanics
And like how to mechanically build a game
Which makes me think that he doesn't have like a game in mind that he like he doesn't have like an idea for a game
He wants to make like he's just kind of trying to figure it out
As he goes from what I understand on the patreon post
he like has like a couple of ideas for games that he wants to make and he's uh
He started off working on one
And then like his his I his plan was that like if he ever came across like a
Insurmountable problem in one project. He tried to move on he'd move on to another one and see and see how that worked
So I think he's on like the second one
Of like his couple of ideas and that one is just like a straightforward action platformer
You know or like a castlevania or whatever
Which is why which is why he has like the rector model
Yahtzee made a really good castlevania like or metroidvania. So I bet I bet you can do it too
I should play that
Uh, stop not stalker poacher poacher is really good. It's a really good little game
It'll probably be a while before we see anything
From this game of his which is kind of which which is a little sad because you know
That means there won't be any videos and you know, a matthew metosis video is is always
I feel like I've got my fill of matthew metosis
I I like seeing him his videos and the way he talks about things is
Is gooder than the his peers I would say
uh
But like in general
I know about video games now. I don't really need
Analysis videos about them. It's just sort of would be nice, but
I don't know
I'm too smart. Yeah, I feel I feel like the meta micro videos
Was uh was already kind of like a a sign that he was probably done. It feels like a final video, you know
I'm not I'm not shitting on my matthew in particular, but I'm just uh
I'm kind of done with like video essays personally
Like I don't want to watch like people talk about some shit for like three hours
I might as well just actually like play the game or watch the movie
I have I have I have contracted the number of like youtubers who's like video essays
I will watch there are still a few who I will like always watch anything they make
Uh, but that that number has gone down
significantly
I love it when people make like eight hour videos about
Stuff like that's like a full work day
It's perfect for me because I listen to stuff. I've been
I've yeah, that's true. I should do that
This week I've listened to
The uh the that one guy the patrician tv guy
He made this this the set the seven hour video about morrowan
And then he just I just finished like the other day
I listened to the uh the 12 hour one about oblivion
Can't wait for the 26 hour one about skyrim. I've never even played any of these games
12 hours is actually the cap on like uploads on youtube
So if it was 26 hours, it'd have to be three parts. Yeah
I noticed that it's exactly 12 hours long. It's 1200
And I was like, is that a coincidence?
I didn't I didn't even know there was a limit because I maybe they change 20 hour long videos before
Yeah, I have to maybe they changed it again
I think it's 12 hours at least maybe maybe it is when you're uploading stream vods
I am pretty sure in fact that I have seen like one of those memes like oh
It's a thing that it happens for 10 hours except it was 100 hours. Oh, you're you're right. You're absolutely right
Remember when uh the youtube limit was 10 minutes
Hell yeah, but if you those were the days, but if you're like role on youtube was director
You got to ignore that that was like your little director. Yeah, like early
I've never even heard early youtube had this like thing where like you picked like uh
I think it was like a genre of video you would upload and they all got different
Yeah, I know right. This is like so crazy to think about they all got like little perks
Uh, the only one I remember is that if you if you yeah your class like you speck into a class on youtube.com
And one of the classes was director and since you're a director you make movies like oh, okay
So as as a director you get to abscond the upload limit and upload videos. I think as long as you wanted
Well, I don't remember that at all
I all I remember is the partner program
And they used to
They used to make it so you couldn't make custom thumbnails unless you were in the partner program. Yes, that's all I remember
I remember I remember that as well. I I don't think I did it myself, but I do
remember
The the the technique of putting an image at the very middle part of a video so that it would become the thumbnail
Yeah, so while you're watching it, it'll just be oh the thumbnail image for like five ten seconds
Yeah, people tried to get around the system
It's it's really crazy to think how archaic shit was back then but also how shitty everything is now with youtube
Yeah
Now it's shitty in more deliberate ways. Yes
Now it's shitty in ways that serve them. I think
Oh, did you they uh
The fucking the the the draw cast which is the name of the channel
that has um oblivion fall
and teleperte and ctole
They um ctole messaged me. It was like, hey, can you help uh
spread this around
And uh youtube just terminated their channel
For like scam content. Yeah, I don't know what the hell that was about
No reason at all that I could see thankfully it's back. I think they got it back. Yeah, it's it's back
That's crazy, but like that was really bizarre. I've
They just said they it was like it was like scamming or like two like a couple other things
they said which is like just
not even
Just absolutely no logic behind it whatsoever that that that anyone could see
So I guess it was just like a glitch or something or just uh
I don't know a cosmic ray must have like flipped a transistor in there
In there in there come in there
Super computers at the youtube headquarters and it and it made this happen. I also wish for a testium
The isr on cast its gaze on the draw cast was it was over
It's back though now, right? Well, but it's back. So it's fine. All right. It's fine. All right. We're moving on
Yeah, but the eye of that's the thing about the eye of sauron it looks at you and then everything's over, but then it's fine
Yes
There's a gonna be an episode of me
on there soon
We recorded it a while ago
It's gonna be out the the the draw cast the draw cast animation. We had to make an animation real quick
Oh
And teleperty was on that one and of course and that was uh, well, that's not even fair. That's not even fair sure
Uh, but I still made people laugh. So I think I win. I think I win my I didn't embarrass myself
I thought I would but I didn't give one give one the moral victory
Sure, sure
Well, I'm jealous and then there was other like really good anime everyone else
Aside from sito who is not an animator on that on that draw cast was incredible
It's it's like it's like they're like professionals or something. They like draw for a living
Imagine drawing for a living couldn't be me that's for sure
Like literally it could not
Fuck
Fucking christ, dude, dude
It's same
I sneeze like that as well. I didn't think other people did
I heard I heard you uh, I heard you have an internet troubles kid
I was I was they were they worked out um
And it's all it's really good. Actually. It was like
30 25 to 30 megabit so megabytes per second upload, you know, whatever the thing says
I'm not upload download, but that's still really good. Yeah
Well, I mean we're at two hours
So it's almost time for us to be moving on to voicemails unless you've got like anything you wanted to to talk about
uh
Well, uh cc tech you guys good with uh with starting up the voice the voicemail segment
I would um of the procrastinator podcast. I would feel bad if I didn't if I didn't talk about uh a certain thing before
uh moving on to voicemails because um
Was the last couple of times the last couple of times on our 9 11
Yeah, well, we actually did that earlier on. Oh, but uh, yeah. Yeah, too late. Uh, well, I guess I
The last couple of times I was on this podcast I was uh between projects so to speak
um, uh, but um
And I really haven't been making a lot of videos recently, but I do I was uh
Involved in certain like collabs
Lately, uh one of which was this uh this thing called gaming and the golden record. It's a bunch of like uh
YouTube people came around and like were like the the basically the
The prompt was like what game would you uh, would you send off the space to like have aliens discover it?
You know like that uh super mario brothers
Yes, yes, I'm sure uh, I I believe that was picked by someone
But uh, I was I was involved in that video
Uh, someone asked me and I acquiesced and then just uh just last friday
Or uh a week ago as of this upload. There was another
Another little collab where a bunch of people got together and made one minute long essays
about basically anything and I um, I also was uh in that I talked about uh
I talked about the b-52s the band
Uh, and it's all it's all it's all uh back-to-back like yes the essays the video is all the essays together
Yeah, and they like another minute remain. That's more of my speed because video essays are getting too long these days
Yeah, that's like the whole I'd rather watch one. That's a minute. Yeah, it uh, I'm I'm I like the videos a lot
I think uh the the editing for the uh the minute long ones are are really well done
and in that like the
The through line is is pretty clear even though like everyone just kind of did their own thing and didn't really like work together
Uh, the editor hot sider. He did a really good job on that one and also I like the the golden rickard video as well
I was uh happy with my prompt
All right, uh, I guess we'll put links
Those down in the in the nice content
Do they do yeah nice con nice content world world very proud of you
I I need to get into more content creation, but uh, I'm too lazy. What game would I send out into space?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, um fucking fans. I was revenge. Obviously. Yeah, uh, I got the tails gets trolled book
I got it. I bought it. I have it now. It's on my shelf. Oh, you beat me to it. I'm so happy
I still haven't gotten it's been selling pretty well, which is awesome
Me and laserbot haven't gotten our copies yet because uh, I ordered like free copy. Well, they're free except for the um
Production cost so it was like 10 dollars instead of 30
But they like they prioritize bought copies before um the free copies for authors
so
Me and laserbot haven't gotten ours yet, but I'm looking forward to that
Yeah, it's it's it's cool. I I knew this technology existed where you put up a book
Amazon prints it and sends it rather than you having to do any production
Yeah, print on demand is uh, I mean, it's it's very convenient, but I I never really looked into it
I was thinking about doing it for like my own comics, but apparently it's like it's better for
Uh written words
Um, like the quality of the paper is not like oh, uh smooth like
uh
Whatever you call it paper
Manga paper not manga paper a comic book stuck
This stuff and and the colors are a bit glossy the colors are a bit washed out, but
Um, it's cool. It's cool seeing tales and and him getting trolled
And all the events that that follow
I actually had to edit the colors myself, but because in the first copy that I ordered, um
Like, you know the parts where like luigi and the troll king are fighting in the cave and it's like really dark
Oh, yeah, I looked at those
That that whole part when I if you just put in the comic pages and print them as is that whole part is just like pure black
Yeah, I so I have lightened up
Yeah, I had to lighten it up manually
And the the other complaint I have is that it's really finicky about which like files
It accepts if it's like inside the margins at all it like freaks out and it's like oh, you can't submit this
So I had to like keep editing it over and over again
And I I have like four or five test copies
Because of that because I had to keep like changing it
But I think yeah, yeah
I think it turned out uh the final version turned out okay
Yeah
Well, I better get I better get one a bit of quick procrastinating
Yeah, what what what comic book wall what comic book shelf is is incomplete is complete without tales gets trolled next to the vapors chapter two
And don't forget your kato anthology book. Oh, I should got that a few weeks ago
I haven't I haven't got mine either. You know, I haven't checked my p.o
I haven't checked my p.o. Box in a while. So it could just be sitting in my p.o. And then soon the lord of ghosts comic
Oh
Yeah, congrats my my children
Uh, all right, so voicemail time I think before the voicemail I want to say one thing the reason I say
The reason I say stuff like that is because of the first sonichu
it uh, um
issue where
This is like the funniest uh sonichu thing in my opinion the the cover of the first one where
Chris says go out my son and zap to the extreme and then sonichu says I will thank you father
Yes, of course. I mean, of course. Sure, of course. I'm familiar
I'm I'm familiar with the material
It but that that's like the whole reason I like added that to my vocabulary because just because of that
It's go it's go sonichu go out and zap to the extreme. I will thank you father when when chris read it for like the audio
When chris did like a video where she where she flipped through the page and like narrated it live
The way that she said that she read sonichu's line was like I will thank you father
Just awful
That I will zap to the extreme
That sounds that sounds like her accent
But yeah, a little bit the way I imagined it is like I will thank you father. I will
Well, I would I mean in my head he just
I originally in my head. He just sounds like sonics. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Zap cool. Yeah roast juice hot. Yeah, we're gonna fuck. Yeah zap bow bow
Team rocket. No, thanks. I I know. Yeah, sonica is team rocky, but uh
I this might be controversial to the tales gets told fans because I know that the um the fan dub is like really popular
But I always usually read the characters voices and like their actual voices
Like uh, you know, I haven't actually heard the fan dub. So I I can't
But I mean, yeah, I would imagine that they sound like their characters
Uh, they they don't well some of them do but some of them don't like
The fan dub gives sonic like a really nerdy voice and he sounds like
Oh, yeah, take tales
Uh, this problem can be solved without any feelings. It doesn't sound anything like that, but it's like a similar. Um,
You know, I respect
It sounds like a bold artistic choice and you got to respect that
But it's it's it's funnier to read in like sonics actual voice because he says, you know, how it is, uh
The tales is getting trolled. They're calling him gay and shit. He can't take it because it's like something that the actual sonic would never say
and it's just funnier to
Imagine it in his voice. They're calling him gay and shit. He can't handle that
Yeah
That's no good
Remember kids if any trolls call you gay
That's no good. They should get you should tell shadow. They should bring Joliel white back
As the voice of sonic
To bring him back from the grave, you know, roger craig smith was gonna quit voicing sonic and I wish he did because
Like he sounds okay and like sonic boom, but like other than that
Uh, I don't really like his voice as much as the previous sonic voices. I think he's fine
I'm just more I just want them to just fucking stick to a guy, you know
And they've had roger craig smith for so long
They might as well just keep them like imagine if mario's voice changed every like five years
Yeah, uh, they've had uh roger for the longest so they might as well keep them
I know they like cut a bunch of the other I think
I thought I thought they would get like a different guy for like I mean, you know
The boom continuity is different from like the game continuity and yeah, that's that that's that's that's why that's why I think
Roger sounds best because it's like a different interpretation of sonic
Yeah
So I would assume they would have two different guys, but whatever
Um, well, they sort okay. Well, I don't I don't know. I was gonna say they did in the old days
But sonic didn't have a voice in the games me old days. Oh, yeah, that's true. He does
Well, actually actually actually I I take that back because
For um sonic underground
They got julio white but that was that came out at the same time as sonic adventure
So he actually did have two different voices
and then later when they did is
When he gets a uh a bubble of air doesn't he say something?
He talks in that doesn't he?
You know in sonic cd when you uh, you're when you're right when you when you run out of time. He says i'm out of here. Yeah, yeah
And I think I think a japanese woman voiced him there
Bass the same japanese woman who's saying the um tutut sonic warrior thing. Oh, no, I think that was the same one
This had her voice them there. That's pretty cool
Yeah, all right. All right, if I remember correctly, I could be wrong
Let's let's get going. Let's go before you do the voicemail. I need to get some oh my god
I need to get some water. It's hot here. It's like 160 degrees
Go. All right. Go like the way go get water
I'm gonna I'm gonna I've had enough. I've had enough. You're all misbehaving
You're all you're all keep delaying the you're all
You're all delaying the inevitable, you know and the thing about the inevitable is you should actually just rush headlong into it
I'm excited in fact
Yeah, if if at all possible
If there's like a like a
A a cow that will happen then it's the inevitable
I got it. You true true
True
Oh
Like the imagine just ran around his room
All right, uh
Sonic underground they made about their mother will be Sonic underground
First in peace voicemail
The first voicemail is called try to guess what's inside. You can't
There it is. Okay. Here we go in three two one go
Welcome to the voicemail cast the only podcast that takes place in the voicemails. I'm your host the voicemail king
And today we have with us ben saint
We also have give and take uh, hey
Right, so the theme of this episode is cooking personally
I enjoy making fried rice because the recipe allows for so much variation and the ingredients are very affordable
What kind of dishes do you like to cook? Uh fried chicken. I like to put chicken in the oven and cook it and bake it
All right. All right. It seems like it's time for the voicemails
Ben will you do the honors?
No, you already did the honors. No, it's cute. I think someone else is done. Uh, that was a very uh
Succinct summary of an average pcp episode
All right. Well, we've onto onto the voicemails. I guess uh, the next one
I think I don't think it has a not a name, but it's from uh, it's from doid gazers. So, uh, let's get hype
Okay, uh three two one go
Hi, it's doid gazers again. And today we have a fire diss track against one ben saint associate
Tommy j
Tommy j you've been leaving too many bad voicemails. Let's get on
Oh my god, I love you. You're my best friend
Tommy j Tommy j. Let's go hard in the paint
Tommy j Tommy j. No one cares what you say
Nobody likes your voicemails because all your voicemails are scaring
Tommy j Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j.
RIP iS we're back in class. So where am i?
I sleep six weeks back. I'm a rat-tat-tat with my big ass cat. So accept your work. You think that's bad?
Tarpault credit from Knapp, your family, and rent some moss in my mangy off that mother's face
They could disappear like they best for no witnesses man, no stupid fire
You cannot deny or you cannot compete with this either empire. I crene I don't beat
I rap I don't sing and that's how you do the voicemail queen
Tommy j Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. Tommy j. I think that you may have ass burners
If you leave another voicemail, swear to god i'ma beat your ass like i'm
That was very good very nice
It was finally the new studio made something good
Hashtag wow good damn
Hashtag not all kiwi farmers
This is the best this is the best track i've yet heard out of the out of the the trial of the golden witch discography
She's really upped her game this time
Not all kiwi farmers this guy
Hey doid gazers come on over leave behind leave behind your sinful kiwi farm with come in come into the light
Leave the sith ways behind and join and join the path of the jedi fairway with your bloodstained past
Like Cecil from fawn fancy forest time to become a paladin of the pcp
Yeah, pc paladin, baby. We're doing it. Uh, don't be it. Don't be it. Don't be a kiwi farm is blaggared when you could be a pc paladin
Yeah, that's what i'm saying
You should you should have you should have banned in the white race and help us in that genocide
Absolutely. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, you definitely don't want to be white when we take power
You want to be you want to be putting yourself as far away from that as possible? Yeah
Next next one is called, uh
Fuck wait
It's on the other page. I gotta look at what the other page is. Uh, it's called
Uh
Eat trash die fast. Oh three two one go
So if you died right now or wherever you spend the most time, how long do you think it would take for people to find you?
Uh, yeah, my my roommate aka my dad is here. So he would find me
I think it would take I think it would take a few days. I think that
Nobody would come into my room
I mean
No, I think it would probably take probably munchie and kazzie would would would get suspicious
About where I am because like, uh, we're supposed to we're supposed to lift
Don't don't you have don't you have roommates or like
Apartment mates?
Well, they wouldn't well, they wouldn't come into my room. They wouldn't they like I said before like we don't like interact with each other
Oh, okay. Uh, so so they would not come looking for me unless like it started to smell
Unless my body started to now they just think that was a classic ben saint move
Uh
Gotcha
If I can be like if I can be more specific, I think it would take like an hour
For my dad to know if I was dead
Uh
Geez, no, look at me. Look at me
People care about me enough that they'd find out I was dead within less than a day
Yeah, I wouldn't like I mean there's there's both good and bad to that because
The bad part is if my parents died, I would probably kill myself because nobody else cares about me
Sorry tails if this looks emo to the viewers
But uh, I think um, I think in the I think
It would be less it would be less than a week
I think just only because now I have um supposed I'm supposed to lift regularly
And if I started missing my lifting schedule, then people would be like, where is he?
Before that it would have probably taken like a week or more for anyone to be like haven't heard from ben in a while
And there's a weird smell coming out of his room. That's different from the usual one
Hmm
These smells are a bit different from the normal smells
I think before
I think if it were like, okay in my old house
It might maybe would have taken like a week for anyone to be like suspect something. I think here
And except for that my my new schedule if I were on my old schedule here, it could be like a month or more because like
Nobody would expect me to be anywhere
None of my roommates would be like wondering where I am
They would be yeah, I would be here indefinitely
But not would you would you skeletonize?
I think so. Yeah, I think I if if possible. I would attempt to skeletonize
Legend has it if you die and skeletonized come through the window if you die and skeletonized before somebody finds you
You get to be live life as a skeleton. You come back to life
Oh, that would be so awesome
You really want to make sure you die in a in a draw in a hot dry place
You really want to get that uh that process uh started. Oh, just just move to arizona where I live and you'll die pretty fast
Just in general pretty fast
Yeah
based
Uh next voicemail next voicemail is called
Uh, ben saint scaring me three two one go
Ben i'm not gonna lie. It's pretty uncomfortable going on twitter every day to see
You tweeting about trixie. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't like her just as much as you do at least anymore, but
I'm feeling comfortable. It's pretty disturbing. I'm not gonna lie. It's disturbing. Oh, I'm disturbed
Oh, that's so crazy like oh
What am I even watching right now? What am I even looking at? What is your fucking problem, dude? Take your fucking meds. Okay
It's a meme
What yeah, it's so weird. It's so fucking weird, dude. Like if you think that is weird, I don't
I don't know how you deal. I don't know how you deal with life. You're not gonna be ready when life attacks. Okay
You're a nothing master is what you are
Uh
It's weird because it's like I have to say maybe they're thinking oh
Other youtubers and like brand twitter accounts don't like talk about petty things
But you've been doing this for so long. They surely should understand. This is the ben saint way. I fucking do
Um
I don't know. It's just yeah. Why now see I was just thinking about this like other like people people were complaining at me
Then like ben you're too salty ben. You're too you're too mad you'd live in in your head rent free
But it's it's gotten like it's gotten to the point where I think
People have just accepted it now
And it's just and and most people are just like yeah, that's just been you know like yeah, that's just normal whatever
And I was thinking like I made it. I broke through to the other side
I've brought everyone along with me to a new world where I can be as petty as I want to
And everyone is just fine with it
But this guy's a fucking hold out this guy's a part of the old world and it has to be destroyed to make room for the new
Well, I don't think it's good, but I just don't care to do anything about it anymore
I know I know I've just exhausted you. I've just exhausted you to the point that you it's you can't criticize me anymore
I can't believe I'm on a podcast with ben sane known tweeter. I know
I know
So embarrassing same
You're telling me
true
Yeah, it's hard to it's it's hard to be a brand manager because like you want to like start arguing with people
But that's not professional, but ben doesn't care. He's just like, you know, fuck it. We were saying
Okay, we were saying people were talking about uh, like nate
In like nate's approach to the tricksy thing is like when people have asked him about like cantonate is like so
averse to conflict that he goes like
Eh, these things happen. Eh, it's nobody's fault. Eh, the project just died no one to blame and it's like
No
Everybody knows it's so strange that tricksy killed it by move. It's so like it's it's so obvious that like it's like
It's like you think that like it will automatically look bad if you say anything negative about anyone
But like no if someone does something bad
The right like the normal thing to do is be like, yeah that person fucked up
And if it's true like as long as you're not like making that accusation baselessly like it's it's it's fine
And it's good to say that and it's weird not to it's like I think what could possibly be like
Oh, he doesn't want to burn the bridge with tricksy. I don't think that's it. I think it's oh if people see that
I have emotions and I get angry at stuff. Maybe I'd be angry at other things and it's like
Sponsors won't want to interact with him if they see that he is like upset that
His former partner fucking bailed on him and like wrecked their thing together
Like if they saw that like that bothered him, they'd be like, well, I don't want to work with this guy
This guy's a loose cannon. It's one thing to just like not talk about it because I I guess it's your business
But if somebody asks a question and you answer it with
Hey, what whatever no no harm done
It's like that's that's that's a strange thing. Why would you answer it if you're gonna do that?
It's just the way just the way the cookie crumbles. It's nobody's fault. It's just it's just destiny
I guess I don't know. It's just like that a joker meme where it's like you think tricksy killed the thing
I I do and I'm tired of pretending she didn't
You know, oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Fucking the rv situation whatever we all know we all know about the rv situation
Uh, the next one is called I sort I sort of know but I don't you can get into it later
It doesn't dad about the book the next one is called tarpitt
trandor thaw
three two one go
Fast-talking craftsmen and indestructible super god tarpuk transom here to mine the past once again
For only its good parts and discard the rest on the last pcp
So like two weeks ago by the time that you hear this you talked about fertility statues made by like cavemen types
And you remembered it as basically porn
Well, I heard that as a kid too, but a while back some female archaeologists slash anthropologists slash whatever
Notice that it's what you see if you're pregnant and you look down
That's right. It is a sculpture made from the first person perspective and holy shit if that is not a cool as fuck idea
Innovation how is it what if cavemen just had pregnancy fetishes? Okay, just because someone said it doesn't mean it's true
Yeah, I mean it's still hot either way look down like pov
statue
Like surely surely a pregnant woman
If she's making statues can look at other pregnant women and know what that looks like and then make a little
Chubby short statue is like this is what it likes. It looks like to be
Fertile pregnant babies come out
Gross, what do you know? That's hot
Mmm
The I mean maybe I mean
Obviously, I mean, yeah, obviously what it is and what it was used for is like it's anyone's guess who knows
Who fucking knows I I didn't really think it was probably our competing barrier. It's it's potentially
I mean, I've heard people say it and I think it's it's just sort of like it doesn't it doesn't sound that crazy
Like I don't know whether I mentioned it at the time, but I always thought it was like
Similar to any other statue. They would do is just like art is
Observing the stuff around them. They draw the story of when they killed the mammoth on the wall in the cave
I mean, they make a little fertile. Why wouldn't it be born? Why wouldn't it be born?
Because they'd be actually fucking I don't know. I don't I don't see any reason why
I don't see I don't see any reason why it couldn't be born
Well, I didn't say it couldn't be born, but I feel like it's it's not as I don't know if they were that horny
Then in in terms of like being repressed and what are you fucking talking about?
They would just fuck they were insane. They wouldn't like spend time spend time making a statue. Oh, that's psychotic
That's crazy. That's that's what you mean. What do you mean? That's insane. No, no, no, you you you you you you missin you
Misinterpreted what she was saying. She was like
They don't need to make porn because they can just fuck whenever they want
That's what you said. Yeah
Makes sense. I'm just no it's that's insane. What's you're crazy? What are you talking about?
What do you mean? You think what do you think human?
What do you that you think that like a civilized society
Humans are just like going and like grabbing people and fucking no and they're just like, yeah, okay
Just living like fucking like orangutans. Yeah, just like just oh just the the unflans just just swinging around the boreal range and forcing copulation
Well, that's what you're describing is inhuman
Isn't didn't they make those statues and like caveman times and shit?
They didn't need porn because they would just say they didn't need it and it's impossible
I'm just saying it feels more likely that there's just like
statues of stuff
Like they would make art about things about life
I yes of
Yes, but sex is a part of life and like yeah, I know sorry, but like when you're when you're when you're
Can do you not like the urge there?
Like when you figure out like ah, I can craft I can craft the likenesses of things
Like obviously there is a a demand there and there is like an idea there
It's like, huh, I could make something looks sexy and makes me fucking hot
And and we still do it and believe it or not. We still do it to this day
We still craft images that get our fucking rocks off. Yes. I know and I'm pretty sure that impulse was probably there since the beginning of time
I know why were you calling me crazy? It's not like I disagree with any of that
but
But you said
Because I think that the thing about like oh, they they didn't need porn as much because they could just have sex
I don't know what that means. That sounds that's because all right. What I was getting at with that totally
point
was that as society became more civilized and cities and stuff
from like small tribes
To like giant cities people became more detached from each other
and so porn became more like
prevalent
And necessary because you I don't know
That's just a hunch. I'm I'm trying to like I think think about like
I think it's victorian england that there would be a lot of porn
I think that in any era
Any era at all of human civilization
there would have been
men
who wanted
Who who were who were not men men who were seeking sexual gratification and were not able to find it
immediately
I feel like that's like going to be a universal thing throughout all. Okay. I just I just think it may have been
like
Like if it was a graph, I think the thing would have gone up
In in more like city
Like you you think you think that you think that like uh, uh, uh, what uh, what's the word? Um
Unfulfillment sexual unfulfillment would go up. Yeah with the rise of urbanism. Yeah
Well, I mean, I'm thinking like not even just that but like this the in england in victoria
I'm just thinking of victorian england is like
There was a lot of like oh, you're not proper unless
unless you like
Like don't masturbate ever and like sexual repression became extremely fashionable
And and I don't know religions and stuff
Back in the caveman times. They didn't have as much of that or at least, you know, there was a time before it
I don't know sure
They might not have had
Puritanism is like an ideology
Uh, okay. I mean, I guess I see what you mean, but I still don't agree with it
Yeah, I mean, I'm not basing it off of anything. It was just a like a general hunch thing
Okay, I think we've made some great progress today
All I'm saying
All I'm saying is I'm not crazy. Okay, it's what you it's what you it's what you see when you look down and you're pregnant
Whatever, okay
Sure, where's the where's the ancient fertility dildos if that's if that's you know what if that's what you see
If that's what you see when you look at the statue, that's just as valid as anything else
You know what if they were if they were really horny. Why didn't they make like uh
Flesh lights meaning out of rocks and shit
You know, I heard someone told me
I don't remember who told me this but recently someone told me that they discovered an ancient egyptian vibrator
nice and
What it was it's you're not gonna believe this. This is what they told me
I don't know if it's true. This is just what I was told
But the way that it worked was it was a hollow tube into which you would insert live bees
Inside them the hollow tube and that was what caused the vibration. No, I just heard this. I just heard this
No, it's funny enough to be true
See, all right
There's another thing about all of this is that the the the sexual nature of a lot of
Archaeological finds that were presented in english
um at the time of of like
The industrial revolution and areas around them is like, oh
So barbaric, we can't let them we can't let people know that there were statues of penises and stuff
there's like famous um
Of like a like a a carving of a pharaoh with his wang out and he's got an erection
And in the british museum, they chopped that off
They just chopped that part off and so that so so the people couldn't get like so ladies wouldn't faint
They wouldn't get a case of the veins. That was can't can't cancel culture gone too far. Yeah
They circumcised him. Yeah, and so like I'm not sure how much of like the education
of history
In that way continues
So maybe I grew up not knowing enough about how horny everyone was
Okay, I mean I mean I think
the the I'm gonna say that the
The the gatekeeping the gatekeeping of sex
I believe is is probably a part of human society
Even even even in caveman days like even in caveman days you like before there was any civilization whatsoever
You would have had like, you know
You would have had like try, you know families that live together that wouldn't just want like, you know
Fucking roving some fucking roving like, you know, vagrant like wandering
But yeah wandering by and just like like raping the raping
Like no, like no, I'll fuck I'll fucking kill you if you come near my fucking family you fucking scavenger
Did they do that in the bible?
Oh, no, they they sold their daughters into sex slavery. That's what they did in the bible
Yeah, for a few loaves. That's whatever everyone it was. It was the hottest thing
It was like the hot new thing to do. I'm not proud of it
But you know peer pressure kind of at the time it it just seemed right. It just seemed cool. Everyone was doing it
I don't I don't like doing it, but it works
Didn't want to be cringe
You know, you got a hand at two of them though. It really works. It gets results. Yeah
Uh next voicemail next voicemail is called. Okay. There's an image and a video
Attached it's about cuneiform. It's making it's writing with the cuneiform clay tablet. Okay three two one go
On the topic of old stuff, I've been thinking about how cuneiform was used for writing for like 3 000 years
So it's longevity far outstrips any other way to write anything
Uh and then I looked in would further and I found two things a holy shit is it ever small like goddamn
And b nothing I've ever seen
In depictions has really captured the three dimensionality that it has how important the shadows are for being able to read it
And what the shapes actually look like in person. Yeah
The picture that I included is of a tablet for scale
And the number file video of it that if that goes through
Will show around the three minute mark what the shapes really look like. Uh, I just
Appreciate how its literal durability has allowed it to endure with perfect legibility
And uh, I thought that was cool and wanted to share this is well
I mean, that's why we still talk about it is because it happens to be the writing form that is best preserved
I really like this tiny fucking iphone
It's so cute with the little squishes like you squish the little things into the clay
But it's an iphone remember like
tiny little
I want a cuneiform phone. It is really small
Uh, yeah, I've seen like when you when you when you see it written out like on paper like black ink on white paper like it doesn't look
I mean it looks different obviously
I don't know not knowing much about it. I have no fucking clue what i'm talking about
Oh, it's like cave paintings where I mean it looks kind of cool. It's I like how it looks
It's like in certain cave paintings where um under like a torch
I mean a flashlight a flashlight would um, it wouldn't work
You'd just look at it and be like that doesn't look good
But with a torch light and you move the torch around the fire the flames they flicker and they make it look like it's a moving
image
It's it's it was it was like uh, it was like, uh, it was like a video I watched about it told me that
I don't really know
They said it was like the primitive animation like that sounds incredible
But I don't I don't get it wait primitive animation. Oh like like the flickering flickering of the torch would make the thing look like it's moving
But only with fire you can't like shine like a bright led light on it
And as some guy figured that out when he realized that why they wouldn't have fucking led spotlights. What am I doing? He turned them off
And then he turned on he he lit a torch and he was like, oh my god, they're dancing
They're dancing
Amazing
I'm sure it looked very cool back in the day
Lit by uh by camp firelight or whatever
Uh next voicemail is called
Behold he is the one he is one with the form
three two one go
Every day I listen to the pcp and for those brief moments. I was you I was there
Is that a spicy salts reference? That's uh, that's uh, yeah, it's a very spicy meme. Yeah
A very spicy hero, isn't it?
Uh, is it a year now?
What what no what meme or I would I was away for a second
Uh, it's the thing. Don't worry about it. No, I want to know. It's just this little crazy thing
It's the guy that tried to kidnap. It's the guy that tried to kidnap Trixie's nazi fiance
Oh, I have no idea what that is. Would you like to know more? Yeah, I know
You've made that perfectly clear
Uh
A very I just wanted to end on this thought
A very spicy christmas
The christmas special
Oh boy. All right, maybe it will has it
Okay, has it has it been a year it uh, I don't think so
Am I maybe it was in october it happened? I don't know. I don't know when the fuck did when the fuck the void gazers start. Yeah
I have
Honestly, I have no idea cares never mind
honestly
Because we didn't hear about it until months later
So it happened at some it happened well before we heard about it. So maybe it has been a year
um
Next voicemail is called, uh
I seek an answer based saint three two one go
My class reunion so cringe. I don't know. I never been to one. I I didn't go
I thought it would probably be cringe and also I was like busy and I was like, uh, who has the fucking time?
Who cares though? I just didn't go fuck it. Uh, next one is called
Crypto is over and done with three two one go
So, uh, I just wanted to let you know that I bought some uh, cripple
No, not right before el salvador
Gardening house and let me tell you
It was not the most uh, wisest decisions because I lost nearly 20 percentage of my investments
So when there'd be occasions to not to follow my example
Yes, do not do
What we do and check out this video by the grivel institute. Uh, it might it might educate you a little bit
On your if you bought it like a week ago, then yeah, I'm really sorry
You owned it when it went over that cliff when fucking el salvador adopted it
I don't know why that like it hurt the price so much, but it sure did
It's 20% though. Uh, yeah, I can't speculate on why I think it's just sort of something
It's a new thing happened. Oh, everyone did do something and they did
A new thing happens and yeah, yeah, everyone do something
It's like musical chairs just like find a chair buy sell
I don't know just do something and then like people see what where the trends are going
They follow the trend and then the trend becomes a huge thing
And it went down. Oh my god, Elon Musk made a made a tweet everybody find a chair
Everyone find either a red chair to sell or a green chair to buy. Oh, everyone's sitting in red. Uh, well price goes down
Okay
See you next time
Um
Next voicemail is called. What is it? It is called, uh
Crypto is over and done with number two three two one go
This is a follow up to my ripple and divorce
I ended up cutting my losses and go in on the chain link
But as fate would have it
It's even worse
Why?
So, yeah, just
I you cut your losses and made a worse decision
I guess it fell cut his losses sold his other crypto
Yeah, well, it's it's not cutting your losses if then you buy some more of a different crypto
I think i'm out of the crypto
Buying for for now unless I see some like really compelling evidence to like. Oh, no, it's it's gotta go
It's gotta go really far down from for me to get interested again
I've made my small profit and i'm good to sit on that forever
Man, I don't know if
People people are still saying it's going to 100 by the end of the year and I don't know that's just hopeful
They just want that to happen because they're invested in it
There's only like I want it to go to minus 100 by the end of the year so I can invest again true true
Uh next voicemail is called, uh
Yiga Yiga gazers three two one go
Hey, this is right
Where is the money?
Yeah, I don't know
You tell me it's coming
It's coming. Yeah, it'll be right here. It'll be here in a minute. It'll be here in a minute
Uh, like that scene from uh from the room when he's on the roof. Where's my money denny? It'll be here in a minute money tricksy
It's coming. I swear. Just give me five more minutes. I'll have it for you. Just give me five more
Who sold you the drugs?
What kind of drugs do you take?
But are you buying them to them selling them to them? What is it? You're not my fucking mother
Next voicemail is called next voicemail is called big guy three two one go
Hey, then can I drop in our of your ocs? No
Oh
This is a reference to the fact that I told
I saw an artist asking another artist like oh your oc is cute
Can I draw them and I and I I said
You don't you don't have to ask them
You don't have to ask for permission
And they and they were like i'm doing it to be courteous and respectful
And I was like that's dumb
It's it's courteous. It's not discourteous and it's not disrespectful. In fact personally
I find it annoying when someone would ask me. Oh, can I draw your oc? You know, it's even worse than that
Yeah
People ask me for permission to make tails gets trolled like fan art
And it's like first of all, I didn't even make tails gets trolled is
Felsichold is fucking fan art. You fucking imbecile actually fucking claude actually. No, it isn't it's it's above fan art
It's even more sophisticated than fan
But uh, I see the thing is I didn't even make tails gets trolled
And even if I did like you can do whatever you want. So it's like
I don't you can literally do
Whatever you want. Yeah, you do whatever you fucking want
Uh, this person got all defensive and blocked me
They said they said I was uh, they said I was uh, they said like don't speak for another artist
It's like I didn't I just said it would annoy me
It would annoy me if someone asked me can I draw your oc's because yeah, of course you can
I didn't speak for anyone else
She got mad and she blocked me and then everyone in my discord
Everyone in my discord had a fucking fit sporktown harrowin had had one of her fucking psychotic episodes
And uh and got everyone to uh to dog pile on me
So, you know very funny very very good. Ha ha we all had a good laugh
Uh, and that's what this is about. So there's context damn
I know right next voicemail is called
Wait, was that was that yiga gazers we just listened to yes
I think what no no that was
No, um
It wasn't uh, was it yiga gazers was the one before
So that's me that was that was big guy. Yeah
I think I might have switched those names around
But like who cares whatever um next voicemail is called
All
Nate on the podcast three two one go
You talked about how
Nate doesn't want to be on the podcast because he doesn't want to talk about himself as much as you know
Random topics and I think you misinterpreted what you know you're wrong and ignoring the possibility that Nate just doesn't want to be on
The podcast because it opens him up to criticism
um
I think what he really meant is that the current focus of the episodes are normally what's been going on in my life
And you know what's been going on in my head the past week. What have I been thinking about whereas the
Topics often encouraged talking about yourself. Yes, but talking about your opinions on other things
Talking about your deplore backstories as a content creator
um things that audiences would be interested in
um
Viewing the podcast as part of your repertoire of personality driven
Okay, all right. Okay, buddy. What this person is talking about with across to you are giving that
You are giving Nate way too much credit
You have thought this through way more than he did the fact is that when I ask him
Why he doesn't want to be on the the show and he says because I don't want to talk about topics
That doesn't make any sense and it's nonsense and he doesn't know what it means either
So like you're you're giving me you're giving you're like you thought it like no
Here's like here's this like actually what it must mean is this like oh and if I if I connect these dots together
It's because oh it's actually because his interest must lie in this other place
And it's it actually conflicts with like his core philosophy of this. It's like no, it's just nonsense
It's just nonsense. Didn't um
Didn't he talk about himself or like stuff he was doing on the gamer zone?
Of course, what would you what would any what is any podcast?
What do you talk about in any podcast you talk about yourself what you're doing?
And and what's up?
What is any podcast?
Yeah, so it's just nonsense guy. Just just don't think about it anymore. It's not it's it's there's nothing to think about
Uh
Next voicemail is called ben bullying
Nice hold on. I will post it right there
Yeah, there it is. Okay, three two one go
This is a message for past ben
It is
9 11 at 12 24
And there's no episode of the pcp
And fuck you ben. It's not my fault. It's game's fault. Gotcha
Uh
Sorry for the late episode, but like, you know, whatever it was like 10 hours late like oh, sorry
Why why was it late?
Oh, I I I uploaded it wrong and then I was away from my computer for a long time and I didn't notice
I didn't schedule it to upload. I I just put it up unlisted. Yeah
Because I just forgot to hit the schedule button because of internet problems
Uh, yes, but it wasn't exactly I was moving
Okay
Uh, okay, the next one is an image link. So I will put that uh right here
Horseshoe versus dr. Wolf. Let's go. Okay. Here we go
All right
The virgin in horseshoes didn't credit munchie for the pony avatar gets mad about inconsequential things is yellow
But we'll deny it the chad wolf assembled huge teams of unpaid volunteers features an equestria girl's dvd art
proudly white
Is that second one was he an equestria girl's dvd art?
No, I like how we don't question like, oh, of course. He's proudly white, but no
But the equation is probably well, I mean look at him. You look at him. He's white. You can see it
I mean, he's kind of gray. He's kind of gray, but like this is a good picture. Wish there were more blurbs
Only three eight. Yeah, come on. We can think of three is
There's there's wasted space. Yeah
Uh, hold on. I would say dr. Wolf. All right. I found a video of dr. Wolf himself reacting to it
Wait
Okay. Yeah. Yeah
Oh, okay. So the the box art people
Did they put a screenshot of a dr. Wolf video talking about equestria girls on the back of an actual dvd?
What what the fuck? What a terrible
That's awesome. Why would they do that?
That's insane. That's so bad
I guess the person doing the design just didn't give a shit the person who made it probably just thought it was from the show
And didn't know that happens actually a lot
Weird it's probably like looked it up dr. Wolf's thumbnail or something or uh
Clip from his uh from his show was like one of the first results and they were just like, ah, here we go
Oh
How bizarre but yeah, wow there is
Yeah, horseshoe or there be yeah horseshoe horseshoe never got on dvd box. Hey, where's the dvd is tricksy
Where's the blue rays? Then we could then we could have had it then maybe there'd be a uh a conversation to be had
Lamal, uh, no
I mean, I guess Chad Wolf wins
There's just no contest. So okay easy
Uh uh
Next one is called
Oh
There he is
My man. Oh my god. Oh my god. Okay. Okay. It's like that fucking
It's like that picture monkey tweeted once where he added like some dumb character to the simpsons lineup and pretended it was real
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Gumbly. He didn't he didn't he didn't uh invent that. He got it from like he got it from 4chan
But it's exactly like that
I didn't need to stop looking at this. Oh, oh, you mean dr. Wolf in that screen. Yeah
Yeah, like why would there be a little anthropomorphic wolf? Don't they know that the whole premise is that everyone is a human?
Didn't they watch the movie?
Well spike is a dog. I don't know
Oh, shit, you're right
There's dog. I can't believe this is real
This is insane. This is so funny. Uh, okay. Next one is called Subaru
Su-wat-ter-u-yo Subaru Su-wat-ter-u-yo
Three two one go
You have the power of full mind control
But only of five people
Who would you choose and what would you make them do?
Joseph Robinette
Rainbow Dash rarity twilight
The other one I'd be twilight. Huh?
You'd mind control people to role play as the ponies and you would be twilight. I would
I would mind can he's got my control fictitious people
Uh mind control five people. Um, I don't know. I'll just mind control five really rich people and haven't given Joe Biden and George Soros
Hillary Ron Clinton, uh
Jeff Jeff Bezos Elon Musk, uh, uh warren gunnels, uh
Who's the other one been saying rich three? All right. Yeah, I've been saying obviously
uh
Best guy ever, uh, uh the golden witch, uh
Endless just give and take uh lethal roar mage tom oliver
Muchi wears tiny hats and then we get and then I would force them all to come back on the podcast
They need to be more specific
They need to be more specific about this question. Like is there a like a
distance limit to
How you can like control like mind control people or can you just like mind control anyone from anywhere?
I like to treat it as a blanket. So it's like risk. It's it sounds like you can just pick five people
That's that's sort of how the death networks because you know how you can like write make people do stuff before you kill them
Of course
sort of like that
I would get all of my favorite
Artists to read and enjoy my comics and say good job. That's what I hear here
Here's my answer. I would uh mind control joe biden to legalize weed
That's perfect
Yeah, I would I would I would control I would mind control joe biden to enforce a
vaccination mandates. Oh
Wait, I it looks like I did it looks like
No need anymore
What a coincidence. I thought you're gonna say mandate people to watch my little pony
Well gen five is you don't know me very well. Do you then? I guess I guess not
No, it would make them make them read homestuck if anything. Oh, yeah, that's true
Yeah
That's that's the only way. Well, I'll make Joe Biden read homestuck and talk about homestuck at length on one of his speeches
At like 0.5 percent speed
Oh, yeah, and instead of his state of the union address. It's the homestuck address
He addresses he addresses he'll talk about his favorite state of the state of the fandom state of the fandom
Uh, yeah
Next voicemail is called a message from your gaping ass three two one go
Oh
Hey, Ben just sitting here in the mcdonald's drive-thru and I was just wondering do you point on doing
A physical release of slime and pushman because if you are that would be based
Yeah, I'm yeah, I've definitely said it before I'm definitely gonna do a book when when
Slime and when the when the game is done and I finish the comic. Yeah, I'm gonna
Uh, I'm going to
Yeah, I'm gonna do I'm gonna do like a like a homestuck book is is the idea
It's gonna be like, you know for four panels of page and like commentary on the bottom
I think is what I'm gonna do. I already started laying pages out actually actually I laid them out a long time ago
Uh
You know up up to what I had done at the time
You know, I need to uh go back and uh complete that obviously
So, yeah, short answer is yes
And it will be like and it will be because it'll be it's many many more pages than the vapors
So it would need like a an actual like, you know, perfect bound, uh, like soft
Softcovered book not like a not like a saddle stitched, uh, you know
Copy a comic whatever you call it
Uh, yep
Next voicemail is called a message from your gaping ass two three two one go
Hey, I also want to say
Uh, turns out you're actually the soy lord, uh stopping. So god damn soy already. I don't even fucking I don't even like soy
I like uh, I like almond milk and I like coconut milk. I don't like soy soy soy
Oh, no, never mind never mind the soy programming is activated soy soy soy
You at one time I tasted it was enough
Now I I was wrong. I was wrong about that soy is good
Uh, uh, yeah guys actually soy doesn't turn you into a girl
Actually, soy doesn't have phytoestrogens
The watch the h-bomber guy video where he says that soy actually won't mind control you and turn you into a live
Hey, that's that's that's what I want. Yes. I want everyone to see that
I want everyone to think it's good for you actually
I really wish it was as easy as eating like a different or drinking a different kind of milk or whatever
But yeah
Eating them eating the miracle burger because why why would you get on hrt if you just eat soy all the time? Yeah
Soy soy soy
Hell if it was that easy, I would do it too
Soy if it were if it were you gotta eat the miracle burger. It's got like 100 times the estrogen
Oh, you mean the uh impossible burger from burger king. That's the one. Yes. Yes the impossible burger
Lamel
Also the 5g signals
Someone in a burger
Someone in a restaurant. We were I was joking about like, uh, you know vaccine conspiracies and a guy at the table over
from us, he he chimed in to say something about like
5g and and like vaccines and stuff and like, uh, uh, like, you know, uh
heavy metal particles or something and and
Okay, the the point is
He chimed in and I genuinely could not tell if he was like saying like ha ha
Actually, there is some truth to the coveted like the vaccines are poison thing
Or if he was like chiming in to like make a joke along with us like ha ha. Yeah, that's so funny
You should check this stuff out. It's funny too
I genuinely could not figure out which one it was and it made me very uncomfortable because I was like
I don't want to laugh and I don't want to engage with this guy on the chance that he is being serious
But I don't want to shun him and make him feel bad on the chance that he is just trying to have a goof with me
And I and I was I was really I was really caught between a lot of rock and a hard place on that one
That's quite a conundrum. I know
I kind of just had to sort of thread the needle and be like ha ha like act like I was amused but not too amused
You know
Yeah, that was my solution
Um, I know that feel
Next voicemail is uh a message from your gaping ass three
Three two one go
Okay, here's my true thoughts about benjamin sing
Uh, he is hilarious
Absolutely funny. I love him true god here in terms of humor
But god damn how I want to strangle him sometimes with his fucking lefty opinions
It actually hurts me, but like it's funny. So I don't care. I can't tell if this is like a parody. I don't care, but uh
Cool, man, have a nice day. Thanks for the email. Is he what was the last bit? I think he said he's floundering or something
Uh
Yeah, you sure did. Okay. Next one is called
Fuck where did I put it? It's called a message. No, this one is called apple jack
Yeah, here we go uploading now
apple jack three two one go
Cady phantom horn. Sorry. I haven't made a voicemail in a while. I've been real busy
I'm here at the apple orchard. I just got done picking apples
I was listening to the latest episode and I got thinking you should make your own brony lecture
Jenny Nicholson got a million v's talking about bronies
You could do it too if you talked about your time in the fandom
The history of it all the stupid things that happen in all the freaks
You meant like brony curious and cake standard cake, especially as a gold nugget that needs to be mine
Call the video the truth about bronies or the dark side of the brony phantom
Anywho, I need to get back to picking apples fucking apples you idiot
Why would you get it wrong? I don't understand. That's apple jack, right?
Yeah, what the fuck something's up. Honestly a change honestly yet
If we if we ever got the opportunity and it was in it was lecture time
Yeah, a re a redo of the brony lecture by like one of like phantom horn. You'd have to cosplay as phantom horn to do it
Oh, yes, I could wear the blue wear the blue of spray painted blue horse head the wear the hooves
Uh, yeah, it's not I might it might be worth doing because I mean there is a there is kind of a funny story there
Uh, so I guess I just agree that lovely to hear from you apple jack, even though you're a capitalist whore
Uh, uh, uh, but uh, you know
You look you look lovely in your leather boots. So it all it all uh, it all evens out
Uh, uh, no, she's not my type
She is a horse
Or she's a filthy, you know, I'm not like, you know, phantom horn is not like that filthy that filthy
That travel vlogger who likes to mingle among the commoners who likes to show up and like date, uh, you know date like
Earthy, you know, like lower class like like earth pony girls because he thinks they're exotic or something
You know phantom horn, uh, it doesn't fetishize them like that phantom horn would never mix races in such a problematic way
Uh
None of that please
Next one is called, uh dick punisher
Three two one go
How do you refer to each other off mic?
Do you call each other by your irl names or your user names? Also. Fuck you. Tommy j
Yes, I say benjamin
And I say his last name also
I I call I call gib gib
Generally and uh, I mean I call tom tom. I call Nate Nate
I mean
Everyone calls me ben
The only person who I okay, honestly, I I used to always call munchie munchie. Sometimes I still do sometimes I call him anthony now
Uh, it's so I guess it's kind of
Munchie and kazzie I go half and half with like I sometimes call them
The one name and I sometimes call them the other gib. I always call gib. I never I never call you louis
Uh, I never have
It's on your patreon. I know
But most people don't think about it
I only use my real name for like my friends
Or people people people that I've people like that. I know really well for most people like, uh
Um, most people I meet online. I just use their online names
Unless I've known them for a long time
There was there was a a phase my my discord server went through a phase where everybody everybody made their uh, everybody made their
Their discord name their real name for a minute there. I thought it was their middle. I think there's some people was yeah
Some people it was their middle names
uh
So, but uh, I don't know
I think it's
Cool and stupid. I think it's good and bad. I don't know what I think about anything
Um
I don't know my screen name is my is my real first name anyway. So it's like, you know
No, no no confusion there would be no reason to like having a podcast
Like name that we just don't refer to each other as that'd be really weird
Yeah, I thought st was your real last name
It is not it is not
A lot of people a lot a lot of people think that and a lot of people have assumed that nate's name is nate saint because
I love that. That's one of my favorites. Yeah
Yeah, that's pretty funny, but it's not it's not true. It's not. Yeah, he took uh, he took their mother's name
That's why are you brothers?
You what do you even?
Yes
You fucking goof wait, wait. Do you tell him what tbap stands for?
Wait, don't you tell him
Tbap stands for two best brothers bitch about ponies. Uh, yes. Yes true. Yes true
But um, I can't I keep for some reason I keep thinking of this
But the whole nate saint thing reminds me of the mario mario luigi mario thing again
You're you're obsessed. You're obsessed with mario mario luigi mario. That's that's like my favorite movie the super mario brothers movie
I had that thing
I had it on vhs as a kid and I remember liking it
But I remember like the like the second half got taped over so I remember the first half really well
And I remember the ending
I remember when like the dimensions merge or whatever. Yeah, and there's a big section in the middle that I just don't remember
Um, we got one final last minute voicemail
Gender abolition extremists in the making
three two one go
Is there anybody whose life is actually improved by
Gender being a factor like compared to if it didn't exist and femininity and masculinity weren't real things
And everybody was just described by individual factors like
At best it feels like a total non factor where you're just you know, like you don't care. You're fine. Just be in yourself
Uh, and at worst it's a completely crippling condition that leaves you socially dejected and hating yourself like
Why isn't everybody on earth just a day then who the fuck came up with this?
Fuck this is what I've been saying. Yeah, it's I mean
gender
I think
But if in terms of like having a gender binary or like oh masculine feminine male female
um
men women uh
The utility is temporary in that people grew up like for me
I I like doing the woman things because it makes me feel better than
Like compensating for having lived as a man for so long
but ideally
That would have never been a living as a man and wanting to live as something else
It would have just been they them from the beginning
Yeah, that's that's that's kind of how I am like
I don't really like strongly identify as any gender like I've just
People think I look like a man. So I guess that's when I am out of convenience, but I I
I don't really care either way
I strongly feel that uh the like the the existence of gender like the the convention of gendered pronouns is just a very unfortunate sort of like linguistic
accident
That we didn't really need it didn't need to be that way
And it's it's unfortunate in that it like
Causes all this fucking all this fucking strife and confusion and all apparently
I wish we just didn't have it and then and then there would just there would be no
There would be so much we wouldn't even have to debate it apparently. It's like even worse in other languages besides english
sure
For us to have genders. I never really understood what that even means. It's it's a it's a it's a it's a it's a bit of
Like over complication that it's like do we I don't think we really get I feel like we don't get that much out of it
I feel like it's a cabinet in
Italian is feminins like why what is it?
How did it make well, I mean in some in I learned this from yon yon misily in some languages. It's like
It's genuinely like completely arbitrary like what vert like what nouns are masculine or what a feminine like like even if it's a person
Like if it's like a certain kind of person like a nephew or or or something like
So something like the word for a nephew can just like be masculine even if it's like a girl nephew, right?
What some languages
Oh, you mean other languages. Yeah, some languages are just completely arbitrary and there is literally like no
It doesn't it's not like oh this is this thing is called female because we have a
Female conception of its use or purpose like no like it's it's literally just like someone picked it at random once
That's like every word real quick. Have you talked to yon misily?
No
Okay, uh
Why would I have talked to yon misily because you just said you did oh you said you watched a video
He's a he's a youtuber. Oh, okay. Yeah. I thought they like I thought they were like on the podcast or something
I watched their um, I watched their mario video the other uh the other day
About how many I found them
I found them through that video and then I went back and I watched all their conlangs
Yeah, I actually I actually found them through uh their rhythm heaven videos because that's one of my other favorite
Uh game series yo cc. I've never played a rhythm heaven video, but I went back and I also watched the rhythm heaven videos
And that was really good. Yeah cc. Did you get the new wario where?
Uh, no not yet. Ah, it's great. I get I I I guess I'll have to uh
I'll have to get it to fill the void in my heart that
A new rhythm heaven game isn't going to be made anytime soon. So
Well, thank you. I'll have to wario's there get that as a substitute
That's right
Hi, at least at least kotake uchi is still doing art. Yeah, I like his I like his style. It's good
Uh, yeah
Great game. How much play?
I've you know, I don't know it you more of a wario land kind of guy
I'm just I'm just you know, I look at the game
Which it's like it's just a bunch of rhythm based mini games and I oh rhythm heaven on I
Yeah, or or or even wario where and I'm just like, I don't know
It seems like
I guess it just doesn't appeal to me as something that I want to do is like sit down and like
I'm not I'm not into like rhythm stuff. It's just like it's so it's so simplistic
I I understand that like why it would be fun. I guess but it's like
Doesn't it I'm not it doesn't call out to me like then you should you're gonna you're gonna get you're gonna get something out
Of this experience like uh
This kind of seems like a distraction
From what's really important well
Which is arguing on twitter which is posting on twitter about how I will pay money for people to unsubscribe from trixie's patreon
I must have my vengeance at any cost. Well, but that's what that's what matters to me right now. This is the real phantoms revenge
Yes, true
it's like uh
Mario's legend of the seven stars or whatever you get you're the shell
And if you time the button presses
correctly
It does extra damage
It's also like extra damage. It's also like mother three if you've ever played that. Oh, yeah, the battle played earthbound
Oh, yeah, the earthbound I have not played mother three
The battle system is sort of like rhythm heaven in mother three also
Yeah, you like time we have to press is to the music
Yeah
fascinating
uh
Is that it?
I really I really like the yon misleys. Uh, he means like three videos or something about rhythm heaven
Yeah, got a lot out of those. Well, if you if you ever get him on the podcast, you should invite me to
Okay, I mean if I ever just happened to stumble upon yon misle
Yeah, you can you can see him walking outside sometimes
If I if I ever just just walking around town and I bump into the guy and I say hey, man
You want to come on my podcast four thousand something followers? Let's see how much ben saint
Five thousand, you know, you may consume him to uh absorb him onto your podcast so it works
Steams are open. Wait, how many?
Yes, he is less than five thousand followers
Okay, this is this is this I want to mention this is uh, I'll feel embarrassed. I'll feel a little embarrassed if like
He what is it happens to listen to this episode and like here's me say this on the episode
But I was a bit I was pleasantly surprised and surprised surprised the other day
When I saw a youtuber that I know pledged to the patreon
Uh, uh to snaker the guy who does the yakuza video. Yeah, he pledged to the page
I was like is that is that really him? Is it the to snaker and it was um, it's like it's like wow
He watches nice. Yes. He's a cool guy
Yeah, oh
Well, shit, maybe I should say hi. Maybe you can probably get them on
I really like uh, I mean I don't play yakuza
But I really like his I really like his yik video and I really like his evo video and uh, there's a few more I think
Those are the two that I also was good. Yeah to snaker is great. I don't
I'm not sure if I've seen the pack. No, no, I have. Yeah, with the Dead Rising 4 video
I think is probably can you link to his channel because it sounds interesting
Do you yeah, okay, he does um, he wanted to hear that hot tricks he got
He maybe he did. I mean, I guess uh, he he uh
Yeah, he does um, uh, yeah, he does long he does long
He does he does long video essays in which he
Describes a video game which are just what I like
Uh, so
Yeah, I thought that anyway. I thought that was cool
Uh, hi if you're listening, I'm embarrassed to have uh, outed you like this
Sorry, not as embarrassed as you must be at the moment
Oh, even revolution was also a good video
No, the sub that surprised me. Oh, yes
I have seen I I have seen I think I went on a big binge where I watched like all of his stuff
I watched a lot of the yakuza stuff too, even though I'm like
You know, I don't play that. Yeah, like whatever. It's like he's he's he's a good narrator
Uh
There yeah, good stuff. I'm pretty sure the snaker is also in those collabs. I was in too
He's a he's at least in the in the minute one. Yeah
Oh, no shit. Oh, that's neat. Well, that's pretty neat. Okay
What?
Well, how about that?
Okay, well if you want to be like to snakerer and hundreds and thousands of others
Satisfied customers. You got to go to patreon.com slash the up procrastinators
Uh and pledge and get that hot tricksy goss
And uh and many more access to the and many more actors of the pcb minecraft server
You watch a hidden hidden gem of the bonus episodes if everyone's repledging
Watch the watch the minesweeper episode the minesweeper episode was a joy. Yes. It was a real joy
It's a little visual and I reckon it is a bit visual. Yeah, but um
I really had a lot of fun making it. So hopefully it'd be fun to watch
as well
Um speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail if you want to leave a voicemail
uh
Yep
And I oh um remember if you ordered a if you have a kickstarter
Pledge of a hundred dollars worth of radcon 4 and you are getting a road to radcon book
And you have changed your address make sure to send a kickstarter message today when you hear this immediately
Because I am sending them out very soon and I wouldn't want to send it to the wrong address
uh
I guess that's uh, I guess that's everything
Yeah, tectonicimproff.com. Yeah
Yes
talesgetstroll.com
What by the book by the book
by the book dot site
uh
Lord lord, uh kickstarter. Uh, you still take no reason to go to the kickstarter anymore
Uh, I will look at it. Just look at it for a bit. I want I want to be more specific if we're uh, if we're shilling shit now
um, sure
The the the link to buy the talesgetstroll uh volume one
tgt volume one physical edition
It's uh my pin tweet on uh the talesgetstroll twitter
It's also on the front page of uh
talesgetstroll.org
Because a lot of people are like oh where can I buy this and you know, I just don't need to look that hard
It's there. Yeah, you'll find it. Well good
That's where it should be
Yeah, uh, okay sick
Anything else anything else before we wrap up? No
Oh, I wanted to talk a little bit about uh, the talesgetstroll like actual new pages coming out
But we can do do that some other time
uh
Unless you I mean is there news if you want to share some news. Um
I'm trying to get pages out faster, but you know embergram is writing the scripts and he's a grown-ass man with kids, so
He might not be able to
Do it lazy grown-ass man with no work ethic lazy. Well, he has to take care of his kids
and work and shit
boo
Then again, I have to work too, so
Boo, that's not content. We're all busy. That's wasted content. I know life streaming the kids
remember uh, remember when laser bot made like uh
Like six pages a week
Yeah, those were the days
Those were the days. I mean, I wasn't even reading at that point. I read it. I found it later
Yeah, I'm uh
Those would have been the days
They were they were the days even though I wasn't around for them. Yeah, I'm a talesgetstroll the
What's what's the word?
aficionado veteran veteran old fag veteran is old fag the word you're looking for lmao
Yeah, but I wanted a more how dare you say that you can't fucking say that
I meant like a more
PC term than old fag like basically that but like not old guard. That's all you want. You want old guard old fuck
Old guard. Yeah, old shit
Because because we don't we don't we don't we don't say fag anymore
We've never said a bad word and we never will no
Uh, okay, I think I think it's time. I think we're wrapping up. I think it's the podcast is over. Thank you everyone for joining us
We'll see you next week. See you on the bonus episodes when you give us the money
So we can get that extra 60 dollars so we can pass trixie's patreon
The ultimate act of vengeance the real phantoms revenge right here and he will he will he will pay you to unpledge
I will pay you to unpledge from trixie's pager. That is true. That's true, and I've done it
All of you. Yes, trixie who have made it this far. Oh
They're all still here. They've all been listened. They're all they've all been thinking
I think ben can still redeem himself. He's not he's not totally
He's not totally sick and rotten to the core is either. There must be some good. No, but it was no
No, I mean we all heard that doigazers rap today. I think I might actually go play
I can't I can't argue I can't argue that was quality production. Yeah came that came from the heart
All right, that's it. Goodbye end of the podcast so so long