Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
not joking. I looked over the comments and the consensus cash money. Don't worry, I will
use my god powers responsibly. You wouldn't have them if you were going to use them responsibly.
If I don't, the police are standing by. Anyway, Ben Saint, welcome.
Little Ben, John Saint. There is Lil John Buuh, my favorite guy.
I don't want to be on the podcast this week. It's because I stayed up all night last night.
Typical Ben.
Crossing animals.
Oh yes, let's get right into it. Yes, tell us about it, Ben. Tell us about it.
Well, I'll tell you this.
I've had development.
I'll tell you the struggle. I'll tell you the struggle. First, I had to catch the new
sea fish. I had two nights ago.
I caught a new butterfly today. It was based. It was green.
I loved it.
Did you have your bird wing?
You know what? I'll pull it up right now.
I'll tell you in just a second.
Well, a couple nights ago, I had Ethan and Kazi over my island because it was raining.
We all kind of visited each other's islands, but it was raining. There was a thunderstorm
and they both were like, while I'm here, I'm going to catch a sealocanth. We all fished
and everyone caught a sealocanth. Even I caught a sealocanth. I didn't even want one.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I forgot.
I forgot that the reason we were doing it was because Kazi had like a meteor shower and
so we're all there.
Bro, I've been nuts with the meteor showers. I found like a hundred meteors in the sky
the first time, literally. Over a hundred.
I think I didn't know what to look for, but now that I know what the sound is to listen
for, I feel like maybe they've been happening more often than I thought.
Yeah, I think so.
But I got it today. I just happened to log in and Isabelle's like, by the way, tonight
there's going to be a meteor shower, so watch the fuck out, which I assume means there's
going to be like a lots, which is pretty neat.
Guess so.
But anyway, so the other night they were doing that. We made wishes, caught sealocanth. Everyone
had a sealocanth. It was great, but I didn't want a sealocanth. I wanted the barrel eye,
which is another weird rare fish, and I hunted for it and I managed to find, you know, the
barrel eye was my white whale, you might say, and I got two of them legendary. But last
night I was like, well, there's a couple more fish I haven't got. I need the mahi mahi,
and I need the giant terravale, terravel, whatever.
Don't know it.
And so I fucking took me to like five in the morning. I don't know why. It was so hard to
get these two stupid fish. I don't even like them that much. I mean, they're fine, whatever.
But I did. I did it. And then I was like, I was up, and I was like, well, I can't go
to sleep now. And you know, I've been meaning to terraform my island and turn my little corner
of Yakitori Island into a steam and steel steampunk nightmare, a mountain fortress.
So I just started doing that. I just started building up giant walls, like three level
high walls around my little peninsula. And you know, things will have to move to accommodate
it. But it's just sort of the initial, just sort of the initial planning stages of my
industrial hellscape. You know, things will, but you know, it takes a long. It's so fucking
hard to get like a clean edge.
I know, it's a true nightmare.
To even get like the edge that you want on like your river or your cliff is hard enough.
But to like get the river edge and the cliff edge, like to match each other on like, and
then to smooth out the cliff on both sides, including one adjacent to a river, like is
so it's so it's awful. It's just terrible.
Took it.
Did not have a plan for that one.
So, you know, that took me another like five hours. And it's not, and it's all not even,
and it's only even in the planning stages. It's still very much a work in progress, but
well, if it was easy, if it was easy, then everyone would lose interest with this shit
game instantly.
It's so poorly optimized.
That's true.
But of course, feature not a buff.
Punked.
But no one will ever lose interest in Animal Crossing, New Horizons, certainly not now
that I just like nobody ever stopped playing the previous seven million games in the Animal
Crossing series.
Correct.
Well, they live on, well, they live on as confusing counter data that you might find
while browsing a wiki.
That's true.
They live on, they live on as misinformation telling you about when Nook's cranny opens
in the morning or whatever.
Truly their legacy is eternal.
Yes.
Thank you. Thank you, Tetus. Appreciate the contribution. It was a peacock butterfly,
which apparently has been available for quite a while, but I only caught it this morning.
Well, you know what?
Looking in my museum, my butterfly exhibit is looking tight as hell.
Well, you know why?
It's going to be voluminous.
I have a guess why you might have just caught the peacock butterfly.
Yeah.
It only appears when you have black flowers, which I do here and there.
Oh, fascinating.
So if you maybe just newly acquired those, you might now start seeing those we didn't
before.
I mean, we probably started doing our flower breeding maybe like a week or two ago.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's not just black.
It's like black or blue or purple, I think, so.
Okay.
Yeah.
The point is you need some crossbreeds to get a bunch of different bug types, but in
particular, the peacocks are good.
They're one of the more valuable ones, and they're not even, and then once you have the
flowers you need, they're pretty common, too.
So they're big moneymakers.
So Ben, did you...
An animal crossing sucks.
No.
Nintendo Switch sucks.
Nintendo sucks.
I haven't made a good scene.
Hey, you idiot, complaining just because we're talking about a video game you're not
interested in.
Why don't you get with it, Scrub?
I say, sewing, moments before I will be suffering through another hour's long monologue about
Final Fantasy VII and thereby reaping.
Indeed.
Yeah.
Truly, that is a bra moment to which I say...
Bozinga.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ben.
What were you asking?
Did you rise with the morning sun as I did, Ben, of course, and I believe I saw that
you did.
Invest all your bells and turnips this bright and shiny capitalist morning.
I'm close.
I know I did.
I invested a fuck ton of bells.
I put 700K down for those turnips this morning.
All my savings, basically.
That's all your savings?
Chewah.
Yep, pretty much.
Okay.
We're gonna have to collaborate to make sure we don't lose our investments.
Yes, of course.
Of course.
I had about three and a half million in the bank, which I technically owe most of it to
Tom Nook, but I don't gain anything by paying it back, so I'm just putting that off until
it's not a...
So you've achieved your final expansion or whatever?
Yeah.
Yeah, I've got the final expansion, but I haven't paid it off, but you don't get very
much for paying it off, so whatever.
I had to just wait till Bernie gets elected and he'll just absolve you of that.
No problem.
Tom Nook will be dragged into Central Park in shot.
He...
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh.
What was it?
You're dead.
You're 3 million in the bank.
Oh, yeah.
I was gonna just invest all of it.
I was gonna invest all of it in turnips, but it actually got...
I had to buy so many turnips that I realized that that would have been eight or 10 full
inventory loads, like you had to fill my entire inventory with turnips and go back and forth
to an island, because we're gonna collaborate, you know, we've all got an old Discord server
where you compare turnip prices.
Yes, we do.
The turnip?
And I realized, like, I'm gonna have to go back, I'm gonna make like 10 trips, I don't
want them, that's tedious, so it actually, it was out of sheer, like, this is boring
and it's tedious, I don't wanna buy any more turnips that I stopped.
Truly, you have hit the skill ceiling of Animal Crossing when you start to feel that way.
Skill ceiling is how many turnips can I fit in my inventory?
And deal with the horrible mon...
Not to mention, you can't even store them, you have to place them in the island and then
you have to walk around and pick them up.
Just save you...
I'm not willing to place them on the island because I share my island and people and I
won't look...
Right, right.
No, I had to fill my house with them.
I had to take up most of the furniture, which, to be fair, most of my rooms are pretty sparsely
furnished anyway, so it wasn't that big of a problem.
I picked up all my furniture.
Now my attic, my basement, and two of my side rooms are all entirely filled, like, wall-to-wall
with turnips, and there's a few more in my back room as well.
And that is 2 million bells worth of turnips.
That is 4,000 turnips, I think is the number, or no, 40,000, no, 20,000, it's 20,000 turnips.
Now Ben, you and I are in this together, both heavily investing, so we turn up trackers.
Our stonks must reign supreme, so we will all collab in our server, in our secret investor
club where we will obtain glory.
And you know, I think it was Steve was red-pilling me.
We're all going to be billionaires.
Indeed, indeed.
Steve was red-pilling me, I believe, or maybe it was Ethan, I forget.
On the whole, there are online communities where people coordinate on stuff.
That's gay.
I don't want to do that.
It's too much work and too uncool, not interested.
If we have even like two or three people, our odds of turning the profit are, like, enormous.
Yeah, no doubt.
It's like incredibly unlikely.
Cassey hooked me up.
Cassey had the big spike, 315 bells per turnip.
Ooh, the profits were out of this world, paid off my house experience immediately.
Seika messaged me this week to say that her price has spiked to, like, 400, but I didn't
have any bells.
I didn't have any bells at the time.
I did get a spike that big once in the past, but I didn't have as many bells to invest
at the time.
I think I only had, like, 200k invested or something.
It was a huge win-fall at the time, but it's nothing compared to what I expect this week.
It was bringing me back to watching the stock market in Endless War, all those years ago,
the glory days, and sparring in the dojo, investing your slime and slime coin, watching
that market rise.
And one final question, Oben.
Is there actually, lol, he's dead, guys, epic.
Is there much to be gained with the amount of bells that one had, like, the millions
and millions?
What do you actually do with those?
That's been my only question.
I mean, mainly, you would just buy, I mean, there are some furniture items that are, like,
obscenely expensive, like, in the hundreds of thousands of bells.
So, I mean, if I wanted, if I wanted, like, you know, like, 20 grandfather clocks or something,
then I might actually need, like, millions of bells to do that.
Okay, okay, fair enough.
Yeah.
So it's not, it's not like, it's, I mean, if you hit, like, 10 million bells, then you're
probably at the point where, like, there's not much that I can't do anymore.
Right, right.
But I'm not quite there.
I was even thinking of, like, maybe, like, actually, this is one thing.
Where everyone harassed Steve online, because Steve has more privilege than anyone else in
the world playing Animal Crossing, because Kazian for me, he has the recipe for Sakura
lanterns.
He's the only man I know.
And these are the most beautiful, like, pink, glowing, made with the Sakura petals from
Spring Lanterns.
And now I understand the cruel, cruel mistress that is the, what is it, the making shit system
in this game, the DIY recipe system.
And I want those Sakura lanterns, and even having infinite money, like, I don't even
know if anyone would want all that money.
You have to have something to trade them, I guess.
I just barely missed my chance to learn from one of Ethan's villagers a recipe for a golden
candelabra, which I'm a little disappointed by, but, you know, I came home and my best
friend, Carlos, who I now have a poster hanging of in my main foyer, because he's my bro, he's
the coolest guy.
I assume he has a poster of you, too, I would hope.
I should...
Oh, oh no.
Maybe you can give him one?
What does this mean?
I mean, yeah, obviously he does.
Yeah, of course.
Okay, good.
Well, I mean, but he wears the jacket that I gave him, like, half the time.
That goes a long way.
And, you know, he looks really great.
Like, his girth is, like, stuffed into it in a very flattering way.
Fantastic.
But he gave me a recipe for, like, an iron, like, doorcrest, which is like a shield.
It's like black iron with, like, a shield with lions, and it looks so fucking sick.
It's way better than any golden candelabra.
Sick.
So, yeah, I only got...
The only, like, Sakura recipe I got was, like, the Sakura Pondstone, which is, like, dumb.
It sucks.
I think I have one of those.
It's okay.
Yeah, I didn't...
I didn't...
You know, I caught Sakura pedals.
Like, I didn't, like, I was no slouch about catching them.
I don't know why I didn't get more recipes, because, like, there were some that looked
really nice, like the Sakura lanterns and the Sakura bag was pretty good.
But, like, I don't know, I guess I missed my chance until next March or whatever.
Until the cruel question looms its head, now that I'm bored, is it finally time to start
time traveling?
Oh, that's what I'm thinking.
Right now, I'm able to hold off the demons.
My switch owner said his condition for us playing on his island was, you can do whatever
you want, but no time traveling.
But perhaps a Judas, a Brutus, backstabbing.
It's for fake gamers, he said.
And we signed the pact in blood that we wouldn't be fake gamers.
Well, understandable, understandable.
The quest continues onward for Animal Crossing Dominance and Supremacy.
We should've played the jingle.
Okay, whatever.
Bum, bub, bub, Ben St. Animal Crossing Hour.
Bruh, bruh, bruh, bruh.
And I have a lot of, and I have a lot of black roses and a lot of purple ones too.
And I gave Kazi some black and pink ones, because she wanted them, and it was cool.
And that's the story.
Ah, fascinating as always.
Eleazar, put in timestamp this moment in the description.
Podcast starts here.
No.
Lord of Ghost, Lord of Ghost chapter seven is out.
Act two is finished.
Oh, I read it and I loved it.
I have not read Act seven yet.
Acts, you mean chapter seven, but yes.
Okay, yes, sure.
It's, it's, it's, it's really cool.
Don't say Act seven.
I have bad connotations with Act seven.
Wait, Act seven is actually okay.
That's the one page flash, right?
Act six is the bad one.
Uh, yes.
Okay, all right.
No mind.
Would be fine if Act six didn't exist.
Right, right.
You are right.
It's always been my opinion.
Okay.
Read Lord of Ghosts, everybody.
It is great and I did love it.
And the events that transpire, I will not spoil, but who, baby, it's great.
I really like it.
Yeah, it's, it's, it was a start of the little like, I wonder if I could make it
like a real comic sort of thing.
And it's, it's pretty, it's pretty close to something that's like, yeah, you
know, like actually good people saying, oh my God, I didn't realize you had any
talents at all.
Lol.
Lol, haha, dude, I say that all the time.
Um, I'm tempted to, I'm tempted to ignore you guys for a while and go read it
right now on, on the podcast, haha, but not tell you that I'm doing that or
anything.
Well, that would be so crazy if you did that, but it's not that long.
So it wouldn't be that big of a deal.
Yeah.
Well, I will, I will say that for now, for the next three or so months, it's
going on hiatus for a very specific, important reason that I am going to apply
for the Tezuka Award contest thing, manga contest show in Japan.
I will submit a manga and I have to make that in three months, which is why I
can't really work on Lord of Ghosts because the maximum page, I'm already
way over that with Lord of Ghosts.
It's like almost a hundred pages now.
I see, I see.
How, so to tell me about the specifics, I'm very curious about this and how, how
you plan to go about it, just technically speaking.
Right.
So the Tezuka thing, it's the 100th anniversary of the thing.
If you, it's the thing, it's, and they're opening it up to Spanish speaking, English
speaking, I think Chinese and Korean speaking countries for the first time.
So it's always been a Japanese manga contest.
Aitra Oda submitted famously.
And you got second place, second place, baby.
Yeah, I have no, I have no like delusions of grandeur that I'm ever going to get
anywhere close because it's like, there's so many people who could enter and
there's so much talent out there.
But I think it would not be, it would be pretty cringe if I didn't try just
because of that.
So I'm going to, I'm going to take an idea.
I've come up with a little, little plot and I'm going to make a 30 page manga.
It has to read right to left, but they will translate it for you before it
gets sent to the Japanese where they will judge it.
I don't expect, I, the way I'm expecting it to happen, there's no like
information, but like the judges include Akira Toriyama and Aitra Oda and some
other people that I can't remember the names of.
So like if it gets to them and my comic appears in front of them, that would be
incredible, but I feel like there's, there's only five of them.
Let me just get the link to the thing.
Sure, sure.
I assume they probably won't like read every single one.
There's probably got to be some filter before it gets to those guys.
There's got to be a filter.
So here it is.
So the people is Aitra Oda, Kazue Kato, Kohei Hirokoishi.
I can't see his names, but they're notable people, obviously.
Yeah, yeah.
Looks like the creators of Bokunohiro, Slam Dunk.
I don't know.
Is that fucking sorted on?
I don't know what that is.
One piece, Dragon Ball and Blue Exorcist, Kazue Kato.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
I've just arrived at a twist in a certain webcomic that I am not currently
reading while you discuss something that I haven't been paying attention to.
Does it have anything to do with a problematic creature?
Yes.
OK, all right, all right.
Probably.
You could probably say that about a lot of things, though.
Well, I think there'd be a more obvious yes.
If it's OK, maybe I'm wrong.
OK, anyway, I think.
Oh, no, I see what she's mean.
I see what she's mean.
OK, no, that wasn't even the one I was talking about.
Oh, fuck.
All right, Jesus, fucking Christ.
Oh my God, I just want to say, since you're OK, I won't I won't spoil it.
But like the way that you do the very end of that chapter, you build it up
and you just you just give that little joke at the end.
Perfect.
Mwah, the best.
You don't end on a big, gay, total thing.
It's the I love it.
I just love the way that was done.
That's why you're going to win the Tezuka Award.
I believe in you.
The whole thing is a big, gay, total thing.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Well, yeah, they got the.
Japanese people, I hope that it would get to them,
but I'm pretty sure there's going to be like thousands of other people
vetting, like choosing the wheat from the chaff.
Got to be, got to be.
Hopefully, these guys will probably see the finalists get me far.
I don't I don't I don't want to try and be like, oh, I have to be Japanese
and exactly like everyone else if I want to win.
Right, you just got to be cool.
Yeah, that's what that's what I'm sure that's true.
Thinking back to his style and how he's always been like very different.
You know, it's it's funny.
There's definitely like a generic anime look like the A1 pictures look
that we're all familiar with.
And of these, like the blue exorcist one is I think that's Kazue Kato or whatever.
I think that's who that is.
Like that one is a little bit close to it.
I mean, Slam Dunk a little bit, but Slam Dunk's always had like very kind of
realistic and I don't know, cool masculine art and maybe Deku a little bit.
But even like, like all the others have very distinct styles.
And like, sure, Dragon Ball has gone on to like influence a ton,
but it has a very different style for a lot of these birds studio.
Bird Studio, I mean, I was I looked at the picture of Goku expecting to see
Toriyama. If you scroll down a little bit,
you'll see a picture of the six judges and their names are Kira Toriyama.
Oh, cool, cool.
It's got to be like, but I'm saying, I don't see a Kira Toriyama.
It says, I scroll down and his name is there.
Oh, in comments from the judges or something.
Yeah. Oh, in the article, I see. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Well, in any case, yes, as long as it's good,
I mean, I can't speak to the rest of these guys necessarily,
but I am sure that Oda is at least open minded to appreciate all different
types of styles and they probably all are.
These guys are comic artists, right? They know what's up.
They've been around the block a few times.
So very, very exciting.
Yeah. So I just want to read Slam Dunk.
Slam Dunk looks so cool.
I love the art from Slam Dunk.
But yeah, I'm going to be doing that for the next three months.
I it's going to probably be very like a lot of ghosts is built off
of ratty fuckers cop killers.
You know, it has that law already going into it.
This is going to be a completely unique story that has to be built
from the ground up with characters and stuff.
So I'm hoping I can do that.
You've done it before with a canon story once or twice.
Yeah, you know, I look at it.
I could just submit that really.
Just submit that I'm really excited to see what you produce.
Do you know the like the hard deadline for like when you need to have it done
to turn in or whatever first of September?
OK, OK, shit, dog.
That's really exciting and I can't wait to see what you produce.
I mean, I'm tempted to say, maybe I should join.
I should submit something too.
But like do it. I don't know.
I mean, maybe if I think of something that I want to do with that, I would.
But if I don't, then I won't.
And then that's what I have to say about that.
Fair enough. Fair enough.
So, so, Ben, you've you've read the chapter now.
What do you think of the Lord of Ghost chapter seven?
What do I think of the Lord of Ghost chapter seven?
I think that it's the final nail in the coffin.
I think that it's like a personal attack or something.
Christ, I hate it.
I hate that fucking much.
I will end you.
I think I don't know.
I think it's based, but not very breadpilled.
And that's what I have to say about that.
There's two criteria you've got to meet.
And if you meet one and not the other, dead, dead.
Wait, I'm just clicking through the end of the end part now.
Lo Dan.
He read it fast.
He's just looking at the pretty pictures.
He doesn't know the lore.
He doesn't know the the pathos, the ups and downs, this fucking guy.
I chose the name.
Oh, yeah, let's just wait for Ben to finish rereading the chapter.
That sounds like they're discussing the name.
And I've got to see, OK, what else do they say about the name?
After I got to that part, I kind of skipped ahead.
OK, OK, what's the short way to say the name of the the town?
New, New, Biggin by the sea, aka Neo York, right?
Yeah, I mean, I can't think how to.
New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New, New.
By the sea, aka Neo York, it'll be butsakini.
Butsakini.
It's like Osaka, but different, but London, butsakini will sick.
There it is.
We'll put that in the show notes so everybody could see that.
Well, this is fucking based.
It continues.
It continues to be my favorite content on the Internet.
Hell, yeah, I can't think of anything better right now.
Oh, perhaps with one small check, though, it is a different sort of thing.
And it is. All right.
We guys, we got to address the big thing, the big elf in the room that we've been
beating our ourselves around.
Of course, the big beating our me too, got to stop, got to stop ignoring it.
We have to talk about the new Plinkett video that came out about Star Trek Picard and how it was based.
All right, here's my hot take.
I felt like this was a kind of a bad Plinkett review in so far as it doesn't contain
all the necessary context in order for you to really understand what's happening.
And I didn't really feel like I understood what the reason for it existing is, because it feels like
it's just sort of saying a little bit extra on top of those reviews that they did of the show.
I understood the context, but it's because I've been watching the reviews.
So I basically had all this information already.
Yeah, I watched the reviews as well, but like I won't go back to watch this Plinkett review
because I need to watch the reviews as well in order to really get it.
Like it doesn't stand as well on its own.
That's that's my point, you know, I mean, I've been following this with great interest.
And I've rewatched those the reviews on Plinkett like many times, because I mean, I am a huge
I got into Star Trek due to Red Letter Media's Plinkett reviews of the like the old movies,
like the next generation movies and stuff.
And I love those.
And they're basically a very similar style of content to what this is.
So like to me, it was kind of like a return to the classic old Plinkett from way back.
And, you know, maybe it's true that they like those ones do a better job of explaining the context.
But those weren't built on the back of like existing reviews that had already been done.
So perhaps it's slightly different context or whatever.
I also just happenstance.
Like I've been rewatching, re listening to all of the Plinkett reviews.
Star Wars Awakens, the original Phantom Menace and all that.
And I've noticed that there are a few that I like to rewatch.
And there are a few that I just they don't stand up like the Titanic one.
You know, it's OK, Indiana Jones.
That's all right.
The Ghostbusters one is really good.
That one feels like a full like it feels like it's not just here's some bad
media and here's me talking about why it sucks.
It's like a bigger thing than that, because there's a lot of stuff
around the Ghostbusters movie to talk about, right, right.
And, you know, the original the original Plinkett reviews were about
the prequel trilogy of Star Wars and how people don't realize that it sucks so much.
And he's trying to explain to everyone that George Lucas is a hack fraud.
And he's right.
There's much more to those.
Yeah, like it's not just bad movies.
It's like George Lucas was never that good, actually.
Empire was the one he had the least to do with creatively and all that sort of stuff.
Star Wars Awakens review is about the fact that Disney is a terrible company
and is going to ruin our lives forever, not just the Force Awakens review.
So like things like Baby's Day Out, the Titanic.
Don't hold up this Picard one.
I feel falls into that.
I'm probably not going to rewatch it that much.
So it's still fine, but like some of the jokes also were a bit.
I don't know, forced.
He made a poop joke once.
Oh, but that's classic.
It's classic.
But I feel like there wasn't enough of it to be.
If you know what I mean, like you just threw it in there because
Oh, Plinkett's supposed to say, oh, shit, joke.
Let's put this one.
Definitely, I mean, it definitely was a little more bare bones in like the
I would say like the Plinkett lore and the comedy.
It was more of a straightforward discussion of the series.
And then there was like some funny bits like the what was that intergalactic treaty
intergalactic and it's really funny.
I'm watching Star Trek Voyager right now.
It is a huge.
OK, I don't know the full Star Trek lore post Voyager,
but like this this show takes place probably a few decades after Voyager ends or whatever.
And but the idea of a transgalactic treaty, as mentioned in that, I mean,
since I'm currently experiencing Voyager for the first time, the entire conceit
of Voyager is that they are so far away and the galaxies divided into quadrants
in Star Trek for I don't know how that works, but that's how it is.
And they're in the Delta Quadrant and they're trying to get back to the Alpha
Quadrant, where like all of Star Trek took place.
And they are 70,000 light years away.
And there are various types of they call it trans warp, like like faster
than the hard limits beyond the faster and the speed of light that warp travel
gives them that would make journeys like that potentially possible.
But like the idea of a transgalactic treaty that there can be no like
synthetic life is it's just one of those things that any Star Trek person would
immediately be like, you're telling me that the like the Romulans and the
Klingons and the human, the entire Federation and the fucking Vorta and the
fucking Founders in the fucking Delta, that's the Gamma Quadrant of the fucking
Dominion, they all agreed to not make sense.
Very silly, very silly idea.
It's it's it's a it's a game of thrones.
It takes two minutes to sail all the way to the fucking.
Yes, it's very much like that.
Like they don't understand the scale.
I mean, I'm not a Star Trek person, so I don't know any of that.
And I don't feel like Plinkett made it like abundantly clear how ridiculous that was.
I don't blame you or anybody else who feels that this video was a little bit
like lacking in the punch or more of the Plinkett stuff they would love.
But for me, it's because these guys become a deep or Star Trek guy.
Sure, sure, that's fine.
But it's just that I brought the context with me because I know all these
characters and I've explored it over the last like the last like five years have
been me getting ready for this video.
So like I have been fully prepared watching like all these shows during that time.
And it was just in time to consume this.
So I recognize I'm in a slightly different position from from people who who have not.
But for me, it was a big coom after after a long time.
But, you know, there's another personal element that I appreciated.
It was that this video was made in a very fast period of time.
It is like a real Plinkett video.
You know, maybe it's not one of the best like wouldn't be rated by critics
throughout history is like the best.
OK, understandable.
But they made a real Plinkett video after finishing Picard
like a month or two ago and they got it together.
I thought it was pretty great in a lot of ways, really impressed.
And I just find that inspiring as a guy who struggles to get content out.
It made me feel like, you know what, Nate, maybe you don't really need to like overthink.
And of course, the video instantly gets a million views.
And it's it is like the best.
Even if you love the reviews of Picard, which I do, I absolutely love them.
And I've watched them many times.
This video is the best condensation of the arguments, basically.
And, you know, it's got extra style and pizzazz.
And I love the little gimmicks that they put in there.
I take a lot of inspiration from that personally.
So I will continue to suck Red Letter Media's Dick.
This hit really well for me personally.
But I get if you were to rank in some cosmic order, what are the best Plinkett reviews?
This probably would not be the top based on like everybody's experience of it.
But for me, it just hit the right spot.
And I really got a lot of good feels out of it.
You know, no.
Delicious Keto ice cream.
Can't get enough of that wonderful stuff, baby.
But wondering, Nate, about like your
your workflow, like, how's how's how's that working out for you?
How are you dealing with making stuff at the moment?
Well, I mean, since deciding to shift the way that I'm releasing content,
I have I know I've talked about it here and there, but just in summary,
I've I basically fully committed to a process
where both I have multiple videos in the works.
I have like two at least two scripts basically being worked on at any one time
with my editor, no need for like just doing the edits on
like the visual edits after I've done like the the writing and the mixing and all that stuff.
I sent off to him.
He's working on that while I'm working on a separate one.
And that's like a separate script that's been
whatever, prepared like I'm editing that with all my little autistic touches and whatnot.
And basically, I think that right now I'm setting myself up for
a much improved rate of output with higher quality videos.
And I am pretty close to having stuff ready to release with this like updated workflow.
So basically, I know it doesn't look like it right now.
There's been no results of this change yet.
I'm very keenly aware of that.
But I think that in the next like two to three months,
people will see a change in the output specifically with the way I'm doing things.
And I think a lot of people are going to be like, oh, shit,
this is like this is like classic Nate stuff and we're getting it like faster than ever.
We no longer need to wait like six months between videos.
Now I'm getting one like every month or whatever, or maybe even sooner.
So, you know, again, like I don't want to do that thing where I'm just talking up about,
oh, it's going to be so great soon, guys, just wait and see.
It's but I do have a lot of confidence that with the changes I've made
and having having another edit I'm working with.
And if I could get like even another editor
who I would also happily pay and work with and stuff,
then I would probably have three projects be working on at once.
And ultimately, I would love to get to that position as well.
Just have more people to work with.
But but for now, I'm pretty damn confident that
at least my patrons will be will be happy boys pretty soon with my output.
And really, the patrons are all that matter.
Yeah, there you go. That's that's my thoughts on that.
OK, you know, speaking of content,
you know, man, OK, so this is weird.
I was going to bring this up, but now I have a final twist to put on it.
I was I tweeted angrily the other day
about how no new episodes of Mon Ben have gotten translated recently.
Orisao and now Kinoman Ben, which I've talked about before.
I probably do I need to explain what that is again?
Just would you quickly?
Briefly, this guy, Orisao Nauke, is a mangaka
who has done a bunch of pretty famous manga.
He did 20th Century Boys and yeah, there's a couple.
He did Pluto that they talked about in the show,
but I don't think that one was is like as well known.
Yeah, it's it's not.
There's a there's a couple others.
I mean, he's done a lot for getting them.
But you know, Pluto, I read that one.
It's pretty good. Which one? Huh. It's about it's called Pluto.
It's about robots. I like that one. OK.
20th Century is my favorite by him.
And it's like there's like four seasons of the show.
And in every episode, he places cameras in the like work
station or the workplace of other mangaka films them for a week.
And then most of the show is like there's a there's like a narrator
who sort of narrates like what you're seeing, like they'll talk about
like the kind of pen they're using or like what goes on, what's going on.
They'll sort of get this narrator will like give context to the footage
and also give like commentary on the conversation that they have.
And they basically Urasawa Naoki and whichever one he's got this week,
they'll like sit down and sort of like have a conversation where they watch
the footage and like sort of talk about like, oh, you do this.
Oh, you do that. Like, oh, I noticed this about like, oh, that's like,
well, don't don't you think don't you think artists are kind of like this?
Like, yeah, yeah, the thing about art is that it's all about fetishism.
Every time I draw the male clavicle, you know, like that's the secret fetishism
coming out. Yes, art truly is the most the most honorable of professions.
Indeed.
Anyway, there's like there's like 16 episodes, right?
It's four seasons and each season is like four episodes.
And I think there's a pilot.
So there's 17 episodes.
But we were missing one, two, three, four, five.
There's like six, six episodes that I never found.
And they're they're not in order.
It's not like the last six.
It's like one from season two, two from season three, three from season four.
I can't find them anywhere.
There is this one guy who's uploaded the ones that exist on this daily motion
channel called Habanero S. And that's where I found all of them.
And actually, since making that tweet, I found one more.
I think it is season two, episode four.
It's one that I had not seen before.
So I did find a new one, but it was uploaded on another daily
motion channel that is named Naoki Urasawa.
So it might even be the guy himself uploaded this one as like a sample or something.
OK, so I found that other one, right?
But there's still five episodes that I've never seen, don't seem to exist
anywhere on the Internet.
And I'm like, God, somebody fucking dropped the ball or or there was or
maybe there was a copyright issue or something.
And but just now, as I was thinking about this, I see this tweet from
Echophoria, who replies to the tweet saying, I know, right?
The last I heard the guy doing the translator was undergoing chemo.
I'm afraid to say it, but he might have died.
Jesus Christ.
So that's wild.
I wonder I don't know how that's that's such a specific fact to know.
I wonder how they know that.
But or where they heard that from.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know. Maybe it's not true.
But in terms of how it affects me personally, it sort of doesn't matter
if it's true or not.
It seems at this point that unless somebody else steps up and does something,
I might never get to watch the rest of Mon Ben.
They have some time in time.
Someone someone will take.
I hope so.
Hopefully I fucking hope so.
They have, man, they probably they probably already translated the one
with the most famous people like they did.
Um, yeah, they did the Junji, the Junji Ito one got translated like last year.
And there's another one with, um, fuck, I've always forget his name,
but the guy who did Poon Poon.
Yeah, yeah, I forget his name, too.
They did one with the guy who did Poon Poon, Inio?
Inio? God, I don't know.
I don't remember at all.
And and the guy who did, I think they did one with the guy
who did I am a hero, the zombie one.
Yeah, yeah.
OK, I know that one.
And there's a couple others that I had never heard of anywhere else before,
but maybe they're more popular in Japan.
It's such a good show.
It's so interesting.
My favorite one is the guy who draws like another one I'd never heard of,
but he does like very like he's like totally into like just action shown and stuff.
Like that's all he does.
And he's like an older guy, but his work, like.
There is like this this woman,
the one like the first episode that's other than the pilot is about this woman.
And she is like incredibly prolific.
She pumps out like a new like 30 page chapter like every week.
Sometimes she does it on like multiple stories, running concurrently.
And she's got like a huge team.
She's got like eight assistants.
They all work in this little office and they're all like
they're all like running around with like folders and like like like pens and pencils
and like just doing little like jobs and stuff.
And it's kind of it's it's it's pretty assembly line.
And that but that's cool.
But then there's this other guy, this the shonen guy, his workspace.
He just it's just him and three assistants just sitting at a table
and they play like heavy metal music all the whole time.
And like the rule is like no silence.
Like we've got it like we're like the atmosphere has got to be like upbeat.
We got to be like cracking jokes the whole time.
Just like having a good fucking time while we do this.
And they're just like passing pages around.
And like that's he's my he's my favorite.
He's my favorite dude.
That's cool.
What a great fucking program.
And what a shame if I don't get to see the other five episodes.
That is a fascinating idea.
Yeah, I should watch the show.
I'm just remembering that when Munchie came to London as depicted
in Lord of Ghost Comic, but also in real life.
Spoilers, dude. Spoilers, spoilers.
Spoilers, dude.
When when Munchie came to London, we went to I think it was the British Museum.
Something there was a a manga exhibit
and you go in and there's a bunch of like original pages.
Like we we saw the the page in one piece
where Luffy remembers that he has friends after the the Marion Ford War and all that.
Ah, yes, like that actual page.
I could see how he shaded in the the hair.
I was like, whoa, it's right.
It's just right there. Hell yeah.
Um, lots of cool stuff.
And then also on a TV was Man Ben and it was subtitled.
And I'm like, wait, is there an official subtitled version of this?
It was just on a it was just on a loop on it on a on a on a on a TV
and a little thing next to it saying Man Ben is a show where it goes around to
manga authors. I was like, oh, I know that from Ben St.
Huh. That's you know, I also got the impression that there was an official
subbed version because I saw like the one on the channel called Urasaki
Naoki. I might have say the name wrong.
Naoki, that's right.
Yeah, Naoki, the one on his channel, it's subbed in the exact same way as the
I want to know where this Echoforia person gets their information
because my, yeah, my impression that these were official subs
that had just not been released due to some kind of copyright issue
because there is a website, Naoki.
There, there is a Naoki Urasawa dot com, which you would think is his official
site, but it's not. It says, I'm not Naoki Urasawa.
I'm just a supporter of his work.
On this site, you'll find English subtitled versions of Urasawa, Naoki,
Noman, Ben, the interview series created by himself, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I didn't actually read this, but I should probably.
OK, OK, so he and he has a bunch of episodes posted, but then he updates
on January of last year.
He says NHK flagged his videos for copyright and his YouTube account
got taken down, which I did see and then, but like the videos are still
listed on the web.
There are some of the videos are still listed, but they don't seem to be listed
on YouTube. And when you click them, they don't see not available.
They say publishing in progress, which I've never seen before.
That is strange.
And other ones of them say video on available as though it's a YouTube thing.
That publishing a process might be that thing where with YouTube, if you set it
to automatically be public, but like it goes through a process of first
it uploads and then it processes.
So maybe the video is technically available publicly, but it maybe it's
stuck in that limbo due to copyright.
You'd think it would just finish processing and then say blocked on
copyright grounds or whatever.
I mean, the fact that I have never seen this message on any YouTube video
makes me think that it's not that.
Yeah, you might be right.
But I don't know what it is.
Anyway, anyway, the point is that my impression was that these were
officially subtitled episodes that were just being distributed, you know,
underground and that had been like claimed by the copyright holder.
You should ask that.
But maybe if I went information, but maybe if I went and I watched the end of
like, if I actually looked at the subtitles, you know how the subbers will
like include their like subber credits?
Yeah, yeah, right.
I could probably find out if I just watched and paid attention.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
And then maybe I could go look them up and find their blog where they say,
hey, guys, I'm undergoing chemo and I might die.
And then the blog goes silent.
I go, oh, that would be.
Interesting information.
Yeah, that'd be.
Yeah, totally.
Oh, no, please.
All right, well, that's that's all well and good.
Let's see what happened with that.
But seriously, we're glad to that guy.
Maybe there's he could probably just hook you up.
Is is my maybe if he has information,
unless he's just talking Abel Salute out of his ass, doesn't know where he's
getting all I was just asking, like, where did you get this information?
Gonna need a link, bro.
Gonna need a source fam.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fuck you.
Yeah, fuck you.
Indeed.
Oof, hmm.
Well, should we talk about Digi?
That's, you know, that's the thing.
I mean, I was asking about she's a woman now.
Well, there's not much to say.
There's definitely not that much to say.
You would think there'd be more to say.
But I mean, yeah, I can acknowledge it.
I mean, OK, I guess I will say that.
I thought it was a joke.
Digi also seems that she phrases a joke.
No doubt at first.
She needed to clarify that no, actually, I know it sounded like a joke
when I said it the first time, but no, this is serious.
And I asked her in the discord, I said, hey, is this real?
Or is this like a ruse?
And she said, no, this is real.
And I said, all right, well, I will match your level of dedicate.
I will take it as seriously as you do.
So if you're serious about it, then OK, fair enough.
And that seems to be the case.
And she thought I was saying like she said like, oh, you know,
I will say funny, funny, funny.
This is before that she made the posts about it,
being a girl or whatever.
I had post, wait, no, I can't say it.
It's a spoiler.
Spoiler, OK.
You know what I'm talking about.
Oh, I do know what you're talking about.
Yeah, is that a spoiler?
I'm going to say yes.
We've got to keep that in mind.
No particular reason.
I posted a female character in the discord
that was based on myself for some reason.
Shut up.
And I was like.
Oh, you cut all that.
Cut all this.
Don't cut all that.
It needs content.
It's fine.
Look, don't worry about it.
And a 10 of viewers will be rewarded with nuggets of information
that they can piece together bits of the puzzle.
And I posted that.
And Digi was like, is this your trans sona?
And I was like, lol, no.
I mean, I thought it was a joke.
But no.
And then later, she said, oh, OK, no.
I actually thought this was a legit trans sona.
I didn't realize what it was actually for.
And I was like, lol, what a silly mistake to make.
And then when I said, OK, I will match your level of dedication
to this.
And Digi said, oh, you mean you're
going to be dedicated to being feminine?
And I was like, no, no.
I mean, to you being feminine.
It's spreading like a virus, boys and girls.
What they tell you is all true.
Digi just now, Digi has the trans agenda.
And she wants to spread it.
And she wants to spread it and propagate it.
She wants to sink her claws into me and turn her,
turn me into a genus.
All I see.
As well.
I turn my gaze out.
All I see is eggs.
For the fate of the white race, we must resist.
All I see is heroic trans individuals and eggs.
And except, of course, in over 30-year-old women.
Now they have no eggs at all, of course.
Yes.
It's just science, guys.
But yeah.
Delicious, delicious eggs.
So that's my story.
That's my struggle with Digi coming out as trans.
This is how this has affected me.
And I will persevere.
And if you want to support me in my endeavors,
in spite of all the hardship I face,
patreon.com.com.
Slash, Ben Sains, to help me get through this trying time.
Thanks very much.
It's kind of funny.
There isn't really much to say about it.
It's just sort of like, oh, cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But there were a lot of people.
I was curious why so many people said, oh,
I've seen this coming for a million years.
This is bound to happen eventually.
Lol, I saw it coming.
And I'm like, I didn't.
Do I not know Digi well enough?
Am I stupid?
Did I not pick up on all these things that they say?
Don't you remember all the times
that Digi talked about wanting to be a little girl?
I just thought that was an anime thing.
I just thought that was a hymn thing.
I mean, it could be.
It could be.
But I heard people say Digi is an egg.
And I thought, I guess I could see it.
And now it was true.
And I'm like, yeah, not a huge shock, I guess.
Yeah, I'm not too shocked.
It's just like I'm a little confused
as why I couldn't see the signs or what.
I don't know.
I mean, visibly outwardly, Digi's always
presented pretty male.
Or that seems to have been due to sheer laziness, which
hey, we all do, right?
The biology there is male.
Got a beard and whatnot.
What can you do?
So I mean, who can say what's going on in a person's head?
So I don't know.
Yeah, not that surprising.
I mean, she said, you say, a person says,
I want to be a girl a whole bunch of times.
Like what?
Like, you know.
Yeah, but who doesn't?
I mean, Digi personally has been like
confused specifically.
I mean, you know.
What man has not wondered what it would be
like to be the other sex for just at least a day?
I guess.
Indeed, indeed.
Nate, I missed what you said.
I don't know.
Nothing important.
I mean, Digi has constantly expressed confusion.
So I mean, I don't think it's crazy to be like,
okay, who knows exactly how this will pan out?
Again, it seems like a pretty reasonable way to turn out,
but yeah, that's it.
Anyway, anyway, all this is to say
that she's kicked off the podcast.
Yeah, she's.
That's correct.
Okay, now.
And we kind of buy that.
Looking forward to the makeup tutorials and the,
you know, the, what is it?
Well, where do girls shop?
Girl, clothing, hall,
girl, store.
Women be shopping.
They be shopping, man.
And it's disgusting.
Yeah.
Prepare to receive the white hot lens of my misogyny.
And it's going to come in hot and hard.
So be prepared.
Okay.
But like women, am I right?
What's going to be really embarrassing is that,
you know, when we have Raek on five
and we do our customary like gay orgy,
it's not going to be gay anymore.
There's going to be a woman there.
Oh, gross.
Well, now it's not funny.
No, canceled.
Well, hey, Digi did say that Fuda was the preferred
identity of choice.
So Fuda is somewhere on the gay spectrum, right?
Um.
I'm going to go with a yeah.
Oh, wait.
I mean, I don't know.
Hotly debated, I guess.
It is debated.
One day the scholars will inform us,
but we'll just have to wonder until then.
Well, I mean, there you go.
You jackals.
There's your hot takes on the trans question.
Asked and answered.
We saw it.
How much you say?
We sorted it.
Yep.
Settled the issue.
I mean, hey, that's all I got.
I got voice mails.
Surely something else.
Surely something else must have happened
in my life this week.
Oh, wait.
You're saying something?
It's quarantine.
I was just going to say that I've been rereading Berserk.
Yeah, from the start.
Yeah.
Well, I rewatched the anime,
or rather I watched the anime all the way through
for the first time.
I was like, oh my God, I love this.
It's probably one of my top 10 anime favorites.
It is really good.
It is just exactly what I like in a show.
It's slow and it's epic and it's quiet.
Have you watched the famous bloopers
that are attached to the Berserk anime
and the English dub?
They are the stuff of legend.
Like I have not heard that.
I will acquire for you the link.
The Berserk anime is famous for its blooper reel
or whatever that are wrong takes done to it
and you should definitely check it out.
Berserk anime bloopers.
Cool.
It's like 10 minutes long.
Or no, it's like 40 minutes long.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, here we go.
But yeah, I watched the anime and I was like,
okay, let's read the manga from this point.
Because I've read all the manga all the way anyway.
So I'm rereading it and I'm like, dang,
this is just like, this is so good.
This is how many pen lines is that?
That's like one million little pen lines on that drawing.
How does he do that?
How does his hand not fall off?
I'm just being enamored.
I think it's that one image
in the latest Lord of Ghost chapter
with this lot of shading, a lot of cross-hatching.
That was because I was looking at the part in Berserk
where it's in the holy place with the tower.
With the priest and the, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and it was, it's like night is falling
and all of the big scary gloop monsters
are sucking up everyone and climbing the tower
and forming a giant hand.
It's just like that.
It's like so fucking visceral,
so fucking well-drawn, every fucking frame, a painting.
I love Berserk.
It's so much of an inspiration to me.
I think about it constantly now.
I'm just, I just, if there could be anything
I could do in my life, it would be to draw Berserk.
That's plus one to the list of the things I just want to do.
I want to draw one piece, draw Berserk and draw Homestuck.
Any thoughts?
Oh yeah, go on Ben, go on.
Well, I was going to say,
I also revisited a classic work of massive cultural import
and breathtaking, stunning quality and craftsmanship.
I'm talking, of course, about the entire angry video game,
nerd, videography, I like played the entire fucking series.
I just put on the playlist and let it go
for like a whole week.
Did you listen to the series videos like hours long?
Yeah, yeah, the ones that are the entire series
put together in one video, right?
Yeah, those are great.
Yep, I just, that's what I've been sort of like having on
for like the past, however many days or whatever.
It's so easy to just do all of them when you start,
but like watching many of them.
Like, it is, it's like, they just kind of,
it doesn't really feel like one ends
and a new one begins a lot of the time.
Really?
Sometimes it does, other times it doesn't.
Yeah, a lot of the endings are like really abrupt
and don't really like, I think a lot of the time
he just ends an episode with like taking a dump on the game
and then the next episode just ends with him
like talking about, so this game is a piece of shit
and it feels, and it makes me feel like a piece of donkey
doodoo hurled out of a grizzly bear's vagina.
And what were they thinking?
What were they thinking?
That's a good one.
I don't know, but you should have that as one of your sounds.
I'm adding it to my note,
the what were they thinking anime video?
What were they thinking?
I've been saying that.
The anime video game nerd, that's gonna be me, yes.
The anime video game nerd, that's pretty good.
That's right, Konnichiwa, fucku-faisu, fucku this game.
Sakuwe fucku of Shinobi Dick.
If he's the anime video game nerd,
he's not gonna be angry, he's gonna be anime.
Yeah, he's just a video game nerd who has-
He's just a nerd who is an anime anime.
If only I had this much sound, but I'd play it.
Well, okay, this one works.
When he's angry instead of screaming
or when he's playing a video game, instead he goes,
Yeah, you give us one of those, you know?
Yeah.
We'd also do that, doke doke, yo!
You know that one.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The one that- That's a classic.
The one that you hear at the beginning
of the pastel defender heliotrope game.
And you hear at the beginning of Jiraiyo's theme
and the Naruto artist theme.
I don't care about that.
Watch my fucking J.D. Jennifer Dayan Wright's lecture
and at the beginning, there's the game interlude
where you see the video game that has a yo-hoo, whatever.
Yo-hoo!
It's a kabuki thing.
Little kabuki theater fucking sound effects
and she mixed with like pinball video game noises.
Legendary, aesthetic experience.
Bass.
I should add that.
It's so fucking good.
You should add that, that's a good one.
You should add the entirety of Berserk to your soundboard.
That's a good idea.
Auto play.
I have, I did remember one more thing that happened to me.
More thing that happened to me this week.
I ordered more, remember how I was making gummy worms?
Of course, of course.
But then I ran out of that syrup
and the distributatively weren't selling it anymore
for mysterious reasons.
Right, right.
Well, I have good and bad news.
I ordered the powdered form of it, not the syrup form.
That's the good news, I got the stuff again.
The kind of bad news is I was like,
what is the relation of this syrup to the powder?
Is the syrup just the powder dissolved in water?
I don't know.
So I tried just mixing it in water and it kind of worked?
Like it did mix and it did give the gummies like more of that.
I think maybe I put too much in because like,
I don't know, there might be a balance to be struck here
because I tried using this stuff.
It did give them more of a gummi-ish texture.
It gave them too much of a gummi-ish texture.
They were like very sticky
and they didn't hold together very well.
And also, but also it didn't mix perfectly.
And there were sort of like kind of like the bottoms of them
were kind of a little bit hard and chewy.
And sometimes there were even like kind of lumps in them
that you couldn't even really chew at all.
And it was a little unpleasant.
So there's work to do.
There's work to do on getting it right with this powdered form.
But we'll get there.
We'll get there boys.
And one day maybe we'll return to the Promised Land.
That sweet, sweet tapioca-soluble fiber syrup
once it returns to the internet wave stores.
And that will be-
I'm looking forward to it.
Was that it?
There we go.
Classic.
Base.
I love Japan period.
Well hey, I guess for voicemails
because I've said all I have to say.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to go.
All right let's do it.
Let me see here.
Where did I put them?
Oh the chocobay.
Oh that's not a voicemail.
that's the Joker baby easy to confuse let me say okay here we go here we go
my favorite part of the Joker movie is when Joaquin Phoenix turns to look
directly into the camera and says now I have become the Joker hmm now we did it
Batman now we finally became this face now this face is the mask the makeup is
my true self I don't I actually haven't seen it he might very well say that I
haven't seen it I meant to see it but I never got around to it I don't watch
any movie base animal I'm a Philistine what are you I have a movie I think I'm I
think it's like a depression thing where I like don't appreciate art anymore of
any kind the thought of it sickens me except the Lord of Ghosts the only thing
that doesn't make me feel that way speaking of saturation due to an
overabundance of media if that's not what I was not what I was talking about
alright but depression at least partially induced by hating the universe in
the world and being sad its existence that yeah her to me but before we
discuss that listen to this voicemail called where I put it this is a reverse
nostalgia okay take it away go I had a really strange experience recently so I
like had not played Animal Crossing at all prior to New Horizons coming out and
like I'd played Smash Bros you know and there's like Animal Crossing characters
and stages and music and stuff in there and all of it was just kind of like okay
yeah whatever that's neat to me you like you know it was it was just like okay
it's a game I don't really play but I mean it doesn't it doesn't it's like
whatever but now after having played Animal Crossing New Horizons I get like
almost all of the references and stuff and it like feels so invigorating like
playing Smash Bros again just like to know all the Animal Crossing shit and
like I know that I want to do that for more games now like I haven't played
every single game on the Smash Bros roster but that this experience has made
me want to play more of them just to like get that feeling because like I
would like get all of the like I don't know Mega Man stuff or whatever like
Mario you know yeah because I had played those games and it's like oh yeah
that's like the level from the whatever the character but like there's some that
I just don't even fucking know man like it's crazy I don't even know how to
describe this feeling it's like reverse nostalgia there it is title drop what
it's cool is that I saw it and I clapped that's what you're feeling I know
exactly how it feels I feel the same I played Earthbound long after Smash and
then I was like oh shit I want to go check that out I don't know if I feel the
same way because like a lot of the time like like in um fuck the city the
earthbound city that's it's it's Eagleton right or Eagletown I think it's
on that no no on it Eagland is the name of the country on it is the town you
know you see on it in Smash Bros and it's like all 3d and there's all this
stuff happening you play earthbound and on it is like it's just like some it's
just like some pixelated houses it's like it's like it's not much more than
like a Pokemon town oh yeah yeah but it's fun to when I things are interpreted
I guess but I feel like I would feel the same way about like a Mega Man level or
something or whatever I think what a lot of my experience with this kind of thing
is a lot of the times I'll see something reference as like an important
video game history thing yeah or whatever and then it in the unlikely
chance that I do go back and you know play the thing watch the thing whatever
and get that context a lot of the time my thought is like oh like that's all
it was back then like because it was because a lot of the time if it's
something that's like became famous it at the time was just like a pretty humble
thing that maybe didn't even call much attention to itself you know what I mean
yeah that's true like the town of on it was not like this landmark thing it
wasn't like the game wasn't about it it wasn't fleshed out that much but I guess
just because it was the thing in the game that was such a hit it you know got
recognition and became sort of sort of famous in its own right and then
especially so when they put it in a smith because I needed a setting from the
game what's the setting for Earthbound first one to come to mind on it I guess
okay we'll go with that all right now it's a famous video game location as long
as people don't have some like weird expectation I guess they should like you
should know like okay this game was made like 19 what like 89 I don't know like
like super NES way back in the day you should just keep that in mind you're
like okay like it's not gonna be it's not gonna like blow my mind but then there's
a lot I mean there's a reason people love that game I played it like way later in
life and I absolutely loved it even as like a kid either as like playing game
well earthbound is we're not talking about that's just an example the only
thing I know about earthbound is that it gets really really fucked up and that
there isn't a really fucked up earthbound stage like why is that is it
doesn't it get into like psychic horror almost well there is the the big city
from mother three in in brawl that was put in there and that has like the
chimera which is a big fucking monster I mean they could have done nightside but
like nightside is like a weird version of like what is it forson that city or
whatever I can't remember exactly we're like four cent garbage the one the one
where like yes is no and no is yes yeah yeah that would have been I mean they
only have so many stages and it just reverses all your controls or whatever
yeah fuck you player you just have to you have to ask the smash staz to why
they thought some made for better stages than others but but this question was
not about earthbound I was just using this no no right right we just fine I
mean I totally know what this guy I mean when to city I was coming out the city of
Final Fantasy in like 2008 that along with my longtime fandom of Final Fantasy
I was like okay fuck this I need to now go play like all the final fantasies that
I've missed and then I went back and I think I played like three and I think I
played four and like the I don't know if the sequel to four was out then I'd
already played like five and six I think I think I played like I tried to beat a
but didn't finish here something I don't I played like a bunch because I wanted
like oh yeah like I don't know who the fuck onion knight is I want to know what
onion nights about so I'm gonna go play Final Fantasy 3 turns out like there is
nothing to onion night that's just the default class and it is good and cool
but I mean a better thing is that like in the original dissidia and they fucking
changes for the sequel which is stupid the Bartz's ultimate attack like cloud
has omni slash okay big iconic of course that's ultimate attack Bartz's is
rapid-fire dual-wheeled spellblade which is just a really efficient and strong
combination of powers from Final Fantasy 5 it's like literally called that
which is just like a meta thing that like the community was aware of and it
became like his quote-unquote ultimate attack which is pretty pretty based
pretty cool so I don't know it like and it's fun to just go back and like learn
how such things came to be such that whatever that that's not like really a
cultural touchstone this particular combination of attacks but I mean in the
community it is I don't know whatever I certainly get where this guy's coming
from oh there was another thing I want to say about this guy so that voice is
probably familiar to you ladies and gentlemen because this guy leaves a lot
of voicemails I don't know if he has like a handle or a name I just want to
say for the record this man this this creature left like 16 voicemails this
week and I got to 16 and I'm letting you know I tweeted about this before I just
stopped listening after like I would listen to like 10 seconds oh it's this
guy again don't leave you there's stop don't do that I don't have time to listen
to 16 voicemails from the same person cut it down cut it down is that the same guy
that just did this one yeah that guy I mean this question was fine it was the
first one I heard but then he just went on to do more and more and more and like
some were fine but I just got absolutely bored I was like I'm no I'm not
gonna like they were not like amazing ones each one they were just like hey
I'm thinking about this save it for your diary bro do not need every thought you
have just give us your best get like three and that that's plenty you know
what they say if we can't accept you at your if we if you know what they say
James if we can't accept your worst voicemail then don't bother sending us
your best voicemail so yes I think that's exactly that that is true so to you
sir I say there you go all right moving on consider the ramifications of your
actions all right next up we've got a little voicemail called a workout world
buy one that place that I still owe like a hundred dollars to LaMalle yes yes
they're on to you take it away ww go
workout world this is Bartholomew how may I gain your macros hate that yeah boss
we got a caller oh hi I didn't see you there were my massive
hector Alice majors let me run you the laps babe this is workout world tired of
bodyweight exercises we got Smith machines with machines barbells bare
chest bells horse drills jump your jacks off so you don't end up looking like
a retard bouncy balls snake pits indoor escalators self-motivators what can I
say but we've been kicking around since 86 there's no mistake it looks like we
got the Ben St. backlog card yes yes of course we'll have your money shortly
lawyer man they'll never fucking catch me they're they're on route Ben they're
live they're like a two-minute walk down the road from me and they're they're
hiding in plain sight yeah they're lunging over to you right now with 80
pound dumbbells in each hand you shouldn't have had one month machines fuck the
Smith machine they aren't embarrassing any self-respecting jam yeah they are for
pussies and the disabled yeah all right what is a disabled person but a pussy
who just needs to you know just get over it bro just like grow new limbs bro like
what's the big hey did I talk about the history of cheese making memes I don't
think so all right let me just let me just break in here to tell you about the
funniest thing that happened to me this week sure and sad to say it was just a
meme that I found on the internet okay I was kind of drunk but I saw this meme I
saw a tweet that said all I can do now is make history of cheese making memes and
there were a couple of memes but let's tell you the best one it was you know
the one of the anime guy who's gesturing at a butterfly and he says is this
something right of course well this one was the guy was a human being in
Mesopotamia circa 5,000 to 7,000 BC he's gesturing at the butterfly the butterfly
is a goat's bladder can a sheep's bladder containing rennet an enzyme that
promotes curdling is this a good place to store milk
that's it's well I was like that's good out of breath
there were a couple other I guess I guess I guess that no no no no you see
there was another meme attached you see he would think no the answer was no but
then there was other me with it's sort of like the Drake reaction but it's like a
girl and the first she's going like but the second she's going hmm and the first
is like opening up my sheep's bladder to find that the milk I stored in it has
curdled and then the second one is realizing I've just invented cheese
the thing about being the thing about being a human in Mesopotamia circa 5,000
to 7,000 BC is that you would never ever go anywhere without your trusty
sheep's bladder you're always looking for places to store all this milk like what's
the point of doing like it's like no no no the first guy who put who put milk in
there in their rennet rich sheeps bladder it was like the guy who first put
peanut butter on chocolate
my question is how do you get the cheese out do you have to squeeze is it still
liquidy I guess it is yeah yeah okay okay fair enough I was wondering if you
have to lose a perfectly good bladder for such things there was a third meme I
don't know it was also about rennet what I don't give a fuck you get the point
more rennet try to link those if you can find a band for adoring you know I'm
sure it won't be hard for me to find okay okay all right let's move on to our
next voicemail yes of course Caligula is calling in he apparently has something
to say take it away see dog hey guys last episode y'all talked about melee and
there's a lot of misinformation I'm a melee player I'm super in on the scene I
want to give some things oh cool one melee is not like super big we get really
good viewer numbers but we're not a very large community we don't have the
biggest numbers especially evo ultimate pulls like double almost triple the
amount of entrance we do but the real reason melee was kicked last year is
because with ultimate coming out you know 2019 didn't want to have two smash
games for like the fifth year in a row they only have nine spots for so many
fighting games and they're really important they're already doing it and
melee does use CRTs which are harder to get especially now in 2020
archaic tech so mr. wizard the evo owner kicked us and most people think it is
not just because of those reasons but also he doesn't really like melee he's
insulted the game a lot we only got enough like a donation drive in 2013 and
we just were big enough he had to keep us around on pressure but yeah it really
wasn't any reasons a Nintendo or anything like that it was really just no
two smash games CRTs are kind of annoying and mr. wizard really does not
like melee okay that was just an ad no it wasn't an ad that was just a response
to our discussion about melee it was just giving us an inside scoop it was an
um actually but that's fine you know I guess it kind of was an um actually I
guess that's fair to be honest I was gonna make a comment sorry voice voice
jail it bored me voice oh no come on okay damn it you got one voice bail per
episode if you're on the episode all right okay well let's see if this one
rises to your lofty standards this is let me see Shawn recommends the PAP oh
yeah okay okay let's let's give Shawn here a opportunity are you tired of the
same old PCP you know it like derivative content do you absolutely like to dab
on the Jews do you want to hear what Australia is let off my brow do you want
to hear what a real Ben St. fan has to say do you want to hear a really good
shaggy impression well if you answered yes to any one of those might I recommend
the procrastinators anonymous podcast which I the voicemail God will be on
the next episode wow I'm tuning in by the way this one I have a feeling like the
teen see you know oh that sting oh what who was leading the teen CP I think was
just called teens with a teen CP yeah his teen CP is just shrinking right
becoming more teensy by the second he's become fully RFCK pill he doesn't care
about the PCP anymore yeah face dab well fair enough well there you go there
you go though the floor is yours procrastinators anonymous podcast I've
listened to episodes I thought they were pretty interesting I just I mean mostly
I know that their icon on Twitter is a very unflattering photo edit of me oh
that's right it is very I really cringe every time I look at it but I mean that's
some that's a me problem other people might feel differently mm-hmm there's at
least one you got you got Simon on there he's the hardcore Ben had so he's there
going to bat I didn't know I know I like listening to it because sometimes they
talk about me and that's all I care about is me I guess I guess I sure hope
they are the primary audience I guess I should probably give it a listen I mean
I am I guess they're mascot so I yeah um you could descend from the clouds do
dude to visit them dune Coon is on it right I believe doing Coon is the is the
general organizer if I if I understand correctly he's the one who I most well
dude you're doing a great job on the procrastinators anonymous man all right
well they gotta consider this a consider this a very tepid very tepid
lukewarm non-committal endorsement of that certainly not the best not validating
the best time some might say okay now look look I'm not gonna lie to you the
next one's a bad voicemail but but oh my you should listen to it make
you should hate thinks it's bad I just in had a visceral enjoyment experience
listening to this voice I wonder if this is gonna be one of those cases where I'm
like that wasn't bad that was awesome in its own special well I don't I don't
think so but maybe it's from Ukrainian mythbusters like 20 seconds long so
okay let's give you a shot Ukrainian take it away not that Ukrainian
one CP child pornography no thank you I mean to shoot on there being a fat
stack of playboy magazine so together by semen I believe can stop a bullet in
this episode of Ukrainian mythbusters you putting the burst on me
you see what I mean I can't I can't say it's good there was there was something
compelling there yeah it's like to there's a certain undeniable emotional
core behind this terribleness of it putting the boost in your myth or I
think I think that's what he said about I don't know he's mentioned something
about like enough semen stickin together playboys with semen yeah I mean you
intriguing just like the little pause and then please call back like voice
jail voice jail hmm voice jail no I got a voice bail them out he's a good boy
damn it do nothing okay but our both our voice bails have been used so everybody
else I'm well get ready I'm gonna nominate every other caller for the
voice I'm gonna abuse my fucking privilege here well I think we'll need
that time to start the PC police state sure right PC private prisons for
profit the PC PPF Pagoolog yeah now go back to go back and go home and be a
family man fair all right let's please ban this man who is violently ramming my
large PP into Nate's bussy all right take away go stop stop too hard it's too
hard I can't do it and I'm stupid
oh yeah that's good that's good that hit is the bonus episode out yet by the
time people see in this no they're not okay it's just that yesterday I got
absolutely blitzed out of my mind laughing at a meme that we were we're
talking about in the bonus episode that we recorded like earlier this month and
it was hilarious as hell I can't tell you what it is okay I'm trying to think
like a cryptic one okay it involves the musical stylings of a oh boy a a regarding
a so a cerulean attack individual what as sung by a aspiring dentist musician
enthusiastic about dental hygiene okay all right that's the best way beyond my
ability to decipher listen the new bonus episode I will have to go to patreon.com
slash TP crassinators the procrastinators and pay fine and if I pay poultry meager
pittance of five dollars to get a cavalcade hours no doubt hours and days
of delicious exclusive content including so like so that I can experience
reverse nostalgia and come back and watch this episode with new context that
makes me experience it looks like it's all new brand new a whole new way a whole
new world for you and me now that is based all right next one we've got
ah speaking of voice jail okay straight out of voice jail we've got a message
delivered to us on the outside smuggled out no doubt illicitly from a I'll die
of embarrassment all right I'll die take it away no oh sorry didn't see you there
oh I'm just busy self-flagellating for my horrific offenses you know that's good
last night I said that in my she directed die buster when it was actually
I can't I can't bear you that's the sound of just a moment you're right you're
right I deserve to be here until I can prove that this is not characteristic
please I must suffer for this until you've realized you know until you no
longer identify as someone who mistakes the director of FLCL then then we can
have a conversation this could be the start of a redemption arc perhaps I like
to think so I like to think see his fellow inmates first step I but he I'll die
is sending a good example for his fellow inmates by going above and beyond
what our normal jailers do of torturing and beating them daily by doing it to
himself in his own time and I just want him to know that that is appreciated and
we respect the effort if I think we should send him to voice jail so that he
could be a good example to all the other inmates he's already there he's already
there that's the thing oh he's uh oh okay well good see my instincts were right
yes as usual oh okay very excited this our final voicemail brah it's what to do
when Nate uses the soundboard okay take it away oh it one second voicemail
let's see how that goes and thanks everybody that's another episode of the
procrastinators podcast in the can thank you everybody for being here it's been a
good time the what else we let those patreon.com slash the procrastinators is
what we do give us money for bonus episode including that illicit tantalizing
teaser that you've received yeah should we say anything about the shackled latest
shackles for heckles uh Minecraft stream oh I mean we could certainly say I mean
I feel like we had yeah we had a long touted the return to the PCP Minecraft
server we held the first PCP Minecraft server tournament it was oh god I hope
it was quick scope right quick scope one name the champion with his with his
his his champion or his his his ace Pokemon Ren Ren the espion and there is
now a statue of Ren in the in the the town square honoring his achievements her
I think it renders a girl whatever yeah and we hope I would you can visit that
statue you can go check it out right now if you go to patreon.com slash PCP
Minecraft we had a cease during the tournament we had open play for anybody
who wanted to join that is closed for now until the next events when we may or
may not open again there will be times after five dollars a month people having
just having to spectate the last one I am I am very much I regret not joining
myself so I am committed to I am going to fucking bunker down get a good team at
least a good enough team that I won't feel like I embarrass myself indeed
showing up and competing in the next one it's gonna be sick I am I'll give you a
little hint I'm hunting my my white whale one of my many white whales in fact is a
good a good a good natured you know good IVs and big most importantly it has to
be big size contrary Malamar I would like that to be right or so on my team
that's one of my one of my favorite months both aesthetically and
competitively you see water poison no he's dark psychic dark Jesus cry okay
I look like a poison boy he does live in water biomes though he's a squid so
whatever right well there you go hey defeat Ben Saint in single combat in
the next PCP Minecraft tournament which will be one of these days I do it see if
you can I mean who I mean Quicksilver's clearly knows what they're doing and
then some some people were certainly using decent strats I wonder what the
real experience level is like there was there was some good strats there was
some good there was some good there's some good turnabouts there was some good
there was some good upsets in the trees in that in the yeah yeah he defeated how
was it was the sediments who was number two no the sediments lost earlier second
place was shit I can't merit now not Marrypan Marrypan had already lost Marrypan
lost to oh no I'm blanking see this is what happens when you're not the winner
what you should do I mean what you should do is you should go we should go
back and just check out the stream of the yeah go watch you can watch the
tournament we recorded there was a lot of on the PCP was a lot of bullshit at the
beginning because we didn't know what we were doing after an hour and a half it
nobody knew what we were doing and it took a long time for us to actually get
started but once it actually started it was pretty smooth it was relatively
smooth sailing and a fit MC joined us he was hanging out in PCP MC serve baby
it was a good time also which was pretty based yep yep yep well there you go
I had to leave early to go oh yeah that's right and to the what's it called I
don't know the name of the stream is just may may may streams yeah I don't know
I'm sure they have names and that was fun well that's good watch that if you
want to see me talk about that thing that I've made on Twitter Lord you mean
Lord oh your chart right your chart about productivity I could have talked
about it here but I forgot that's fine I thought it was funny I haven't oh just
one of those funny little things you do look at it I guess well link it in the
show notes no doubt and have a gander ladies and gentlemen all right well
yeah that's enough go go play Minecraft with us we'll be we'll be doing more
events we'll be streaming more so you know come fucking play the game with us
and hang out probably do at least one a month and we're always building new
stuff with our admin so that's good time let me see what's going on we've got
follow us on Twitter at tbcrasnators updates and what not radcon stuff chugs
along we're working on a bunch of behind-the-scenes stuff but progress is
being made currently up Ben is holding a production of a certain element that he
needs to get moving on I know it is what it is my fault I have no excuse
anymore yeah correct correct we everyone else has done their duty even when I got
me but I got wow yeah I got the first I got the first pin from the from the
routing no oh my god I want to see it though please link it I I don't think I
tweeted it maybe I should tweet it I saw it somewhere I put yeah why not I'm
excited I will I will I posted it in rfck in the rfck okay the pilot pins
discord I did add everyone I but yeah I got I got the one sample pin and I
compared it to like the poob up in and stuff in size and it looks great is that
from the the Chinese company or the original it's from one Chinese company
I ordered another sample from another company that I was gonna compare the two
I don't know where that one is and they haven't been very communicative and this
one looks about as good as I could hope for us so I might just end up going with
this one just on like a customer service basis but I'm in the pilot pins chat
right now the last message was yesterday is it was a couple days ago
oh okay oh I see it I see it oh looks good pretty good very good looks pretty
yeah it looks great rowdy fucker looking looking sick and solid and I'm sorry
did you say that was the Chinese or was it the other the other company this was
that this is a Chinese company this is a Chinese company I'll just I'll fucking
say I'll fucking it's time to oh shenzhen long you crafts hmm hmm how much
cheaper are they than the original thing they are good quality some amount
I don't remember exactly they're they're considerably cheaper but also shipping
costs a lot more it's the reason why it's not like a as big of a savings as I
was hoping for is because shipping is fucking murder but it's still probably
saving maybe like at least like 50 bucks a pin no yeah we're saving probably
saving like at least several hundred dollars by using these these Chinese
dudes indeed indeed because they have they have more like they're more granular
they give you more options like the the UK based company that I had been using to
make pins it's like they don't they they they will charge they will charge you
like they they wrap the the production fee for the mold into it they don't
charge you separately for the mold they just charge you a base price that
includes the mold and a certain number of pins so you can't like fine tune it
like that they don't charge per color they just have like you can get up to
this many colors yeah presumably they just charge the max as assume that you
will do the maximum stuff like that but yeah this this one looks like pretty
much identical in quality so you know thumbs up success oh you know what I'm
just reminded all of a sudden that I want to extend the olive branch to one
sigh a.k.a. the cyborg because I saw somewhere I think of the car S. Y. Y.
Yeah S. Y. Y. Okay yes not Gungham style not not Gundam style not that sigh not
any other sigh okay because sigh felt I think at least somewhat wronged by my
interpretation of what I self-described as an overly long and dull voicemail
about how the voicemail sucked and and we dabbed on them for a little bit based
on that I just I'm sorry if I misrepresented yeah that's why that's
all I just follow the crowd I think it wasn't the most uncharacteristic but
sigh I want you nobody no bad blood on this I'm sorry if I misrepresented your
point but you have my love and respect that that's it that's it anyway let me
see what the patreon as we said speak pipe leave more voicemails but I
certainly don't need like a dozen from a single person let's be reasonable here
people let's uh let's not burry Nate under a flood just just you know write
down your ideas and just at the end like the day or two before be like okay I'll
be like these three these three are the best ones he probably wasn't gonna play
these ones anyway and to save me the time or I will just skip them cuz as
somebody sitting in 16 I'm just guessing they're not all absolute gems all
right there you go and nobody wants to hear the same voice ten times on an
episode anyway even if they were theoretically all good okay space that
shit out okay I think I think they get the idea okay all right a patron bonus
episodes play Minecraft with us speak pipe TP Crass news Twitter boom there
you go more rad content one of these days we're working on it there it is
thanks for listening everybody we'll see you next week another PCP time another
PCP actually the same channel I'll see you then