Hello everybody, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's me, Hippocrit, the guy, and we've
got with us a big packed car. We're on a summer vacation. It's all hot and sweaty in
the car. Clown car. Yeah, there's too many people in here. We're sticking to each other.
It's gross. We got Munchy here. I'm a sequel of 9-11, like a soft reboot. You know how
like Godzilla solely went from being an antagonist to a protagnist? That's like 9-11 in me.
We got Nate. I am the best Jihadist ever. That's the terrorism episode. We got Davoo.
Munchy, on your comment about how Godzilla went from bad guy to good guy, Rambo is similar.
He starts off as just like a violent maniac antihero in the first movie. Then he becomes
a hero. Then he becomes sort of a mixture in the fourth movie. Godzilla and Rambo should
actually do a crossover. They have so much in common. They're both accidental byproducts
of war. So what you're saying is you're a soft reboot of the Holocaust, Davoo? Sometimes.
We have Mage. The heroineys? That's a word. Mage coming out swinging. We have a Tom. Everyone
has been saying a lot of words in these intros, and I find them to be overly verbose and
bloated. The spirit is lacking. Bad show. And the man of the fewest words, Ben St. A man
of no words, preferably. There he goes. There he goes. Look, I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
He was doing the joke, and you interrupted his silence. Well, I didn't. I was proved
the fool. All right. Everybody today's episode is confusing because some people think it's
called words, but it's actually language. Language in general. I mean, I can go on for
ages. I have notes written in language in words about language and words that I will
get to maybe. There's so many people here. I'm doubtful that I'll actually get to Amish
Go. Just go. Just start. All right. Oh, wait, Urban Dictionary, though. Computer language.
Wait, I got it. I've got language. Break the structure. Check it out. No. Language. Urban
Dictionary. A way of humiliation. The leader of this episode. You can't just take over.
But he didn't want to read it, so I'm just doing it anyway. Urban Dictionary is a dictionary.
Therefore language. It sucks. Listen to this one. Listen to this one. This is a meme, though.
Okay, language. Wait, it's a meme, everyone. What your fucking horse is. Language. What
your mother claims movies she doesn't want you to see has too much of C, swear, and you
know what? You know what? That leads perfectly into my point. Language sucks, and it's bad,
and it doesn't do the job it's supposed to do. Wait, can we quickly segregate ourselves
to pro and anti-language? Can we be sure? I'm pro. I am pro. I am pro. I am pro. Munchie,
the God King is pro-language. This is the pro-languineders podcast. Wait, okay. Just
keep your anti-language. Say I. I. What language? If you're anti-language, if you hate it with
a burning passion, if you want it dead, I, me, me. So those of you keeping score at home,
that is DeVoo, Nate, and Hippo on the Axis powers, and everyone else is on. No, it's not
DeVoo. DeVoo, yeah, DeVoo wasn't actually. So is it just Hippo and Nate? I think so.
Cowardly green boys. The cowards fighting on the losing side. Cowardly green. We will
win. You are the Dark Souls boss to our rolling and stabbering. That is so unique. I never
would have guessed that the minority opinion would be that language isn't good. I would
have never suspected that. And there's nothing weaker and more pitiful than a Dark Souls
boss. Well, I mean, you know, I use a lot of language, and I feel like this. I feel like
this. It's like, like you got guys who are on the extreme left. Nate, please communicate
your ideas without using language. It's impossible. No, but I'll tell you why. You can't do it.
You've lost. As soon as you explain anything, you've lost the argument. You're using the
tool that you hate. Incorrect. Incorrect. We can, we, see, I have a solution. We've
forced this on him. Everybody shut the hell up. Let me make my goddamn point. Everything
about, everything about hap, everything happening here is entirely in my favor and probably makes
as well. He's right. He's right. Language is a terrible tool. Which because it is a translator.
It translates thoughts, feelings and ideas into a package that has to be untranslated
by the recipient. And the recipient can like misinterpret things. Anything written down.
You can't, like speech is better than stuff written down, but speech is still not as good
as just actually experiencing real things. Yeah, well, you know what else? Google and
Apple can't release a patch and change the word rifle to water gun. Well, they could,
but they haven't yet. So there you go. I don't know what that is in playing as your argument.
And I don't know what your argument is. Why words are better than emoji. Okay, but listen,
well, sure, but listen to this though. It's like people in the far left, for example,
like hate, wait, wait, no, no, it's just an analogy. It's like people in the far left,
for example, hate the Democratic party because they're not left enough. And like that makes
the mad at that. Cause like they're not, they're, they're the ones who quote unquote like represent
their ideas, but they don't do it like well enough for their taste. In that same vein,
I am mad at language for not like I use it a lot. It's, it is a tool I use, but it's
not good enough at doing what I want to do. And that's why Munchy, you should be on board
for this as should you Tom. Cause what I want is whenever I meet someone, I don't want to
use this bullshit language, shitty analog system we've got right now. I want to literally
pull out my fucking cord, like it goes to the shelves, jack it into your fucking neck
and have the raw, unfiltered data stream of my real life shit into your body.
You fucking coward. Don't you want to like what that's language too? That's a digital
language. You're converting it into a computer language.
All right.
Everything in reality as a language, I'm defining you as a language.
Language is a form of communication and doesn't have to be verbally. It can also be a language.
Is every, is every communication language is my question.
Yes.
Fuck language is just like a hyperbolic clickbait. And what you really want is just more words.
No, no, no. You guys are dead wrong. You're misrepresenting your own points. Okay. Okay.
You know what? You know what? We should have a hundred percent of all calamities.
Listen, hey, everyone, I want to make a prediction. I want to make a prediction. I want to make
a prediction. Speaking.
I want to predict something right now. I see, okay, I am the greatest mind of our generation.
My mind is so vast that it contains all of your own minds within it. I know exactly where
this conversation is going. And I already have the groundbreaking point that will smash
everything that is about to be said entirely asunder. But I'm going to wait. I'm going
to wait on it until later.
Okay, no. I just want to point out that once you say that in our mental retardation.
Okay. Davoo, Davoo, what were you saying?
You've called me out on that multiple times, dude, and I've done it explicitly to like make
you upset, except that's not actually true. I say that I'm just retarded, but I want to
hide behind like a veil of me doing intentionally so people will think that I'm cool, but I
actually just say hi.
Look at these terrible words you're using. I just don't even care about anything. They're
all bad.
Representation of points is the reason I don't like what I call language. See, this is the
whole point. Language, as I think of it, is like text and speech and stuff, not communication
on the whole. Like communication obviously is a good thing.
What's the word? What's lexicon communication?
What I'm talking about is like speaking and the written word as like more specific forms
of communication. Here's the thing. Language, well, I'm going to call it that. I'm going
to continue calling it language because calling it words and speech is kind of...
Yeah. For what words do you mean nothing? We might as well, right? That just helped
your point.
The fact that you guys defined all communication as language.
Nate, it's literally called body language.
Exactly. There is an adjective attached to that to differentiate the two from just the
broader point.
It's not even that we are correct and you were all wrong.
Yeah, we've got to be on the same page here.
It's all like a fucking... It's a mess. I've got so many different specific points to go
into.
No, no, okay. It's all about...
I'm going to start with one of my points. The specificity of language is a boon. It
helps us to do a lot of things, but it is a curse when all of humanity is linked together.
It's weird how it sucks is what I'm saying. It sucks because...
Yeah, okay.
Right. First of all, I'm not very good at using it.
Look at Twitter, dude.
Here's an example, though.
I do have notes. I just didn't write them in a way that I could read them.
Oh, no.
Okay.
I feel like you're confirmation bias saying...
I didn't write a speech. I wrote, like, here's a point that I can expand on.
The specificity of language is you have words meaning specific things, but it only works
in small communities like tribes, where everybody can decide on a word, and if a word's meaning
is changed, everybody in the tribe can be like, oh, okay, that's different, so deliberate
on that.
Can I give an example?
Can I give an example of that?
That's brilliant.
And the bigger the tribe gets, the more people that are supposed to, and expected to use
a word, they have to look to an authority, but there is no authority because the dictionary
is reactionary to the way people use language, and that just results in divides when people
can't decide on the new or the old definition of a word, such as, you know, literally being
used in, like, a figurative sense as written in the dictionary now, because that's how
people have been using it or misusing it. It's just, language creates barriers between
people because we're such a huge conglomeration of human beings, and it should be for small
sections and small communities having their own language.
First world problems, bro.
Pretty so, but listen to this, here's the exact, this is a word that the poor definition
of it is indicative of the problem with language at large, and I, like, I think what you guys,
what your side and our side will commonly clash over this entire podcast is like, but
isn't it better than nothing?
And the answer is yes. The answer is absolutely yes, but there are still problems, and I think
that's what we're going to be talking about.
Okay, here's the word.
The word is racism.
The word is racism, and the problem is that different huge groups, for example, in America,
use that word in completely different ways, but because there are multiple definitions
for that word, it causes huge misunderstandings, see Sky Williams' video on the subject.
Is it multiple definitions of the word?
There's one definition of, no, no, no, there's one definition of the word, and then there's
a whole political subset that has taken that word and changed it to mean something else
to...
Is that a difference?
Is that any way different from having multiple definitions of a word?
That's a problem with people and ideology, not with language.
My point, my problem is there's too many people using the same language where we should
be...
Not that we should be, but the way the language was invented was it makes sense for the small
tribes.
A word only means what people think it means, and if there's no consensus on what it means,
then it's not useful to use because it causes arguments.
The problem right now is there's a big problem because the internet has created this problem.
Made this problem way bigger than it ever was in history.
I agree with what you're saying, how language has problems with multiple interpretations
and how words change over time, but the specific example Nate's using isn't a natural evolution
of language.
It's a very conscious choice to twist something to suit an agenda.
Maybe that's true, but that is completely irrelevant to the point that just the reality
is it is simply used these ways.
And like you...
Okay, like I sound like the SJW side of things right now, but it's just like, I don't actually
care who's right or wrong about what the word originally meant or who's twisting it
for an agenda.
All I care about is that there is a miscommunication going on and people are talking past each
other, and that is the problem with language.
And that's exactly what Gibb is talking about.
Just for example, you've got SJWs...
Okay, but let me just finish this real quick, just take a second.
It's just that you've got a camp that just views the world from a situation where racism
means prejudice plus power.
And you've got just this other camp that just believes to their core that it simply means
discrimination based on race and power is irrelevant.
Because these people are so deeply entrenched in believing these things, it doesn't matter
where it came from.
This is simply where we are right now.
We can absolutely talk about why it's a problem that we got here, but it is the reality that
people just can't agree on what they're talking about.
That is not a problem with language.
That was done on purpose to make it medial.
Language facilitates this issue.
Let me speak.
Let me.
Language is a tool like any other.
Blaming language in itself for the faults of humans is like blaming water for people
who drowned in it.
Just because people can't drown in it doesn't mean the water is supposed to be blamed for
it.
No, no, no, wrong.
Okay, go on Gibb.
The thing I should make my argument more specific, it's not that language sucks.
I just say that because that's funny and you're like, oh, you're being all hyperbole.
We're all about the memes here.
We're all about the hyperbole.
Where are the memes?
Well, there they are.
I hate it.
What my point is, is that the way language developed initially was like we were banging
rocks together and people were grunting and we were like, what is this thing that is different
from this other thing?
And they came up with words.
I mean, I don't know how it happened, but eventually over time, people invented words
to mean certain things and they were like specific to wherever they lived and whatever
they had.
And that's why languages are like different all over the world.
And when a language spreads to other places, it becomes difficult to police, like keep
the language consistent among all those different places.
Okay, but that's not the languages fault also, like because of the internet.
No, this is what I was getting to.
My point is not that language sucks, it's that language over a large amount of people,
like too large.
It stops being useful for communication, which was its primary purpose in the first
place is to communicate ideas.
If between different groups that are like, there's too many people and so many large
groups of people have different interpretations of certain words, then the point of language
becomes, well, the point of language is lost, like that certain words are not able to be
communicated properly between people.
They have ideas, they have thoughts, and they're using words that other people don't agree
with.
Like in a magical world where we didn't need them, we could like telepathically transmit
ideas into people's heads, that would be better.
Not possible.
Give me that USB point, boy.
But that's my argument, that like when there's too many people using the same language, it
will inevitably stop being useful as a tool.
No.
Are you saying that we've reached that point or just that will theoretically happen in the
future?
Have we reached that point now?
Is that what you're saying?
We're facing the issues as a result of it for sure.
Give language time to catch up, the internet was invented just like how many years ago?
Mage, here's why it'll never happen, Mage, this will always be a fundamental problem
with language.
Okay, to your credit, you do have a point.
Given enough words and given enough time, like the reason people write articles, right,
to flesh out arguments and they write books to explain things, the problem is there is
a fundamental problem with human beings and language, because human beings just read headlines,
we just read titles, we read condensations of points that other people present to us,
and that is because asking someone to read a fully articulated point.
We watch analytical YouTube videos explaining the anime to us instead of watching the damn
anime.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean that is kind of an issue, yeah.
The problem is we're asking too much of the weak flesh of human beings to spend the time
to learn things, and people can get over it, of course they can, but they don't, enough.
And this is a problem that people just don't want to spend the time reading something when
they can get a shorter version.
But I was supporting my national point about blaming water where it's the people who are
being dumb.
So language is bad because people are lazy for some things?
Are you fucking retarded?
That's the dumbest point I've ever heard.
Yeah, what the fuck?
Language is bad because people are lazy.
That is your point right now.
You guys want to just say that like, oh well humans can always adapt and change, but you're
not facing the reality.
No, the reality is some people are shit and some people aren't shit and that has nothing
to do with language.
Okay, okay, yeah, I understand what you're saying that like it's just human nature that
that's how people are gonna read, but like, but I don't see how that's language, like
that's not language's fault.
Yeah, actually, you know what, no, it is language's fault.
Nate, I agree with your point to the point that it proves your point wrong.
What you get down to the core of this is that people in their eternal laziness try to find
some sort of tool or technique or a secret trick to just make it easier for them or to
take the effort out of it, like reading the headline instead of the article or thinking
it's possible to have some form of word-based lexiconal communication that allows you to
actually make everyone understand you all the time.
Maybe there's no easy way out, no shortcut home, you just have to learn how different
people use words every step of your way through as you go on through life.
Words are like a martial art technique.
You must master it, experience each fight that comes along the way and improvise and
be smart.
There's no, we aren't a bunch of computers all manufactured in the same Chinese sweatshop.
We're not all the same.
Even if you can communicate dream to dream, dream brains aren't all made the same.
There's no easy way out.
You just gotta fucking be smart and put a lot of effort in to communicate all the time.
Yes, yes.
And the fact that that is all true is the problem with language, that is the problem.
So you're saying that language sucks because people spread fake news on Facebook and that
this specific problem with internet headlines, that's the reason why language is flawed.
The problem is that language is an incredibly inefficient medium for which us to acquire
information and people just don't put in the work to do so and it's because language is
so shit at it.
The point is...
Those two are intellect.
So what do you want?
I agree.
Well, I agree.
That is true.
Well, I have real experiences in less talking, less reading, less text.
There is a language of visuals, there's a language of visual art.
How?
Wait, wait.
I said earlier that I'm talking about text and speech, visual art is like I'm not talking
about language in general.
I have a couple things, I have a couple things.
First of all, I think visual language is a double-edged sword because it can be more
specific in some ways, but can also be way more abstract than language in other ways.
You can draw a picture and it can clearly represent something literally, but if you're
trying to communicate something subtextually with an image, it's way more vague than text.
So that's a problem, but Nate, are you trying to say that your argument is that we need
some form of language that instantaneously downloads an entire article's worth of content
into someone's brain along with all the context for every single word choice behind it from
that person's point of view?
Is that what you want?
I am saying, if such a fictional thing existed, then that would be a better option to give
people all the information for each point.
Then sure, science fiction is definitely better than reality.
I will give you that point.
But considering that...
But that is every...
I think that is...
That language is not perfect, is my point.
Yeah, that is it.
Well, congratulations.
Nothing's perfect.
Yeah.
This is what a completely useless point.
So what do you want then?
You want me to just say, yeah, it's perfect.
I guess I'll just say...
No!
It's not perfect!
Who wants language to be perfect?
Okay, I don't...
You guys are literally worse than Hitler.
You're oppressing my ideas.
You don't care about the Jewish people like me.
Fuck you guys.
I don't...
Why do you want to abolish Israel?
Tell me why.
Just tell me why.
I don't particularly disagree with what I think is like the morsel of truth here.
But it's just a gross hyperbole.
And I don't understand why you guys are taking this to like the most instant degree.
Yeah, why does the fact that it's...
I don't understand why the fact that it has problems mean that it's bad.
You guys are literally just mad that I'm articulating the problems with language.
That is you right now.
No, I'm mad that you're saying that these problems mean that they are a net negative
and that language is bad.
If we abolish...
Do you think that things would be better if we abolish language?
Of course not.
I think that's exactly what I said.
Exactly what I said.
That it's not actually about language just being an overall negative.
I said it's a boon.
Maybe fucking talking about...
We came out...
The problem is we came with this from a meme.
That's the whole problem.
We've been talking about this...
We said a meme that language is bad.
That's not actually true.
It's a meme.
You dip.
Visual language is like fucking...
People only taught with the visual language back in the medieval times to teach the Bible,
Jesus.
And I'm thinking...
They only talked about visual language?
What do you mean?
Visual communication, right?
They just have fucking stained glass windows to tell the whole Bible stories, right?
Didn't they have the Bible though?
Yeah, but those people couldn't read back in the day.
They're all uneducated.
That's why all those mobs had to illuminate all those manuscripts.
Right.
They had to illuminate all those manuscripts.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm fucking thinking about it.
If the Second Amendment had been, instead of any words, had been a guy just with his
family holding a gun and then a police officer taking the gun, but there's a red X over that,
there'd probably be a lot less room for miscommunication, I suppose.
If you think about...
I mean, maybe.
If you go to a fast food store, you see that little yellow sign, it'll say something in
Spanish that means, you know, don't slip.
Like with that image, it could be interpreted as a guy taking away the gun from the officer.
I mean, that is...
It could be interpreted different ways.
That open...
Visual mediums just open up a whole, like, different set of possible issues, you know?
And we can get into that.
But I think...
I want to say a point, though, before everyone started yelling.
I think language is a tool, just like any other.
Like I stated, you don't blame the pencil if you can't draw, you don't blame the brush
if you can't paint, you know?
You can't blame the chisel if you can't sculpt.
So why are you blaming the language if you can't use it as a tool to communicate effectively?
Because this is why, mate.
Because this is why.
Because, like, when I'm signing a check, I do blame the pencil if I use to sign the
check because it is not doing everything I want it to do, i.e. actually inking.
It's just, like, it is doing a different, not as good job as the tool I would ideally use.
What do you want a language to do?
A better analogy for that, Nate, is that, you know, language is like a paintbrush.
And, like, you know, a canvas is whatever.
It used to be, you dip your paintbrush, it's a tiny little paintbrush, you dip it in,
and then you can fill in like a square, like a one centimeter square.
Fill that in real quick, real easy, when the square is small.
When the square is, like, 200 feet long and 300 feet tall, and you still have that same
paintbrush, it's the same tool, it's just not as effective as it once was.
The paintbrush isn't the same, though.
There's also a multitude of colors.
You don't blame the paintbrush, you just blame the situation.
The situation is there are too many people that use the English language for the English language
to be a really good form of communication between everybody.
I love the English language as a non-native speaker.
I really love it because it's so broad and has so many words to describe the same things.
It's literally, like, it's almost the same to me as drawing because you can shape your words
like your sentences into specific things.
I like role-playing with people via text because I can shape sentences to reflect what I want to say
and make, like, it's reading the replies, it's like watching art because I love it,
I love how unique it can be, like, you can use different words.
You got different words for, like, the animal, like, you got pigs and then you got pork
because that's the way, like, English evolved is just be peasants used to use the word pig
to kill shit.
Don't misunderstand.
Don't misunderstand me.
I love a lot of things about the English language, specifically how, like, looking at a word like yesterday
and then understanding that yester is like a thing that you can apply to other words,
like yester year and yester week.
Like, seeing how words come into being, puns, like, I love so much of stuff about language.
I love puns and I think, like, is there any other language that has puns, by the way?
I'm just curious.
Of course.
Japanese has tons of puns.
What?
Japanese.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, okay, that's good because I don't think Lithuanians are very good at puns.
Lithuanians don't have puns?
That's outrageous.
Well, because I tried to explain to my mother what a pun was because, like, a long story,
but, like, she seemed very confused.
I was like, wait, don't we have puns?
So, like, if there's any Lithuanians listening right now, if you know any Lithuanian puns,
please let me know.
Post some Lithuanian puns.
Post some Lithuanian puns in the comments.
You know, not to be mean or anything, but I feel like I'm watching, like, a kid's cartoon
and, like, the little imp goes back to, like, the evil dark impville and they try to teach
their family about happiness and smiles.
What is this sharing you're speaking of?
What is this?
Agreed.
Okay, but listen, listen.
Like, we are currently experiencing what my problem is with language, and it is a large
issue, and I'm perfectly willing to say that.
And, like, it ties into Ben's question that he asked before.
What do you want language to do?
Okay, so that is a great question, and the whole reason for screaming and yelling, I
think we basically are all on the same page, but, okay, let me approach it.
It's like, me and Gib are viewing this conversation from the perspective of how things are not
perfect with language.
Whereas, I think someone like Maze, just for example, is approaching this as how the
world would be worse without language.
So, to have language, she sees all the benefits.
So, she's focused on the positives and is like, well, how can you say, you know, language
is shit?
It does all these good things.
That's a perfectly reasonable thing to say.
I think because we're approaching it from different perspectives, that's the issue.
I'm not saying languages, but you're saying fucked language.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry if this comes off as shitty or anything.
I'm sorry if this pisses you off.
But I'm really waiting for you to get to the point.
I have many times already.
I do disagree, though, on how you described my view.
No, my view is a language is a tool and it's up to the people how they use it.
If they do a shitty job, that's not the language's fault.
If your point is that language is imperfect, then, you know, gotcha.
Message received.
Yeah.
I mean, podcast over.
But listen, listen, though.
Ben's question, what do you want language to do?
Okay, that's what this all hinges on.
I want, like, language is what it is.
It, like, again, we're talking like spoken and like written language.
Like, that just, it is what it is.
It can't really change that much.
You could probably update with, like, Esperanto they're trying to.
That's fine.
But there are inherent limitations.
Like, what I want is a better form of communication that, for example-
So, like, a different language.
It's, you're defining communication as language, which I think is just wrong.
Because there are things that are not language.
Okay, no, no, now you're, now you're hopping because like-
Well, then I'm telling you, I'm telling you right now, I'm talking about spoken and written language.
I don't care about anything else.
But just now, you just contradicted yourself.
Listen.
Have you-
Tell me how I contradicted myself.
Yeah.
Okay, well, I don't think we agree.
Okay, you don't seem, okay, I don't get why you don't think that any form of communication is a language.
I think that it definitely is.
And I think that, yeah, text and speech is imperfect and can be improved upon.
But like, it's, you're not gonna, like, you can only iterate on it and make it better.
You can't replace it with something else that does the same thing.
But I'm not trying to say it does the exact same thing.
Also, listen to the definition of language.
A body of words and the systems for their use common to a people who are of the same community or nation,
the same geographical area.
Listen, it's words make up language.
If you're not communicating with words, it's not a language.
Okay, well, I'm sure I could find some alternate definitions that do not-
Oh, yes.
Because, yeah, that's not the only kind of language there is.
Okay, there's one down here.
There's another definition that says communication of meaning in any way.
So now, here's the question.
Yeah.
Are you wrong or am I wrong or are we both sort of right?
What's, what is it?
It's up to you to define it.
Exactly.
Yeah, I guess we're arguing across definitions a little bit.
It is shitty.
Exactly.
And therefore, a problem with language.
Thank you, everyone.
Okay, well, I guess I've been blown out of the water.
I guess I've just been completely-
That solves nothing.
That point does not change.
Even we had some magic psychic language where we could instantly say things.
If I disagreed with your fucking definition of language, it doesn't matter if I could
understand what you meant perfectly.
I'd still disagree.
This change is nothing.
This is not a plea to make the world more agreeable.
This is just like, you know, sometimes I kind of get mad that people don't agree on words.
That's all my point.
Well, I mean, my point is more specific to something not quite what Nate is going for,
I think.
But like, you know, the classic thing, pictures worth a thousand words and all that.
Pictures are good.
They convey a lot of meaning and a lot of things that words can't do quite as well.
My favorite expression, don't say.
Well, more than that is that if I were to either explain a story of a baby being born
and then the mother dying or something like a tragic story, oh no, it's sad.
If I were to explain that with words, even if I was really good at speaking, even if
I was really good at writing, it wouldn't work quite as much as like being there and
like seeing the tragedy like unfold before you.
It wouldn't hit you as hard.
And I feel like not that you're supposed to go out into the world and see tragedy.
That's not really the good thing that you, in fact, tragedy is bad and please don't actually
happen.
But if you would tragedy, spare us.
I feel like people spend a lot of their fucking time talking on the Internet.
And I think they would be much happier and much more fulfilled in life if they just forget
about speaking for once and do something real in the real world and Pokemon Go.
I agree with your point.
But I don't know why you're like, you're like, you're taking that point and channeling
it into like language is bad.
Like I agree that people should go and experience the things and not like just like communicate
through art or words or whatever.
Okay.
And just fantasize about like the abstraction of it.
But I don't understand why that is focused directly onto language.
Well, I think how Nate has sort of co-opted my feelings on the matter.
I don't speak for myself.
We just so happen to be like kind of on the same side.
I'm not like saying language sucks and I don't think we should get rid of language.
I don't think anything should happen to language.
I'm just like, wouldn't it be nice if you just sort of like you sit on you sit out on the beach
and you just sort of look at someone you smile and you can share a moment with each other.
And it's like, you don't need to say, I'm happy that you don't need to draw a picture about it.
You just sort of like you feel it.
You feel it more innately and more real.
There are things that words can't describe and those are very...
Yeah.
Have you guys...
Words that can't describe.
I'm completely on you with that.
Have you guys ever heard the phrase, writing about music is like dancing about architecture?
Yeah.
I just thought that was interesting.
Please continue.
I do agree with Hippo and it doesn't invalidate my opinion whatsoever.
Oh man.
You know what guys?
I think I want to just say that even if words aren't the best communication or far from the worst
because dancing, like interpretive dancing.
Okay, let's see.
She spun around.
She spun around 90 degrees.
Okay.
Oh, now she spun around 180 degrees.
Is this Morse?
Oh, she jumped.
Oh man, this totally is like the fucking Renaissance period, right?
Oh man, here comes some Bohemian shaking your hand around a little bit.
Oh, I totally understand this language.
Definitely.
I'm not bored.
I'm glad you brought this up.
I feel like we need to dig into the issue that like the definition, Nate, the definition
that you were using, like you were defining like a linguistic language like English or
French, but like I think it's more and I'd rather talk about language in the more abstract
way, but there's a thing like the language of like cinema, you know, or body language
or things like that.
Okay, now just the point that is distinct from everything I made points about previously.
I was not talking about anything besides the spoken and written word and I'm happy to talk
about that, but like those points do not apply in the same way.
Okay, well, how are you guys pro or anti language in general, like the language of cinema?
Pro communication, so yeah.
Well, okay, let me just say as a larger point, so we made a huge mistake about having a serious
discussion on this matter by even taking a for or against position.
It's like this.
My position here is that there are imperfections with the theoretically ideal form of communication
I envision in my brain that the spoken and written word have it is not perfect.
In my opinion, these are large issues and they cause big problems.
We can then but like, but I want to just identify what those problems are.
That is what it like to say that I'm anti language puts a huge label on like I'm in this team,
you're in that team, and then we just argue that is a huge mistake if you want to have
an actual debate as to like, or not not even debate, just a discussion about what the actual
points are.
Yeah, labels themselves are badly used words.
No one has brought in the idea that language is perfect besides you.
Like none of us have said that language is perfect in any way.
That's not I am not debating that you think language is perfect.
I'm simply saying language has these problems and I think they're a big deal.
Alright, well, I think we're well past the point.
I don't think anyone disagrees with that idea, but the way you've been phrasing it.
Then why were you arguing with me?
Because you were expressing it.
When did I ever say that?
I very much appreciate that.
I think Nate's got us all got you all in a little trick and little ruse.
Nate has been arguing his point by using language really, really badly to explain his point.
Nate, thus proving the point in an old and rare double reach around.
I'm literally a thousand times smarter than all of you.
You are ants.
You are babies.
You are children.
We've been doing this show for over a hundred episodes now.
And in that time, I've heard you discuss many a topic.
And I think this topic more than any has maybe realized with no uncertainty of how miserable it must be to be you sometimes.
To be trapped in this endless intellectual masturbation of all these incredibly insane ideas
and having to just constantly be thinking about them and unable to just let them go.
Hashtag fucking earned.
Yeah, I think about things more than you guys.
That's true.
What a miserable existence you must lead.
Someone's got to do it.
Thank God it's not me.
And death is the key.
If you can get away from the central institute right here.
I would like to do one pro-language little point here that I think me and Ben can get into on this.
This is the reason why language is great.
Give me something to sink my teeth into.
There are big words and there are rare words.
You have your commoner, pig-slop-speak.
You have your ants and thes and hellos.
But then you bring out shit like keroskero.
Oh, what's another big one?
Is that English?
Or Tentious?
It's Italian.
Antidisestablishmentarianism.
Yeah, there it is.
You've got big shit like that.
And I love, I fucking love to break out big words and rare words.
It's like getting a Pokemon card.
It's getting like a holographic Pokemon card.
You're reading an essay, you're listening to something.
He says a big fucking word and you go, wow, that guy's fucking smart.
And it's great.
Okay, yeah, that does support my point.
I'll just quickly adjust it.
Rather than language being a paintbrush, rather language is a paint and you're the paintbrush.
So whatever picture, like, and it's up to you to paint the picture that you want to paint.
You know?
And so language is kind of like that.
Each word is a color and you have to, you know, make it all come together.
I mean, in Japan, that's quite literal.
Language is like a bunch of Jenga blocks and your sentences are the tower.
Oh.
The curves are something.
And they all come tumbling down.
And you know what?
Some sort of data link that communicates all context, all the points that you're going to make
that just instantly transferred that information would be a better,
would be a skyscraper that was invincible and indestructible.
Nate, fight me on this.
How is that?
How is the data link or some kind of like digital data transfer between minds?
How is that not just using another language?
How is that not just converting things to computer language?
I'm still confused.
If you're arguing arguments, none of us suggested.
You're just arguing your own damn ideas.
But see, but see, you saying, but you saying that language is good in these ways is in fact a completely separate.
I'm not saying language is just good.
I never said language is good.
I said language is the tool.
You literally said language is good way before.
Language is good.
You fucking asshole.
And I agree.
But that's not my point.
Then what the fuck are you talking about?
That's not perfect.
Nate's point is that it's not perfect.
I need to say it's a tool.
You use it.
If you use it poorly, it happens.
Oh my God.
You just don't.
Nate, the problem is that, let me, let's go back.
Hippo, what was the last time you bought Pokemon cards?
I got it a couple months ago and it got a hollow in my first pack.
Why don't you get out of my eardrum?
It's hurts.
I lost two cents.
Stop by hating us some more.
We're just talking past each other's problems.
I actually have a point to make.
I just came up with, but it's something I've always opinionated.
Do you really think that I think language has no value, even though I distinctly said that's not the case?
No.
Nate, the problem is...
God damn it.
Okay.
I'm pissed off.
Nate, I'm pissed off this time.
This is why he wants a better alternative for language, because he can't use the one we have.
Let me tell you, Nate, the ambiguity...
I don't understand any of your points against me.
No, it's just funny.
The ambiguity and misunderstandability of words is, saves as many lives, prevents as many wars as it causes.
If someone asks, oh, hey, person at the grocery store, how are you today?
Dude, you're literally making that up.
You have no justification for that.
Can I just...
I want to go back to an example that you said, Nate, just not to argue, but just to request clarification.
Okay.
I want to better understand your position for the sake of extending an olive branch.
One of the first examples you cited was talking about the racism definition and how there's multiple definitions,
and that causes confusion and that's a weakness in language.
What I am trying to figure out is because you're saying that we need a superior version of language
where we can kind of communicate all subtext and all meaning in addition to the points we're saying.
But using that specific example, if somebody who's a super far-left, crazy, regressive, lefty kind of guy
was able to communicate this way and communicated their idea of racism, whatever,
instantly into someone else's brain who had the more traditional definition.
How would that change anything?
Because the person...
I'm so glad you asked.
I have a point to make about this.
I will make it later.
Motherfuckers, I'm going to say it.
Give me some time, but I'll really get back to it.
Okay, but Tom, that's a great question.
I'm really glad you asked.
Okay, here's how.
Because I would argue that because people are using, for example, the different definition of the word racism,
they're using the same word, but they mean different things.
That means they are not actually debating the ideas of one versus on the same level.
So again, somebody who uses the older version of the word saying that, for example, saying minorities can be racist,
and then you've got a big SJW saying, no, minorities can't be racist,
but they're not actually saying the same thing.
They're not actually debating the same idea, and therefore a real communication,
a real examination of those same ideas is not happening.
If they just knew, if both sides knew exactly what the other meant,
and we removed the ambiguity of the word, they could...
The person would say, well, like, oh, okay, like the right-wing person would say, for example, here,
like, oh, I get it.
You're saying that privilege is real, and I could admit that to some degree,
but I still think it is bad to discriminate based on race across the board.
And if the left-wing person with the new definition is saying, oh, okay, like, it's good that you accept that,
and what we actually disagree on is if it's, like, okay, to discriminate against people who have power,
you know, for example, like, white people who are the majority in America.
If we're having that debate, that is a substantive debate, which I think is just way better.
Do you not think that that's happening in the vast majority of cases when this debate is being had?
Absolutely not.
I've read articles and listened to videos of people using the regressive lefty form of racism,
and I understand the position they're coming from, and I still think it's retarded.
But, Tom, would you say, would you say, Tom, that even if, as you say, the majority do that,
if there's even a good chunk of people who are making this mistake, wouldn't it be nice if that didn't happen?
I mean, I can't solve other people's issues of stupidity.
Well, I think you guys are talking about different things.
Nate, what you're saying is just that the conversation is a non-starter,
because from the very beginning, when both parties are using the same word, the same signifier,
to mean different things, then no real communication is taking place.
Exactly.
Like, it would all be fine if we could make two different words for those two different things
than the conversation, like, saying nothing about who's right or who's wrong.
Just the conversation could then proceed in earnest.
That is exactly right, Ben. Thank you.
The ambiguity of language is invaluable.
It's how our society is made.
It's the fact that we can say a thing, and we could have different ideas of that thing,
but we can still, sometimes, still kind of carry along.
And if we did data link for everything, and you're in the store and someone goes,
hey, how are you today? And the answer is, I would have fucking killed somebody!
You know, that would be kind of hard to go to the grocery store.
Wait, wait, wait, so you're saying it's better to not know that there are murderous people around us?
If you had the ability to just suck your brain right into someone's actual thoughts,
you'd be running and scampering up, down, left, right for your life.
That should be like a video game or something, I don't know.
You don't have to broadcast your thoughts to anybody.
I mean, even in this theoretical situation.
Oh, what's that thing in the psychopath's code?
You're a motherfucking...
Psychopath.
...utilitarian society, where all of our mouths are sealed shut,
and we all have USBs in our fucking necks.
A bunch of nosy people will start poking around their USB cords,
trying to poke you, trying to surprise you.
Like, boop, plugged in, now I get to know exactly what you're thinking.
And it's like, fuck you!
Devote, devote.
I want hate sex with you.
I'm happy to make hyperbolic statements.
I like language because language is anarchy. That's nice.
Language is anarchy.
I don't like anarchy.
I want to talk about datalink.
I want to pick apart the idea.
I want to pick apart the idea that we could somehow circumvent
an imperfect language through the use of some kind of datalink.
We can do that if you want, but I think that's a huge waste of time
because I'm not actually trying to defend this whole podcast.
I agree.
This podcast sucks.
Why does everybody think this is a huge waste of time?
This has been a great podcast.
It's been a great discussion. I've really enjoyed it.
I'm not trying to defend myself.
I just think to attack this hypothetical system,
I'm not actually trying to defend a hypothetical system.
I'm just promoting one way that we could improve language.
You and people throw out this idea
that if we could just digitize our thoughts
and communicate them directly to each other,
that we would somehow know more about each other.
But I say that that is just a different version of the same thing
because you're still converting to a shared language, a computer language.
And ultimately, okay, here's what I want to throw out
and I think we could discuss it,
or maybe everyone will think it's a big waste of time, in which case, whatever.
Fuck you.
Are our thoughts, are our innermost thoughts
like a language of their own, or are they language-less?
Yeah, I think so.
The different brains are different, obviously.
If we were to date up the language as it is now,
it's a translation tool to get things out of your brain.
Right.
But do they originate?
In your brain, do they originate as pure thought,
or is pure thought happening in an inner language?
Don't you think people will find a way to manipulate those thoughts anyway
and just not be honest in some way?
People will do that.
Humans have fucking glands and things that create emotions.
I'm trying to think of the words, I can't think of the words.
Humans feel lust and rage and sadness and all these things,
and those are caused by chemicals in the brain.
Fill in all those right now.
Well, question.
Question.
Does an English speaker think in English,
or do they think in an inner language and then translate to English?
I think what happens is that when you're...
I mean, that's on the internet.
...before you learn the language.
I think you probably don't have specific words for those things.
I think as we grow older and learn our first language,
that's how we identify things.
This is something I've thought about sometimes too,
because I've always thought about learning other languages,
and people who have learned other languages,
your internal monologue is always going on.
And like, Mage, maybe this is a question for you
because you don't speak English.
Because I don't...
Yes, she does.
You don't speak English.
I don't speak English at all.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
I have no idea what that meant.
My point is that, like...
If I learned another language,
my brain would probably still be thinking primarily in English,
and I'd be translating to that other language.
So is your internal monologue still in Lithuanian,
or does English poke in there every now and then?
Actually, for me personally,
I can't say this is for everyone because it's probably not,
but for me personally, my internal monologue is English.
And I usually...
Wow.
I default to Lithuanian usually when I start counting things.
Nice.
That's usually the only time.
Well, the only Lithuanian allowed on this podcast
is Lithuanian puns, so...
I feel like there's a difference.
There's a difference in the brain,
in the mind-brain-thought-brain tank.
Between, like, monologues and thoughts,
I feel like I don't think in words
until I think about thinking in words,
and then I can't stop thinking in words until I forget.
And then I'm like,
oh wait, have I been thinking in words all this time?
Or have I been thinking in, like,
just a nebulous sort of feeling,
like a gut instinct sort of thing?
The scientific reason for that is because, like,
you have your neocortex,
which is the newest part of your brain,
and that's our capacity for languages.
But then we have the limbic brain,
which is where decision-making and emotion comes from,
and that has no capacity for language.
So when you're thinking emotionally,
your brain isn't even thinking with words,
because the part of your brain doing all...
Oh yeah, and we can turn those signals into...
And we can brainwave,
blast them with a thing.
But emotions are sometimes irrational,
and if you communicate your emotions,
there's going to be a lot of miscommunication.
Do you ever fucking notice,
do you ever fucking notice that, like,
something will happen or someone will even say something,
and you have a reaction,
like, maybe a second later,
do you even, like, realize why you had that reaction?
Like, you don't need it.
You react the offense before you even actually
understand why you're offended.
I have that sometimes to do,
but I think it's just because I'm a child.
I don't know what the problem is for everyone else.
Well, hey, let me just throw this out here,
because I think this is happening,
and I just think there's a little bit of talking about it.
Like, May just point just now, you know,
it's probably fine, I'm not trying to attack you.
So, like, give an eye, for example,
say that, like, okay, there's a problem with language,
and it's this, and then, like,
we say, like, okay, here's, like,
what we could consider, like, a better version.
So, for example, you know, this, like, telepathic communication,
where we can really articulate ourselves
and communicate, like, everything in a blame blast.
It's fictional, I get it.
And then, you guys, in response to that, say,
okay, but that has these additional flaws.
No, I'm not saying that it's not enough of an improvement.
Or it's not enough of an improvement.
I'm saying that it doesn't make any sense.
I don't think it circumvents the problem at all.
If you're gonna, if the point is there's a problem with language,
I agree, there's inherent problems with spoken language,
and there's limitations.
Would a brain blast be superior in some ways?
Sure.
Jimmy Neutron's got it down.
Does it still?
Brain blast is always superior.
Does it still have problems?
Wait, wait, wait, let Tom finish.
It's still, but there are still issues.
There are still issues, even with that.
Because, yeah.
Man, you've entered the same issue.
Tom, Tom, I 100%, Tom, I 100% agree.
Munchy, I think you are objective, okay.
No, Munch is right.
The specific point I made, for example,
about including, like, more context.
Like, for example, the fact that, like, the word racism, again,
you mean different things.
Yeah, but to go back to that example too, though,
is that even if everybody understood everyone's context,
not everybody agrees on the context.
So you're still not gonna have 100% understanding.
But Tom, debating the context, my argument,
is that is a more productive debate
than just using the wrong word.
Like, that's a step back.
And I would like to be that step forward,
where we're actually clashing on the ideas.
You can say that, like, that's useless.
I disagree.
I guess my problem is that, like,
that's an issue beyond language, right?
Because if you really wanted to solve that problem,
like, you could write an article,
and then you could have little hyperlinks
over all your hot-button words
and explain exactly what you mean by them,
and then people would understand what you mean by racism.
You just hover over racism,
little pop-up thing comes up.
This is what I mean.
Prejudice plus power.
And then, like, you can know that.
But what you're doing is you're offering
exactly what I'm offering,
like, a fix to this specific problem.
Sure.
But I don't...
It doesn't involve brain tubes.
I don't...
I just don't think that that's...
That's just a joke.
I don't think that's inherently a problem
with language in and of itself.
Like, it's a limitation,
but, like, it can be addressed.
I just think that...
Oh, it's a limitation,
but not a problem, is it?
Oh, I see.
I see how it is.
Yeah.
Because even if you were able to address this
with, like, psychic communication,
automatically know everyone's context behind it,
like, people still aren't going to agree.
The problem lies within the human mind.
Is the problem this?
We're calling it a problem.
You called a limitation.
Is the problem just that one has a negative label
and the other has, like, a neutral?
No, no, Nate, listen.
The problem lies within the humans,
not within the language.
I mean, I disagree for all the reasons
I've already stated.
I think that language is inherently limited.
I don't disagree that language has problems, by the way.
Well, that's my point, though.
But no, you said language is bad.
But I mean, I've walked that back.
It is not bad.
It is way better than having no language.
And so, like, you win.
Language is not bad.
My point is just that it's not perfect.
And maybe I'm wrong.
I never said that it was perfect.
There we go.
Done.
Humans are flawed creatures, and they, you know,
it's okay to blame the humans for misusing words.
But I feel like, like I said earlier,
the usage, the point of language is to communicate ideas,
and it doesn't work on such a large scale
as it is in today's age of the internet
and everybody being connected.
Does anybody have, like, an issue with that statement?
I think the internet, as a whole,
proves that language is doing a damn good job.
I mean, the only, I, the only,
it's not even a rebuttal to that game.
It's just that, like, that is a consequence,
just sort of of, like, as more people
from different backgrounds and areas
came in contact with each other.
That was, you know, that was just going to arise
as soon as that happened.
But, like, yeah, it's basically,
it's a more archaic form of communication.
Just the fact that we have multiple languages
is basically, like, an archaic thing
that it would sure be nice if we could, like,
get past that particular issue.
You know, I went to the springboard off that,
why the fuck haven't we gone, like,
Star Wars or Star Trek and have, like,
a universal basic everybody listens to?
I constantly think about that.
Like, Esperanto, why isn't Esperanto, like,
funded by everybody
and a requirement for all countries?
You know why?
It's because people are tribal
and they like their history.
That's why.
There's no reason to not just have that
in addition to, like, it should be happening.
Fair point.
Also, people are lazy.
There should be a stripped-down,
very basic form of language
that everyone learns.
I'll tell you exactly why I would argue.
Like, the reason I wouldn't want to do it
is because English looks like it's doing
pretty well right now.
I'm just going to hold out hope
that English just wins
and everybody starts speaking English.
Therefore, I have to do as little work as possible.
I think a lot of people
probably hold up that hope.
That doesn't seem very
utilitarian.
Where are the structural issues
in language made?
Like, is there anything inherent
to language that makes it undesirable
or would just adding more words
and more syntax be accomplishing
what you want?
I think ultimately the problem with language
is that it is based on, like,
group consensus, as Gibbs said,
and just inherently as, like,
if we could theoretically impose some,
like, like, French, for example,
French is a language where there is an organization
in France that dictates what
words mean.
They have, like, a body that decides this.
So, in France, technically,
like, you know, they'll, like, write in stuff
of, like, the consensus just changes
and they incorporate skiddy,
scuba de bop.
That means, like, a skateboard.
It's just another word for skateboard.
Cool.
But, like, in that language,
you can't just make,
you cannot, like, change the definition
of a word.
Well, the problem is that's not enforceable.
Things will just change no matter what.
You can't even have an organizational body
impose from top down what words mean,
because they're just responding
to what people do in the world anyway.
Well, there you go, Nate.
It sounds like the languages reflect the cultures.
No one would even think to do that
for English because it's like,
okay, is London gonna decide?
You think you're gonna have any luck getting America?
This is all to my point,
that these are limitations of language, yeah.
But French, I mean,
I'm sure there's lots of French
places around the world,
but it's mostly France, right?
Isn't it?
Yes.
So, like, France is a big country.
Yeah.
There's a lot of places that speak French,
like in Africa.
There's different French dialects.
But what's your point?
What's your point, though?
The point is,
French can do shit like that
because it's a little bit more centralized.
English can't, you know,
other languages reflect their
geographical realities,
so I think those languages are perfectly fine
for those kinds of people.
I...
Okay.
The racism problem.
Why can't we just say,
okay, racism...
People think racism
means two different things,
or maybe even multiple different things.
All you gotta do is just correct them.
So, let's...
Let's just add an adjective.
Oh, this is special racism,
special racism.
Like, are there...
No, because people with a...
Traditional racism.
People with a political agenda
don't want to do that
because they want to manipulate the masses.
That is true.
Like, when you...
When, like, somebody says,
that was racist.
Or, like, just for example,
if, like...
This is just a crazy example,
but, like, if a minority, like,
kills a white person,
they say that's not a hate crime
because it wasn't motivated by race.
Like, even if the person said,
like, let's say this person said,
I'm killing this white person
because they're white,
that's why I'm doing it.
Like, like, the new definition
can make a case that that wasn't a racist
and wasn't a hate crime
because, in their definition,
it's...
You can only be racist
if you lack social...
Here's my fucking thing.
Yeah, if you lack social power.
With the confusion of words,
here's why the confusion of words
is natural and good
and should be embraced.
People...
What you're doing, Nate,
is you're doing the fallacy
to reframe what I said earlier,
the fallacy of wanting to have
permanent simplifications.
What I want is interesting conversations.
How is it...
What is the fallacy?
There are...
It's not, I guess, a fallacy...
It's not like a logical fallacy,
but it's a...
What would you call it?
A fool's errand
to try to find some sort of formula.
Okay, sure.
And I know it's a fallacy
that programmers,
especially fallen to all the time,
they want to, like,
come up with some sort of formula
that just takes the edge off.
And that's what people want
with, like, communication.
Oh, if we just have this
perfect formula.
No, no.
I'm finishing this point.
So, that's the reason
why these podcasts
always derail into these
technical conversations,
because we're trying to, like,
find the perfect, like, formulation
of the exact definition.
Whereas if we just let
the confusion reign
and just, like,
iron out little kinks
as we want,
then the podcast will be better.
And if you let conversations
and different disagreements,
like what racism means,
means you can always make
communicating your definition
of racism part of the conversation.
It gives you something
to fucking talk about
and makes the conversation
a little bit less inane.
It's a waste of time.
And if you know exactly
how to rebut
every version of the
wrong version of racism,
you can already have
your prescripted rebuttals
ready to go,
won't even take any effort.
That's not true.
The thing is to prove,
in this very podcast,
I have seen people
bring up things that Nate
has gone back on.
Um,
like, maybe they,
like what?
They didn't,
they forgot about it.
Like, like, like,
you saying language sucks.
Like, we only said that
right at the very beginning.
That's the one thing
I went back on.
And, but, like,
that has, like,
colored the perceptions
of everyone.
And, and they, they,
they hang,
they, they hung on to that
to, to, to bring it up
and like,
well, I'm framing this
from this perspective
that you have now gone back
on, but I forgot,
or like I didn't listen,
or I wasn't really
thinking about it.
It's just Nate is still
on this whole,
Nate, you're still on this
whole case of like,
fucking, uh, well,
you know,
language isn't like perfect,
but it's not like bad,
but it's not like perfect.
Like, I don't care.
Got him.
Well, for somebody
like, oh, oh,
got him.
Oh, I don't see me
dabbing right now.
I don't know who's been
got here.
The one thing that I,
I feel like is like,
it's kind of like
lawyering.
It's kind of like the
law, the justice system
and laws and lawyers,
where the,
the point of,
like using,
co-opting a word
and making it,
have a different definition
to, to push a
political agenda is,
um,
like just like how law
is written to be
incredibly confusing
so that poor people
can't figure it out
and they have to pay
a really expensive guy
to translate it for them.
Sure.
And, um,
this is,
this is a really nasty thing
and I don't like it.
These are,
these are trans issues.
The fact that someone has to
translate, I get it.
Oh, well.
And it's,
and it's,
it's just sort of like,
people don't have,
like,
say a word is changed,
like 50 words are changed
and somebody just
wasn't paying attention
because they don't use
those words often.
And then they see,
they read a thing
and they're like,
they're really confused,
but they don't have
like the time
or like they're too,
they just don't,
it doesn't come up enough
in their life
to think about
all the different things
that are going on
and keep track of all of them.
They probably have to pay
a guy to,
to, to give them
like an update every so often
like an app on their phone
to like,
all right, here's what this
word means now.
You got all the books
that in the,
in the past,
now you know why they're
so confusing.
And it's like,
it's just,
I don't like it.
I don't have an answer.
I know why we can't do
that thing with racism.
I know why we can't
like just be like,
okay, well now there's
two different racisms.
It's because that,
it's because unlike,
unlike the French,
those rat bastards,
we don't,
we don't have like a council
that decides what words mean.
Words mean whatever we say
they mean.
Words mean whatever
we collectively agree
that they mean.
And, and that's why,
there's a disagreement
unfortunately.
There is a,
there is a disagreement,
but there's no authority
that can step in
and say like,
well, here's what it actually means.
Yeah.
That's the biggest problem.
But, but new words
have been made before.
There have been new words made.
So can't we do that?
Well,
but they weren't,
but they weren't like,
to be used by everybody
is really difficult.
They weren't passed down
from on high.
They were like,
they, they like generated,
I mean,
except maybe in certain cases
they were generated
out of the ether.
And like,
and like a grassroots kind
of campaign could like,
you know,
campaign for a new word
or something.
You know,
you know,
remember there's a book called
frindle.
Remember that book,
frindle?
I never read it.
Do you remember that book,
the Hobbit?
the Bible?
No,
no,
it's an actual point.
Okay.
J.R.R.
Tolkien created a language
of Elvish.
He created a whole language
of Elvish
that people can study
and it's like really funny
and they can pretend
to be elves
and they can speak
with Elvish
and it's all really funny
and cool.
And the reason that language
will never change
is because people don't want
to be non-canon.
They don't want to be like
that guy.
So they will always stay
to the canon language.
So there is an authority.
So Elvish will never devolve
into something like,
there will never be Elvish
like,
slang.
I don't know, slang.
Yeah.
I mean,
you could have your head cannons
and stuff,
but no one really want,
people who are into that
don't really want to do that.
And I like that.
I just enjoy the fact
that that can exist
and authority
that people all agree on,
like yes,
we'll stick to this.
We talk in Elvish,
we know exactly what the other
person is saying all the time.
In fact,
everyone should speak in Elvish.
It's really funny.
Actually,
if we start using it,
we'll just face the same problems
we have with English now.
Yeah, no, no.
Hippo, hippo, hippo, hippo.
Secret, secret, secret club,
like little brother languages
where you're like,
instead of saying,
hello, I'm going to say,
go, go, go, go.
And,
you know,
secret languages like that
between two people
are the tightest form
of communication.
I always prefer that
to like speaking real.
So the reason why Elvish doesn't change
isn't because of like fandoms.
I think we have experience enough
with fandoms to know
they missed the point of the work.
It's the fact that no one
is a like resident of Elfland, right?
So like no one fucking is actively,
like it's not their primary language.
No one like lives a society of Elvish.
You only do it in the form of studying.
There's no people to evolve with.
Right.
So I think the reason
why Elvish doesn't change
is for the same reason
like I guess Greek
probably doesn't change anymore
because no one actually
like uses it like a real language.
They just use it
as a thing they've studied.
Besides the country of Greece.
The Greeks do.
Oh, the Latin world country of Greece.
Latin is a dead language.
Latin.
There we go.
Yeah.
That one.
That fucking one.
Yeah.
Let's all speak Latin.
That's an issue with language
that's brought up.
How, you know,
the Bibles ran exclusively
in land in the olden days.
And so the poor,
you know,
the poor baby bitch fuckers
couldn't actually read the Bible.
They didn't know what the fuck
was going on.
That's a problem.
Used to subjugate people.
I did it.
I'm the anti-language person.
Okay.
I have a statement
and I want to see
if everyone agrees.
Okay.
We have language.
It's not perfect.
False.
No, no.
We have language.
It's not perfect.
If there were better
alternatives,
that would be nice.
But there aren't any.
So what we currently have
is better than nothing.
Yeah.
Agree.
Well, I think Nate
was like going on this
like maybe they could
like could we work
towards like stuff
like we should start
working towards a better version.
Yeah.
That's part of my statement.
If there was a better version,
that would be nice.
Oh, actually,
I do know a thing about this.
I remember reading like an article.
I read the actual article.
Well, okay.
I skimmed it.
And it was about how like,
oh man, wouldn't it be cool
if we instead of like
all these really messy languages
with all these inconsistencies,
you know,
even if you go to like,
Japanese or Korean
where it's like,
hey, there's no pronunciation
bullshit.
Then it's like, oh, you know,
Japanese,
here's all this kanji bullshit,
right?
So it's like,
it's like technical and accurate
and clean with no bullshit.
And someone like did a study
of this.
They like had like computers
algorithmically like generate
some languages
and it had people like practice
with them.
The point is what they found
and I don't know how tested
this was yet,
but humans actually only
really get a grip on
bullshit languages
because our brains are
themselves a bullshit
mishmash-pishposh
of billions of years of evolution.
So like,
we don't actually
ever think as cleanly
as robots ever will
because we're just a fucking mess.
We're a fucking mess
genetically.
You know what the future is?
The future is like Isaac Asimov
where all the kids
don't learn English,
they just learn programming
language and everyone has
a programming job
because that's the only thing
humans are useful for.
Eventually that one
is being useful.
They maintain all the robots.
That's sad.
A lot of robots be able to do
that before too long too.
It was really sad when I first
read it,
but I kind of,
I think it's kind of cool
how that guy that from so long
ago had that idea.
Yeah, but I like
language because
I'm specifically English
because of how silly it can get.
I like the stupid,
oh whoa,
and verb,
and doggo,
and shit like that.
I love it.
It's great.
It'd be sad to see it go.
Yeah.
This will be an extremely
unpopular opinion,
and I will be,
I'll,
no, go for it.
Language.
Sorry, I was stretching
while talking.
I'll be berated
both in the comments
and right now.
But isn't the sort
of uncertainty of language
kind of romantic?
Isn't it kind of neat to be able
to write down something
that's awful,
how to be interpreted
in different ways?
That's like why.
I think it's good for like
having a friend
and chumming out
and like making a funny joke.
Yeah.
But when it comes to politics,
I feel like people should
talk in bleeps and bloops.
It gives rise to like poetry
and puns
and,
you know,
cute shit like that.
I like that.
I'm probably willing
to accept the artistic
narrative language.
Yeah, I mean,
it's,
language is both an art
and a science depending
on how it's being used.
Mm-hmm.
It's funny though,
like if we're used to it
like this,
like things that are serious
being used with words
that can also be used
to make art.
But like,
imagine if like politics
was done with drawings
instead of,
you know.
Sorry,
just imagine
politicians finger-painting.
Yes,
if finger-painting,
having the deviant art
being used
instead of like Donald Trump's
Twitter,
it would be like,
Donald Trump's made another
mural.
Trump's made another mural,
everyone,
check it out.
That's why he wants
to make the wall
so he can put his
mural somewhere.
Politics does
definitely need to be
a much more visual medium
than it is.
I remember back in like
2012,
like,
Mitt Romney was all like,
oh man,
there's been less oil drilling,
less American energy
than Obama.
I was like,
oh,
it was actually 45% up
the previous.
No,
it was like 25% down
the previous year
of the government grants.
All right, guys,
you bitches need to
have a fucking easel
and show us some fucking
charts, please.
I can't hold all these
words in my head at once.
Here's where
I will spiral into
absolute madness
that I deserve to be
criticized for.
But it's like,
beyond language,
I get frustrated
with facts.
Yeah.
It's in the sense that
I've had enough of these
facts.
I've had enough of
these facts.
But the problem is,
just like with language.
Yeah, I know,
I know exactly what you're
talking about.
With this Mitt Romney
example,
who knows,
who's like,
when Mitt Romney said a fact,
I'm sure that fact
was true.
Then Obama
raises more facts
that contextualize,
but it is entirely possible
that there are yet facts
beyond that
further contextualize.
Oh,
that's why I don't
research things.
You know,
it's just like,
you know what,
how,
what are we expected to do?
That's why,
like I want to know
literally every fact
to make an opinion.
You're talking about
cherry picking facts,
where you present
a fact that sounds good
without it's a broader
context to give it more meaning.
I mean, the problem is,
the problem is to me,
like you've got
guys on like the
left wing and the right wing.
And like,
if you just see a fact
tweeted by like whatever,
you know,
a journalist or whatever
that's like in your team,
you can read that.
Then the opposition will say,
well,
you didn't contextualize it,
blah, blah, blah.
But then,
and then like a person
by doing this like first
level fact check
will feel satisfied,
but it's entirely possible
that there's an infinite
spiral of yet further
fact checkings
that need to happen.
That's because life is complicated.
And if you want to be informed,
you have to be the guy
that's like,
I guess I'm just gonna
have to do a deep dive
on every tweet
ever tweeted.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, you really do.
Like you have to basically
like check up facts
as a lifestyle
to where you get
an intuitive sense of it.
That's the only way to do it.
That really is.
And you know guys,
no one does it.
This is,
I mean,
it's similar to just
my personal frustration.
You know,
you can feel free to
disagree as you have,
but it's just like,
that's why when someone
like says a sentence,
like that,
I feel like make a tweet.
Like I feel frustration with this.
Like I can try to make it
seem like what I want it to.
And I know that
like Twitter is limited
as opposed to like
writing a blog post or whatever.
But it's just like,
I just want to communicate
literally every fact
about this thing
I'm trying to say.
And I feel a deep frustration
that it's so hard to do that.
And you know,
I know language is
a ton of great stuff.
But I just,
oh, it kills me.
Kiss myself.
But it's like,
oh no, no, you don't understand.
Like I was actually
at the urinal
and there were just a couple of drops.
I was like,
I'm not a real guy.
Like technically,
yes, I did piss myself.
And also I was spooked
by a clown.
So it wasn't even my fault.
Like this is,
there's yet further context
beyond this.
And we can go all day.
And I was at a clown rodeo
as a matter of fact.
So like,
maybe I should have been prepared.
So maybe I'm actually
in the wrong here.
You know, we can go all day.
The problem with language
is like the problem
with all things,
clowns over the abundance of clowns
makes us all piss ourselves
and languages ruined forever
at the site of one jug alone.
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad
we went through with this exercise.
I guess,
do we have final points here?
You want to wrap up here?
What language do you guys want to learn?
I want to learn,
I like English.
I want to learn American sign language.
I want to learn Arabic.
I think that would be really funny.
More like Arabic.
Arabic looks really nice.
I like Arabic.
I like the way it's all swishy and swishy.
It looks intimidating to learn.
Yeah.
It probably isn't.
That's from the early,
that part of the world
is where the first languages
even came out of the ground.
I want to give...
I mean,
the Arabic numbering system was pretty good,
so I'd hope their actual language holds up.
Is that what we use?
Yes.
One, two, three, four, five.
That's right.
Way to go, guys.
Didn't they invent the zero over there, too?
I think it was India, actually.
I think it was zero.
Oh, okay.
Some fucked up freak.
As I'm sure everyone knows,
I wish to continue learning Japanese
specifically for just practical
and artistic reasons,
because I think it's cool.
Yeah, same here, Nate.
I just want to be able to listen to anime
while I'm doing the other shit.
Same.
That would be great.
I also want to learn Esperanto
for some of the reasons we talked about here.
Having that universal language,
I think everyone should learn it.
Everyone should learn it.
It'd be great.
I dab on dubs.
That's what I have to say to that.
Ben, you didn't talk about how cool
big words are with me.
Oh, wait.
I thought you were saying
that you liked the rare words,
because I prefer a rare word to a big word.
Well, okay.
I agree that rare words are better,
but big words are also nice.
I feel like most of the time,
they're in tandem.
Like, most of the time,
the reason words are rare
is because they're big
and no one wants to say them.
Yeah.
You like flexing your vocabulary
every now and then, you know?
Exactly.
I love it.
There's nothing wrong with flexing,
but I think better than using
a big word or a rare word.
The best thing is when you need,
like, an unusual word
to express something nuanced,
and then you fucking have it,
and you pull it out at just the right second.
Sure.
And you express something so nuanced
and so subtle
that everyone is just blown away by it.
Your vocabulary is fucking awesome right now.
That is satisfying.
Vocabulary is great.
Back in, like, sixth grade,
there was, like, a vocabulary word of the day,
and, you know, you would teach you shit like
fey or, you know, whatever the hell,
basic bitch shit.
I wish there was just, like,
was mage toward it.
Mage, there was an opening.
You can just jump in.
Just jump in there, mage.
Go.
What is it?
I said earlier,
what do you know what a sesbicodalian is?
No.
Equestria daily?
No, sesbicodalian.
Sesclid.
I do not.
Your vocabulary eclipses.
Is that a flower?
No.
Dalian.
What is it?
Well, look it up.
I don't know how to spell that.
Well, anyway, I'm saying that there should be
vocabulary words of the day for everyone, forever.
E-S-Q-U-I-P-E-D-A-L-A-N.
It means gay.
No.
Mages calling us all gay.
How rude.
No.
I called you weenies at the beginning.
Sesquidalian.
Spelled F-A-G-G-O-T.
Look it up, everybody.
Oh, no.
You might enjoy that.
No.
Hey, Nick, can you spell A-G-O-T real quick?
I'm doing an exam.
I'm doing a spelling test right now,
and I was wondering if you could try to figure it out.
I don't want to be bullied.
I won't do it.
I won't suffer.
Vocabulary is good, kids.
Check it out someday.
Words are cool.
Hey, have I talked about this before?
I think this is the time.
There's a part in the book, The Plague,
by Albert Camus,
where the main character,
he goes to like hang out with this guy that he knows.
And the guy kind of,
they kind of open up and become a little friendly.
And the guy finally decides to share with him
this thing that he's been working on,
that he kind of doesn't usually talk about,
but he's like, okay, I'll show you.
I'll show you, because you're my buddy.
And he brings it out.
And what it is,
is this thing that he's been working on for like years,
is he has been polishing one sentence
to be the ultimate sentence,
like the most beautifully poetic sentence
in the French language.
And it's, um...
Your mom gay.
Le Danque means...
Okay, well, he...
Like, he revises it a couple of times,
so I'm not sure if this is the original,
but it doesn't matter.
The sentence is, more or less,
one fine morning in May,
a slim young horsewoman might have been seen
riding a glossy sorrel mare
along the flower-strewn avenues of the Bouda Bouillon.
Aw, that's pretty good.
That sounds pretty good.
I like his sorrel.
Yeah, I liked it.
So he did it.
The sort of horse-boy-fucking-horse?
What's with the horse-boys?
And he says that one day, when it's perfect,
he'll bring it to the publishing house,
and he'll show it to them.
And everyone on all the publishers
will stand up and say, gentlemen, hats off.
Hats off!
It's like that family guy bit.
It's like the best joke ever,
which is, guess what?
Chicken butt.
That's it.
Perfect joke.
You know, a family guy is basically
a modern-day Albert Camus, I think.
Here's Languages Fatal Flaw.
The word nautical does not mean radical.
Nautical, by all rights, by its birthright,
deserves to be a cinnamon for, like,
sick or con-
A cinnamon?
A cinnamon, you say?
How delectable.
A cinnamon.
It deserves to be like, dude,
that's fucking nautical, bro.
Yeah, dude, fucking it.
Shouldn't it be the opposite of radical?
Like, you can be radical, or you can be nautical?
Nautical, yeah.
No, no, I think...
I mean, that's good, but I think it should be, like,
reserved for when we invent underwater skateboarding.
No, that's coming up real quick.
Like, not surfboarding, underwater skateboarding.
Like, with really heavy wheels.
Yeah.
Imagine grinding upon the Great Barrier Reef
right into a shark.
You had that really heavy shoes, too.
The Great Barrier Reef is, like, gone now, right?
That's completely dead.
That's just because of all the grinding of the
so many skateboarding people are doing.
We need to stop.
Sick.
Grinding.
Why don't we...
I feel like we're Peter and Adher fan.
What do you think?
I think I'm ready to move on to the question.
I think we need to close out...
I actually...
We need to close out with teaching everybody a new word, right?
I just did.
I'll speak with Dalian.
You didn't tell us what it means, though.
Well, it's just anything.
It's homework.
That's cute and all, Mage,
but let's talk about a really important word
that Nate taught us before the podcast began.
It's Alexa.
Alexaed on everything.
Oh, yeah!
Alexaed, yeah.
Commanding a person like you would command
an Amazon Alexa.
Kid 1, mom, stop.
And mom did stop talking.
Kid 2, wow, mom.
He just Alexaed you.
Truly, language is evolving in a beautiful way.
That's my point.
Host about nuclear gaming.
Nuclear gaming.
You know that?
Also, there was a gif of Ed Sheeran under that definition.
I don't know why, but it was there.
And we all have to live with that.
Well, I feel Alexaed to getting to the goddamn Amazon.
I was planning.
I actually signed up onto this episode
so I could talk about free speech
and where people draw the line
between free speech and where you can have a...
And how it relates to words.
So, we'll save that for another episode.
Free speech, guys.
That'll be a PCP episode at some point.
That's a good idea.
I like doing that.
We should actually write that down.
Yeah, add it to the list.
I actually did it while Nate was going off
his five-hour inane, whether or not words are perfect.
Thank God something was done today.
You're just mad, because I'm literally Starfleet.
Look at me go.
Okay, go on, go on.
Guys, Magiskule.
Yeah, what's that?
That's the word I'm bringing to the table.
Magiskarp.
Try and figure it out.
Magiskule.
What do you think?
It's like minuscule, only a magic version of being minuscule.
Very close.
It's the opposite of minuscule.
Instead of saying capital letters, you could say magiskule.
So, when are we going to get some magiskule reviews on Hippocrate?
That's fucking sick.
I should definitely do that now.
That's a great idea.
And what is something that's big, other than something that's small, that's magical?
Rayman2, everyone.
Rayman2 coming up next video.
Magiskule review.
Well gone, the Magiskule bus.
Nobody cares about Rayman2 except for you.
No!
It's Rayman2!
They're cheering!
They're clamoring for Hippo outside of my window.
There's just a crowdful piece of Mandigrad.
I mean, Rayman2.
We're done.
We've had a lot of fun here today, but it's time to get serious.
Yeah, it's time to close.
Time to nut up or shut up.
Before we get to questions, me and you, Nate, have followed that we need to settle.
That's right, everybody.
If you listened to last week's episode, Munchie and I made a sacred pact where we both agreed
that we would be healthy boys in different ways and made some health resolutions.
So let's lay our cards on the table.
Munchie, what was your thing and how to go?
My resolution was that I would not drink a single carbonated drink
because I've been drinking too much energy drinks.
And I'm happy to announce that I have not drinking a single carbonated drink since that recording
until now.
Oh!
Look at Munchie go!
What a shame.
He's doing so well.
Well, you know what? There's nothing wrong with taking a cheat day, you know?
Or a cheat meal.
Wait, Munchie, how's it taste?
It feels so fucking good!
No, he's a lost cause.
So to check in, congratulations Munchie.
You've earned it. You've earned that.
So my thing was I swore off sugar.
And it's kind of hard to avoid sugar just forever.
So what I defined that as was I defined it like anything with additional sugar added to it.
Gee, I don't know if I agree with that definition of sugar.
I think we're going to have to have some psychically connected language here
to get to consensus on what sugar means.
Well, I mean, there is no consensus. I make the rules and this is what they wear.
To me, sugar is sexist language and I should say it.
So here's how it went. It went great until Thursday.
And here's what happened. Here's what happened.
I was at the grocery store. I was buying, you know, nutritious food with no sugar.
And I simply walked by. My mind was absent. My balls were empty.
And I walk by a free display giving away little donut pieces.
Oh, no!
Little cookie pieces. And I just don't even think.
I just say, oh, cool, free. And I take a piece and I eat it.
That capitalism just overwhelmed everything.
And then I take a cookie. There was these little cranberry cookies and I just eat that.
I continue on my way. Don't even think of it.
And then I realized like a fucking shock from God.
I realized what I have done.
I've done this before. It was the worst.
I almost did this too. It's funny that like you guys did like a diet thing
or like a good boy thing because I've been doing a good boy thing for the last week as well.
I've restarted doing intermittent fasting because I enjoy doing it a lot. Yes.
Aren't you skinny enough, dude?
No, no. I'm like 220 pounds, dude. It's disgusting.
220 pounds? Okay.
You're also like six foot two.
Yeah, that's true. I forgot.
The scale doesn't care how tall you are.
So you just you only eat in an eight hour window and it's fast for 16 hours
and it's fucking great.
I did it for a week and I almost did that because I've been going to the coffee shop
and they had like little free samples.
Have you been weighing yourself? Have you been weighing yourself?
Do you have progress?
My scale is broken, but I feel significantly better and that's enough for me.
That's good.
Okay, so intermittent fasting sounds really great, but okay,
because like I'm never hungry when I wake up in the morning.
Like I don't want to eat until later in the day.
Yeah.
But isn't that like what they say not to do?
Don't they say to like space your calories out over the day or something?
Well, usually they also suggest to not eat like two or three hours
before going to bed or something like that.
That is commonly suggested.
That's true.
The science behind quote unquote the science behind this.
Yeah, that's all bullshit.
But it's like you have there's like a your when you start,
you're like metabolic, whatever, like when you start digesting things,
like it goes for like, I think like the 10 to 12 hours and then it stops
and anything you eat after that like doesn't get properly metabolized or something.
So like you're, you're designed, I guess designed not to do that.
So I'm just eating it at eight hour window to make sure that that doesn't happen.
I guess I don't know.
I've had, I guess that makes sense.
I've done it before.
I couldn't hunt animals all the time.
And I lost the fucking time to wait just doing it.
So I'm doing it again because it worked for me.
That was last week's topic that you guys were like doing good boy thing.
I wasn't on last week.
So I was drugs.
Okay.
Yeah.
I guess that would be that would be good topic.
We had to, we had to detox after that podcast.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's a good part of the podcast because this week has been very fun for me in terms of
eating food.
And today I've been eating nothing but cake.
So because it's my cake day.
Yes.
It is.
By the way, just continuing going forward.
I've made a resolution.
I'm just, I'm giving up additional sugar just forever.
I'm just, I mean, you know, one day I'll probably go back on that.
But just for the future, I'm not putting sugar in anything.
I'm not eating cake.
I'm not eating anything that has sugar added to it.
I'm like the biggest thing I might do is I might indulge in a glass of fruit.
Juice.
I may do that because that's not, that's not like additional sugar.
It's just the fruit.
But I'm going to try to stay away from it.
Juice is bad for your teeth.
Fair point.
As is coffee, which I have been drinking and I want to be away from it.
But anyway, just brush your teeth an hour after you consume something sugary.
And by the way, since I'm doing this anyway, I'll check in everybody.
I'll let you know how the sugar thing's going.
If I fail, I'll let you know.
I'll let you know.
I wouldn't throw my hand in the ring, but honestly my life is just worse not drinking
carbonated drinks.
So I'm not going to do it.
I'm like my hero Thanos.
I'm willing to take personal sacrifices to achieve the greater good.
As soon as I watch Infinity War, I'm like, this is Nate's OC.
It's Nate.
It's not even.
Yeah.
Like the whole, like having to the movie, I was just like, I was like, Thanos is war.
All right.
That was just my headmate.
He's my headmate.
No, no more Infinity War.
No more.
Wait, he's right.
I'm good too.
I want to say I'm a good boy.
I started tracking my calories again.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
I can make it, but I'm back.
Great.
Then what is the fear to crack cocaine?
Poor.
Oh yeah?
Are you working out, Ben?
Are you lifting?
I did a bit ago start again, and then I stopped again, but I mean to start again, and I feel
like I've still got a little bit of that momentum, but yeah.
So I did for a second, but I didn't keep up with it.
Why does working out suck so bad?
It feels good to actually do it.
Actually, you know what?
I'll do that today.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
Thank you.
I've been personally, I've been adding running to my lifts, to my exercise feels great, but
whatever.
Let's move on.
Ben, what, hold on.
What is the pulling out your beard hair about?
Like I've never had that before in my life.
What's why?
Oh God, do we have to talk about this embarrassing?
If you don't want to.
Yeah, I fucking, yeah, I have like a nervous, I have like a nervous tick that I fucking pull
my hair out.
I have a worse nervous tick, Ben.
Yeah, I saw this.
Don't want to make me feel better.
My nervous tick is I bite the shit out of my lips until they bleed.
My nervous tick is I scratch my face off.
My nervous tick is that there's a tick who lives on my head who's just very anxious about
life.
That explains a lot about life.
I have a very wild nervous tick, which is that I grind my index finger.
I do that too, but it's funny.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let Davoo say, let Davoo say something.
I grind my index finger into my thumb on my right hand, and if you do it for only like
a minute, it creates a little groove.
So even though I was only nervous for a minute, I now have like a bubble wrap popping tick
to keep grinding into it and making it worse.
Right?
Hippo.
Like the hair does grow back, but like if it gets bad and it does a lot lately, I will
pick like a small patch or even sometimes like a really big patch.
It has happened before that I have picked off like a large portion of my face has been
like plucked free of beard hair due to my fucking brain problems.
Take your hands busy, Ben.
Well, easier said than done.
Yeah.
Wrap it, wrap it.
I know.
But like just get into the habits.
Your hands can't stand against your face if they're wrapped around your cock.
It does grow back, but if I do it, if I do it too much of it too fast, it will leave
like a bear patch.
And then I'm like, well, I can't fucking walk around like this and then I have to shave
my beard because.
Ben, you don't go anywhere.
What does it matter?
Well, it just makes me sad all along.
You should wear a coat for your beard.
Tom, I bite the inside of my mouth all the time and I'm constantly tasting blood based
on it.
Oh God.
That would drive me crazy.
That's rough.
I bite my nails.
It's pretty bad.
Sometimes it gets bad.
No.
Shall we get to the question?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's.
Hey.
Don't bite your nails.
It's very bad for you.
You couldn't be more right.
I wish I stopped.
I was.
Yeah, but I'm not Michael Jackson of two hands.
That's it.
That's my excuse.
Listen, everybody.
Hashtag ask PCP Twitter at TP Crastinators.
Here's some also in the patron discord, $1 pledge to our fucking patron here in there
and we'll read more questions.
Here's the pity question and we don't need to spend a lot of time with this because I've
looking there are like no good questions, but here's the here's the one that's like
sort of good.
You're all going to hate me, but I'm a read anyway at chemotherapy just asks if giving
up a year of your life advanced human progress by 50 years.
How many years are you willing to give up to those advantage you're waiting for?
And what are they?
Well, zero unless I thought that like within a window that I could buy with that time,
we would hit the singularity.
That's the one.
That's the thing.
Yeah.
My question is, do we advance instantaneously like would I be living in a society 50 years
more advanced by giving up your my life or would it just happen somewhere down the road?
Because if I don't get to experience it, everyone can get fucked.
If I can give up a decade and get a robot body instantly, therefore living forever sounds
like a fair trade.
Yeah.
I mean, I do that.
I guess the question is, do we think we're going to hit the singularity within like, I
don't know, let's say we all have like 50 years left.
So like within 2500 years, will we hit the singularity?
I would give up one year if the advancement of humans by 50 years destroys hypothetical
questions.
Come on.
You know, even even if I don't like him so much, even Digi.
You and Digi are, I have an ethical problem with people that don't like hypothetical questions.
I don't like hypothetical questions.
These are so cratic exercises.
Disliking of hypothetical questions is just evidence of a small mind.
The thing about this particular one is it's just like, here's some numbers, which number
like?
It isn't.
It makes you fucking think.
It makes you fucking question your values.
I'm not thinking.
I do like certain types of hypothetical questions like the ones that like give you really bad
options and then like makes you mentally suffer for them.
I hate those.
Yeah.
No.
I like the ones that make you think like this one is fine, but the ones is like, oh,
would you kill one baby or would you kill like three babies?
I'd definitely kill three.
Unless we have the best.
Here's a hypothesis.
I like that one.
That's funny.
Like what does it mean for it to progress by 50 years?
This isn't vague at all.
God damn.
Yeah, this isn't very vague.
Here's a hypothetical.
What if like the Simpsons were like in Undertale though?
Well, Nate, well, Nate does have yellow skin, so perhaps that's not as far fetched
as you think.
Oh my God.
We're in Undertale Homer.
We got to get out of here.
Back to the original hypothetical question, like if let's say I give up a year, right?
And like I see the advancement happening like immediately.
And would I still have the option to give up one more year after I see what's happened
within those 50 years?
That is a good question.
I don't fucking know.
That actually does make a big difference.
Yeah, because let's say if I could see what's happening.
This is the reason.
This is the reason why I don't like hypothetical questions, at least of this kind.
It's that sometimes the question, like if you're not with the person who made the question,
you can't clarify and then you are just, the discussion is about, I wonder what this question
actually means.
Yeah, I mean, sure.
I think I may have just straight up heard the question wrong.
What exactly was the question?
It's giving up a year of your life, advanced human progress by 50 years, how many years
would you give up?
Yeah, that's too vague.
I insist that that is way too vague.
You guys, you guys, let's get on to the other questions.
Other questions.
This is a significantly less boring than whatever.
It's fun to think about though.
I agree.
So anybody fucking looking at the goddamn question bar?
I'm looking at it.
Okay.
What do you got for us?
Are we looking at the lounge?
I'm looking at it.
I don't fucking have anything.
Are you joking me?
It's all shit.
There's a question.
Is it made just for you today?
Or did you just really like cake?
Both.
Yeah.
That's good.
I'll just substitute the word birthday for cake day because it's more fun that way.
Okay.
I'm just like looking for questions.
Someone asked me, Kajaro Bitterthorn said, if you suddenly acquired a shit ton of money,
what would be the one ridiculously indulgent thing you'd want to do?
I would want a house.
I need a place to live.
Indulgent.
What the fuck dude?
Be happy with your living cube as dispensed by the state.
Your 3x3 foot.
God, I wish I could have a 3x3 living cube given me by the state.
That's all I need.
As a millennial.
I wouldn't even complain.
Yeah.
Same.
As a millennial, you don't get a house, you get avocado toast instead.
Oh, yeah.
Much like how...
You get Burger King foot lettuce and nothing else.
Much like how Gen Z's, me, are post job.
Millennials are post house.
They do not.
They don't have need for housing.
I don't even want one.
Okay.
I would totally live in a cube.
You know what?
I don't see any good questions.
So it's time to bring back the hashtag PCP bullying segment.
So here we go with Kajaro Bitterthorn asked this terrible question.
If all the members of the PCP had a future diary style battle royale, who would be the
last one standing and who would...
What would your wish be?
I know a person who wouldn't be standing as fucking you because we would all get up on
you and fucking kill you.
You piece of shit.
God!
Agreed.
I'll give it like...
I don't know who would win, but I know who would lose.
The future diary was like because the world was ending, they needed a new God.
So like if none of us did anything, the world would just end and I...
Let it burn.
Who wants to live in a world with questions like these?
If Nate Besman found a journal that when he wrote down the name of any person on earth,
they died instantly, what would he do with it?
That has to be a joke.
That has to be intentionally bad.
I've got to write a manga about that concept.
There's no way that fucking...
There's no way that that guy who got that fucking book could make nearly as much of
a clusterfuck as the utilitarianist machinations of Best Guy Ever.
Yeah.
You ain't wrong.
Hey, here's a question that's not inherently shit, kind of.
Night Shift Clint asks, is all porn cuckoo-y?
Now hang on, you aren't pleasuring yourself to something slash someone you want to fuck
or get fucked by being fucked or getting fucked by something else.
Yeah.
What do you think?
That assumes things about the porn that you want.
I think yes.
Oh, well...
No, I mean you're just watching other people fucking and it's not you, so you know.
There's porn that is not to people.
Oh, well, I mean that's true.
That is true.
Well, still, you're watching something desirable and not participating in it yourself.
True.
But you know what?
It's really...
If you're a real cuck in real life, which again, there is no act...
It's fine if you do that.
Can I jump off this for a second?
But you enjoy not being involved.
Do you?
I would prefer to be involved in porn, physically.
This is something I thought about.
Do you think that cuckolding became a thing because everyone just watches porn so much
now?
Hmm.
I've always thought...
The rise of cuckolding is a result of people watching porn.
This is actually like really surprising to me.
Lots of thinking emojis right now.
I can't believe this.
That someone just casually dropped like an existential like total actual accuracy bomb
like that.
But I think I'm going to go with yeah.
Like, because...
Well, I don't know.
Because now I'm thinking about it, because I'm not into cucking, but I'm thinking...
I feel like I can possibly empathize with it a lot better now, because it's like the
idea is if you are not part of the, you know, you're just watching it, you're just...
You're not really there.
You have no accountability, no responsibility, nothing you can do wrong.
You can just project yourself on completely guilt-free, and that's kind of like why porn
is a lot easier than like actual sex, you know?
You don't have to like worry about anything.
I feel like...
I'm not cuckolding.
Just makes me sad.
Like down to my core, I hate it.
I mean, sure.
I feel like the appeal would be slightly different.
Like if it was like a live action, and then the girl says, haha, you're not doing it.
And then the person watching the screen is like, damn.
Yeah, that's real cuckoldry.
That's real cuckoldry.
Even if you're like...
If it's playing into that aspect.
If it's a picture, then you couldn't possibly be there, because they don't exist.
Yeah.
It's slightly different.
You know, I don't think they're like one and the same.
There might be a thread of connection, possibly, but I mean, I don't think they're anything.
You know, I have felt this way.
I have gone down this rabbit hole before and been like, okay, I'm watching this thing that
I like, but it's not me.
And I've gotten a little annoyed about it, like, damn it, why am I enjoying this?
Like this is just, this is what they want from me.
Like they tricked me.
Oh, yeah.
Like the porn.
Damn it.
Yeah.
They've won.
Like they went and did something good, something cool, and I am over here, like what, appreciating
them for that?
Fuck that.
I mean, you know, I mean, there's like, for example, you know, like video games are like
achievement simulators that you're not actually like, so like in the same way, you're kind
of like a cuck to like success of other people in a way, though I guess you are like playing
the game, but it's a little different, I guess.
You right now, viewer, are a cuck because you are not debating with the legendary best
guy ever.
You are leaving by carestakingly with the other podcast members.
You are a cuck right now.
Kill yourself.
All the rest of us are such relatable characters and Nate is just such a, such a, such a hateable
villain.
So he's a juggernaut of industry.
Here's a question by my cool man from the Patreon lounge.
When is the right age to have children?
And I also want to open this up to when's the right age to get married because this
is a thing that's, that's kind of a lot with the PCP as we all know.
Well, okay.
I think.
Yeah, go ahead.
Go ahead.
I think the right age to have children is whenever you're ready.
But yeah, I think having it too young will, like if you have it in your early twenties
or mid twenties, that's a lot of people did do that, but they, they, I mean, I can't assume
how they feel about it, but I, I don't think they would have, like some people may not
have liked it.
I guess it depends on what you want out of it and how you would want it in the first
one.
That's a yes to finish education just, just in case.
How it is when you're figuring out all the basic things in your life and you are no longer
feeling challenged, then do it.
Don't have kids because your parents want grandkids.
Oh yeah.
Fuck people.
Sure.
That's definitely, you gotta be financially stable.
Don't let the wanton of a baby be the thing that makes you have the baby.
Make it that you've, you've basically, you can go through your life day and be like, wow,
I didn't like freak out or emotionally melt down over anything and I have enough money
to be stable.
Wow.
It's a little bit boring.
Wait for when you're a little bit bored, not out of like depression boredom, but like
out of complacency boredom.
You know.
Then have kids.
Then you'll actually love your children for like genuinely and not like the sort of passive
aggressive love that most parents give.
I'm like, oh man, it sure is great taking care of you and not having a life.
And like, because the way I sort of see having a child is like your life ends there and like
now you're solely dedicated to making that child be successful.
There's been a rise of the argument that like immoral, it is literally immoral to have kids
and like, I understand the argument there.
It's immoral to have kids.
It's like bringing someone into the world against, you know, they can't consent to being
bored.
I mean, that's true.
And there will be some suffering in life.
And so like, I could see why people make that argument, but like, if you're trying to give
your kid the best chance possible, then I personally would argue that that's a pretty
pessimistic view.
I feel like there's good to be had.
I feel like there's sort of pessimistic, but it doesn't make it wrong.
Well, it's pessimistic, but it doesn't make it wrong.
Having children is immoral.
No, I'm not saying it's wrong.
Is kind of strange.
Well, hang on, Ben.
Are you arguing?
What do you think about that argument?
Well, that's, I mean, I don't.
It's tough.
I know it's a complicated thing.
Well, I think, I don't think it's immoral.
I don't think it's immoral to create a life, no.
I get, I could see why someone would think that if someone thinks that life is suffering
and terrible and not worth living, then I could see why you'd be like, well, why would
I want to force that on someone?
Like, I get it.
I think it's immoral.
I think if you're not able to properly take care of the child, I think if you're, that's
definitely true.
Even if you are able to properly take care of them, that doesn't mean they're going to
have a good time.
No, it doesn't.
But at that point, it becomes nebulous.
But I think it's absolutely wrong to have a child when you're not properly able to take
care of them.
This whole issue, I remember hearing this, like, way back, I've heard this on the internet
forever.
Like, oh man, a life is suffering.
Is it right to bring kids?
You know, like, if there was like a reverse limbo where you hang out before you have life,
like all it would take is some propaganda.
Like Pixar could have like a five minute little short animation before one of their movies,
which is this, right?
It's just like these little identity list souls hanging out in like pre-limbo, right?
And like they're all like really excited to like get a chance for life and they get, they're
given warnings.
It could be painful.
It could be hard.
But like if you're given the chance, you might be able to like live and experience things,
right?
And they'd be all like, everybody would be fucking excited to try it out.
So no, I'm going to say it's immoral to have kids if you're not ready, if you're being ignorant
about it.
But that's not actually how things work though.
I just consider ignorance to be a bad thing in general.
That's a very underrated sin.
Well, about the whole, back to the question originally, I do feel very strongly that there
is no right age to have kids or get married or do anything right.
Well, there is a certain age past which you should probably not be having kids if you're
a woman due to...
That is technically true.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, I mean...
Do you mean like you shouldn't or like you couldn't?
Well, it becomes a lot more complicated the older you get, like there might be birth complications
in the child you birth might not need.
That's true.
That's always a risk.
Yeah.
To a certain extent.
No, no, no.
I'm not saying you shouldn't.
It's just like you might want to start thinking about those things.
Like Maja's saying, like just as it makes sense to establish yourself financially before you
have kids, it also, in the same vein, like it is a biological fact and the current
world that like the older woman is, you know, like when a woman's like 65, like the likelihood
of their kid, I think specifically was having Down syndrome.
The percentage goes up a lot.
The menopause starts around 40 years old, I think.
Okay.
Let's say 40 or whatever it is.
So it's just that you're like, I'm just saying it's, I'm not saying it's immoral or anything.
It's just like you are not inherently necessarily giving your kid the most optimum chance in
the world.
That's all.
You know?
Well, we've all got to do the best with what we're given.
Yeah.
I agree.
Just saying.
Yeah.
It's just something to consider about your own life and stuff.
It's a fair point.
I definitely agree with you, Ben.
There is no real like right age to do anything, but I think there are certain like ages you
can genuinely like say where someone will be like maturity or like, you know, financially
or like, you know, well off wise.
Yeah.
You want to be stable.
I would say like the golden age for both those are probably like 35 for me.
That's probably a nice like late number.
Yeah.
That's pretty late.
I mean, for, I don't know.
Maybe not for millennials.
I mean, maybe not for millennials.
Literally 35 when they had us.
I mean, the average age is getting later.
Yeah.
I think.
Oh, well, actually, I mean, just unfortunately for men, that's perfectly fine.
For women, it actually does have some ramifications.
Yeah.
My parents were both 34 actually.
I think our parents were in there like mid-30s.
Yeah.
They were right around there.
My mom was fucking 40, baby.
That's why you got that fetal alcohol syndrome.
Yeah.
Give it up for Down syndrome, everybody.
Because as you get older, your blood just turns to alcohol.
You just ferment.
Yes.
I'll just say that I agree that like getting married and having kids is basically fine.
You know, biologically speaking, it makes sense to do it fairly early for a woman and
then financially you want to be stable.
That's really all I have to say.
But I would also just say that as opposed to age to do it, I personally just think I
would really want to vet the person I'm marrying before I commit my whole fucking life to
them.
That's true.
I'd give them a couple years, frankly.
That's me.
Yeah.
I don't think anyone would disagree.
A couple years.
No, I think you should probably jump into these things willy-nilly.
Yeah.
In my humble opinion, feel free to disagree.
All right.
Well, fuck it.
Let's move on.
Oh, there was one other question here that I wanted to reach and this goes beyond just
the specifics here.
It's just StanOnWheels asks, I'm sure in reference to the Furry podcast, is ActionGiraffe a fursona?
And this pretends to all animal boys.
Obviously.
No, he's not.
He's a separate entity.
Obviously.
Yeah.
ActionGiraffe is a completely separate entity.
He is a real-life globetrotting superstar who is a headmate of mine occasionally, but
he just travels rift to rift and, you know, he's got nothing to do with it.
Oh, he's occasionally, but not exclusively, a headmate.
Like, yeah, he has his own, he's got the outside.
He's incidentally also your headmate, but that's just kind of a coincidence.
He owns some time shares in your head.
He's got Ramona flowers.
The Ramona flowers like Skateboards.
Oh, okay.
Skateboards in a sick way.
When he doesn't have any other place to crash you, especially Skateboards.
Boy, that's right.
He owns a time share in Nate's head.
Boy, that's a new twist on the character.
When are we gonna get new fucking lore?
It's been like years.
What the fuck?
Why don't you watch ActionGiraffe is the best shit?
Why don't you watch the currently released as the time of this release, Weagua, that
is out right now that may or may not have him in a starring role?
Wait, does it actually, though?
Literally yes.
Okay.
I was like, why don't you go watch Weagua?
He may or may not be there, but actually he's not.
It's a lie.
But he's not.
Yeah, go watch Weagua, everybody.
ActionGiraffe.
There he is.
He's making a hiatus from his globe trotting and his movie Action starring with Tom Cruise.
And his AIDS habits.
No, no, no.
There's no hiatus from that.
He's committed to that lifestyle.
But I was just gonna say, everybody, that stupid walrus digit keeps insisting is a real
character that we all know isn't.
That's not a fursona.
Is investigator a fursona?
No, obviously not.
These are real human being non-animal boys.
They're their own guys.
Hey, are we done with that question?
Yeah, I'm not gonna say that.
I see Kajoro Bitterthorn asks, to all the members who haven't made lectures yet, do
you plan to in the future and what would they be about?
Yes.
Hey, they're all out, everybody.
Just shout out.
They're all out.
All lectures from RadCon three are out.
Mine was the last one from RadCon.
That's right.
Actually, it was the last one to happen, too, and the last one to release.
Neat.
Nifty.
I'm probably gonna say fashion.
You're excited?
It was the last one to be done.
I feel like I said in a questions of a PCP already that I'm planning on thinking of doing
a lecture.
Well, I guess everybody else.
When's the mage lecture gonna come out?
I don't know.
I don't know enough about things and stuff to do a lecture on.
Mage, just do a lecture on Lithuania.
Water cats.
What?
Water cat.
Oh, wait.
Do the lecture on what are those things where you sell OCs to people that's under their
things.
Exactly.
One, to transfer Munchy, I never read the water cat things.
Oh, it seems right up your alley.
Reading books of my alley.
Excuse you.
Anywho.
The adaptable thing.
I'm a very newbie in that area, so I don't really have the authority to lecture anyone
about it.
That hasn't stopped any of us.
Yeah.
I don't...
There's really only one thing I could do a lecture on, which is the game over thinker.
We've been talking about that for a while.
Davoo, you have to do a lecture on the Bible.
It has to happen.
I know.
I've been saying that right now.
I want that hot Davoo take.
We've got to do that.
We've got to film that in a church.
No, no, no.
Move the lecture.
You're supposed to lecture on something that you have an exceptional amount of knowledge
on, not just like above average.
That is true.
That's the ideal.
I'll do a lecture on God in the church.
I'll get the priest to do it.
The tough thing about the game over thinker is that I want to just psychoanalyze Movie
Bob for all day, but I think I'll just focus on the plot of the game over thinker series.
Just somewhere like that will probably be sufficient.
Would you argue that Movie Bob's game over thinker is similar to Sonichu in that there's
a story of a man behind this.
Yeah.
It actually apparently just relaunched the game over thinker series.
He's been trying to keep that ball rolling for a long time.
Yeah.
I guess I'll talk about that in the lecture.
I have a little bit of catching up to do, but not that much.
By the way, Davoo, on the last episode for drugs, I was doing the show notes and I searched
up the game over thinker episode like seven or whatever it was because you mentioned
they had bad audio.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
The audio was on parallel.
It was unbelievable.
Yeah.
I couldn't have fathomed.
It was behind seven walls.
It was behind seven walls and it was into a tin cannon and also underwater at the same
time.
You really can't oversell it.
Anyone who's getting hyped for how bad the audio is is not getting over hyped.
I'm going to look at that.
I have a couple good questions by this one guy.
One's bar.
Yes.
The two that I think are the best are, have you ever had any interesting or noteworthy
encounters with panhandlers or homeless people?
What do you think about how your community services deal with homeless people?
San Diego is notorious for being like one of the worst homeless cities in America.
It's absolutely terrible.
They just roam the streets constantly and they are just everywhere.
Absolutely everywhere.
Funny story Jackie told me about the homeless population in Atlanta.
Apparently when the Olympics came to Atlanta a couple years ago, the government of Atlanta
just paid lots of homeless people to leave.
They were like, here's some money.
Get out.
The Olympics are coming and we don't want you embarrassing us.
Oh my God.
That's a fix right there.
That's a fix.
Well, I'll tell you right now.
Just enough for a taxi ride?
That's a temporary solution.
I'll tell you right now.
Thanos would have implemented a permanent solution to this homeless situation if you
know what I'm saying.
When Hippo said how much money, I was just imagining him thinking, I'll find out where
the Olympics are going next and I'm going to be homeless there.
Free money.
What?
What an elaborate scheme.
I'll be the most homeless person on earth.
This was not exactly a homeless person or a panhandler, but one time I was walking around
New York.
I was in college and I was walking around and a guy, you know, he was like a black guy
in like an African robe or something.
He was all like traditionally dressed.
He was one of those guys that's like something about being Jewish, like black people are
like the real Jewish people, you know?
Those guys.
I was with my girlfriend at the time and I was taken completely off guard when he shouted
me out in the crowd and he was like, do you know that you are the devil?
Oh.
Because I was white because he was saying that white people are the devil.
He was like, do you know that you are the devil?
And I was like, no, sir, I did not.
Damn.
And I thought I handled it pretty well.
It's fucking just how true some facts are.
Well, as a future homeless person, I'm sure I'll be able to answer this question in great
detail in like a year or two.
Tom's going to be on the other side of this question.
All my crazy adventures will be great.
Actually, when I said no, sir, I did not.
Some guy in the crowd started snickering and I was like, yeah, guys.
Got him, dude.
Turn it around.
The other question from one spar is, do we need to answer this?
Oh, wait, wait, sorry.
Can I just respond to that?
This is just a short thing, but like this guy was home.
It wasn't like panhandling, but it was like a homeless guy.
So when I was in Japan and this experience haunts me to this day, I'm walking back from
the gym.
You know, it's like, Japan's like wealthy.
I'm just, I'm in Tokyo.
Just everyone's like going about their business, being a real dude in the city.
And I'm just walking back.
You know, it's the American guy walking through the city.
And I just, I see a homeless guy sitting on the side of the road and he's got all this
shit around him and stuff.
He's like, you know, dirty and stuff.
You know, it's fine.
It's just what he was.
And I look at him and I'm like, wait, he's playing with something.
What's he holding in his hands there?
His hands are like down, you know, like by his, by his crotch.
I'm like, what's he holding there?
Wait a minute.
No.
It is.
Is that his penis?
And it was.
And it was in fact his penis.
And you jumped in.
He just, he had his dick out.
He was playing with it like in public before the eyes of God's and man.
And he was just doing that.
And what stood out to me was I was like, what?
What's going on here?
So I was like shocked, but what truly fascinated me about the situation was how everyone else
just kept walking.
Like this was an obvious thing.
Anyone who looked and see this shit, but nobody stopped to say anything.
I'm not saying that I'm a hero or anything.
I'm just saying like it was amazing.
Who wants to engage with that shit?
Yeah.
I just.
Excuse me a homeless guy.
Put that junk in that trunk.
I mean, I just was like, I fucking did a double take.
I was like, what?
But like people just.
Looked past.
Maybe he was like doing a performance and he had his hat on the floor.
He's supposed to throw a little coin in there.
Yeah.
Nice dick.
You walk over to him and you're like, hey, sir, put that away.
And then he takes off his penis revealing that it's actually a hidden camera.
And he says, you're on national TV.
That'd be great.
A candid camera type of show, but it's exclusively guys jacking off.
Like just always jacking off.
They're always actually jacking off.
It's not actually a prank.
They're just filming it and then making fun of you for noticing.
Social experiment.
Yeah.
I don't see how this can go wrong.
Oh dude, right?
Confort, right?
Munchie, I see this in your future as a performance artist.
I'll be 18.
It'll be all good.
Finally.
The last question I think we want to do here, another one by OneSpar.
Do any of you listen to the news either on radio or TV?
And what are your preferred sources for world-slash-local news?
Alex Jones!
He'll give you the real shit.
I'm a BBC lad.
I grew up watching that.
I don't look at it that much, but whenever a dad comes home, he puts it in the mouth.
I knew someone was going to say it.
I had to go there.
It was so obvious.
I had to.
Wait, what?
Big Black Cox.
You love him.
The BBC.
I mean, unrelated, but yeah.
What an unfortunate abbreviation.
Coincidentally, a fan of both things.
Well, hold on.
You can say all of them.
It's just another failure of language.
BBC came first.
All of them could be like that.
But the big black cock came as well.
Well, the big black cock has been here long before any of us, and it will be.
It's referenced in the Bible.
Literally all of them could be abbreviations like ABC, anal block, clog.
Did you get anal beat cleavage?
Did you know that big black cocks are in fact referenced in the Bible?
Is that true?
Actually, someone, okay, I wanted to answer this question, but I didn't have a good answer
prepared.
Someone asked a favorite Bible verse, even if you're not a Christian.
Now I know it, because I remember there's a verse in the Bible that specifically, it's
something about like, we don't fuck with that tribe over there.
We don't let our women go over to that tribe because quote, their flesh is as the flesh
of asses.
I think they have big donkey tics.
Are you sure that's what they meant by that?
Well, I was assured that it was.
The person assuring me could have been wrong, but I choose to believe that it's good.
And God said gizam.
Look at that shit.
I personally listen to a variety of news sources.
I really try to mix things up, and like, there's no one is unbiased.
So I just try to mix up and listen to a bunch of different biased people.
Like the young Turks.
I'll listen to Kyle Kulinski.
Kulinski, whatever his name is, secular talk.
Like a review tech USA, sometimes less of a news guy.
And then like also like Ben Shapiro.
Whoa, you took a right turn there.
Well, that's the thing.
There is no online person who's really in the middle.
Like everyone has their agenda.
So I just try, and Stefan, I'll listen to some things.
I just listen to as much biased shit on either side.
And then I just form it in my mind and mix it.
I just like hear whatever like comes through the fucking, you know, osmosis.
By the way, my favorite Bible verse, Ezekiel 2320 through 21st.
There she lusted after her lovers whose genitals were like those of donkeys
and whose emission was like that of horses.
Dude, I think that's exactly the one I was talking about.
That's probably the one.
Damn, emission was like that of horses.
So they like, they know what a horse emission is like.
So you longed for the lewdness of your youth when in Egypt
your bosom was caressed and your young breasts fondled.
Now we're talking.
Opposite of me, it looks like I'm going to be a Christian.
I'm sick of the porn on the internet. Bible porn only, please.
There's one more question that we, you know, this could be our final thing.
It's just, it's again, it's for once bar.
And here, this is it.
It's, do you think there is enough PCP fan content?
Should there be more?
No!
And what would you like to see or not like to see?
First of all, the answer is no.
Great question.
And based on this question, I'm actually happy to announce
we're beginning something here today
that we've been discussing amongst ourselves
and we are starting a contest
to create an opening theme song for the PCP.
Oh, right.
Remember that, guys?
Remember that?
So starting right now.
Hashtag PCP theme.
Or I don't know.
Yeah, well, I guess we'll stick with that.
The PC theme.
PCP theme, whatever.
Or PC theme.
Do the first one.
It's clear.
Listen, everybody, make music
or whatever the fuck you want.
And we will listen to it.
And we will not necessarily pick one,
but they will all be reviewed
and we will do a fucking thing.
We're looking for some intro song.
We love the one that we have now.
It's just a little low key, you know,
which it works better as an outro.
So we're looking for something to start the show off
in a hype-ass kind of way.
So if you're an audio mixer,
you're a musicsman,
and you want to submit this,
go to the Twitter.
Hashtag PCP theme.
Submit some fucking audio that we can listen to
if you want to be fucking entering this thing.
That's it.
What you should do is get, like,
songs from all of our favorite bands
that we have mentioned at various points
and just put them layered on top of each other.
It doesn't matter whether the BPMs are correct
and go right up to the mic and say,
That's a good one.
I like that one.
But this is real.
This is going to be a big thing.
We've been dancing around trying to figure out
how to start the shows off for a while,
and this is our solution.
This, we throw it back to you guys.
You'll be forever immortalized
as a fucking intro song if we pick it.
So that's it.
That's it, everybody.
There is no prize.
There is no fucking prize
other than the legend.
Well, the prize is that your thing
will become the thing
and that we will say well done
and point people in your direction.
And you'll be credited in the video descriptions.
It's literally exposure.
Of course.
That's correct.
So only do it if you're happy to not be paid.
That's the thing.
There you go, everybody.
Started right now.
Hashtag PCP theme.
Get going.
There you go.
It feels wrong for me to say,
Yeah, guys, make more PCP fan-er.
It feels wrong to be like,
no, there's not enough fan content.
But all I know is that I would enjoy
if there were more little bit of munchies
running around.
I would like that.
Yeah.
Well, Munchie, you and me both know
that by asking for fan-er, it will happen.
Our retrieval has so much more fan-er
than the PCP.
But that's because our retrieval is good
and it is inspiring.
Oh, you're right.
You know what it is?
Our retrieval is way more specific
and has a visual style that can be utilized,
which is like homestuck style and stuff.
So that goes a long way.
That goes a long way, I'd say.
My favorite PCP fan content.
You know what I gotta say?
How has it been at this point two weeks
since the furry cast?
And we only had one person draw us all his furries.
No, there was more than one.
There were two.
Well, you, Ben, got a few extra arts.
Yeah, like Ben got one.
Yeah, us all as PCP.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I got a bonus.
That was good.
Pretty disappointed with all of you.
You're not gonna lie.
The best PCP fan stuff was not even by a fan.
It was by fucking Ben St. here.
And it was that comic that was just the PCP University
and it was just like a little comic
based upon a discussion that was in the episode.
That was a mess.
Yeah, it was the PCP University one.
I think I did two of those, right?
I did a second one.
I don't think so.
I did the one up into the table.
Yeah, yeah, of like Nate.
It's like, it's just me.
It's nobody else.
I'm here.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, so I've done two of those.
I should do more.
Of course, a shout out to the PCP animated guys
who did those.
Zenhuxnable and the other person who I forget at the moment.
Shout out to 1, 2, 3.
Wait, no, who was that?
Our schedule animated, which was unparalleled
and the best thing that's ever happened to me.
That was the best part.
Yep.
Best piece of fan content that has ever happened to me ever
was to shout out to 1, 2, 3.
Sure.
Our schedule animated.
Our retrieval and therefore banned and elicit.
Absolutely perfect.
Also, thank you to everybody who draws punk.
That's the cool.
I like it when you do that.
Asha in the AM was the other one.
That's the one.
Thanks, Asha.
All right, guys.
I think we're done here.
I think we've done all we need to do here.
Okay, please.
So listen up.
Listen up.
Patreon.com.
Slash the procrastinators.
Give us $1.
Get in the chat.
We're in there and you can submit questions
that we read more of.
$5 and get all the bonus episodes.
Our most recent bonus episode was Wild Card.
It was Wild Card.
Seto Kaiba is there and he's good.
You're going to want to get in on that.
That's our friend Seto.
14 episodes are available now with $5 fucking pledge.
So you're getting your buddies worth at this point.
And follow us at tbcrastinators for all that shit.
Hashtag askpcp for the questions that we answer.
And you got links to some stuff you could buy in the description.
I haven't.
Can I announce something for myself?
Sure.
This week I shipped all the books.
I shipped all my Kickstarter books.
That's right.
Congratulations.
They're real now.
People are all like the tweets.
The tweets are already pouring in.
People are taking pictures of themselves.
They're stylish books and wearing their pins and shit.
It's fucking sick.
I can't wait.
I gave them, they got real nice envelopes.
Did you remember to use the media mail then?
I did not because it said that comic books don't meet the criteria.
What?
They're fucking cowards.
Yeah.
Wow.
You should have just said they were regular books.
I know, but I was scared of the police.
Typical cop killers.
I'm putting out a warrant for the rest of anyone who does not do the following.
When you get your pristine Vapors book, flip to Vaporet for an unantiled Magda Vaporet
by a munchie smiley face.
Turn to the last page and take a selfie with that page in the background.
So take a selfie with that page and send it to me right fucking now.
That's your new homework.
What's your Twitter at?
Munchie, W, tiny hats.
There you go.
There you go everybody.
You've got all the tools before you now.
All right, that's it everybody.
We're done.
Thank you for listening.
A good time as always.
Give us money on Patreon.
Do not forget that important step and we'll see you next time.
Bye.