I want to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Okay, I'm recording.
I am also, also what?
I am also recording why?
Context clues.
Uh, yeah.
Context what?
Clues.
What?
What do you mean what?
Huh?
Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Oh, we gotta sync.
Okay.
No, that was a good start.
No.
Let's leave it in.
Okay.
On the count of three, say sync.
One, two, three.
Sync.
Eleazar, leave that intro in, it's good.
Uh, yeah, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm weary, I guess, exhausted because I've been moving furniture and cleaning stuff
all day.
Oh, why is that?
It's like a spring clean, moving stuff around.
Hmm, yeah, okay, fair.
It's nice every so often to be like, okay, well, furniture has been here for so long.
Why don't we just put it somewhere else in the room?
Oh, yeah.
It'll change the feeling of it.
Did I tell you, when I, this was several years ago, I lived with a guy, coincidental
only named Conrad, no relation, who was, uh, uh, what's the word?
He was, oh, no, was it OCD?
No, it was bipolar.
He was bipolar and he would have moods and when he would get manic, there was one time
in particular that I caught it.
I didn't really realize this was going on at the time, but he was, he was in a manic episode
and he was, uh, he insisted to me, like we have to move the furniture around, like we
have to move the furniture around, like right now, like we have to move the couch from one
side of the room to the other side of the room and like we have to move this chair
up the stairs.
You've got to help me move this chair up the stairs and like we have to move these shelves
to the other side of the room.
We have to, we have to just reverse everything and then like mostly kind of put it back where
it started and ever since I don't, I don't think people with mental illnesses should
have, should have equal rights.
Oh, I thought you were going to say I don't think people with mental illnesses should
own furniture because then they wouldn't be able to move it.
Well, yeah, that's, that's, that's one of the rights I think should be.
You'll sleep on the floor and here's this nice straight jacket, padded, so classic.
Here's a, here's a, here's a, here's a single pizza oven for you to cook the rest of your
meals for all eternity.
That's pretty good.
You can make pizza.
Yeah.
We don't give them much, but we give them a rustic, a rustic wood-fired pizza oven and
a pizza pillow and all the fresh vine ripe, fresh Jersey tomatoes.
Oh, like I talked about, I thought I was making a PCP.
Reference, but no, that was, I talked about, I talked about Jersey fresh tomatoes on my
main character syndrome podcast on Cheezy's channel with YOLO swag.
Oh, yes.
I hadn't got around to listening to that.
It was pretty funny.
We talked about fucking the subject of, the subject of pizza sauces came up and I referenced
what's that one, what's that one that comes in the can?
Papa, no, Don, Don Pepito, Don Pepitos, Don Pepitos sauce made with fresh Jersey tomatoes.
Whenever, whenever you like, I don't know, whenever I have like Googled around for like
authentic pizza sauces, Don Pepitos is always one of the, one of the first ones that pops
up.
Pepito.
It was, I opined there like, wait a minute, isn't it Pepito, a pumpkin seed?
I guess it's Spanish and they're not the same language, but I don't know, is he, is he Don
Pumpkin seed?
We'll never know.
There's no way to find out or verify this.
You know what?
I'm going to do it right now.
Translate.
Here we go.
Uh, enter text.
Uh, all right.
Spanish.
Right.
Here we go.
We're going to find out.
Why is a Spaniard got a pizza place or a sauce?
Spitalian.
Oh wait.
I'm, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
When I try, when I attempt to translate Pepito, which I have certainly seen pumpkin seeds
called, the translation it gives me is nugget.
So I'm a little, I'm a little bit taken aback here.
Pumpkin nuggets.
They're, that's not, they're, no, no, under no, uh, no, under no frame of reference.
Here we go.
In Italian, uh, Pepito is nothing, Pepita is also nugget.
Okay.
Whatever.
Great.
So he's pop, he's Don Nugget, maybe I don't, I don't, I don't trust, uh, I don't, I don't
really trust Google translate to, I'm missing some context here.
It's fine.
I've learned nothing, but you know what I didn't learn nothing doing, going, wait, no,
yes, I did.
Going to the library.
I finally went to the library.
Oh my God.
I've been threatening to go to the library for months and I finally did it yesterday.
What did you read?
Yeah.
Well, I was looking, I looked for, I looked for some Foucault because I want to read Foucault
and they didn't have any.
So I put some on hold and I reserved some from another library and they're going to send
that.
I'm not sure when it'll be there soon, probably.
In the meantime, I checked out, I checked out two like, uh, sort of like career advice
books just to like, maybe I'd learned something useful from these and, uh, I've read like
30 pages of one and I don't, I don't think the advice in there is for me.
I don't think it's really what I was hoping it was.
Step one, go to business school.
Step two, write a self-help book.
Heh.
I mean, yeah.
Uh, no.
This, I, hold on.
This was called, let me find it.
Yeah, I started reading one that I just grabbed randomly off the shelf.
It's called What You're Really Meant To Do by Robert Steven Kaplan and, uh, I feel really,
I read like the intro and started the second chapter and it seems like this is for someone
who has been like working a job that like a nine to five that is starting to bore them
or they've decided that they're not that good at and they want to like switch careers.
They were like, oh, I actually always wanted to be a concert pianist.
Oh, but my wife and kids won't understand if I stop being a jewelry salesman.
You know?
Yeah.
Uh, it's like, well, I don't know, it's exactly what it is.
It implies that you have the capabilities to, to save up using your current job you already
have in order to, to make a big splash on a new scene.
Um, right?
Well, that's what I feel like a lot of these things are, that they assume you have more
means than you actually do.
That's not really what I, that's not really what I'm getting at.
What I'm getting at is that this is for someone who's like in a job they don't like and like,
I want to pursue my, my real dream.
What's my real dream?
And I guess I, I guess I'm already doing that.
Like I guess I already don't have a nine to five.
I already sustained myself, such as I do, uh, you know, doing art or whatever.
And you know, my advice is not how do I quit my job and follow my dream?
I guess I already did that.
How do you follow through, well, maybe the later chapters are like, how to, once you
got your dream, what do you do now?
Yeah.
You die, probably.
Uh, yeah, you just, um, you just wait to die.
You just burn through all of your shit.
There's no more mountains to climb.
Um, I was thinking about it.
I don't know.
I just, I just liked, I just liked, uh, working on, I just liked making cool stuff in like
a team.
I think, I think that's what I liked.
Uh, I liked being a part of something.
And, uh, I think the most fun I ever had working was, uh, making T-Bap with Nate back in the
day.
Uh, and, uh, I don't know, I guess I would, I guess I would like to do something that
feels like that used to feel, you know, uh, I don't, I mean, making, for instance, making
Phantom's Revenge was good and all.
I mean, it was a good, uh, it was a good thing to do.
It was, uh, it was fun to work on in its own way, but it didn't have that, uh, didn't
have that feeling of like I'm part of something, you know, because I was all by myself.
I was all by myself making it for, basically just making it for, for me, uh, and it was
different, you know, you know, so I think that's part of what I'm like.
I think that's part of what I'm feeling now, like something's missing.
And it's that.
What if you try doing art for someone else's comic?
What if, what if I write a comic and then you draw it?
I mean, uh, that's not, I'm not saying that wouldn't work, but it's not.
Yeah.
Well, when you think about like being part of something is like, does, do you need to
be emotionally disattached from it or like super engaged with it?
And also someone else happens to be the same engagement.
Like with tea back, I'm sure like who, who you got Nate to watch my little pony, right?
I think so.
I started, yeah, I think I, I, I roped him into checking it out first.
Yeah.
And then when did you decide to make a show?
How did that happen?
Maybe, maybe a couple months after.
Well, like, like, I think I've told the story.
The idea, the thing was we would always watch the new episode and then we would
always be like, lol, what'd you think of that new episode?
It sucks, uh, it stinks.
Um, and then we were like, Hey, you know, we always like have these conversations
about the new episode.
Why don't we record them and make and put them on the internet?
And that's what we did.
Um, like who was, whose idea was that?
Do you remember to like make videos?
I believe it was mine.
I believe it was me who was like, we should record these.
I think so.
You know, you know what though?
I should, it's, it's two things.
There's two, there's two distinct elements here that should be split from each other.
There's the, there's the jolly cooperation and like being a part of a team thing.
I did like, when we were all of it, when we were all single-minded of purpose,
that's good.
And I, and I do like it.
But the other aspect is, is that it was part of like a scene.
It was part of a scene and there was like a community and people and there was like a,
you know, phantoms revenge is not part of a scene.
Right.
Uh, uh, or at least not a scene, despite getting on equestria daily.
And I guess despite being like CWC relevant, I don't even know if you could call
that a scene.
And even if it is a scene, it's a scene that I despise.
So, so there's no real scene there.
I liked that it was part of a, uh, uh, part of a scene, part of a community,
part of a conversation.
Um, and that lately, it just feels like I'm just talking to myself.
You know?
Yeah.
I'm going, I'm going crazy.
The pony thing was like a good rallying point, I guess.
Yeah.
I think a lot of my, my like creative drive is like, I feel inadequate.
And so I need to prove to myself that I can do things that I want to do.
Be like, I'm not that good at drawing.
Ah, I gotta make drawings then.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Sure.
That's funny.
It's, it's not like, I don't, it's, I don't have that particular hangup.
My hangups are different.
It's like, uh, not that that's like the sole reason for making anything.
I have like creative drive, uh, in general, just like, oh, I want to do that.
Everything I do is solely motivated by proving that I am not bad at the
specific thing I'm doing.
Yeah.
But like, I brush my teeth in the morning.
I, oh, they said I couldn't brush these teeth.
They said I couldn't do it just because I'm British.
Yeah.
Uh, I showed them.
Um, but like, I don't feel that like isolation as like a drawback, like, oh, I
make something, I guess it is a bit like upsetting sometimes when you make
something, it's like, ah, that was good.
And then nobody, nobody likes it.
Like physically, like, I'm sure people enjoy it, but they don't like click the
like button and like, dang.
Yeah.
And that's what it's, and that's at the end of the day, that's what it's all
about.
It's all about that feedback.
It's all about that engagement.
You know, it's all about that algorithm.
I mean, I know it's, well, I mean, the algorithm is whatever.
It's just sort of like, if you don't get feedback of any kind that people are even
paying attention, then it does feel like you're literally throwing things into
avoid.
It's like, why did I upload this?
Why did I make it?
Do I like it?
And then you look at it and you're like, do I like, I don't know.
Maybe it sucks.
Maybe that means I sucks.
I passed, uh, I passed 300 downloads on phantom's revenge, which is a number
that I feel mixed about.
I feel like, you know, in one sense, it's kind of a good number.
Like, like someone downloading the game and hopefully playing it is higher
commitment.
Like that's worth more than someone watching a YouTube video or liking a
tweet or something, but also just, just not enough.
It's just not enough people.
And, uh, I, uh, I don't know.
I need that I'm a little, I'm a little, uh, I don't know.
I'm frustrated because I know I need to, like I anticipated that I would need to
do more after it was done to get it seen.
Uh, I need to make a trailer.
I don't want to make a trailer, but I have to make a trailer.
Um, um, mostly I have to do the Kickstarter.
I have to do the slime and punishment Kickstarter.
And I feel like just that alone is going to get some eyes on the game that
wouldn't have seen it before.
Cause Kickstarter, for some reason, Kickstarter is always like generate.
There's always sort of like generate hype in and of themselves.
It's pretty cool, I guess.
So I don't know.
Like that's, that's a big, that's an instrumental part of the whole thing.
I won't, I don't feel like I can look back on the, on the launch of phantom's
revenge and call it like, you know, a failure until that's over.
And then I can, and then I can truly look back and be like, so how did it actually
do?
What did people actually say about it?
Um, yeah.
So I don't, it's just a lot to do.
It's just a lot to do.
And it just continues to feel like I'm just talking to myself and going insane
and losing my mind.
And for what?
Yeah, nothing.
I can't think of like what, like a solution to that, that feeling.
It's like, oh, just, just have it be different.
Like, I don't know how does that work?
I know, I know, I know, I know, all you got to do is take a cup of flour, add it
to the mix.
Sometimes I have mused, sometimes I have mused about like, uh, getting a job at
like a, getting a job at like a small game studio or something.
That would be my, that would be my, my, probably be my dream job.
As long as I like liked my coworkers, I would just want to be, that would be my
dream job as long as like, I, Mike, I thought my coworkers were cool.
And I respected them and they were all, and I considered us all to be, uh, uh,
instrumental parts of a, of a team.
That would be very exciting, I think.
But it's so, cause like, what if I, what if I tried, what a nightmare scenario?
What if I tried to do that and I do it and I get a job at a studio and I, and I
feel like just a cog in a machine.
It would literally just be worse than not, than nothing.
It would just be a trap.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Life is very stupid.
Dude, you hear about the pumpkin alley, pumpkin patch?
Yeah, I didn't play it, but I saw the announcement.
Uh, Sixten actually found all the lizards.
No shit.
How many lizards are there total?
Uh, there's eight.
Wow.
Okay.
Fuff.
Fluff.
What color?
Woof.
What colors are they?
Um, all the colors of the rainbow.
There's, there's only seven colors in the rainbow.
You, Nini?
Uh, well, um, the, the, to the rainbow.
The turquoise is a color.
Shut up.
Uh, there's an infrared one.
He's invisible.
There's a, there's a chroma key one and not a chroma key.
Uh, what do you call it?
Like the, the, the alpha channel is an alpha channel colored one.
It's invisible.
Oh, oh, I see.
I see.
There's a, um, well, there's, well, there, there, the, the colors of the, there
are the colors of the more inclusive, uh, LGBT flag.
They had, you got the six colors and then you got brown and black for, for people
of color, I don't know.
Uh, you got one, you got this, you got the seven colors of the rainbow.
And then you got, um, and then you got brown.
Oh, the black, but there was a, no, there's not a black one.
There's a white one.
I guess if there's all the colors, the seven colors plus white would be kind of,
I know there is a white one.
I saw Keyblade Spirit find it on her stream and I was like, whoa, a white one.
Ah, I want to give this one like a better test score on it.
Standardized tests and like, give it a job.
I want, I want to make this one my executive vice president.
Hmm.
I relate, I relate to this one.
I want to see this one in my superhero movies.
Is there a lizard based superhero?
Wait, wait, uh, uh, you, you have no right to judge him just because he was white.
Wow.
Uh, you, Kimba, your fur is white because you come from a long line of great leaders.
I hope I can be like my ancestors as well as look like them.
Yes, Kimba.
Wow.
You're just a white pussy cat.
I look, do you know that?
You've seen that YMS Kimba video, right?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That does.
He's the whole subplot about who's persecuted for being white.
I mean, it makes, it makes sense for an animal, but it's still just really funny.
Yeah, especially since it's in Africa.
You're right, right.
Africa, the whitest land.
Persecuted for being white.
So this is what happened, this is what happened, this is what happened to Davoo.
When Davoo went to, was it South Africa to be, it was somewhere in Africa to be a missionary
and she, and the only white people she had around for comfort was Mario and Luigi.
Wait, what?
I remember that.
Do you remember, she said, she went to Africa for that, but like her parents did like missionary
work in Africa and she said, I don't know, I don't want to blow it out of proportion,
but she, she definitely commented for once or twice that there were no other white people
and she, and she occasionally found it comforting when she would play, I think it was Mario,
Superstar Saga, I think, on the GBA and she'd be like, oh, look, I relate to these, my fellow
white people.
Well, I mean, I forget how young she was then.
Even though Italians aren't white, but I mean, you take what you can get, you know,
when you're in the, when you're in the heart of darkness, so to speak.
When you really strip it back, is there like, like white is not actually a thing, it's just
a color of skin.
Do people mean like a specific thing and then like, oh, well, these Europeans are not technically
white.
What do people mean when they say that?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it's very.
It's always arbitrary.
It's Italians and Irish used to not be considered white.
Yeah.
Jews are sometimes, some people don't consider them white and it's all, it's all arbitrary.
You could, you could just be like, well, it depends on the, on the tone of your skin.
But I mean, you know, some Asian people have the same color skin.
It's like, are some Asian people just white because they're paler?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Very few, very few people would say that.
Yeah.
At the end of the day, it is all just kind of, it's all kind of made up.
That's why I think transracialism is good and based.
I actually kind of do though.
I actually, I actually kind of was thinking about, and like, I really do think that like
race really is just as socially constructed and there, there really is no reason why,
like if someone said like, I actually consider myself to be, you know, white, like what am
I going to, what am I going to, and you know, they're black or whatever, I, what am I going
to stand there and be like, well, here's why you're wrong, sir, here's why I disagree.
Here's why you can't do that.
I would never do that.
I think it's weird, no, you know what, I think it's weird, not weird, but like, it doesn't
work like from, to say like, oh, I identify as white because it's, it's not a specific
nation.
Like, there's like, it's vague enough that that's like, not as weird, but like, if you
say I identify as black, there's a lot of like cultural significance tied to the skin
color, at least in the Western world, white, white just means it's the color of your skin.
And it doesn't just mean that.
No, but like, if I said I identify as Italian or something, I feel like, I feel like people
would be like, well, no, we're not from Italy, it's like, yeah, yeah, I mean, nationality
is a little, I mean, it's honestly, honestly, I feel like you could probably construct a
similar, I kind of think if someone was like, I identify as Italian, I'd be like, well,
who am I to say you're not, I guess, I mean, I guess to be like, well, have you ever been
to Italy?
Like, do you know any Italians, you ever, you ever eat a pizza?
I understand this, like it's arbitrary, but like, I feel like it would be weird.
And like, I wouldn't expect anyone to respect that, yeah, like race or nationality, I mean,
if you go in there and live there, well, here's, then I think it's different, but like, when
it comes to like black and white, people look different.
Yeah.
Uh, I think we should, I think we should stop, I think we should stop respecting racial distinctions
more, I think we should respect them less.
I think we should, we should acknowledge that they are socially constructed, and therefore
subject to an individual simply deciding that they don't believe in them, or don't agree
about how they're defined.
And I think we don't, I think we, I think we have to, I think we have to accept that.
I think it's true.
Okay.
I mean, I guess, like logically, it's fine.
I'm thinking of like, I'm thinking of like practicality, though, like, when it comes
to like trans, the boundaries between men and women are arbitrary, and like this, you
know, but there's also a lot of people who are socially constructed.
It's socially constructed, but there are a lot of people who are trans, so it makes
sense then to respect like trans identities, because does it only make sense because there
are a lot of them?
I think there's an argument where like, I mean, hypothetically, I say there's exactly
one person in the world who is trans-racial, and they feel that way.
I don't want to be like status quo.
You got to kill them.
No.
You just got to kill them.
I think it's just sort of, status quo, status quo, status quo.
I've never thought of like, arguing this for this thing, because it's like, it's odd,
because you don't hear about trans-racialists, like really existing.
You don't.
You hear about that one lady.
That one lady, and I guess, practically, like, logically, logically, sound.
It's true.
Nobody does it.
Nobody seems to want to be like, I actually just feel like a white person on the inside.
Well, I mean, that's not true.
What I mean is, it's so weird and unusual that it's like, kind of not worth currently,
at least.
Not worth worrying about.
Trying to implement that into society, because the benefit it would give is like so minor.
If there were lots of people, like a significant portion of any population that sincerely feels
trans-racial, then we should actually think more about it and try to shift societies to
make it more acceptable in practical terms.
I guess at the end of the day, a society that recognizes trans-racial identities doesn't
really look any different on paper.
Because on paper, at least, nobody in general in modern countries, mostly, are specifically
denied any rights for being one race or another.
We don't have, shit, what were those laws called, like post-slavery segregation laws?
Jim Crow?
We don't have Jim Crow laws, we don't have the remnants of them.
You can't use the right, that bathroom, you got to use the other water fountain or whatever.
There exists remnants from those laws in current legislation, which is that.
And there's obviously racism in the general populace, but the thing that they're racist
about is simply the look of the person, not necessarily what it says on their legal definition
of what race they are.
If you could get your race changed on legal documents, people would still profile you
for being one skin color or another or look in a certain way.
So it's not as simple as just saying, alright, this is the way it is, you have to respect
it, because not that you've got to capitulate to the people who hate change, but if there's
one person, it's different from if there's lots of people for societal change to be actually
important.
I mean, I'm not proposing any societal change, because like I said, on paper, there's not
a lot of explicit rules about what black people can do anymore.
So it's not like suddenly they're like, oh, well, just because this person identifies
as white doesn't mean they should be.
Imagine Twitter in the day, Twitter in the Jim Crow days, ridiculous, this person just
because we're just going to accept that this person says that they identify as a white
person and just because of that, they're allowed to drink from the water fountain, making everybody
feel unsafe.
We have to crack down on this transracialism.
The current racism in the institutions is more implied than explicit.
So there's nothing that would necessarily change to the institution if transracialism
was legally recognized and whatever.
They'd just shift it to be like, oh, well, you may be white, but you are still of a certain
culture which I don't agree with, and it's like, okay, you're still being racist.
I mean, that's already what they do.
They say, oh, it's not about brown people immigrating, and it's about people from a
different culture.
It's about cultural differences.
They're destroying our culture by cannibalizing.
They come over here and they have different food, and I don't like it.
Western values, Western values, they bring Allah, and he's-
Allah, these nuts.
They should say that when they cross the border.
If any refugees from Syria still coming in, any Muslims-
They should say that.
Why don't they say that?
I don't know.
They would be so much more accepted if only they said Allah, these nuts.
I think so.
And then everyone would go, ah, you got us.
That's what I would say.
It is all of those nuts, I would say, slapping my knee.
Okay.
Shit.
Do I have anything else to say about that?
How do we get on this topic?
How did I-
I was talking about my career books, and then-
And so all of a sudden, Allah, these nuts.
I genuinely don't remember how we started talking about this.
It's that COVID brain fog.
That's not true.
I've always been like this, but I had a horrifying thought.
Let me just continue.
Oh, I said I went to the library.
Yeah.
And then, I don't know, whatever, point is I'm waiting for Foucault.
I'm waiting for Foucault to- it's like waiting for a good dough.
Foucault, the Japanese sexual lingerie model.
My favorite.
The one that- I think we talked about that on the booby bonus episode.
The booby bonus.
What do we call that one?
Oh, it was just ass versus nothing.
Oh, no, boobs versus nothing, tits versus nothing.
Yeah.
No.
Funny you should- I didn't even- yeah.
Pronounce the same.
Foucault, well, emphasis is on the- oh, but no, F-F-O-U-C-A-U-L-T.
Just a bunch of people who I watch on- a bunch of YouTubers that I like have all referenced
his work.
It's like, well, maybe I should read some of it.
So I was going to read some.
Instead, I got this fucking career book, which is like- this is not- I don't even-
It's a fucking career, North Korea, South Korea, I don't get it.
Very nice.
And it- whatever, no need to- whatever, I don't remember how we did it, but it's okay.
Back on the subject of- oh, the game.
I had a horrifying thought, I had a horrifying thought, and it is that- see, like, I know
and I always knew.
I always knew that it was, like, toxic, that it was Sonichu related.
Like, I know that that's bad, and I've always known that that's bad, and I know that- how
it looks, right?
I know how it looks when you say, oh, I made a video game.
What's it about?
Oh, it's about Sonichu's.
Right?
It's specifically about murdering Sonichu's, so maybe it's, like, anti-Toxic.
Yeah.
Well, here's the- here's where my thoughts.
On the one hand, I was like, what if- what if the Sonichu connection is so toxic that
if I want this game to, like, ever be seen by any kind of audience at all, like, the-
the smartest thing- the most efficient way to do that is just to base- not fully remake
it, but basically just rebrand it and release it as a new game with, like, a different story
and, like, different assets and no Sonichu's.
And maybe no My Little Pony either.
Just call it- just call it something else.
And, like, I guess I-
I mean, it's, like, not even that difficult, aside from all the assets you need to draw.
Drawing the assets is not that bad, depending on how, like- depending on how much I had
to remake some of the cutscenes or the dialogue would have to be re-considered, which could
take a while, I mean.
I mean, here's- I mean, if I knew- if I knew- if God came down and told me, Ben, if you
just took the Sonichu's out, this game would see, you know, 10,000 people would download
it on Twitch.
Or on- on- on itch, rather.
I'd be like, okay, well, I guess I'll do that.
Uh, but I don't know if that's the case, and I don't know if it would be a waste of effort
to do it.
I would do it if it- if it would help.
And I- I put it- man, I don't know, maybe it wouldn't.
So I guess there's two thoughts that I had, and one was maybe, what if the thing to do
is just to undo all that?
No, I wouldn't- like, I would leave Phantom's Revenge up, and I would just release, like,
a- a different version, is- in- in this timeline.
The- the socially acceptable Phantom's Revenge, but not Phantom.
Yeah.
I would just- I don't know, I would just theme it, you know, just a little more, like, its
own thing.
I- I would- would have to think of what that would look like.
I don't- I have no idea.
Um, what if it was keg standard?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
He's- he's much more marketable.
Yeah.
Um, I mean, what- if it- not a pony, then what character would it be?
Would you have to-
I genuinely have no idea.
Like, design a new thing?
Could it be a Beastars game?
Beastars?
No, uh, not Beastars, uh, Biscopades.
I mean, I don't think so.
I don't know how- I don't know what that would look like.
Well, you got your little guy with his helmet and he's got a weapon or something.
Does he have a weapon?
I forget.
I feel like he did.
No, he does.
A Beast Knight has a weapon.
Oh, he's- wait, does Beast- does Beast Hustler have a katana?
I- I think?
I thought he did.
I think- I think he- I forgot, yeah, he totally does.
He has a sword that he picks up off his- I totally forgot.
Beast has a weapon.
You could have little beasts come and they'd be like, eh, eh, eh.
I should reread Biscopades and get myself caught up on it so that I can, like, continue
it.
Yeah.
I need- I need to, like, remember what's actually in it before I keep it going.
But that's not- that's not what I want to talk about right now.
What I- Anyway, so that's the one way and then the other way would be, like, lean really
hard into the Sonichu thing, but in that way it's like- it's a game about killing Sonichus.
Yeah.
Phantom's Revenge.
The game about killing Sonichus.
The game about taking revenge on Sonichus.
The game about- the game that ended Sonichu forever.
It's the- it's the end of Sonichu.
It's- you kill him.
Um, and I was thinking about this because I was reading, like, articles and listicles
about, like, how to market your indie game and, uh-
Make it about killing a real person's stuff.
A real person's stuff.
Oh, that's like- that's the advice.
Yeah.
Uh, no.
None of them said that.
Um, uh, some of them, they were talking about, like, uh, I don't know.
I'm getting sad just thinking about it, because a lot- a lot of what I read was, like, oh,
you need to be- you need to be sending emails.
You need to be sending, like, emails to, like, people to, like, YouTubers and- and journalists
and, like, video game people, just people with clout, just send them emails about your
game.
So, you're sending emails and here's how to write a press release and a press email?
Yeah.
I mean, that's not too difficult.
Once you've written it the first time, you just send it- find what you're sending it
to.
Well, here's- so they- well, yeah, how do you do that?
Like, genuinely, that's the hard part.
Who do I send it to?
Uh, I mean, I was sending, uh, or rather, Charlie sent, uh, we wrote, like, emails, uh, being
like, hey, this is a pumpkin alley, this is a 3D platformer, maybe you'd enjoy it.
And we send it to a few people who play 3D platformer games.
I don't think any of them, like, noticed, uh, but whatever.
It's just a demo right now.
How did you find those people?
How did you assemble that list?
Um, it wasn't that many people.
Charlie had just been, like, looking at, like, smaller YouTubers who talk about those sorts
of things, like, 3D platformer enthusiasts, um, thinking, okay, this guy's got a couple
thousand subscribers.
They talk about platforming games.
They also specifically talk about, like, new and upcoming things that you'd get excited
for.
So, like, potentially, there's a chance we can get featured on that.
So, like, aim low in terms of, like, clout to begin with, because nobody knows what your
thing is.
Yeah.
Um, you're not gonna, like, immediately get front-paged on some big thing, although it
doesn't hurt to try, I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, even when I was, like, starting out hypocrite, I would, like, email a bunch of
my favorite YouTubers.
I would email John Tron and Peanut Butter Gamer saying, hey, uh, maybe you think this
is cool.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It was, like, really embarrassing, but, like, it's possible.
I mean, I, um, I may have mentioned this once or twice, but, uh, when I was doing, um,
when I started doing, it's all so ugly, you know, my, my short-lived, uh, uh, what do
we call it?
Like, what's the word for whatever it was?
Webcomic?
Website?
Yeah.
I feel like more, more specifically, I want to call it, like, a three-panel comic, but
it wasn't, like, three panels.
Whatever.
Like, my comedic joke strip that didn't last, whatever.
Uh, I, I emailed a bunch of, um, yeah, emailed a bunch of other comics people, and I asked
if they wanted to, like, uh, you know, like, do, like, a comic trade, like, you know, I,
they post one on my site, I post one on their site.
Um, I didn't get much reply, except, funnily, I did get a reply from the guy who does Death
Bulge, but I got a, like, yeah, it's, it's a comic.
Uh, I think it also, I think they, they made a video game, a tie-in, like, I think it might
have been a few years ago at this point.
What is it with comics and video games and the people who make them?
I don't know.
Man, dog, people just be, like, liking video games and shit.
Um, the, the, um, what was I talking, oh yeah, Death Bulge, man, made a, oh, he, he replied,
but he was like, ah, I wish, I kind of wish he didn't reply, because he, because he replied
being like, yeah, maybe we could do something like that, and I'm a complete nobody, right?
I have no clout, like, there's nothing, there's nothing in it for him, but I, but I, you know,
I was like, but he was smaller at the time.
He was not, he was, you know, I'd heard of him, so he was not nobody, but Death Bulge
definitely got bigger since then, that I, you know, he replied being like, yeah, maybe
we could do something like that, and I was like, okay, well, like, uh, you know, uh,
I tried to, like, you know, press further, be like, well, you know, how about, you know,
what do you want to do?
Like, I'll, I'll, I'll draw a strip in the Death Bulge, so do you want to draw something
that looks like mine, my style, we trade, and then he, he comes back and he's like, uh, yeah,
I mean, might be able to do something like that soon, like, maybe be able to do, could,
I'm not sure when exactly, uh, and like, I think I might have tried, like, one more time,
be like, okay, well, uh, you know, here, I don't know if I drew, I should have drawn
something, I'm thinking back in what I should have then done, what I should have then done
is drawn a, like, haha, this is my take on Death Bulge strip and just showed it to him,
and then maybe he would have been like, haha, I like it, okay, here, I'll draw one for you,
I don't think I did that, that's what I should have done, but nevertheless, he kind of just
continued to sort of, sort of, uh, noncommittally reply a couple times until I think I eventually
got the picture and was like, well, I guess this isn't happening, uh, hmm, hmm, yeah,
if I wanted to make that happen, I should have taken, I should have taken the next step,
I'm thinking about it, hmm, yeah, I guess I fucked up, oh well, it sure is really hard
getting your creative work known by anyone, yeah, in my head, I'm thinking, okay, as long
as I keep making, getting better at doing what I do, eventually I'll make something
that's so good that I won't even have to try, yeah, that's the dream, right, that's
the dream is you can just make it and you don't have to worry about, like, God, an email
list, like, kill me, like, shoot me in the fucking head, hmm, hmm, yeah, I mean, the hard
part for that, more than just writing the email, because I think I've gotten better
at, like, just sending emails, if you just gave me a list of 100 people to email, I would
just, yeah, share whatever, I just write 100 emails, like, I don't care, but how do I,
but how would I, what's so difficult about finding them, you just, like, Google,
who, who, who, comics, websites, and find people from links from links, and then be like, okay,
this person seems like the same sort of size, a little higher, I'll just email them, write
it down in a note, it'll just take, like, a day maybe of research, I don't know, I can't,
okay, well, I've lived my entire life, and I genuinely cannot think of even a single
person who I would email to tell them about Phantom's Revenge, and say, like, hey, check
this game I made out, maybe you'd like to, well, yeah, with Phantom's Revenge, it's
a little weird, yeah, exactly, not just because the three things that are involved, there's
ponies, there's Endless War, which you're already, like, you know, you're part of that,
you made it, and, and the Sonichu, like, Sonichu's super toxic, the people in the Sonichu
verse are like, they hate you, or they would hate you, mostly, mostly they hate you, just
because, because they, you know, transphobes and all that.
That's part of it.
Um, and then the pony stuff is like, sort of, sort of toxic in its own way.
Yeah, but like, two outsiders, it's considered, it's crazy, the pony, the pony, like, community
is like, disbanded largely, and the big names are all like doing different things, and like,
either distance themselves, or like, not interested in pony anymore.
Yeah, the people who are left are like, I don't know, I don't know too much about them, but
I don't think they're cool.
They're just furries, pretty much.
Well, yeah, I mean, like, but like, there's nothing exciting going on in that space, as
far as I know.
Not really.
Not really, no.
There's no up and comers anymore, because there's nothing to strive for, like, what, what, what,
what sort of person sees the Brony community and thing, and has a twinkle in their eye and
starts their career.
Yeah, there's no one doing that, it's just old people, old guard who are like, just
committed to talking about pony on their channel or whatever.
Yeah, and then everyone with talent has branched out, like, Living Toonstone and, and
God, what's her name?
Jenny, Jenny Nicholson, right.
I mean, even Save Your Spark, you know, all those, they just doing other things.
So, I mean, so there, so there you go.
So you wonder, so you understand my dilemma.
I do.
Yeah, there's no one you could send this to.
But you said you already knew that, kind of, you knew it was super niche, niche.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
I did.
I feel like there probably is an angle.
There probably is some angle I could, I could sell it with to somebody.
I just don't know, I just don't know who.
I mean, do you think it's worth, like, just because you don't go into, like, your
own opinions of, of Chris Chan and all that, it's mostly just about killing
Sonichu and Nightstar.
If you went into, like, Sonichu or Chris Chan related spaces and say, hey, you
want to kill a bunch of Sonichus?
Like, you would get some people having a look, I guess.
Yeah, sure.
I'm not, I'm not above that.
I'm not above that.
And yet, like, honestly, I mean, I haven't, I kind of wonder, I mean, I
guess there's like the, I mean, there's the quickie.
But the quickie is like, okay, I guess there's like a board.
There is a board.
I wonder if Slash CWC even exists anymore.
I'm not, I'm not above, uh, dipping into that well.
But also, I'm not sure how much of it exists.
You know what?
It's, it's, it's Kiwi Farms now.
Like the, the, the Chris Chan community is just Kiwi Farms.
Yep.
I would, I would imagine so.
And, uh, and we know how they feel about me, which is fine.
I don't care.
Uh, I don't know.
I don't know if they're interested.
I don't know if they're interested in a game that I made.
They're interested in like, is Chris going to jail?
Like what is Chris writing in her letters from jail, et cetera, et cetera.
Si.
So I just don't, yeah, I just don't know if there's that much potential there.
Uh, I feel like the only hope it has is like people, I don't know, people who
just like weird stuff.
Um, and I mean, I like weird stuff.
So like, that can't be a complete, they can't be nobody, right?
I don't know.
Like, um, there must be some sort of a community out there that would see it
and be like, what a, what a, what an oddity.
What a curious, what a curious artifact you suppose.
Okay.
Well, well, I don't know.
I don't know the entire internet.
Yeah.
I'm trying to stay positive here.
What, what sorts of people, um, I guess, I don't know where you would find
people who like weird shit specifically.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, they may not even be like online that much.
That's, I should start, I should start a 4chan thread about it.
Why not?
On a slash MLP.
Law.
I mean, what, I mean, why not?
Yeah.
Um, honestly, not even something, not a terrible idea.
Maybe I will fucking do it.
Uh, who cares?
You know what?
There's no rules.
There's no God in heaven judging my actions.
There's only the devil.
There's only the devil and he lives in, in me and he tells me to do these things.
He tells me to make this game in spite of knowing that it has no audience.
And then tells me find the audience then, make an email list then.
You got to, you got, you got to get this on the front page of the question daily.
Uh, thanks again to Oblivionfall for, uh, thanks again to Oblivionfall for
telling Cepisto to put it there.
Cause it really is, it really is like it doesn't matter.
It really just doesn't matter what you do.
Uh, it's just, it's just, do you know a guy?
At the end of the day.
Yeah.
I was reading a, I was reading, it was one of those like, get your indie game
scene, get your, like, indie game published thing.
And it was like, yeah, some indies will like partner with a, you know, the
partner with like, you know, a bigger studio or a publisher, you know, for
marketing and it, and it literally is like the, the single biggest thing that
those people can do for you is that they'll know a guy.
Cause they know, cause publishers know everyone.
So they'll know a guy who can maybe get you like a table at a, at a, at a, um,
an expo or something.
And just like, that's the only way to do it.
You got to know a guy.
And if you don't know a guy, you got to like, you got to find people that know
guys and like pay the money for the, for the guys that they know.
Uh, it's just, it's just, uh, it's just a cruel world.
Um,
Yup.
Uh, okay.
Well, that's, that's all.
Anyway, I went to the library and I'm waiting for those books.
Um,
Uh,
something else.
Let's change the subject.
Um, well, I, I sent, I'm, I'm beginning to send the rest of the Lord of
ghosts things.
Um,
I sent my first few packages now that the ghost costumes are done.
So the, the packages, including like the plush, I think Simsies is on its way.
Oh good.
So Simsie will get his and a few others.
Um,
I'm going to do, try to do another big like bunch going to America,
right before the end of the month.
And I don't know, just like every day I could, I could fill out the, uh,
fill out the fucking thing and the customs and just put it all together.
I still need to do the doodles.
I don't have like,
I think I need to go and get some cool pens or just some good enough pens to
start doing those.
Hmm.
Bah, but, you know, there's plenty of that I can spend my time sending that
don't have doodles and I'm going to just get through as many of those as I
can as quick as possible.
And then, uh, there'll be less stuff in my room, cluttering it up.
I need, I need to check my PO box.
I haven't checked my PO box in a while.
I'm afraid that it's like overflowing with packages that have been returned to
me.
You know, I send a lot of packages.
Yeah.
You, you mentioned you were going to check it last week.
I was going to, and then, uh, I had a thing to do around that area.
Cause my, my PO box is in a different town because it's near my old address.
So, uh, I had a thing to do in the area that I was going to check my PO box
while I was there.
And then it turned out, oh, the thing was on a Sunday and post offices
aren't on Sundays.
Oops.
Uh, so I didn't do it.
So, uh, yep.
So I haven't, still haven't done it.
Uh, gotta do it.
It's just so annoying.
I have to take the butt.
I have to take like two buses to get there.
It takes like, it probably takes me like two or three hours.
Just let go and like check my fucking PO box.
Who wants to do that?
Although I guess it's getting, I guess it's getting warm out.
So it's a little, it's a little less miserable.
It's nice going on walks.
Um, I think, uh, the, the post office, the delivery office with royal mail is quite
good.
I buy the thing online and then I have like a QR code email to me.
So I can bring the packages to the delivery office and say, Hey, um, could
you put labels on these and send them?
Thanks.
And then they just print the labels right then and there.
So that's pretty good.
I don't know whether they can do that for customs labels.
So I bought a bunch of labels for that.
If I can, if I need to do them at home.
Uh, I also, last time I went or a few times ago when I went to the post office,
uh, they made me wait.
They made me, uh, wait in line.
I would, I would always like wait in line.
And then I would get to the thing, get to the desk and be like, here, here's my
domestic packages and here's my international package.
And they'd be like, okay, and they'd sign off the domestic ones.
And then they'd be like, here, for these international packages, you've got
to take these slips and fill them out.
And so go over there.
And then I'd go and I'd fill out the slips and then I'd get back in line
and wait a second time and then I'd send the international ones.
So the one, so I finally was like, I got you suckers and there was a stack
of those slips and I stole them.
I stole a big stack of those slips.
And now I just have them and now I can fill them out beforehand.
So when I get there, I can be like, I already got them.
I only have to wait in line one time.
All the international ones are all, because it's not enough.
It's not enough to just write the info on the package.
You also must fill out a slip with the same information.
And then they must take that slip from you and look at it and painstakingly type
in all the information you wrote on the slip into their little computer and print
out a label that says that information and then stick that label on, on the
that seems so, so old fashioned, I guess, a bit like with the Royal Mail thing.
Like you do all that online when you purchase the, the, the, the postage.
And so they had, they can, they can just like print the label.
Well, they give you like what the, the, the print, the label print like PDF.
So you, if you want to print it yourself.
Oh, really?
Take it in.
Yeah.
If you got like label paper, you can print it at home.
And then stick it on and then just bring it in and drop it off.
I wonder if there's a way to do that with the USPS.
And not that I know of, but I could be missing something.
That would be a little, that would be a little more convenient.
I used to have, I used to use a website called stamps.com that lets you,
I don't know if it would let you do international labels, but it would let
you print your own stamps of any denominational, like you could specifically
print like a dollar, $1.09 stamp, if you wanted.
But it had like a fucking monthly fee.
It was like $20 a month and it literally would not let me cancel.
Like I tried to cancel and they were like, are you sure you want to cancel?
And it brought me back to the website and, and, and it was the same website,
but the cancel button was gone.
Like it was just gone.
And I was like, okay, so this website's a scam.
Even though it works, even though it literally works and seems to be endorsed
by the United States Post Office, it just is a scam.
It's scamming me.
So I had to call my credit cards and be like, hey, do not authorize payments
to this company.
Simply stop paying them.
And they'd be like, well, we have to give you a new credit card.
It's like, fine.
Cancel my old card.
Give me a new card so that I can stop paying these devils.
Couldn't you have like, like customer support called and say,
did you please stop charging me?
Well, that's, oh, you mean to stamps.com?
Yeah, to the.com.
Maybe I could have done that.
I, I feel like I, yeah, maybe I could have, I mean, I exhausted,
I exhausted all of the web, web-based methods I could find.
And I felt like that was proof of their ill intent.
I just didn't trust them.
I just didn't trust them that they were going to actually let me quit,
no matter how bad I wanted to.
Yeah.
So, uh, oh well.
Anyway, so that's, so that's, once again, I don't remember how we got here.
I was just talking about Lord of Ghosts.
Oh, right.
Yes.
Actually, that's a fairly, a fairly direct through line now that you mentioned it.
Yeah.
So like, aside from the doodles of which there are many, but like not like an unbelievable,
like I would die sort of amount.
It's just sort of, I want to first get as many of these like that are, that I can packaged and sent
and hopefully before April, because like that April is like text
moment, like everything before that.
I forget which date, maybe it's the first of April or the end of April or some number.
One of the dates would be like the text thing.
And so like the income I got from the Kickstarter and then like spent would be part of that text here.
And then I could write it off from that text here.
Yes.
So you want to wait.
So you're waiting.
You're waiting.
I'm not waiting.
Oh, you're not waiting.
I'm trying to get it done before April, before the next text here takes over.
I don't know what I'm doing, but I have just a feeling that like,
since the income from the Kickstarter was in that text here.
And then if I spend as much of the money that I was required to spend for the Kickstarter before
the next text here takes over, then I could do my taxes for that year and not pay
anything, because I would get a bunch of income from the Kickstarter, but then it would all be like,
oh, this is, I spent it on like what it was supposed to be, including the postage.
I really should have done all of this earlier.
But you know, making a fucking video game in the meantime.
So you want to wait.
So you want to report your income and your expenses in the same year.
That's what you want to do, so that they cancel each other out.
Yes.
So it doesn't count as like super, I don't know.
You know, when like you go over the money and you can't write enough stuff off,
then you actually have to pay taxes and that sucks.
That's bad.
So yeah, yeah, but sure, you don't want to imagine like paying taxes on a bunch of money that you made
and then and but then like had to spend on something else.
But then you, there was like a delay so you didn't get to report
the that you spent the money on the thing.
You paid the taxes on it as though you weren't going to spend it.
No, that wouldn't be right.
That wouldn't be.
Yeah, I mean, I'm sure there's like ways you can say, well, there's like,
I haven't spent the money yet, but I will because of like this.
And you can write that in somewhere.
I feel like I've seen that.
But it's like a lot of business jargon and a lot of like, I don't get it.
I'm just typing in numbers that are basically correct.
Sure.
Then I get my tax return and they say, wow, you're okay.
I thank fuck.
You got to do your best.
At the end of the day.
Well, things considered, Texas is quite easy to like figure out.
It just takes a while.
I guess I got to pay mine.
I guess, well, I guess the deadline is like three weeks from now.
So I guess I actually kind of got to do that somewhat soon.
And that sucks.
I'm sure I'll file for an extension.
I always do.
I have all my forms.
I got all my forms from like Google AdSense and Patreon and whoever the fuck else.
Taxes are actually going to be kind of shit.
Taxes are going to be kind of shitty this year because I got a bunch of them.
Because I got a bunch of COVID unemployment and you have to pay money on unemployment benefits.
Yeah, it sucks.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not complaining because I did get a bunch of free money,
but I will have to pay some of it back.
So I don't like that part, but I'll do it.
I'll do it.
God damn it.
Why don't they just take that out if they're going to?
If they're going to make me pay it.
It's fine.
I had two more things on my stupid list of shit I wanted to talk about.
Is that okay?
Yes, it's fine.
I don't have too much to say either because it's mostly just been like, I don't know.
I guess the only other thing is that I've got another appointment
set for laser hair removal on my arms, which is like, well, I'm just doing that now.
I'm zapping my arms with lasers and my hair will stop coming back.
It's not much to say about it.
When did you start doing that?
It was only a few days ago.
I had my first session.
Oh, that was your...
You mentioned it on the last episode.
That was your first one?
For my arms, yeah.
I had been doing it on my face for the last year, and that has been going pretty well.
There's only a few little patches that keep coming back, and I'm like, okay,
I need to do some more on that.
I'd finished my 10 sessions and they're like four weeks apart.
God wanted you to have hair there?
No, no, he made a mistake.
He put it there.
Well, he made a little oopsie.
He made a little oopsie, and also I piss on God.
I shit on his grave because it doesn't know what he's doing.
No need for you to piss off all of our God-loving fans.
No need for you to trample on my free speech by saying that.
You're not allowed to say that.
No, I think it's fun to trample on your free speech, Ben St, and I will do so forever.
Sound by it, sound by it, sound by it.
I had the 10 sessions four weeks apart for a while, and I was like, okay, they're over now.
Now I don't have any more appointments coming up, and I liked that for a bit.
It was like, okay, I don't have to go into that.
But then my hair a little bit started coming through the top lip,
and there's a bit under my chin.
I was like, okay, this is starting to feel sucks.
I don't like it.
And so I was feeling a little down just because of I'd feel in it there and being like,
I shave it and it comes back.
It's just like how it was before, but the majority of the hair is gone forever.
It's just little bits.
So I finally sorted everything out because I had that hanging over my head.
I had the pumpkin alley hotfix pumpkin patch that we were working on getting done quicker.
And then there was the fucking, there's always a lot of ghost stuff to do.
There was the ghosts to make the costume for the ghost plush.
And so there's all these things going on.
And I'm like, God, I just, ah, and it's a little overwhelming for a few weeks there.
But I finally got the next appointment.
I called them up.
It was just one of those days where it's like, everything's fucked and I need to get this thing
done.
So I called them on the phone and I got an appointment and it was so easy.
But it was like, I don't like calling on the phone.
Is it expensive?
For, they said for eight new sessions on the face and eight sessions on the arms,
that comes to around like a thousand pounds.
So it's, it's expensive, I guess, but I'm paying it off like in monthly installments.
I feel that I can, that's worth just because it makes me feel so much better.
Sure.
But you know, expensive, patreon.com slash give and take.
Yeah, sure.
I remembered, by the way, I remembered how we got on the transracial thing.
It was the white sal, the white lizard.
That's, okay, okay.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, you, oh yeah, you should play the pumpkin patch, by the way, because it's not just the
secrets.
There's also the gameplay, the game feels a little different, maybe a little tighter.
Do you want to mention what you changed?
Um, I mean, the patch notes explain in quite a lot of detail what changed.
But like, there's things like,
yeah, see pumpkin alley, pumpkin patch, like devlog, if you scroll down, you'll see it on the page.
Charlie, charlie-batten.itch.io.
Yep.
Here, oh yeah, pumpkin patch.
Yeah.
Oh, there's, it's quite, yeah, there's quite a few things here.
Yeah, some of it's technical.
If you don't know about things you might not understand, but like,
we're just like listing the things we were working on and being like, okay, what literally is
different, jumping is different in brief, jumping is different.
There's like collision differences when getting up to an edge of a platform and like,
like being stuck on the platform when you jump on it.
There's a few animation changes.
It's just sort of like cleaning it up based on what people were saying
and what we already wanted to make look better.
You can turn the camera higher up so you can look up more.
And yeah, lots of little, no, no drastic new content.
Some of the geometry has changed.
Some of the decorations have been altered.
And it's harder, not impossible, but it's harder to get out of bounds now.
So the path forwards is more clear and like signpost, like you don't accidentally feel like
you're going the right way when you're like going out of bounds and jumping on top of the hills.
Removed a bit of clouds for performance, huh?
That's interesting.
Yeah, the clouds objects, there were two of them.
But instead of like, they're like generating like, it's like a particle effect,
but just really big particles on the clouds at the top.
There were two of those to fit over the whole level, but we changed it to one.
And then that one like tracks the position of the player and like,
it only renders in a certain radius around where the player is.
So that saves on performance.
And then there was some other stuff like people in different language computers,
the signs weren't like, they were translating strangely,
or they just weren't showing the text.
So there's lots of little glitches, hopefully those are all fixed.
Opening the photo album didn't work for some people.
And that's the gist anyway.
My patch was much shorter than this.
A couple of people have said that a couple of people have reported
a like getting a soft lock in the Phantom's Revenge,
but I have not, I have not been able to like duplicate the conditions
that anyone has described it happening on there.
Only two people have said it happened.
And I have gotten and tried to do what they did to make it happen.
I have not been able to do it.
So there may be a bug in there somewhere.
I just don't know what it is.
If I ever identify it and what's causing like a small amount of people to get that.
You should definitely ask them what of course system, no, I mean like what computer they're using.
If it changes randomly on different like operating systems.
Well Keyblade said she was running the game,
she launched the game from Steam, which is a thing I didn't know you could do.
But she said probably that steam.
Yeah, like she launched it through the Steam launcher.
I guess you can like you can like tie non-Steam games to the Steam launcher.
I just launched them through Steam.
Weird.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
She said maybe that might have something to do with it.
I think some people have maybe, I think sometimes it's not actually a soft lock.
It's just like the game gets a little stuck.
And if you like wait a little bit or like you hit spacebar a couple times,
the game will eventually advance.
It just gets a little bit like hung up, which is bad.
And if I knew how to, and if I knew what was causing that,
I would fix that as well, even if it's not a soft lock.
I haven't been able to replicate it.
I think it's usually has to do with when Virginia dies and like
the cutscene is trying to play of a phantom like being like, no, Virginia.
I think that can sometimes cause a little bit of like,
the cutscene can sort of like get stuck temporarily.
But yeah, that seems to be what people have said.
But again, I haven't duplicated it and I haven't figured out what has made that happen.
So I haven't fixed it.
I will if I ever get the chance.
I can actually, I'm pretty curious about the pumpkin patch.
I would like to boot it up and just like jump around a little bit
and see like, does it feel any different?
How much of a change do I notice?
There was an aspect of the jumping where people,
they didn't like how long they had to hold down the jump button
to get the maximum height out of the first jump.
So we changed that so that you don't have to hold it down quite so long.
And the second jump is like a fixed amount.
I don't know.
I played it and it was like, this is better.
This is like, it's hard to like define with words,
but like it just feels better.
It doesn't feel perfect.
I'm sure there'll be tweaks we make before the finished game is finished.
But this is good for the moment.
Yeah, neat.
Very cool.
I'm gonna, I'll probably look through this whole list in more,
in more detail later, because I'm interested.
Various alley-oop problems fixed.
Well, that's just not very helpful.
Yeah, those things with her like falling through the floor,
which should be mitigated.
I think it still happens if you throw it hard enough.
All right, I'm cracking open my second gridlock energy of the day.
It's one, it's one of those days.
It's a two gridlock morning, if you know what I mean.
I, yes, I know what you mean.
What? Oh.
Oh, that's not a, that's not a gridlock.
That's a, that's a bang, delish, strawberry kiss.
Okay, that's fine.
It's not, it's not what I was expecting.
It just has a similar color can.
Refreshing.
Um, I got two stupid things on my stupid list.
Here's one.
I was playing, a funny thing happened.
I was playing Hades.
I was talking to some dudes the other day.
Last weekend, I was talking to some dudes about Hades.
Munchie had not played it, but some other people had and we were discussing it and
we're talking about like the mythology stuff.
And I said, I think Zagreus is like, Zagreus is like an original character
for context.
Zagreus is the protagonist of Hades and he is the son of the, of the titular Hades, the god guy.
And I was, and I thought he was an original character for the game.
Hades didn't have a son.
Turns out he is not an original character.
He is in like old Greek writings, like not very much, but he is there.
But it's confusing because he is, he is sometimes called the son of Hades,
but he is also sometimes called, he's also sometimes a,
he's like the same as Dionysus.
He's like some, he's like an aspect of Dionysus and,
because like Zagreus is the son of Hades and Persephone and Dionysus is the son of Zeus and
Persephone and like, I don't know, there's some, but all, but the one who, the one who is the
Zagreus that is, is Dionysus was like killed by the Titans and eaten and like his parts were
cooked in pots or some shit.
There's like all the shit about Zagreus that just seems to be about a completely different
guy.
And I read this and I was like, well, that doesn't make any sense.
Probably a different author's thing going on.
I guess so.
I'm just going to remember just fun facts that I remember off the top of my head from reading
the Wikipedia article.
The name, the name Zagre, okay, Artemis, when you find one of her boons in the game,
she says Zagreus, your name means great hunter.
Haha, they must have been thinking of me when they named you.
And in fact, his name is not, does not mean great hunter.
It specifically means like, it means like pit trapper is a Zagre, a Zagre is a hole in the
ground meant to trap live animals in.
So yeah, his name means pit trapper.
Dude, that's just like in Minecraft when you don't want your horse wandering off and you
don't have a leash.
Yeah, I dig a hole and put them in there.
There, there you go.
He's the god of doing that.
So, so that's funny.
Anyway, anyway, so I read this and I was like, well, that's weird.
Anyway, now I know that.
And funnily enough, right as I read that, like literally, okay, like the day before I had read
that I had gotten a little cutscene in the game.
I had found a boon of Dionysus and Dionysus said like, hey, Zag, Zag man, hey, why don't
we play a little prank on Orpheus?
Why don't we like spin him like a tall tale about how we're like connected or something?
And then, and then after I read that wiki article, or the Wikipedia, not just any wiki,
uh, there, there, there upon began a funny little sort of subplot where every time Zagreus would
talk to Orpheus, he would tell him like, hey, so yeah, like, actually, you know, I was originally
born of like a snake from Zeus, and you know, I was actually like torn apart by the Titans,
and they ate my parts, except for my heart, and my heart actually grew into Dionysus.
And like, we're actually kind of like the same God.
And Orpheus is like, whoa, that's crazy.
And, and Zagreus is like, lol, fooled him.
So I felt like I read, I don't know, I was just like, haha, I have the context to get this joke
now, because I read the Wikipedia article.
That's a very, very, if I, I guess if I didn't know that, I would just think it was like a
weird, funny, like, goofy thing that's in there.
But now I know it's like, oh, this is, this is inspired by like a weird, like, inconsistency
in these like ancient texts.
Just thought that was pretty neat.
Thought that was pretty neat.
Timing on that was pretty convenient.
Got that context right when I needed it.
Boyo, um, Skelly calls you Boyo.
He's a guy.
There's a skeleton.
Did you know there's a skeleton in the game, Gib?
No, I've never would have a guess.
You, there, believe it or not, there's a skeleton.
There's a, there's a funny skeleton who, uh, who hangs out in your courtyard and some
mysterious benefactor is paying him to stand there and let you beat the shit out of him
over and over again to, to practice with your weapons.
And he loves it.
And he's your best friend.
I got it.
No, un, un, not joking.
You know, he's like an NPC and you talk to him and he's really funny and I like him.
I like maxed out my friendship with him and he gave me the thing that lets you,
I didn't even realize this was a thing at all until he gave it to me.
And I was like, I can't believe this.
He, he gives me his like charm that lets me summon him in battle.
And his like thing that he does in battle is he, he does what he does in real life is
he just stands there and distracts your foes and your enemies just beat the shit out of him
until he dies and that's his use.
And I, I, I, unironically, which felt so heartwarming.
I was like, I can't believe Skelly is here with me in, in battle.
He's here and he's helping me in real life.
I can't believe it.
This is the most joyful thing.
What a pro.
A beautiful, beautiful moment.
Uh, it's great.
Skelly is great.
And I think he turns out he's voiced by the same guy who voices Zagreus.
And I really like Zag's voice actor.
He, he, he sounds so, um, he sounds so dignified all the time.
He's, he's, and then, you know, and then Skelly's just like, hey, hey, boy.
Oh, hey, uh, hey, why don't you hit me right in the vertebrae there?
Hey, give me, give me a shot right in the eye socket.
Um, uh, and they're the same guy.
And it's like, yeah, pretty good.
The future.
Huh?
Future Zagreus.
This is what happens to him.
I unlocked, uh, I unlocked one of my, I unlocked the final aspect of one of my weapons.
And, uh, it's the aspect of a future person.
I won't say who it is.
It's a spoiler.
But it's a guy who doesn't even exist yet, but you unlock it and he's like, whoa,
this is the, this is the blank weapon of blank, like a great king who doesn't even exist yet.
But I'm channeling his future power into my weapon and it's awesome.
I love Hades.
Um, anyway, that's been a lot of fun.
It's a good game.
It's a good ass video, it's just a good ass video game if you ask me.
Um, final thing on my stupid list.
This is an annoying thing that happened with my stupid roommates who I don't even know at all.
This guy, I think I might have, I think I might have alluded to this one guy who lives here,
who every now and then will pass through the kitchen and mutter something about, hey, you know,
I've got another letter from, uh, the guy who used to live here who says like,
yeah, I guess the electric bills are like still in his name and like,
you know, he wants us to like, you know, send him some money for that.
So like, you know, maybe I'm going to do that soon.
Okay, bye.
Well, he finally, he finally, uh, he finally, what's the word?
He finally dropped the hammer and he asked me like, hey, Ben, uh, you know, this guy,
that guy, you know, he wants the money for the electric bill.
I'm going to send him some money.
Like, can you give me some money to send him?
And he's just like, no, leave me alone.
What are you talking about?
Uh, he seemed, he seemed taken aback.
He seemed, he seemed taken aback, I guess from his perspective.
I don't know.
Are you not paying the electric bill?
Well, here, well, there's, well, here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
When I, when I moved in, the landlady says like here, there's no, she said, no,
you don't have to pay a utility bill.
You just pay the rent and whatever the internet costs, like you guys are
responsible for your own internet bills.
I don't provide internet, but she said, this is the rent, no utilities.
I was like, okay.
And then, uh, you know, and this, what this guy is always muttering about is like some,
he says that like the guy who used to live in my room, a guy who I have never met,
he claims that for some reason the electric bills or the gas bills or the power bills
are in his name and that he has been paying them for us, which doesn't make any sense.
Because this guy is not related to the landlord.
This guy is not like affiliated with the land.
He's just a guy who used to live here.
There's no, there's no reason why the bills would be in his name.
And furthermore, I see the bills that show up on the counter and they're addressed to occupant.
So I don't even think, I mean, I don't even have any evidence that this is even true,
that this, that this guy I've never met, who I don't see why he would be involved at all,
supposedly has these bills that are supposed to be for us and we should send him money about it.
So to me, this guy is just asking me to pay money to a guy I don't know,
that I was not supposed to have to pay for some mysterious bill that I've never seen.
So like, of course, I'm not going to do it.
But he seemed like, does this guy even exist?
Maybe this guy is just asking for money in a roundabout way.
I kind of think he is.
I kind of think he's just scamming this other guy.
And like, sorry, he seemed taken aback because he was like, he was like, well,
you know, the bills in this other guy, yeah, the bills in his name, he keeps getting the bill.
And I was like, well, let him pay it then.
Honestly, like, why, why would the electric bill, why would the power bill for this building
be a, be in the name of just a guy who lived here last year?
Why, like, there's no reason it would be like that.
Like, the landlady is, is responsible.
And this, and this guy, this muttering guy is like, uh, he's like, oh, well,
if we don't pay it, they'll shut the power off.
Like they won't shut the fucking power off.
The landlord is responsible for making sure the power doesn't shut off.
If they shut the power off, if the landlord is so negligent in the power bill that they
eventually, which I don't even think they're allowed to, I don't think they're like legally
allowed to just shut the power off to a building, at least they would have to give everyone living
their, like, notice.
So if, if, but if the landlady was so, uh, derelict in her duties that the, they just
shut the power off, I mean, that's something we take her to court over.
Because she's responsible for making, for making this place livable.
So there's no way that the power is just going to be shut off and it's, and it's going to be our fault.
So, I don't know, he seemed taken aback.
I, to me, it's unthinkable that I would have to pay for this.
So we're, we're at an impasse here and there's, but there's no way that he can compel me to
do what he wants me to do.
So I win.
Mucher is zero.
Speak louder.
I feel sorry for him.
He seems like, he seems like kind of a nice guy.
And I think he's just, I think he's just getting scammed.
But this is, but I, but I, this is what I've said to him in the, in the past when he's brought
up this bill thing, I've, I've, I've said to him, like, I don't know why this guy is even involved.
Like, why are you, you even talking to this guy?
Like, why is he like, I, this doesn't make any sense.
Like it seems weird.
Why is this our responsibility at all?
Et cetera, et cetera.
So it's not like this was like, it's, it's not like this was the first time I've expressed like,
this seems weird and I don't really get it.
It doesn't, it doesn't make any sense to me.
But, I don't know.
I was like, he was, I was like, let him pay it.
And he was like, wow, dude.
Wow.
Like, huh, that's so callus of you.
Oh, that's so, like,
Oh no, I don't want to be known as callus.
Like whatever, man.
Some nonsense.
But I, I doubt I'll, I doubt I'll be hearing about it again, because like there's just
there's just no, there's just no further, there's just no further anything to say about that.
I'm just, it's just nonsense.
It's just not going anywhere.
But it was annoying.
It's annoying.
And it had been building for a while because he even mentioned it.
And I, I could, I could sense, I could sense.
He started talking to me this time.
I was like, this is the time.
This is the time the hammer's dropping.
He's finally going to actually just come right out and be like,
hey, give me money for this thing.
And you know what?
I like, and I killed him.
He's dead.
Nice.
I buried him under the parking lot.
I buried, I buried him in the construction site in the, in the building that they're building
across the parking lot from my back lot.
He's going to, he's just going to be in the floor there.
He's, they're pouring the concrete.
So he's going to be in, in there.
I'm going to save him a little bit of concrete money.
That's going to be good.
Anyway, that's what, anyway, that's what happened.
And that's what happens.
And if you don't believe me, then fuck you.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Well, that was my week.
That was my week too.
Nothing happened.
Nothing happened, but we sure did talk for an hour and a half, but you know,
that's not even that long.
That's nothing.
No.
You want to go to voicemails?
Uh, yeah.
I just got a P.
Sure.
I'm back.
I think I heard your mom.
Yeah, his food, but I'll get it later.
Is she Irish?
No.
Did she sound Irish?
I mean, it was a little hard to hear.
I thought, I thought maybe a little bit, but uh, I guess what do I know?
Where is she from?
England.
I mean, like, yeah, but which part?
Oh, uh, fucking, uh, Cheltenham, which is like south, south, it's sort of a posh-ish area,
south England.
All right.
Okay.
It was a bit, I mean, it was a bit kind of like in and out, like just barely breaking the,
the, uh, you know, the noise gate.
Yeah, the noise gate.
Uh, anyway, that was, that was funny.
Hi.
Hi, Gib.
Uh, you're gonna come down, you're gonna come down for dinner.
Faith and, faith and begota.
No.
You're gonna come down and kiss the Blarney Stone, Gib.
No, don't you dare insinuate my mother is Irish.
Yeah, don't insinuate-
On Mother's Day.
Don't insinuate she's not white.
Of all day long.
Is today Mother's Day?
For me it is.
Right.
In May, May 8th in America, right?
Different, different days.
Different.
Did you hear that they, I think that I heard that like they, they canceled
daylight savings time in America?
Fucking cancel culture.
Yeah, I think I saw like articles that like,
yeah, they, they, or no, no, they didn't cancel it.
They made it permanent.
So it will never, it will never stop being daylight savings time ever again.
Uh, well, whatever.
I guess I'll hear about that when it relates to me.
Uh, right.
Well, I don't know, like, they just heard about this, like immediately after daylight
savings time, like a couple weeks ago, and I think, I'm sure next time it's
supposed to be daylight savings time, I will either hear,
yes, they really did cancel daylight savings time.
It's actually gone finally.
Or, oh yeah, no, it's, it's actually not gone.
Sorry, everyone.
It was almost gone, but then they were like, no, we were just kidding.
It'll be one or the other.
Breath, breathless thing pieces about why either one is the case.
Um, let's, let's listen to, you want to just listen to
them on speak pipe this time?
Sure.
Okay.
It's, I always get like fucked up, like moving the files into discord.
Oh, and logged out.
What's the password?
Uh, here I'll just, let me just say it out loud.
No, it's so secretive.
Let me just post a, let me just post a screenshot of the password in this discord
server where people other than our trusted confidants live.
We should have, I should have another guest on a mentioned cyber cyber shell.
I asked him if you wanted to be on last week and he said he could not make it,
but he would be on soon.
Did not ask him again this week, although I would like to have him on again soon.
I kind of like to get snake back on because I thought snake was pretty cool.
You know, yeah, you know, this is, um, here's something that fucked me up.
I was reading some of those.
I don't know if this is insane.
I don't know who's crazy.
One of us is crazy.
Not you or me, me or the person whose article I was reading,
an article about like how to, how to push your game, get your game seen by people.
I think this was specifically in reference to like telling
YouTubers about your game to try and get your game seen by influencers.
This, this article said like, send them, you know, send them a, send them an email.
Don't inundate them, send them an email and then if they don't answer,
maybe send them one or two gentle reminders.
And if they don't answer after that, you know, you should assume that they're just not interested.
Um, but they said like, don't like bother them.
Don't annoy them with like, you know, don't inundate them with emails.
Maybe send one every, you know, don't send more than like one a week or something.
And like, I don't know.
That just seems like to me, one a week seems like really fast.
Really fast?
Yeah, my, my, my, I don't know.
To me, it's like, damn, you only waited a week.
Like, fuck you.
Like, I, like, I don't know.
I would, I guess I just, my timetable would be slower.
I would think like, if I don't want to bother someone, like I wouldn't, I wouldn't,
I wouldn't write them back for like at least a month.
I think would be my instinct.
But I guess it depends on like how, like how big the person is.
If they're like, like physically unable to respond to so many things.
And then like, oh, yes, I was going to get around to that.
And like, they just need our reminder, literal.
Or it could be, if you don't want to bother them, I feel like if, if you post,
like you put an email, they don't read it because they're not interested.
And then you give another email after a week.
Well, then it would feel like too quick.
But I feel like even after a month, like what would be different?
Yeah.
They didn't care about it the first time.
The more I think about it, the more I think that I'm, yeah, that I'm being silly.
Like, like, yeah, why, why wait more than a week?
If you, if you wait a month to follow up and then you wait another month,
they'll just have forgotten about the original email.
Yeah.
If they, you know, assuming they ever saw it in the first place.
So I'm, hmm, I don't know.
You're giving them like time to get around to seeing it.
Yeah.
And a month is like a lot of time.
They would need to be like a super, like they would need to be so big that they wouldn't
really read all of their own emails.
They would have like a secretary.
They're like a million sub-youtuber and they get like a thousand emails a day.
I actually don't know if people send emails these days, but like I assume they still happen.
They do, but like, it's for like, it's like press stuff, press release stuff.
Yeah.
I don't think.
Human beings don't send emails anymore.
I think probably, yeah, probably less.
I think people mess, message each other in various ways, more, more so.
At least young people do.
Okay.
Anyway, let's get the, let's get the voicemails.
Uh, first voicemail of the day is called, uh, niggle me this.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Three, two, one, go.
What is 13 yet 51, Mr. Saint Man?
What is 13 yet 51?
Like 13 years old and 51 kills in Halo.
I don't know what that is from reference to.
What is 13 yet 51?
I have, I have no idea.
Wait, is this a racist thing?
Oh, wait, is this, is this like a, is this like a crime statistics or like a, an IQ distribution thing?
I think this is a racism.
I think, I think we just did a racism.
I like my 13 year old Halo player.
Yeah.
I'll call it a new player better.
I, I genuinely, I don't know what, it's something like that.
I, you know what, I could probably figure it out if I thought about it, but I won't.
Um, next, uh, next one is how's paradise?
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
Funny, dumb racism aside.
How is wrapping up rad con for stuff?
The only reason I ask is cause you know, it's just a little over two years since those faded times
and I haven't tuned in in a while.
So I'm curious.
I feel like I, I feel like I talked about this last week and maybe if you had listened.
Yeah.
I talked about this, uh, Nate is, Nate keeps saying he's going to do,
Nate keeps saying he's going to do the, um, the, the music video.
He said he would do it last month.
He didn't do it.
And then he said, okay, for sure Friday, he didn't do it Friday.
And then he said, okay, I didn't do it for it, but I'll do it for Sunday.
Today is Sunday.
We're recording on Sunday.
So later today, I guess I'll ask him, hey, do it.
I have no doubt he will eventually do it.
Um, anyway, he's got to do, he's got to do that.
And then there's the, the OVA needs to be edited, which, uh, is the biggest thing.
And then I mentioned this before.
I hope this is, no, this is, this is not a, this is not a thing that Kaiju Koon is responsible
for yet because he has not accepted any money.
But I, I hope that if Kaiju Koon gets some time free, he will, uh, take on the job of
finishing the, uh, the dojin, uh, because I don't know who else can do it.
Uh, because the other guy bailed.
The other guy, the other guy fucking, they, they bailed.
They japed us.
They japed, they japed pretty hard.
Anyway, that's, that's the answer.
Um, next one is called T-Bap from Gibby Wibby Cutie Woody at itsthetruth.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Two best buddies, bitch about pirates.
Yeah.
T-Bap, the Ben St. Gibb and take pirate podcast.
That's what I, what did I say last week?
I said, um, two, whatever.
I said something else.
I thought you said something to like the podcast, but like the same.
I, I made, I made a T-Bap joke about a different acronym.
I did.
I don't remember what it was.
And then I said, oh, the deep, the depo cast was my joke from last week.
Cause what?
Why not?
Um, next one is called I found your secret Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
Um, hello, Ben.
Yes.
I know your secret.
I read the flight records.
Ben saying, I know, I know.
I saw you, you and Mr. Epstein quite close.
Or are you not?
I believe that, I believe that, um, your, your brother will want to hear this.
No, don't tell him.
Then he'll, then he'll never finish the music video.
Okay.
You got me.
So such mirth, such glee in those words.
He loved it.
He, he, he won me over honestly.
His enthusiasm for me being on the Epstein flight was just infectious.
Okay.
Next one is called a song.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben saying, I'm going to come to your house.
You better start running.
Okay, I'm running.
That's a good song.
A good song.
Good song.
Uh, intro song?
I don't know.
I don't know if it's quite, I don't know if it's quite at that level.
Um, next one is called congratulations.
Three, two, one, go.
Congratulations on another shit on my desk yearly.
Great.
Yeah.
Yes.
Hit both, hit your, your give and take.
That's right.
That's true.
That's your name.
That's my name.
Uh, yeah.
Um.
Yeah.
Another shit on my desk yearly came out.
It's number six.
How many more of those are there?
I believe there are nine in total.
And that's was what, yeah, number six.
So, wow.
It'll be entertaining us for years to come.
Yep.
Ah, hmm.
I just had a weird sensation in my face and I'm wondering,
am I having a stroke?
Probably.
Okay.
Next one is called Dublin Wild.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi, uh, Ben Gibb, whoever the fuck else is around.
I've been skulking around RFCK for a while and I kind of just
wanted to call in and thank y'all because, uh, slime and
punishment and Lord of Ghosts kind of lit a fire under me to
like start drawing and so I've started drawing and it's all
shit, but it makes me happy.
So, uh, thanks, everyone.
Well, shucks, uh, cool.
That's good.
Good for you.
Keep at it if you like it and, uh, you will certainly, uh, get
better and, uh, that will probably be gratifying and, uh, who
knows what the future may hold.
That's cool.
Okay.
Thank you for the voice.
Wow, a sincere, a sincere voicemail.
That's fucked up.
It is.
Oh, how are we supposed to, what are we supposed to do with
that?
Just say thanks.
That wasn't even a little bit racist.
Not even as a joke.
What?
Okay.
Next one is called Slime and Punishment, Physical
Release and Phantom's Revenge.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, what are you going to do about the game when you
release the physical release of Slime and Punishment?
Yeah.
Are you going to do like the Homestuck books did where
they took like screenshots of all their games and like,
but like text underneath explaining stuff?
Or are you just going to have like a big splash page where it
says like, uh, okay.
And then the game happens.
And then go and play my game now.
What are you going to do, Ben?
What are you going to do?
It's a good question.
Mostly I'm just looking forward to reading that index
because there's so much in that comic where I'm just like,
what, what does any of this mean?
I don't even know what, yeah.
The index is going to be a work unto itself.
I haven't even finished like finalizing like the page layout yet.
I think I'm, this week, I think I should actually like pick a
layout, order a sample copy and like get that process underway.
But, uh, yeah.
So for the game, I thought about this and I think what I'm
going to do is the game is basically indispensable to the
comic.
Like the game is like a very important part of the story.
I can't like, I can't just like cut away and be like,
and then go play the game.
So what I think I'm going to do, and I think this will look cool,
I'll think it'll be good, is I will just have,
I will just have a series of screenshots from the game that
just sort of tell the story of the game.
And what I'll do for like dialogue scenes, uh, is I,
when possible, I will just have like, I mean, imagine, for
instance, the, the initial, you know, when Phantom meets the
first Sonichu, right, it'll just be like the screenshot of
him just, they'll just looking at each other.
And then underneath, I will just have the text boxes as
displayed in the game.
And I will just show, like in a, basically, probably just in
like a vertical row, like all the text boxes in sequence of
like, you know, Phantom says this, Sonichu says this,
but, but, but, but, but, but, but, you know, those, I will,
I will use, I will use screenshots as necessary.
And then I will just show text boxes in sequence to show,
like, this is, this is the dialogue.
That, that's my idea.
And I'm gonna mess around with it and see how I can make it work.
That's the plan.
Good question.
Um, I think it'll look pretty cool, honestly.
It'll be, I think it'll work pretty well, actually.
It'll just be like reading a comic, but just, you know,
the panels just look like a video game, but it will be
Yeah.
perfectly comprehensible, I think.
And I'm kind of excited for that, actually.
Um, yeah.
Something I'm not excited for is getting the, the, the video S
revert into a book form, because I feel like it's going to be,
annoying to screenshot the video to get like images for the
book, because the, you know, the, um, I don't know if I'm going to
use the right word for this, but the video is all like, you
know, interpolated.
So like frame by frame, you know, there might be like blur in
between.
Like if something is moving, there might be blur or like, what
do you call it when you kind of see two frames at once as it's
transitioning from one to the other?
I, I don't know.
Well, that's cool.
But yeah, you know that.
Yeah, that.
So, um, I feel like it might result in poor image quality, which
would be have the original, like,
editing file for that.
I have all the assets.
But I would have, God, I mean, I guess I could do it.
It would be a real hassle to like, just take the original assets and
just put them in like, manga studio and just move them around and
compose them into recreations of frames from the video.
I mean, I could do that.
But like, how was it created in the first place?
Do you have like a, an Adobe Premiere file that you could like?
Vegas.
Like, could you not like, just scrum through that and find a frame that
isn't like, interpolated?
Hmm.
And then like, export frame.
Like, that's usually a thing you can do in editing software.
You know, you know what?
Possibly.
Yeah, I might possibly be able to do that.
I, it's, it's a Vegas file.
Vegas is a little bit feature light, but they'll probably,
there's probably a way to do that.
I think so.
That's, that's a good.
It's a good idea.
I didn't, hmm.
Yeah.
I might do that if the, yeah.
All right.
That's an option.
Next one is called a message for cyber.
Well, it's shell, but it's got an apostrophe between the E and the L.
So I guess it would be cyber shield.
Three, two, one, go.
Cyber shield.
I heard you give me on this week.
I got a very important message for you.
Here, one second.
Let me just do my voice together.
I'm sorry.
He said he would be on soon.
Uh, sorry about that.
Uh, whoops.
Next one is called a daemon Targaryen from the rogue prince at westeros.gov.
Three, two, one, go.
Now, there's a joke that nobody's going to get.
Um, I, yeah, I don't get it.
Uh, uh, press Preston Jacobs in some of his older videos when he was talking
about like Westeros history, he just has a joke where anytime he mentions daemon Targaryen,
he, he refers to, I guess he just thinks daemon Targaryen is a bad ass or the books
just treat daemon Targaryen as a bad ass.
So he, he always, he always refers to him as daemon Targaryen, the rogue prince.
And then he plays that little music sting as like a panning shot up to daemon Targaryen's
face plays.
It's, it's in like one or two of his, his older, uh, series.
So I appreciated that voicemail.
Uh, daemon Targaryen.
The rogue prince.
Uh, next one is called Twilight Roaster.
Three, two, one, go.
I need, what, what's, what would be the, what's the point?
What's the point of, first of all, I mean, if it's always the same number of frames,
then the damage is consistent.
Whoa, the, the, they're tied together.
They're tied together so they don't become dis-coupled from each other, which,
I mean, what if your computer slows down and the frames are different?
Well, if it's, if they're slowed down, it will still render the same number of frames.
We'll just do it slower.
Uh, I guess.
I mean, some, some things that, I know that in some games, things tied to frame rate
mean that if anything affects the frame rate, such as a, uh, like a computer, um,
like being unable to, to run quickly enough, it makes, it changes the gameplay,
not just like visually what's happening.
Well, unless like, unless like Game Maker just like automatically does such a thing,
there's no such feature in Phantom's Revenge.
So it, it shouldn't make a difference.
Uh, it shouldn't, it shouldn't skip any frames or change the,
change the outcome in any significant way.
Uh, I guess I don't know.
It's possible that there's something going on that I'm not aware of.
Uh, I mean,
I mean the, the damage ticker, like, I mean, I don't know, just see,
it just seemed like the easiest way to do it, to make the damage ticker move in real time,
is to just have the damage be dealt in one frame increments and have the timer update
in real time.
The, Ben, you solved the problem one way.
Why didn't you solve the problem other way?
The, shout out.
Fuck you.
Fuck voicemails.
Um, next one is a YouTube video.
I'm gonna look at what the YouTube video is.
It's a three-minute video.
Oh, it's a transistor sound.
Transistor original soundtrack, old friends from Supergiant Games.
Okay, uh, let me just listen to the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
Guys, I'm not a big fan of Bash or even Hayes, but you must play Transistor.
The game is super short.
Only six hours long, but the vibes are immaculate.
Immaculate.
If you like the song attached, this will be some of the best six hours of your life.
Also, this game has sword marriage too, wink, wink.
Oh, right.
Very good.
Hmm, you know, I agree that a six hour game is a short game,
but I think of myself playing it, and I'm like, this is not gonna take six hours.
And, uh, I don't even really play games for six hours at a time.
Like, not always, unless I'm really into it.
Uh, I mean, um...
Pfft, duh.
I guess, uh, I guess since I like Hayes so much, I guess I would consider taking a look at Transistor.
Uh, I mean, I would play it.
I'm not against it.
I would, I mean, I definitely play in six hour bursts commonly, so that's not a,
that's not a problem for me.
I might be able to finish it in one sitting.
Um, um, uh, I mean, it's a...
But I'm gonna listen to like two seconds of the, of the...
Game sounds pretty good.
Music sounds pretty good.
I thought of something.
I had a, I had a thought.
This is, let me tell you my funny joke that I thought in my head and didn't tell anyone.
Uh, last, last week I was talking about the music in Hayes, and I said,
there's some kind of, you know, there's that something, something sorta guitar.
And you said, you asked Spanish?
Like, is it Spanish guitar?
And I was thinking about that.
And I, and I, the joke that I wish I had made at the time is what it killed
is I should have said, I don't know a Spanish guitar from a Mexican pizza.
Right? Killer, right?
Uh, I don't get it, but yeah.
Smashing, smashing.
Um, anyway, I might, I might play Transistor.
I might, I might.
Um, I just got a comment.
I just got a comment on my YouTube channel.
This is, this is not a voicemail, but let me read this comment.
I think it's, Brendan J says, Hey Ben, as much as I like this video and the subject matter,
I cannot in good faith subscribe or recommend your content.
Why did you say the N word?
I suspect it is because you were in a space where you, one, felt very comfortable using
this offensive slur, two, knew no one would call you out on your behavior.
You could have just said N word or even F word.
Wait, what?
That's okay.
All right.
Whatever.
Okay.
Anyway, I don't think you're a bad person or regularly engage in shitty behavior like this.
It's just the level of ease you express using these slurs makes me uncomfortable.
Thank you for the laughs.
Uh, I think, okay.
I just, this just popped up on my dash, my desktop and I was like, okay, I want to look at this.
Uh, what do you, what do you think?
Do we kill this guy?
I'm going to kill him.
That's not true.
I'm joking.
I mean, the people are free to decide whether to recommend a person.
So like, I don't know.
Yeah.
This, I will, I agree that this person is right in hindsight.
I could have, I could have just said N word.
And in fact, I kind of think I should, I think I should have, if I were going back,
I think I would just say N word because I'm pretty sure tales gets trolled,
prints it with, I'm not sure if it originally printed it with asterisks,
but like now when you read it, it's got N, like asterisks, asterisks, asterisks,
R, I think.
So they're talking about a specific time.
I don't know if it originally did like sure.
Yeah.
In the, in the tales gets from, because you know, there's the, there's the words of power
that cause you, um, oh, I see that, that kill your enemies and the N word is the ultimate one.
I think it just kills you instantly or it kills your enemy instantly.
It kills yourself instantly if you say the ultimate word of power.
Yeah.
So, you know, I probably should have just said N word honestly.
So I agree on that.
Yeah.
I guess I said it, you know, I was, I feel, I do feel like there's a difference between
saying it, like calling someone it versus like saying, you know,
hey, this is a work of fiction.
And in this work of fiction, you know, this word is a story, what's the word is a story conceit
and like this is the word and this is what it is saying.
I feel like it's different.
So it's, I don't know.
It's different, but like there's no, there's no detriment to putting the N word in place
of it when you're talking about it.
Honestly, there would have been no detriment to just saying N word.
So I guess I kind of agree.
It's not like people are confused about what that means.
Yeah.
I mean, that's my answer to the the ease of express using them.
I wasn't, I don't know.
I don't know if I would say I was using it.
I wasn't using it.
I was saying it.
I was referring to it by its name.
So I sort of, I agree with some of this comment, but not all of its spirit, I guess.
Also, I'm confused by the, you could have just said N word or even F word.
Maybe they mean, maybe you say the F word.
Do I also say the F word?
I don't remember if I say it.
I might.
I mean, it probably comes up.
It's tails gets trolled.
Those trolls are very foul mouthed.
Yeah, probably.
I mean, I guess he's right.
Actually, I guess knuckles and shadow are very foul mouthed.
They're all foul mouthed.
They are.
They say all the words.
I wonder, now I don't know, he might be consistent about this.
I wonder if this person would recommend tails gets trolled,
despite the fact that it contains those words.
I, maybe he wouldn't.
Maybe he'd be like, I can't in good faith recommend tails gets trolled because
of the ease with which they use slurs.
It makes me uncomfortable.
That's possible.
I doubt it, but it's possible.
I mean, it could also just be that they, the people that they would recommend it to
would be taken aback and offended if they heard you say it.
I, it's, it's, it's honestly fair enough.
If you're like the fact that I say that in the, in the video is like,
I can't recommend, I can't show this to anyone.
You know, I get it.
That's one reason why I think if I were doing it again, I wouldn't say it.
I don't feel like it added really anything.
And it, it, and it's, you know,
it's kind of like, it's kind of like how I feel about the Usopp.
Usopp's design, if somebody doesn't like it and finds it offensive, finds it like to be
problematic, a problem affects their enjoyment, they can't recommend one piece because of it.
Like, yeah, that's fair enough.
And I just think, and I think it's a shame that he is designed in a way that makes some
people feel like that.
I think it's unfortunate.
And I kind of, for that reason, I kind of wish maybe he had not looked quite like that, perhaps.
But it is what it is.
So, okay.
I guess that's all I have to say about this YouTube comment.
You did.
Okay.
The next one is called, is Tixie still getting a cut of the Radcon for profits?
Since she, from, since she's not a member anymore at gmail.com.
The answer, I think I talked, yeah.
That was one second long, so yeah, that's the question.
Yeah, yeah.
I think there is, I think I talked about this last week.
The answer is yes.
She is still getting a cut because she was involved.
I am, I am getting part of what she would have gotten because she did not follow through on her
stuff, specifically with Road to Radcon.
I would like to take all of it.
I would like to deny her everything, but I can't.
I can't, I don't have any grounds to do that.
I think she deserves less than everyone because she famously worked the least and complained the most.
And then wasted all of her time with the lecture that she decided to trash.
But, I mean, she, she was involved, I guess.
So, it's part of the initial agreement.
She's entitled to a cut.
And that's sad, sad, but true, sad, but true.
Yep.
Rail against the cruel fate.
So, yeah, she will get a cut.
Okay.
Next one is called, does Ben not like Ash Vampire?
If so, why?
Wait, where's that?
If you reload the second page, I think we got another one and it pushed everyone.
All of them down.
Okay.
It's just, it's just the question.
No, I don't like Ash Vampire.
First of all, why do you even know who that is?
Stupid.
Ash Vampire is totally irrelevant.
So, you must, so you must know them personally.
In which case, I feel sorry for you.
Ash Vampire is one, a dummy.
Two, a Nazi.
And that's it.
No, I don't like Ash Vampire.
They went on a, they went on a deranged rant about how George Floyd was just as bad as,
what was the cop's name?
He had a funny name.
It was like Big It or something.
It was like, no, it was-
John Big It.
No, he genuinely, his name was like Chauvin, like Chauvinist.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Derek Chauvin.
Ash went on a deranged rant about how George Floyd was actually just as bad as Michael, as Chauvin.
Just as bad for being murdered as the guy that murdered him.
They're actually, they're actually pretty the same when you think about them.
They're just, they're two sides of the same coin.
No, I don't like Ash Vampire.
If you're Ash Vampire's friend, you're an idiot.
And I don't like you either.
And, and I mean that.
Lamal.
Also, Ash Vampire is just a dummy.
And I haven't listened to their Bionicle lecture, but I'm sure it sucks because I have talked to Ash Vampire.
And they're an idiot.
Like they're, they're, I used to talk to them about, they used to be in my Discord server.
And they used to just bore everyone with like, wanting to talk about like the submarine that
they used to work on all the time.
And everyone would like, and everyone would like, talk about them behind their back,
because they would like, talk about how like, they would, they would talk about
stuff that happened, like on their, on the submarine that they were stationed on.
And they would, they would describe like, unfair things that were done to them or like,
things like, oh yeah, you know, they, the rules are like, like the system's designed to fuck you
over, you know, when you do that, and like, it's really obvious that like, they're just an asshole
and nobody likes them.
And that's why like, people were like, that's why they were, they would get in trouble for
things that other people didn't get in trouble for, like, like vaping on the submarine.
They were like, oh, you know, they just, you know, they just had it out for me,
because of my controversial opinions or whatever.
But they were obviously just an asshole that nobody likes and like, vaping on the submarine.
Yeah, other people got away with it, and they didn't get away with it.
They got discharged for it.
The reason is just because nobody likes you, because you're just a dick.
And that's, and that's it.
So no, I don't like Ash Vampire.
Good, good question.
Great question.
Do you have anything to say about that?
I mean, I agree that they don't seem like a nice person because of the George Floyd thing.
I do remember reading, I think it was in like May's discord when she had that,
or maybe she still does.
She wrote it in text in the May's discord, and then on their stream, she read it out loud.
She read it out loud in a stream with Glink, and May and Glink were like,
yeah, very interesting.
Yeah, sounds good.
Yeah, so I have no reason to defend them at all.
I don't really care about them.
I hate them.
And then that was the time.
That was the time, and I'll just briefly remind everyone, that was the time that,
in response, I went ballistic.
I went ballistic in the call on the stream, called them all.
I genuinely, I don't even remember what I called them.
I condemn them in the strongest possible terms.
And then immediately afterwards, Trixie DMed me to say,
Ben, you're just mad that you don't get to fuck May like I do.
You're just mad.
You're just mad and you need to have sex like me.
It's a famous interaction.
A famous interaction.
I mean, it's famous to me.
The moment when I think I knew that actually, Trixie's not a good person.
Maybe I don't like them.
Anyway, next one is called Ben's Weekly Reminder.
Play Deltarune Chapter 2.
No!
I will eventually.
Maybe when Chapter 3 comes out, I'll finally play Chapter 2.
You won't comb through Chapter 2 enough.
Or I still got to go back and fight Jevil.
I never fought Jevil in Chapter 1.
No!
Yeah.
I mean, Jevil's really difficult.
He's really difficult, but I like, I like games.
That are hard.
I like, I like a, I like games that are hard.
Like Demon's Souls, Demon's Souls.
What's the devil may cry about part?
No, wait, what was he?
I forget the lyrics there.
I don't remember that many of the lyrics.
I like games that are hard.
Like part one and three.
Two is easy and it sucks.
I like games that are tough.
Right.
Forget what game he was talking about though.
It was Devil May Cry for sure.
Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
Devil May Cry 2 sucks.
Famously, everybody knows this.
Yeah.
I, I played Devil May Cry 1 at my friend's house and I loved it.
And then Devil May Cry 2 came out and I rented it.
And I was like, hell yeah, Devil May Cry 2.
And then I played it and I was like, this sucks.
And then I never played a Devil May Cry game again.
But then every other Devil May Cry, I was like fine and good.
That's not true.
I think I did play some of 4 and it was, and it was good.
But they're just, they're just not my, they're not really my favorite.
Character action games are not really my like thing and that's fine.
Things that are tough is too tough for me.
You beat Phantom's Revenge.
It's kind of hard.
That was a thinking game though.
I like thinking games.
I don't like like stress inducing like reaction time games because it's using my muscles and
I don't have any of those.
I see.
My brain's real big but my body is a skeleton.
There's nothing there.
That's, you gotta play to your strengths I guess.
Next one is called, no, Twitter Sparkle.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you get those people on Twitter?
You know those people that go around saying that depicting everything in media is bad.
No toxic relationships.
No crimes.
No enemy balloons.
And especially, no rule 34 of anything.
That isn't an adult human being.
They even came after those bloody gory MLP cartoons.
Where do they all even come from?
God, I miss Newgrounds.
Twilight, I mean Twitter Sparkle, Newgrounds still exists.
It does still exist.
In fact, it's like it's had a like a resurgence a bit recently.
The clock gang is still posting.
What's up with those clocks?
I never really clicked on any of those.
I was just like why are the clocks of everything?
They were just a group of animators who just kind of had like they were sort of a gang who all kind of
themed their animations similarly.
Damn, that must have been the life.
That's exactly what I want.
Is to just be in a fucking art gang, making a splash in a scene.
It's all I want in life.
And I've been cruelly denied it.
What do you have to say for yourself?
I mean, wow.
Defend yourself now.
Well, I mean, we could start an art gang.
I'm doing things.
Yeah, I just, I mean, yeah.
I mean, what constitutes a gang?
I don't know.
Do we need more people doing it?
That's a good question, honestly.
I don't know.
I don't, I can't answer.
I can't answer.
I'm sorry.
I don't have one.
But it's something to think about.
Okay, but we'll be a gang.
We'll be a gang.
Yeah.
Well, what makes a gang is we have to like wear headbands and like go around with like
bats with nails and then like bash and stuff.
And then, and we got to go and we got to snap our fingers and go and like break into song
when a rival gang shows up on our turf.
Oh, yeah.
Those are the two criteria.
And we're, I was thinking more of like an Italian mobster gang.
Like violin cases.
That's also, you know, fine.
That's, that's cool too, I guess.
Next one is called Cyborg Ben Saint Sextal.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah, this sounds like me.
Thanks.
Have a great day.
Taru.
What the fuck is that?
It's your favorite musketch phrase.
Haru.
Taru.
Oh, true.
56709.
Oh, Taru.
Taru.
56709.
You know that, you know the 56709?
Of course I know.
Okay.
Awoo, 56709.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Um, next one is called We've All Thought It.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you ever, like, look at someone and think,
how the fuck were you the winning sperm?
Sure.
I look at myself in the mirror like that.
There you go.
I don't know.
I don't really think of sperm when I look at a person.
It's not the first thing I think of, sure.
Okay.
Anyway, next one is a...
All right, well, there's an Imgur album link.
So let me check that out real quick.
Oh, okay.
I clicked on that.
Wait, wait, it says voicemail is unrelated,
so react to this first, please.
Okay.
Getting people to play just your game to catch all the bugs.
You fucking lizard replay the entire game now, you loser.
New fucking lizard.
I mean, I mean, it's just, yeah, it's that's,
I was just going to say it's just true.
It's true.
It's funny because it's true.
Why would you get people to play test it?
When they could, when they could play like...
You just put a lizard in.
Just put a lizard in.
Just put a lizard in, and there you go.
Free play test.
I get that the implication might be that if I'm going to make versions,
I should have a beta on Alpha.
I think we will eventually do that.
If we make a Kickstarter, there'll be an Alpha where people can access it
before the full game is out.
But for the demo, we only wanted to make one other patch to solve some things.
It's not an ongoing thing.
But I agree, emphatically, with this meme template.
And I will download it and use it.
Thank you for that.
Actually, yeah, this is, this is good.
This is, this is, this is reusable.
It's very funny.
Okay.
Well, the voicemail is called, it's rant about voicefakes at twitter.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you have any idea how hard it is to find a good voice to fake?
This is my third.
Actually, now it's fifth.
Account on play.ht, fakeu.com is pretty great and free,
but it doesn't understand punctuation at all.
I have to break sentences into tiniest chunks,
thinking like characters I am using would.
And even then I have to retime it all in audacity to make it sound natural.
And when character doesn't know a word or its acronym or a number,
I have to use other words and splice them together.
Trial period has expired again.
Oh, and those nostalgic critic and linkara voice banks.
No way, nostalgic critic never said katana or anime.
But somehow it understood.
Sonichu.
Understood.
Why you want the fuck?
What's supernatural?
Not a single voice bank there has the word.
Anime.
I'll just put Google translate voicemail next time.
Cause fuck that.
P.S.
Wanna hear something funny?
Here you go.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
One, one, one, one.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
That was pretty funny.
Yeah I like that.
That the computer interprets a sentence
filled with ones would go in that direction specifically is amusing.
What do you mean by that direction?
Well, you know, the pitch would change, you go one, one, one, one, one, like, and speed
up.
It makes me wonder.
And then it would settle into a loop at the end.
Like, why does it think that a sentence like that should go that way?
It's like, it's...
Yeah.
I did wonder, like, why are some of them at different pitches and stuff, like, how does
it...
Like, oh, people talk like this at the beginning of a sentence, they have a horizon, like, I
noticed in some AI things, if you put a question mark at the end, it'll read it all, and then
it'll, like, have the upward lilt of, like, a question voice in there, like, not just
at the end, like, the way people ask questions is, like, kind of specific.
Sure.
My fucking superintendent, or whatever you call him, is, like, bellowing at my fucking
window over my house again.
I hope that's not picking...
I hope that's not picking up on my microphone.
I guess I do not hear anything.
I mean, I can faintly hear it.
What is he...
He's always yelling.
He's always yelling about shit.
He doesn't know how to leave a voicemail, so he just wastes it while we're recording
and then screams it.
Next voicemail is called...
Oh, okay.
There's no voicemail.
It's a second long.
There's a link.
I'm going to follow that link.
Voices.com slash blogs slash how to submit a podcast.
Okay, right.
It's because I didn't like hearing that one voicemail where you explain something, something
or other.
No, Tom actually got back to me.
Tom actually got back to me with a...
What I was hoping wouldn't happen, but Tom got back to me with an explanation of how to
do it.
So he said he might do it, but the fact that he explained it to me makes me think like
I'm probably just going to have to do it for now on.
Okay, whatever.
How to submit a podcast?
Whatever.
Okay, next one is called Please 3, 2, 1, go.
Thank you, please with the broadcast on Spotify.
I'm going to fucking kill you.
Probably I will do that, only because Tom finally...
I'll have to figure it out.
I mean, he's gave me an explanation and it was really long.
He sent me like several paragraphs, like, well, it was split into lines, but it was at
least like 20 plus lines.
So like there's steps involved and I don't want to do it.
I don't want to learn how to do it, but I guess maybe I will.
Next one is called Fan Theory on Tom, 3, 2, 1, go.
Fan Theory on Tom.
He moved to Virginia because it was where Nate is and he was thinking that Trixie's
there too.
Well, is that where she lives now?
But anyways, I know Nate lives there now, so, right?
Yes.
I don't know.
Both of them, right?
I'm not fucking...
You're definitely wrong that that is why he moved there, but you are right that Nate
does move there.
Trixie also lives there.
So I mean...
I don't know.
Any day now, PCPHQ.
Yeah, three of them.
I don't know.
I don't think...
I don't know exactly where Trixie lives.
I don't think she's like that close to Virginia Beach.
Nate is in or around Virginia Beach and Tom, I don't know where in Virginia he lives.
So I don't actually know how close Tom could be like way out in like the boonies part of
Virginia, perhaps.
I mean, it's all boonies, honestly.
But it would be really funny.
It would be really funny to see like Tom in like a Trixie vlog one of these days.
After all, she's done.
I mean, she didn't do anything to him.
I guess so.
Well, she sort of dropped Iron Games or like wasn't...
I guess it's not really that much.
Yeah.
He seemed a bit like maybe not even offended or maybe not even hurt, but like at least
confused that like she didn't even mention Iron Games in that one time.
But like, I don't know.
I don't really know how Tom feels about anything.
So I don't...
I just...
I don't know.
I guess it would be...
I would be surprised.
I would be surprised to see Tom in any like Trixie thing.
But I guess I wouldn't consider it like impossible.
I wouldn't like it, obviously.
But like all kinds of things I don't like happen and that's just like...
Next one is...
Yeah.
It is kind of funny.
Like, yeah, they all live in Virginia.
I don't know if they talk at all anymore, any of them.
So maybe they'll just live in around there and just not have anything to do with each
other.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Next one is called More Buffalo Bill, please.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, that's it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wasn't that a voicemail I called Buffalo Bill?
Oh, there was.
Yeah.
Yeah, why are you asking us?
I mean, I guess they're just getting the word out.
Yes.
Okay.
Now I remember.
Next one is a YouTube link.
The video...
That's about the best video game.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Next one is another, is a link to a soundtrack piece from the other Supergiant game, Pyre.
So I wonder if this is the same voicemail.
Anyway, yeah, it's called Gushing About the Best Video Game.
Three, two, one, go.
You brought up Pyre by Supergiant Games on the last podcast, and holy shit.
No.
Pyre is so fucking good, and people need to play it, actually.
So, like, the objective is to play Magic Basketball to free your party members from
exile.
Success means you have to periodically get rid of your highest level characters, so you
have to play and you're leveling around that.
But if you lose, you don't get to try again.
You just keep going, and one of the other teams gets to be freed from exile instead.
A lot of the time, these teams are really great, too, so you might even want to intentionally
throw some of your matches for their sake.
As a result, the narrative is focused more on the modular storylines of each character
and how they interact with each other.
And in the end, you can read about every single ally and enemy to see where they ended up
in their relationships with the other characters.
There's this huge net of interactions that can be wildly different depending on how you
play, and it's so fucking good.
This is also not mentioning that the soundtrack is God-tier.
Never to return, and especially in the flame are probably my favorite songs from any of
the Supergiant games.
Yeah, I watched a video about all the Supergiant games, and Pyre seems very weird, but that
guy...
I don't remember who it was, honestly, but he really liked Pyre, and it seems interesting.
And it's just really funny that we had another voicemailer send in a YouTube link to a transistor
game, being like, I haven't played Pyre, but you gotta play transistor.
And this person is like, you gotta play Pyre.
Here's another YouTube video about how the music is good.
I guess I might give him a shot.
Maybe.
I'm still working on Hades.
I think what I'm working on now is boosting all my relationships with all the characters,
because I think that's gonna unlock post-game stories content, so I'm working on that.
Okay, next.
I got the credits now.
You beat the game, but that's not the end.
There's more to do after you beat it, until you have to beat it in certain ways to get
the ending, which is the credits, but then there's still more stuff after the credits,
so that's where I'm at right now.
Next one is called Nikolai for Voice Grail, please at gmail.com.
I mean, he did die.
He did die, but dying doesn't mean Voice Grail.
Necessarily.
I don't know.
Do we feel that Nikolai made substantial contributions to the PCP culture?
I feel like Nikolai was alright.
I don't think he's Voice Grail.
Yeah, I don't know if he's Voice Grail.
I'm sorry, Nikolai.
Rest in peace.
Rest in peace in hell, because you're not getting the Voice Grail, buddy.
Next one is called, I know how much Cybershell likes these, 3, 2, 1, go.
I'm so sorry, but Cybershell is not present at the moment, but I will pass along your
message for him.
Go forward these.
Yeah, to his agent.
Next one is called Ben Stop Listening, 3, 2, 1, go.
I heard it in your voice last week.
You want to talk about the one piece stuff.
So without spoiling, what are your feelings?
Are you in the, this is cool camp.
Are you in the wait and see what Oda does camp?
Are you loving it?
Are you bad and wrong?
I don't think you're bad and wrong, but you could be.
But yeah, don't spoil it for Ben.
He'll never, he'll never expect Sanji's giant dildo foot.
I have been, I have been not fully spoiled, but I know something about what has been,
what has transpired.
What do you know?
I know, okay, what I think I know is that something has been revealed about the gum
gum fruit that has changed, like the gum gum fruit has some capability that is,
that has like changed everything seems is what I'm picking up from the, what,
of the discourse I've heard.
It's something like that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Personally, I, this is the sort of thing I would have loved to talk about on the
podcast, but like, I don't have like that anymore.
Yeah.
And it feels, I don't really care.
You're not, you're not, you're not part of the gang.
Not part of the gang.
You're not, you're not part of the cool art gang.
You're not part of the scene.
You're not making waves in the scene anymore.
I'm sorry.
You just can't have it.
That's how I feel.
That's how I feel all the time.
Welcome to my dark twisted mind.
All right.
So without spoiling too much of anything, I find that it's, it's, I can see that it
came to this point.
And I, and people say that it's like, Oh, to plant it, just look at this, just look
at that.
And I'm like, cool.
I think it was a bad plan.
And it undermines a lot of themes that of the whole thing.
But I don't know exactly where they're going with it.
It's just the way it was revealed.
It does not leave a lot to the imagination.
And I, I don't like what I saw.
I'm not that into it.
Sounds like this guy would call you, sorry, this individual whose gender I am not aware
of trying to be any, whatever.
This, this, this person thinks you, you're bad and wrong.
I mean, maybe I am, but like, I, I'm not like seething and like, if this was on a podcast,
I imagine Nate would be screaming and I would be like agreeing, but not screaming along
with him.
It's, it's one of those like, I, I, I don't like, there's parts about it.
I like, like the visuals, like the, the, the sort of like, it's, it's, um, I mean, it's,
it's a problem that I've had for a while.
Ever since, um, like the, it was sort of shifting like the importance of Luffy as a person.
Like he was already always kind of important because he had like very powerful and notorious
relatives.
Yeah.
Um, but like he himself, uh, is just like, he was a kid who ate a fruit.
And then like out of happenstance and then was like, had a, like a rough childhood fighting
and wanted to become a pirate.
And it's like, that's his journey of his, his like journey of just trying to be a pirate.
I mean, not even, and now it's becoming, yeah, it's becoming a bit more like, and it was always
meant to be.
And I'm like, not, not even about this, the latest relation revelation, which I'm not even aware
of, but like other things, like the fact that his, his dad is like the, yeah, his dad is
the leader of the like revolution and like his brother is, is this captain of the, or
you know, the first mate of the shanks crew and, uh, you know, he's got.
The white bear pirates, the, the, that's what I meant.
Um, and, uh, he's like, yeah, he's got all these powerful relatives and like Sanji's
got this, like his dad is like king of the whatever.
Yeah.
I hate, I, I think I have the same feeling about that stuff.
It's like, why has he got it?
It's like the, I haven't watched the new Star Wars, but like how they made Ray like, oh
yeah.
Palpatine sir grandpa.
Yeah.
It's like, why?
It, it couldn't possibly be a story about a person who just is exceptional for their
own.
Yeah.
From, from themselves.
I mean, I think of like a really good protagonist, which everyone agrees with is guts from berserk.
Yeah.
Like he's overwhelmingly strong, but that's because he was fighting since he was like,
like 10.
And like he's had a really tough life constantly fighting in bandit wars.
And then like, you know, fighting, fighting with like sell swords until he was a young
adult and then fighting with the band of the hawk through his whole, you know, into adult
life.
And then after like the big thing happened, he was fighting like demons and and he's fueled
by rage and hate and it's like, he wasn't anyone special.
Yeah.
Like he was just some kid who got roped into this stuff and it's like, it could have happened
to a different person and it's like, the more time, the more times the agency is taken
away from the protagonist and put onto a special advantage that they had the whole time, the
less I can relate to that protagonist, the less I can really feel like I'm rooting for
them.
It's not that I don't root for Luffy anymore.
It's not like that drastic.
It's not like the end of like my enjoyment of one piece, but it is a bit of like a like
a it's one of those sorts of feelings.
I mean, I think I said this about my hero academia when I thought I thought the initial
premise was interesting and then I found out because it was like, oh, a guy with no powers
in a world of people with powers and then it's like, oh, well, actually, no, he just
he kind of gets the best power actually.
It's like, okay, that's fine.
All right, that's fine.
I'm not interested anymore.
The best character in Naruto was Rock Lee, because it was really compelling.
It was really compelling that he's this everyone else has all these fucking is these fucking
wizards who have these like magic spells and like his thing is like, he just he doesn't
have any spells.
He doesn't have any fucking super magic.
All he does is like, he just trained really hard and he's really strong and tough and
he knows what he's doing and he's just he just makes it work.
He just makes it work like that.
It's more compelling.
It is.
It is compelling.
There's a part near the end where like, there's a very dangerous fight going on and Rock Lee
has to like, open like the gates like the and he opens too many is like putting himself
at risk.
Yeah, sort of like, yeah, the unfortunate reality of him not being a main character that like
he can't rise to the heights that Naruto can rise.
Yeah.
Even if he tries his hardest, but he will still try his hardest anyway.
And I think he wins that fight with the help of guy.
I can't remember exactly what was I going on.
I remember him opening the Chakra gates.
I did see that part.
Yeah.
And it's like, despite everything, despite all of his hard work, he cannot be main character.
And it's sad, but it's like, it's cool that he still has a mystic viewpoint on that and
he's like, he's going to try his best.
It's sad, but like you can I mean, he's still at the end of the day.
You can look it's like, well, he's still accomplished a lot.
Like it's still like incredible how far he made it.
Yeah.
And it's like, wow, I love broccoli.
He's so cool.
He's so great.
But yeah, and that's the sort of the thing you I feel like this is true for a lot of
media where like the main characters, the chosen one and blah, blah, blah, whatever, they've
got the main character syndrome where they're just sort of uninteresting.
You kind of know what's going on with them and then you get you fall in love with like
the side character or like the anti hero or someone else.
They're your favorite.
You know what was really, you know, it was a really great twist, though.
I complained a second ago about like Sanji's Sanji being sort of an important guy for
an important family.
I really liked though that he's like, you know, he's from this, he's from this, this
litter of like clone experiment children that all are like superhumans.
But he's like the one failure that like didn't get superhuman power, but he just like is strong
anyway.
Cause you know, it's like cause like cause one piece rules just, I don't know, Oda used
to say stuff in SPS is this is like in one piece, just if you have a strong will, it
just makes you strong.
And just these characters just have so much will to accomplish their dreams that they just
are powerful.
And it's like, yeah, you know what, that's that's all of the explanation I need for why
a character is powerful and strong and accomplishes what they're set out to do.
They just wanted that.
I mean, that's, I mean, that gets you, that gets you most of the way there.
No, no, no.
I mean, I agree.
But like, uh, wait, it doesn't matter.
Don't worry about it.
I can't tell if you're being like sarcastic and being coy because I don't want to spoil
anything.
Anything about one piece?
Yeah.
I, okay, okay.
You know what?
I am curious.
I am pretty curious what everyone's talking about with his latest something or other.
In the grandest scheme of things, um, it's not like a deal breaker.
Like I said, it's not going to make me stop reading.
Sure.
Um, I'm sure it's still going to be like my favorite manga ever.
Yeah.
It's just like the further they push the whole like chosen one angle, the least the
less I enjoy seeing what happens.
Yeah.
I feel you.
The less viscerally I feel this, the, the triumphs, even though I know like he's doing
his best.
Yeah.
Uh, the, that was that voice man.
I agree.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, all right.
We've got, okay.
We've got one more.
All right.
Next one is slime times weekend update 5.0.
Here we go.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Hello gangsters and gangsters.
Welcome back to the slime times weekend update.
Gangsta.
This installment leaves your dear reporter with some based news and some difficult news.
Last week was a week of changing alliances while this week culminated in slightly more
sobering events since there's much to report on.
And this is also a bit of a catch up job for last week.
I'll be separating this new segment into two parts.
Last week, rowdy loom, a robot girl switched over to killers while mischief, a humanoid
rabbit switched from killers to rowdies.
This was dubbed a cultural exchange program, though either gangsta may decide to stay with
their new posse if they find it just too cozy.
In addition, killer Angon managed to trick Matt into pardoning himself while trying to
pardon another player.
Simply bereft of his rowdy affiliation, Matt quickly proceeded to don his best purple flannel
and take a nice little picture.
Finally, last week, the rowdy territory control party known as Kappa Palooza took place, as
organized by Soba, during which rowdies blasted music, shouted like idiots at each other,
and turned the entire map pink.
Ha!
Uh, based?
I mean, I shouldn't celebrate something like that.
That's pretty base.
It's kind of base, though.
It sounds like fun.
Uh, alright, well, there's the second part.
Slime times weekend update 5.1.
Uh, 3, 2, 1, go.
Part 2.
This week, the curator of the Nalakakaw Museum decided to hold a celebration in the saloon
and drop some archeological hints.
As a result, a new area outside the city was discovered.
The darkened dank caverns which harbored the Ark of the Sludgeonant, another relic of yore.
These were the ones to solve the riddle and open the cave, but due to the obstruction of
a gameplay bug, the killers ended up catching up with the thrashing explorers and were able
to take the artifact for themselves.
Unfortunately, the frustration of this event proved too much for a few rowdies, and they
decided to take a break from the gang warfare.
They also took some time to complain about the community and the killers in place of
the longstanding issues, and the whole event had people from all sides pretty bummed out.
This hoping heart will be uplifted in the weeks to come.
That's it for this time.
And remember, the slime time is the best time.
Oh, seemed to have some time left.
Fuck you guy who set the PCP episode for too long.
Fuck you for telling us that we shouldn't send in voicemails this week.
Guess what?
This one is twice as long.
That's right.
A full minute 20.
Piss in your general direction.
Your mother was a slime corp grunt, and your father was a stay dead.
The word, pretty much the two worst things you could be.
I was going to say, I hope the ones that decided to take a break from gang warfare, I hope what
you mean is that they committed suicide and went stay dead.
Historically, that is how you register disdain for gang violence, is by killing yourself
and being a ghost and hanging out in the sewers.
I hope that culture is still alive and well.
Oh, the movie never ends, it goes on and on and on and on.
Okay, next one is called Prince Isolation BTWs A Question Answered, 3, 2, 1, go.
Oh yeah, you guys were asking where that little message is, where you say that the PCP still
has a hashtag that takes Twitter questions.
It's on the PCP voicemail speak pipe page.
When you click the link below your videos on the description, yeah, that's where it is.
I see, I would never, I didn't even, hmm, okay, all right, maybe we should update that.
Maybe.
Okay, next one is a vocaru file, all right, 3, 2, 1, go.
Oh, my God, my baby's about to say his first word, come here mate, look at, oh, it's Ethan.
What did he say?
See?
I can't hear it, stupid baby, stupid baby, that's barely, speak English, what are you,
foreign babies, freak, can't understand you, give me a fucking break, anyway, there's an
image, actually I'm not sure if this is, I think this is unrelated, yeah, the next voicemail
is an image, that's the girl who thinks phantom horn is a trans allegory, has changed a major
feature of his body in a way that made him happier, trans colors, there they are, yeah,
has a dead name, but what's phantom horn's dead name, you know it, is it phantom horn,
no, you don't remember his family name, oh, fuck, it was something like the dad is, wait,
is it standard?
It is standard, yeah, they're the standard family, so he's just a standard guy, until
yeah, he changed his last name to horn, well his full name, it was substandard, lol, I
imagine being like born and your parents call you substandard, well he was meant to make
sandwiches at the deli, that was his destiny, but he decided that he had a higher calling
in life, it's funny, who names the pony, like it would have been a baby, a little filly,
he doesn't know that he doesn't have a cutie mark about subways, I think it might have
been a digi brony thing theory, or maybe it wasn't even digi brony, maybe it was some
other one, but someone had a theory that a pony's name can change if their cutie mark,
that a pony can change their name when they get their cutie mark, and that would explain
why some ponies have weirdly on the nose names, I mean it's the only way you could explain
that really. Yeah, so it was according to that theory,
their family runs like a deli, and their dad was like, this son is going to make the sandwiches,
and so they called him substandard, and yeah, I mean that's it, that's the joke.
So it owns at least one katana, it's the next thing, I guess that's a trans, you know,
I don't have a real katana, but I do have a fake one in the corner, little wooden one.
I have a couple, I guess I'm not trans, but I have a couple shinai, I have the bamboo training
swords, that's like pretty close, that should count for something, that means I'm an ally.
That's a non-binary sword, I think. Oh, well, oops.
Former question mark, MLP fan, do they mean like phantom horn?
Yeah, I mean he canonically, you know, he had the YouTube channel where he reviewed
My Little Pony the show. Did you ever like explore like the in-world
like implications, like is phantom horn watching a show that takes place in his hometown?
Yes. Like a documentary?
The answer is just, no, I think it's, honestly, I'm not sure if it's like, if this is a documentary
about like Princess Twilight Sparkle coming to live in Ponyville, or if it's about like
fictional characters in a real setting. Yeah, I'm not sure which of those is true, I don't
think we ever really thought about it. One of them is definitely true. Like, yeah, actually
that's a great question, like are the main six and like all the events of the show, like
are they canon to the T-Bap universe? I don't know. Maybe I should ask Nate his opinion
about it. Like the T-Bap universe is, the T-Bap universe
is the My Little Pony universe, if nothing interesting happened.
The T-Bap universe is the Brony Analyst universe, because like Gibb and Take and all the others,
I love Kim Possible a lot, technically, because you appeared in her video.
I did. I did, yes.
Everything's connected. Dr. Wolf is part of that universe.
It is all connected.
Yeah, well, the most sensible thing is that they're actors, actresses, and they play like a show.
Like, what if our world was cool, the show?
That's kind of like what real shows are like.
I suppose so.
What if our world was cool? Yeah, do you think that's how it is with the
the Brony Analyst community at large? Are the events of My Little Pony merely fictional
events set in the world that those YouTuber avatar characters inhabit?
Yes.
Then I guess that's how it is for T-Bap, too.
Yeah, I mean, make sense to me.
Honestly, now I wonder if there's an answer to this among like the Rift Cafe.
I wonder if the Rift Cafe exists anymore.
I very much doubt it exists in any forum like they used to.
I mean, I'm sure it would be different. I would imagine people just like are still friends.
I mean, some of them still do pony content.
People still, there are still pony YouTubers, still pony tubing.
Is Dr. Wolf still releasing like an analysis anarchy episodes?
I think he is. Yeah, I think so.
Incredible.
Now, I shake my finger.
I wag my finger at anyone that tells me that Phantom's Revenge is too niche and can't succeed
when analysis anarchy, you know, is a cultural juggernaut in a powerhouse.
Like that's, it's honestly, it's just, well, it's maybe not just as stupid or just as niche.
I mean, Team Fortress 2 is something that more people know about.
It's Team Fortress 2 and it's like jokes on the level of Big Bang Theory.
Yeah, honestly, I guess it is even more niche than analysis anarchy.
Were you there in the panel room?
Yes.
That we went to in the BronyCon 20 years.
We sat right behind Christian.
Oh, God, she was there.
She was like right in front of us.
Well, yeah, what a time to be alive.
What it was, they were good, good times.
Anyway, rest of this image.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So former MLP fan and Loccom equals found family, I suppose that's true.
Yep, for sure.
Transitioned from Pony to SlimePony.
That is, that is true.
The ultimate HRT is Slime.
You're jet, you're probably not wrong at all.
That's literally alters your DNA.
Yeah, there's, there's no, you're just right.
You're just right about that.
Slime has an E in it, coincidence.
I don't know.
Like estrogen, like as much like estrogen, yeah.
And epic epic communist classic trans character trait.
Now, I'm not sure.
I'm not sure how much of this is tongue in cheek.
But I mean, I'll just say that, like.
I mean, Phantom is this isn't a stretch at all.
Phantom is explicitly, honestly,
originally sort of a cruel mockery.
That's overstate.
He's sort of a cruel send up of being trans originally in a way that I feel
some guilt over in the way that I originally.
Invasion, I didn't.
I mean, I didn't mean him as like, I didn't mean him in like a cruel way.
But in hindsight, I feel like the way that I
designed him in a way that was commenting on like, yeah.
I identify with having a horn.
Yeah, I don't I don't really.
I don't I mean, I wouldn't literally has like purple hair and has pronouns.
I mean, he literally does.
He literally has his blue fur, blue fur and pronouns.
He he what could I what could I say?
What could I say about him?
He I mean, I was I guess I was just defending
being transracial on this very podcast.
And that's basically what Phantom is.
So like.
Yeah, he was he was sort of he was sort of supposed to be.
A like.
I hate to say it.
This is this is true.
But I think he was kind of supposed to be like an S.J.W.
that takes it too far.
You know what I mean?
He's like, oh, well, this is this is he's he's just taken it.
He's just gone too far with all this.
His weird, his progressive values or whatever.
And now I just think he's he's just I just agree.
I have come to just agree with him unironically.
That's that's character development.
I yeah, so he's no longer a joke.
And and that's a and that's character development.
Yeah, you're right. You said it.
So there you go.
You're this image is just correct, I guess, more or less.
True good to get through all I can say is true.
Yep. OK, the next one is
next one is called One Piece Lamel three to one go.
You know, I hope I still made it in time for the podcast because
I heard you had trouble like getting it on Spotify and Google Music and stuff.
So I hope I can help you by saying like you got all the distro kids now.
I heard really great service costs like ten bucks.
So you have to log in and it probably tells you what to do.
I don't really know. So what it maybe check it out.
I thought I thought what's he recommending?
Obviously, you don't know how to do it.
So I thought I something something Spotify.
So keep it up.
I've been listening to the podcast in like a couple of months
because because I'm on Spotify, I'm like, well, I'm going to listen to it.
So I hope I can help. Bye bye.
Thank you.
Thanks for the voice.
I think that was a joke.
No, I think he maybe just didn't realize that's what he sounded like.
Like if you do it through your phone and you don't listen back to it.
I can't tell.
I can't tell if that was like a serious voicemail or not.
I could barely make out what he was saying.
I think he was just saying, hey, I'm ending some service that does something
that helps with putting it on Spotify.
OK, well, thanks.
But I think you need a little help getting it on.
Speaking, getting it on speak. Yes. Yes, exactly.
Yes, you're you got it.
You got to fix your own house.
Fix your own house before you try to clean up my living room, buddy.
Next one is called puns four weeks late.
Three, two, one, go.
An episode there, too.
You were trying to come up with puns for marriage, divorce and a cliff.
How about they being in a rocky relationship?
What?
Oh, a rocky, oh, a rocky relationship.
Yes, in the slime times, we can update about the two people getting married.
Yeah, yeah, two people got married
and then they like shoved each other off cliffs and died.
So a rocky relationship, like they died on the rocks.
Oh, yeah, I think that works.
I don't recall that.
Maybe it wasn't on that one.
I remember.
So, yeah, you know what?
This is better than anything I came up with.
I would say that's a I would give this a solid B plus.
And that's at least a passing grade.
I think that's it.
Is it the last one?
Yeah, that's our last horseman.
There we go.
We did it.
All right.
I feel like I got.
I feel like I said some I had some insights to share on this episode.
Glad I got to talk about phantom a little bit.
Glad I got to talk about my views on transracialism
and saying the N word on this episode.
Pretty pretty.
I'm happy with I I can.
I can look myself in the mirror and say you're on a podcast and respect
the face I see and say, how are you?
How are you the winning sperm?
I can look at myself at the end of the day.
I can still look myself in the eye and say you are on a podcast.
I guess that's it.
Yes.
Play phantom's revenge.
Play pumpkin alley.
The pumpkin patch.
Check out the pumpkin patch.
Find that eight lizards.
Can you find eight lizards?
Can I only find four?
Can you find?
Can you?
Can you though?
You think you can, but can you?
Let's find out.
Speakpipe.com slash whatever link in the description.
I don't remember.
Patreon.com slash the the procrastinators.
I will upload some bonus episodes soon.
I was saying before there are a couple of like bonus episodes of like behind
the scenes conversations that I just forgot to upload.
I think there's like two.
That's just I haven't put up, but I will this week.
Yeah, I'll do it this week.
Um, that's it.
You got any last words before I make you walk the plank?
Yarr part.
Yeah, yo, yeah, yo.
Oh, no, um, uh, uh, I just got shot and I'm dead.
You killed her.
OK, bye.