Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Well, it looks like it happened again. Another solo cheesy cast. The only member of the PCP who actually shows up on time around here.
Well, I mean, I guess we could go into questions. I don't got that much to talk about. I usually write notes, but I didn't this week for this.
I told you guys I'm moving, right? Yeah, but I thought long and hard about this, and I'm thinking that I kind of don't want to live in a place with like 10 other people anymore.
I think, I don't know, I think that isn't too good for my psyche. I'm thinking maybe I need to like look for like a solo spot, but Boston is expensive.
And I was thinking like, hmm, it'd probably be cheaper to live in an RV. So yeah, I'm going to invest into getting an RV as soon as I can.
And you know, just shove it in your studio space. Am I right gamers? Am I right gamers?
Anyway, I guess it's question time. Time to pull up the questions right now. Right now.
Ben, you can jump in now. I'm out of material.
Wait, what? Huh? What? Oh, was I supposed to jump in?
Oh, shit. Oh, sorry. I, sorry. I was, um, I was distracted at watching the new Geo Wizard video, uh, the new mission across Scotland.
It was just so engrossing. I know you were doing a bit and I was supposed to jump in, but I just, I started watching his, his journey, his journey across Scotland.
And I was just so engrossed. I couldn't, I couldn't tear my eyes away.
Oh, okay. Well, at least you were doing something productive. Am I right?
Am I right? I just wanted to hear your, I just wanted to hear you, your Ben saying impression. Got to say, I'm offended.
Is that really what you think of me? Is this, is this, is this true?
I think if I want to do a better Ben saying impression to be like.
Was your heart in it?
It would be like, um, have you ever seen the, the movie Italian Spider-Man?
No.
Wait, wait, wait. Is that's the one with the gift of the guy going, oh.
Like he's pointing. Yeah. Yeah. Um, there's this one scene where these, uh, these Italian like college boys are a cat calling one girl.
And then Italian Spider-Man just comes out of nowhere and punches the boys and says, respect women.
And then the woman, the woman, the woman goes up to Italian Spider-Man and says, thank you Italian Spider-Man.
And then Italian Spider-Man just punches her in the face and says, shut up pussy cat. Now give me a macchiato.
Okay. Is it supposed to be funny? It sounds like it's supposed to be funny.
It's like if, um, I, the premise is like, imagine if like in the seventies, like somewhere in Italy, someone made like a bootleg Spider-Man movie where he acts nothing like Spider-Man.
He's just named Spider-Man and that's it.
It's, oh, he's just like, he's just happened to be called Spider-Man, but he has nothing to do with the character.
Right. Yeah. But throughout the whole, yeah, but throughout the whole, the whole movie is on YouTube and I think it's like under 30 minutes.
It's not too long. And yeah. And everyone just calls him Italian Spider-Man.
Like they say that.
Like in the movie, like in the movie, they call him Italian Spider-Man.
Yeah. They call him Italian Spider-Man.
Right. And besides that,
Why are they, are they Italian?
Um, it's implied. I mean, it's, it's the way it's shot is that
Does it take place in Italy?
Um, I don't know. I think it takes place in, I think the, the production company is Australia and I think they filmed the whole thing in Australia.
But, um, the, the joke is that they, they said the whole, they said all the lines in English, but then they dub it over with like Italian, right?
So it looks like, um, you know, it looks like that bad kind of dubbing, but that's like part of the charm, you know?
I see. I don't, I don't understand. I don't get it. I mean, I've seen the GIF.
I'm surprised I don't know more about this movie because I've been hearing about the Italian Spider-Man movie for like years.
Like that's such an old meme.
Yeah.
And yet I, I, this is all news to me.
If you watch the Italian Spider-Man movie at the end, like after the credits, it says, go visit the Italian Spider-Man MySpace page to get more info.
It's, it's that old.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
I was going to say, I mean, that's newer than I thought.
Like I thought it was from like the 80s.
No, no, it's supposed, it's supposed to look like it's from like the 70s or 80s.
Like that's kind of like the bit, like they did that on purpose, you know?
Oh, well, they, they got me.
They got you.
They fucking tricked me.
They fooled the Great Ben Saint.
They got him under his fucking nose.
Nothing, nothing gets past me.
Yep. Nothing gets past Ben ever.
Um, I will quickly mention at the beginning of this episode that if you've been listening, you know that every so often I bring up, we have the Kato anthology guys on the Kato anthology, the Kato anthology Kickstarter is ending this weekend.
If you're hearing this, it will be ending on Monday.
So this will be the last weekend.
It is, um, it is closing in on $4,000.
I think the next stretch goal is for $4,200.
Nice.
Or 4,200.
Yeah.
Get in there.
Let's get that to 69.
Am I right?
Yeah.
So link, link in the description.
Check that out.
It's your last chance.
It is the last opportunity.
Um, yeah.
Check it out guys.
Very good.
I would check it out.
I would donate, but, um, I am broke at the moment.
I just moved into a new place.
What are you?
Did I go on?
Broke?
Yep.
What are you fucking, what are you fucking stupid?
Like what's wrong with you?
But you don't have any money.
Is there something genetic?
Something genetically wrong with you, my guy?
Like, well, how can you be broke?
Broke?
You're got, you're being real queer coded right now.
Cheesy.
That's really queer coded.
Ben, you're giving me a lot of gender envy right now, Ben.
I would recommend you stop.
Uh, uh, I mean, that's what I do.
That's why I just go out there and perform my gender in a way.
I just, just, I'm just, I'm a dysphoria machine.
I'm an engine for it.
Everyone's jealous.
I wonder if there's anyone out there who watches, who watched like the
Sonichu lecture and they're all, they look at you and they think,
damn, Ben's giving me some real gender envy right now.
No.
I'm sure there's not.
I'm going to, um, I, I saw, oh man.
Okay.
So I watched the Sarah Zed video about the, the, the, the,
what are they called them?
A Bimbam brothers.
Oh yeah.
McElroy's.
I had, I didn't know anything about those guys.
I had like, I'd heard their names.
I knew that they did a D and D podcast.
I didn't know what they were famous for or anything about them.
But the one with the purple hair looks uncomfortably like me.
Oh no.
With the pink hair.
I didn't, I didn't like, I didn't like seeing that and wrecky like,
oh that's, he's kind of got my vibe going.
Oh no.
He's me.
I don't know.
I don't know if I feel about this.
It looks like me.
He does a podcast with his brother.
This, this is too real.
He does.
It's too spot on.
Um, he's, he's like a, he's like, if, uh, he's like if Ben St.
We're a loser.
That's like what people should say.
I look at what is it to me?
I don't even know which one.
I was about to say, I was about to say it's like if Ben St.
was productive.
I was going to say.
No.
Got him.
Um, I was, um, I was shocked.
I was just, I was surprised listening to that video because she
mentions that one of the Mabim Bams wife does a podcast called
Saw Bones and I had heard of Saw Bones because John Boyce
mentioned Saw Bones in the pretty good episode where he talks
about the set.
I think it's the second ever like Olympic marathon where like,
do you, do you know this, what I'm talking about this video?
Is that the, is that the story about the lady who like cheated
or something?
The lady who cheated.
In like a marathon or?
No, you must be, you must be thinking of something else.
No.
If this, the, the John Boyce pretty good video about the
Olympic marathon, basically the story is that it was held in like
110 degree weather on like a dirt road and it was like, yeah,
like the runners were like collapsing from heat.
They were like breathing in like dust and like choking.
Some of them almost died.
There was like no water available on the route and it turned out
spoilers.
Go watch this video, but if you haven't seen it, it spoiler is
that it turns out that like the guy in charge of it was some kind of
like, I think he was some kind of like sicko fucking Auschwitz
Nazi scientist or something who like used the whole thing as
like an opportunity to test what happens when humans are
deprived of water.
It was like a sick experiment.
Do you know what year this was?
I think it must have been in the 1800s or so.
I don't, I have no idea.
It was like recent enough that there are like pictures of it,
but they're like old timey black and white photographs.
Yeah.
So in that episode, he talks to the lady from Sawbones,
which I guess must be one of the McElroy Brothers wife and asks her
if because one of the doctor, no, not the doctor, one of the
coaches, like one of the runners coaches is like following along
with him in a truck and he won't give the runner water because
he thinks that drinking water will like prevent him from
running.
He instead lets him like coat the inside of his mouth with egg
whites and then gives him like strict nine pills as like a
stimulant.
Yeah, that's what they fucking did.
It sounds like you would fucking puke on on the fucking
spot if you gave me that fucking shit.
Like they all like nobody finished the race.
Like only like a handful of the runners actually finished it.
Well, I mean, if you puke in the middle of the race,
secondly, you should be faster because you have less weight in
you, right?
Well, that must have been what he was thinking.
Right.
You don't want that all that heavy water weighing you down.
Exactly.
You know, maybe also if you shit your pants while you're running,
you should be able to run 10 times faster, right?
Just get it all out.
Right, exactly.
Cut your arms and legs off too.
They're just weighing you down.
You know how swimmers are like swimmers like fucking have to
trim all their body hair because hair like slows you down
when you're swimming, right?
It creates drag.
Right, exactly.
I assume it works the same way.
Jesus Christ.
I was just, I was shocked to hear that thing mentioned in,
I don't know.
It was just like, wait, that thing is connected to this thing.
And I know, and I know what that thing is.
And it's two different things.
It's that podcast incest.
I'll tell you that much.
I had another moment like this one, and this one really,
really pissed me off this week.
I've been, I've been listening to a bunch of Tim Rogers stuff from
Kotaku.
Well, yeah, it's a bunch of Tim Rogers videos, his own stuff from
Action Button and his older stuff from Kotaku.
And no, sorry, I've, I've unburied the lead.
I've spoiled a little bit.
Sorry, I meant to bring up, there's a new atrocity guide video
about Bob's game.
Oh yeah, I saw that.
Which is like, yeah, the story about the guy who made a game,
demanded that Nintendo publish it on the DS and staged like a,
like a hundred day strike and did all these like weird protests
to protest Nintendo not publishing his game on the DS.
In that video, she says that like someone who was involved in
like breaking that story was a guy who knew Bob and that was
Tim Rogers.
He like knew the guy.
And I'm like, oh wow, that's a weird coincidence.
And then I'm, I'm listening to want some old Tim Rogers video
on Kotaku.
And he just casually throws out like, yeah, I don't even remember
what we were talking about.
I think they were going shopping for games.
No, it's the video where he's going through games and he's
describing their box art from memory without looking at them.
And he's talking about finding a game on a shelf in a store.
And he says, yeah, I was shopping at a mall with my good friend
Vito Guisualdi.
And I'm like, I know that guy.
I hate that guy.
Fuck that guy.
This makes me so mad.
Isn't Vito that one like edgy, like internet comedian guy?
Yeah.
The guy who, the guy who I thought he seemed okay until I saw him
being like, JK Rowling actually makes some good points.
I was like, okay, nevermind.
Nevermind.
Fuck this guy.
He kind of reminds me of Lilith Lovett, who I hate too.
Who?
Lilith Lovett?
Yeah.
Do you know who Lilith Lovett is?
I do.
I've never heard of them.
No.
She's a trans, like libertarian who like, I don't know.
It's like, there's people on Twitter that I always see who like
every time I see one of their tweets, it's always like a fucking
atrocious ass.
She must know.
I wonder if she knows Aria DiMzzo.
Remember Aria DiMzzo?
That sounds kind of familiar.
Friend of the show.
Friend of the show was running for, was running for sheriff of
that county in New Hampshire.
I mean, they couldn't.
Another trans woman libertarian.
I'm not surprised.
They hope so.
Yeah.
Lilith Lovett was like, I mean, I feel like that's not a huge,
I feel like that's not a huge like, like van diagram crossover.
Those two things.
Maybe there is.
I don't know.
Not really.
I was about to mention earlier that I think one of the
McElroy's brothers were like a former Kotaku writer or something.
Right.
I mean, they're, I wouldn't surprise me at all if they did.
Cause like, I mean, when you're, when you're famous, you can just
write for anyone.
Anyone will publish your shit.
Right.
Yeah.
You could have for like a second.
I just, just made me mad.
Just made me wait.
What?
I said you cut out for a second there.
Oh, sorry.
Um, I just made me mad cause like, um, oh fuck Vito.
Fuck all these people.
They're all in a big club and I'm not in it.
It's all about who you know.
It doesn't mean it's all, it's all, it's, it's all a bunch of horseshit.
You know, you know, people, Ben, right?
You have a laundry list.
No.
Who do I, who do I, this, who do I fucking know?
Who do I fucking know?
Oh, oh, I'm that.
Oh, Ben St.
You mean that guy who's friends with Digi bro?
That's, that's me.
That's my legacy.
Yeah.
That's me.
You might be wondering how I got into the situation.
This, this is what it is.
This is the reality of my situation.
And it's so bad.
It's so shit.
You know, I think at some point in the past I must have thought like, yeah, maybe
like, you know, this is what you do.
You get a bunch of people, you get a bunch of creatives or whatever.
You form a little click.
You form a little collective.
You, you, you, you become like, oh, you're, you're associated with that group.
Oh, that group does all this stuff.
I don't know.
You forge a, you forge a collective identity.
Um, and then you all like mutually support one another and stuff.
Uh, well, I don't know.
Maybe at some point I thought that's what was going to happen, but it didn't work out
that way.
Uh, things didn't go, things didn't go quite how I expected it.
I'm, and I'm, and I don't like it.
It frustrates me.
I'm like, why couldn't I, why couldn't I have been?
We could have, we could have fucking, I don't know.
Maybe if I'd made better friends, we could have, uh, we could have started our own Kotaku
or whatever.
I think the, the real, uh, Genesis point was when, uh, Ben say it became a comedy.
I think that really ruined everything.
That I, if, you know what, if, if that hadn't happened, we probably would be, we probably
would be, we probably would have started a video game journalism outlet on the internet
and, uh, you know, or whatever.
We probably would have, you know, really hit that algorithm and like, you know, just gotten
to the front page of Reddit every, every, every day.
I don't know.
I've been saying, I've been saying this for years.
I've been saying this for years.
Uh, PCPs got to go back to their alt-right roots, you know.
How many years have you been saying it for?
It's been too long.
I've been saying it for years.
Like, yeah, like it was much better when, um, Ben saying didn't like people who are a
darker skin.
It was a way funnier era.
The jokes are funnier.
Um, spiral has continued his, uh, his quest to document every usage of the N word in,
uh, in the PCPs history.
Uh, he says he will eventually make a spreadsheet.
Who said it the most about it?
Um, who said it the most?
Um, I mean, like, is that what he's trying to figure out that like he's going to have
a spreadsheet?
Well, among, among, among other things, among other things, hold on.
Um, um, hold on.
He's posted some of his incomplete data.
Uh, I will summarize.
Was in the lead.
Tell me.
Okay.
Yes.
So it was before, okay.
Apparently there is a, there is a big moment.
There's a big point in which, uh, it gets said a lot, uh, and it was the empathy episode.
And I think that it was like, Trixie says it a lot.
I think a bunch of people had said it before.
Trixie says it a lot in the empathy episode, but I want to see the before empathy and after
empathy numbers.
Oh, wait.
Yeah.
I remember that episode.
She famously said, I have no empathy for the N words.
I remember that classic line.
Is that what she said?
No, that's not what she said.
No, what the fuck?
That's terrible.
No empathy for the N words.
I'd say she has too many, she has too much empathy for N words.
That's why like bird is like transracial or something, right?
No, Riley is transracial.
Oh my gosh.
Or something.
Yeah.
One of them is transracial.
I remember Trixie tweeting one time like, I'm a fusion of like Huey and the other little
girl from BoomDocs.
I forgot, but she's the one who's like mixed.
She has like a black, a black dad is like a lawyer and a white mom.
You know what I'm talking about?
Wait, who are you talking about?
The one little girl character from the BoomDocs.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh God, I don't remember her name.
But I know what you're talking about with the big, the big buns.
Yeah, exactly.
Hair buns.
Yeah.
I remember Trixie saying that she was like a fusion of her and Huey.
Wow, that's stupid.
What a stupid thing to say.
I don't know.
You should tweet out your fusion of Applejack and Twilight Sparkle or something.
Okay, so before the empathy episode, which is episode 30, the N word count for soft A
was Trixie 11.
Everyone else, nothing.
Damn.
The hard R count before episode 30.
I think this is right was, no, or is this just the episode, or is this just in the hard,
in the episode?
I don't know.
I think this is in, I'm a little confused looking at the data, but whatever.
The point is after it, after episode 30, episode totals were soft A, Trixie, 15, Nate, 14,
9-0, 4, but gets a pass.
Obviously, DeVoo, 2, Ben, 1.
I think I said it with the A one time during the empathy episode.
I think it was my first one.
Looks like Ben wins again.
Ben's the real winner here.
Well, no, because a bunch of names aren't on here.
That is true.
I'm surprised.
Hard R, hard R, Jesse, 8, Nate, 6, Trixie, 6, Monkey, 6.
Oh, I just wanted to say I'm surprised Monkey's not on the list, but never mind.
Well, he only used the hard R.
Oh, epic.
That's very in line.
Very epic.
It's crazy because now he's on a podcast.
Actually, so did Jesse.
Jesse only ever said it with the hard R and never with the A.
I am not surprised.
It's crazy because Monkey's now on a podcast with Reactor and Rusty Cage.
I don't think he says the N word at all on that podcast.
He saved them all for the PCP.
Reactor fucking sucks.
Reactor's a piece of shit.
I'm not a fan of Reactor.
Rusty Cage, I don't know.
He seems all right.
I thought he was, I don't know.
I have this inclination towards people who just make comics.
It might be a bias.
I kind of just respect people who make comics more than normies, you know?
Absolutely.
Right, exactly.
If you don't make comics, you're not even human to me at TPH.
As Monchi once said, it's the most heroic art form.
The most heroic art form.
Rest in peace, Monchi.
We miss you, bud.
Yeah, but that being said, I don't know.
I think what really kind of bothered me was that he was getting a lot of advice from Doug
to Naples.
Doug to Naples probably gave him a good ass comic advice.
That being said, I don't like Doug to Naples.
Yeah.
Well, I think from what I know about him, he's just another, he's a real Scott Cawthon.
He's a real, who's that other one?
He's Two-Faced.
Orson Scott Card.
Oh, it was a guy who makes a Dilbert.
Who's the one that?
Dilbert.
Oh, that guy's his own can of words.
I was going to say he's like another, who's the Timmy Turner, fairly odd parents guy?
Butch Hartman.
He's just one of these fucking like Christian children's entertainment douchebags.
It's funny.
He's like a huge like, transfer, but I remember in, I think in One Stream, I was watching that,
he was on the Drunken Head.
Who, Doug, Doug Tennipal is?
Yeah, yeah.
He's like this huge ass transfer.
Yeah.
On One Stream.
On One Stream, he was talking about how he thinks, he says that Rebecca Sugar is like a genius.
And I mean, I think Rebecca goes by day, I think.
They, um, they were like, yeah, I'm not, I can't remember.
I mean, I could always look it up.
I'll look it up in a second.
But, um, they, um, they consider Rebecca Sugar a genius and Rebecca Sugar is like a former
student of Doug Tennipal.
Cause he, I don't know if he still does like classes on animation, right?
So it's, it's, it's, it's, it's interesting.
I don't know.
Some people are like, I mean, I think Scott Coffin is probably the example of like, oh,
I really love the LGBT community.
You know, the big part of the fandom, but you know, like, like, you know, we shouldn't
like, uh, we shouldn't, uh, you know, we shouldn't encourage it.
We shouldn't alienate people who are Republican and want to wipe out LGBT people.
Have you read his, uh, have you read his apology?
Compromise?
Doug's apology?
Uh, no, um, Scott's apology.
Scott, Scott Coffin's apology.
No.
Yeah, yeah.
I didn't, I didn't actually read it.
I saw it and I was like, I get it.
I saw like, uh, the couple of, like I, I retweet it.
Guys, here's a fucking surprise.
Probably no surprise.
I don't really read the majority of the shit I retweet.
Um, if you follow me on Twitter, it's all kind of blends together after a while.
Yeah.
My, my, my stream, my Twitter is a stream of consciousness.
I'm just fucking retweeting shit.
I do not care.
Like, like the only reason that I see any art on Twitter is because you retweet it.
Um, based.
Pretty based.
That is pretty based.
Yeah.
That is pretty fucking based.
Um, speaking of art.
So this, by the time this podcast comes out, um,
Speaking of comics, I think.
Speaking of comics.
Yeah.
So I think you're talking about how heroic they are.
Yeah, exactly how you're probably, you're just probably a better person.
You're probably handsome.
You probably got like a big dick too.
Like TBH.
Most likely.
Right.
You ever, um, oh, now that you're, now that you are a Daniel Klaus fan, uh, Ben, have
you ever read that?
True.
You ever read his, is he made like a little comic called Ink Studs?
You ever heard of it?
I think I've heard of it.
I haven't read it.
It's, it's like, what was the one that you, what was the one that you gave me to read
and remind me what the title was again?
Daniel, Daniel boring.
No, it's not.
I mean, David boring, my bad.
David, yeah.
David boring.
Yeah.
Okay.
I knew it.
Right.
David boring.
I liked it a lot.
Uh, I'm glad.
I'm glad.
You should read the rest.
But anyway, he made this one comic called Ink Studs.
This is all it is.
It's just one page.
And it's basically just like, hey ladies, ditch these loser musicians guitar, uh, like,
uh, betas and get with the real chats, which are the comic artists.
Oh, wait.
I've, I've seen this.
I've seen, you might have shown this to me actually.
Oh, it's great.
Uh, 10 out of 10.
Also it's true.
And it's not ironic.
Come to think of it.
I'll take an ink stud.
I get it.
Come to think of it.
Hmm.
Per.
Now that I, now that I've run the calculations again.
Uh, yeah.
Gotcha.
Oh God.
But yeah.
What was saying?
Yeah.
Okay.
So also on Monday, I think I'm going to have, I'm going to, no, I'm not, I don't think I'm
going to have pre-orders for the next physical copies of villain verse, but I'm going to
also villain verse.
Yep.
Eleazar.
Hey post, post the cover, post the title or not the, yeah, post the cover for the next
issue that you are, that you are releasing, I guess, publishing, opening up pre-orders
for.
Hold up.
But show it on screen.
Eleazar.
It'll be on the screen right now.
I'm going to post it in a second.
Anyway.
Um, yeah, I'm going to rework it because if you, uh, Ben, you bought like previous copies
of villain verse.
I think I bought, uh, I have two, I have two, uh, comics.
Do I have all of them?
I think you just might have all of them.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
I think this would be, this would be the, the cover.
All right.
This is the cover for the.
There.
Yes.
Oh dude.
Is that a, is that a champion reference?
Cause he's got tusks.
Oh yeah.
Ben saying inventor of tusks.
I forgot.
I invented tusks.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Ben say directed the movie tusks.
It's pretty good.
Check it out.
Is that a Brunswick reference?
Dude.
Epic.
Bro, is that, oh my God.
A reflection.
Is that, is that a vapor's reference?
Oh my God.
Is that a glass, is that a glass reflections my favorite anime YouTuber reference?
It's a vapor's reference because none of the characters in vapors reflect on themselves.
I just spoiled the ending of the vapors.
What was it going to say?
Yeah.
So if, if you, if you, if Ben, if you were to grab your physical copy of villain bridge,
you would notice that it, each physical copy includes like two chapters in them.
Right.
I, I'm aware.
I've read them.
This was a dumb mistake.
I'm going to fix this.
I see.
Because I only did that because I wanted people to read the prologue and jump right into chapter
one.
Like I didn't want anyone to like take a break or anything or like have to wait for chapter
So that's why like I have the prologue and chapter one in the same book.
And then the next one I put two and three together.
But then I realized like, wait a second, why am I doing these for the next books?
Like the other ones could be just self-contained.
So I, I, what I'm going to do is just make after chapter one, each chapter is just going
to be a single issue and it's not going to like be a combo book anymore because it's
like,
Are they going to be longer chapters or are you just going to chop them up?
No, but chapter five, which is,
I mean, honestly, honestly, the second book is pretty thick.
Like for a, for a, what do you, for like a trade paper, it's, it's quite thick for a
trade paperback comic book.
So like may make sense.
Yeah.
The, the first book was like the prologue is like 20 pages and chapter one is like 25.
And then the second book is chapter two and chapter three and both of them are around
like 26 pages.
Right.
So that's why it's like thicker.
Yeah.
Also, I started adding like, I started adding like bill and verse fun fact sheets at the
end, you know,
Which is good.
That's what, that's what I like.
That's what I like in a trade paperback is.
Extra.
Fun facts.
Yeah.
If, if I, if I could, maybe I'll start doing this, but I'm a big fan of like the little
like, you know, in the chapters of one piece of what the beginning of each chapter has
like a single image that would be like its own like story that takes place outside of
the one piece story.
Oh, I don't remember what those are called, but I know what you mean.
Yeah.
And then later on in the story, like those would connect back, you know, I kind of want
to fucking, God, I would, I'm tempted to kind of do something like that.
Um, because there's just constantly things happening outside of the main bill and verse
story, you know,
Expand the universe, but naturally.
Right.
Exactly.
But I don't know.
I'm still thinking about it.
I kind of liked the fun fact stuff because it's kind of like, I guess easier to dump.
Like, oh, um, this thing they use, it has a name or some, some random bullshit.
I think I'm going to like highlight like lesser villains and, um, and these next fun fact sheets
like, um, like you see a lot of like villains in the background who don't get names and
I think I'm going to like start naming them.
There's some, wait a second.
I want to highlight.
I want to ask you what one's name is cheesy and entertain them for a moment.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, um, so how about them?
How about them?
Mets.
Am I right?
Gamers?
Oh my God.
If you haven't read Villainverse, uh, go read it.
That shit's free.
It's all going to be free when it's over.
Uh, chapter five should be out by now.
That should took too long.
That should took like five months to make chapter.
Okay.
I'm back.
All right.
So let me, let me, let me get, uh, let me find the one who I remember.
I was taking a shit as I often do when I picked up my copy of Villainverse chapter three.
Ben ran out of, uh, paper, uh, toilet paper and he thought like, oh, well this Villainverse
chapter might do.
Exactly.
Uh, it's, it's when they're all getting eaten by the bugs, um, spoilers.
Uh, uh, no, it's, it's further ahead than that.
Uh, yes.
Yes.
Shit.
The pages aren't numbered.
Yeah.
No.
Describe the panel.
I know all of them by memory.
Okay.
Well it's the page where all the bugs are like coming out of the ground in a big like tornado
and like they're all like coming at the, the camera and they're just crunch, crunch, crunch,
buzz, buzz, buzz.
Right.
And there's the guy in the door face is like running away and he looks scared and underneath
the villain says, yes, yes, eat them up my children, fill your bellies with their flesh.
Right.
While one is one, like he's like black, like he's being bitten and he's being stretched.
He looks like, he looks like a cartoon.
He looks like a, like a squash and stretch cartoon.
Oh, and then on the previous page, on the previous page, there's a bug guy who's shooting bullets
at him.
Oh no.
Or like two pages before there's an action scene and a guy with a, like a praying mantis
head is shooting bullets and this same like squash and stretchy, stretchy black man is
like out of one side.
He's got like drool coming out of his mouth.
Yes.
Oh wait.
I know what you're talking about.
No, no, no.
Before.
Yeah.
It's like two pages before the eat them up my children.
It's someone, it's like the kind of small, it's kind of like the big, it's like the panel
at the bottom.
I know you're talking about.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
That's the one.
That guy's name is inky toad.
And he's like inky toad.
Yeah, that's his name.
He was actually like, so what's cool about villain verse is that like it's a good excuse to just
use a bunch of character designs I created when I was younger.
Right.
Yeah.
Cause I drew that guy, I think in like high school, maybe.
And then I like found the drawing of the guy and then I like read.
I'm like, oh, this guy could be like a villain.
Right.
He's like a little guy.
Yeah.
I think, um, I think the bug guy is called like, I think he's just called the roach maybe.
I don't care.
I don't care about that guy.
Yeah.
I'm a big ink.
I'm a big inky toad Stan.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
There'll be, um, there'll be more inky toad.
Um, like, I guess I think I said this before, but the ending is going to be very Avengers
end game where like everyone comes back and there's like a giant.
It's like a giant fight, but that's, that's the most I'll say.
Cool.
Oh yeah.
There he is.
Mary is prototype.
Yeah.
I, I, I noticed this guy in a couple of shots and I was like, this guy doesn't have a name,
but I'm, I'm kind of interested.
He actually does get it.
I'm sure there's more to him because.
Yeah.
Does he?
Wait, he, um, hold up.
Does, does he get in?
Does he get introduced and I missed it?
Yeah.
Let me just, I'm looking for.
Damn.
Okay.
Wait, this is filed too big.
Ah, I'm going to pull it out in a second, but just say what you're going to say.
I was going to, I mean, there's like, there's like hundreds of these guys that all have
names and numbers.
So I wouldn't be surprised if I missed one.
Oh, there he is.
Inky toad.
VSR.
What is it?
Eight, 20, eight, eight, 89.
That's, that's pretty good.
That's not too bad.
Yeah.
I think.
All of these guys are just like little OCs or characters that I created when I was like
younger and I'm just repurposing them.
You know, it's pretty fucking.
Makes sense.
Yeah, it's pretty fucking base.
But, um, also some of them I've been like, I think I'm going to might reuse a couple
other designs that exist out.
Like, like, let's say the inky toad character pops up in a non-villain verse related word.
You know, cause like, why not?
You know, why?
Yeah.
Why not?
Why the heck not?
Yeah.
I guess.
Cause, um, I think later on it's going to be implied.
There's like multiverses.
Right.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's that's some of it.
When is the is the is the villain verse going to merge with our reality and the dimensional
merge?
Oh, did you not?
Oh, wait, hold up.
You gotta read the fun facts page, Ben, because I remember one said that one fun facts page
said that humans are extinct and a villain verse.
I remember that.
Um, so, but if our dimensions merged, well, no, it must, it must be a different, it must
be a different universe than C one nine seven because there are definitely humans in C one
nine seven.
God, I wish, I wish, uh, I wish they wouldn't merge.
Um, I wish Chris, uh, Sina would read villain verse.
Please.
That's the, that's the, you just call it Christina.
Uh, is that, oh, it's Christine, right?
Christine.
Yeah.
Um, uh, that's, that's the strat.
Right.
That's the marketing strat.
Yeah.
Christine.
That's how you do it.
No, no, that's how you become, that's how you become famous, wildly successful and famous
is you get that person to acknowledge you and then everyone respects you for your work.
Yes.
If you, if you get her to obsess over your, um, like franchise or your, or your IP, your
instant, instant cash starts flowing now.
Are you on board for the hashtag save MLP movement is I, I think I retweeted it.
I think I retweeted your quality, but what is it?
Uh, can you go in specific?
What is it?
I, I, at first I thought that it was just like an account that she made.
Now I'm, I'm not sure.
I think it might just be some other weirdo, but the point is it's a Twitter account dedicated
and, and a petition dedicated to get Hasbro to know, do not make, uh, uh, MLP gen five,
go back to gen four, we, we have to go back, um, we, we, we, we none of these new ponies
keep us with the old ponies, please.
And I guess they want to retcon.
They wanted to like, they want has, they like, literally they want Hasbro to be like, actually
that last episode didn't happen.
That flash forward to like princess twilight didn't happen.
That was all fake, uh, never mind.
We were joking.
It was a dream or something.
You know, this is like, this is not the first time you hear about like people trying to
petition like, Oh, fine episode is not canon anymore.
Like, has that actually fucking worked?
Like, is that like what the fuck, what's the point?
Uh, I wonder, I feel like, well, I mean.
They did, uh, Mass Effect, right?
Everyone complained about the Mass Effect ending.
Did they retcon the ending?
And they didn't like, I think they didn't like change it, but I think they did maybe
retcon some bits of it.
Like in DLC.
Oh yeah.
I remember that.
Actually, there was like a DLC that what I'll go fix it.
I, something like, I remember Mr. B tongue was not particularly impressed with the retconning
job that they did, um, the, um, bass, I guess, uh, so I mean, I guess sometimes it kind of
works a little, it's, I don't know what's like, um, it's so, I don't know.
I wouldn't, isn't that, isn't like, I think like the current, um, the last one is a gen
four.
Is that, is that the one?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
So gen four is the one with Twilight Sparkle, Pinkie Pie, Fluttershy, etc.
I think what's kind of really cool here is that they could kind of do like a magical girl
power ranger kind of thing where like each gen, they have like a certain number of like,
um, main six they have to like create, right, but they're like different every gen and then
they just have crossovers with previous gens, you know, like I, I anticipate, I mean, since
gen four was such a hit, I feel like it's a virtual certainty that we'll have references
to it in gen five and, uh, maybe, maybe even some, maybe even some character, I don't fucking
know, it could happen.
I mean, like power rangers do that all the time where they like, um, cross, they always
have an episode where they cross over with the previous, uh, team, right?
Yeah.
And you know, so based, so based, so based, you know, I, uh, that one episode, that one
episode with like the eight, 18 different red rangers from like all the previous incarnations.
And I mean, I've, I've seen the Linkara, I've seen the Linkara retrospective.
Yeah.
Oh, big Linkara.
Pretty much.
Big Linkara head shout outs to tectonic improv to tectonic improv, although that's not technically
about that lecture.
That's about, um, the Toboli flee, which the lecture does not, I guess no, the lecture,
I guess the, I guess the power rangers, he is in character as Linkara.
So I guess it is.
Is he, he doesn't do any like skits on the history of power.
He doesn't, he doesn't do any skits.
No, he doesn't, he doesn't do any skits, but I, I think he's still, I think he's always
like in character as, I mean, because like his, his reviewer persona is Linkara.
So as far as I'm concerned, if he's reviewing something, he's Linkara, whether he's doing
a bit or not.
Where does the, where does, uh, Lewis begin and Linkara and, you know, it's Lewis.
Lewis love hog.
I forgot.
Um, but that's pretty, that's a pretty cool name.
It's, it's all right.
It's all right.
It'll do.
I was thinking about Linkara.
Oh, so, um, yeah, shout out to tectonic.
Um, next time I come back, I always try to come back every two months, like motherfucking
Jeepers, we can't, we can't get rid of you.
Right.
Exactly.
You can't, um, you know, we need a little mosquito buzzing in our ears.
There's too many, there's too many voicemail that, that say we need more POCs on, um,
the PCP dog.
You heard, did you, did you hear the last episode?
Um, I listened to half of it, but, uh, okay.
Well, if you only listened to half, then maybe you don't know about the voice.
I'm dreading the voicemails this episode.
I think they're going to be real bad.
Okay.
Let's just drag this.
I think there's good can and say, Oh, we ran out of time guys.
I'm with the LA's are I can edit the rest though.
No voice fails this week.
We have, first of all, we have a lot of them, which to me seems like a lot of people like
heard the last one and maybe responded to it.
And I'm, I'm, I'm a bit concerned that like the gates have been thrown open and
people suddenly realized, I think the, I'm, I'm, I'm worried that the, the, the
interrupting pig or whatever has like, let people know, yes, you totally can fuck
with a system that, you know, overtly has no oversight or moderation.
And people go, Oh my God, me too.
Oh, I'm going to fuck.
I'm going to make bad voicemails on purpose too.
Ha, it'll be so funny.
It's going to be so cool.
I think it's time to hire a person to look over like all the voicemails.
Right.
This is, this is an app like this is a, this is an application wanted a DM
Ben, if you want to be the, the voice, no, leave, leave me a voicemail.
Leave me a voicemail telling me your qualifications.
Submit your resume, uh, if you want, if you think you have what the gumption,
what it takes prove to Ben, you have good taste.
All right.
Like leave a voicemail and say the most good.
Okay.
Here's, here's the thing.
Here's the standards.
Leave a voicemail and say the one line that proves you have good taste and that
like is evidence that you'd be a perfect moderator for the voicemails.
Right.
It's not, it's not actually true.
I think, I think if it ever hits the point where we have, where I have to
start like reading or like pre-screening the voicemails, I think that's the
point where I just say no more voicemails.
They're over.
Why don't you, um, why don't you just like listen through them while you're like,
I don't know, drawing or something.
Cause that sounds terrible.
Cause that sucks.
What, what, what more do I need to say?
That sounds miserable.
I don't, cause I don't, cause I don't want to.
I guess you're getting paid.
How's that for an answer?
Cause I don't want to get paid enough to do that.
I, the point, the point.
The whole, listen, this, this is the Ben St.
show now.
This is my solo show.
What would be the point if I listened to them before the show and then listen to
them again on, on recording?
Oh my God.
The point is to react to them.
The point is to be surprised.
No.
If, if I have to pre-screen the voicemails, voicemails are over.
All right.
So yeah, if you, if you want, if you, so listen, if, if what you want is further
never to be another voicemail again, then yeah, I guess do flood
the voicemail submission box with deliberately bad voicemails.
I have an excellent idea.
How about you just like, you just accept like the first, I don't know, 10 voicemails
and the rest are instantly thrown in the trash.
So people have like a, like kind of like an, a window, you know, it's like a
death battle style, like voicemail.
I, I guess, yeah.
I mean, I guess that would be one way to do it.
I guess that would be one way to do it.
Right.
So people can't just, you know, I mean, there could be like one guy,
like, well, well, well, that's what I would do if there were just simply too
many good voicemails rather than like being flooded with bad ones.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's different.
It's different, uh, uh, just like with Digimon, you know, like different,
different conditions, right?
Like different, like win loss ratios will let your Digimon evolve into a
different champion and ultimate form in the same way.
Like, you know, different qualities of voicemails will cause that segment of
the show to evolve into a different final evolution.
Right.
Exactly.
It's like, it's like raising your chow.
It's like raising your chow.
It's like, are they darker or are they lighter?
You know, are they hero?
I don't want them darker.
I don't know.
Are they a P are they a POC or not?
Yeah.
How neuro divergent are they?
I was fucking playing Sonic Adventure, um, last night actually on my game cube.
No shit.
Yep.
And we went to the chow guarded and the chow guarded in the first, um,
adventure game is kind of, it's kind of boring.
There isn't that much you could do.
Right.
Yeah.
I think in two is where they have all the fucking little funny little fucking
mini animals pieces.
And I mean, I've never played any of them.
So I don't know.
Oh, it's probably for the good.
I mean, like, look, like I love shitting on Aaron Hansen, but he was kind of
right about those adventure games.
Like not going to lie.
Yeah.
What?
And that's just that they're not as good as everyone remembers them.
Yeah.
They're not as good as I'm sorry.
Well, I mean, I mean, I've, I feel like fans recognize that like in, in cyber
shell, not cyber shells in, in, in running Shine's review of it, he's
just like, here's my guide to whether you'll like Sonic Adventure.
If you liked it as a kid, you'll probably like it.
If you didn't, you probably won't.
I, I, yeah, I liked it as a kid.
Like I beat the whole game.
I did, I did every campaign.
Um, and, and just to let you know how much like as a little kid, I liked it.
I didn't realize like I beat like bigs, like level is like campaign, but I didn't
realize that everyone on the internet actually hated that campaign.
I kind of just thought like, oh, yeah, what's so bad about that?
Right.
Yeah.
Sure.
I mean, as a kid, you don't fucking think about those things.
Um, no.
Right.
Exactly.
Um, so we got a shitload of voicemails, right?
There's quite a few.
Yeah.
Okay.
Why you want to get to him?
I mean, uh, I want to say it, if you want to, if you want to, uh, if you want to,
I kind of want to say two last things before we do that.
Um, I mean, you're more than welcome to say, you're more than welcome to say as
many things as you, as you want to say.
Actually, I have another news, but go on.
No, no, no, baby.
No, no, after you, no, after you, you know, by what it means.
No, after you, no, I insist.
No, but I insist.
Listen, you're, you're a person of color.
You're higher on the purpose of stack.
You need to be platformed ahead of me.
We need to, we need to elevate your voice.
So please speak.
I command you.
Oh God.
Okay.
All right.
I, I'll go first.
When a white, when a white man tells me, never mind.
I take it all back.
When a white man tells me to speak, I will speak.
You are right.
That's right.
I mean, I mean, I mean, I, it's complicated.
Okay.
I think I was going to say that, like, uh, yeah.
Shout out to take tonic.
Uh, next time I come back, I want to take tonic back.
Love that guy.
Um, shout out, shout out to his podcast, journalism, not included or journalism,
not guaranteed my bad.
Yeah.
It's pretty good podcast.
Oh no, I did a, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, baby.
But, um, what else are you going to say?
Yeah.
Uh, read villain verse, uh, pre-orders will be on Monday.
Um, fuck the Cato anthology.
Just buy villain verse.
I'm sorry.
You're like, I would have done the Cato anthology, but like I have my own.
Well, now if you, if listeners, if you hate cheesy and you hate villain verse,
then you should buy the Cato anthology out of spite, cause that would make him
really mad.
Those are the two teams it's.
And same, and same for if you really hate the Cato guys, you should buy villain
verse out of spite.
Cause I, I, they told me this was in DMs.
I won't show screenshots.
They told me that they would be so mad if people bought villain verse.
Yeah.
I'm ironic ruin their day, like behind, like, um, I was, I was supposed to be on
the Cato Cato anthology episode, but then Ben told me, like, yeah, um, they,
they don't fuck with you.
So you can't, they hate you.
They told me, they told me like that guy's toxic.
He, he, he saw what I post on Twitter.
They say I'm too political.
And in my opinion, they were absolutely right.
I wish I had the courage.
Right.
So I wish I had their courage.
I wish I could tell cheesy to a stupid fucking face.
You shut the fuck up on Twitter.
Yeah, but I'm too, I'm too fucking scared though.
Too cocked.
They'll do those teams.
These are the teams.
Team Cato versus team villain.
Uh, which side are you on gamers?
Uh, comment below.
Yeah, please.
Okay.
I, I think, uh, okay.
That's it.
Uh, all right.
Uh, see you later, Ben.
I'm like, no, I want to complain.
I want to complain about my life.
All right, all right, baby.
I broke, I broke my fucking toe again.
Remember how I did that before?
Yeah.
You remember how I've done that like five times?
Why it happened again?
Was it the same piece of furniture?
No, I'll, I'll go through the history of my, of my feet.
Um, the, the first time I broke my toe was when it was in this house, same house
I live in now, I was coming down the stairs and I missed a step and I like fell
on my foot and I broke my.
Metatarsal the like side bone on the side of the left foot.
And then at Radcon two, I think I was, I was during the, I think it was during
the Tony Hawk pro skater, let's play that Jesse and Vic were playing.
I run through the door and I stubbed my toe, my left toe, same toe, different
bone against like a piece of furniture, break it, go to the hospital.
Oh my God.
Uh, yeah.
It happened again.
I don't even remember when it happened again, but I like basically the same
thing, stub that same left toe.
This time I didn't go to the hospital because they don't do anything.
All they do is tape it to your next toe and give you a sandal to wear.
And they're like, wear the sandal.
Don't walk on it too hard.
Yeah.
So that's what I did.
So, and that's what I'm doing this time, but this time it's my right foot.
This is the first time I've broken my right, my right pinky toe.
I was, I was working on my game.
Patreon.com slash Ben St joined my patron discord channel where I post
exclusive updates.
I've been posting updates there.
I've been posted whips, works in progress for those that don't know.
I've been posting sprite art.
I've been posting like animations, being like, Hey guys, check out this coming
along, new feature added, new feature added.
The updates are coming fast and loose.
Um, I want, and I, and I was in the zone and I was like, all I want to do
tonight is just grind out sprites.
I know I just have like a hundred sprites to grind out.
I just want to grind them out.
I'm going to go and buy some alcohol and just get a little drunk and just kind
of zone out and do it.
And that's what I did.
And it worked great.
It was working.
The plan was going according to plan.
It was going perfectly.
I wasn't the night was still young and I had gotten plenty done and I had run
to get plan.
I was in the zone and then I go to the bathroom and I'm coming out and I'm
little uncoordinated and I just my toe against the door frame smashed it.
It's horribly bruised.
It still hurts.
I still hurts to walk on it.
Uh, and I am upset.
My summer is ruined.
Uh, this is, this comes on the heels.
No pun intended of me needing to go and like, I need to be house hunting.
I need to be out on the streets, looking for a new place to live.
And now I can't fucking walk without it hurting.
Damn.
This is awful.
It's like you're, you're like a curse or something, you know?
I, it's, it's, it's, it's not fair.
You know what?
It's not fair.
You know, it's not fair.
It's, it shouldn't have been me.
It should have been you.
I wish, I wish it was you instead.
You know, it's funny.
Just right before I got into the recording, I did stuff my toe on like the
doorframe of my bathroom.
Right.
Well, you should have stubbed it harder in solidarity.
It's, it's, it's annoying.
I don't, I don't know.
It's hard to tell if the bone is broken or not.
It doesn't look like bent or anything.
It was quite bruised for a while.
The bruising is, is letting up a little bit.
Um, it doesn't hurt to like push.
I can touch it and it doesn't hurt at all.
And I can like stretch my toes up and that doesn't hurt at all.
But when I curl my toes down, it feels weird.
It hurts.
And if I walk on it, it hurts a little bit and it's, it's uncomfortable.
It's got a weird feeling.
I think the bone is like micro fractured or something.
Yeah.
I'm just bummed.
You're bummed.
What, what, what, uh, bones.
Yep.
You're bones.
It's sad.
It makes me sad.
I am like, when I think about it, I'm just like, oh, that's unfortunate.
An unfortunate thing happened to me.
Why?
Why, bed?
Well, why, why must this straight?
Why boys suffer so much?
Why must, why must dad things happen to good people?
You know what, Ben, I'm, I'm being honest with you.
Here's my honest opinion.
I don't, I don't believe that you, you broke in your toes or any of your toes
in any, all, I think all those stories are fake.
Um, okay.
And, but I think the only way you can probably, the only, the way you can
probably prove to me that those toes have been broken.
If I don't know, if you took a picture of them every time you're like, I don't
know, stop them and you DM them to me, you know?
Uh, man, it was very purple.
It was very purple and splotchy and horrible looking for a day there.
Uh, it's, it's bad.
It's a little better now.
It's just kind of like red.
The bruising is letting up a bit.
Ugh.
Um, I just want to, I just want this, it came, this happened right as.
Oh yeah.
The rad content has started to come out again.
The, um, did you see the Brad lecture?
I saw, I saw half of it.
Yeah.
It's a, it's funny.
I don't know.
I remember it.
Like it was only yesterday.
So watching, watching it again, I'm like, it's so weird.
All the, all the comments were so like melancholy.
All the comments I noticed that all the comments are like, damn, it's just sad.
Like watching what it used to be.
And it's like, look at the state of things.
Now it's, it makes me sense.
And up, you've, chin up, you fucking, you fucking, you fucking saps you fucking dweebs.
Get over it.
I should have come life has changed.
I should have commented on that.
I was going to, I, I was going to comment like, damn, I, I, oh, like seeing them like
this now, I, I hope that my comic could somehow travel through time and they could
see my comments and just warn them of things to come.
Warn them of the things to come.
Yeah.
You can tell them, no, there will, no, there will be a pandemic.
No, coronavirus.
No, go becoming trans.
No, watch out, it's coming.
It would be like, it would be like Oedipus, like, um, was it the fucking fortune teller guy?
The Sphinx, the Sphinx, right?
Or was it the Oracle?
I don't know.
That was like a, you know, the Oracle tells, um, Oedipus dad that like his son is going
to kill him and bone his, um, his wife and he like tries to prevent it from happening,
but it happens anyway.
So I go back in time and I warned them about, oh, you're all going to transition and that's
going to throw out the PCP.
Everyone, no, it was the Oracle warns Oedipus's dad, but I think, I think at some point he
has to answer a Sphinx's riddle.
I'm like 75% sure that happened.
I think it's, I think it's referenced in the story that he does that.
It's like a previous adventure, right?
Previous adventures.
Yeah.
World building.
A lot of world building, you know, it's like, it's like in, um, Star Wars, uh, new hope
when, uh, Princess Leia said that you help my father in the Clone Wars and you're
wondering, whoa, where are the Clone Wars, right?
Um, that was Ben Kenobi that said that.
He says we fought in the Clone Wars and Lucas, you fought in the Clone Wars and then
Solid Snake, and then Solid Snake goes Clone Wars.
Uh, what's that?
Man, Star Wars sucks.
It's garbage.
I, I agree.
I'm not a fan.
It's overdone.
It's overrated.
There I said it.
Sucks.
Except for episode eight.
How would you say something so controversial and yet so?
I'm going to say it.
I'm not scared to say it.
I'm not going to, I'm not scared to say it.
Star Wars kind of lame.
You're kind of a big nerd.
I wish I had your courage, cheesy to call out the Star Wars to call out Star Wars.
I have a biggest media property in the universe.
If you say that, they're going to come down on you.
I'm going to say this, the fist of an angry guy.
Villainverse is better than Star, Villainverse is like, if Star Wars was good, I'll
tell you that much.
I would, I would say it.
I would say it.
If the corporate, if the corporate oligarchy didn't have their thumb on my, on my.
Yeah, I can't afford to speak the truth like you.
I'm not free.
Villainverse is more nuanced than a Star Wars and Star Wars is like, what?
Oh, I'm, oh, I joined the dark side.
I'm a bad person.
Oh, I joined the light side.
I'm a good person.
I got like, oh, okay.
All right.
Very child, very straightforward, very simple for man, children, you know,
Villainverse, it's like, Villainverse, like looks you right in the face and says,
like, bro, like capitalism, kind of bad, kind of not good.
It causes a lot of villains, causes a lot of villains, if you will, which, which panel
is that the ending, the ending of Villainverse, the villains just grabs you by
the scruff of your fucking shirt and grabs you the viewer and
speaks through the fourth wall.
It says, I am a metaphor for capitalism.
I invented capital.
That's what the villain says.
He invented all that as E1.
Then he says capitalism.
He also says he invented Star Wars too.
But that's, that's, that's, that's, this is Joey.
That's just, that's just a little, that's just something for the fans.
Cool.
Um, God.
Shit.
All right.
Do you want to go?
Do you want to start voicemails?
Yeah, let's go to voicemails.
Let's, let's, I will, we're going to blast through them because I fucking hate
all these people.
I hate, I hate their, their, I hate their solo.
Oh, I'm so funny.
Oh, I'm so clever.
I made a voicemail.
I used a voice modulator.
I played the piano.
Um, all right.
Here we go.
First voicemail is called.
Giga fa de fa three, three, two, one go.
Why though, why though, why though, okay, next one, why though, next one is called here we go.
It's called Mike Hunt.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, Ben, finally looked at that Kato collection thing you've been chilling for the last 20
to 30 years, saw the cover you drew, gotta say, boy, that shit ass piece.
I don't, is he saying the cover is shit ass?
I, I, is he saying the cover is not bad, it's like it's a bad cover.
Hey, man, I'm sorry.
I'm, I'm, hey, can you, can you offer any more specific, can you offer any more specific
criticism?
You're just jealous.
You're just jealous that you didn't get to draw the cover.
That's what I think.
Uh, okay, whatever.
Next one, huh, what?
You guys want to say, you guys want to say?
I don't care, Ben says, I don't care about the cover.
I ain't reading that shit.
Next voicemail is called drive through Joe.
Three, two, one, go.
Absolutely.
Right away, sir.
Okay, I get it.
Next one is called, uh, wait, what did something happen?
He just started screaming.
Nice.
I'm glad I stopped listening.
Next one is called message for Gib and the gang.
Three, two, one, go.
Fuck you.
Ben no, Saint, Tom, Oliver currently makes $400 plus a
Patreon.
Okay.
And Saint is not.
That just, yeah, that, I mean, that's proof that Tom is better
than Ben.
That's, that's true.
I mean, that's true.
I know he's better.
He's better looking.
He has a bigger cock.
You know, it's taller.
It's like that old, it's like that old, uh, it's that old, uh, Mr.
Schoes get more money equals better than it.
Yeah, I never thought about it.
I never thought about how true it was, but the average Ben
Saint fan and the average Tom, Tommy Oliver, enjoyer, you
know, Oliver, Oliver, enjoyer has the average Tommy Oliver,
enjoyer has about 25% more money to give to, you know,
creators that they value, um, and good for them.
Yeah, that Ben is advocates too much for lower income people.
So those lower income people only get a little bit of money.
It puts off the, it puts off the high rollers.
Right.
Exactly.
Um, next one is called sad, but surprisingly, no, sorry.
Next one is called smashly three, two, one go.
So in the last episode, you guys were talking about the image you
used for the podcast of the graveyard.
Um, you guys realize that's like a military cemetery, right?
That's why all the two stones are the same.
So basically you guys have been like desecrating soldiers, graves,
pigs coming out of cars for like several months now.
And honestly, that's pretty big military, the American
imperialist machine.
Um, absolutely.
I know, I know, you, I know people are going to be like, Oh,
my brother was in the, oh, my dad's like, they're an idiot.
They're fucking idiot.
I said they're idiot.
Brother is a victim of a, of a system that made them fucking
throw their life on their fucking chopping block.
They got exploited.
American oil dolly.
They did, they did.
They should feel bad about it.
They shouldn't be proud.
I don't, I'm sorry.
Like there's no honor in being exploited, you know, sorry.
I don't, I agree.
The hard truth.
I agree.
Right.
Good voicemail.
Finally, I like, I like that one.
Uh, okay.
Next one is called, um, wait, sorry.
We got, do the, do the one that's numbered three, three, two, eight, three.
Uh, next one is called a sad, but surprisingly enticing boy.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, I designated your Kato anthology cover to be
asked a couple of days ago.
That's right.
I had some time to think about my words and I wanted to apologize.
That cover was a mess.
That assessment was way to harsh of me and that stepped out.
Agreed.
Sorry.
We all make, that shit, but though we all make
mistakes.
Well, we all make mistakes.
It's cool.
Did he say that shit fucks though?
Is that what he said?
I think, I think it's, he said it's shit, but yeah, that, that shit, but that shit,
but so, you know, motion in the right direction.
All right.
Okay.
Next one is, next one is called wholesome w or L in disguise.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm really baffled on Twitter right now and I want to know what you guys think.
You know, when someone can't afford their medical expenses and their family has to
like sell possessions or open it, go fund me in order to pay for it.
Sure.
I'm like, wow, that's fucked.
It's a failing of the system and it's a tragedy that it would be put in that
scenario.
That's right.
So from dudes posting their w is a situation that is exactly identical,
except it was a kid got a bunch of donations after selling his Pokemon cards in
order to pay for his dog's medical treatment.
This is not to say that dogs should be under like the healthcare system, but
the point is that regardless, it's a situation that is still fucked in all
the same ways, yet everyone on Twitter is treating it like it's a wholesome W.
Like what do you really think it's a W for this kid that the only thing keeping
his dog from fucking death is the sale of his Pokemon cards?
No, you're insane.
Yeah.
Why do you feel about the count of men posting their W's?
I mean, most of the time when I see it, it does seem pretty wholesome.
Mm hmm.
I don't know if I think I think I've seen that one that he's talking about.
I get it.
I like, they seem pretty like I, it's interesting to see like the contrast
between like men posting their W and women posting their W.
Like the majority of women posting their W is like, oh, I graduated.
Oh, I got a doctorate.
Oh, like my journal got to play.
I got a job or whatever.
Yeah, I used to be a felon, but now I got a, I'm a lawyer.
Yeah.
It's all like very kind of like education, like these big achievements.
But like men posting a W is kind of like, oh, I just kept kicking this little
rock and I was just having fun with it.
And it's, and I think that says a lot about society.
It's a lot of like, it's the ones that I see are usually like, like a good
Samaritan man, like help someone out or, um, I mean, I don't know.
I'm a little torn on this one because like, yeah, I don't know if I think
that like animals should be covered by universal health care.
And if we had, I don't know about that.
So it is, it's kind of nice.
I mean, it's nice.
It's pretty heartwarming to think that a kid like sold it.
Do kids even collect Pokemon cards anymore?
I mean, I mean, it's like, I think it's one of the fucking Paul brothers
made Pokemon cards popular again.
I see, you heard the story about like all these people now buying a shit load
of them, right?
Oh, oh, yeah.
I thought that was magic.
I thought like people were like fucking lining up and like storming stores
for like the new magic set or whatever.
Is it Pokemon too?
Yeah, it's, it's, it's Pokemon.
Like people are buying like Pokemon.
Yeah, like I think now one of the, one of the polls, like on their podcast,
they like do a lot of Pokemon unboxing videos, Pokemon card unboxing videos.
Right.
I mean, it makes sense.
Like I like was a kid when Pokemon first came out.
Right.
So, you know, weren't we all bringing it back?
Huh, not me.
I'm not a nerd.
Nevermind.
I grew up on how old, how old are the Pauls?
Are they like 30?
They're like 20, I think they're around my age, maybe like 25 or wait.
So, so if he was a kid when it came out, then you would have been a kid
when it came out because the generation that came out with the
generation I remember as a kid when in elementary school, it was a Ruby version.
Like that was the, that was, yeah, it was, um, yeah, it was home in that region.
Right.
And then a Diamond and Pearl.
Those were like the big two I remember.
So, so yeah, it was a, you were a kid.
Okay.
I got you.
Um, well, I don't know.
I think it's pretty sweet that a kid sells his Pokemon cards to save his dog.
I think, I think that is heartwarming.
No, I think I'm going to go with it is a W.
I think it's, um, I have this weird, like, if I can like analyze both like
accounts of like, when posting their W and men posting their W's.
Wait, wait, before you, before you do that, before you do that, I just, okay.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, I, I guess I do, I guess I do have to agree that the kid,
the kid's dog probably should have had been able to get that fucking dog
surgery without selling his Pokemon.
I don't know.
Yeah, I, I see what you mean.
It's kind of, it is kind of sad that like, if the story hadn't gone viral or
whatever, if someone hadn't picked up the, then like, oh my God, this kid
selling his Pokemon cards to save his dog.
That's so sweet.
Let's donate.
Like if that hadn't happened, then the dog dies.
Right.
The kid sells his Pokemon cards.
He still can't afford it.
The dog dies.
I mean, yeah, he's fucking terrible.
So I guess it's like, what do you choose your Pokemon cards or your dog
living, right?
Well, it's really sweet that the kid would choose his dog.
Right.
Exactly.
I mean, probably a lot of kids would, but it's nice.
I mean, it sucks that like the surgery costs.
I mean, just like, well, pets are like a luxury, right?
And so of course it's going to be fucking expensive, you know?
Yeah, a little bit.
I don't know.
Vashh hasn't made a video about pet health care, so I have no opinion.
Yeah, it's true.
Yeah.
So we got to move on.
We got to move on.
We're not, we're not qualified to speak on it yet.
Okay.
But what were you saying about the two accounts?
Like, I think it's kind of interesting about like, you know, about, um, obviously
patriarchy, blah, blah, blah, whatever.
But, um, like the, what, what is like the standard for, for men having a W and
what's like the standards for like a woman, right?
Or like, I don't think this is on purpose.
It just might be some sort of subconscious shit where it's like, for a woman,
it's like, they have to have a degree.
They have to have a high paying job.
Like that's like the W standard for women, like a tire.
And for men, it's kind of like, bro, I just found a sick ass stick and
I'm just hitting stuff with it.
Right.
Yeah.
I haven't seen, I haven't seen any men Ws that are just like, lol, I found a cool
rock that looks like Abraham Lincoln or like some, I haven't seen any like goofy.
I'm sure there are some.
I, I swear, I swear, there was like one where, um, oh great.
There's like a shitload of like men posting their Ws accounts.
Huh.
I'm looking for the one, I think, well, there's, but there's the one, but
there's the one big one.
Yeah.
The, the, the one with, with Leonardo DiCaprio, right?
Is the icon.
Yeah.
I'm like looking for it, but I'm seeing like ones about like ones where it's
like men posting their W, but they have like the Swedish gamer.
Um, Swedish gamer.
Well, the guy, the guy was like, no, the guy who says yes.
Oh, the guy was like, gamer.
The, I, I've never heard him called that before.
Isn't, isn't that what that meme is called?
Or what the guy was just saying?
Yes.
And he has like the Chad look.
Yeah.
You know, I don't know what is, I, I, if you'd asked me, like what is he called?
I don't know what he's called.
Maybe he's called Swedish gamer.
I would call him, I would call him Nordic.
Oh, wait, it might be Nordic gamer actually.
Hold up.
He's not, he's not always a gamer though.
No, but I think the original, sometimes he's just a head.
I think the original version was like supposed to be a gamer.
Yes.
Chad, also known as Nordic gamer.
Yeah.
He's when I, I mean, when I think Chad, I think, you know, tiny beetle like
stride arms perpetually in contra posto.
Well, I cannot out shirt.
I cannot find the fucking.
How can you not find the men posting their W's?
It's so weird.
What the fuck?
I can't find it.
It's called, it's called dudes posting double.
I found it.
Oh, it called dudes.
Yeah.
I found it right away from a Google.
It's called dudes posting W's.
Ironically funny and wholesome DMs open for submissions.
Dudes post.
Oh, okay.
I found dudes posting their W twos.
I mean, I see the guy who called an Uber for a, an injured bird, um, uh, a biotech
startup has 3D prints, faked rhino horns, poached rhinos.
I'm going to do my own, um, I'm going to make my own fat guy who lost a bunch of
weight, I'm going to do my own like, uh, dudes posting their W's account, but
every post it just so happens to be like about someone making a comic.
That's just constantly, that's the only W I acknowledge.
And I'm sort of just looking at all these W's too many, a lot of like, a lot of
like fitness and like health related W's, uh, things in things that people
invented, you know, heartwarming moments of like personal, you know, with, with
helped a kid do something.
What do you, what do you think about like wholesome, like wholesome accounts?
I always feel weirdly suspicious about anyone who like parades as like a wholesome
type, you know.
Well, I mean, I mean, the guy who runs the like women posting their L that guy,
um, it's not blackpilled.com.
It's, uh, he's like, uh, what's that guy's fucking name?
I, I, I can't remember, but I know he has like some sort of podcast where he's
like a huge misogynist.
He has like a Duke Nukem avatar or something.
It redux something redux, doesn't he?
Doesn't he kill a redux?
Doesn't he also run the bad movies, opinion account or like bad film takes?
He, he runs a bunch, he runs a bunch of account of like gimmick accounts.
And he sucks.
He sucks really bad.
And sometimes his, and sometimes his L's are just like, I was raped.
Like sometimes that's, like, oh my God, yeah, exactly.
It's so fucking, I remember back when he, when he was running like bad film
takes, like just any, like, any, like film take where someone shits on the
Star Wars prequels, he would consider bad by the fault.
And everyone just kept pointing it out.
So cool.
I just kept saying like, well, like the, yeah, the peaks, the prequels aren't
that good, bro.
And like, why the fuck are you constantly defending them?
And, and he would just quote, he would just like screenshot the tweet and just
post it as the bad take.
Oh my God.
Okay.
I saw, I saw an account.
Uh, whatever.
What?
Yeah.
The, the, the wholesome ones, the W's accounts, they generally seem okay.
Like I haven't seen very many W's that are like, ooh, that's kind of
problematic that you could really, you're calling that a W.
I think the W's accounts are fine.
Whoa.
I mean, I'm not going to fall.
I don't care that.
Whoa.
Father, make sure his children are all of lighter skin.
W, bro.
Whoa.
Father, father, father, uh, uh, convinces his, his trans daughter to be a boy again.
I'm good job.
To de-transition.
Whoa.
This doctor convinces teenagers to de-transition.
Um, based.
Whoa.
Epic.
Based.
Next, next voicemail is called, um, what is this called?
Based Ben, based Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
Based Ben, Homestuck was at its best in the early parts and it peaked in act four.
Uh, I agree.
Yes.
Yeah.
You haven't read Homestuck, have you?
No, I've not, but, um, but I'm going to, I'm just going to say my hate it.
Okay.
Homestuck got, Homestuck got really popular with the addition of the trolls,
which was in like act, it's kind of started, I think in act three, but they got
more and more prominence through acts like four and five.
What's, uh, what's your take on the trolls?
Do you like the trolls?
They're, they're, I don't dislike them.
They're fine, but I mean, I, I think they're good even.
I like the part, I like act five.
I think act five is good.
It was just, um, my favorite part of Homestuck is the early part, which doesn't,
which it's not good because it doesn't have trolls.
It's not like the trolls are ruined it by being there.
It's just my favorite part is the early part, which doesn't have any trolls.
And it's very focused on this very like goofy, very problem, sleuthy kind of
like just sort of winging it, like coming up with weird shit and like giving it
weird, funny names, and then like just kind of making up rules as you go along.
And then like really, really rigidly adhering to those rules, even when it
doesn't make any sense, uh, which the story becomes more of a, the story becomes
more of a traditional narrative as it goes along in lockstep with like the
trolls becoming more and more prominent.
And I think, you know, I think that has more mass appeal.
Right.
So it makes sense.
But that's, that's not what hooked me about it though.
Did you have them?
Yeah.
This guy's base.
You guys, you guys, you guys talked about the cycloneos, Anthony, right?
We, oh, I don't think we.
Cause I, I think we said we were going to do a, a cast about it and I
haven't reread it yet.
Oh, damn.
Cause I, I, I read, I read all of it.
Yeah.
And I, I don't think.
Yeah, you've read it.
Yeah.
We can, we can talk about it here a little bit.
Oh yeah.
Well, so how, how do you feel?
Spoilers.
Spoilers for cycloneos.
How do I feel?
Um, you know what?
I don't, I don't want to go too deep into it because I do want to record
that cast with Gibb.
I think all I'll say is that like about the ending.
Yeah.
It, go on.
I, it's Fight Club.
The, what?
Cycloneos is Fight Club.
They're literally almost the same story.
Um, okay.
Let me explain.
So I see what you mean.
Right.
So there's like in Fight Club, both are about main characters who, um,
who like created an alter ego and they create like a movement and it becomes
like kind of massive, like huge, almost like out of their hands, right?
And then like at the end, he has to like have a confrontation with his
alter ego and then he kind of realized that that's like what he really
wanted was like, like a human connection, like a relationship, right?
And that's kind of like what cycloneos is.
Like, like, if you read like kind of like the little epilogue thing with
the note in the bottle, it's like, she says, like, loves, like loves the
answer, right?
And, and I thought, yeah, I guess that's okay.
But I thought it was okay to me, like, I guess as a resolution, that's fine.
To me, the story was not like about finding love.
So like the fact that it ends in that way is a little like, okay, I guess.
Whatever.
I guess, I mean, it could be like, you probably make the argument
that's like, oh, influencers and like, what do they need?
Like what, like maybe this void that she was filling with me and an
influencer could have been just filled with like loving someone.
Hold on.
She wasn't, I'm going to, I disagree.
She doesn't, she doesn't fill the void by becoming an influencer.
She fills the void by becoming like a fucking warlord.
Yeah.
Do you, I mean, do you, do you think they're basically one in the
same in, in the, in the story of cycloneos?
I mean, I'm not, I'm not like surprised.
Like that's, that's like what Andrew Hussie is trying to like tell us.
Right.
Yeah.
I think in retrospect, I think I probably overhyped myself too much
with like the socialist angle because it doesn't really go into.
Honestly, the conclusion is very like, oh, you know, everything's
kind of inevitable.
You know, anything ideological is just kind of like the fact
that the fact, the fact that the clown revolution, this is very
spoiler, the fact that the clown revolution is left wing is like
very incidental and ends up kind of not mattering at all.
Like it's just a, it's just a thing.
Yeah.
It's just an aesthetic, which I guess is kind of the point because
like, oh, this is actually a like alien mind plot, which, okay,
makes sense.
But yeah, I guess it's a little disappointing that like the movement
itself and what it stands for is not really important.
Not what the story is about.
It kind of doesn't even have an opinion about it.
Right.
Like really, like it's really more about like.
Human connection.
And I mean, that's fine.
But you know, like, like, I don't know.
Like I was thinking about this and I was saying like, I love
rewatching Fight Club.
I think rewatching Fight Club is pretty great.
I don't know if I like want to like, maybe I'll reread
Cycloneos eventually again.
But it's I am going to reread it.
I think it, I don't know.
I think there's a chance that I might like it less on my second read.
I, but I think there's also a chance I might like it more.
I genuinely don't know what I'm how I'm going to feel about it.
Because I know that you I you made the same.
You chose the same thing I did at the ending, which is the crown.
Right.
Because because to me, that's way more interesting.
Yeah, absolutely.
She chose to me.
Yeah.
It's more.
Here's my calculus.
It's more interesting.
I would say that there's a this is so spoilery.
Whatever, I'll fuck it.
I will elaborate more on this in the eventual in the
eventual Cycloneos cast, but the the choice at the end
between sword or crown, it's like there's a calculus because
this being is telling you like what is to be one if you if
you take the crown and what she's offering is like huge what
she's she's basically offering you like pseudo immortality
and like cosmic power and it's like if she if that's true,
then like obviously you should take the crown like anything
else you could get by refusing the crown is not as good.
But there's a chance that this is just a delusion that you're
having and none of this is real in which case if you take
the crown, you're basically just going to die for no reason
and you there's nothing to be gained in which case like don't.
So yeah, in the end, I'm like, well, is this a delusion or
is this real?
I don't know.
But yeah, it's a more interesting story if I just go for it.
And so I'm going to go for it.
I think I think a part of me was like because like when I was
reading the last chapter, a part of me was like didn't want
to accept that because I had a I had a rousing suspicion that
like the final message was going to be all you needed.
All you need is love and that's so dull.
That's so like it's not it's not it's not super exciting.
Like yeah, like I don't like it's like and then it kind of
makes me rethink about like Andrew Hussey and it's kind of
like, yeah, this guy is like a rich white guy like it's like
I mean a rich fucking white guy who wrote this like all you
need is like fucking like come on.
It's so it's so frustrating.
I started I see what you mean.
I see what you I mean.
I feel like it's it's sad because I feel like Hussey is genuine
in his politics.
He is like a he is like a Bernie bro.
I think he is like left-wing and anti-capitalist in his
personal life, but that's not really that's that's only here
in psycholonials like aesthetically right and it's not
really a theme.
I've been very kind of like we're realizing a couple of
things about like I've been thinking a lot like works of
media like did you did you hear recently about like the the
Bo Burnham like special and there's like a clip.
Sure.
Yeah, there's a clip that going around where like this like
sock puppet the sock.
Yeah, I like mentioned the problems capitalism and people
were calling that radical when it's not it's not radical like
the thing is like here's the thing.
I haven't I haven't seen the special special is good.
I like the contact special is pretty good.
I like the special but that being said it's not radical like
it's not radical to say capitalism is bad.
That's not radical at all.
What's radical is like what do you do about capitalism?
That's radical, right?
And I think yeah and there's like only a handful of works
that I feel like are very explicit of what to do about
like capitalism and I think the first one that comes to mind
is like the movie sorry to bother you.
That one's like very explicit of like what do you do about
capitalism, right?
Is that the one with the white voice?
Yes, you got to watch that Ben.
I think you haven't I haven't I know that one but I haven't
seen it.
It's really it's really good but and and then it got me
thinking about how I like like I love One Piece.
I think One Piece has like moments that feel very like left
but there's like other moments that feel very like like the
fact that like it a lot of the arts kind of end with like
reinstating a monarchy, right?
Which is pretty which is pretty unbased I'll I'll say it's
pretty fucking pretty unbased pretty unbased and in my
head I see it so easily like the fucking social is shown in
it's so visible in my head right like it's easy like it's
like it's like you it's like you take like the One Piece
formula of him going around helping like disenfranchise
people on different island and then he unifies the people
right like like on paper what Luffy is doing and at times in
the narrative it does seem pretty like radical but then what
they actually yeah what they actually do a lot of the time
is they they fight they fight a terrorist and they reinstate
the monarchy.
Right exactly it's totally do yeah it's like a lot of
reinstating monarchies and I guess it goes back to like
because probably in Luffy's head it's all like oh yeah I want
to be the pirate king and here I am helping other kings am I
right and it's so I mean it's so annoying yeah it's it started
making me reflect on my he's got class solidarity Luffy's got
class solidarity with like the Shichi Bukai and stuff like
really they have the same because they're all on the same way
but that's you know it's just like it's just like Tim Rogers
and and Vito Giswaldi and fucking Mr. Bob's game or whatever
they're all they're all the elites they all control our
lives they're all in a big club and you and I aren't invited
right exactly fucking Grimes isn't a fucking communist she's
fucking she's rich.
Yes, you're right like she's an example of course she's going
to fucking date someone like Elon Musk actually communists
should like my billionaire boyfriend owning everything
because he's going to make a spaceship one day it's so fucking
frustrating God it's like it's making me reflect a lot on my
work like I'm gonna say this right now that I mean like
all villain versus like capitalism bad right and like
I'm not gonna say that like villain versus radical at all
it's not it's not like radical but I think from now on I'm
gonna try to like make sure my works are a little bit more
radical right cuz I'm just so tired I'm so tired of like
stories that are very like all you need is love or like like
or humans are stupid right or it's it's kind of like I'm so
tired of stories where it's like humans are these aren't these
aren't radical messages yeah it's not like I know humans are
stupid I live with humans all my fucking life I know they're
fucking stupid I want a story that's like yeah humans are
stupid but like you know we got to still do good despite of
it you know we got to like like change it so it's so
frustrating you know and I guess I got fucking tricked I got
tricked by because Hussey was like oh here's clowns and
communism and I'm like oh base but no it wasn't base it was
actually cringe anyway it's like a 7 out of 10 I can't really
disagree with you I'm gonna I'm gonna do a reread I'm gonna do
reread but I agree it's too aesthetic I mean not I mean not
not not every story has to be no of course message message
laden some times a story can just be about a bunch of really
powerful guys fighting each other right like like that's fine
like that's fine too yeah don't get me wrong it's just I'm
tired of being kind of like like tease you know I'm tired of
like um no I hear I hear you I'm tired of getting like like
fucking I'm getting edged all the time everyone's fucking
edging me all like give like give me a theme like the theme of
psychologials is definitely not you know it's definitely not
that like the workers should own the fruits of their
production productive labor right like that's not what the
story is saying it feels almost like maybe just ideology is
inherently destructive or something which I think is a very
like yeah brain dead fucking take on it because everything
is ideology yeah you're at yeah it's very much like like I
said this before in the end it doesn't matter what the movement
was about the movement was doomed to be co-opted by you
know the the power hungry right it was going to take the same
form no matter what happened it's so which I mean maybe
maybe that's true but it's not radical yeah yeah it's not
right it's not radical right I mean yeah okay not every piece
of work has to be radical but like I like I like stories like
devil man I think they'll man is like pretty good because I
think it's I haven't read it it's pretty it's pretty short
actually like the man goes not too long I would recommend
just like watching devil man cry baby but anyway here's here's
devil man here's devil man if I wrote it this this would be
me yeah hell yeah there's devil there's devil man if I had
read it right there's devil man once you read the man's gonna
make more sense you're gonna be like oh it was capitalism
the real enemy was it actually capitalism no it was it was
God it was God and the inherent like the ultimate theme and
like devil man it's kind of like human fear is like
incredibly destructive right sure right make sense and then
there's like a there's like a little moment in devil man
where it's kind of like I'm gonna unify all the devil people
together and I'm like oh yeah base awesome right but that's
like only like towards a little bit towards the end and then
it kind of it has like a spoiler is like a sad ending I guess
you know a good story anyway 10 out of 10 10 out of 10 all
right let's let's move right along all right cool we've we've
got another voicemail here this one that I posted before it is
called what is it called a glimpse into the future bends
ascension three two one go the year is 20 xx Boston has become
a massive super city now known as megachucin space neo
American England a true capitalist hellhole this is where
our story begins in the slums a small apartment with Ben
Saint hard at work on his keto gummies it was upon a certain
day there in a Thursday that Ben Saint perfected his keto
gummy recipe Saint consumed the first of the batch but he would
find no need to consume another as the slime shaped gummy dissolved
into Ben's gut all of his chakra gate flung open and he entered
a state which many only theorized of 13th level ketosis
rapidly releasing energy Saint's apartment and much of the
city block was consumed in a blaze Ben nowhere to be seen
the naysayers assumed he was dead but soon signs would be
found that Ben had not perished in the fire but ascended no
longer Ben Saint but Ben God this is the future before you even
now the hands of fate move ever closer to the eventuality this
the really based future I gotta I guess I better get back to
making the gummies again because my substitute for the
isomalt oligosaccharides the Alulose it just isn't very good
I haven't had good results with that it's been very discouraged
very discouraged and can't you not buy this isn't that the
replacement for like another ingredient that you like ran out
over something
no it was it was the isomalt oligosaccharides where the
powder that I can't get from China anymore Alulose is like
another it's like another sweetening powder that I saw the
the the product that inspired me the sweet smart this sorry
the smart sweets that inspired me to try making them they
changed their recipe they still taste all right they switched
from isomalt oligosaccharide to Alulose I was like well I guess
I'll try Alulose and it's not good you're not it's just taste
weird I like not like mixing it right and the proper ingredient
you're not you're not turning the knob correctly maybe
I may have like cooked it too much and given it's sort of
like a burnt flavor in like trying to cook it down and
like dehydrate it to make it chewy because it's like has
like a sort of caramely flavor that I didn't that sounds good
when I say like that but it's not good it's it's not good
anyway it's true it's all true next voicemail is called a
fuck been saints that mp3 3 I said what I was thinking
321 go
been saying you're also a fake compared to give and take
you take the cake so there's 102 we're all feeling blue
Christine Weston Chandler's way more reliable than you
all we want is content you think your game is God sent your
cheese or garbage in your GML is nonsense don't so we're more
simple a few cent charted course to a world without horses or
anime been you're as lame as any fantasy sleep will ever be
the same I'm not a loser now and Riley is his name I'm a bird
now and his meat keeps me sane I like steak served and we
don't pay for plates the college fund is depleted so please
remind me I'm busting more rhymes in your ears can't believe
it darling house you're made the darlings house but our future
has no ceilings because we don't have a house should have
foretold why gg studios all we make is gold the same channel
Riley said if we change it up and stay with scramble abandoned
everything that I work for over the last decade of my life so
much time
but don't burn out right away.
This has been a YGG production.
Was that do it was that do it.
Gazer that do it.
Gazer again.
I think that was do it.
Gazer are you sure that I thought that was Trixie that sounded
like her.
Yeah Trixie of the famously of the of the do it.
I that's man of the college funds depleted now that's a no it
can't be do it.
Gazer there's no way that some Kiwi farmer would know about
the college fund and the college fund possible that's that's
even before my time.
This guy is a hello.
Yo who's that.
Oh my God someone just snuck in it is I zero are you recording
the fuck are you are you recording.
Yes I'm crashing the PCP.
Oh my God I knew this would happen remind me this would happen
eventually remind me who zero is again.
I'm from Kata.
Oh that's why we were just talking shit about you really here.
That's right.
Yeah I should have crashed the podcast.
Yeah we have a rivalry now you and I we are we're rivals in
the sense.
Are you hot hot blooded rivals.
Yeah yeah yeah we established earlier.
Yeah I was talking mad garbage about Kato and I told people
don't read the Kato anthology read my comic villain verse far
superior now there's two teams team villain team Kato right.
Oh my goodness yeah yeah that's the only way I recommend you
also read it had to be it had to be this way I recommend you
also read villain verse so you know your enemy you know.
Right of course you want to know who you're dealing with.
The one way to settle this right of course you just everyone
has to read both and come to their own conclusion.
Okay yeah okay read both which one read Kato.
Yeah look all I got to say is that Kato needs like how many
people are in the anthology we have 10 come okay Kato needs
like 10 people to make one comic villain verse just one guy
and there's five chapters and a prologue for her numbers don't
lie numbers don't lie I'm just saying you're I'm saying
there's going to be a lot more villain verse they need to be
catching up on then Kato.
I don't want to forget about Kato to try to do everything by
yourself wait wait I'm sorry man I turn to you I'm sorry
what you say hoodie and I believe in the power of friendship
we don't try to do everything by ourselves and that's why we
will defeat a villain like you.
Yeah okay she's a young man for someone you're taught you
talked really you talked really big about about wanting socialism
but I mean you know you seem like you're the sole owner of
the means of your own production.
That's just a little much.
No I swear I can't I ever do anything on YouTube without
being called a fascist it's it's happening it's happening
just just embrace it be the PCB has to go back to its far
right roots got to go back to being all right okay I'll say
I'll say the word I'll say it right.
Oh God I miss it I miss I miss those days I was going to say
the word the forbidden word.
Oh well you wouldn't be the first one yeah then then what's
the name of the guy who's making the list he's going to have
to add me into the end word spiral spiral spiral that means
going to be one for cheesy.
This late in the game so zero what's a challenger arrived.
Oh I just finished my book club.
Finish your book club what happened in the book and you just
thought you'd come waltzing in here.
Yeah just come sauntering on in like you own the damn place.
Yeah I figured it'd be a good opportunity to come say hello.
Hey what's up.
What's up.
I would do what's got what's poppin was poppin you know it
was all chill until I realized y'all were talking shit.
Do you want to listen to the next voicemail with us.
Yeah since you're here anyway.
Okay well the next voicemail I'm putting it there in the
general is called can Nate grow a real beard.
Okay three two one go.
So I'm watching the Brad lecture.
Did did any of you bang the Gina statue or not card cut out.
Two very different questions.
What happened to that cut out.
What happens at Radcon stays at Radcon.
Next voicemail is called.
Fuck where is it.
Oh God yeah yeah Trixie Trixie.
Yeah Trixie left her gender at Radcon.
Left it in Gino's beat hole.
Yeah yeah gross.
Yeah yeah and given both given Trixie that's where they left
their gender at Radcon.
That's for just like I just like I left part of my tooth at
RFC Kcon.
Shoutouts shoutouts shoutouts to RFC Kcon boys.
Next one is called gushing three two one go.
Hey PCP monotone bitch here.
A couple weeks ago I called and I like pee pee poo poo.
I don't understand why you want to draw comics.
I just like illustrations because I'm a lazy loser terrible
and I actually read you all sorry and holy shit because
they're so cool.
Then aside from the insanely strong character writing my
favorite part of the Vapors is how you play with lighting
and the lack thereof.
Wow that page in the first chapter where Vincent is walking
at the games club and it's all dark and everything made me
kill myself because it was so good.
Yeah Lord of ghosts and give you have all these sick panel
layouts like when the flower head slices the blood worm in
half and I'm just like whoa whoa that's so cool.
Anyway I finished that and now I have two comic pages sketched
out and I'm going to do another one after work.
So thank you guys for being so inspiring I guess fucking hell
yeah.
More voicemails like this where you just gush about how cool
our stuff is.
Got another one.
Yeah I got I just I just happened to be a little bit
looking at I had Saint comics open the other day and I just
happened to be open to I think the exact page you're talking
about where he's walking down the path and like the lanterns
are on and he sort of has this little shadow is coming off
of his feet and he'd like the silhouette of the of the buildings
in the background I think I know the exact panel this guy's
talking about I thought he was going to say the one where
Vincent comes through the door and he's sort of like shadowed
in the front with the the the the the what's the word for the
little dots that you put on a comic the screen tone though
he's got the screen tone shading on but no no the inky the
inky blackness of that night with the bubbling lights of the
of the lanterns the the the the light the light posts yes
thank you guys.
The villain versus pretty cool that guy hey that guy gig a gig
a chat or whatever his name is got some Kirby crackle coming
out of his head I mean that's oh yeah I'm a fucking I'm a
fucking sucker I'm a simp for the Kirby crackle I'm a big Kirby
simp I I I feel it I feel it oh wait Kirby deserves simps
I think he deserves simps yeah more than stand there I said
it was wait wait I'm him saying that he now is working on
a comic just made me realize something you guys know about
the Eisner's yeah yeah I saw Casey I saw Casey Noak tweeting
about the Eisner's and saying that they suck the other oh they
do but I still want one anyway sure and I think I know how
so apparently like this year that they're like doing these
forms where if you're just working if you just work in the
comic book industry you just fill it out and then they'll
send you like some sort of like email where like you get to
vote on who wins but and then and and the thing is that it's
just like an open link like anyone could get the link and I
applied for it because I like technically self published
something right and I'm seeing I'm seeing if maybe if that
allows me to be able to vote which makes me think like
maybe I could rig the Eisner's or like one of my things to
that's what I'm hoping because like it may be because what's
like exact like this because it's like what what what are the
qualifications do I have to have worked in the big two or just
like those indie stuff count if I indie and like relevant enough
that's fine because there's like so many people who don't work
or Marvel and DC who who are like mostly indie guys and
they're getting like Eisner's even people who do like web
comics you know like they get Eisner's too so it's like you
have to just like make a comic to get an Eisner so I'm thinking
because I'm pretty soon in the next couple of months I'm
doing this one podcast with like my other with other like
friends who also make comics and we're going to really push
like our audience to make comics and I'm thinking like if I
get enough of my audience to have published a comic in a way
maybe I could get them to sign up to do Eisner voting and then
like rig it so I win.
That's my and if you can swing it. Yeah, that's swing it.
What do you say?
She said Casey Noak said God the Eisner's are stupid congrats
to the four or five people who deserve it and dumb grats to
Craig Thompson and the rest of the mediocre dipshits.
I don't know who Craig Thompson that sounds very aggressive
is your is your your comics Gator.
Oh, I know what you're talking about.
I have no clue.
Craig Thompson's graphic novelist best.
Oh, I've heard of some of these ways.
Is he like a groomer or something?
I couldn't tell you because like every other like graphic
novel motherfucker turns out to be like some sort of groomer
creep.
Just he made he made blankets.
I think I've heard of blankets blankets covers familiar.
I think I've seen it in stores.
Wait, I think I own.
No, wait, Trixie loaned me that book.
I think but I never read it.
Damn thing unless I'm confused.
I don't know.
I think you should read more Daniel Klaus.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Next voicemail is called next voicemail is called
um it's called.
Yeah.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
So I'm probably like the fucking millionth person to say this
exact same shit.
Yes.
But you know, I go away for a while and I come back.
Oh, everybody's different.
I know the pony.
You see these different show up and there's no fucking pony
lecture and Trixie just had to go in like she's life is
change and fuck it all life is change.
What the fuck I agree and and for what so she can go live in
a fucking hovel a bunch of fucking drug-addled fucking
losers.
I agree.
Fuck this.
Fuck it all.
I you know one good thing though I can the one good thing
to come out of this you know based God been saying continues
to be right about everything.
Thanks, Ben.
Uh, thank you.
Donate to patreon.com slash been saying.
Yeah, you said it.
They said it.
He said he said the line.
He said it more voicemails like this.
Please voice grail voice grail voice grail.
Hmm.
No, I don't know.
I don't got a fucking vote in that.
No, I'm just I'm just I could I could if I wanted to just
voice grail this person on my own, but I would feel wrong.
I'm just I would feel wrong.
I'm just fan favorite reoccurring guest cheesy Manfredo.
I have no say in the grail or not.
True.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called grill ish three two one go.
Then why don't you like the dick show?
Give what are your thoughts?
Why don't I like the dick show?
Well, I don't.
Go on.
He's annoying.
He is annoying.
He's yeah, he's annoying.
It's I I don't know.
I think like, like, look, don't get me wrong.
Cheesy Manfredo loves a good misogynistic joke here and there.
Right.
But I think I think Dick's whole bit is like incredibly like overplayed at
this point.
What I don't.
What even is his bit?
Does he even do any bits?
Like I don't even think anything is a bit.
I the thing is like all of his fans like think he's all of his fans think
he's a fucking genius and that he doesn't really he doesn't believe
in anything he said, but he's been saying the same shit for like years.
Now he's he's he's like.
Remember that time Tim Poole was like from now on.
I'm just going to say random shit all the time.
So no one knows what I really think about anything.
Dick is like that, but he didn't actually say it.
All his fans just assumed it for him.
Yeah, it's so weird.
Like, oh my God, what's this?
Like is Dick is Dick a genius?
Like I don't see it.
It's so Dick is a someone's responded to me on Twitter the other day and they
said the thing like Dick being a gene like the idea that Dick is smart
probably came from the fact that he was on biggest problem and Maddox is so
dumb and Dick looks so smart in comparison.
Oh my God, like Dick seemed like a genius at the time because he because he
clowned on this on this idiot.
This idiot this idiot that people used to respect.
He clowned on him really hard.
He made him look like a fool and then he fucking bounced off of that and he
got a bunch of clout over it and he made a bunch of money and it's like,
yeah, he sure did.
He that sure was a that sure was he sure was a dude posting a W right
there.
He is the embodiment of dude posting the W.
Am I right gamers?
But what is that really?
What does that really say about him other than the fact that Maddox is an idiot?
Nothing.
No, I find these content creators who like capitalize on comment wars about
the dumb shit.
They say very interesting that kind of is that kind of is the the the cycle.
Right.
It's like say say something say something that will annoy people and then and
then make sort of a public spectacle about like, you know, responding to or
or, you know, doubling down on or or even apologizing.
You can play it any number of ways.
But the way you get clout is you say something that annoys a lot of people
and then you make a big show about responding to the outrage.
And I mean, that's all he does.
That's all that's all veto does.
That's all anyone around the people who defended you at the start
will just stick around.
Yeah, right.
They'll never change their mind.
So do you guys remember when you guys know the game, Yic right?
10 out of 10 game.
Oh, the Y2K the postmodern the postmodern RPG.
Right.
Exactly.
You know, like that guy was like that guy is like a fan of the Dick show
and he even put Dick in Andrew Allinson.
He put Dick in the game.
Yeah.
Dick's in the game.
You could meet him and I think he has like voice over lines too.
And he gives you a red pill.
No, no, no wonder.
No wonder that game came out so good.
No wonder it was so epic.
I mean, the thing is that I think like it's funny because the whole game is
about kind of like about this like straight white guy like kind of
reflecting on his character, right?
But the game like the game does like a terrible job of doing that.
And I think I think evidence of the fact that maybe this guy could
never truly reflect on being like a straight white guy is due to the fact
that he's like a Dick show fan.
Like I think that's like evidence that he probably could not do this
like introspective on himself, you know.
I mean, yeah, it's it's it fits.
It fits my it fits my my serial killer like forensic profile
style understanding of like the listener of the to the Dick show.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I do that too.
I feel like I think at some point I thought that Dick Masterson
or the Dick show seemed like Jordan Peterson, but for people who don't
think they need to improve.
Like like if you if you're like, oh, man, I'm all fucked up.
You know, oh, my I got to get back to my traditional values and sort
my life out.
Then you go to Jordan.
But if you're like, I'm gonna I'm fine.
You know, it's just fucked up.
But like I'm kind of above it.
I don't care any.
I don't care that it's fucked up.
Like I actually kind of like that.
Then you're like then you go to listen to the Dick show instead, which way
Western man obviously just women are just terrible.
Like on ironically, well, I mean, either way.
Yeah, either way.
Obviously, we can all agree on that as we unify this brings us brings us
together.
Yeah.
Anyway, sometimes dicks have some funny stuff.
That's about it.
I have I have laughed at a few.
I mean, I thought that I thought the biggest problem was pretty funny,
but I just don't think he seems like a very good guy.
I don't think he's a good person.
I don't I don't agree with anything he does.
I just yeah, I think he's I think he's garbage.
Yeah, garbage funny guy.
But I mean, and I mean, and I mean the the the the Maddox thing was funny
back in the day, but that was like six years ago.
And yeah, I know that like Maddox Maddox brought the lawsuit against them
and that was pretty shitty.
And like, okay, yeah.
Still like that's the thing.
And like who who cares anymore?
In my opinion, I hope that answers your question.
Anyway, yeah, what?
Yeah, Dick Masters in front of the show.
A great guy.
Ten of ten.
He come on some time.
Hey, buddy.
Next.
We should have you we should have you and him on to debate.
Oh, you should debate.
You should debate whether or not someone who makes the better argument
wins or someone who's right wins the argument.
Oh, yeah, I got this.
I got this in the bag.
I got this and I have to like prove it.
I didn't have to prove that I'm right.
I got in the bag.
You just you just have to be right.
And then you win automatically.
If you're right.
Yeah, exactly.
Next voicemail is called Benjamin St.
Jimman three, two, one, go.
I mean, I am I hold my anime stuff in like a box for a while.
And I'm trying to set up my room and I I I wanted to put up my serial experiments
lane wall scroll.
Don't do that.
And I noticed I can't find it.
Oh, I think I think Ben St.
took my scroll.
So I think I'm going to make 20 more voicemails about this.
I think it would make a thousand more voicemails about this to become a new character.
I'm going to be like, I'm going to be like the Samurai guy.
I'm going to be like the Samurai guy.
I would be like, I'm going to be PCP famous and I don't want to fuck me.
I was like a fucking.
Oh, my God, imagine wanting to be PCP famous.
Typical, typical PCP listener right there.
That's what they're all thinking.
Average PCP fan, average dick show enjoyer.
Am I right, guys?
If like, you know, yeah.
You know how, you know, like ever you see that you see the Amogus everywhere.
Well, if you listen to the PCP everywhere you look, everything looks like a scroll
and you think like, how can I pretend that Ben stole this from me?
Why? Yeah.
This might be a dumb question, but why a squirrel?
I don't know.
Is it just because he's the first one?
The original just picked the scroll and that's it.
Yeah, that's the sort of thing you would steal.
I asked Cassidy or Cassidy said something to me about this one
and because I was like why a scroll and she she said that like I said something
about a scroll like I responded to the samurai off the top of my head.
Just like something about a sacred samurai scroll.
So like I apparently I came up with it.
So it's my fault that it's weird.
They're trying to gaslight you and to believe in you came up with the with the scroll.
I probably that's probably true.
It's they use the Shadow Clone Kagi Bunshin Jutsu to deceive me.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called my toe hurts my broken toe hurts and it's making me upset.
That's a weird name for now.
That's right.
Henlo Corgo five voicemail grail and jail three, two, one go.
So I finally checked out that Google doc of the voicemail grail and jail and I mean
if I suppose if there is an easier way to listen to these, you'll mention it when you
respond to this in the next episode.
But I really want to check those out and find out why they're both in the grail or the
jail and I can't really find an easy way to do that besides listening to every fucking
episode of the show.
So if you could make it slightly easier to track those down and listen to them, much
appreciated.
I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to go back through all the episodes and keep track of who got grailed
when Ben doesn't get good luck to fucking do.
I don't get paid and I don't get paid enough to do that.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Like that sounds like a fan thing to do.
You know, fans love to go back and like count maybe maybe maybe spiral.
A spiral is going through them anyway.
I don't think he's he's probably well before the point where voicemails even started.
So maybe out of the kindness of his heart, he might be willing to take down some notes
on when people get grailed as he completes his coveted n word tally.
Once he gets the n word trophy, he's going to get the grail trophy.
That's right.
They're one in the same.
Yeah, next voicemail is called sorry.
I didn't put it here in time.
It is called wait.
No, sorry.
Listen to the one that's called three two nine five.
That one is called hi Ben three two one go.
Hey, what's up guys?
So for the last decade of my life, I've been reading the secret pretty constantly
and I think I willed into the universe.
The inevitable crossover between my two favorite podcasts.
That being the procrastinators podcast.
That's me as well as a podcast called let me tell you about.
So I started willing this into the universe around 2017, 2018.
Is he peeing?
And slowly but surely, I think he's peeing through sheer power of will.
Yeah, that's me.
All right.
So let me tell you about has now crossed over into the loudest podcast,
which is loosely affiliated with you guys through Trixie and The Dick Show.
And I'm I'm supposed to be on Chris Dery.
So by the way, I've been supposed to be going to cross over.
So why not go ahead and make it happen now?
It's a lot less willpower on me and my spiritual chakras.
And I mean, I got both.
I got into both of your podcasts around the same time trying to look for a way
to introduce normies into Chris Chan.
So I feel like you guys have a lot to talk about.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, make it happen.
All all the stereos or Sriracha needs to do is just message me because they
long, long ago, they said, Ben, you should be on an episode of Chris Dery.
And I said, sure, of course.
And since then, it's come up.
They've said like, yeah, we're going to do that.
You're all they have to do is ask all they have to do is ask.
I'm down.
I don't know if a crossover would work because I actually have seen.
I used to watch.
Let me tell you about whenever they would talk about a topic I was interested
in and basically the premise is that one guy just tells us co-hosts all about
a topic, right?
Yeah, I've seen the I've seen it around.
I've never listened to one.
And I forget his name.
I think his name is Ted or tab.
Oh, dude, I'm sorry.
I forgot this guy's name.
But he's he seems like a cool guy.
He's been on the he's been on the Laos podcast a couple of times.
I mean, I mean, I could see Ben and him being on the podcast together
because sometimes like a stereo likes to get little group chats together for bits.
But I don't know.
I don't know how like connected Ben is to a stereo's.
You ever listen to like my little podcast that I did with a stereo's?
No, it's something I notice about a stereo's that like
in retrospect should have been obvious is that like, you know, you've been
on a podcast before you talk to people and then you you'll pause to let like
the other person say something after you like say after you say something,
you let someone you pause and you let that person react, right?
Yeah, right.
Like for some reason, I would pause for a stereo's to react to something I said
and he would not say anything.
It was just kind of stay silent and I just I guess I just got to keep talking.
I just kept on talking because they didn't want there to be dead air.
And then I realized something comfortable.
Yeah.
It felt weird.
I don't even know if a stereo's realizes this, but um, but then I realized something.
I realized something that a stereo's only talks after you explain something
very long to him.
And that should have been obvious weird.
And that should have been obvious because on the loudest podcast,
all that is is Sriracha explaining stuff to him.
That's it.
Wow.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, that's the vibe I got.
I don't know if you talk to him and things just feel different.
Maybe I'm maybe I'm the weird.
I've never I've never I've never I've never like talked to him with my voice.
I've like, we've like tweeted at each other a little bit.
It's someone asked the stereo's why he's so weird like that.
Um, he's probably just because he's a boomer.
Probably because he's a boomer or maybe I'm the one next voicemail is called
Hi Ben two, three, two, one, go.
Sorry, I forgot to flush.
Yes.
Good, good man.
Never forget to flush.
That's a that's a W.
That's a dude posted his W.
That dude posted his W right there.
That's a blistered mail grill.
That was a good, that was a good, that was a good bit.
I'm like the inferior, um, like metal was called metalhead pig.
The one I just interrupt.
Yeah.
We can all agree that the interrupting pig is a bit that was just basically
just doomed to be bad just by its very, just by its very conception.
Just the very idea behind is just rotten to the core.
Has any like interruption joke ever been like funny?
Maybe.
But not this time.
Next one is called two five, two five, two, three, two, one, go.
Which radcon was the best?
Hmm.
Um, I, uh, I'm going to say three.
That I'm going to say three, four.
No, four was the last one.
You fucking dingus.
Yeah, I don't watch radcon.
For, I mean, four was fun, but we've said this before four was really busy.
Like we were like on all of radcon for we had like every day we had to wake up
and we're like, okay, we're going to film this.
Okay, we're going to, we're going to work on this.
We're going to make that we're going to stream that we got to get ready
for such and such.
Um, so like it was in terms of which one I think I enjoyed three more
because we didn't have as much to do.
We didn't have as much like in mind of like, okay, these are the things
we're going to make while we're here.
We were just kind of like, we'll get together and we'll just make a bunch
of shit and whatever we want to do.
So it was more relaxed like that.
So I would say right on three.
Um, I mean, I guess we had the arena, but that was like, you know, that was
so we recorded that in one day, uh, the, the OVA and stuff took like several
days, uh, including the Brad lecture, which is out now on the channel and
more stuff related to that will be coming soon.
I think more rad content.
Close to being ready to come out the pipeline.
Lamar base.
Um, base.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Riley singing.
Add the backing track.
Ellie is our earn your keep.
Okay.
Three, two, one go.
Hey, what's up?
Fuckers.
It's me, Riley.
The busy.
This is definitely do it.
Gazing.
And I thought that was had peaks up for a second.
Have a clear reference point for my beautiful singing voice.
Three, two, one.
Let's hit it.
My T is gone.
Call the boy ring.
Why I got out of bed at all.
The morning rain clouds up my window.
Yeah.
Can't see it all.
Amen.
If I could.
Put your picture on my wall.
It reminds me.
It's not so bad.
It's not so bad being me.
Riley.
I know this is do it.
Do it.
Gazers because do do it.
Gazers particular quirk is that his Riley impression sounds like a cold
Corona impression.
Oh my God.
No wonder.
Trixie.
They right.
Yeah.
Magnet magnetized.
I thought I thought he was going to go into the the rapping bit from the
what's the name of the song that samples.
It's Stan Stan.
Yeah.
Stan like dear Trixie.
So just so and so.
So I can't do it right now.
I don't know what the lyrics.
That would be you could probably make a pretty good a pretty good Stan
you could probably make a better one than Riley's a weird like parody
discord.
You might not have.
Did you hear did you hear that last episode?
I did not.
Yeah.
I don't think I got that that far.
But what is it?
It's it's hold on.
The procrastinators podcast.
Yeah.
Someone someone submitted a voicemail that is a clip of Riley singing a very
slightly altered lyrical version of the discord song discord.
I'm howling at the moon.
Oh yeah.
I got to that part.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, it's real.
Oh shit.
Someone who who posted it.
I'm going through the comments.
Neckbeard bananas in the comments last time posted a here it is too.
I'll we don't have to listen to it, but it's a real fucking thing.
It's like a him and some guy I've never heard of called a hazen cruise and the
joke of the song is like that someone is like talking shit or like trying to
cancel this guy hazen cruise and they're doing it by posting screenshots on discord.
And so the song is like ha discord is the villain because that's where
they're trying to cancel hazen whatever.
The point is just that it Riley sounds really bad.
Riley's voice just sounds really bad on this track and it's very fun.
I mean, so we thought it was fake.
We discussed it last time and we both me and give fight.
I'd be like, this would be really funny if it was real, but no, I can't be real.
No, this sounds weird.
No, that doesn't sound right.
I think it's fake.
It's real.
It's real in case anyone was still wondering.
It is amazing.
It is.
It's a pretty good find.
It's pretty good find.
A pretty good archaeological discovery.
We need to describe what the topic of the song was.
I'm like, yeah, that sounds like what a dick show would like talk about.
That sounds like their priority.
Yeah, I mean, they're trying to cancel.
They're trying to cancel my boy hazen cruise.
We got to record a we got to record a fucking parody brony
diss track at them to shut up the haters.
Yeah.
Hello, this is Ben from the future with a with an urgent urgent alert.
Red alert.
The song has been deleted.
The the legendary the the legendary track by a vizier
of yig and the presumably also legendary hazen cruise performing
their relevant Tory hit single discord by the living tombstone.
I think has been deleted in shame.
If anyone has a saved copy, I would love to see it.
If not, then I guess these episodes of the PCP will be the only
place you will ever be able to hear these lost masterpieces that
just wanted to just wanted to keep you updated.
Okay, back to the episode.
Next, next voice.
Next voice.
Now listen to 3299.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, listen to 3299 is called High Ben three three two one go.
Hey, what's up, Ben?
What's next after 102 and slime and punishment?
The game, the webcomic, the game.
Yeah.
Inquiring minds would like to know.
I think baby you want to say anything?
What the fuck?
Um, okay, uh, after, uh, yeah, after I finished the game and slime and
punishment, I think the next thing I'm going to do is I'm going to go back
and I want to finish Beast Capades because Beast Capades had an ending.
I knew exactly what the ending was going to be and I can just finish it.
It might take me a little while, but I know how it ends.
So I just have to do it because because when I have an idea.
When I have something that I want to make or an idea for a thing that I
could make, it is a demon inside of me and it torments me until I can
manifest it into the world and put it out there.
And the demon of Beast Capades is still inside me.
It has been tormenting me this entire time.
Uh, so it'll be the easiest.
It'll be the easiest one to exercise.
Uh, once, once I get this slime demon out once he's gone.
Uh, that's, that's the plan anyway.
Okay, next one is called Mark Fisher is what?
Huh?
What?
Yes, something to say.
I was going to make a con joke, but we could keep on going.
Okay.
Next one is called Mark Fisher is dope.
Three, two, one, go.
Been talked about Tim Rogers recently and as I have an unhealthy
parasocial relationship with the fellow, I'll shut some contacts for the
second time I'll speed myself up.
You can piece the story together by watching his stuff as it's a mixture
of personal anecdotes and game analysis.
This is what I've pieced together.
He lived in Japan for a decade, working out a few large companies before he
lost his reason how to leave his friend to go back to America.
He worked in various shitty games.
I think that's self-amended and notably, notably no more heroes.
He did stuff in America for a while, then got a job making video content
for Kotaku.
This enlarged how many people knew about him.
He's been writing on action button net for over 20 years now, but
games highly recommend his written f of six review called how and why I
never finished becoming a detective.
Anyway, when he left Kotaku, he announced he was going to start making
his own videos and the wide reach of a large corporation ended up with
him having a huge Patreon.
But really, there's no one like him that I've found.
There's so much overlap between his videos.
He has an interesting writing style and little things that you'll pick up
if you pay attention.
Spoilers for his f of seven and toky make a video in the middle of toky make
he goes off and attention about his best friend in Japan.
Tim often uses friend when referring to his girlfriend and how they
chatted every week until he says a date and then cuts himself off before
going back to the analysis, implying that something happened.
And the end of his f of seven series.
He explains quickly why it's important to him and how it overlaps
with his best friend who died.
I'm pretty sure they're the same person.
It gave me chills when I connected it and it still does.
Anyway, cool guy.
Interesting.
Oh my God.
He knew a guy.
He knew someone that killed himself.
Oh my God.
That blows my fucking mind.
So hard to shit, dude.
Oh my God.
It's a twist ending kind of based.
I mean, it's a good series.
I watched the final fantasy seven series.
It's a good series.
Yeah, it ends with spoilers.
It ends with kind of the twist that he's been talking about this friend
every once in a while.
In the end, he reveals like, yes, she killed herself later.
And it's like, oh, that's sad.
He annoyed me.
He annoyed me in one of, not in that video, in a different video.
Someone, I think it was about the, the, it was either the action
button review of the final fantasy seven remake or it was the Kotaku
pre-review of the final fantasy seven remake.
He says that people have been asking him if he's going to make a
like slow translation video series about the remake like he did
with the original.
And he says no.
And then he says like, and by the way, the final fantasy seven
video wasn't about making fun of a bad translation.
It was about, you know, going back to a work and having like new
perspective on it later in life.
And if you think it was about, you know, making fun of a bad
translation, I don't know how to help you.
He says that he says it in a way that's very much like, if you
think that's what it's about, you're wrong and you're stupid.
And I think that he's an idiot because it is about the thing that
he said it is about going back to final fantasy seven and having
a new perspective on it from gained life experience, but it is
also definitely to some extent about pointing out funny bad
translations and having a good time doing so.
It definitely is.
It's about fucking both.
You fucking, you fucking dweeb.
That was a real, that was a real pretentious moment.
That was a real, that was a real Jesse moment right there.
I didn't like it.
Real Jesse moment.
That was a real Jesse moment.
Real Jesse.
Here's my, here's my, here's my, here's my Tim, my Tim
Rogers impression.
That's why Tokimeki Memorial objectifies love and makes you
a fucking demon for playing and that's the bottom line.
And I would know.
I mean, I had six pack abs in high school.
I ran a five minute mile.
That's, that's, that's Tim.
Oh my God.
Um, we should get Tim on the show.
We should get Tim on the show.
Um,
Tim, come on down, buddy.
There's a, people, people have, people, Tim says weird stuff
about himself and I don't know.
He, he says, he sometimes will talk about like the memory thing.
He claims to have like a memory condition that makes him remember
everything all the time.
And I don't think that's real.
Oh, like Dr.
That sounds like some, that sounds like some Chunebio,
like, um, Alexandria's Genesis, like, like fake disability stuff.
I don't know.
I know that like, idetic memory is a thing, but that sounds fake.
How does he remember things all the time?
I don't know.
Like, just kidding.
Just, just have perfect memory is other words.
I don't know.
Just sometimes, sometimes he claims to have a, I haven't read
that Final Fantasy six essay.
I should, I should find it because he mentions it in, um,
I think it's the Final Fantasy seven remake review.
I think I haven't seen it yet.
Uh, he, he obviously doesn't remember everything because in
the video where he remember, he recollects game box art covers
from memory, he doesn't get everyone exactly right.
He's pretty good at a lot of them, but he definitely doesn't
get all of them right.
So his memory is not perfect.
And like, what, what does it even mean to like remember everything?
Also, apparently he's a Mensa member, which is not impressed
me.
That just makes me think he's a dweeb, uh, being, being, being
in Mensa's lame.
It's not cool.
What does it even mean?
I don't think he has perfect memory.
He, um, he didn't make a video talking about memory 9-11.
He forgot.
I forgot.
I'm like 9-11 is crazy.
Whatever.
He's his videos are kind of good.
I guess I like them.
I guess at the end of the day, he's like, he's my class enemy.
He's like, he has, he, him and he has more in common with Vito
guess Walde than he has with me.
He doesn't, he lacks solidarity.
He's my fucking enemy.
He's a class trader.
I will behead him.
Given half the chance.
Um, that's what I'm, that's what I'm saying.
That's the PCP is pro guillotine proitarian podcast.
Prolet, the, that, the P, the, that would be the PTP.
No, no.
Yeah.
Change to the PTP.
Next voicemail is called lesbian.
Three, two, one.
I'm going to read it.
I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to announce these like Tim
Ryder's now three, two, one go.
Hey guys, I'm at work.
I just thought about this since when is Trixie been into dudes?
I just realized she's dating Riley, but I've seen like she's not dating
Riley video ever.
Nobody can keep it straight.
And she's always been like super into lesbianism and you know, like only
watched lesbian porn and like all that stuff.
How the hell does that happen?
Uh, yeah, it's true.
It's true that now she likes guys, I guess.
I don't, I mean, I don't know.
It's not, it's not crazy because I don't, I've known a couple of
like, uh, trans ladies who were like kind of explicitly lesbian, but
then dated like guys, which isn't a bad thing.
You know?
So they, so they weren't, so they weren't exclusively lesbian.
Yeah.
I guess maybe they find out they're like bisexual.
I mean, I don't know what Trixie would classify herself.
Who can even say who even fucking knows whatever people, people's tastes
change.
They change their mind.
They try any things they do, whatever.
I don't know.
How the fuck should I know?
Ask Trixie.
What are you asking me this shit for?
She's got a podcast.
She's, she's.
Yeah.
Ask Colin, Colin to fucking void gazer.
I'm sorry.
I'm, I'm, I'm being mean.
I don't mean to be mean to this person, but I genuinely have no clue and I
don't know why you would think I would know.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to get into another void gazer live show.
Maybe.
Yes, please.
Next, next voicemail is called, um, it's, it's the three three zero two.
It's called Lord of ghosts, fake, angry face.
Three, two, one, go.
Wait, so the Lord of ghosts isn't an actual ghost?
I know.
Why the fuck is it called Lord of ghosts?
My God.
That's like calling yourself the Lord of marine life.
If you're not actually a goddamn aquatic creature.
It just bundles my mind.
Why?
Why are they fake?
That hurts so fucking much.
Okay.
Uh, you could be.
Well, it's like.
Well, it's like Jesus, right?
Jesus was king of the Jews, but obviously he wasn't a Jew because
he was a Christian and he believed in his own divinity.
So there you go.
That's how it's like,
it's funny because she's not even here to shame and answer this question.
There's, there's, um, I mean, there's so many like kings.
There's so many like kings and royalty that ruled one country that
were from another country.
Like I'm pretty sure several of the Henry's were just like Dutch or something.
I don't know.
This happens all the time.
You can be the Lord of something without being a member of something.
You can just be their Lord.
Um, it's easy.
Easy shit, man.
This is, this is basic.
I think I, I think I recognize this voice, but I'm not 100% sure.
I think it's, I think it's a friend of mine.
Um, God, I hope not.
Yeah, I hope not.
Imagine being friends with this freak.
This guy.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
If it, I think it, I think it is, um, it's, I think it's death alchemist.
We send that voicemail and all I have to say to that voice.
You think so?
I know, I know death alchemists.
I think that sounds like, well, death alchemist.
I talked to him like every other day cause he's very acted in my server.
Um, but that sounded like him.
And all I have to say to his question is that, um, the Batman in the dark night
returns is a fascist death.
He's a fascist.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to death.
He is a fucking fascist.
Like he fits the description perfectly.
Bomber.
Yeah.
Then it goes to the next place now.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to hear that I'm right.
You know, I'm sorry to hear that too.
Next voicemail is called, uh, I'm stupid.
Uh, the next voicemail is called influences.
Uh, oh, well, can't wait to listen to it.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
So in regards to influences, I think one thing that I just want to say
is don't pull from the influences that other people want you to pull from.
You got to pull from your door.
This is definitely, no, you're right.
This is that.
Actually based on a robot from Wallace and grommet, like really
Wallace and grommet is connected to undertale.
Like, do you have any idea how weird that sounds?
It doesn't need to be anything big when it comes to your death.
I already told you that.
Oh, we are a serial mascot.
You like my return.
Yes.
I want to put this in my webcomic, put it in your webcomic or just
something you like, even from a YouTube video.
Hmm.
Yes.
I will take this and put it in and make it unique me uniquely my own.
Just, just some food for thought.
I absolutely agree with the sentiment.
And also that's really funny that Mediton was based on the robot
from the wrong trout.
Wait, no, it's not the wrong trout.
It's the one from the.
It's the isn't when they go to the moon.
No, no, no, the one in the wrong trousers.
The villain is like a penguin.
Yeah, I think the one where they go to the moon.
Yeah, the villain is like a it's basically like a refrigerator.
Yeah, the ski is around on the cheese.
Yeah, that's me.
Uh, I totally see it.
It's totally true.
That's so funny.
I never saw that before, but I completely believe it and I like it a lot.
Okay.
Fucking fucking Windows Explorer just like keeps freezing on me
and not letting me click and drag like that's voicemails.
It's fucking late.
By the way, we had it's so late.
We have we don't have that many left.
Okay, no, we got one, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 34.
We've only got 16 more.
So we're good.
Okay.
That's too many.
I'm leaving.
All right.
I don't forget to read villain or not fucking left.
By zero zero couldn't take it.
Honestly, honestly, I can't blame him.
Honestly, I can't play have the boys on like us.
The next one is called inmates in the asylum, the sharpest sharpest
swords on the horizon.
I think I know what this is going to sound like.
Three, two, one, go.
Yep.
All of it.
Sharpening a skill to be a giant sword that lies on the horizon.
People head to the intro music doesn't go into the learning
do something brand new.
You're a single drop that amid something huge, a single fluid
motion through the roiling ocean.
Just go with the flow until you know for sure.
You gave it all you got and you can give it some more.
We're inmates in an asylum now.
We'll try again and again until we learn how the intro music,
the pipe organ didn't flow into the poem.
They were like two different things that just cuts off and then
the poem started.
I don't know.
I feel like I feel like it should connect.
I feel like I thought that the poem was supposed to interrupt
the pipe organs.
Well, then what's the point of the organ intro?
I don't know to throw you off.
I feel like I'm not sure.
I don't really like these.
This is the like the bear cyborg guy, right?
Yes, this is this is this is the bear.
I think I think these need to I think these need to shake up
the formula a little bit.
Yeah, a lot of these are kind of starting to sound the same.
Oh, zero says.
A screenshot.
I got a screenshot.
Zero says, ha, ha, canceled on discord.
You're going to post this around all over the place.
Uh, uh, uh, zero said, sorry, fellas had to run.
Thanks for having me.
You're going to post that on Twitter and whip up on angry mob.
Show that on show that on on screen.
Ellie is our show.
The proof also proof is in the pudding.
Make sure you add my comment.
This is read villain versus under it.
Sure.
Why not?
You got to remind me.
Okay.
Next.
Next voicemail is YouTube.
Poop.
Wait.
What are these all like all these are all like completely out of
order.
Here we go.
YouTube poop.
Uh, it's loading.
It's loading.
Okay.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Bring a YouTube pooper onto the PCP.
It'll be really good for them to talk about their shit.
Just just smear their work all over the audience's faces.
It'll be great.
And by the way, Gib, I have a playlist of good YouTube poops.
If you ever want to take a look at it.
Oh, this is typical death.
Always showing his YouTube poop playlist.
He does this in all the other chats.
No, this is not joking.
This is like his bed.
He does like show his YouTube poop playlist.
Must be very proud of it.
Proud of his poop.
Ben, Ben, please, Ben, please just agree with me.
Please just agree with me that Batman's a fascist in the Dark Knight Returns.
Just say you believe in me.
I haven't seen the Dark Knight Returns.
If we just say yes.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Of course.
There you go.
Yes, King.
Right away.
Thank you.
It's all I needed.
Next one.
Next one is called Japanese learning English, not hentai.
Three, two, one, go.
I have a bad case of diarrhea.
Wow.
Wasn't this from like a Jon Tron video?
I don't know.
I remember he made a video.
I think I think he made a video where he watched like Japanese like VHS tapes
or something and I think what this was like one of the bits maybe.
Lame.
Okay.
Next one is called this is a 3307 based to cringe to question mark.
Three, two, one, go.
So Ben, I got to say at first the rad con with you in show was kind of funny.
Then it got really cringe, but now I think it's come back around to being
actually good and funny.
So you got to keep it and for all you bronies out there.
That's the real horseshoe theory.
Oh, also, if Ben is so flanged, why hasn't Eleazar put some flanger on his voice?
Take care.
Tom will never die.
Is a flanger like an audio effect?
I'm the bull.
I don't know anything.
I have no idea.
Uh, next.
Next voicemail.
The intro is based the intro forever chug jug.
Okay.
3308 in three is called quit yo bullshit.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys.
So that's what you were talking about when it's okay to accept free work from
people and you specifically mentioned turning down offers of editing episodes of
the PCP are making a website.
Well, I know that's a lot of hot shit because it in a 2019.
I made that exact same offer and you guys welcomed it with open arms.
Now granted, I came to you guys and said that I'd do the work for free, but
not once did any of you resist the idea.
I'll refer any money and that's despite the fact that I paid for a
domain, web server and premium plugins all out of pocket.
Instead, you let me do dozens of hours of unpaid work and then when the site
was 99% completed, you just went silent and ghosted me.
So here I am.
I go to be past telling you to quit spouting that bullshit.
Whoa.
Okay.
I believe this.
I believe this could be true.
I don't, uh, I don't know.
This might be true.
I remember.
Okay, but we didn't use the website.
I don't, I don't think because there is because there is because the website
we okay.
The website we ended up using is, um, it's the pro natures.com.
Um, I feel like I didn't talk to this person.
I remember someone offered to make the website.
Oh my God.
Wait a second.
Okay.
This is off topic, but I just typed in the procrastinators.com.
Yeah.
And it's like a country.
It's like a country band.
It's two guys sitting on their porch strumming guitars.
They are they are they called the procrastinators.
Yeah.
The procrastinators.com.
They've got a fucking Texas flag as their logo.
What is their anti PCP?
The procrastinators.
Um, I'm getting as a bunch of clips for the amazing world of the gun ball.
Okay.
Now I don't really remember.
I didn't talk to this person very much.
I knew that someone had offered to make the website.
I don't know what was discussed or with who, but I'm pretty sure we didn't
use the stuff because like you said, no one offered.
No one offered to pay you, but we didn't use what you offered us either.
I mean, I think that's why.
I mean, I don't think that we like took what you were giving us and said
buy.
Uh, I think it was like that.
The Nate will know more about this.
Maybe prop probably.
Adam, Adam on Twitter.
Does even use Twitter now?
Nate tweets once in a once in a long, long while.
I don't know.
Okay.
I'm Michelle at Michelle.
This is on four.
I feel, I feel bad.
I feel bad.
I feel like maybe if we, if we weren't going to use this guy's work, we
probably should have just told him, no, we don't want you to make a website
for us, but maybe we were like, oh, maybe we should.
Maybe you got to financially compensate him for his time.
I don't know about that.
He has to, he has to actually prove that, um, he does to happen.
He needs like receipts.
He needs like screenshots.
He needs like emails, you know?
Yeah.
Because I guess any asshole in here and like, I don't want him.
I don't, I don't want to like shit on this guy because it seems like he
feels like we did, we done, we done wronged him.
Uh, which, uh, I don't even, I genuinely don't know.
I genuinely don't know the details of, of what was discussed here.
I just kind of heard about it from other people and like, oh, is that guy
making a website or is he going to do that?
Or is, are we, are we like in use it or what's the deal?
Oh, no, I guess we'll see.
I guess we'll see.
Kind of lame, kind of lame.
Yeah.
Well, like, uh, yeah, I guess, I guess he won't get no conversation
because no one could remember who he was.
I remember that this was that I remember that this person is real
and I believe that this is probably a real voicemail from that person.
I don't see any reason not to believe that this person is real,
but we don't acknowledge is real as being a real thing.
So I get by that logic.
This didn't happen.
Absolutely.
Okay.
The next voicemail 3309 is called reused voicemails three, two, one go.
Whoa, someone reused old voicemails.
That was surreal.
Is it going to be a pig?
I sent that creative immortality mail like two years ago or something
and remember quite clearly that you guys were talking over it.
There's a prankster among us.
Don't only PCP members have access to the voicemail archive.
They're, I mean, yeah, we have, you know, we do actually.
We do have access to the archive.
I don't know if we can like, can we look search for it?
Imposter.
There's an imposter in the PCP.
Funnily enough, old voice mail.
No, you know what?
I'm an idiot.
We, we, we can.
Yeah.
No, I can like type a search thing and go through our archive and be like
and find voicemails based on what they were titled.
That is totally a thing I can do.
I didn't realize.
Next voicemail is called SM part four.
And sorry, I'm posting it right now.
SM part.
No, sorry.
Yeah.
No, SM part three.
This is SM part three.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm the guy who sent in Riley seeing discord the other week.
Just want to say that was 100% real.
I don't know why you guys would think that some fan would just
pretend to be Riley seeing discord would be a really weird,
strange thing to do.
Anyway, it's on a sound cloud.
It's like a parody of discord related to the Maddox drama.
That's why he said I'm not a fan of Redditors.
Instead of I'm not a fan of puppeteers.
Yeah.
Anyway, verse two.
I got fishes that is cool.
He sounds so bad.
Oh God, you like breathe in the middle of his lines.
He sucks.
Oh, his voice breaks.
He tries to like do a falsetto and he cracks.
He doesn't crack, but he's so breathy.
It's really floundering.
Sucks.
Um, yeah, it would it would be weird for someone to fake it.
But I mean, people do weird things all the time.
I don't know.
I mean, I know that it's real.
How old is that like sound cloud account?
I don't know how the account is, but the song is only like eight
months old, I think.
I mean, and eight eight months ago, like no one knew who the
fuck any of these guys were.
Oh, no one in the PCP circle.
Maybe not no one in the PCP did.
That might be true.
Wait, hold on.
Let me confirm the song was posted.
I mean, the comments are from like eight months ago.
So I don't know if I can see whatever it doesn't matter.
But that's like if it's about the Maddox drama, that seems
really late.
Yeah.
Okay.
No, it was posted two years ago or more than a year ago.
Well, they still talk about Maddox.
I don't know.
I'm sure.
Yeah, too.
A bit.
I mean, I don't think he's been doing.
I think now they just kind of like will like see Maddox
live streaming and like make fun of him being awkward.
I think that's just kind of where it's at.
How entertaining.
How how.
Yeah, I know, right?
Uh, okay.
Next one is called quick and painless, right?
Wait, it's loading.
Oh, is that a 3 3 13?
3 3 13 is called quick and painless.
All right.
Wait, did we skip one?
Did we skip 3 3 12?
Yes.
All right.
3 3 12 is called read.
Just do computer science, bro.
3 2 1 go.
So CS is a very good way to make money that with minimal
with less less time in college than you need to be like a
lawyer or a doctor or whatever.
I just would warn that that caller that not everybody is
cut out for it.
And this is the test.
Watch the three blue one brown linear algebra series on
YouTube and if you can make it through it and you enjoy it
and you can follow along with what he's saying, then you're
fucking perfect for it.
But if not, it might you might not be the thing for you
because CS just requires that a lot of math and a lot of
abstractions.
It requires you to be able to think an entirely theoretical
space a lot in order to do it well.
But if you pass that test, you'll you'll do fine.
I have never heard of three three blue one brown.
It's a YouTube channel.
I guess.
Okay.
I mean, check it out if you want to know about thinking next
to voicemail is called quick and painless, right?
Three, two, one, go.
You know how your perception of time can change like particularly
when you're in pain or under stress?
What if as your head is being crushed?
It feels like a fucking million years or some shit.
Yeah.
That would be so epic.
I would.
I would suck.
I would not have a good time.
What if when you die, you.
You're dead, but your consciousness doesn't disappear.
Rather, it's just stuck in whatever sensation you were
feeling at the moment of death forever.
I'll be there.
Oh, God, I hope that's how it would die coming.
Hope I die coming.
Yeah, I'll be on my death bed and I'll tell my my my son's like
got really fucking drinking off your dog.
I'm really this is this is important.
This is the one thing I'll ever ask of you, son.
You got me.
Yeah, you drive me up and up on his death bed.
And I'm going to the only way I'm going to die when the nut hits.
I got to die in fucking bliss.
You ever pull the plug when the nut you ever see that one that
one tweet that was a good screenshot of a fortune for it
where this guy was talking about how you like he pitched his
idea for a book to so many publishers.
And I'm one and like, I think he kept getting denied because
his book was too fetishistic.
And people are kind of like, well, what's your book about?
And he said like, oh, it's about a guy who like, I think
it gets into like a car accident or or no, it's about a kid
who I think falls into like a cement mixer or something and
that kills him.
But his consciousness is still in the cement and that cement
is like used to like pave like streets and he talks about
all the sensations of like feeling people's like feet on
him and how much he likes it when like he likes like women's
like bare feet to walk on him.
I see.
Yeah.
I have not seen that post but I get it.
Next voicemail.
Next voicemail is called rebutting Nate revisionism.
No, sorry.
Next one is called games for Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, are you aware of disco Elysium?
It's a very Bencore game.
You probably like it.
The characters in the setting and shit are all extremely
Bencore because they're about like cops that fucking suck
in like conflict between communists and libs and yeah,
I've seen the setting is like there's this fucking actually
I won't spoil that but the setting is fucking crazy.
You'd like it.
The it looks like maybe this kind of story I would like
but it's also like one of those isometric are CRPG's and I
like don't really play those.
So I'm like maybe I'd like it.
Maybe.
I don't know.
It sounds cool.
I want to play it eventually.
That's just not my usual genre.
It could be good anyway.
Next one is called rebutting Nate revisionism.
Three, two, one, go.
Nate was not a good host like he was all right.
But remember when Nate had the most control over the podcast
like around episode 120 X or one one X or so.
It was fucking terrible.
Every single episode needed to have a fucking topic and it
was terrible and nobody had anything to say about the topic.
So it sucked.
That's true.
Nate was weirdly Nate was and like continues to be weirdly
fixated on the idea that like the podcast must have a topic
or it's like not worth doing even as though as though the
it was ever about the topics like it like all it was always
the case that like the topic of the episode was just an excuse
to like get the ball rolling and get us like talking about
our own weird shit.
I don't know how he doesn't understand that.
I really don't get it.
But he but when I asked when I've asked him he said like,
yeah, you know, the show's different now.
It's you know, it's not about topics anymore.
You know, it used to be about the topics, man.
It used to be about the topics now.
I don't know, man.
Just without those topics.
I'm just I'm just not feeling it anymore.
I mean, I'm paraphrasing obviously some but he has a he's
weird.
He's weird about I don't get it.
I genuinely don't understand what what the thought I process
even though I've asked him and he's explained it to me.
I still don't understand it.
I remember back when you guys still did topics and how I let
I left like a paragraph long like comment on the on the episode
titled monsters because like it didn't really seem like everyone's
favorite.
Yeah, no one had nothing.
No, no, no monsters.
Monsters to was the one that was like legendarily bad.
Right.
Well, I thought monsters to was a patron exclusive.
I thought maybe maybe you're right.
Yeah.
No, I think you're right.
Actually.
Yeah.
Because monsters one was the one where like, yeah, it just seemed
like you guys did like it's so weird because it's like this was
back when you guys would still actively talk about like Pokemon
and that's like a monster, right?
Like because we always talked about Pokemon.
We don't have anything else to say about Pokemon.
And I don't fucking care at all about like Kaiju's or whatever.
Right.
Exactly.
Oh, wait, did you, um, did you see the trailer for that like
Pokemon knockoff game?
Oh, the one where they're like working in a sweatshop.
They have guns.
Yeah.
It looks stupid.
I don't know.
I kind of think that yeah, go on.
It doesn't look like the kind of it looks like the kind of thing
that would generate interest from its kind of like surprising theme,
but then like wouldn't actually be a good game underneath it.
I'm very that's that's what it seems like.
I'm very interested.
I'm hoping it's a good game.
I think it'd be very funny if it was a good game because I kind of
like it would be cool if it was good.
Yeah, I'm kind of interesting.
I mean, I like the angle of like, yeah, yeah, this is just like dog
fights and we're just criminals and we poach and we use sweatshops.
It's just I don't know.
It's like your team rocket.
It's like you're playing as Team Rocket, though.
Finally, finally.
Well, we all want it.
Yeah, it could be cool if it's good, but I kind of think it won't be good.
All right.
I don't know.
You got to go next voice mail.
Yeah, absolutely.
Next one is called more thoughts on archiving.
Three, two, one, go.
The destruction of knowledge, like the removal of an archive so that
you can only know about something through fucking memory and word of mouth
again, like in the in the prehistoric age, the fucking destruction of
knowledge like that of information, of media, of whatever is like
existentially horrifying to me.
It's terrifying.
I hate it.
I haven't heard anything from like whoever's in charge of the archive or
I mean of the of the PCP Wiki.
I don't know if maybe that person like reconsidered their position on like
deleting or privating the Wiki.
I kind of hope they do since like I and I kind of think most people
think it's not what should happen.
What happened to them?
I guess I didn't hear about this.
Some someone someone said that like the Wiki was being deleted because
like things changed and it was things were different now.
As though like that's not the purpose of an archive is to record
how things previously were right.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's that's weird.
Like what if things change you are super weird.
If things change, you archive the changes.
You don't like that's what you need an archive.
Yeah.
You don't fucking rewrite old like information just because things
change like you don't just like, uh.
Yeah, you know now we got we got Darwin's.
We got Darwin's theory of not intelligence.
We got Darwin's theory of evolution now.
Like I guess we better I guess we better burn all these like
Lamarckian books on like on design design or whatever.
Like we don't do the science has changed.
So this shouldn't be archive.
We should delete it.
It's like if it's like in like if the like Marvel or DC comic
Wiki like every time they read with a character, they just get rid
of the old information or replace with the new one.
No, delete it all.
Delete it all.
We can't have anyone remembering that.
Yeah, that character isn't like that no more.
It's dumb.
I mean, I guess maybe you need probably a fucking Nate had that's
the guy who runs is probably a fucking Nate had maybe.
I mean, I have no clue.
It wasn't even the person who did it who was like voicemail.
It was like someone speaking on their behalf.
I think I so I'm a little bit mysterious actually like what's
even going on with it.
Right.
I don't actually know who runs it.
Oh,
little sus.
It's little sus.
It's Jeff.
It was always Jeff.
It's always Jeff.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Ben.
I live at the beach.
Please join me three two one go.
Then I just want you to know I was really offended that you thought
I was going to make pig noises at you.
I'm sorry.
It's very rude.
You're going to do it.
You're going to do it right now.
Oh, you didn't do it.
Okay.
Actually, the next one is going to be the pig noises.
Someone's got to do it.
Someone's someone's someone's going to do it.
Okay.
The next one is called Johnny tsunami three two one go.
Hello, bcp Johnny tsunami calling and again from Tokyo.
Your podcast gets worse every week.
I don't even listen to it anymore.
It's never so bad.
It's terrible.
Really, you know what you should do?
You should kick Ben from the podcast even so I would be better
than him if you can't get Nate back at least replace Ben with
someone who is a brain dead like Dr.
Wolf.
He has a hundred twenty K subscribers forty seven million views
or I love him possible 130 K subscribers twenty six million
views unique winners on your show.
Not losers.
He's right.
God damn it.
What did you hear?
Yeah.
Yeah, go on.
I was gonna say is he doing Trump impression Jesus help him
that fucking lag.
Was he was that a Trump impression?
Yeah.
Was that a Trump impression?
Is that what you're wondering?
You're curious.
You're not sure you're you're on the fence about whether that
was a Trump impression moments that sound very like he got a
couple of the Trump isms like I'm pretty sure that was like that
was like it.
Oh my God.
Yes, that was definitely I think that was like a Trump
soundboard or something or like a or like an AI Trump voice.
Yeah, yes.
It was definitely a Trump impression.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think have you seen that clip of a Kamala?
Yes, I know what you're talking about.
You know the one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, do not come do not come.
I'm gonna come.
Yeah, cuz the Trump saying I'm gonna come.
And then he's like the crowd.
Yeah.
And he's like, oh, it sucks.
Yeah, I wrote it for the wrong guy.
I miss him.
God, why do we have to have all these what you know, it's so
sad that we have all these like Nazis running around ruin it
for us.
Trump was the funniest president.
We could have all just enjoyed it and had a good giggle
except people had to go and get serious people had everyone
had Trump was being ironic guys.
It was just satire everything he was doing.
Trump Trump was being ironic and then some idiots had to go
and take it too seriously.
They took it too far.
They ruined it for all of his fans.
I don't know that he's ironic.
He's supposed to be satirical and they just took.
Yeah, they took it too far.
Yeah, it's true.
It's true.
I choose to believe that it's true.
Donald Trump has the worst fandom of any of any show on the
hub, right?
That is discovery.
Okay, next.
I'm sorry.
I I dead named discovery.
Next voicemail is called Henlo Corgo 6 3 2 1 go.
Okay, so I honestly cannot remember for the life of me
which lecture it was.
There was a PCP lecture where you been reference the song
Communist daughter by neutral milk hotel with the lion's
seam and stains the mountain tops.
And for you, I've said I've referenced that all the time
just sticking around.
I can tell but since in the airplane over the seat by
neutral milk hotel is my favorite album of all time.
I was just kind of wondering like how much you actually
like the album or if it's actually had an influence.
This is goofy.
This is a goofy question.
Just please talk about neutral milk hotel.
Just talk about neutral milk hotel.
I don't care if you love the album.
We're eating a lot of neutral milk hotel talk about
neutral milk hotel.
I have the I think I do remember the others one lecture
where I just starts on seam and stains the mountain tops.
I yell.
I mean, when I lived at Digi House with Trixie and Davoo,
there was like we had a running joke where we would just
start yelling neutral milk hotel.
We would just start yelling I love you Jesus.
And I've done it on the podcasts many, many times.
I mean, it is a funny joke and it's a funny meme and
they're funny lyrics and it's fun to go.
I mean, genuinely, I really like them.
I don't listen to very much music, but that's like one of
the few albums that I have like that I do come back to
every once in a while, listen to the album.
I would say I'm a big fan of that album specifically the
album as a whole.
I think it's a masterpiece.
It makes me cry.
That's what I think about it.
But also it's funny to go.
All I know about that album is that it was for and Frank or
not.
Yeah, yeah, that's all I know.
You're gonna say Lisa Frank.
Yeah, Lisa Frank.
I love.
Yeah, Rip Lisa Frank.
She didn't have it come Rip Lisa Frank then.
Yeah.
Yeah, I see taken from us too soon.
If I if I see those Nazis, it's on site.
I'll just tell you that much.
Lisa Frank still has shooters out here.
Nazis were based until they killed Lisa Frank and then
it got too real with Nazis that Hitler was being ironic
and he was just being satirical and like I took it too
fucking far.
They just took they didn't they had no sense of humor.
Exactly.
That's like oh my God.
That's why I hate the left on ironically he was he was
just he was just being he was just being a contrarian.
You know, he was just putting some he was just putting
some controversial shit out there to stir up some controversy.
Get people talking make a big spectacle out of it.
It was a bit guys.
It was like bro.
It was just a bit.
Look at his bus is mustache.
It's a Charlie Chaplin mustache.
It's a bit guys.
He was fucking clowning on it was a bit.
It was a bit.
Nobody understood.
Nobody understood postmodern humor.
Nobody.
Nobody was operating on the same wavelength.
Oh, yeah.
Um, yeah.
How many was that?
No, that was it.
That was the last one.
Okay.
All right.
We're just under three hours.
It's amazing.
Oh, yeah.
I guess let's fucking.
You got any flat final words already.
I already mentioned villain verse couple of times.
Um, okay.
I guess I guess another thing.
I'll where do people find it?
Where do people find you?
Where do people buy it?
You just look up cheesy Manfredo on Google and you'll find
either my gum road or my itch that IO page.
Um, and you can get like digital copies.
If you type in villain verse, um, you'll, you'll find like
this should be a tumbler that has like the first three
chapters that are free.
Actually, no, by the time this comes out, that'll be the
first four chapters that are free.
You know, I plan to eventually have all of all of villain
versus going to be free to read when it's over.
I promise you that.
Um, right.
And I guess one more thing is that if, if you know me from
Twitter or any other like social media, my profile picture
is a little plush.
It's a little plush clown.
Right.
And if you want your own, um, I'm not selling push.
I'm not selling like plush pasta, the clowns, but, but,
but the person who custom made these, um, which is my partner,
they are currently, um, you know, they're currently fully take
commission commissions now.
So they have a slot.
So if you want something in the same quality, you know,
they do, they do all sorts of things.
They have a whole commission.
They go by a rod and egg shop.
Yeah.
It's a nice plush.
It's a, it squeaks too.
The note, the noise, the nose.
If you look at it, it squeaks.
Yeah.
Oh, now that's, now that's delightful.
Right.
Exactly.
It's pretty epic and base.
I recommend you guys buy one because you won't just be paying
for their rent.
You'll be paying for my rent too.
We'll check out, uh, we'll put a link to cheesy stuff in the
description, along with also a link to the Kato anthology.
Vote with your dollars.
Are you team cheesy or are you team Kato?
Right.
Are you, uh, read, read both and then, and then weigh in on
the, uh, on the, on the debate.
Right.
Exactly.
People are talking.
Yeah.
It's, it's hot topic.
You know, yeah, exactly.
It's a hot topic.
And if you're not in on, if you don't, if you're not a breast
of like, you got to know all the deeds.
You got to, you got to know, we're going to teach the controversy.
If you, right?
We got to teach, we got to teach both sides.
You might as well, like, you might as well have like forgotten
the majority of history.
If you don't know about this current hot, like contrast
is going on.
T. H.
Absolutely.
All right.
Okay.
Bye.
And, and become a patron.
Yeah.
But procrastinators also.
Okay.
Do that too.
Do that.
Okay.
Bye.
End of the episode.
Later.