Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever and let's see here we've got Gibbontake over here.
Hey guys, go to Gibbontake.site to read comics that I make. This is a, I'm gonna chill my
comics forever every single time I speak.
That's an option. We've got Tom Oliver over here.
Why is Final Fantasy VII Remake sold out on Amazon?
Sold out?
It's sold out. We can't fucking buy it and I refuse to buy a digital copy.
You're a better man than I. I bought digital.
Bullshit.
Coward.
I just don't care.
I just don't have the hard drive space. I've done the research, apparently it takes
up less space on your hard drive if you have a disc.
That makes sense. I believe it's, it was 87 gigs if I remember correctly.
Ooh.
It's a lot of space.
Holy shit.
A lot of fucking space.
And we've got...
For one third of a game.
Less than that, bro. Less than that. But we've got her here.
Endless Jess, of course.
Hey, it's me doing my yearly like three episodes of this show before I get to be here again.
Guys, we've got to talk about this fucking, what you just said.
This whole, this digital copy standalone. Oh wait, Nate did this himself, but you know
him.
You know me.
So like, I was, it was like the day before the game came out and I was looking at it like
it was like, oh, pre-order now and you can download the game early and then it will unlock
at midnight.
So I'm like, yeah, okay.
I mean, it's like no one can go out.
So I can't get a physical copy, I guess I might as well do this.
So it's like, okay, there's like standard edition for $60.
There's like the big edition for $80.
And like the big edition just has like a cactar summon and a carbuncle and a useless digital
art book.
Seems like, you know, not worth it, but it's like, ah, it might as well.
I guess I have to, you know, get the main, the big edition.
Yeah.
They got me by the balls.
That's, we always knew that would be the case.
But so I get that and like the download before midnight thing doesn't work.
It doesn't do that for me.
I don't know if there's some kind of like, you have to learn to code to figure out how
to get it to actually do that.
You do have to learn to code.
Yeah.
So like, I bought it and like, I'm like, where, I don't understand.
Someone helped me and then I fell asleep and I woke up at like, you know, in the morning
and it like, it still wasn't there and I'm like, oh, come on.
What is this?
That's ridiculous.
I woke up on Christmas morning and finding like just a shit in a box instead of what
you wanted, which was a different kind of shit in a box in this case, a shit without
a box.
It's like that thing when parents say like, listen son, we're not going to buy you any
presents, but we're going to go out the day after Christmas or like two days and we'll
go buy you gifts and it's like, well, mom and dad, I mean, you know, I appreciate that's
economical.
I, you know, it's unfortunate that you don't love me, but you know, I mean, we can, we
can make this work, I guess.
But then the next day, I ended up having it.
I ended up having to go out for some reason and go to Walmart and like wade through the
sea of boomers and they're stupid little masks and everyone's got like, everyone's got like
a cute little camouflage pattern, like mask now and like little colors.
Like it's just, it's just a fashion statement now.
We're all okay with it.
We're all just okay with this.
It's totally fine.
It's the new normal.
You know, my mom, my mom made us a bunch of masks and sent them to us while I was out
at the grocery store.
We were wearing our masks.
Michelle, like a, like a cute little dog one, a lady just says like, Hey, where'd you get
those masks?
And I'm like, oh, my mom made them for us.
She's like, can I buy some from her, please?
Give me her contact information so I can have a mask.
And yeah, that's happening.
It's cool now.
There's nothing weird or wrong about it at all.
In fact, everyone was rightfully looking at me with disdain for not wearing a mask and
looking at me like the scum of the earth and just a mutant crawling up from the sewers
and walking among the streets to infect everyone in the populace for the crime of not wearing
a mask on my trip to Walmart.
But anyways, I'm at Walmart and I'm looking at the games behind the glass case and there
it is.
There's the physical copy.
First of all, I didn't realize that the physical copy would be fucking beautiful.
And it's, it's, it's the white, it's exactly like the original box, the same box art.
And I'm just like, well, too bad I already spent 80 bucks for the fucking digital.
And then I see the price tag.
It's 50 bucks.
The, why?
Oh, that's right.
They always mark it down.
That's true.
Why is the physical copy 50 bucks?
And the digital is at least 60.
That's a Walmart thing.
Is that just a Walmart thing?
For whatever reason?
Yeah.
The reason is go to Walmart to buy your games because they just mark down like all games
$10.
I don't know why.
Oh my God, what a crock of shit.
I was so mad.
I almost, I actually got the virus right then and there just because I was so upset.
It found its way through, it found like a weakness in my constitution and it got inside
me in that moment.
You're going to be hearing a lot of this of me in the coming weeks and months.
But there's some, seeing, I know nobody in the world cares, seeing the cover, I just
Google it, seeing the cover of this game being a long rectangle and not a square makes
me unreasonably angry.
It makes me want to rip my heart out and stop it on the, it's supposed to be a square.
It's like Square Enix.
Remember that company guys?
You are such an autist.
It's not even funny.
It's supposed to be a soft square made out of some kind of, made out of like noodle material.
Oh boy.
The disc should be a square shaped disc.
The only one of its kind.
The only thing about that, I, well, I don't know, my story is bad.
I'm just previncing with that information.
And it's just that I also downloaded the game pre-order because I just had to have, I just
had to have that extra chocobo chick materia that you get as a DLC pre-order bonus.
I didn't want it.
I didn't fucking, is there no option to just not get the pre-order things?
I literally hate them and don't want them.
I just want, okay, whatever.
But the, I realized in order to download it or when I bought the game, I'm like, why
isn't this downloading?
I should see something on my thing right now.
What's going on?
I, I Googled it and figured out in order to download ahead of time, you have to fucking
like navigate into like several sub menus and like, like choose to like preload the game
in like a week.
You'd think that would be like, I remember doing this before.
When you buy a game, there's like with Kingdom Hearts 3 on the screen, on the PlayStation
download library or whatever, or on the store, you just press X and it fucking downloads
and that's all you had to do it.
Why was this game different than you?
I had to go, I had to Google how to figure out how to download the game and navigate
to another weird menu.
It just had to be something.
That's not a game problem with a game, but what, what the fuck?
What was that?
It was a query.
They have to, they just, Square Enix can't help themselves.
They have something good and they just have to meddle with it.
Maybe it was like Sony.
Like maybe it's a, the platform itself is the problem, like they changed something about
how it works now.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's their fault, but like that night after I had purchased it digitally
and then fallen asleep, you know, before I woke up the next morning, that night I actually
had a dream about Final Fantasy seven and it was like, like I had a dream that I was
wrong and the game was good and it was beautiful.
It was like, this is not a bit.
This really happened.
I had this dream.
Sure.
And like in my dream, like Cloud and Tifa both had like Southern Hick Drawls cause they're
fucking Backwoods white folk.
Tifa's a cowboy.
And there was like all this like weird, like the, like the new stuff was like expanding
rather than like taking away and it was all like appropriate and respectful and it was
all good and wonderful.
And I'm like, oh my God, I was wrong.
I'm so happy to have been wrong.
And then I woke up back in the real world and realized I still have yet to play it.
And I'm like, oh no, oh, it can't possibly live up to my dream that I had.
So anyways, then I played it and I, well, okay.
First of all, I don't know how to fucking say this.
I assume you have a ton of complicated feelings that are hard to express.
I do.
I know I do.
First of all, like it's fucking phenomenal.
Like the game is fucking amazing.
Like, just like we said last week, like eight year old me has died and gone to heaven playing
this game right now.
Like I just got to wear, but like also I was right about everything.
You know?
Yeah.
Yep.
So like, I like, I just got to wear like, I got to where you meet Tifa and you go to
the bar and you're in the slums and I'm just like looking around and like there's the bar
and there's the plate.
I can look in the sky and see how the, like the sun is shining through in certain spots
of the plate and I can see like this massive area that is now the slums and I can go around
and cloud has a little apartment right next to Tifa and there's like this little section
where you're just walking around with Tifa just going about your day doing side missions.
I did every side mission I could and just like, this is like the comfiest.
This is the best thing that's ever happened to me in my life is just I'm walking around
the slums with like the original waifu, my original wife Tifa.
I'm just walking around with her like going on side missions and like this is all I've
ever wanted in my entire life.
You go to the bar and like, you can actually, you can go behind the bar now.
Like my whole life, I've wanted to go behind that bar and you can't do it in the original
game and now you can, 10 out of 10, it's the greatest game ever made.
They fucking, you know, and so, and there's like, and there's like, there's like missions
where you, you learn more about the members of Avalanche.
They're really like trying to make you care more about Biggs and Wedge and Jesse.
You go to like Jesse's parents house and, you know, it's this, you meet, you know, you
have to sneak into her dad's room and her dad's, this is a kind of a spoiler, I guess,
but whatever you sneak into it, it's early in the game.
You sneak into her dad's room, her dad's got Mako Poisoning, he's there and you learn
about her, you learn about her plight.
You see cloud like starting to warm up like, like, I was so afraid that they would like
have him just be advent children cloud the whole game, just like the smoke.
Yeah.
No, he starts out like, correct.
He's like, he's like a trying really hard to be a nonchalant badass.
And like, you almost buy it at first, but it starts like, you see cracks in it as you
keep playing.
And then he starts warming up as he learns more about the members of Avalanche and their
plight.
He starts remembering how much he cares about Tifa, like the characterization is like actually
on point.
The voice acting is like, mostly incredible.
Like most of the characters are so well cast for once Tifa sounds great.
I think the dialogue is like actually good.
I can't believe, I cannot believe that the dialogue is good and like well written and
like how people actually talk and it doesn't feel like weird or like anime-ish and all
that.
And like I'm playing it.
So I'm like, I'm like five or six hours into it and this is a moment where I'm, I'm just
taking it in.
I'm just, I'm playing darts and I'm in the bar and I'm talking to Barrett and I'm looking
at Merlene and she's like scaring Barrett says, don't scare my daughter, you fool.
And I'm talking to Tifa and she's making me a drink and everything is great and it's
all wonderful and I'm in fucking heaven and I'm standing outside and I'm just looking
at the bar.
I'm looking at seventh heaven.
I have died and gone to seventh heaven.
I'm looking at the plate above.
I'm looking at the dirt on the ground below.
I'm looking at all the ramshackle fucking shacks all over the fucking slums and I'm
like this is it.
This is the, I can't believe it.
Maybe I was wrong.
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe this can be an actual good experience.
And then the Nomura character shows up.
You're riding on your motorcycle and they do a little motorcycle mission and here comes
this guy, this new character called like Doge or Douche or something, some stupid fucking
name.
He's got like a stupid haircut and he's got a goatee like it's 1999 and he fucking, you
know, he looks more 1999 than the game which came out in the 90s and he's fucking, he's
coming in on a motorcycle and of course that's where the advent children, flippy fucking motorcycle
sword fights have to start and I'm just watching the scene.
I'm in it and I'm going oh my god you were doing so well but Square Enix just can't help
themselves.
Nomura couldn't help himself.
They had to create this guy and stick him in here unnecessarily just, and he's just,
and this guy starts talking.
The fucking words.
I mean you said no anime dialogue but then this guy shows up and the words that come
out of this guy, it's like he's from a different game.
It's like every other character is in a totally different game and the dialogue is actually
decent and good.
And then this guy comes in like he came in from the crisis core universe.
He found a wormhole and found his way into this game and instantly the quality of the
whole thing nose dives immediately and he just starts talking in poetry and he starts
talking like Genesis like quoting plays and sonnets and shit and he's going oh the flames
of our rivalry shall burn forever.
I can't wait to have sword fights forever.
You're my fated rival because everyone is gay for each other.
Let's be gay for each other and let's scissor, let's have a nice motorcycle scissor sword
fight.
I'm so happy to have found my fated rival in this world.
The dying embers of my heart, my romance and my passion and I'm like what happened?
In five minutes the game went from the most incredible thing, like all my dreams came
true to then all my nightmares have come true like right one after another.
Hold on just a second.
That sounds like it was tongue in cheek.
Did Cloud give a shit about this guy?
No, Cloud rightfully hated him and wanted nothing to do with him.
Thank God for that.
But just like the fact that this character exists and like they just had to-
Yeah, you've got to think that like this is what Nomura considered like worthy of an
addition to the tapestry that is the story of like this guy who's just basically like
a Genesis character like you said.
He's extremely similar to Genesis and he has equally advent children moves.
I mean these are just all the elements that I don't know about everybody else but I hope
to see very little of and to have more of just the other stuff.
And the thing is, it's like I get the idea behind this character and it's not even a
bad idea like you see him and they go-
Do you see a soldier who's like not-
Yes, a soldier.
That's good.
That's good stuff.
Oh, he's a soldier and you read his bio.
He's like a soldier third class and like he's got like the suspenders and the outfit and
it's like it is a legitimately good idea to like expand in little ways like having another
soldier to be like a rival to Cloud throughout the game.
That's cool.
That's great.
Why do they have to be this?
You know, I've got a nuanced point and I'm making a video about this.
I'm about 18 hours into the game.
I am blasting through this thing.
I'm going to be done with it soon and I have so much to say about it in one maybe more
videos, I don't know.
But about this character, there's a moment later when, okay, you know when you meet Reno,
when you arrive in Eris's whatever, you crash through the ceiling of the church and whatever
and Reno's there.
Reno had a fascinating point of dialogue that in retrospect, like this is a moment that
I think the remake is like literally better in the- because there's like additional levels
of expressiveness it can do and it's that specifically Reno says like, who are you?
Cloud says, ex-soldier.
Reno's like, really?
What class?
And Cloud says, first class.
Reno, when hearing, and maybe this was in the original, I'm going to replay it to double
check.
Reno like laughs and is like, bro, like it's obviously a joke that you're a first class
soldier.
Like I can tell you're not that powerful or something.
What that did for me was make me be like, oh, you know what this is doing all at once?
What it's doing is it is throwing into question like the validity of Cloud's story in a very
reasonable way that characters who like, who are in the know would actually be able
to like, with a degree of authority on the matter, like question specific elements of
Cloud's story, especially considering we have already met a soldier third class.
Like I know it's no more of stuff.
And like that guy seems barely more powerful than or like Cloud seems like only a bit stronger
than that guy.
Now there is issues with this because like Cloud is doing literal advent children shit
that like no one has ever done in the history of the world.
So it doesn't the power scaling does not really make sense once that stuff has been included.
But I mean, combat was always kind of an abstraction.
I'm guessing they're continuing that with like the cutscene combat as well.
I don't know.
But like that's a moment that they've taken what already exists and just added a little
bit of extra detail.
Yeah.
And they're making a lot of story more like I'm shocked at how the only point I wanted
to get about that.
And it was just that the issue about that is that the game is already like everything
I said just there is set up for the mystery of who is Cloud?
Like what is his backstory?
That's all those points I just said are adding to that mystery that was in the original.
The problem is that mystery itself is not maintained in this remake in the same way
it was in the original, which leads me to believe they don't understand what they're
doing with these additional details.
They are just putting new things in.
Some of them hit the mark, but they shatter the illusion in this game, which is supposed
to be the first fifth or sixth of the fucking game where that information is not supposed
to be known yet.
So like ultimately, what was the point of it?
It's such a fucking one foot one step forward.
How is the mystery revealed?
I mean, I don't want to spoil it for you.
I'm aware what like they you are very cleanly aware it is stated to you that cloud is not
a soldier.
This piece of my worry of that is that I mean, like I'm at the point now we're like because
it's so clear that they did actually give a shit more than I gave them credit for, you
know, or more than I assumed they would like, I'm shocked at how many little things there
are like that Reno line you mentioned where it's just like, oh, this is like a good addition
to the canon.
Like I like this more of this please.
And like just little moments where like things are expanded or like are touched upon.
I'm shocked at how much there's that that I like I guess my worry is that they're going
to cram all the character development into this first game.
And then what the fuck do you do for the next, you know, five games, bro, they've got no
plan.
Yeah, they've got no plan.
It just seems like they're really I can feel how the story is set up in this one that they're
kind of rushing through these character beats that, you know, in the original game throughout
the whole game.
I mean, that's definitely true.
I mean, Sephiroth's appearance after the first fucking mission could could not be clear as
to exact.
Oh my God, Jesse, the thing that maybe the most angry, I wonder if you I don't know if
you also noticed that I mean, it's very clear in the story, but it made me this is the moment
I was like these people are fucking up blowing up their own reactor.
Yes, it's the chin.
Are you kidding me?
Are you fine?
You're rewriting Avalanche's role in the story.
That is the worst change in the game so far.
You mentioned that and flip shit because I played the demo a couple of weeks ago.
I know you guys didn't and to make it clear for everybody in the audience, I've never
played Final Fantasy 7 and I haven't on purpose.
I want to play the remake without the perspective of all the baggage that you guys have just
just as an experiment.
And so I play the demo and I did a podcast on it and I specifically mentioned that scene.
I was like, I am 99% certain this is an addition to the remake and was not the original game.
You don't have to be a nostalgia fag.
You just have to have a functional fucking brain.
Because it just felt so fucking like the lot.
If we can't have the main characters be underwritten terrorists anymore, even though the whole point
is that they have an arc and they learn their lesson, they change people.
Later on, fucking like Jesse's arc is like feeling guilt about the terrorist things they
caused.
So like, oh my God, on the one side, we get our characters feeling guilty about the collateral
damage.
And on the other side, from a meta perspective, we're aware that they're pure as the fucking
driven snow and they have nothing to feel bad about.
They literally did nothing wrong.
And you like other characters in this remake?
I don't know if you saw this line.
There's a line about, look, whatever, there's like before Crisis Shit about how Avalanche
is like a large organization and just barrets like Cell of Avalanche that was never clearly
raised in all but whatever.
It's before Crisis Bullshit.
They expand it in like some side games.
Yeah, it's in the Jesse mission and suddenly there's like other Avalanche cells that come
out to like, apparently they have some rivalry with you because like, oh, they don't like
the way we do things.
Like, what are you talking about?
What is this?
Dude, they say, this is the fucking, this is the thing.
Those other ones are like paramilitary organizations.
But Barrett Cell is specifically called like, they're ostracized because they're too radical
is what they say.
And yet, we're shown that like, no, they're actually all good, like they would never hurt
anybody.
And so how is Barrett Cell, how is it, how are they also the ones who are too radical
and also the ones who are like understaffed and like have no weapons and no money?
It doesn't make sense.
It makes no sense.
Like the whole point of them is that they have nothing.
They're like a startup.
And the worst thing about it, maybe the worst thing about it is how cucked Barrett and our
Avalanche guys are by being shown to be so ineffectual, even when they are able to like
do a little terrorism.
The bomb does nothing and they're robbed of all agency in the story.
The implication in the original game, in fact, I think they even flat out state this, when
you go to Cosmo Canyon, Barrett went to Cosmo Canyon as a young man early on and that's where
he got the idea to form Avalanche.
It is a grassroots organization that came up from the slums of poverty.
It is not a paramilitary, you know, coalition that spans the globe and has access to God.
It is now.
So like, I think there was a line in the original where Jesse is like, oh, I think the blasting
agent was too powerful.
I think I made it too powerful by mistake.
You know, so that was in there, but at least it was still her mistake.
It was her, you know, like they still did it.
They're still culpable for killing all these people and blowing up the reactor.
And now like that line is still in there in the new one.
In fact, they make a whole side vision audit of her like, oh, I got to go get a weaker
blasting agent because I feel guilty.
Okay.
Well, you feel guilty, but we're going to find out later.
You didn't even do it.
It's not even your fault.
You did nothing wrong.
So what's the point?
And then she's a waifu, Jesse.
She's not allowed to do anything.
She's not allowed to have any character.
She's there to be sexualized and observed for us.
That's her only role.
That's all that these characters exist for.
And then like, and then there's the part where, like I started out praising it.
Now like now that I think about it, you know, it's like you start thinking about it and
then you get more into what you hate about it.
Like the part where, you know, there's this slightly clumsy bit of dialogue where Tifa
says she feels trapped and she only says that so that later cloud can have his flashback
of her as a kid's thing.
If I'm ever trapped or in danger, you'll come save me.
And it's like that whole scene where she's going like, oh, I just feel trapped in this.
I don't, I don't like what we're doing.
We're, we're going too far, you know, you know, the other characters like Jesse has
a line where she's like, oh, Tifa's heart's not really in it.
And it's like Tifa in the original game was a vengeful fucking rage fuel.
She hated Shinra.
Remember how they killed her family and village and, you know, her famous line when her like
dad is dying in the maker reactor is like, I hate Shinra.
I hate Mako.
I hate soldier.
I hate them all.
No, no, no, no.
She's a delicate flower, Jesse.
She's not allowed to be a to have anger in her heart.
She has to be pure.
Our thighs are too thin.
They are too thin.
It's little too small at times.
Hey, I've got, I do want to say that I do agree with your initial sentiment.
There's a lot of good stuff.
And let me say two moments.
I cried at exactly one time, exactly one time out of pure emotion.
And it was, this is, it was like the shortest scene ever, but this is always fucking, okay,
you go through the bombing mission at the beginning, right?
And like Barrett's such a fucking asshole piece of shit.
When you get home after that mission, Barrett walks in the door and Marlene runs to him.
I fucking burst into fucking tears.
I've never felt anything more.
Barrett and Marlene are the best part of this fucking game.
And you know what's sad?
They cut out like tons of their fucking scenes.
We don't even get to see them together most of the time because we've changed how the
story, whatever.
I mean, that's a, that's a nitpick, but I fucking love Marlene and she doesn't have
enough of a presence.
For my taste.
There's so much good in it.
But I just know that everything good in it is going to be sabotaged by something else
in it.
That's shitty.
You know, like, I love that.
Like, I love how they, like, they took so much care and attention to detail on certain
things.
Like they even remembered like a minor character like Johnny.
He's in the game for like a little, like I was like, oh my God, I can't believe it.
That's really cool.
But I just know he's going to come back later.
Yeah, he's going to come back later and fuck Tifa in front of you or something.
How exciting.
I was reading a little bit of developer commentary about like the original stuff and Johnny was
like in the original.
So there's another thing going on here.
Johnny was originally planned to have a larger role in the original game.
Okay, they couldn't add that due to like time or like things didn't work out.
But now that there's a remake, they like take that opportunity to expand that role.
I have mixed feelings about that because like, I mean, I won't get into the big spoilers
later.
But like whatever your plans were when you made a game originally, like I love the game
that you did make.
I don't love this game that exists in Nomura's mind that he wish he had made, you know, 23
years ago or whatever.
I don't know about that game.
I don't care about that game.
So that is no, that does not affect me in any justification that like, oh, new bad things
are in because they were planned to be in the original doesn't matter.
Not important.
Don't care.
But, you know, speaking of coloring good things with bad stuff, there was another scene
I really loved.
Really my other favorite part of the game.
And it was just in the original after you save Eris from Reno and you escape, you run
across the rooftops.
I got to that scene in this game.
It's much longer as, excuse me, everything in this game takes a million times longer,
which is kind of annoying.
But it's just a simple scene of you and Eris walking along rooftops, getting to know each
other, kind of bonding and doing all that stuff.
And that scene was charming and delightful and was absolutely beautiful.
That was like the time I took the most time to just observe how amazing this game looks
and how, I mean, to be, to simply be able to pan the camera up and see the underside
of the MiGar plates.
That's like the point where I like, where I was like standing in front of the bar and
I was like looking around my surroundings and just taking it in and just like looking
up and seeing the fucking pizza in the sky.
And like the parts where it's unfinished and the sunlight is coming through, I'm just
like, it looks beautiful.
It looks so good.
Hell yeah.
There are some people out there who are shitting on it because like a lot of the, I don't
know if you've noticed, a lot of the textures and background images are extremely grainy
and...
Yeah, that's something that only the nerd would notice.
I don't fucking give a shit.
I have noticed, but I don't really give a shit.
I mean, like the original game was like programmed to the box of matches, so.
I would argue that while this game...
Because together with Scotch tape and thumbtacks.
I mean, that's true.
Since this game is trying to create a, as I said in my video years ago, a more complex
illusion.
Any breaks stand out more and are more jarring, but I mean, you know, whatever, who really
gives a shit.
I love the gameplay.
I don't know.
Like it feels good to fight.
I love the little additions, like being able to level up the buster sword so that I can
keep using it throughout the game if I feel like, instead of like immediately having to
switch it out.
That's cool.
Yeah.
That's a nice feature.
I mean, I don't know.
I love seeing the material on Tifa's gauntlet and cutscenes and like...
I gotta say, I've always wanted more of that shit and it looks really cool.
As a tech demo of Final Fantasy 7, I basically can have no complaints.
It's like the most amazing thing I've ever seen.
The one thing that I also do appreciate is that the game is literally called Final Fantasy
7 Remake.
It's on the box.
So there can be no believing that this is Final Fantasy 7 for anyone.
If you believe that it is, you're wrong and get out, except for the parts that I like
which are correct and good and it can't.
But all the parts that I like are not canon.
I mean...
That is a big thing, like calling it a remake.
One thing I've always hated, it just comes down to the Googling.
Like you Google the name of a thing, knowing that there is an original and a remake that
is exactly the same thing and you come up with like the thing you don't want every time.
You have to clarify and it's just annoying.
Good thing you don't have to type Final Fantasy 7 2020 or whatever to distinguish it.
Yeah, Sonic 06 and whatever.
Yeah, there's a lot to say about this game.
We'll all keep coming back to say more about this game until we've all beaten it.
And then for years after.
I just found it on Target.com and ordered it.
It'll be here in a few days and I'll be able to weigh in on it more next week.
There you go.
Hell yeah.
Presuming that the rest of this game and the following games in the Final Fantasy 7 Remake
series are of a similar ratio of new good shit and new bad shit, would you recommend assuming
that is what you've played so far?
The thing about that is you are not allowed to publicly state your opinion of this game
as a remake until you have beaten it.
You're just not allowed.
Jesse you have to beat this game before you because the things that happen I mean are
just a note of note until somebody says yeah, play it because I have no real burning desire
to play Final Fantasy 7 again.
It was a good time but like I need to know like I need someone I trust to say yes, please.
I mean I feel a little bit raped because I never had an option but to play this game.
It literally I had no choice.
I had to do it, I've been abused and all I'm saying is.
It was like being drawn to the Earth Crater.
It's in my DNA.
Reunion had to happen.
It's what this is reunion.
That's right.
Oh Lord.
This really is reunion.
Is this a meta commentary Nomura?
Are you trying to...
He's made our lives Final Fantasy 7.
That's the real trick to all of it.
Playing the original infected us with Jenova cells and they're just trying to...
How likely is it that the ending is going to be like explicit one way or the other what
happened?
What happened with what?
Well you know at the very end there's the last cutscene where it's like it cuts to like
years in the future and you don't really know whether they survived or what happened
exactly.
Oh God.
No.
Well first of all there's...
I can't say anything.
But I don't fucking know.
I do know.
Can I make him explode?
I'm going to explode.
I do like the Sephiroth dialogue more than I thought I would even though he's you know
shoehorned in way earlier than he should be.
I mean like obviously they could not keep him a surprise like he was in the original
game.
That's just something that they could not replicate.
So I guess I understand the reasoning of like I mean like if like who doesn't know
who Sephiroth is like who doesn't know that he exists.
But I mean by that logic Jesse I mean I get like I was talking with some people about
this.
Final Fantasy 7 is different from other remakes because this game is like mostly known specifically
for its story as opposed to other games.
It's like it's two different games because like there's so much of it that has so much
attention to detail and is so clearly trying to be like a one to one representation of
the original game that is exactly perfect and exactly right.
But then there's also completely new shit and rearranged shit and stuff that's like totally
off the wall zany.
And it's like how are both of these philosophies coexisting in the same game.
It's Namora right.
That's what I would assume.
Yeah.
It's pretty clear.
Short hand answer for everything.
They just felt they needed filler and you know there's some sections of the filler that
I don't love at all.
I can't help as a guy who played the original but be aware every moment of every mission
that I'm like like this game is just wasting my time in between story beats that I know
are there.
I did like the one line where Cloud like first sees this apparition of Sephiroth and he's
like oh I killed you and Sephiroth is like you did or something like that like oh you're
dead.
He goes that's it.
He goes you're dead and Sephiroth goes I am like fuck you buddy I'm right here motherfucker.
I wish that they would just go crazy with it and have them talk like an idiot like it's
me I'm fucking Sephiroth buddy fucker I'm right here you're here to fuck up your day
dude.
That'd be cool.
Yeah I mean.
Well I'm like I am you know I'm sure that they're going to go over the top with this
and make Sephiroth like totally gay for Cloud like they always do now whereas like in the
original game Sephiroth like didn't really give a fuck about Cloud at any point.
You know Sephiroth's first line in Final Fantasy 7 to Cloud on the SS Junon or whatever
the ship's called.
It's literally who are you.
Yeah that's his line to Cloud.
Cloud was literally just a grunt who got lucky.
He's not like Sephiroth's fated rival.
In what way is Cloud any more important than any of those shambling like empty husks of
clones.
He's not.
And that's like all Sephiroth's dialogue is like he keeps saying you're nothing you're
nobody special you're a puppet you're my little fucking meat puppet to do what I want
you suck you're not even cool bro that's this is the whole problem the meta has infected
the shit it's all about like destiny now and shit that's uh it's like.
We'll get there.
Hey what one other point I was I was saying how much I like that heiress like rooftop
exploring I just fucking hate modern games and how like you you know like you know those
little arrows that you walk up to so that they're like an automatic motion going down
a ladder takes like 10 fucking hours every time ever jumping across a little gap the
charm of seeing Cloud slowly balance across a fucking beam as he walks along is not enough
to justify how much of my time is being wasted in the reactor where it has that section it's
like okay you've got to run fast when the when the lasers are off and it's like yeah like
I couldn't do it because when you press run he doesn't immediately run he has to go into
his animation of like starting to run because it has to be like a realistic thing now and
it's like that kind of modern games design I hope there's not more of those fucking lasers
because that sucked I think the thing that felt really drawing to me playing the demo
at least was that like when you're not in combat like the controls are different you know like
because you can't like swing the sword really or do any of the like movement stuff that you do
in combat outside of it because in the original game you have overworld controls and then you're
in turn based combat and I know they're trying to replicate that but it's like at the laser part
I'm like man if I had my fucking dodge roll right now I could get through this a lot easier
you know I am I'm constantly pressing R2 to run not realizing there's still an enemy on the screen
and it goes into like the tactical menu and it's just like a little thing around every time I'm
like god damn it I wanted to run that's just another really annoying thing the way like one of the
reasons I love Kingdom Hearts 2 so much is that like you're you do the same things all the time
there's no like in combat you do different stuff the control scheme is consistent and when you use
like a dry form or whatever like all you do is you get new abilities you haven't lost anything
why that like that gets changed in Kingdom Hearts 3 where you just like swap out movesets
why do video games still have a dedicated run button when the analog stick has been around for
literally 20 years well it's a sprint button in this case but I'd get what you said why do that
like why bother like why not just I mean I would assume you know I mean I was thinking about this
the other day like like um you know you push the stick to move and like why is there a slow
movement like why do you have to get running shoes in Pokemon there's no reason to walk yeah um
but I I've realized that I mean in certain small situations certain smaller areas where you need to
walk a short distance between things you don't want to overshoot it all the time that's true being
able to walk is useful I would rather have a Tom's point about the analog stick solves that yeah if
you just tilt it a little bit as opposed to the thing it's it's it's easier to just push the
direction all the way than it is to like but like it's not like it's not like daintily in the remake
you have because you're always gonna want to the thing is like in the remake you it's not like
you're running you're walking and running it's that you're running and then running a little bit
faster I mean that's it's very strange hey you know the only game the only game I recall that is silly
that did this well I was playing for my banjo video I was playing a little game called banjo
twoy in order to get this one jiggy there's a sleeping plant that you got to like really slow
creep up on for like an extended period of time and it was actually I was playing on an emulator
and it was like it was like literally impossible I had to remap the entire controller to get it to
work I was looking around apparently that's like a very common issue with that sequence of the game
but yeah you walk slow which is a little creepo sneak no noise animation you get the jiggy and
I was like this is the best game ever banjo twoy remake featuring genesis remember when uh in the
banjo twoy remake gruntilda came down and said uh banjo I will never be a memory I shall give you
despair banjo I loved that oh god the fucking the literal feathers that cloud keeps seeing
oh enough with the literal feathers I hate birds I hate birds man I hate birds the fucking wing
shit is this I hate it I've always hated it I'll always hate it you didn't have a fucking wing
one winged angel is not a literal fucking aspect of his character it's like a metaphorical it sounds
spooky like name of his fucking theme song he doesn't have to have a fucking wing I just like
the point it again sephiroth was literally never a one winged angel even in the original game what
he had was one arm got replaced with a wing when he turned into safer sephiroth for one fight and
that became he was like a weird judaeo christian like 15 winged angel yeah and it was fucking
based it was fucking sick why doesn't he turn to that instead of pull out his wing all the time
safer sephiroth fucking ruled but uh fucking whatever fucking new sephiroth always pulling
out his wing when no one wants to see it stupid ass I hate no thing but a chicken wing I'm gonna
fry that chicken wing sephiroth anyway Jesse you gotta let me know when you beat this game I would
I'm very eager to hear what you think you should do a video like a double I I've been recording
all my gameplay so I that's no doubt do something with it I I've been doing the PlayStation when I
see something happen that I'm like oh that made me smile and then I see another and I'm like oh
that made me fall into deep depression yeah do a snap that little shit thanks PlayStation for the
players speaking of speaking of PlayStation games I've been playing a better game than Final Fantasy
impossible uh Ratchet and Clank 2 I've been streaming it non-stop every single day I love
Ratchet and Clank 2 how's that going yeah it's going great I for the first time I've decided to 100
percent complete it doing all of the the special skill point things and and uh you know there's a
lot of secret shit in those games a lot of good stuff to find yeah I mean like compared to modern
games there's not like hundreds upon hundreds of thousands of millions of like checklists like
get 100 well yeah uh fucking it's what's known as a good game not a bad game yes it's a game that
has the no fluff in it and everything is good um and the combat's great and I've just been I've
had in the time of my life playing old video games hey why would you why would you ever need to play
a new video game what is the why do people spend money when Ratchet and Clank 2 already exists
because people don't want to spend time uh like analyzing what game would actually be like most
satisfying or enjoyable for them they just want the zeitgeist to present them with a new thing
to get on board with which I don't blame them for I mean people love being part of the zeitgeist
we were talking about that a few episodes ago like yeah people just love to be in the know
even if they don't give a shit or maybe it wasn't on the episode I was talking about this on
my stream on GibbonGaming.com youtube.com slash Gibbon Gaming where you can go and watch all
those streams they're all titled the same because I don't care and it's it's hard to understand
which part comes first um but um like the the the idea that um people will get into media more
so to be part of a conversation than they would to like enrich their lives or entertain themselves
uh like generally speaking if there's a new thing and everyone's talking about it you're like well
I I guess I should and you do it even though there's better things that you could be doing
and you know there are there's always like a big backlog of like the greatest things ever made
that you haven't got around to yet but it's not it's not culturally relevant right now
that sucks to give people to give people a little bit of credit like it's not purely malicious at
least from the consumer side because a lot of people they're just they just you know things are
just presented and they're like yeah sure okay I mean I'll watch that so it's not you know it's
just a product of the way we live I just like you know there's been like um some reservation uh of
like playing the same game over and over again forever like I only play like 20 games and they're
all ps2 games and then sometimes it's Dark Souls it's like I I'm I'm missing out on all of these
great experiences but I'm also having a lot of fun and I don't really care so I don't know how to
feel about it hmm yeah I don't know everyone's just got to decide how they want to live and what
they want to do you know there's nothing wrong with playing the same game over and over your whole
life because I mean you know how much will your life real will your fucking soul level up if you
play more games versus playing the same games to a degree sure it'll give you more experience
but these things are all fairly arbitrary in what you do with your life anyways I was just
thinking about it because it's like if you personally are bored then obviously try something new
um yep but like I just am able I mean I can't play the same game like multiple times in a row
all the way through but there's a health there's like a enough games in my like nostalgia rotation
I can just sort of loop back around and doing doing you know I played Okami recently yeah
I told him I know you've beaten that I think I just did a few days ago it was fucking sick
what do you think uh it was fucking great it's the best Zelda game ever made
because it's actually fun and not gay and formulaic and like it it obscures the formulaic nature of
the Zelda format in a way that's much more fun and you can like zendots things and slice them in
half and the brush techniques are all fucking lit the game looks gorgeous uh the puzzles aren't like
overly obtuse or annoying except for some of them what we need is an Okami remake in HD like you
know you know we just need to no no no I mean like we need to remake the game like fix the stuff that
was bad like the art style for example we need realism we need realism we got to get rid of
the game the game unironically was originally going to be a realistic style you go when you
beat the game you unlock the original alpha trailer and it was a realistic game yeah and then they
changed it at some point that is amazing I gotta go check that out sometime there was another
trailer that you unlock for beating the game where uh there's like another older build of the game
where the reflector that Amaterasu carries around is like a fucking cannon and you just like fight
all these other guys and blow shit up I was like I want to play this bill what the fuck that does
look sick and then if you dig back far enough you find the true alpha version of the game
simply known as road toads and things would just expand from there yeah think about it they're
very similar a little thing rides a bigger thing that moves it around how is that not road toads I
ask you it's the same game yeah you soon looked a little different in road toads it was a toad
it all worked out in the end yeah okami's great uh it's so good I loved it and uh I'm really mad
that I was 12 demon fangs away from s ranking the entire game without even realizing I had no
ideas being ranked on my performance could you not go back and just get those to achieve an s
rank perhaps I don't know well if you know the save file you probably can yeah but it's just like
the joy of like just accidentally s ranking the game on your first playthrough that makes sense
it's just this that serendipitous moment was just taken away from me and uh I'll never forgive myself
for such dismal failure alas alas there's so many fun ways to play a game speed running trying to s
rank everything I don't know just being a yeah I feel like idiot not even beating the story playing
playing a game over and over again I think it's like a precursor to trying to speed run it like I
tried to speed run retching clank 2 to get to the new game plus where like the game is actually
a lot better because they have the bolt multiplier yeah if you if you don't get hit you can multiply
the bolts you get and you get times 20 and then you get a load of money and then you're rich and
buy loads of guns um but like speed running is hard and I couldn't do it but I did manage to beat
the whole game like in six hours on stream so that's not bad wait okami no no no retching
clank 2 and I got to the new game plus and I've been streaming that at a reasonable pace getting
all the skill points uh yeah I'm thinking of doing like once I've done that I'll do retching
clank 3 do the exact same thing and then I'll do jack and dexter jack 2 jack 3 and then slide 2
slide 3 and I'll just be like a playstation stream boy hell yeah it's it's it's the perfect
version of like what hypocrites should have been it's not like hypocrite was just my excuse to play
these games again and analyze them and figure out why why they're so cool and explain to people
why they're cool but I realized while streaming that I can do that analysis on the fly with examples
so it's it's just a lot easier to just play the game and then say oh this bit this is right
and here's why uh and then like oh this part is bullshit and here's why although I do go on a lot
of like um angry rants when it's not actually bullshit uh because I'm like a rager I'm like a
rage gamer I'm a big rage quit guy and I love that about myself it's the coolest thing about me
is that I rage quit things and I and I say no I respect it greatly it's fucking cool yeah
that's sick dude that's sick you should title them slightly more and uh informationally so that
anyone can discern one from the other just a little you should title them less informationally you
should title them like just like strings of shit you should title them uh in some way so that when
I go to your homepage the names form like some ascii art thing that I can you know put the pieces
it's like a big smiley face you should just title them video game one video game two video game
footage just no parts just video game every single video human person plays video game on stream
yeah but he's also sounds great god I I want to be done with this fucking remake so bad I
want to just set me free I've got probably 10 hours to go at least oh god I'm at the uh I'm at
the pillar falling part right now when I was going down you know I started playing like a second run
of resident evil 3 right before like this came out yeah because like and like like you said like
you play it more and you get faster at it it's like a precursor to the speed running so like I'm
playing at the second time and realizing that like I complained about it being too short originally
it's even shorter than I thought now that I know where everything is I'm just like I'm done with it
in five minutes then I'm like and I'm like oh my god should I play it again to get this stupid
like extra knife and this stupid unlimited sorry if I don't even want it I don't even want to like
what is the point of these of these power-ups for a game I don't even want to play anymore I'm just
like by the end of it I was like please Final Fantasy 7 remake deliver me from this set me free
from resident evil 3 even if you're bad so is there any upside to playing it again have you
discovered any joys you missed no it was bullshit they gave you like you get like store points to
like buy like these meaningless upgrades but all the upgrades suck and the one that I bought was like
for like 7 000 points it's like a hot knife and it's like oh this sick yeah this hot knife
this hot knife will carve through but zombies like fucking butter yeah bro speaking of speaking of
store points uh have you seen this shit by any chance have you uh uh you better need not lay a
finger on my butter finger says cloud strife in canon of Final Fantasy 7 remake by two participating
products upload your receipt and score unique dlc for the Final Fantasy 7 remake an exclusive ps4
dynamic theme container I saw an image of this I thought it was a joke it was just an image of
you get dlc bro finger next to him as much as I can see cloud being a butter finger guy I don't
approve of this anyways he's just sort of like staring at you like you're gonna buy one it's
just his default art from like the fucking by the and jesse jesse I don't know if this perplexes you
for decades I have been continually vexed by the fact that every fucking incarnation of cloud
strife has his fucking uniform a different color yes is it purple is it blue is it black he
literally looks black here in the game he usually looks blue sometimes it's a little purple just
making purple it's like it's like there are times when like the lighting you look at it like oh I
guess that almost kind of looks purple or blue baby but then the rest of the time it looks black
depend you know it's like just settle on a color just make it purple it was always purple the original
purple is an unrealistic color jesse it's not too unrealistic we can't have that in the game it's
that's hokey 90s purple it's not purple it's just so fucking unrealistic but that spiky hair that
defies gravity that's the realism I want to go back to the 90s I miss when things were colorful
and fun and cool what happened it wasn't even like downplayed purple or cloth purple it was just
bright one solid brick of a color purple the whole game no matter what the lighting was inside
outside didn't matter always so retarded that you had a main character just wearing this giant
purple fucking jumpsuit I fucking loved it uh you know what gives me like more joy I'll just
be walking along and in the distance I will see it's almost like character designs like standing
out and being cool like is good in a video game I just see the little bit of it's it's this it's
this one thing the red on Tifa's gloves I don't know why I get such emotional comfort by seeing
that there's like some color on Tifa's design yes it's just that beautiful red color everything
else is like realistic and gritty and like low color but the bright red they toned it down too
there used to be more but just something about that it makes me happy imagine imagine it's like
Naruto with this big orange jumpsuit it was like remade and he had like a like a light brown
sort of like a leather coat remakes her mistake bro remakes like oh it's more realistic he blends
in the dark he's like no Naruto is stupid he needs to be he's a fucking idiot that that it forms
his character almost that he's so stupid that he wears yeah that's a question yellow that's a
thing to ponder does cloud wearing purple do anything for his character well and not really
not really know although it's always been weird to me that okay just in the even in the original
we see other soldiers specifically only they are like enemies in battle sometimes you will
occasionally fight like soldier third class soldier second class maybe even first class I
can't remember or not if those are an enemy somewhere they they're wearing like blue and
red if I remember you like never see another purple wearing soldier except for Zach so I did I
don't know did cloud steal his clothes why is what is Zach wear purple I don't know uh like
that's one of those things that's like that's a detail that's in his head I assume that's the
I just assume that like if it is like a part of his memory is like uh Zach likes purple and then
so cloud also does maybe well it seems like the the soldier's first class we're just told look
there's kind of a uniform that you can wear but you can pretty much dress however the hell you
want Sephiroth you can get away with with dressing like a outer space biker I don't give a shit you
know which is cool yeah I mean that that would make sense to me it's just that I mean guys guys
guys we need to make a remake to answer this question why the fuck uh okay you know what it
doesn't matter it's been retconned he literally wears blue now uh as did all the fucking soldiers
in crisis corps which thank god that game came into existence and you know made Zach the literal
plot device that he was into the I do not understand why people love Zach so much I don't
fucking understand it I love Zach before you were fucking born you piece of shit and I loved him for
the right reasons yeah and in fact I loved him less when crisis corps came out because crisis corps
was lame and stupid and made because they flanderized him to fucking hell they made him like literally
Jesus and like angel wings and shit god it you look like you look like you're a guy who hates thing
when you have any kind of like criticism of thing and they like it's like oh we're the heroes man
we're the fucking heroes who want more good fucking what's his face being a god but no I
fuck you you're stupid if you like if you like crisis corps you are stupid what are you what are
you fucking hey hey guys what are you going on hashtag just slurping I got pasta remember remember
when you did that during the buster cast and all the half the comments are just like Ben why are you
doing I I did hear about that literally what one comment one comment was like wait a minute I
cannot listen to this because there's a yeah there are like two comments on that video when I look
at guys I've got I've got an update oh this is fascinating uh okay I was slightly wrong about
this I'm looking back at the enemy design of finalized seven characters and we can see because
there are soldier enemies that you fight in places you fight I found it at the very least
there's a soldier third class and a soldier first class that are like fodder enemies you know obviously
the first class is like a late game enemy or whatever are they like the soldier first classes
they do wear purple and brown boots exactly as cloud wears basically you're talking about the
file fancy seven original yeah here look at this look at this right here yeah but are those like
soldier or are all those like soldiers you know like this is a wikipedia entry for soldier first
as a soldier first class which you fight sector eight when you return to midgar later in the game
and there you fucking go it looks just like I mean they're a little darker but that's that's
clouds costume yeah that's fucking clouds outfit weird there you go that guy I yeah I don't remember
you do fight a couple of soldiers man I really like soldier soldier itself is one of the most
undeveloped fucking things in final fantasy seven and they thought that crisis core was like the
right way to flesh it out it was not it was not the right way to flesh it out uh they fucked it
like a daytime soap it was like the most homo erotic like weird pansy shit it was just like
this constant like like the whole the entire game soundtrack is just wonderwall being played
like drunkenly in the background while all these characters are soliloquizing that's that's that's
soliloquizing that's a word that's that's a sick remix of non non biori and wonderwall which I will
put in the links down below and you should listen to it because it's great uh every fine okay you
make a game everybody loves it then you make a sequel and you have to take the things that the
people loved and you make them like way more important than they ever were intended to be
originally because the meta has infected your story holy shit soliloquize is a word
soliloquize I knew I was fucking smart ah whatever soliloquize well it just sounded so wrong coming
out of me like I've never actually spoken the verb of soliloquy before hey you know what else
is beautiful I you remember the fucking hard edge remember the hard edge from final master seven
which is that weird ass fucking sword which is like a blunt tip yeah it kind of fans out and it's
got sick ass kanji on it that I don't know what it means but it's fucking cool that that hey guess
what that weapon it's in the game uh it's cool I love final fantasy seven uh just looking at it
makes me happy this whole game is kind of you know that really hd like incredibly sexy designed
that like some girl did of tifa that like leaked onto the internet somewhere as like her fucking
senior project that should have been this whole game one in the game I mean it's so much better I
mean it's incredibly hot it's pretty sexualized so I get why they wouldn't use it but like the whole
game has a lot of just that it's just that making things real making it amazing uh and making it
fucking 3d texture I can see the fabric like a little like
bestiary and like read about all the little enemies you fight and like the assessment area
being like more robust and like having little paragraphs just a little paragraph about everything
I fight is so cool and adds so much to it wait are you get do you guys think the final fantasy
seven remake is good we've been we've been debating that we amongst ourselves it is a very complicated
issue Ben I think even you Ben if you played it to simply be able to control okay after the
fucking two hours of mandatory scripted scenes of literally like not gameplay when you finally get
to like seventh heaven and you look around town you see tifa and you look up at the plates of
midgar and you're like holy shit they made this real it's like I think it's almost impossible to
not be stunned it's so good in every way except that it's filled with dumb bullshit that sucks
Ben I will be I would love to regale you with the tales of the massive failures of the game
you are telling me does not sound cool at all you really you think so yeah well if you if I like
fan art of things I like fan art of final fantasy seven I I enjoy such things as as fan art this
game is like the best fan art ever made I think we're just an agreement here that like just seeing
the stuff is in itself a cool experience but like there's an internal war going on inside me every
second I'm playing between what sucks and what's cool I don't want to be unfair and I even want to
give them credit that like a lot of it can be annoying and just gets in the way and I don't
think the dialogue is particularly well written overall but there are moments of just like chilling
in this world with like a little bit of ambient dialogue that does just make shit feel fucking
real like what I've always wanted the child I can't deny there are two wolves and one wolf
sucks and one wolf doesn't suck and which one is stronger is the one you feed one wolf is cringe
and the other is base exactly that's right and then they found it wrong I don't know I guess I'd
have to see it but I hope there's there's issues oh boy none of us have yet beaten the game so like
well I've heard and I've seen much of the the ending and what they do with it I'm waiting to see
sex bathtub scene I don't know yet I I don't want to spoil it but I mean well okay I'll just say
that's gone no that that's gone they cut that now there is other extremely homoerotic things
happening so like I'm sure many will be satisfied but that particular thing is not in the game
you know that's what I like I want I want good old-fashioned physical homoeroticism not lame
emotional homoeroticism like in crisis bro they've got the worst of all worlds they've got anime
homoeroticism I saw a clip or a gift or something of like going to like buy panties so that cloud
can be sexy for don something and he can wear this the women's underwear and it's like okay
lol you didn't do that there's definitely other stuff walking around a wall market in general
like again as a tech demo is like holy shit this is like this is amazing to see the fucking lights
and see Don Cornio's mansion and I don't know meet the amazing donut steel new OCs that have been
added I mean that part sucks but uh I don't know it's it there's so much going on in my brain
when I play this game it really is like very painful does does it feel like Final Fantasy 7
at times it really does at times it absolutely does at other times no at other times no it
does not um I mean we talked about it for a while but like when like there's a new soldier third
class guy who just comes in and is the most like advent children like retarded OC over the top crisis
core motherfucker that guy fucking sucks the fight with him was fun but you know the combat's a
separate thing that guy sucks uh was annoying oh and of course I mean they fucking introduced the
motorcycle chase stuff early on yeah man Final Fantasy 7 had so many like amazing one-off little
minigames yeah playing through that game is it's like holy shit like a new minigame just
unlike apropos fucking nothing it never uses the same trick like more times than it needs to
you know most of them it only happens once you know and if you want to do them again you go to the
yeah the gold saucer as a containment area for like replaying minigames you loved so cool just
snowboarding oh my god I love snowboarding in that fucking game yesterday could ever possibly imagine
because there's young which makes them automatically stupid and capable of forming thoughts but just
try you know to imagine you know you're playing a game and you think the game is just this for like
12 hours and then all of a sudden out of nowhere there's a crazy cool motorcycle chase that you've
never seen before in a video game in your life because it's a PlayStation one and the graphics
are mind-blowing to you and you know then you go out and you think like okay this whole game takes
place in a city and then you get out of the city and you go what the hell there's a whole planet
to explore what not in this game baby not in this fucking game there is one city to explore
you know I feel like a lot of people I'm definitely gonna talk about that when I make a video but
like I feel like a lot of people will say things like like okay modern games are filled with like
basically what you guys are describing here like like busy work and like side stuff you don't have
to do like I played darts in this game I thought that was pretty fun I enjoyed the little dart
minigame and I won and I got a little prize for it that was cool but I don't know it's I guess it's
hard to articulate but it's just a matter of like context it's probably the fact that like
Final Fantasy 7 as a game originally is so consistent in that there's like two modes of
operation you're running around talking to people or you're in combat it's super consistent
nothing any deviation from that felt like a side quest they were side quests the game was packed
with side quests but none of it felt like you're just going to some point on a map that says like
oh this activates a quest Jesse you tell me you tell me you enjoyed going to hunt those fucking rats
as a side mission in this game you can't you can't tell me you enjoyed that I actually like it forced
a laugh out of me like a like a snide contemptuous laugh because like it's so generic every RPG
you start out with a rat mission at the beginning like they had generic is the keyword yeah for these
additions and like oh don't you love meeting this amazing cast of characters of like nameless
shop owner number one yeah I don't know I didn't hate those you know there's a there's another big
veneer here and it's just another modern games thing I fucking hate voice acting I just want it
gone I just wanted gone from all games I don't give a fuck if you need voice acting to get attached
to a game it literally makes it worse because then I can hear these terrible English voice actors
just give me text I can fill in the blanks I don't need voices yeah when it when it's when it's
voice acting genuine question has voice acting ever made a game better well okay such a thing
is good performances do exist Metal Gear Solid okay it is a game famous for its voice actor
okay um I'll give you that one okay some games it makes sense other games it does not I would
argue that because this game has such a retarded story and has so many fucking weird stupid plot
details and they insist on shoving so many characters in our faith I have actually war
men or memories of many of like remember when cloud went into like in the sector seven slums
next to seventh heaven you walk into a house and there's like that section where it's like cloud
lecturing those guys on like how to fight like what combat is there's a lot of really funny
dialogue laced in there about cloud being cocky those guys being like teach a sensei like come on
bro teaches what to do as text I like all that stuff when it's voiced it feels forced and overdone
and annoying and I'm gonna I'm gonna disagree with you I I agree with the spirit of your argument
but but I think I'm in the camp of in this game so far I've thought I've been very very impressed
by the voice casting and acting and the dialogue I think it's all been really good I mean like
whoever the name is who's playing Tifa like as soon as I heard her talk I'm like oh my god that
sounds good like that sounds how I'd want her to sound whereas I think before she was played by
Christy Carlson Romano and Advent Children and it just sounded like a girl you know but she
sounds like she's got some years lived in her you know she sounds like she's got some city miles
and I suppose I know what you mean and like Barrett I think is perfect I think like he nails
like the Barrett being tough but he also nails the Barrett being sweet with his daughter and stuff
and like you can buy that this character has like a heart exterior and has a good heart
kind of like my favorite character I mean I've always fucking loved Barrett he's just
wonderful to see although he's legitimately scary sometimes he kind of scares me because he's so big
and I fear black men you know just across the board I'm assuming that cloud is still Steve
Burton like he's been for years I think he's really good in this game better if it is the same
guy it comes off like it's a lot better in this game I don't know and like this the dialogue to me
for the most part feels like real people talking and it's better than I thought it would be and like
I said it takes an immediate nosedive as soon as crisis course shows up on his fucking motorcycle
you know just to be clear none of my complaint I mean I don't know I think a lot of it is kind of
generically anime like dub voice stuff like I tried to do in Japanese I was like I can't tell
these fucking gooks are saying fuck this shit I went back to English the one the one that I don't
like as much though is wedge I oh I liked wedge he had like a unique kind of raspy yeah he sounds
like a like a really like a sweet little fat boy um but I don't like I don't like that all of his
dialogue is about being fat well I was going to say the problem is the writing not the voice
yeah that's the one area where I'm like can't wedge say something different besides
flanderization I mean I I don't know if you agree but I would start like flanderization is the theme
of this game is it really flanderization in wedges case because he didn't actually say much of
anything in the original okay no I was gonna say he has always been like a silly character who wasn't
that serious so that that's fair he was always like a cloud fanboy so they got that aspect oh you
know what actually I take it back because he has there's more to him just being fat but I thought
they were laying it on a little bit thick with the constant I'm running on empty guys I need pizza
and my fat little piggy belly but it's so relatable though but it's a symptom of the disease and
quota whatever of because there's just more stuff characters need to say because we need to give them
more lines like the writers are sitting there like okay what do we got for wedge like what can we
have this guy say and they just think we know one thing and one thing alone about wedge that he's fat
we this is why we have like the design bible right you're flipping you got like
character sketches and like bios is written in like wedge it's just blank they're like
scrambled to come up with some something to say about them you know I think Ben you I bet you
would agree with me look this is the thing kumars and waifu heads are gonna fucking love this shit
I hate it what and it is exactly how I believe it's that how much they have cranked up Jesse's
obsession with cloud oh my god she is so fucking thirsty oh didn't she just like damn did she just
like I okay honestly I don't really remember what Jesse was like are you she oh I remember like him
or did she just like think he was yes because he was like really strong she did she did like him she
was flirty and she was kind of like a klutz all of that is in the game but there's like a lot more
of the first thing that's what I'm saying about flanderization they're they were like in their
design bible what do we know about Jesse like okay she was kind of the smart one okay we can keep
that also she loves cloud well this is advent children writing boys let's crank that shit up to 11
she worship is the fucking ground he walks on she's so into him instantly I was like I was like
Jesse it makes her pathetic yeah at a certain point I was like okay why is she this thirsty
and then like there is kind of like a line that lampshades it a little bit where wedge is like
hey cloud uh just so you know don't fall for it she just likes to fuck with guys
you know I'm like I don't know wedge maybe she just likes to fuck with you because that might be
believable if we if we ever saw her flirt with another man ever at any point but we don't and
there's only directly apart where it's like one character's like oh uh bigs is pretty neurotic
and like the next time you see bigs he's like sweeping outside of his house like doing like
you're gonna rabbit from Winnie the Pooh shit like yeah like he wasn't doing anything neurotic
before that line but then someone said it and now it's like oh don't yes I am now that you
mentioned it I'm sweeping the dirt outside my house for some reason I did think I oh boy I did
really like I mean she's not just flirty they did try to make more to her I really like the
mission going to her house bro I want to be an actress I fucking hated it I hate it all oh my
god I loved just like I liked how that was the moment where cloud started to warm up because he
sneaks into the house and he sees her dad with mako poisoning mako poisoning if I can whatever
I'm calling it mako I don't give a shit exactly mako poisoning and so then you know you're talking
to bigs and wedge outside and there's that scene where they're walking down the street just kind
of talking about her upbringing and how she came to join avalanche and you can you can see that cloud
is like kind of like understanding and like relating to the mako poisoning stuff because
like he's bent through all kinds of like mako infusions shit as we'll find out more of later
and he's just like yeah okay and it's like I like I love that little scene it was like really kind of
heartwarming and like kind of like uh like as like you know the fucking Stephen King or the boys
in the woods they find the body you know it was like that kind of feeling and I was like yeah
I like this so they I don't know maybe they'll flesh her out even more but I like the flushing
you know I didn't hate it but let's not forget there's that section and then the roche like
thing happens immediately afterward I know everything good that I want to say it's don't
forget then then that guy shows up and and the other thing is I have to weigh that okay we get
some additional characterization of Jesse I think it okay it's it's okay I don't I don't hate it
instantly but I mean it's filled with like dialogue of of wedge bill oh my belly's so full of the
midgar special pizza I want to eat a whole pizza myself just see oh please uh but the and then
I'm weighing that at every moment in my head which I think is totally fair to do
versus you know what happened in the original cloud went to sleep and then we got to the next
reactor mission and it was fucking sick uh and like I'm just thinking like I could be doing that
right now I could be moving the plot forward I could be you know I don't know I like to have
the time to breathe and like walk around the slums and do the side missions I had plenty as it was
but I get your point just watched gun buster and die buster and been once again reminded
that shorter is always better there's never a time when a story can be made longer and better
you have to choose one uh yeah I don't know um the idea that like oh they just they just expanded
all these character traits and like made it last a lot longer is kind of like oof I don't know about
that I don't know about that you gotta ask the quite like so they're expanding them they're
filling in more detail who's writing that dialogue to what end and I I mean my general argument would
be like overall it's not worth it they're not adding enough to these characters to justify
like they kind of have to because like that that's another it's a totally separate thing
once it was decided they were making a game out of a tenth of a game they had to fill that time
so there like was no option so like you can fucking game gonna be bro they haven't told us
anything about that no one knows it's totally a mystery but I can tell you that this game
encompasses about four hours of the original out of like a 40 50 hour game that's you know
a tenth of the runtime I can't I can't fucking wait till the ps6 comes out so I can finally buy
Final Fantasy 7 remake complete edition on four discs won't that be fun well it's gonna be really fun
when the initial parts look terrible compared to the end parts and it you know yeah well thanks
they'll have to remake the remake well I'm glad Square Enix figured out how they're gonna stay
afloat for the next 20 years I I mean I still I still insist okay economic times are you actually
can't wait for Nate Nate at the ripe old age of 50 recording his podcast about the end of Final Fantasy
7 I'll be there baby I'll be there you know I've got a little story to tell just to put a cap on this
well first of all I don't um uh I I think given what I know about the end of this game I I think
by prediction will come true that I think sales for volume two or whatever it's called will be
nothing compared this game has been very successful of course it has yeah I think that the next one
will not be similar what what if they just like they sold the first one it was wildly successful
but they're like okay but the sequel will never be as successful so we're just we're just they might
just gonna call it here they might know what I would not even blame them or be surprised if they
did that not at all not at all uh but here's my quick little story it's just when I was a kid in
in like middle school and high school me and my friends all loved this game and we talked about
it and we we even back in fucking like 2001 like 2000 even before that fucking 99 and shit
we were like okay maybe not 99 a couple years later it came out in 97 probably like 2004-2005
when they were starting to legitimately make remasters of Final Fantasy 1 and 2 and 4 and
Fidever got one neither did 6 but like and Final Fantasy 4 got like a 3d remake on the DS
Final Fantasy anthology on the ps1 there you go which is uh that's one and two or is that
five and six five and six right right when they released those on PlayStation one
back in the day so okay boy like my mind has been filled with the prospect of a Final Fantasy 7
remake since I was a fucking child I've been dreaming of it coming out and you know it's not
just about me me and my friends we we basically made a pact that whatever happened we would like
at the time we were kids we were like man we'll buy whatever console imagine we might buy a ps3
if we have to to get this remake we'll save up our pennies and we'll save our allowance when we're
like 30 that's right when we're 45 you know what's happened since then every single one of those
friends has lost interest I am the only one left of that group who still cares I was just talking
to my college friends the other day none of them care they have all lost it's only me now I'm aware
this game is successful but I think that is very interesting I know exactly who they're marketing
this to and it's not me and uh I just think it's and now that it's here and I'm seeing what they're
doing with it now that I mean I basically know what the ending is uh I just there's just I don't
know what I'm saying there's just no no respect and in my mind there's no hope uh for I mean look
I gave up hope years ago years ago I gave up hope we knew again that there would be no respect
and no hope and like you said there there's parts that are good man this part that some people cared
some people loved what they were doing uh but like the I mean what's most important this is a story
driven game the fact that like there is are even you Jesse have gotten to parts where they've said
like we need to change destiny things need to be we need to set right things that are wrong
like the the the ghosts the time ghosts that show up at the very beginning to fuck with things uh
is there is there a fucking point is there maybe some
like plot thing in final phase seven that's considered like maybe like a sad event or
like a tragic event that like maybe we might want to try to avoid maybe something that might be like
one of the most iconic spoilers in all of all time is there something like that in five of seven
I I can't think of anything but uh you know it would sure be okay stop stop dancing around
and spoiling shit without spoiling it Nate I know what you're getting at I can fucking read
between the lines here enough yeah we can stop talking about this I want to be surprised by at
least something yeah okay okay and again I'm just this is just speculation but the only
like positive thing as someone who has no context just listening to this conversation
the only positive thing that I can possibly see of like the crazy fan boys and that comes around
from final fantasy seven is that if the hardcore fans like you Nate are super pissed off by this
entire project when it hits pc you know someone's gonna mod out all the bullshit and they'll have
like the fan director cut where it's just like all the good shit and all the bad shit's gone
and you'll just have that and and you'll just be able to get it from the fucking nexus and it'll
be fine again I I don't want them to keep raping my game I just uh would prefer they did not do
that personally I will seek all right so we've talked a lot about a game that is maybe
maybe good maybe bad maybe kind of bad let's talk about a game that is unequivocally good
that is perfect okay let's talk about animal crossing guess do you guys play animal crossing
we are all stuck inside we're all quarantined it's it's animal crossing season baby it's the
opposite of that one summer when everyone went out and played pokemon go now is the plague times
when everyone's stuck at home playing animal crossing this is what we're doing hey hey we're
recording this on bunny day uh ben have you obtained all the recipes as a matter of fact
I am the king of easter yes I'm I'm one away I'm a one away and I don't know where to find it
who's driving just just pop balloons I was also one way actually uh okay I think I found it on the
beach in a bottle but just pop balloons I already checked the beach god damn it so you are playing
it yeah yeah I'm playing it I bought it uh two weeks ago maybe three that's epic okay let me let me
tell you let me tell you what I'm doing let's visit each other's islands Ben we should visit each
other's islands let me what I'm doing right now my wait what fruit do you have what fruit do you
have apples oh I've got oranges and peaches I what we've based my my roommate has already found
peaches and oranges on like random god damn it with the one we need is pears we are only missing
pears um you should head to idub's girlfriend's island uh she's a pear shaped head that's the joke
okay so my my project right now is um I am uh I am trying to breed roses balloons right now I'm
breeding roses I looked up a guide it's I want to I want to make I want to bleed breed black
roses and purple roses and you have to you have to do all this bullshit you have to you
have to plant them in a certain way and like wait and my my rose beds have been planted for days
I have I have created two black roses and one purple rose and today a freak anomaly occurred
and somehow a pink rose was bred out of what red roses which is not supposed to be able to happen
nevertheless there it is staring me in the face in defiance of all facts and logic can you transpose
flowers between areas without destroying them because I've had issues with that do you have to
dig them up correctly you just dig them up you can't you can't destroy them unless you sell them
or okay okay cool yeah in fact you can even water them dig them up and replant them and they're
still watered sick for the rest of the day um based uh you know yeah I upgraded my house yeah I gave
it some cool like skull pattern carpeting uh you know yeah yeah I gave it a black roof uh yeah I
built like a cool like a wrought iron and stone like fence around the whole thing um yeah I'm gonna
move to like live up in like a scary castle on the top of the highest hill uh yeah you know it's all
pretty good then provide pictures please I want to see it I will try to get some pictures I lost my
switch charger on some trip somewhere so I can't play any well hey that's okay it just
uses a usbc you can uh you can get a cheap one of those I can do a what it's it's a usbc uh like
generic uh plug I'm literally using my phone charger right now to charge my switch yeah cool
it could be done there you go you're welcome hippo are you gonna say something no I was just
well yes I was uh there's a balloon I found a balloon please have my last recipe it's gotta be
an egg balloon it is an egg balloon oh my god is this it live please oh it's a fucking sky egg I'm
sorry you're gonna need those sky eggs for the final right spoilers but after you get the final recipe
he gives you another recipe that you have to then craft I've got a million eggs I can trade them in
for that I'll be I'll be good it's it's like this is a perfect example but um
animal crossing has been extremely amusing to me because everybody I know is playing it
and um a lot of the people I know playing it are big gamers and this this cute little fun game about
like having animals and a house on an island has most of the discussion I see is like hardcore
gamer goon like min maxing like strategizing graphics like graphs like like spreadsheets of like
it's it's so intense maximizing your returns on the stock market return at price it's hell yeah
dude hell yeah it's so much of that it's really funny to listen to have you guys seen Hideki Kamiya
is like tweeting tons of animal crossing shit that he's playing right now he's got like a weird like
he's got just like his ground laid out with like sorted massive amounts of items like on the on
his fucking open field I don't know what he's doing but uh he's doing something and it's very
interesting it's just like if I were to play the game I don't have a switch but if I did uh you
know I would I would consider it because it's it looks pretty cute and I've never played an animal
crossing game before but like to be in the conversation is like everybody is talking about
like extreme shit and I would probably just be like chopping logs or doing whatever like I
missed my chance to invest in the stock market um today because I was too late to catch the uh the
turnip pig another balloon it's just so funny no idea if I'd even like animal crossing I've never
played it before I have like pocket cam installed on my iPad I figured to give that a shot you know
Tom I think you like the actual I played I played the old um I played the old one on the like the
the 3ds uh yeah uh yeah I think I played new leaf um and like I was into it for a while you know
eventually I you know I fully upgraded my house got on my island taken care of and I was like okay
I did everything I keep thinking maybe I'll just start playing animal crossing and then I look at
my computer and the little doom eternal icon I'm like I'd much rather kill demons again I just
play I mean I still to beat the fucking last level of doom eternal I think animal crossing is pretty
fun you know the way the way to play at hardcore I don't know like it's tell me please I want the
stretch well I mean maybe I'm doing it wrong but all you do is you just um like you have the little
like nook miles plus uh mini goals you just you just do those yep like you just run around doing
those and everything else takes care of itself you do those uh and yeah that's that's true pretty
much that incentivizes you do you do those and then what do you do with any recipes that you think
look really cool and you want like a cool leather sofa or something yeah well what do you do with
the miles though because you can cash them in to go to different islands you yeah you explore other
islands you spend that well you I mean have you like upgraded your inventory oh I one time yes
oh dude get the final get the full inventory upgrade how big is it like how many you can get
two upgrades up to four rows okay why the fuck have I not done that already all right yeah um
that's what I need I mean yeah I'm pretty much at the point where I don't have anything essential
to spend my miles on anymore so yeah yeah it all just just buying like telephone poles and street
lamps and stuff just put out you know you know I I was given a fucking uh one of those oh I bought
the uh the god's giant Godzilla that's that's hanging out next to my town hall now actually
just this morning isabel moved in the wife who was here boys whip your dicks out wait here we go oh
I expanded okay because I um my friend had already been playing because right because
there's only one island per switch so my friend had already been on the island he had already
done a bunch of stuff he had built like a couple of bridges and things so I moved in and like the
town hall is already built there's already bridges and stuff like I already have access to the store
so I kind of had it easy because he did he like took care of a lot of the bullshit
he gave me some stone so I could make axes like right off the out the gate you know uh I do have
a little story about Animal Crossing this is I was thinking of making a video but now my brain
has just been consumed by uh by uh the remake the final seven remake and stuff so like I still might
make this this might be one of those instances where me talking about it means I'll never make it
but fuck it I can get it out there somewhere it's just that so I was playing Animal Crossing and
there's a certain point you hit okay there's this feature that when you when you eat a fruit uh and
it makes your like you're like super effective and so yeah mistakenly I accidentally shattered
like every rock on my island they grow like the first day they do grow back but this was extremely
frustrating me when I realized what I had done uh and for like two days I was getting like no iron
and it was at the point where your bottleneck where you have to give them iron to like upgrade to like
build the the shop or whatever to to keep like the progression of the town going or whatever oh okay
yeah I never had to do that sure sure but I did though because I'm Michelle and I are both playing
but I play more than she does um a typical man you know the woman just fucking dragging her ass um
but uh a man's a man's place is in is in the home building furniture catching butterflies
planting flowers and doing interior decorating um and whatnot so I uh so the the bottleneck of that
iron ore was making me see to put it lightly and for days I was getting like two iron at a time
because I had so few rocks and because it was also um you know Easter season so I was getting those
fucking eggs instead of any fucking I'm so excited that the eggs will be gone I hate them every time I
hit a rock and eggs pop out I'd like one of my dick pops out and I have to jack it out of rage
it's infuriating yeah uh that's how it goes so so I was even doing you know you use the thing you
travel to other islands I haven't I have literally I have never found a fossil I only find what
eggs yes insane that's crazy yeah uh truly shocking truly shocking well yeah eggs need to
fucking die and they'll be gone tomorrow thank god um so I was bottlenecked with this iron ore
it made me so pissed and you know I was like uh you know what fuck this game this game's literally
bad uh it's terrible it wastes my fucking time and of course you have to say every action in the
game is designed to be comfy as opposed to efficient and like give you a little like talk you talk to
people oh they'll tell you about your day you walk into the store they waste a full second of your
life as they say hello instead of just letting you walk in and get your fucking business trading
trading eggs trading eggs with the Easter Bunny one at a time one at a time it takes forever it's
a nightmare it takes like 12 lines of dialogue just to do it I can't you have to click so many
fucking menus okay it's awful so so at a certain point I said you know what literally fuck this game
I'm never playing it again I'm gonna go play fucking factorial so I'd never played factorial but I
wait when was this this was I mean this all happened within the last like seven ten days something like
that earlier today it was like a week ago or something um so I I started playing factorial
and I was like oh god yes uh this this game is designed for efficiency it feels so fucking good
it's like it's like um oh shit what's that fucking game we have got it on this switch
it's that game where you build an island and you aim to animal crossing new horizons it's
something like that no wait it's right there on my menu forager it's like forager combined with
like starcraft so it's just about building buildings make an efficient and it's it's
amazing I've seen destiny play it a few times I was always curious um it's all about building
treadmills and creating these elaborate circuit systems in order to generate items that are used
to build more complex items uh whatever it's a very complicated like you design factories basically
and layouts and stuff and for a while I was like oh god we know it from the mathematosis video
oh I oh shit he's oh I gotta watch that instantly because I fucking love that game now he's done
he's done videos on like this game and like every other game this company has ever made
oh that was those guys this is uh one of those guys fucking yeah what is it called uh yeah he's done
he's done a whole series those were great but I didn't fucking miss that completely I didn't
understand them I thought they were neat to look at this game uh okay it's awesome until it became
the worst game I've ever played in my fucking life uh and it it it just hits a point where it
seems like the theme of the entire episode this game was great until it's animal crossing was so
great until these fucking eggs showed up and yeah listen listen it's just that I was playing the
factorial loved it for like two days and then you you hit a certain point where like okay I've got
a factory going you're okay basically in order to progress you need to generate like these potions
you start with like red potion then you go to like whatever like green then like blue to make
those potions you need like weird combinations of different like tools that you have to have
factories generating and stuff like but it gets exponentially more complicated to get each of
them I hit the point where I was just like fuck this I'm not doing that you can't hold me hostage
making any more of these fucking potions I give up and it was just too complicated my brain is
too small and at that point I picked up animal crossing I'm like you know this game's actually
pretty good it's not maybe maybe efficiency and aiming for like autistic factory simulator isn't
always good sometimes you just want to shake a tree and get a coconut and that's what I'm doing
that's what I'm doing at this very moment and it feels pretty fucking good oh god so it's been a
journey it's and I still might make a video where that where I encapsulate this arc in a more artistic
way but this has been my uh this has been my journey through these games efficiency pretty cool
for a while but then I kind of get fucking sick of it and you just want to talk to a buddy yeah
yeah well not well not the bunny someone else I hate the fucking bunny but uh I don't know Tom
who who who are your villagers okay I've got a fucking hamburger ass looking sheep she looks
like a fucking hamburger wait no I'm talking about wait is it that Carlos her her name is Frida her
name is Frida no she looks like I was gonna say I've got a ram named Carlos but uh okay she I
think she's a female ram um I've got a purple bear who I like her name is Megan Megan the
purple bear she's kind of cool mm-hmm I have uh a hippo I have a hippo who loves to lift weights
who I forget his name uh wait I can go to the menu something shit hippo crit uh and he hates the mud
puddle he hates mud he likes to steal an iron well he's a freaking freak he's a monster and uh who
just move in was I've got like a lion girl or something who has no discernible personality
so I I've got let me let me wrap I got Carlos the kind of the pretentious ram I got I I met on an
island a pig named Gala who I I invited her to live with us she's here now um my other friend
Toby just met a snow leopard who he invited she hasn't moved in yet a like old snow okay there's
a snow leopard that's Cassie there's an it's just a snap yeah a snap that's right this like this
old fox who dresses like preppy but his like wallpaper is like gangster like like tags and
like like graffiti and I do not know what the fuck his deal is but he just moved in he's in his
chief uh like grumpo is this like gruff bear who is always like singing on the beach diva the just
the terrifying frog um uh flora is like this episode got weird at a certain it did get weird
but this is cool wait I think I can remember them all I'm oh okay all of our favorite is um um
Weber the duck he just like he's tiny and he just like waddles around and like he's he's like he's
always like thinking about things like huh uh eggs you're made of candy and like they taste
really good it's almost like it's all designed on purpose he's aware that he's a video game
character yes quack quack we all we all like Weber he gave us medicine when we got stung by wasps
oh that's nice and uh uh uh there's um fauna is a deer she's fine she's my neighbor right now
best guy is bam who is like a a stag or something he's like a blue like like deer stag and he is
like a weightlifter and he's always like making shit in his house and when he goes outside Noja he
literally like puts his arms he goes to the beach puts his arms behind him and Naruto runs around
the beach like he's pretending to run like he's pretending to headbutt stuff and the other day
I talked to him and he was like hey hey Ben looking built kablang and I was like yes I love bam
he's my favorite um so those are my boys is this game like any kind of substantial improvement over
Animal Crossing GameCube from 20 years ago or is it just there are some tiny efficiency improvements
because everything I hear from it I didn't play the GameCube one so I don't know what that one
was missing it's got like a new crafting system well everything I hear about Animal Crossing
you know it's never this Animal Crossing is good for this reason it's always Animal Crossing is good
like every time they're all the same game comes out there's no information anywhere
then the crafting is definitely an improvement yeah it adds a lot um other than that I mean
it's basically the same game just with more stuff yeah I think maybe there could be that there's
space in the world for like an extreme in-depth analysis of all the Animal Crossing games well
that's true because because I have the same problem like Animal Crossing is just beloved by everyone
but like I mean there's just two things do I do I need to really play it it's it's cute things and
it's like a very like gripping like a progression loop yeah of like of like they get you get a lot
of rewards and there's a lot of like shit to work towards mm-hmm like in a meta sense Animal
Crossing exists in two states pre-Isabel and post-Isabel when Isabel became like the most
important aspect of Animal Crossing in-game though she just doesn't do anything I mean she
won't if she fucking works behind a desk I gotta tell you I'm very proud of myself uh Caleb found
my friend Caleb founded the island he named it Yakitori Island and uh I designed the flag and
it is a yakitori hey that's it's all coming together baby it's just a chicken on a stick
just today since Isabel moved in I was able to change the flag I'm going to make it some kind
of pirate flag possibly but cool that's why I did the old days with my my ds version I put I put the
New Los Angeles City theme song in as the town tune but I don't really think it fits so I think
I'm gonna change it do you have to construct the song at a note so I was gonna do that I just didn't
get to it yet yeah yeah yeah they give you a little like fucking Mario Mario maker like uh oh that's
cool a tune creator to maybe all people give me a little like do do do do do do do do do do do
wait wait you gotta give it a do do do do wait no as soon as I'm done with this I'm gonna go and
I'm gonna make that the town tune good idea good idea uh yeah it's gotta be quite a few
are there any skull masks that we can get I want to be sans there's I have a skull floor and I have
a skull wallpaper it's really good is sans a killer or a rowdy I would have to say he's a killer I
I don't know I feel like sans is a juvie killer aligned maybe he might just be like a really tough
juvie yeah yeah I mean if it's like papyrus and sans like papyrus is the rowdy of the two and
it's definitely killer or of the two but they might just both be juvies I don't know
sans is too powerful he's above the gang war yeah that's true pretentious fuck
so yeah animal crossing I'll try and get pictures of my rose garden please do please do
get us the flag and let's see what things look like that hell yes I'll show that shit off
mine is not impressive enough should I like um hey okay I haven't done any like multiplayer
with it is like if I just like show my like my like island profile will it have like a
number on it that people can use to like send me stuff you know I don't I haven't done anything with
it yet um if I knew I'd I'd say but I could be I could be like hey guys here's my island number
you can mail me things if you want maybe I that might do unboxing videos I've seen I've seen
people posting like their custom designs online and I think you can just like type the number in
like a serial number and just get it that's yeah there's something like that um or you might have
to like send you might have to buy it from them or something there might it might be more complicated
than just knowing the number I did I did enjoy very much being able to this wasn't an online thing
but I sent Michelle a letter from the post office that said uh something along the lines of like
dear Michelle fuck you get off my island uh sign Nate I um my um my my friend Dube was uh he was
watching me play and he he was like Ben you're stripping the island bear of all its resources
like you've like taken all the rocks and all the and all the fruits and I was like I left
some apples in the north he's like oh apples oh great apples thanks to the worst vegetable
so I felt so I felt bad so I went and I sent he was like you're you're denuding the island's
vegetation so I denuding denuding I'm pretty sure that's a word so I went to the post office
and I sent him a stimulus package of 10 000 bells and I said sorry for denuding and uh that was my
story look at this video I found okay I think I might want to get this game
I see oh it's uh Anka yeah have you guys seen the incredible Anka pornography that exists that
video by minus eight or whatever what that one's pretty good yeah it's it's world famous everybody
knows that one wait hold on I haven't seen it yet uh the the the where's the fucking discord link
it's in the main chat god damn it oh lol anyway I think this uh I'm sure if this was posted on
twitter.com or whatever there would be many links to that video no stop that stop tea is it wrong to
sexualize a cat I mean she's humanoid right it's fine it's fine she can consent she can definitely
consent but she doesn't look like she's consenting here uh well correct no she's not so that's a
problem and you know what I say we can work on that all right now about animal crossing yeah I've
said I have to say about it we we got the voicemails you guys there's nothing else you want to talk about
yeah just go to voicemail I got him okay okay um let me see okay got it right here uh every
every one ladies and gentlemen as you know voicemail time link in the description two voicemails
send us some leave them it's good speakpipe.com slash whatever it is down there oh and there
was something I was going to say oh before I play the voicemail I just wanted to say
sigh of relief famous old nibba of the pcp circles and creator of like the original
discords or all right he made the um the bot or she I don't actually know um made like a
fucking bot girl girl okay there you go that uh uh the bot the bot that updates us in our
fucking feeds about new PCB stuff really cool stuff um sigh made that subsized based um and
had like a unfortunately awesome yeah now you know unfortunately left like a three minute long
clip that was too fucking long sigh I'm sorry you gotta keep it shorter you gotta do it but I
will summarize quickly and it's just that sigh is organizing a procrastinators rewatch uh like a
review or not a review but like a uh pcp highlights things you're gonna go back and like watch old
episodes is this arm retrieval but like something like that something like that is the idea to
scrub through to find like the highlightable moments what no I don't know uh well first of all
there's a link in the description alizar please put in the show notes link to like the three minute
video that sigh made that like summarizes the idea it's just a rewatch to just re enjoy old stuff
now there's so many episodes I think I don't know all the details that's fucking awesome yeah that's
gonna be old good new bad oh please god no no it's worse than that they're gonna they're gonna
go back and discover oh wait the old version was just as bad as it is now worse would I want to be
vindicated at such a high cost I don't know it's just bad it's always has been always will be there
was never a golden a golden era of the past to return to well regardless if you're interested
so uh click on the link in the description to uh uh in the in the show notes down below
to sigh's video and then in there there will be a link to the discord where sigh I think is organizing
it so go ahead and do that if you are so interested wow indeed indeed okay but beyond that we now have
actual voicemails that we will play um let me get the red chat here here we go okay first one is
simply called wait how many we got oh I there's seven I believe but they're pretty short oh okay
there's eight total but they're they're pretty short okay so here we go uh here's just a simple
one called how many lectures are there take it away for every rad con now and in the future you
must clearly state how many lectures there are because I have no fucking clue I I mean it's been
that's it it's it's been stated I guess just not clearly enough like I we know we've said it yeah
well first of all we don't care for your tone over in every stream someone asks it I don't care
for your fucking tone buddy we don't oh you shit we've already made a bunch of lectures more are
coming you know that okay but to baby if he means that we have to say it before we don't know how many
there will be before yeah that's true afterwards what okay let's be clear we've got uh uh Ben's
lectures already the diana writes tom's animorphs gibbs vriska nate one piece okay ones that are
known to be coming digi is working on his pony one uh brony munchy harass munchy right pony lore uh
brony brony lore the fucking um harass munchies that he will actually make another the endless war
birthday is over he is fucking a french revolution one because it is awesome no he needs to make the
guest vapor and no okay well maybe do that leave that malon just harass munchy in general and then
don't not harass him right right ben's second lecture uh cwc 102 cwc 102 and the legendary brad
lecture those are coming and they will come uh so that's there's four left four out four are coming
so there you go there's your answer eight total not bad not bad uh quality may vary that's it
that's it answer uh complete on to our next one okay here we go so here's a message from foxy socks
ketu okay have written in before let's see what you got go hey pro crest leaders i got a major
time critical life or death situation here and i need answers post haste if you've read my twitter
i know ben has i plan on doing a lecture video like you guys did with radcon but there is a catch
we live in a post-covid society and i can't get outside to preach to people about warrior cats
because every second i spend in the presence of lesser beings is another percentage take up for
the chance of be keeling over and dying to the virus the question is should i live stream a lecture
and open up the chat for community members to discuss or put up a discord call get some friends in
record do you have anything else in mind also the finalists for choices are more or less decided
i'm just trying to figure out do i want to do one on warrior cats or magic the gathering
i need to know please respond okay foxy socks
personally i'd much rather see a lecture on magic the gathering just because i play it and
i don't know enough about the lore there's so many novels and shit i read quite a bit of it um i think
i mean on the one hand i know less about warrior cats yeah on the other hand is it funny like is
the lore of that's the question i was gonna say is it fun to summarize like grand like uh like
magic would i be would i be surprised by what i heard is on the other hand though fucking like
magic is like no one knows the fucking lore of the magic series that's a good one that's like um
it's like um like kingdom hearts is like nobody's played all these fucking games but came out to
is way funnier just inherently because it's so retarded so i mean if it was me if you're really
split between them personally i'd go for warrior cats but i can't tell you what to do i don't know
which is uh well warrior cats seems easy the magic one will be successful because yeah that's
probably true warrior cats would be too warrior cats has like a big internet like cult five magic
the gathering would be more successful maybe because more people are familiar with magic the
gathering and lots of those people don't know the lore and might be interested so you know that's
probably a safer bet honestly in terms in terms of the other half of his question uh how to do it
when there's virus i i don't know how well a discord call with people shouting at you through the
screen while you're like doing a thing like i don't know whether that would have the same effect
you could do it that way okay here's i mean just do a warrior cats lecture get a bunch of cats and
have them yeah you could i mean yeah i i agree like you could do it live stream i do think it
wouldn't be the same you your your quest your if you want to do it live you know your choices are
like either wait till the pandemic ends or maybe is there could there be a way to do it while social
distancing just don't come within six feet of anyone while you keep everyone six feet apart
the thing is like lectures are basically video essays but with people in the room
and then it's more of like a like a real physical thing i don't think it can be underestimated
how important the people in the room thing is for the the the atmosphere helps with the if you're
just standing there talking to a camera you may as well be making a video about it rather than
like a long uninterrupted unedited thing i mean well what's your time frame too like if you're
willing to wait a month a month a lot of things could change for this might be longer than a month
it might it certainly well could go be dead in a month in which case yeah i suppose so
uh i mean if it was me i think what i would do was like based on the crew i've got
i would probably like i can't recommend this to you because maybe it's a little irresponsible
i would just try to like vet them like okay guys like are you are you sick you've been going out
what's what's your deal and if not i'd be like okay i'm gonna take a risk and just like get to
i mean i think it's you're not supposed to do that no i mean it might be low key it might be low
key illegal oh that it's i don't know whether it's illegal it should be and i wouldn't respect
and like enforceable to like yeah i'll push you back into your house if you get caught well it's
well the point is i mean the point is it's that it's irresponsible yeah here's what i think you
could i think you could do it in a responsible way okay say you've got like a bunch of say you've
got like maybe one location that you want to go do it in and you all go do it and like
i don't know you wear gloves just wash your hands you take all the vitamins that you have in your
house all the vitamins and then you get uh like just eat them up no you get apple cider vinegar
and like the spiciest chili powder that you have and you put it all in a blender and you drink
a whole thing of it and then you're immune to everything forever and you'll become a super
human that's like a plant and so then it won't have an effect on you and you can do whatever you
want there you go i think if you know people it's all about brewing the right potions
i just think i would say if you can find a place that you can do it that everyone could
like get together like deep clean and then sure yeah sanitizer and wash your hands a lot
it would probably be okay i hope you don't i hope no one dies as a result of me saying this
just don't touch each other don't breathe on each other six six six six feet away six six six
indeed six six six feet away if preferably just get like a fucking air hang out no more no less
you know i mean i mean we all waited until radcon to do a lecture that took two years
sweet until the fucking pandemic's over yeah he doesn't sound like this is like urgent use the
time to take notes hasn't even decided what he's gonna do yet exactly so i mean to be fair a lot
of us kind of made up our mind while we were there so you could do you could do like rehearsals like
none of us i don't think do like live rehearsals where we try to speak the whole thing i i know i
probably needed to do on yeah yeah oh by the way did i mention have you guys seen my my one piece
lecture has cleared 100 000 views not bad not too shabby not too shabby i got recommended it
did oh that's oh that's the bet you know i'll just tell you guys i've made
about over 300 off that video i'm very glad that i did not i was so close to just letting it be
demonetized i was this fucking close i was like why was it demonetized well because i put okay this
is the weird thing that it's the binks sake song from the show that like got claimed at times i just
did a little creative editing to just like remove a little bit actually like the singing vocal part
was like the most the end song i originally wanted the whole like like the fucking straw hat crew
and the rolling pirates on thriller bark where they sing it with brook and stuff i wanted like
the voices of the crowd singing it kind of weirdly fades out now that was not intended that was just
to avoid copyright stuff so anyway i'm glad that i did and uh thank thank you jesus for
hooking me up with that one i want to say i think it's cool foxy that you're thinking about doing
a lecture i think i think it would be cool if more people just kind of did like hey i'll do a
lecture in the style of the pcp uh one other person did one uh tectonic improv did one on top
of the floor the lore of the lore of lingkara i haven't watched that which is but it's good it's
cool i i do know a bit about lingkara yeah i mean it's the it's the in universe like story of his
yeah like like his the like i don't want to watch all those reviews to get that so i
of course no ever since our men yeah you guys are aware of me um back years and years and years ago
when i posted the video of me and lingkara yeah at the time i met him at the fucking whatever i
don't remember that was before i followed you but i am aware of it i think it's amazing couldn't see
the video but i have seen clips of it and i have seen it at some point so yeah i was at um
yoma con in detroit i think it was like 2011 and i was like i was just a little like baby boy
youtuber this was during my that guy at the glasses forums days yep and um for some reason
i was just like up in one of the halls just like sitting there just like grumpily eating a lemon
like with the skin on it and everything because right because for i don't even know why i did this
but i like i oh because someone was like passing out lemons for some reason like being quirky
like i was like oh you think that you're quirky i'll show you fucking quirky so i'm you know so
i said the person i was with i was like hey fill me i'm just gonna sit here i'm gonna eat this whole
lemon and no one can stop me no one tried to stop me but that didn't matter so i sat there but
nonetheless the point was yeah and i like and i did i ate the whole lemon i was chewing through
the fucking rind and the fucking the gristle and the grime and the grit of the bone all the bones
cracking yeah the blood of this lemon pouring down my chin and i and i got the whole thing down
and i was like yeah and i was feeling like a real badass and and like in the middle of it
like linkara was like just happened to be passing by and uh like i noticed him and i was like hey
you it's something and like there was like this weird altercation or like i was like i was like
trying to like be like a badass heal like eating this lemon for no reason and he probably had no
fucking idea what was going on whatsoever but he came up and he was like playing into it and he
like did his man punch thing and he's like i am a man and went to punch me and like and i and i
totally no sold it like an asshole and i'm like well i've got a lemon and i just kept eating the
lemon in front of him like aggressively eating a lemon at linkara until he like got sad and walked
away like like defeated um man i feel like if i could go back and do it again i would have like
oversold the punch i would have like flipped back over a railing and died that would have been fun
yeah but i was but in the moment i was just like how dare you try to be cooler than me while i'm
eating a lemon you son of a bitch and so like i ate it at him and he got he he was he was destroyed
and no one ever heard from linkara ever again and i'm sorry this video is my it's my fault that
that got the glasses was went on play in horseshoe finale i think i've put clips of it in various
videos i think the i've definitely seen it and i think it's in horseshoe finale is that video
available somewhere no the full video i think it was called horseshoe finale yeah right on youtube
the full video of it was on like blip before blip went down i think is why it's no longer available
but yeah you can see clips of it in various places well regardless uh regardless on the point of
doing lectures whatnot i mean i've been thrilled uh to see link link in the description to tectonic
improv linkara lecture by the way yeah i'll use our put that in there it's just been great to see
that and uh ever since the fine bros uh our mentors instructed us to copyright the term lecture
and we've been getting a sweet 50 you have to pay us all proceeds from ad revenue we can so much
part of the schools and universities it's great it's wonderful uh thank you thank you boys uh
for just put it in a letter send it to patreon.com slash ben saint is actually the url i know it's
a little weird but that's where it's strange strange but i believe you uh let's go to our next
voicemail uh all right let's go to uh arcade nova with radcon wrap up okay let's take it away hey
i know you have nothing else better to do so go watch our fucking podcast we made a we made a
podcast about radcon it was pretty sick watch it right now you fucking
shit this youtube.com slash arcade nova they did do that hey maybe while you're there maybe you
could check out my uh i published a couple new videos all right okay thanks bye arcade nova
was uh he was one of the the bros that came to the radcon meetup yep so wait i actually i have
this video up in a tab i haven't finished listening to it it's um uh janez son of marowak
kairi friggin eric is there friggin and uh alex alex v for extreme um and these are yes these
guys were all at the radcon meetup and they did a podcast discussing how the radcon meetup went
satisfied customers ladies and gentlemen that could be you next time give us a like yeah you
can yeah could have been you you can hear it straight from the horse's mouth uh what it's like
to meet us to hang with to cheat death by meeting the pcp in real life yeah yeah cool i listened to
already it was very funny i think i tweeted them the like about how they were talking about how
they met digi and like and oh my god and then they go oh my god i they go to i did it i got the
fucking last recipe for bunny day i found it craft that shit dude you got a bunny table dude i'm
gonna go make it right now hey have you unlocked the um the the dress uh the bunny day dress the
bunny day dress is actually awesome yeah yeah i got i got that okay i i sold all my Easter
shit but i kept that one because i like it mm-hmm that one's yeah okay any okay hip what were you
saying uh no it's funny that i was interrupted by that just go listen to the podcast okay great
it's good stuff okay and make sure to get your eggs in to the zipper the the egg day bunny
please i think is what you meant to say yeah that's right uh when you hear this a week after
it uh Easter days and yeah you can always set the clock the clock back to the 12th oh you're not
doing that shit are you i have not yet done it but i have been a little tempted here in there
since it's calib switch he made it very clear he's like hey yeah you can play my island you do whatever
you want yeah one rule is no fucking clock manipulation because that's for cowards and you
cheat not only the game but yourself yourself you didn't grow you didn't evolve you didn't
so that's why i'm stuck waiting waiting in three three whole days of waiting to have bred uh four
special crossbreed roses but soon soon the population will explode once i get to that
man talk about a game wasting your time yeah in game time it's about the journey yeah fair uh
okay let's go to our next voicemail uh this one is simply called you should be able to solve this
take it away hey fellas disappointed that you didn't get the crab and a half question correct
you should have been able to solve it really i don't know what was the answer much easier one
oh whatever a bat and a ball cost a dollar ten in total a bat and a ball a dollar ten
the bat costs a dollar more than the ball how much does the ball cost okay now you really truly
honestly and ironically should be able to solve this i think i think it's yeah five cents easy
i'm not gonna play your fucking head games that is yeah that is easy i'm mad okay he says we got
the crab and a half question wrong but he doesn't tell us what the answer is that that is frustrating
that is frustrating what was this one a bat in a ball or a bat i don't understand a bat and a ball
like like a baseball bat and a baseball okay a bat and a ball cost a dollar ten the bat costs a
dollar more so the answer is the ball yeah the ball costs five cents the bat costs a dollar five
easy two i really feel like the problem with the crab question if we got it wrong i think it's
because it was phrased confusingly what was the crab that's the point of these riddles or or questions
is that they're supposed it was like a complicated thing like two crabs get in half the crabs get
out i don't know it's all the birds trying to push you towards making like this obvious answer that
is actually the dumb answer but it's just some like your head first so you just blurt it out
because you don't give a shit the they're phrased confusingly purposely to make you think the obvious
answer but it's not actually because it sounds i guess that would have been two weeks ago was it
really it feels like this forever ago on friday on friday or on yes yes two days ago when we
recorded this the new episode came out i had no idea that a week had gone by that i had not been
on the podcast really fast i had no i was like wait i missed one weird and then today today i
missed the first half because i was catching all my fucking egg recipes priorities and lost track of
the time lost in the sauce hmm oh time to go make that wobbling zipper toy fuck yeah and then i'll be
the king of games uh all right well there you go uh let's move on to our next voicemail which is
simply called that's our word the z word okay go hey it's key blade uh three minutes into the new
podcast please don't use saibatsu um i guess that's what you could consider a trigger for me i guess
i'm legally a faggot now um yeah i can't really control it uh it would just make me sad for you
know like give or take two minutes you know we're tuning in every week to the pcp zibatsu cast
shitting on you know my my new internet dad's shitting on the corpses of my old dead internet
dad's not anybody although you know zibatsu being dead a funny joke golf clap i don't uh if you want
some insider baseball on that uh as a as an old zibatsu head um that's funny on two levels not
only because they're all like you know like a live irl none of them have died since uh also because
all of their you know all of the solo channels they predictably made afterwards uh they're all
shit and terrible and boring uh because the fuck is none of them are funny by themselves without
anyone to play off of and they everything interesting they have to say i've already heard them say it
multiple times over the course of years since 2013 when they first started the friendcast
uh so i guess what i'm trying to say is shut down r slash two best friends play you fucking idiots
are in denial it's your last bastion of hope shut down hope become bitter like me
okay okay zibatsu is a japanese term referring to industrial and financial business conglomerates
in the empire of japan whose influence and size allowed control over significant parts of the
japanese economy from the meiji period until the end of world war two okay listen listen at at the
beginning of last episode that only tom was here for i i said a little piece about like oh you know
i heard about zibatsu like i'd heard the term i actually went and looked it up and it is like a
like it's exactly what bends it it's like a cool term that would kind of apply and now i i get what
it meant to the two best friends to the pcb the point was that we are a zibatsu
in the beginning very briefly at the beginning yeah yeah what how did it come up
i got i just started talking i had just been looking it up and i just thought it was funny
because i i thought it was like a wrestling zibatsu yeah as nat was there was a whole
there was a goddamn story where i was like i can't remember why i was googling the company nissan
for some reason and i was like i don't know and it said nissan was formed out of like the
nissan zibatsu and i'm like what the fuck wait what and then i just followed that thread and i
was like oh it's the thing that's why they called themselves that's a business conglomerate makes
sense okay guys i solved it i found the answer here oh that makes me very mad already is that
out of angst business to business whiteboard oh my god listen to this i don't want to actually
listen to it can i no well just go animate that ain't good all right put that this is so fun no
this is so good it's like text to speech explaining what a word i'm upset i'm not having a good time
anymore why is this oh dude we found this is how this is how you do a social distancing uh pcp
lecture we figured out the format maybe you type out the script and you do it in like go animate
rayman things with albert einstein whoa ben how do you get star fragments what the fuck is that
thanks professor that explains zibatsu no problem you get star fragments nate by um at night i have
another recipe for a star one that blathers sister gave to me but yeah the way that you get star
pieces is apparently at night sometimes shooting stars happen and if you are looking at the sky
like you have the camera all the way up and you see a shooting star you hit a to make a wish
and if you do that then the next morning star pieces will appear on the beach whoa yeah and
that's how you get star pieces i'll fucking have to do that so i can make this stupid ass wand uh
sick based yeah well anyway moving on from that uh zibatsu's are cool rest in peace two best friends
or whatever uh yeah there you go that's it all right we've got another here's an exciting voicemail
simply called re final fantasy seven uh okay take it away one thing that i'm reading about about
this final fantasy seven remake that nate will probably never even read about because he has
a tiny brain is uh this one very minor part that i'm like kind of upset about um at the beginning
of the game when you do the mako bombing thing that and you put the timer on the bomb in the
original game wasn't it like 10 minutes you had 10 minutes to like get the fuck out of there
and uh i got out of there like you know first try like it's not that hard but in this game
it gives you like a choice between 20 minutes or 30 minutes and uh chose 20 minutes and still left
with like less than 10 minutes like i left before 10 minutes had even passed what's the
fucking point if like really what really holds your hands with that timer and this new one uh the
boss fight doesn't even count the timer doesn't start until after the scorpion fight is that true
of the game too no no i remember the the the timer starts and then the boss happens like oh
shoot i gotta defeat this guy while the time is going and like the little part where we're sounds
like a good way to build tension in an action indeed it does the little part where jesse hurts
her leg and you go over to savor in the original that was a choice because it was taking time from
your clock you know you were choosing to go rescuer uh in the new one the clock stops during this
scene for this cut scene for no reason the clock stops while you're helping her up it's the little
things to me that reveal that these people don't know what they're doing i don't care that it's the
same people they've lost their touch if that's what's happened it doesn't matter um i don't whatever
it's not all bad but yeah i mean little things like that like the whole game has changed so like
theoretically with like different mechanics that you could make you could design a game where it's
perfectly appropriate to give someone 20 minutes instead of 10 to do x things but they did that
and then also made the game way easier and baby you like if you want if you want to cut those out
just give a little extra time to do the boss and the thing i love like small moral choices that
i actually have to make the idea of like oh i might not get out in time because i don't know how
much longer this is i i but i need to go save jesse uh uh you know what i mean i don't know i feel
like a lot of this is informed by the meta it's because like because everyone knows it's so weird
who is this game for people who have played it before or people who haven't it's i'm very confused
about that it's both that's why it's for it i'll tell you who it's for it's for casuals who played
the game but don't understand it hmm it's for people who it's for people who vaguely remember
Final Fantasy 7 and see the new one and can go oh my god a Final Fantasy 7 remake oh my god
everything's blowing my mind and you know those people will probably love it oh yeah i'm sure
you know all of it i'm fine yeah are you know those people oh that's me i hate myself you got me
all right whatever let's go to the next one yeah we can complain all day about that uh okay last
one last one this is simply called um incoming transmission go hello i'm speaking on behalf
of the pc police all prior attempts at dismantling the pcp alt right blackpilled post food autism
level five pokemon bad the jews did 9 11 save the white race bernie 2020 anime podcast have failed
we are forced to enact expert measures to stop these audio influencers by placing a nationwide
ban on pcp merch anyone caught in possession of this paraphernalia will be promptly executed
think twice before just being cool our next order of business is to cut all funding to all
ritualistic and cult gatherings known as radcon this annual pilgrimage is believed to be where
members sacrifice non-believers in order to raise their christ consciousness our last order of
business is placing wanted posters across all 50 states payment in the amount of any cryptocurrency
desired will be promptly issued after turning in any one of these deplorable figureheads
turning in digi nate or jess will also temporarily earn you the right to mine at night if you hunt
for ben we suggest bringing some for breeze also a tip if he's hiding you can try to lure him out
with any of nate's old belongings such as a pair of shoes or his vampire hunter d hat
it wasn't my hat ben and his primal urge is to steal nate's stuff happy hunting
um there it is i want to announce uh for the record that uh all a pcp merch now comes with
complimentary uh coronavirus it's baked it's baked right in it's a service it's a service
and you're welcome uh yeah you know maybe now speaking of of doing lectures maybe now's not
the time to do a lecture with the pc police uh hot in pursuit of anyone uh distributing pcp
adjacent paraphernalia do it do it do it as a pc protest right you gotta hold the lecture in defiance
of the law right i would gladly sacrifice these bullies yeah the the economy is tanking right
now and we've gotta boost the uh the pc pennies value so please sacrifice your life for the cause
of raising my PC please please boost those pc pennies uh you know you're you're the future
generations of pcp heads will thank you when their currency still exists indeed indeed uh
thank you for your service uh all right there you go thank you pc police for doing your job
appreciate that uh all right that's it everybody that's the last voicemail i have i have one thing
to say before we wrap up so april ninth this past april ninth was endless wars second birthday
oh yes happy birthday clap clap i mean thanks so so endless wars second birthday it turned to
we did a big ol stream uh history was made guys yeah do you know do you know about uh
you know about slime fest you know about the curse of slime fest that ben always loses of course
that i will have lost i was close the first time but i came in at a disadvantage and i lost and i
have lost every single slime fest indeed sorry i've won the moral victory right in every single
slime fest for two years but on april ninth 2020 history was made the trend was reversed
i beat munchy at a game of slime tassan from unicorn jelly oh incredible a game
munchy could rig one the moral pleasure munchy munchy won the moral victory only for me to reveal
that it was all a ruse and the moral victory was fake all along it's just made up there's no there's
no such thing there's no such thing coming the ultimate revelation yes but so in uh as a celebratory
thing we did launch a kickstarter we have a special merch kickstarter going right now it is for we're
we're not planning to make any money off of it basically everything that we raised from the
kickstarter goes into pins we're making pins and we're making like a paraphernalia and like coins
challenge coins i think and and and cool stuff like that and we're just gonna make as many designs
we can every like 250 dollars we raise we're gonna make a new pin so right now we're doing the
rowdy pin and the killer pin we unlocked the smear designed a ghost nega slime pin yeah i saw
that looks great it looks really good i think we've just today unlocked the slime coin challenge
coin which is basically a little like big like collectible coin that you can yeah hold in your
hand a little medallion a little metal medallion of a slime coin it'll probably come with like a
little display stand and stuff which is pretty cool nice so anyway that's going on right now
link in the description if you want to help us get some cool endless war merchandise please
please go and pledge because i have i did a pledge for like five pins and i need i need all five
i need to i need to fucking podron which looks amazing podrons i really i i really hope we
get the podron done i would really like to there's a lot more really good ones that we
haven't that we didn't haven't raised enough to make yet i need that slime court pin bend when
can i get that which one the slime court well if if people pledge and vote for it then eventually
we'll make it but there's the slime court pin the podron pin there's um the muck cup uh uh league
badge is one um i'm forgetting oh i see there's a weird face that's actually like 20 designs that
we're voting oh there's t-fap t-faps legendary uh puking at everyone puking t-fop t-fap uh the
oh red man's face red man's face dire apples red man serious face uh um there's more there's there's
more have been back a serious question on what pin gets unlocked next yeah yeah yeah if you've
pledged then there is a then you get and you're in the rfck discord you get a role which lets you
into a room where every time a new pin is unlocked you get to vote and that decides what the next
one is bend do me a favor uh i mean if it would be i would love to be able to see on the kick
starter page just which ones are available which ones have been like unlocked uh that would make
it very easy for me to decide what i want to have been unlocked yeah yeah because i really want to
know and i can go dig in the discord but i should update the kickstarter to say which ones now that
now the two are unlocked i should update okay i will do that cool also absolutely i was just
thinking red man is very blocky because he is a pixel man is that going to be yeah i think we
might have to change that oh okay yeah i i don't know if that would i threw it in there because
it was like funny mm-hmm i see and it is iconic face but yeah we can we could approximate we
would probably have to not do it in like a pixel form yeah and also what's going on with this play
that well and zap apple what's what's that thing about i don't know the zap apple is a it's one of
the fruits that you can farm in the juvie farms um it may it's the key ingredient in dire apple
cider uh one of the one of the one of the favorite flavors of fuck energy wait so do you at a low at
a 711 near you do you grow them and then harvest them no no you reap them you idiot why would you
even think that i don't know why i thought it's a vegetable you fuck i'm so sorry everyone how embarrassing
no all right all right that's it go so go pledge for some pins guys they're cool pledge so that
the fucking slime court can be real and happy birthday endless war happy birthday we're back
in we're back in the um we're doing the um the yearly uh revert to season one mechanics uh the
game sucks again everything is no no no the game is perfect because i am sitting in the dojo uh
holding a katana and people are sparring with me and i have 52 million slime right now and the
slimiest i've ever been oh it's funny because um the uh yeah you have 52 million slime from
sparring or whatever um the the amounts we were fighting over in the slime fest was like
because shamblers had shut down the city and no one had been able to play for like a long time
we literally went with like eight and nine million like you could make that in one day uh but that's
what we had to work with god do i miss the stock market and the stonks god damn well not in season
one there are stocks again oh okay there are new there are new stocks kfc uh uh uh pizza hut and
michael bell taco bell yeah yeah they're they're new they've split they've subdivided
oh i have to bust the trust i don't know if this exists but i would love a yum brand's
pin of some stripe that would be excellent you know you know that's not a bad idea um i might
make one and just see if anyone cares i made oh you know i wanted to make one that was like
like a weather warning for bicarbonate rain yeah good idea good idea like it may be like a yellow
triangle with like a cloud and like maybe the chemical symbol for like bicarbonate soda or
something bicarbonate bicarbonate rain downpour again and i want a pin to reflect yeah i fucked
around with it i didn't settle on a design but maybe i'll make one and see if anyone likes it
that's a good i'd like it i like it yeah i i think that's cool if i had to choose i'd probably get
like slime corp fucking nega slime i do like this red man face a lot t-fap is pretty attractive
uh what what killers what i like are things that you would see if you were in new los angeles
city oh i gotta say i love the slime coin i mean the slime coin of course is kind of number one
that's i mean the slide we could make the slime coin as a pin too if we wanted but like right now
it's just i like it as a coin i'm sick in new los angeles city you would see people wearing
like killer pins rowdy pins of course those people just would be wearing those um you you if someone
were a muck trainer you might see them wearing the muck league badge uh they might have a podron
pin to them as it exists right now though i do have an issue with this i am the so those are the ones
that i i really like thus far in human history i'm the sole producer of slime corp pins anywhere
they are made of paper but they are real and exist and some of you have them uh so the market's
about to be flooded my pins are going to become worthless which is unfortunate for me we're going
to uh we're going to devalue that currency real soon so uh sell sell sell it's time it's time
all right that's it for the episode everybody that's that's what's up that's what's up
excellence check it out links in the show notes and whatnot uh and we're done that's it for this
episode of the procrastination thanks for listening thanks for being here send me send me gifts on
animal crossing that would be excellent uh uh uh uh leave information in the description if there's
some way to communicate uh on animal crossing to give me free shit which would be excellent uh but
if you've got extra money hey patreon.com slash the procrastinators five dollars for bonus episodes
there are 36 now that's a full three years worth of bonus episodes now for as little as five
dollars a month absolutely incredible uh leave voicemails how much is the how much is the gum
road for uh the like rad con for a bonus concept we we have not yet like released the rad con
foreign for anyone to buy it okay we i mean we could there's some stuff there we could do that
pretty soon maybe at some point we should decide that but the the rad con three one is 11 dollars
and 11 cents for the rad con three stuff maybe we'll make a bundle and sell them both for like
i don't know 15 or something i don't know i don't know um but uh there you go uh leave voicemails
more at the speak pipe link that is in the description uh you can listen to this fucking
show on itunes or not me yeah itunes fucking google play kinds of shit links in the description if
you just want to listen to it as a podcast uh and there you go show notes they're all below
click on the things we talked about here uh have a good time and follow us for updates on twitter
at tpcrastinators uh and more rad con four stuff we'll be coming at you soon four more lectures
to go keep your eye out we'll make sure everybody knows about them uh twitter's good place for
updates so there you go all right we'll see you next week everybody thanks for being here take
it sleazy he's good bye