Hello and welcome to this week's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm your host, the best guy ever, Guy, here with my bunch of friends once again.
First up is Digibro.
Hey everybody, let's get sleazy.
And Hippocrit.
I didn't think of a thing, a penis.
There you go.
And we have a special guest today, our good friend Cotton Candy.
Hi everyone.
I am the Assygnated vagina haver for this evening.
There's much more to it than that.
That's so short because among us, you are by far.
No, it is, it is.
You are by far the biggest expert on porn.
Because not only have I witnessed your sincere passion for the medium,
but you in fact created for money much of the time.
I saw your Megarene Luca body pillow, which was awesome.
I'm drawn porn.
We should clarify.
She creates drawn porn for money.
She does not star in porn for money.
As far as we know.
As far as we see you guys know.
That's true.
Yes.
So can, just for that, can people buy that body pillow somewhere?
Is there like a link we could put in?
It's not finished yet because I want to do different outfits
so everyone can choose which version of Luca to buy.
Awesome.
That's great.
Luca is by far the best Megaloid, Vocaloid.
Vocaloid, yeah.
I like Moogie.
Which one's Moogie?
Is that the green haired one?
Yes.
But that's not.
Wait, isn't her name Goomi?
No.
I just forgot it.
Okay.
So today, in case you hadn't already guessed, we're talking about pornography.
Porno.
Yes.
We talked about all kinds of porno.
It was just, just drawn stuff.
Pretty, just all kinds.
Really the concept of porn in general.
And there's some other topics that branch off of it.
But in the meantime, I thought we'd just start off by just, just airing our general thoughts
on the matter.
So let me start off by just saying anyone who thinks porn is bad for anyone.
I don't care how young you are.
I think porn, I think sex really in general is a healthy thing for everyone to have a
pretty thorough understanding of no matter what your age.
I think a lot of the resentment to it in America at least comes from Christianity, which is
retarded.
And I wish that everyone who didn't like it and didn't support it all the time would
go away forever.
That's my sense.
I think that's getting a little broad because you're kind of equating sex and porn.
And porn is not exactly a good representation of sex.
Okay.
You want to get into that?
Sure.
Yeah.
I'm sure we have to at some point if we're going to discuss porn.
Like, you know, porn gives you very skewed expectations of what sex is, especially if
you watch a lot of porn before you ever have sex, especially if you watch a lot of live
action porn.
I actually think live action porn is worse maybe at educating you than anime porn can
be.
At least there's that veneer of, you know, this is not legit.
So, you know, it's not, well, the funny thing is, and this is going to come up at some point
anyways, but because I feel like we should, we're all, we all watch a lot of anime porn,
right?
Yep.
And cotton candy obviously creates it.
Yeah.
So, to start off by like getting the audience on the same page as us in case anyone's listening
to this who doesn't look at that kind of stuff, like to explain what the appeal is.
Because the funny thing about live action porn is that you know it's not real sex.
Like you know it's not these two people really met and did, like especially if there's like
a story, the story's obviously scripted.
What do you mean?
That pizza delivery guy really needed some form of payment for that.
And it's always, you know, the people are often, which not as much anymore because we
have so much amateur porn now, but it used to be, you know, it's always like fake titties,
big insane looking dicks, you know, like just people who are bred for porn, you know, and
the way that they have sex can be so crazy that it's not like real life.
And so the funny thing is that I think especially for our generation, what sort of attracts
them to anime porn is that it is paradoxically more authentic because while the characters
aren't real people, they are actually having sex because they love each other most of the
time.
Okay.
Because they're really in the situations.
I don't know.
Wait, why are you making that comparison?
I think that.
I mean, now go on Cece.
What do you have to say?
I have very different variations of the kind of content that I got.
I didn't mean to say that they always are in love with each other.
I just meant that the situations are real.
Like even if it's rape, it's real rape in the context of the story.
That is true.
And like when you watch that one arrow gay, like, yeah, a guy comes to work at an arrow
gay making company and they just, they needed miles.
They needed sexual experience to know how to drive that shit.
They're never going to watch a live action porn where there's a real rape scene or there's
characters who really love each other or there's anything real.
None of it's ever real.
You know it's stage.
I guess that's true.
But in the context of the anime, for the characters, like in the most common one, and this is,
to me, I think this is the biggest reason that anime porn is so big, especially in Japan,
because in Japan they value purity a lot.
Sure.
And in anime, it's actually a virgin.
That's true.
If a girl is losing her virginity, which is almost always the case, then she is really
a virgin in the context of the story, because it's a character you made up, you know.
Incidentally, Japan not into the whole bleeding during sex to prove their a virgin thing.
Not a big fan.
I'll turn their word for it.
You know?
I know too much about how that's like, because in anime it's always like, you're not supposed
to tear the hymen.
That is not how it's supposed to work.
Right.
In anime it's always like, they have sex while they're a virgin and then they start bleeding
but then within 10 seconds she's like, now I'm getting used to it.
Oh, it starts to feel good now.
Yeah.
Got to love that.
It's not often like that in real life.
It can be possibly, but it's not usually.
This is a serious question, though.
Isn't your point about it being authentic undermined by the fact that it is clearly fake, because
they're animated?
I mean, is that...
Well, yeah, but it's more emotionally authentic.
It's like when you're...
For instance, I think this is why Yuri stuff is so popular, and this was true for me when
I was younger, because I was only interested in lesbian stuff for a long time.
In live action, you almost never get real lesbian sex.
It's always made for guys, it's always girls doing all this stuff that they wouldn't necessarily
usually do in real life, whereas in anime, if you read a lot of Yuri porn, it's always
extremely sensual.
There's usually a fucking ton of story and dialogue and very little actual fucking, and
it's usually pretty quick.
The girls are always the hottest ever.
It's always like the cutest girls in history are always in Yuri porn, but they only fuck
for two pages, and I always get real pissed off.
That's interesting, because I've been trying to figure this out for a long time.
I have never, ever, at any point in my life, been particularly stimulated at all by Yuri.
I pretty much always need there to be a guy there for me to get at all interested.
Perhaps that's just a weakness of mine.
I need to self-insert into the situation, but when I'm looking at porn, that's more
the stuff that I'm interested in.
Well, maybe it's the lack of a dick.
Have you tried food and airies?
Bible black?
Yes, actually, my favorite, I was going to say my favorite, hence I have all time, is
Bible black, without a doubt, because really, you've got the best of both worlds there.
You've got two sets of tits flopping around, and you've got the dick action that you can
project onto.
Everyone's a winner.
Everyone's a winner in that situation.
So, it's not that you don't like lesbian porn, as you need the dick somewhere in there.
Yes, because that's the focal point of the scene.
You need that going on, so that you have an investment that you can jack off properly.
There's two girls schlicking, it's like, okay, how am I, how is my fapping right now related
to this situation?
It's not.
It's like I'm an alien observing.
I feel like I took a weird backwards trajectory with this, because when I was younger, I would
only look at like, eerie stuff, because I just didn't want to see dicks, I just didn't
want them around, I thought they were ugly and terrible, and I hated them.
And also just like, when you don't understand sex that much, it seems more violent, and
like it's just like, to me like, male on female sex felt more violent, especially, I suppose
you could use that word.
Well, okay, let me take you back to, we're talking about like 2005, 2006, and I didn't
like know how to find porn very much.
Wait, 2005, how old were you?
2006, I'd be 15, I think, yeah, I'm turning 25 this year.
I started young then.
Well no, this is when I started, I just like, I didn't have like, I didn't start using
the internet to find porn until later, like when I was really young, like I found my dad's
porn magazines under the bed, you know, and I was always terrified of like viruses and
stuff like that, you know, because like, because that was common back then.
If you went on porn sites, you had porn and stuff.
Yeah, that's actually how my fucking cousin ruined my computer, like in 2003, I had gotten
a new computer, and then my cousin like was using Livewire to download all this music and
porn and stuff, and he totally ruined my computer with viruses, and I had no idea.
Let me share my first story ever getting this, because I love telling people about this.
I was playing StarCraft, doing like Frogger Mode, you know, like the online Battle.net
stuff, and one of the banner ads, I remember it so well, was this Asian chick, like riding
a dildo or something, I had no idea what it was, I clicked that link, and discovered
a whole new world, man, I remember it like it was fucking yesterday, yeah, exactly.
That's funny, because I remember being in Newgrounds the first time that I discovered
Zone, so I didn't know what it was, I really loved my life as a teenage robot, and I saw
the thumbnail, and I thought it was just like a cute animated clip of it, and it wasn't.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Shout out to ZoneSama, legendary animator.
How long has Zone been around?
Jesus Christ.
Oh god, 15, 20 years, at least 15.
It's a lot of time to be drawing cartoon porn.
Yeah, I think he works for Hentai Key, like on a contractual basis or something, whatever.
So yeah, I discovered, I started trying to use the internet for porn, but it was like
I would just Google search and stuff, or I gradually found out about the image boards,
like, do you guys know Danboru or Gelboru, any of those?
Yes, of course.
So I had discovered Gelboru, and the thing is that I didn't know search terms or anything
I was looking for, so it was just random stuff, so you're treated to everything, every fetish
is all right there on the page.
So most of it, I was just like, I don't want to see any of this, so I would just look at
the Yuri stuff, you know?
And then it's funny because over time, I think the official moment when it became difficult
to go back to, I still love Yuri conceptually, I love when it's girls together, it's adorable,
I think it's the cutest thing ever, but once I had actually had sex and appreciated how
it works, it became harder for me to understand how girls get off when they have sex with
each other, because there's no real lesbian porn out there, and I've always thought I
want to ask, just go around the internet asking real lesbians, but you never know who's a
real lesbian online, because everyone wants to say they're real lesbians.
Why couldn't you just ask a girl in general, I mean, they're experts in getting themselves
off, I assume.
There's a huge difference between getting yourself off and getting another person off,
like are you just doing the same things to them you would do to yourself, because that
seems like it could be boring or awkward, I've always found the concept of the reach
around or the reach over to just like, it seems awkward to me.
That's pretty awkward.
Just ask.
Jesus.
Well, I don't know any lesbians, so.
Talk to the person.
Oh, she's saying during sex, yeah, okay.
Well, I'm not having sex with any lesbians for sure.
You're missing out, you're totally missing out.
I don't know how I'm going to get into that.
How would you ever arrange that situation?
You'd have to set up a threesome situation, that's the only way.
Yeah, you need.
One of them would have to be bi even then.
That's true, that's true.
Well, you could get a unicorn.
I want to know what it's like for girls who have no interest in dick at all to have sex
with each other, and what exactly they do, and of course it's going to be different
for everybody.
There's to some extent to which I can say, because anime sex is weird, but then to some
extent you can look at it and go, well, even if it's one in a million, it could still happen.
Even if the whole popping the cherry and then she enjoys it 10 seconds later.
It could happen.
Very over-represented in anime, but that doesn't mean it never happens.
That's the thing.
These things happen.
Okay.
I know that there are sites that are dedicated to doing real porn quotation marks, but all
of the ones that I know, if you have to pay for subscriptions, I can't really think of
any names right now, but I think the easiest way to find it is going to the comic Ojoisextoi.
Every other time they'll mention a website that does specifically that.
Ojoisextoi, cool.
Over time I came to realize that I think I can tell the difference between Yuri that's
written by women and Yuri that's written by men.
The way it's targeted is going to be pretty clear probably.
It's like a matter of a trend changed because I think a lot more women got into writing
it in the last five years, because I was really into Yuri in the late 2000s.
Most of it was pretty much the same.
It all had the same kind of tone.
It was all very much in this Marimite and Maihime style, where it's usually like an
older girl and a younger girl.
What's it called?
Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke, or what the fuck is the English name for that?
Something about Skye.
In Sono Hanabira, which is a very popular series of Yuri Edoge, those are really hardcore.
They just fuck all the time.
The whole thing is just nothing but girls having sex, and often it gets a little fetishy
and stuff.
Those are clearly meant for guys, not to say that women can't enjoy them.
I'm sure plenty of lesbians do, especially because it was the best thing you had for
a long time.
Once there was what's Yuri caught on in 2010 area, and then suddenly there's Yuri manga
everywhere, and suddenly a lot of it's being written by women, and suddenly a lot of it
is really, really adorable, really low-key sex, and much more story.
Kind of like the greatest lesbian hero of all time, what's her face who makes Hitamari
sketch?
She doesn't make porn, but her passion for the female porn is truly inspiring.
It's the best.
She loves girls.
It's great.
I was reading, I loved this, there was some lesbian porn I was reading recently, and
the author had a little omake at the end, where she was talking about how she went to
this meet-up with all these other Yuri authors.
She was trying to explain that she's not gay, but when she sees a woman, a beautiful woman,
she feels really glad, she feels like she's been rewarded or something.
She's trying to explain this at the meeting, and they go, man, that's pretty gay, and she's
walking home thinking, I guess it is pretty gay, but they just don't get it.
No, no, no.
My intense appreciation for the male form is like the ancient Greeks.
It's the highest form of artistic beauty that there is.
It's meant to be appreciated and studied, and if you get a stiffy sometimes, well, that's
just nature taking its course.
It doesn't mean a damn thing.
I don't need your labels, people.
I don't know.
I've never been the...
I know a lot of guys who feel that way.
Like Jimmy is always talking about how he loves free, because he loves the chiseled male
body aesthetic and everything.
I've never really felt that.
I just like things to be cute and adorable.
But free is like porn for animators too, because you know that they did the muscles perfect
for every style of swimming.
Yeah.
And I was a professional swimmer too, so I just stare at it.
Wait, you were a professional swimmer?
Yes.
That's right.
You've told me that before.
Man, that's crazy.
Professional swimmer, professional porn maker.
Yeah.
What a crazy ride you've had.
And I've also done wrestling and cheerleader and stand-up comedy and all this other shit.
Holy shit.
Globetrotter, multi-linguist.
What else can we add to your insane list of acolytes?
Aren't you like a straight A student too?
Yeah, podcasting.
Podcasting, yep.
This is really your highest achievement.
Might as well say now, this is our first time doing one, so this is the virginal experience.
Yes, we are popping CC's cherry here.
Yep.
No blood on the dance floor.
No blood, yes.
Oh, please be gentle, Senpai.
Well, I guess now might be a good time to perhaps talk about the other...
You know what, actually, Digi, what was that topic you said at the very beginning?
Because I've got something else that's totally a left turn from this.
Let's move on to...
About porn being unrealistic and weird?
Yeah.
Or it being bad for people.
I want to talk about people's perception of it and the whole negative backlash people have.
I mean, sometimes, all of us seem like we're pretty much on the same page, but...
Well, but maybe every one of us has come to that conclusion from different paths, so...
That's probably true.
That would be cool to hear.
Where to start with that?
Well, CC, you obviously are...
You do this with a great passion.
You create these things.
So, I mean, where did your interest in this start?
How did you get into this?
Well, I know, for a fact, having been here in North America for a while,
that you guys are way more sexually repressed.
Absolutely.
Like, every way.
Yeah.
All of the dances in Colombia and everything is way much more open to sex and sex education and all of these stuff.
That sounds awesome.
It was never a weird thing to me.
It was never a tabloid thing.
Like, I was in a religious school, but the government forces every school to allow honest, open, sex eddy stuff.
And also, my parents have a bunch of friends who are sexologists and stuff.
So, it's never been...
What does that mean?
I don't know what they do.
What does it sound like it means?
It means they have sex all the time.
Yes.
In an expert way.
That's awesome.
Like, I don't usually tell people this, but I find it funny.
My first professional job ever, like I was like 12, was to make Valentine's cards for one of them.
It's just penises doing Valentine's cards.
That's awesome.
So, it's always been an open topic for me.
It's never been taboo, which can backfire because I know it can take people as a surprise if I just mention it like gloss over it.
Here in North America, it's so taboo that half our fucking panel didn't show up today.
I know.
Jesse and...
Well, actually, Davout didn't come on because he was afraid of intimidating people with his unusual sexual preferences.
Yes.
He's not even that weird, though.
Didn't want to talk about it.
Okay, that's not fair.
He is pretty weird, but like...
He's only got like one or two things that are weirder than what I like.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, but we're all like...
That's like comparing like a 9 out of 10 to a 10 out of 10.
We're all pretty weird about what we are willing to look at.
Yes.
You know, I want to dispel the notion that we are weird because I think we are in fact totally normal.
I want to put in the description, this video, that everyone needs to see that some...
You know, it's that famous scene from Not Welcome to the NHK.
What's the other one with the...
Genshiken.
Where the guy is describing, you know, why he's attracted...
Oh, yeah, you gotta put that in.
That is the quintessential explanation for why, I mean, among other things, a hentai is attractive or whatever.
Because people to this fucking day say they don't understand why you can be attracted to animation or any of that shit.
Do you people not understand the concept of like human interpretation of symbols?
And like, how could you just read a book?
The fact that you can relate to art at all.
That doesn't make any sense.
It just squiggles on a page.
What's up with that?
Fucking idiots.
Go kill yourself.
Yeah, that's the point of it is to represent something that is real.
And yeah, although if you intro with that, you can't intro with the internet disforbored, which I had imagined as the intro.
We'll have to make up.
That's the more cliche one, so I guess we could just go with the...
I made my own suggestions too.
She did.
Yes.
She gave me a...
I put a few songs.
I said Digmatized by Jenny McGovern.
Smell Your Dick.
All of those are particularly about porn so much.
So intense.
I'd like to teach the world to fap.
That's good.
That one's related.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Is there anything else to say on this?
I'll fuck everyone who says porn is bad.
I think watching porn definitely needs to be destigmatized, although I don't think that...
There's kind of a double-edged sword here, because if you've ever seen any documentaries or heard behind-the-scenes stuff about how porn is made,
it's definitely a sausage you don't want to know the story behind.
That's true.
There's a lot of drug use, a lot of suicide, a lot of rape.
A lot of people get into porn because they're kind of at the rock bottom.
Yes.
But you have to ask a very serious question, which we probably don't know the answer to,
but these people do do it out of their own free will, and perhaps it's a trap.
Maybe it's a vicious cycle where they can't escape, but there is free agency at work.
If you're into free agency, I am, so I think it's up to them.
I don't know about most people, but I'm really picky about when it comes to really any porn.
I kind of have this sense where I have a harder time watching it if it seems particularly skeevy,
or the people seem like they're really not into it.
If it looks especially fake, the girl looks like she's putting on a show and looks tired.
That's a big reason why I prefer 2D a lot of the time, because there is nothing more attractive to me
about a scene than two people just having the best fucking time.
I am all about that.
I want people to have so much fun while they're having sex.
I've seen live action porn where it looks like they're just having a lot of fun,
where it's funny and kind of cute in a way, and they seem to be pretty into it.
Have you seen the new porn that came out?
There's times where I'm like, that girl seems like she's drugged.
There's times where the girl would just be completely out of it, her pupils are all dilated,
and she's just like, ah, or that.
I'm like, yeah.
Dude, have you seen the new porn that I think Brazzers came out with?
It's like the meme fuck or something.
All they do is they spout TV, from the board on, unfortunately, on TV,
they just spout TV memes the whole time.
This guy takes this girl back home to his house.
The whole family is wearing Bane masks.
This is what they do.
They're doing this the entire time.
Every line of dialogue is just another meme.
Why?
I don't know, dude.
Honestly, people love it.
People, I love it.
I need to plug in this particular moment that you're mentioning.
If anyone can find the professional Scooby-Doo XXX parody, watch it.
It's so, oh my god, it's so funny.
Okay.
Do you know who made it?
No, because he, I had this theory because he's really hard to track down,
because of course I did.
And we had a theory with a friend that maybe it's like a real director in Hollywood,
and that's why it's so good, but they don't want people to know.
Right.
That sounds awesome.
I want to find that.
And they even have like this chase scene where they go through the doors,
but it's like sexy and stuff.
It's so funny.
That sounds amazing.
Oh man, I want to see that shit.
And I feel like the cast that they chose for that one is like even better than the one
that they chose for the live action movie, so.
All right, so I got to get down to this because you're bringing this up.
So are you guys more into porn with a story or concept,
or do you just want to watch people fuck?
To be honest, it depends on the mood.
That's exactly right.
It's exactly right.
Because personally, I have never liked like the story concept porn.
Like it just doesn't do it for me.
There's no way that it's bad all the time.
You probably just haven't seen one that worked for you because Bible Black has a great story
for what it's trying to do.
When I want to watch porn, then I just, like I'm in the mood for porn.
Like I just want to go, like I can see watching a story one if you're in like,
like, you know, if you're watching with other people or something,
and it's just like kind of, and it's really funny.
Although even then it's kind of weird because then when it gets to the porn part,
you're like, well, I'm clearly meant to be watching this by myself.
So like it feels weird.
But like for me, I just.
Just reenact it.
For me, it's like, I've got to be, there's basically like,
I'll say three and sometimes a fourth ways that I'll consume porn, right?
It's either go straight to Ex-Hentai and find a bunch of dojins that have art styles
I like and skip directly to the sex scenes.
I don't even care if it's translated.
I kind of.
You like the setup, Gid?
I like the setup.
I mean, a lot of the time I like the setup.
I kind of need the setup or I don't give a shit.
Yeah, it's sort of like if it's got a good setup and you like the characters are actually cool,
or like it's actually like a manga instead of like a one-off thing,
then I can actually remember it and go back to it and enjoy it again.
Yes, exactly. That's a great point.
I guess there are ones where I like the setup, but usually I sort of find that out.
Like, it'll be that the actual porn part is so good that I like want to now find out what the rest was like.
Like, I've had that experience.
Sure, sure.
Being like, man, that was really cool.
I really liked that. Let's see what the story was.
I mean, come on. Would anybody give a shit about Mega Milk?
About the Mega Milk porn?
If you didn't know that it's a little brother and he had a flat sister,
but then one day she got these massive tits.
I didn't even know that.
And it's like, holy, you didn't know?
I'm not interested in the Mega Milk.
Well, that's your hang-up.
I forgot what I was going to say.
No, but you got to know if the characters grow by fucking.
I mean, honestly, like, why do people read erotic novels?
Like, it's the same thing.
Honestly, a huge part of why...
I remember what I was going to say.
Sometimes, when I've, like, I've read one or two,
I kind of get bored by the sex because if, like, the sex scenes are usually,
the artist draws them the same way every time,
so they have, like, one sex scene and then they talk a bit
and they have another one and it's exactly the same.
It's just their, you know, different time of day.
And I kind of, like, I get it by that point.
So at that point, I just skip to the end to see what the last panel is
and what happens.
I know what you mean.
Not necessarily because, like, it was an interesting story.
I just want to know, like, if there's a joke or something.
Right. Yeah, you want resolution.
Sure, it's understandable.
Like, I think a big part of why I don't, like,
get into the stories and stuff, like, at first
is that, like, I cannot fucking stand, like, porn dialogue,
like, during sex.
I love porn dialogue during sex.
I hate it.
It's the funniest thing in the world.
Honestly, it's the best endogenous.
It ruins everything for me.
It's kind of funny.
It's all the way to my uterus.
Okay, to be honest, the one thing that does annoy me
is the clearly patronizing way.
Like, if someone said, like, oh, you're hitting
all the right spots, like, I'm just fucking flailing
in the dark here.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Like, this virgin guy, it's like, oh, you've got
the biggest dick I've ever had.
It's like, really?
Are you really going to talk like this?
Like, this is obviously fake.
That's the thing I hate as well, is when the guy doesn't
actually have a big dick, but she says it's hitting
her womb every single time.
Oh, like, oh, you were shaped perfectly for me.
This is a stupid dick.
I just think, like, for me, the hitting the womb thing
is, like, that's not, that doesn't feel good for a woman.
Hey, you don't know.
You don't know.
I've been told many times that that is not a pleasant
feeling of having your uterus to land.
Before I started, before I had sex, I already knew
about that same, like, oh my god, you're hitting
the womb, and it sounds terrifying.
And I can't, I don't know what that means,
but it still sounds terrifying.
I mean, there is only so much distance you can go
in a vagina before you hit the wall, right?
I assume if you hit that hard, it probably will hurt.
It's just flesh, right?
Yes.
And you have the most sensibility in the entrance,
anyway.
Right, right.
So, yeah, fun fact about sex.
So, yeah, really weird that that is always in there,
but like...
Honestly, I think that's just Japan.
They like to hear bitches shrieking about shit.
Yeah, I can't think to that.
So, okay, so the first one of the four I was saying
was ex hentai.
Just look at the porn, look at the pictures.
It's all about art style for me.
You want to find someone with a cool art style
and, you know, look at that.
I have a list.
Oh, all of your favorites?
I can plug some people, at least for comics.
Okay.
I want to plug Hiyoko Road,
which I don't know if you can access their work anymore
because they're like exclusive from Faku,
and Faku just became premium, so I'm sorry.
Oh, Faku, what happened, buddy?
Fantastic.
And Fish Turtle Paint,
especially his childhood destruction series,
which I mean, you can get this.
That sounds like a must read.
Okay.
And his Jinx C'mon shoot faster.
I will say if you...
Dude, I read that one.
It's fucking legendary.
Yeah, right?
That one's great.
The only problem with...
That's the one where he makes some Caitlyn and the foodies, right?
Yes.
Yeah, yep, it's the best.
It's the best.
Everyone read it.
But the only problem is if you like him,
I'm just going to put a warning.
He is into some extreme stuff in his original work.
Like, if you're not into electrocution and bestiality,
you might find something like that on his work.
Fair enough, fair enough.
You know what I'm leased into, I think, of all porn?
It's got to be mutilation.
You know, like when they turn a girl into a dog
and they put off their limbs?
Not the biggest fan,
which I only see in, like, dojins, but...
No.
I have it.
I'm totally a vanilla guy,
and I love being a vanilla guy.
I want people happy.
Don't want any piss.
Don't want any scat.
Oh, man.
CC, I'm looking at childhood destruction number five.
This art is so clearly, like, influential to you, specifically.
Yes, I know.
You definitely crib from this style.
And I think I've seen this before.
I think I've probably seen this artist,
because this is totally the style I like, too.
Well, you know, I used one of his pages for Nate's banner,
and he rejected it, and I was so mad,
because after all that work,
after all that cruelling work that you made me do,
I didn't accept my favorite porn page, like, bro.
Wait, what, who, me?
No, yes, I did.
You showed me, like, one...
I think the one picture that you linked me to
was, like, of a dude with their arms and legs chopped off,
and I was like...
No, okay, wait, I'm gonna link it,
because...
Okay, fine.
I made the whole backdrop for his banner that,
and he was like,
I don't know if YouTube is, like...
Oh, oh, you're talking about that.
Okay, yeah, fun fact, people.
Oh, I should have said this before.
Yeah, this would have shown up on a television
if he had, if someone went there.
Yeah, yeah, I'll, I don't know,
should I put this in the description?
I don't know if I'll be allowed to.
Probably not.
Okay, I won't do that.
Basically, CC had surrounded Guy's banner,
like, when you upload a banner to YouTube,
you have to upload, like, this insanely massive image
with all this part that gets cut off on YouTube,
and she filled it up with porn,
but the thing is that the reason you have to have
such a huge banner is that when you watch it
on a television, like, if you browse the site
on a television, it'll have that whole banner in there.
So...
It's a bonus.
Yeah, so anybody who had clicked on it on their TV
would have seen this incredible amount of porn.
Yeah, she was really upset that I didn't use
this super porn.
You can see on that little corner on the vagina,
they put a tiny, like, black brick.
I love when they do the tiny sensors.
It's, it's because in Japan,
you're just not allowed to clearly show...
Show it to your kids.
Yeah, I mean, how are they going to learn
if you censor all their hentai?
Anyway, yeah, this...
Although he draws, like, much bigger titties
that I'm usually into, like, I should,
I want to actually say that, like, this style,
this guy's style is the kind of stuff I really like,
and that's why I like CeCe's art so much
and got her to do the banner for me.
Like, because when CeCe started showing me art,
I was like, this reminds me of the porn I like, and...
Oh, that's a good reason.
Yeah, like, when you drew Shiro holding my pony
and everything, I was like, I would read a dojin
that looked like this, you know, and so...
Yeah, and your banner was pretty much the reason
I wanted her to do mine as well, because I know she's awesome.
Yeah, I guess we should have introduced CeCe as the person
who drew both of our channel banners.
Yes, and did a fantastic job.
And I do a lot of work in the background,
and my commissions are open.
Hey, there you go, we'll put a link in the thing.
Yeah, give me enough money and I will do anything
you ask me to link with.
Damn.
You don't even have to pay.
Well, she did for you just for fun, right?
Yeah, that's true, but don't say that.
No, you have to cut that off, because I don't want that out there.
Nate had to pay, so I always have to.
Yes, but here's the difference.
Your commission didn't almost kill me.
Yeah.
Nate's commission was the worst thing I've ever gone through
in my life.
Really? Was it? Excellent.
I'm glad that I have that reputation for an iron will.
I swear, if I wasn't a masochist...
I've got a guy actually doing another commission
for me right now for an upcoming thing.
I didn't even realize you had said, like,
with me and C.C., it was like,
do whatever you want and send it to me.
Oh, I was very specific.
The only problem was that it was too small,
because I gave her the wrong size on accident.
Dude, even now, I notice little things
that I wish that she would correct, but it's past.
Shut the fuck up, shut up, shut the fuck up.
No, shut up.
I'm gonna be a little more red.
Nate, I will leave this podcast right now.
I have thought about a...
I will draw porn of you getting fucked in the ass.
I would love that.
Feel free, that would be all worth it.
I have considered, like,
now that I'm realizing I could just throw money at this
to make it happen,
switching the characters in
and the names out on my banner
because of Gintoki getting cut off by my face
on all of them.
And it's occurred to me over time
that it was funny that we just kind of added
the extra characters on as opposed to moving them inward.
That would have been a good idea.
Although I don't know if you can do that.
I don't know how many...
That's the thing, I don't know how many layers this was drawn on.
Like, is every character their own layer
or is it all just, like, drawn?
No, painter doesn't work that way.
The final version's just one layer.
And it's...
Yeah, so it'd be a pain in the ass to change anything, right?
I would rather just do the whole thing over.
Really?
How much would that cost me, though?
Guys, can we talk business after the podcast?
Sure, why not?
I just sent another link.
I don't know if I ever showed you that, did you?
But I got bored while doing your thing.
Yeah, I remember this.
It's covered in dicks.
It's covered in dicks, for any reason.
Let's move on because I want to talk about something else
related to porn real quick.
I wrote a little...
I wrote a little thing in my notebook
because I wanted to make a point earlier
when did you was talking about how the porn industry
is really dangerous for people.
And I wanted to make a point that that's why it's important
that it stops being taboo because the more recognized it gets,
it's an actual job as an industry,
it gets more regulated,
and then there won't be as much cases
because people won't feel like they're doing something wrong.
They won't feel like it's their last chance,
just like, hey, if you like getting fucked,
here's an option for a job and it's okay.
And I'm just throwing it out there.
I've got expendable income.
I would happily throw down 100 bucks
to just have sex with someone one time.
But, you know, that's impossible. It can't be done.
We need to legalize that too.
Honestly, it should all be legalized.
I don't see any reason why I could...
Decriminalize it and then it won't be...
people won't be criminals while doing it.
And we won't end up with a country full of
extremely sexually repressed men
who have no choice but to shut up schools.
The saddest thing about that
is, like, even on anyone's
political ticket,
you know, like, marijuana
and everything is, like, on everyone's
has to have a stance on it.
But, like, no one has a stance on a prostitution.
It's kind of hard.
The reason it's not a stunt
is because you can't talk about it
because it's taboo, so you can't have that
as a selling point in the first place.
So, this podcast is the first step
in correcting this problem.
Everyone call up your local politician
and tell them to make prostitution legal.
Hey, Bernie, you gotta add to the ticket.
We gotta legalize prostitution.
Give me the horse, Bernie.
Okay, let's move on
to something else that
I bet nobody was expecting us to talk about,
and that is
the end of civilization due to porn.
Okay, so let me
hear what you guys think about this.
So, I see porn
as just one symptom.
The rise of porn, the increase in porn,
I don't think it's the cause of
an increasingly,
what's the word?
isolationist society.
You know that episode
of Futurama where they had the sex robots
and it caused the destruction of all of humanity
because everyone was too busy fucking their sex robots
to do anything?
That's what you're talking about, right?
Okay, that's true, but I'm a little more optimistic
slash realistic where I think that
as long as shit needs to be done
people will be around and get to do it.
But that is only until
we hit the AI
singularity. And by the way, this is what I wanted
the movie her to be about. I was hoping
her would be about a society where people
like become isolated
by getting these AIs
that will just interact with them and give them all
the social interaction they need, and as well as
you know sexual gratification or whatever else they need
we will have the technology to do that
that does not involve any other human beings
fairly soon, and when that happens
as well as the singularity
happens, AIs will become more competent than
human beings at everything, and humans
will have all of our needs already met
we won't need to do anything ourselves
so when that happens, I think it's only
a matter of time before humans are basically
just weaned out and AIs
take over, but really
to get not even about that, I'm just more interested
in whether or not you think
porn itself is a destructive element
only in the sense that
it's dooming humanity because
it's forcing us, or it's allowing us
to not take responsibility
to kind of force ourselves to have
social interactions anymore, because honestly
sex is the driving force of
everything that a human being has probably ever done
at least for guys, that's the major one
yes, that's the whole
saying that vagina is the highest
priced thing on the market
and without
a, you know, porn
with porn and like sex robots that are coming
and all of that stuff, by the way, Oculus Rift
I'm gonna get that, gonna get that a fuck machine
gonna get one of those installed
that's gonna be great
I will have fun
what incentive will anyone have
to pursue any kind of actual
you know, romantic
inclination, because
marriage itself is kind of going away
which
does in fact have, I mean
whether you agree with like getting divorced or not
I'm not talking about that, I'm just saying that
children are worse off when they don't have
parents who are married
I'm not in favor of it at all
but children do better when their parents
are kind of forced to stay together
and forced to have a stable relationship
and without all that shit and with all this other stuff
I'm just saying, it's not looking too good
what are your thoughts?
my thoughts are, I don't give a shit
about any of the things you just said
because I'm gonna go get a wife
and have a daughter and then
I'm gonna be a cool dad and that's all I care about
so you want to have like a real family
yeah, and the whole
me too actually
the whole idea that everything will be
ruined
it's a bit
too cynical
I don't think you can get rid of
well, I don't know
maybe a few generations down the line
but it really depends on what humans value
because for us
we have grown up in an era where
it's not there yet and we
grew up idolizing
our parents who raised
children
I think for us it's more
natural to be like
even though
things are very different for our generation
because the age that people
A should be having
and B do have kids
keeps getting older
I think for all of us, I don't know about CC
but for the three of us
probably none of us envision ourselves having a kid before age 30
at all
I don't want to have kids
not at all
and that's another thing, I don't know any women who want to have kids
all the women I know are like
completely against it
have you seen it?
do you know what goes on?
oh my god, it's awful
yeah, it's pretty fucked up
everything about it
it's a super selfless act
I mean, you're trading your
body, at least for a while
just to have this baby
honestly, that's kind of too long term
for most people, I think of our generation
to be that interested in when they're young
the fact that you get like
a drug released in your brain to love
the baby
and it permanently changes your brain chemistry
you become a different person
that's basically like a fucking
Kafka book, that's awesome
but that is like you being physically changed
from the person you used to be into a mom
and you know, I bet a lot of like
22, 25 year olds
who are you know, just hanging out
sorry I'm late for the podcast
I was busy
masturbating to porn
Jesse, we're talking about the air singularity
and the doom of humanity
the sad thing is Jesse came in for porncast
at a moment when we were talking about childbirth
like the exact opposite of what anyone was hoping for
in a porn cast
he inserted himself
into the podcast
I raped a woman
so Nate is talking about
this insane theory that
humankind is going to die
because of porn
I guess it is a theory in the sense that I don't think
it's definitely going to happen
but it's something that I think about sometimes
I think what I was trying to say is
the reason that
people are you know, porn is on the rise
is because people are so sexually repressed
and if we ever
solve that whole problem
of people being all repressed
then I don't think sex will ruin
the world like that
that's actually a good point
sex could become less valuable
and we turn our eyes to just making progress
because we want to
people just need to stop putting that pussy up on a pedestal
you know what I'm saying
well that's the thing like if
there's two different kinds of theories
there's the theory that
once our sexual needs are met
we feel no need to do anything
because we don't have to prove anything
but then I think
in my mind the opposite would happen
which is that we're sexually satisfied
so now we can just work
on the things we actually want to do
because like why do most people work
jobs they don't like
because they need more money
and you need more money because
you have to impress women
you want more influence in the world
imagine yourself
if you never had
the problem
Nate if you never need
I'm telling you specifically because
you're in this sort of boat
you're more of a classical stand up comedian
guy who he's talking about type
person
if you had
all of your sexual appetite
solved
you never had to worry about women
then all the money that you would need
to make is just for yourself
and what you want to do
so would you not live a far more
austere lifestyle
because like you're just like
oh all I need is like
I need the clothes on my back and a nice
computer and then I could do like
follow my dreams and just do what I want to do
that's pretty much how I live right now
I spend all my money
that's how I live right now
to honestly make my channel better
there's some extent
you wouldn't even have to worry about
your image that much because
he gets ex regardless
if anyone looks
at me in my lifestyle
you'll see I'm not putting any effort
into trying to like get women
but what I do always concern myself with is like
how do I make
my how do I make more money
through my channel because eventually
in the long run I want financial
stability so I can have my own
place so I could have a wife
and a kid you know like in the long
run I would like that to happen but
if those weren't concerns
it was like sex is always
fine and like I can just adopt a brat
or something like it's like I only need to make
enough money to impress myself
or whatever
so yeah
maybe if sex
was no longer the reward
we were all seeking for doing good work
then we would all do work that we like
you know what I call this
something I always bring up
it's the Star Trek
method it's like in Star Trek
you have everything
they say want they have eliminated want
you have everything you could ever need
and what happens in Star Trek they just decide
you know what we're just going to like figure
shit out that's just what we're gonna do
with our lives as human beings
that's my dream
that that is what happens when we're liberated
from our beastly instincts
I mean how many times have you
this happens to me a lot right
this happens mostly with like working out
type stuff but I'm gonna use a more concrete example
to make sense like let's say that
I broke a table
in my room right
and I know that
because I have obligations
to my job and my work
and I have to do certain things and I have stress
limits you know like I can't
I can't constantly be learning new things
and doing new things right
and if a table broke in my house I'd be like
man I really
wish that I knew how to be a carpenter
and I could fix it myself
because it sounds like it could be cool and fun
and it would be a great way to spend my time
but I have to go through all this practice
and all this other shit and I got work tomorrow
and I just want to go to bed you know
I'll hire somebody who already does that
but imagine if I didn't have to worry about that
if like work was just something I did for fun
and like my whole life is just whatever I want to do
and a table breaks and I'm like I'm gonna learn
and like put it back together
I'm with you but to play devil's advocate I'm just afraid
my fear in this situation is that
we won't have the Star Trek mentality
instead we'll have the oh I don't need to do that
oh I don't need to make food
I don't need to learn how to cook
I don't need to learn how to get girls to have sex
I don't need to learn how to do anything
and then as a result everyone is just a worthless
I'm gonna say that as the most
pampered person I know
I still have a very strong desire to better myself
so well I'm glad to hear that
yeah
alright we've gotten like way off the actual
subject of porn itself
exactly what I wanted to say
everyone just go to your local
king community
right and meet them
outside of it and they're just really happy
so there's your answer Nate
everyone you can ever meet
to your king community that go to like
orgy parties and stuff and their weekends
and just go back to work
wait you can just say it like it's just that simple
where can I find an orgy party
for like 10 years
I don't know where they live
where do the orgy people live
CC comes from a vastly superior community
than we do
so please share with us your knowledge on this
where can I find my orgy community
I don't know
every city or so
they have something that they call their king community
so you should just have to look it up
and you'll get like a little organization
they usually like townhouses and stuff
the problem with that
is that you're talking to us
and we all hate people
we hate like
99% of all people
I would love a woman who let me have sex with her
well the thing about
that's the thing an orgy party
that's not even a guarantee for me
I don't think I can even say that
and an orgy party
involves being around
a lot of people
in a situation where you have to deal with them
you don't have to talk
well you'll probably have your mouth full anyway
now hang on CC
but if we're in one of these situations
and we're not getting verbal consent at every step
then you've just committed rape
so how are we supposed to
everyone signs off usually
before going in whatever room
what if I revoke my permission
like they sign a release
well no one's the fucking monster
like you guys
as an expert on rape
this is America we have to be aware of these things
that most people don't report it
are you willing to take that risk
you want to go to jail forever be a rapist forever
in the eyes of the public
in the eyes of Reddit
that's a two part question
I don't want to go to jail but I do want to be a rapist forever
I want to
I think if I go to an orgy
and there's a release form
I'm gonna have like talismans and shit on me
like
I don't know
I just feel like
when she said they're not Yo-Kai and I was like
are they not
well you don't have to
orgy party was just an example
it can be anything else
like the BDSM convention
sometimes it's just people looking at you and your partner
or whatever it is
but what if I don't want to have like kinky sex
I just want to have normal sex
is there like a community for normal sex people
I bet there is
I'm sure there is
Jesse has gone on record of saying
that his fetish is the missionary position
yeah
I like fucking
me on top, eyes locked
socks off a fucking woman
socks off
no stockings on that's the correct
lights off
I don't want to see her
I'm sure there's places for normal people
but
I don't look for them
so
right
you can ask a normal person
you can ask me about
where to look for animals
where titties get fucked
where you get normal sex
it's hard to find communities of people
who share my perversion
but also share my hatred for weirdos
right
yeah
like I said you're talking to us
we hate 99%
of all people
the hardest thing
I think all of us could probably get laid
pretty easily if we were willing to
have sex with normal average people
and we didn't have
strangeness averages
it's not looking good
we all have like really weird
not like I don't want to say high standards
because I don't think it's necessarily that we all demand
that we have sex with someone attractive
honestly I want a girl who's not fat
I'm in America
is that too much to ask
it is
my only standard
I hate fat girls
I hate them
I don't respect them as human beings
I want them to go away from America
they're the real witches
we need to deport them out of our country
have Donald Trump build a wall
I guess I can't pretend my personality standards
are that high
because the girl I did have sex with
had the exact ideological
opposite of me in every conceivable way
and not in a way where
that was like hot
it was just weird
for a girl
if you want to go have normal sex
you have to go to a bar or dance
or talk to people
wait how is that different for a guy
you can walk in a room and someone will fuck you
then I'll take that option
over talking to someone
in small talk about their
what their profession is
torture
I'd rather put a bullet in my dick
than be at a fucking party
and there's like a girl who's hot
and I have to fucking come up with some retarded
conversation topic
and come up to her like hey
I like this band
that is currently playing
the fucking Avril's
Avril Lavigne's my favorite new punk rock band
yeah
exactly
so I'll take communities
over
I think Cece has taught us all a valuable lesson today
fuck the normies
that's always it
that's nothing new but
it's good to be reinforced
I hate people so much because
I was actually recently
with a woman for like a week
and he means recently
as in like yesterday
cause like
I hate people so much
that like even when you're like having
like Cece is a good thing
generally for me
I'm fond of it
it's one of my favorite hobbies
I like it as Donatello likes stuff
yes
the stuff that I like
I love stuff
I love munching rug
however
yeah
it's like
having a girl
I'm gonna find the Donatello in my local kink community
how do we get into that
is it just a club of guys with like purple
me?
I'm like in unison
yeah it's a pizza party
I love stuff
I'm eternal and I can't get up
I stepped on a frog
I hope it will
okay what was your point Jesse?
trying to figure out what you're getting to
I think a girl here for a couple days
fucking her 10 times a day
in every one of us is awesome and great
the sweat glands
are the little known best hole
but there are times when I question
if even that is worth it
when a girl is here for days at a time
like I hate people so much
it's not even like an aggressive
like a bitter hatred
like I'm fine with it
but having a person
around me
is like psychological torture
dude let me tell you, whenever I've stayed over
with any of my girlfriends
even two days
with the same person trapped with them
is a complete nightmare
and honestly I think one of the reasons we all get along so well
is because this is a purely opt-in community
we've got here, we've got this Skype group
and we only talk when we feel like it
if you don't want to talk, you just leave
but it's not like anything
it's the worst with how I tend to see
I meet girls online
with those kind of relationships
because with an online relationship
she comes over to visit for a fucking week
and you have to spend that whole time together
if you're in a real relationship
eventually you get to the point where you know
when to leave each other the fuck alone
and then from there it's smooth sailing
that's where the online shit man
so to tie what is rapidly becoming
a discussion about sex
back into porn
I want to clarify that I don't think
that sex is a replacement
for jacking off
I agree
because sometimes it's just not feasible
I think they both have very different appeals
and that doing one immediately
after the other is often
necessary for me
we're all guys here right
so we know
not all
I can't speak to the female
sex drive, maybe it's exactly the same
I don't know
but I pretty much have a compulsion
to fap every single day of my life
and if I don't do it
that's just me punishing myself for no reason
so why would I do that
I'm not going to arrange sex every day
even if I was married
you don't want to have sex every single day with you
they don't
well CC you're an angel
you're one of the good ones
at least in America
I guess I can only talk about America
fapping is
a lot of fun
and I think it's kind of underrated
I think part of the reason
people don't like to talk about jacking off
is that it makes it sound like they don't get laid
people don't want to say
oh I just jack off by myself
all the time
because they want to think
when I want to get off I have sex
with a woman because I'm awesome
I jack off now when I'm having sex with a woman
yeah I've done that as well
yeah one of the ones who has
I will stop sex to jack off
it's like
on the other room
there's no chance
that another person you're having sex with
for the first time is going to know what you want
honestly I'm not sure after 50 years
unless you're very specific that's true
she's right about that but even then there's a lot of fumbling
there's a lot of figuring shit out
I never realized how much better I understood
my dick than someone else
until my girlfriend tried to give me a
handjob and I was like
what are you doing
people don't talk at all during sex
give instructions during it
it's fine
every girl was like
oh I know how to give the best
just listen to the guy
this conversation kind of during sex needs to be thrown
in the trash and die about yesterday
I've talked about this before
I've done stand-up bits about it
people who think that
dirty talk should ever be a thing
we're not talking about dirty talk
this is not dirty talk
she's talking about having sex that works
but I will say
don't expect it to necessarily solve anything
because they don't know what the fuck you're talking about
because when my ex is trying to give a handjob
the conversation would be like this
no like
do you like with this?
do it
please stop
first of all there's an art form to it
you got to do it the right way
second of all it's obviously worth doing
because
if you want any
you should never have sex with a person once
it's just retarded to have a one night stand
you might as well work that for a few times
so why not cultivate a little bit of understanding
of what you want out of the person
that's just the smart way to go
that's why it's like
everyone has to talk about it
I'm not at all implying it's bad to have a one night stand
lord knows I have a few of my own
I'm a big believer
in getting notches on the belt
that's my main priority in life
beyond actually pleasuring someone
I mean if you want to bring home someone from a bar
who's just some trashy whore
that's great more power to you could not
be more in favor of it but
I'm just saying I think it's
an inefficient use of your time
to only bang someone once
because you have to put all that work and getting to know them
and doing all that shit
I mean if they're just drunk and they want to have sex
that's totally fine but
it's more practical to make it work
at least for a couple times
I generally think that sex is better when there's
a friendship or something there
yeah and like how first time sloppy sex is boring
the second, third, fourth time
when you start to figure each other out that's the best
there's always going to be something that you do on a one night stand
that the other prince is like oh my god
I want to tell them to stop
because this is awful and it's the worst
and I will tell everyone I know about it but you know I can't
because I don't know this person
but to get back to fapping man
you can make a whole
you know it's just because it's you by yourself
and you can really like you know they say
it's self indulgence you can truly
indulge yourself
you can go all out
what?
I was just saying like so is like eating
an ice cream cone but that's not like
something to be ashamed of exactly
it's just something you do
but mate if you masturbate you will go blind
no you're right
vitamin deficiency what was I thinking
I'm never doing it I'm swearing it off
I'm swearing it off
I have to ask like
so do you guys when you look at porn
is it pretty consistent
or do you randomly get
into the mood for weird fucking
like fucked up shit
yeah I definitely go through like
it will escalate
yeah
I want to watch porn and it's like oh my god
now I need to like watch this one video
that I watched two years ago with the clown
and the puppy
I had something of a renaissance in my days
nothing gets me hotter these days than flat girls
I'm into flat girls right now
I don't know it's a complete about
it's a 180 for my entire life
you know what we need to do an entire
podcast about flat girls because they're
I am down they are underappreciated
I think everybody knows that I am more
into
I think it's pretty widely known
that I'm not that into big titties
or big ages
you know into those
I want to get to that
in a second
but like
I have an interesting question
do you find that
your sexual preference are always
the same as your porn preferences
you mean like in real life
not at all honestly there's nowhere near
the choice
there's no way I could achieve my preferences
in real life
I could but if you could do you like
who wears purple all the time but I can't do that
I mean like if you could
do you like fantasize about doing those things
yourself or is it like completely different
Niko Robin would be the greatest sex that any human
being would ever have in their entire lifetime
there is no doubt about it she can generate infinite body parts
you just have to use a little bit of imagination
to think about what she could do sexually
and she can make clones of herself
Niko Robin is the best woman of all time just putting that out there
okay let's move on
what you're asking is like
if I'm not looking at porn am I fantasizing
about the same kind of things that I saw
in porn then the answer is yes
but if you're talking about like
what am I attracted to in a human being
then no
and usually I don't go
like if I look at like women
I'm not comparing them to
like a standard I already have
it's more like I see a girl and I go
oh she's cute in that way
like I didn't expect that
like in porn I have almost exclusively
been into shorter smaller women
but then my first girlfriend was like
6 foot 3 or something
when she towered over me
but I was still attracted to her for her own reasons
yeah go on Suzy
I feel like it's an important message to get out
like everyone has that same opinion but people are still like
no if you watch like this kind of porn
that will like make you into degenerate
which I'm not necessarily
I'm staunchly opposed to the idea
that anything you
watch has any effect on the way
you act
the way you act is entirely determined by
your worldview what kind of person you are
if you are someone
by the way you know I've read a lot of
stuff about psychology and one of the
number one things that comes up
in a mental disorder
look no
I'm just saying this isn't a bragging thing
this is a fucking pointing it out to people
thing alright
the number one thing
that is a sign of mental disorder is if you
tell the difference between fantasy and reality
oh shit
that is always a sign of mental disorder
dropping the bomb
so if you think that porn is going to cause
people to not be able to tell the difference
between it just means those people are fucking
crazy right so let's just say right now
let me say every
even all the porn I don't like
I'm still totally in favor of it existing
I'm just going to tell you I faptololi
all the time what are you going to do about it
tell me what you're going to do about it
baby girls what are you going to do about it
it's really funny to me
because the procrastinators chat
this is not why
we became friends because
I guess we were all into my little pony
so maybe we're all psychopaths
the procrastinators is essentially
a support group for
former brony celebrities
the funny thing about the
procrastinators podcast is
this is the place I've never been
anywhere where
everyone so unanimously
like to lolly
stuff with no
with no one having come in there with that intention
like everywhere I've ever been
there's at least someone who's like
that's funny get me out of here that's disgusting
wait a minute
you're making it sound like we're all
way into
lolly's like
I'm just saying that we managed to make
more jokes about pedophilia
in the procrastinators chat
anyone has probably ever made
in history
and none of us have a there's no guy
in the chat who's like
you gross like there's no one like that
in there
we wouldn't keep someone like that around
I guess but it's just funny to me that
even when we added like the DeVoo
he's the same way
and he brought his own barrel of laps
to that equation
his own smorgasbord of bizarre fetishes
yeah honestly he's the weirdest of us all
when it comes to this stuff
he should be here
he didn't want to come in because he didn't want to share
how weird his fetishes are
that's why I was scared of coming here
so I would be safer if I had someone else
don't worry CC
we'll defend you to use the earth
that fucking bizarre
see that's the thing
this is why I was bringing up like getting into moods
if I was to say
what is perfect for me
something kind of romantic
and cute
the anime series
I can't understand what my husband is saying
not only is that my favorite romance
but if there was a porn of that
it would be the best porn ever
but isn't that because of the story
the stories kind of involved in that
I'd say it's the
the story, the context
nailed him
but sometimes
I want to watch
a little girl get torn to shreds by demons
while they rape her in every hole
and then I go lip that up and fathom it
and it's great
if the art style is great that's all that matters to me
if I'm going through X Hentai
and I see a really cool art style
and I click on it and it turns out to be some really insane shit
if the art style is cool
then it's still gonna be like well alright
I guess this is what we're in for today
can we talk about the prices
that we're having right now in Hentai
having way better covers than their actual anime
like I feel so betrayed
when that happens and it's
getting out of control right now
someone needs to talk about this
you wanna talk about a crisis
there is an epidemic
of Hentai dojins
of famous anime
where the girls are way out of character
and that drives me insane
if I fucking
well I mean some circles like
to make stuff where they like
reinterpret characters and as long as that's like
clearly what it is
reinterpretation is one thing but the personality
there's people who
are just like this is popular right now
and I need money so I'm just gonna make it
I'm not gonna watch the anime or whatever
I just I know how they look
no thought kills a boner faster
than Misada would never fucking say this
yeah that's pretty
well that's why I don't read the dialogue in my porn
well you're missing out dude
there's some good stuff in there honestly
you'll get more out of it
so it's all about the mind
I gotta read the dialogue I gotta be invested in a scenario
as a rule I only watch
Hentai subtitled and read dojin
she's it up and down
when it comes to anime porn
I turn off the audio
I hopefully can find one without subtitles
what are the noises
because their voices are fucking terrible
you gotta have the noises
I can't stand the fake ass noises
the girls going
the girls do generally sound retarded
if you do
your job correctly you will hear those
noises in real life
I will actually
I will actually master baiting which I do often
I imagine him
go on
I imagine him turning off
the audio
turning off the lights lighting a bunch of candles
playing some death grips over it
that's not inaccurate
pulling up a big tarp
of MC ride
talking to himself in that cockney voice
alright
she's a nasty guy
you're a white fucking wanker
you are
you're talking to his dick when you say that
I usually do have my own music playing because I always have music playing
I can't be without music
you got in the mood
you can't be playing just any kind of music when you're jacking off
well actually I can
and I'll ask shit sometimes I'll just be like
I'm listening to game grumps
and I just start fucking watching porn while listening to game grumps
I don't even care
yeah
but if I do want to be like
if I want it to be like special
I'm in the mood
you gotta play enigma dude
you gotta listen to MCMXCAD
the sexiest album of all time
you gotta just find
a well audio mixed
pentai like resort bowen has pretty good audio mixing
in terms of the music
jazz shit but like that's just one example
I just mute it and I play my own shit
there's no bad music that should sacrifice the moans
I agree
if I do keep the audio on
I turn it really low in the mix
so I just barely hear it
like underneath my music
like I can hear it somewhere in the background
but what I'll also do is
when I go to look at porn I'll open up like six different tabs
and have them all running at the same time
and then whichever one
whichever one has the least obnoxious voices
I'll leave the audio on
in that tab
and then even when I'm looking at the other stuff
I'll just be listening to the other audio
so like whichever girl
has the hot voice
her voice is coming out of all the other girls
and that makes a lot of sense
nothing worse than coming on the first tab
and having to in shame
tell me about it
you gotta make it all the way through
well it's sad because
when I go on a porn excursion
I don't like save my progress
or anything right
you open up 17 fucking tabs
on X Hentai
and all of them looked like they were probably good
but then if you find one that's so
amazing early on
that you end up coming to that one
and then you're like I will never know
what the other 16 were like
every porn excursion is like a playthrough of Dark Souls
whatever happens happens
you just gotta live with it
but with Dark Souls you can eventually learn it
it's just gone forever
it's more like a roguelike
that's why fapping has endured
as an activity because it's
procedurally generated
it might as well be
I don't know I'm pretty organized
I think I keep track of most things
that I look at new releases
consume it the same way I do anime
I know some people like
and those are the people I call the porn experts
cause the funny thing is
definitely a porn expert
there are a few friends who are like that
who can like name actresses
or name artists and stuff like that
I'm the guy who every single time
it's just completely new
it's never the same thing
did CC just say hi mom?
are you talking to your mom right now?
no I just found it funny that
they might find this
oh okay
the thing is like
I feel like I probably
if you see this
that like total amount
I feel like I look at more porn
than a lot of the people I would consider porn
experts because
I just look at everything and then throw it all away
and like the only stuff I save
I would challenge you on that
the only stuff I keep around is
if I find something that I
cause if I'm on like X-Hentai and I find something
I really love the art
I'll go look at the artist, I'll look at all their other stuff
and then I'll just favorite one of their things
so that I can get back to that artist in the future
and like keep up with them
you know what I've been doing lately?
I just go to Hentai Gasm
and then just all on the bottom
it's a great Hentai site
on the bottom they've got tons of links for more stuff
that have pretty great looking
little preview windows
and I just open up a bunch of tabs of those
let them play and see which one's the best
and then just focus on that one
honestly it's the best system I've ever had for this shit
we should all name drop some websites
Hentai Gasm for sure
and cause well most of the Hentai that I watch
is subtitled in Spanish
and you know
most of the websites I frequent are deep
websites with no real names
alright I'm into that dark web shit
if you're just into like porn in general
this is not a great resource for anime stuff
or Hentai but the big list of porn
is an index of
virtually every worthwhile porn site
ever they have like
thousands of reddits listed
of like all of the
streaming sites that are worthwhile
they're all ranked by the way
it's a ranked list of every worthwhile porn site
the only thing they're really missing out
like they have an adult art section
but it's not that in depth
personally for anime stuff
I usually just go to
Hentai.animestigma
but they like half the fucking shit's broken there
so it's really not a good right
the great thing about them is that
they bring out stuff when it's new
you know you actually can't keep up with new releases
there to some extent but like
all their old shit's broken so you gotta go find it somewhere else
but uh
and then X Hentai is the
ultimate like manga and
dojin resource like you'll never find
something with more shit than that
except for like a torrent site
what happened to Faka, they were my favorite
oh by the way, quick, end them to previously
you know when I said I fapped to little girls
just to be clear I was talking about the animated ones
just wanted to throw that out there
just for any FBI agents
listening to this podcast
who are big fans of ours
I forgot I was gonna make sure we had an 18 plus
warning at the top of this show
but do we need one? I don't know
I don't think we've said anything
it's called porn
well I think porn is something that everyone of every age
can appreciate
I just raped the woman
I don't think there's an age high enough
for this to be appropriate
we talked about rape
about attacking people killing things
why is it that porn is the one that gives us that
18 rating?
because sex is way more taboo
than violence
it's not so much that we're talking about sex
as it is that we're talking about
decapitation sex
so sex plus
violence is like extra bad
versus like normally we could talk about sex
or normally we could talk about
we never talked about violence on this show
we've described a violent scenario
I've threatened to burn down people's houses before
that's pretty violent
so who here has seen
shade base?
I fucking hate that guy
who's that?
he's this hentai artist
he draws a lot of western cartoons
and anime, like comics
but he's one of those guys who
never stops inserting
his weird fetish into everything he fucking draws
so sometimes I'll just be going down
looking for porn
of a certain show
that I'm into
I want to look at a porn of Teen Titans today
and you find one
and inevitably
his stuff comes up because for some fucking reason
it's really popular
well he's been around forever
and you can tell that he has the skills
to be a decent
illustrator
but everything he draws is like
all the girls have g-cups
these massive floppy
drooping titties with lactating
shooting blood and semen out of their butts
and it's all butt sex
there's never any actual
he's against vaginal sex
there's this one here I'm enjoying
that's of a Gestapo chick
she's puckering her asshole and says
get in there you filthy Jew rats
I can get into this
every shade base comic is like
licking someone else's butthole
let me tell you from experience
licking buttholes gets old real quick
oh my god it's actually Wednesday Adams
doing this dressed up like a Gestapo
yes it is
awesome
okay well Nazi Wednesday Adams is in fact my fetish
so he gets a pass on that one
pardon
but yeah he's very like
he's the center of
what I think is on the internet
that kind of torture porn
especially for cartoons and childhood ruining
and controversial
like he'll draw Nazis and stuff
and mutilation
hey I want to do two quick shout outs real quick
first of all to this guy
probably my favorite animator of porn stuff right now
this guy Pinoy toons
you guys seen this guy he makes by far
it's kind of like a realistic
style he's on new grounds he's on like
I don't know whatever google Pinoy toons
he makes some of the best he's got this
fantastic Nico Robin scene
the one thing about this guy though is he
is always the guy in the scene
it's kind of weird he animates himself
being the one I just
you gotta look past that
but if he's basically a more talented Chris Chan
I assume that like
his purpose is to like
give Filipino guys like an outlet
to put themselves in porn or something
well let me recommend
Salty Ice Cream
as my favorite animator
she only does gifts
but I love it whenever she
updates and she's just a lot of different
characters and they're really cool
and the animation show
this is the person who did
the Pokemon ones right
probably like she's
like started with I don't know
well this is like the same art style
it must be
these are kind of beautiful in a non-sexable way
yeah exactly so
they're all commissioned right yeah
cause this person like there were these couple of
he does raffles and patreon
there were a couple of animations
of like
white from Pokemon White
going like a
like what's the word
not ass to ass but they were doing that
that motion but with a
like a double sided dildo with the
the other girl from that
from white and like the fun head ones
yeah there were like two gifts of that
that were like unbelievably well animated
and everyone was like where the fuck did these come from
cause there was nothing else by him on the internet
at the time and then started doing commission work
and I guess this is where it's come
I assume this is the same person cause it looks
exactly like it that really smooth animation
I'm just like
I'm just like hypnotized right now watching this
are you watching the tatsumaki gift
the girl from one punch man
just like yeah tatsumaki come on
step it up I haven't fucking
and my favorite not say for
regardless in general has to
be pow foo but he mostly does
like he works
he's a contract working in hard blood
so he mostly does gay stuff
so I don't know if you guys
he's posing it so good
I also use him a lot as reference
pow foo
man I'm excited to know that this
this salty ice cream person has done more
work now
yeah this is awesome cause
for a long time there wasn't a lot
you know I'm gonna this is one
another shout out that I am really a big
fan of but kind of is always the exact same
thing it's just this circle
naruhou
that basically does mostly
I know it's very clever
it's mostly naruto stuff
but like it's just the specific art style
he's got everyone's very round everyone's
super thick and they've got it's just
it's very like it's very like
in your face pussy and like in your face
this is what's happening they're not really focused
on the other shit google naruhou
he's got a bunch of them there's like some one piece ones
it's great stuff great stuff
well also acid head no
also does acid head
acid heads awesome as well
two favorite dojin guys
so I uh
I don't want to like
share any of my favorite
porn manga artists because I'm like
weirdly possesses of them
cause I feel like if I recommend them to people
no one will appreciate them as much as I do
or for the same reasons
do you ever have that feeling
only about my wifos
like if you don't find it as hot as I do
so instead
I'm just gonna recommend what I would consider to be
the best anime
sex scene ever
which is uh which you can
if you want to you can pretend
retroactively that this is a sex scene
between ruby and sapphire from steven
universe cause it's a girl with blue hair
and a girl with red hair and they have about that stature
but it's uh from the
classic anime
uh cream lemon
I believe is the name
pop chaser this episode is mostly
famous for the fact that like a lot of big name
animators worked on it but they mostly
worked on like action scenes and stuff
what people don't talk about is how it also has
the best lesbian sex scene
and possibly best sex scene ever in anime
history it is like
six minutes long
really beautifully animated really sensual
feels like totally
it's like emotional like I
like I was fapping and crying
at the same time watching this thing
often brings us up as his favorite
yeah no it's incredible and there's
other porn anime that
has great animation and weirdly it's usually
lesbian like uh
stainless night has like really
beautiful animation but it's
not expressive the way that
pop chaser is like that pop chaser scene
is so detailed and there's so much
movement and stuff that it's like whoa
like it almost feels like it was
rotoscoping a real sex
scene but like an actually intimate one
I don't know it's really great and you should all check it out
it's easy to find just google like
pop chaser lesbian sex scene on google
and you'll like you'll get a video of it
on some porn site but like uh
uh yeah that stainless night is great animation
there's a few
there's a few weird ones oh you were you were
mentioning earlier like like a real
Hollywood director that you thought had done
that Scooby-Doo porn parody
um yes great example
in anime is the famous director
Akiyuki Shinbo
who did like Madoka and
Bakemonogatari and like all these
you know other popular shows
there was a like a period of
three years where he just did porn
under a pseudonym
I don't remember the pseudonym but like everyone knows
it's him because his fucking visual style is so
distinct that it couldn't possibly be anyone else
but he did one called Temptation
one called Swallowtail in
one called uh
something to do with nurses it wasn't
night shift nurses but a different one
and then uh also
was it called sibling secret
all of them are like really
fucked up like the
art style is tricky and
in esoteric oh and Blood Royale was the other one
he did they're all like uh
like just like a lot of rape
lots of like humiliation
one of Blood Royale has
scat in it and there's just like
all kinds of like you know it's just like
really out there and the visuals are so intense
that it just makes it that much crazier
but uh but Temptation in particular
or you Aku as it's known
in Japanese like even though it's all
like rape and and like
stuff like that it's really
well animated like it's
it's really kind of like Bible Black
where it's just like wow they put a lot of effort
into this hang on hang on I'm looking
at Salty Ice Cream's Tumble here and I notice
on the top right it says not safe for work blog
all characters depicted
are 18 plus can we just
tell you how Wednesday Adams is not 18
plus
you have to say that
you always have to say that
no but you have to say legally
speaking if you're getting money for them
even if it's patron you have to say
even if it's like oh
yes you have to
because if you ever looked at any dojin
ever they all say
all characters are 18
you have to say that legally
but it's literally not true
they can just say all characters depicted are not
being real
why don't they just say that
it's not necessarily not true
the character in the context of their story
isn't 18 but in the context of yours
you still have to say it
I don't want them to be 18
I want them to be 9
there is a hilarious amount of dojins I've
read where it starts off by saying
the characters in this are 18 and over
and then during the sex scene the guy will
literally be screaming I'm fucking an elementary school
student
yeah that's it
that's true
and has dwarfism just coincidentally
and all of her friends also have dwarfism
and have all been held back
I hate that more than anything in the world
I want to burn it with a thousand suns
by the way I have to shout out another beautifully
animated porn stuff from
Mezzo Forte and Kite
especially Mezzo Forte has
Mezzo Forte in particular
has like
an extremely fappable cutscene
in the middle of this otherwise completely
it's actually a dream sequence
or no it's not a dream scene it's something else
the guy who did
both of those like he
what's his face he's interesting
he has like a very distinct art style he also did
most recently he did wizard
barristers and
I don't remember what else he did designs for
I think maybe not witch hunter
robin something like that
kitty grade he did the designs
for kitty grade all of his art is like
very really great
really great hot character designs
and then he would do stuff like yeah
Mezzo Forte where it's like otherwise just a normal
action show but then there's just a random
sexy in it but I'm shouting that way
as like the closest approximation
to what like real life porn would be
if it was animated because it's
it's detailed and fantastic
everyone should watch it
is that it are we
wrapping this up now
are you gonna recommend anything
are you still there
I've been here I just I don't know how to
I'm not really like knowledgeable
about particular artists and things
I just look at what I look at stuff and I'd
say was there anything that you've seen
that is so impressive there was one thing
I yeah the one thing I
linked in the chat is probably my favorite
dojin because the
story is really good and
the art is really good and it doesn't the sex
doesn't start until like page
it's you linked it on dojin
moe and it's called nudist beach
ni shugakuro
chugakuryoko
the I don't read that who's that
between it's got a lot of big-ass titties
that's all I know oh the nudist beach
when I remember like a class goes to a nudist beach
yeah okay yeah it's cool
the whole beginning
but where they're all just sort of this is
being embarrassed looking at each other
involved it is actually
I should uh we're gonna
like recommend specific ones hold on
I'm gonna go into my favorites here because there's one
that I think everyone will like
like no matter what it's
called lingua franca
on ex hentai
lingua franca
I don't know anyone who's played megasol 5
will know what that means yeah by an artist
named akatsuki miuto
it's like basically like
this guy and this girl are
like in a biplane and it crash lands on an island
and it's all like these
like a basically I'm guessing they can't speak
to each other they speak different languages
well the whole island
is full of beautiful women
and they yeah they don't speak his language
and they seem to be like sort of primitive or something
like they live in like a tree and shit
and they're just like we need him to fuck all of us
we can all get pregnant and propagate
our you know it's like an amazon thing
like a guy shows up and they all need to
get pregnant by them and it's just like every
possible body type of women
woman all drawn very beautifully
like very detailed
I don't like it when they're like yes
get me pregnant please
I can understand why that would not be
it's not a way to kill the mood
I like it when it's like a breeding colony
why mix sex with pregnancy
you know I mean what do they have to do with each other
it's you know
I'm definitely into the fantasy
of showing up at some place
and then like literally impregnating the entire
populace and being the godfather
of their whole tribe
I find nothing as sexually attractive about
people specifically but the idea of the sex involved
that's cool
well it's cool because they're like an amazon tribe
so it wouldn't be like raising a kid
normally it'd be like having like all these
cool fucking Spartan kids
I feel some responsibility I wouldn't just like abandon it
you have kids with everyone in the tribe
it's a male thing
it's like the idea of being a father
to like hundreds of children
it's like a it's a naturally
ingrained thing
that's cool I think
yes but it will dry your shit quick
is what I'm saying
alright we have to defer to her
okay alright I think we've been here long enough
wait a minute I didn't tell
my favorite porn
shoot
I don't have one
no I do
so I don't really know any porn people
like by name or anything
except like zone I guess had a lot of great ones
yeah
except cc
first of all
but I'm like
the hottest thing
that I ever ever saw on the internet
was like
it wasn't meant to be hot
it was meant to be like kind of horrifying
like it was
it was an Evangelion fan fiction
of course
and uh
it was really well written and played really straight
and like it continued like the really psychological
horror aspects of the series
I'm sure
and in the context of this fan fiction
like instead of how in the series
there was 18 angels and then the world ended
in this story
in the context of the story the angels just never
stopped coming so things just got worse
and worse and the characters went more
and more mental so it picks up like two years
after
and Asuka and Shinji have been fighting like angels
for two years and there's been like 60 of them
which makes them 16
now so it's legal
right we did it
and like it gets to a point where like
Asuka is so mentally fucked up
that you find out that
she's been raping Shinji
like
sure that's fine
she just like
like Misato leaves or whatever for the night
and she'll like come up to him and she just like grabs his junk
and leads him into the bedroom and he doesn't resist because he's Shinji
he doesn't fucking do anything
right
and she just puts him in the bed
and she just gets on top of him
and it's like this really creepy
loveless, passionless
I mean is that really rape?
well it is
it's like kind of from his perspective
and it's like he really doesn't want this to be happening
but he doesn't fight back
I just like to point out that that's definitely not rape
if he's allowing it to happen
but just like you know if I said something maybe
it would be
I think that's still rape
how is that rape?
it's just because he's sheepish
it's like if I picked my nose
and flicked a booger on you and you didn't want it there
but you didn't want to start a scene with me
because I looked like I could kick your ass
if I put you up at your house
and take you to a restaurant and then bring you home after
and you ate the food and then you're like
god that was horrible why did I do that
if the person is fucking afraid to say no
then it's rape
okay well you didn't say that you just said that he was kind of not
Shinji Akari
that would be afraid of having sex with Asuka
I thought that was implied
that's a good thing
well okay he's scared of to death
because if he doesn't do it she'll kill him
okay fine that's rape
so the point is it was meant to be really creepy
and horrifying but I whacked to it furiously
because it was the hottest thing I ever read in my life
I can't believe I forgot to mention
that I used to write porn
I think it's been brought up maybe before
but yeah I used to write Tills of Symphonia porn
way back in the day
was that about Zellos
Zellos was in some of the chapters
there was one where
just to give you an idea
of the kind of porn this was
I was 14 and I
never read
no I wasn't into Lolli back then
I was just into everything
because she's already like a mind broken girl
that was before your enlightenment
well I was just into all
I was 14
before age meant nothing to me
they were like a 14 year old anime character
shit I hope
look I wrote a lot of chapters
okay like every possible
character combination was covered
but I had never like really
looked at porn that much
so I didn't really know exactly what it was like
so the scenarios I created
were just weird
so like the one with Zellos that I remember
was like they had
it was Colette and Zellos
and they had sex in a pool
and it was that like
one of them probably Zellos had like
cause they both had angel wings or whatever
and he was using them to float on the pool
while she was fucking
like riding his dick while he was floating on the pool
okay okay
that was like chapter 2 there's one where
by the way
no concept of rape at the time
so I didn't realize that this was
rape but um
it was the what did you say your name was
the pink haired girl
Prasea
she like went up to Sheena while she was asleep
and took her sword
and like it was like in the sheath
and she like put the sheath in her veg
and then put the hilt in her own
and like raped her in her sleep
whoa
yeah I was like 14
this is like what I thought sex was like
well that is very
cutting in
oh baby
I love
oh man the best part
is when I was writing that
in asterisk war sucks
part 11 there's a part where I say like
this makes about as much sense as the fan fiction I wrote
when I was 14 right
so we tracked down my
fanfiction.net profile so we could
show it on screen now mind you like
most of the porn I wrote back then was deleted
cause they expunged all of
like the porn at one point but
they left up this one thing I'd
written that was like supposed to be like
this dark gritty sin city
esque like take on
Tales of Symphonia called the Mel Tokio
Slums and I was reading it
and it's just like all rape
like all it is is like characters
going down dark alleys and getting
raped and then like
like trying like killing rapists
basically it was like there was like a rape hunter
guild or whatever
and like it just starts off with like
like Sheena wakes up and she's
like all sore from some sexual
incursion she had the night before that she goes into an alley
gets into a fight gets raped by all these
guys like wakes up gets
raped again then all the rapists get killed
by Colette and she takes her to this play game
I feel like these are a lot of enemies
yeah I mean
rape is a very easy way to make a
situation sexual you just write it in right
has anyone ever played Violated Heroin
it's basically a game where you play as the girl getting
raped all the time I'd highly recommend it
I've seen a few of those yeah I like
the one there's one where
I don't actually play any of those because again I'm
impatient I just want to see sex scenes
there's one where it's like a you know every
time you die it's like a like a
monster's oh dude I played a ton
of those yeah those are like
those are kind of annoying because you're incentivized
to play badly which doesn't really work
let me think about this one is that like a lot of those
will be like you you lose
by like the the monster like rapes you
but in this one it would have like your character
was dead like
was getting raped after being dead it was
really bizarre zombie thing or oh no it was
like like there's one for instance
I just remember the like the death
screen that I saw on
like Elboru but like there's one where
it's like this giant like mosquito creature
and it's got like it's like
stuff through your chest and it's got
it like it's thing like fucking her and
she's like just dead like blood coming from the mouth
that everything else like okay but it was
animated so it's really cool
alright let me say one last thing
I forgot to say this before and it was just
that when it comes to porn I know you said
you're not into this digi but I absolutely
am crazy for porn
games because I love working
for it I love working for my reward
and then I achieve it when I get it it is the most
rewarding thing ever that's why I love games
like Sengoku Rants because that game is hard
as shit so when you finally achieve
something it feels so good I would have
disagreed with you on that a couple
weeks ago oh shit I
discovered a little game a magical
game called honey pop
and oh yes my life yes
perfect example
oh god honey pop fucking
rules the only uh
oh my god I would
I will do my own version of honey pop
redrawing every one of the girls because
just thank you I think they're all ugly
the boobs oh my god what's wrong with
the boobs they look great awful like you
thank you someone thank you
you get it
they're all ugly and badly drawn
you're fucking ugly
calling them ugly is hurtful
and misogynistic and I won't stand
for it on this right this fucking
podcast the art work is
terrible Clinton's future America I will
not stand for that kind of misogynistic
the artwork is terrible and the act is
terrible and we've both
tried to recreate some of the
poses that they do like their boobs
and stuff it's not possible
can we can we at least agree that honey
cam studio the sequel looks like a literal
abortion it looks like the worst thing
ever about that
well the only uh the only um
eroge games I've ever managed to play
like any amount of is
sonohanabira and
a game called
wankoto kurasou which is about like
a world where there's dog girls
like who like
they are dogs but they are also
dog girls it's very strange
like the cat
so you can have sex with them yeah what's great about it
is that well like you can
but it's usually for like because
they're in heat and they need someone to take
care of that that's just to give you an excuse it's like
they write that into the story so it's like oh I have to have sex with my dog
it goes like way too in
like it goes really in depth about like world
building to try to make all of it make sense
and it's really funny you know what I'm not into
I'm not into big excuses written into stories
that are like oh I just I have to have sex
with you because well I mean it's cleverly
done and it's a pretty funny
I guess it's a pretty funny
meme thing pretty standard but
if you fucking read it then it's
I'm saying it's cleverly done I'm not saying
the fact that it's heat it's clever
I'm saying that if you read the thing the way
they handle the concept it's cleverly done
I'll be the judge of that
I haven't read it in like five years
but like my point is simply that I played
both of those games because the sex was
constant like the game is like
like a like a ten minute dialogue
scene and then a ten minute sex scene and it's
just that back and forth basically and that's
actually like readable and I read
Sayano Uta because there's only like four
hours long and it's great it's Urobuchi
again and I love him right
the only
creepy as fuck it's cool though
and Sai is hot what's that game
the only a sex game
well it's not really even sex in it
I think but it's
this thing called Simgo which is a really old flash
yeah that I found when I was like
I don't know 13 or something
it was the coolest thing
it was one of the first
things I've ever seen
sort of like
actual
stuff one of these things
okay it's like a dress up thing
yeah well no it's not a dress up thing
it's a dating sim
ganguro girls
back in the day or anyone remember that
I was on limewire for a while well whatever
okay you know what I think we're good
this is a long one
but this was a great discussion
I like that the porn episode had to run long of course
yeah and we'll see you next week
recording live from prison
and if this podcast
has seen you pent up please
commission me because my commissions are open
and I will do anything for your money
there you go we'll make sure there's a link in the description
take your money that you would have given to Ben's
Patreon and give it to God
that's what I'm showing up Ben
I will give you titties and wallies
like Ben can't over
you know
give me your money
yeah Ben it's all about CC
thanks for joining us CC you've been a great guest
glad you're here everybody thanks for watching
and we'll see you next week everybody say goodbye
bye