You're gonna go to the record store, you're gonna give them all your money.
Radio plays what they want you to hear, so it's cool, I just don't believe it.
Sell out with me, oh yeah, sell out with me tonight.
The record company's only giving me lots of money and everything's gonna be alright.
Hello, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Everybody go crazy!
Woohoo!
Yay!
Alright!
I love my arms when I come up with it.
I like dig.
The topic today is the most bestest one there has ever been, selling out everything, giving
it all away, and I'm gonna do the thing we haven't done in a million years, I'm gonna
read the Urban Dictionary definition, cause it's cool for this one.
Alright, to compromise one's values and or artistic vision in order to gain fame and
or monetary profit, commonplace in today's musical society, it is rare to find a successful
musical artist who has not sold out, however this is not to say that they do not exist.
And that's it.
That was a bunch of unnecessary bullshit.
Was that the end?
Yeah.
But, I don't know, anyway, I'm just gonna state my opinion right now, selling out is
the only way to live your life.
If you're not selling out, you're doing it wrong.
Do we not introduce everybody anymore?
Artistic integrity is dead.
It needs to be buried.
What?
Do we not introduce everybody anymore on the spot?
Oh shit, I totally forgot.
Jesus Christ!
Alright!
Alright, we got the Patreon.com slash Ben St.
That's me, that's my name.
The DeVoo Collective.
I don't make my own videos, I just do Digi videos.
So go to Patreon.com slash DigiBro instead.
The 21st century digital boy.
That's me.
Patreon.com slash DigiBro.
It's not you hippo shit.
That's not me.
Mother's Basements.
Patreon.com slash Mother's Basement.
Thank you very much.
Is there an apostrophe in there?
No, it's just all Mother's Basement with no punctuation whatsoever.
Alright, endless jessicles, Greek warrior.
We're the pussy gangsters, give me some macaroni.
And me bestie boy, your favorite guy.
Okay, so you already heard what I have to say, who's got an opinion on selling out?
Jesse, what do you think about selling out?
I want to hear what you have to say.
I was going to say something, but I got confused because you fucking started introducing us.
Okay, we'll say it now.
So, yeah, it's, so selling out to me is just, yeah, when someone compromises their values
or their intent for greater success or marketability or whatever, but here's an interesting conundrum.
What if your intent is to sell out?
What if your values are making money and that's all that you care about?
Case in point, Man Child Incorporated.
Yes, yeah, yeah, that's right.
So Man Child Incorporated is essentially just a parody of selling out, but it's not a very
good parody because I'm incapable of not making good videos.
Yes, it's one flaw.
He can't sell out hard enough.
Yeah, like the idea was, yeah, all the videos are going to be really bad and stupid, but
isn't possible.
Everything I do is gold.
Right, yeah, when was the last Man Child Incorporated video?
Oh, so long.
So long.
Like February.
Oh, no.
What was that, Ben?
You said that all dismissively, like I haven't made a good video since then, let me tell
you something.
I think that's exactly what Ben would say.
Listen, buddy!
You know, I may be a dick, Jesse, but I say that because I miss Colt Corona is what I
really miss.
And I want to know what happens with that fucking scepter and crown.
He's still in the furnace room.
He won't come out.
Jesse, Jesse, Jesse, tell us about the light in the furnace room.
Oh yeah, yeah, so there's this meme going around that Colt Corona is fictional.
I don't know where it came from, but people just don't believe in him, even though he's
clearly there on video all the time, or at least he used to be before he barricaded himself
in the furnace room and started calling a horse you haven't.
He's out of his fucking mind, but you know, sometimes just to prove it even more so, sometimes
I'll be walking around my room and that damn light will be on in there.
I didn't turn that damn light on.
That light is just on sometimes.
And so there's your proof right there.
I put that down.
There you go.
If you pause the video and you freeze-frame it at this one frame, you'll see a beam of
light that couldn't possibly be computer-generated.
And if you look in the background of the video...
And then Jeff made reference to something that one of Jesse's stupid-ass fans did that
we were trying to keep underwrapped so that nobody else would make the same mistake.
Oh no, you motherfucker!
Stop!
Everyone stop!
Shut up right now!
Whoever the fuck is editing this, if you don't take that shit out, I will come down
on you with the fury of a thousand gods!
Thank you, Jeff, for even saying that!
I'm legitimately pissed off right now!
God damn it!
HIPPO, HIPPO, HIPPO!
You were saying something a while back.
What were you saying?
Yeah, yeah, it's about the topic at hand, actually.
Okay, okay, go on.
There's one thing that a lot of, like, YouTubers have done to sort of make selling out or like
selling stuff in general more palatable to people, which I'm kind of sick of.
It's making it into a joke every single time.
Like, lol, look at me, I'mma sell out, whoa!
Yeah, let's you have your fake eating too, it lets you sell out, but if you're kind of
self-aware about it, it's okay, it's funny.
I think that's stupid.
I think being truly self-aware is understanding that selling out isn't a bad thing.
That's true, but it wasn't done yet.
It's not even really selling out though, they're just selling a product or promoting something
and they're just saying, whoa, I'm horrible and terrible, lol, buy it anyway, you know,
that just, I don't know.
I very much agree.
But you know, just like, there's this thing that tons of YouTubers are doing now where
at the end of their videos, they'll just do a little spiel about, you know, crunchy
roll or a fucking loot crate, any of that, and you know, those are annoying.
I usually just turn off the video, I don't like them, I think the video would be better
without them, but they don't really bother me.
But just the other day, fucking George Weidman of fucking bunny shits like put at the beginning
of this really cool video I wanted to watch about Dark Souls 3 or something, I can't remember.
Like he just inserts this like two minute long speech about, I think it was loot crate,
it was the most obnoxious fucking thing I've ever seen in my time, I just put it at the
end.
What?
I gotta say, I thought that was, like, I think he's way smarter for doing it the way
he did, and honestly, like, here's the thing, everyone puts them at the end, no one fucking
watches your ad at the end of your video.
Yeah, cause no one wants to see them.
Right, exactly.
Which means that they're not gonna make any fucking money, which means you shouldn't
put the ad in there in the first place, cause you're not making anything.
I didn't even watch the video, cause it was so bad, I had to do something else with my
time.
Yeah, you did it, but everyone else did.
I did.
I watched the whole video, because of course I wanted to watch it, it was a 30 minute video
about Dark Souls.
But did you buy a loot crate?
Well, I already know about loot crate, and I've had my own advertising for them before.
Well, we're not really the best judge.
That's by far one of the biggest problems with ads on YouTube is there's so few sponsors
going around, Audible and Crunchyroll and Loot Crate and the toaster.
You see the same thing all the time.
T-Blocks.com where you can use promo code M-Basement 15 to get 15% off a t-shirt sent
straight to your door.
Guys, we're just gonna have to start our own merchandise and make our own company so we
can advertise ourselves.
Like, we're just, there's not enough.
You know, I've been kicking around an idea for a while of having a YouTuber Daki Makara
company.
Just selling Daki Makara's.
Oh my gosh.
That would make so much money.
Jesus fucking Christ.
I'm so angry thinking about how much money that would make.
We gotta get on it, man.
Just get Digibro on a pillow, and obviously, Nate, the sexiest man on a pillow is my Digibro.
The problem with that is, though, is for half the YouTubers out there, you'd have to have
double XL wide pillows for that to be practical.
If he's gonna make Movie Bob, just make a bedsheet like yours.
He'd be a couch.
You just gotta sell a couch.
I would honestly buy a Movie Bob Daki Makara.
Movie Bob bedspread?
You mean a Movie Bob futon?
Because that's what it would end up being.
Yeah, that's right.
Holy shit.
I'd wake up every day and turn to him in my sleep and nuzzle his fat Daki Makara neck
and say, sorry for 9-11, and he would turn back to me in my dreams and say, me too.
Ben, Ben, I wanted to ask you.
You seem to me to have something of a complex relationship with selling out, so on the one
hand, you seem to really hate everything that makes money for people that isn't, I don't
know, artistically whatever.
I hate everything that makes people more money than I think they deserve.
Yeah, okay, sure, sure.
But on the other hand, you'd like to go advertise your shit around places, and I mean, not
that that's not really selling out, but it's marketing, I guess, which is similar, I guess.
I try to promote myself.
I post my shit around in places that I think it will be seen by people who it's relevant
to.
I mean, I don't like that.
I don't like doing it, but it's the only way to get seen, and I accept that.
It's a necessary evil.
I don't think that's the same.
I think we can all agree on that.
I think that's part of, yeah, it's like what Jesse was saying.
I mean, I agreed with the first half of what Jesse was saying and not the second.
It's only selling out if you compromise your artistic integrity.
Yeah, but here's the thing.
I don't think advertising yourself does that.
That's totally unrelated to the word.
A lot of times, your artistic integrity isn't all that interesting anyway.
You have to really decide if it's worth it.
One of my favorite movies is that thing you do.
It's a Tom Hanks movie from the 90s.
It's about this teenage band who gets really big, and it's just a fun, happy movie about
them getting big, and at no point does the movie go, oh man, this is such a bad deal
that they're conforming to exactly what the label wants them to do.
It's all shown as a pretty good idea.
Tom Hanks plays this manager who shapes their image, and all of his ideas are good ideas,
even if they're artificial and they work, and then there's one character, one member of the band,
who's like, oh, why are we doing covers?
Oh, why are we controlling our image?
Why don't we just play our own songs, and this and this and that, and everyone hates him,
and he's a big penis butt jerk.
That's very interesting to view, and that's exactly what I wanted to talk about,
as opposed to like, because it's pretty obvious when you've got a dude who just sticks a big ad
in the middle of his video or whatever, but what's much less noticeable is the way that people
tailor their content, and not just by making top tens about whatever the popular thing is,
but by, like, Digi's gotten very good at this, about structuring his videos.
Yeah, the consumable chunks.
It always segues into talking about the pageant.
No, they segue, they segue.
No, no, no, no, if it's in a Digi video, it's a segue.
Fucking animal!
You fucking animal!
It's a Digi video, alright?
It's a Digi video.
It's a Digi video specifically.
Tell me about how much cooler Segyu sounds than Segway.
Tell me about that.
Yeah, Mother Segway makes you picture the thing.
Anyway, with what DeVu was saying, for an example that the rest of us know, Bakumon,
we were talking about it.
I was gonna say, that's the big one, that's the big one.
It's about the glory and the power and the wonderful thing that is
telling your content to the mass appeal.
Somewhere in the middle of the story, you know, Ashiro Gimudo goes to Hattori,
the editor, and they're like, you know, what about, you know, does being popular
mean it's good?
Like, isn't popularity independent from artistic integrity and Hattori just like,
look, I know a lot of people struggle with this, but I just really try not to think about it.
If something is popular, that means lots of people like it, which in a certain sense
means it's good.
Yeah, and like, to all the people that like it, it is good.
Therefore, popularity and goodness are kind of...
What an amazing speech that was.
That was like the most interesting thing to me in the entire series, but...
It was up there.
Yeah, let's go on Davoo, go on.
A couple of years ago, when I was getting into doing YouTube full time, right,
and I was really inspired by the big analytical think pieces, there were things that were
really deep and complex, and that was what I was into developing my skills on,
is doing analysis, and at a certain point, I had made a video that I thought,
alright, there's a lot of great analysis in here, had another video that was like,
alright, this is a great story that I'm weaving about a guy,
and now I'm like, okay, I've gotten good at the baseline skills at making videos.
So, from then on, what's really been exciting me since then is finding something
that is also really good, but is also something that's mainstream.
It's looking at the Venn diagram of what is great and what is popular,
and searching for everything that's in between, and that's what excites me.
That's the skills I want to develop.
Yeah, to relate that just to Bakumon, because Bakumon, like the Ashurigamuto,
understands that what they're best at is that, what's the term they use for it?
Serious humor.
Serious humor, that's exactly the word I was looking for.
And so their big successful series later on is like Tonto, which is like this gag series,
that one never really gets off, it's all their other series that play more to their strengths
when they can find a way to capture what they're good at, and then tailor it to the mass audience.
That's what it's all about.
I think that the way, I think that the only way to be successful and not selling,
like you can be successful and sell out, but there's such a thing as success without selling out.
And I think that happens when people, like you're making what you want to make,
but it also happens to be stuff that people want to see.
Like you have to find something that is what you want to do,
but that other people also want you to do.
And you know, in my humble opinion, I think that those people are just plain lucky to be that kind of person.
I mean, I'm not sure that it's really...
I mean, Ashiro Gimudo had to go through lots and lots of iterations before they found something that's all good.
Yeah, exactly. I wouldn't call them lucky at all.
I wouldn't call them luck, that was hard work and perseverance.
I'm just saying someone from the start who did that would be a lucky person.
Yeah, a lot of mangaka, they have like a bunch of unsuccessful series
before they find something that really speaks to people.
Like Araki made Bao before he made Jojo.
I forget his name, but the Master of All Manga made Magic Kaito before he made Detective Conan,
which is the most successful media franchise of all time or something like that.
It's not even close to that, but it is.
No, but I think it's the longest running anime of all time.
Probably.
Anime, maybe.
What about The Simpsons?
Well, I mean, of course, Matt Groening, the phenomenal mangaka,
who made The Simpsons and then realized that he'd sold out too much
and went back and made the artistic masterpiece that is Futurama.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, but like a lot of the time you do have to iterate on ideas
before you find something that speaks to people, unless you're a genius like me
and you make what's in an OP as your very first video and people just flock to you.
Well, Jeff, we need you to talk to you.
Because you're the master of selling out in this group.
I am.
Hang on.
I want to ask Jeff, because I've been curious about this.
Your content does seem very, you know, appropriate for this stuff.
And I want to ask, how much of being like a journalist helped you, like,
prepare you for your YouTube stuff?
I assume it was massively.
Oh, okay.
So the one thing that you guys who only ever concern yourselves with making good videos
that are well-edited and well-voiced acted, don't get, is that, like,
one of the most important things to YouTube video success is your description,
your tags, and your title.
And, like, not just in terms of clickbait, in terms of if you have keywords
that people are searching all the time in your description, your tags, and your title,
that will factor into how often you get searched.
So part of what has, that's something that gets drilled into your head
when you're a text journalist, is keywords, especially in the first two paragraphs of your article,
keywords, all the fuck over your title, and keywords in your tags.
And that means...
Is this specifically for search stuff?
Yeah, Google search stuff.
That in, like, collected stuff too.
Like, okay, when I was an animator, because I learned this as well from my text blog,
where, what the hell, I heard a woman's voice.
Jesse, are you in a Skype call at the same time or something?
He would be.
When I was doing text blogging, there was, like, a period where I was part of...
There's this website called Anime Something.
I don't remember the fucking name of it, but it was, like, an aggregator of RSS feeds.
So, basically, it was a website you went to, and it would be a collection of the newest posts
from every anime blog that was a part of that site.
And so, there'd, you know, be, like, hundreds of anime blogs,
and every time you checked, there'd be new stuff, and it was kind of like...
There wasn't a huge reader base for it, but if you had a brand new blog,
this was how you got off the ground.
Like, get your URL onto that site, and that way, you'll get at least, like, 30 readers, you know?
And then, from there, you've got a kind of word-of-mouth spread.
But, like, so I was on there, and at some point, I realized that, like,
a lot of my posts would just not get, like, any initial views,
and then someone messaged me, and they were like,
you realize that that aggregator will post the title and the first, like, paragraph of your post
is what it would share.
And with, they had, because they have advertisers,
you couldn't have any swear words in the title or first couple sentences.
Oh.
Interesting.
Miss Jizzabelle.
Hahaha.
Okay.
Wow.
Oh, my God, it's the promised secretary at long last.
This is her debut.
Well, welcome.
Welcome to the DeVoo Collective.
We're so happy to have you.
No.
No, she's always been here.
She's a representative of Endless Jess, and therefore...
Yeah.
It's the fucking...
She's the one who leaves.
If you've ever had a comment on Manchild Incorporated...
I thought she was the secretary of Manchild Inc.
Yeah.
I thought so, too.
Oh, yeah.
Manchild Incorporated, not Endless Jess.
I'm sorry, those are completely different brands,
from what I'm talking about.
This Jesson from Endless Jess.
You all suck.
Hahaha.
That's a fair point.
Holy shit.
Okay.
So, back onto the subject of SEO.
That is very important.
Wait, what's SEO?
Search engine optimization.
Oh, okay.
I'm such a noob.
Alright, Jesson.
YouTube is...
They all suck.
Go to hell.
Fuck you, especially Jeff.
Goodbye.
Is he writing you a script over there?
Is he like sending over like...
What is that?
Using the fucking...
He's writing cue cards.
No, he's pushing the button on his...
Like intercom thing, you know?
No, no.
What I'm imagining is, is Jesse sitting across the room
with a Morse code tapper, and she's sitting across the room
in front of the microphone, interpreting that,
writing it out, and interpreting the words,
and where are you getting into the mic?
Okay, Jeff, go on.
Search engine optimization.
Because, like, what YouTube is, fundamentally,
is it's three things.
It's a video platform, obviously.
It's a landing page that recommends videos to you,
and then it's a search engine.
So, knowing how to game search engines
to get more relevant hits off of search terms
is super important for being successful on YouTube.
So can you give us the example of how you do that
with what's in an OP?
Where's my secretary, Jesse?
Hey!
Jesse.
Jezebel Jezemeen, what are you doing
conforming with these losers?
It's time for my goddamn butt massage.
Get off that stupid fucking podcast
you're coming with me.
There's a whole fucking...
Sorry, sir.
There's a whole...
Shut up! You don't get to talk!
There's a man-child narrative going on right now.
There's a supply.
I need my butt massage!
I need my penis massage!
Yeah!
We're out of here!
Oh, my God.
Go on, Jeff.
Try to force your way.
Yeah, so, functionally, the way that you do that
is you make sure to include the title
of whatever you're talking about
in either the first line of your description,
or your title, or ideally both.
Then you want to tag companies,
creators, musicians,
and anything that people might search
related to your thing.
So, oh, I left my phone on
because I'm a sellout, too.
That's the sound of selling out.
That's the sound of money coming in, baby!
That's the sound of money coming in.
Yep.
So...
It's a distinct Cha-ching cadence, too.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, only Jeff would have a Cha-ching sound.
I actually do, too.
Now that's the sellout we can believe in.
My text sound effect is the Cha-ching
from Roller Coaster Tycoon.
Of course.
That's a good sound effect.
Yeah, so...
So what you want to do,
like, what I do with What's in an OP
is I always make sure to put, you know,
the name of the song
that is the opening theme song,
the name of the director
or the mangaka who created the series,
the name of the company is responsible for making it,
the name of the series itself
and any possible abbreviations,
and usually,
if there's a commonly used abbreviation,
I'll use the short form, like FMA in the title,
and then I'll type Full Metal Alchemist
in the description within the first line
because that, you know, that all helps
with search engine optimization.
Yeah, Jeff, it's funny to hear you talking about this
because I do all of this
and I thought it was obvious,
but now I'm wondering if to everybody else,
this is news.
Well, I don't do any of this.
I don't do any of this shit.
On the subject of selling out,
I've been talking to people at MCNs lately,
and that's apparently the biggest thing
that they do to help people get their channels bigger.
Oh my gosh, that's what you're paying for?
Wow.
Yeah, I shouldn't have known that.
That has to tell you how to use tags.
Those really condescending copy and pasted messages
is like, hey, you know how,
how about we do half of it for you
and just give us all your money?
Now, I also do the whole thing.
Jeff's sold out hard enough to carry all of us.
That's true.
I've also done the thing with tags.
And what I've found...
Yeah, just one pro tip related to tags
that a lot of people don't think of,
put the name of your channel in every single...
Yeah, I was about to say,
I tag every single video I ever publish.
I tag DigiBro.
Isn't that like an inherent thing?
It's the name of the goddamn channel.
Tags control what shows up in your sidebar.
And so if you tag everything with your name,
then if someone gets into your channel,
then suddenly they're locked into your channel.
That's what I want to talk about.
I want to talk about sidebars,
because I've found that that's how I've gotten...
In the time that I've been doing like,
YouTube full time,
only two of my videos have taken off.
One about Roller Coaster Tycoon
and one about Undertale.
So this is the other way to sell out,
is to get in on the big trends,
the big fandoms.
I mean, almost everyone,
all but two people in this chat right now
first started doing YouTube making money
through another big franchise.
And is it banned?
We're not allowed to talk about it anymore.
Anyway, so...
None of my videos were ever really able to...
You did it, Davoo! You just did it!
I know, I was conscious of it at that time.
I was conscious of how I transitioned
from one sentence to another sentence
by going...
So I found...
Everybody post about how cute that is
when Davoo does that.
Everybody complimented him.
I was never able to find...
I was never able to get much success
through getting searched
because I don't know,
nothing that I ever posted
was something that people search much about.
Normally people seem to watch videos
by clicking on one
and then going on the sidebar
and they basically go sidebar surfing.
So people are going to sit down all day
watching Roller Coaster Tycoon 3 videos
if that's what they're doing, right?
Now, that's why so many people
didn't like that video
because they're in the mindset
of liking Roller Coaster Tycoon 3.
Whereas I'm posting the video
in the mindset of being a video game
commentator, right?
I'm going in and the reason
that my Undertale video took off
so much is because it's a really weird
statement in the title
that really throws people off.
And it's...
Yeah, Davoo, I wanted to say
it's interesting to me, very much so,
to compare our two different Undertale videos
because mine is a fucking 10 out of 10
masterpiece of artistic wonder.
And Davoo's on the other hand...
No, it's not even that.
Davoo's was A, much more timely.
B, what had an interesting title to it.
And C, I don't know, maybe had a nicer
thumbnail, which definitely is simpler.
It had a hand-drawn thumbnail
that Davoo created, so it was art in one scene before.
Oh, you made that, dude?
Oh, I didn't know that.
If I made my Undertale videos
title anything but
Mother's Basement Review Undertale,
it probably would have gotten a million hits.
Now, don't forget one thing, though, guys.
If I'd made that video today,
if Undertale had came out today
and I'd done that video, it would have been much longer
because I would have done a much more expanded version
of the script that would have resonated
with more people.
Nobody cares, Davoo.
Well, I'm talking about, like, reaching people.
We're talking about selling out.
I want to ask Jeff, because you were talking about before.
Yeah.
All right, it's just,
the way that you title your videos,
what's in an OP?
I see that you always consciously have chose
to brand yourself, you know, with, like, the name of the thing,
as opposed to someone like Digi, who doesn't do that ever.
And I'm just wondering, you know,
what's the reason for that choice?
You guys, I'm sure you have reasons for that.
You know, I think with Jeff,
he's got one of the few ways that it can work,
because I think that old YouTube,
like, the mentality people had about it
was very much that people were coming for you.
Like, there was individual content creators.
They were looking for your series, your story.
Yeah, YouTube pages used to be, like, MySpace pages and stuff.
Yeah.
And so, and, you know, people like that guy with the glasses
who have very well-defined series,
and those are, like, what people do before you.
Angry Video Game Nerd, his name is in the titles.
Those guys are institutions, though, so, yeah.
But now, like, 80% of all the views I get,
if not more, is from, like,
is from people being on YouTube browsing.
So it's almost all sidebar hits, recommended videos,
you know, people on their home page,
and it recommends them because they've clicked on anime videos,
so we suggest DigiBro videos.
And so, I tailor everything to be for those people,
because anyone who is already subscribed to me,
it doesn't matter.
They're gonna watch my videos no matter what.
So tailoring it for them is completely unnecessary.
I'm tailoring it all for the people who aren't subscribed,
who don't know who I am.
And if it says, like, DigiBro review,
none of them know who I am.
They don't give a fuck who DigiBro is.
They don't care about his review.
What they want to know is, you know,
why Konosuba is genuinely hilarious.
And they're like, I like Konosuba,
and there's a big picture of the most popular character
from the show, who I don't even really talk about in the video,
but she's giving a thumbs up on the thumbnail.
It's adorable.
It's a memorable moment from the show,
and it's the most popular character.
So that video gets 250,000 hits,
which is what it has before it got...
It would have way more than that if it hadn't gotten taken down
for, like, three fucking weeks by Katakawa.
But...
Those fuckers.
So for me, it's all about, like,
what's the catchiest possible title,
no connection to anything, flashiest thumbnail,
what's going to get people's attention,
but without stepping into the boundary of looking trashy,
you know, where it's, like, ten hottest tits in Konosuba, you know.
Well, excuse me.
Looking trashy is the best way to get hits.
No, it is.
I just objectively proved with ass in the thumbnail.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
Well, not an irrelevant ass in the thumbnail.
Yeah.
No, I have a lot of tits in thumbnails and stuff
with the Astroscore series,
but that's because they're also semi-ironic,
because, like, having tits in the thumbnail
fits in with the narrative of the videos
that I'm criticizing shows from tits.
All right, but let me, I mean, if you, like,
just, does any average viewer,
the people that you're marketing the videos to,
do they get that it's ironic?
No, no, no.
I'm not attracting them on that basis.
You see, that's an excuse that you're using,
and I agree with you, it's fine.
I'm not making it as an excuse.
I'm saying why it doesn't damage my brand.
Because if I...
What it doesn't damage is your view of yourself.
Nobody else cares.
Nobody else is thinking about it.
No, no, people do care.
People want to subscribe to people who look smart.
You think so?
Nobody wants to subscribe.
Yeah, I guess.
Like, the biggest criticism, like,
I think most people who hate Misty Kronexia
haven't watched any of his videos.
They've looked at his thumbnails and his subject matter,
and they click on a video and they see his posters,
and they think, this guy is a fucking sleaze, right?
Like, his videos will be, like,
top 10 most fappable lollies,
and it'll be a picture of an ass on the cover.
And then you click on it,
and it's him in front of all these trashy,
sordid online posters talking about how much
he likes lolly ass, you know?
Like, people subscribe to me because they think
I'm intellectual.
They think I'm smart.
They want to be taught something, you know?
You've tricked me out of success.
That's true, that's right.
Yeah, if I put tits on the thumbnail,
and then you click on the video,
and it gives you the impression that it's a clever
subversion of it, then it still feels smart,
and it doesn't hurt my brand.
But if I was talking about a show,
like, you know, some show that is deeply
well-respected or something,
and I just put tits up there,
and then my video has nothing to do with tits,
and it's all heady and deep,
it would be really obvious that it was like
a clickbait thing, you know?
I just don't even know people are thinking about it that much.
Well, it's deeply beloved.
But anyways, the reason that it works for Jeff, I think,
is that what's in an OP is a good title
every single time.
Yeah.
Because it's not a series title, really.
Like, if you see...
It doesn't work for me,
because I don't know what an OP is.
I mean, I kind of know.
It's an opening video.
If you watched one video, you'd know.
Any other anime fan would know that.
Yeah, I guess.
I mean, okay, I did know that that's what it was,
but when I see OP, I don't think that.
I think one piece.
I think all of Jeff's videos are about one piece.
Are you telling me they're not?
Ben, your total plan.
That unsubscribe.
That's double the reason to subscribe.
I thought he was a one-piece analyst this whole time.
God damn it.
What's been happening?
When I saw what's in an OP, Your Lion, April,
on the front page of Reddit,
I didn't think, oh, this is a series.
I thought this is going to be an analysis
of the OP of Your Lion, April.
And then every single time I see it,
it's like, oh, that's going to be an analysis
of the OP of Bakano.
Wait a minute.
Was that a super clever April Fools title?
Because it's Your Lion, April.
Was it not even about that show?
No.
Well, it was.
Damn it.
That would have been so awesome.
That would be fun.
The April Fools video was Corey in the house.
For April Fools next year, I should just,
I should make it, what's in an OP?
Your Lion, April, second OP.
And then just make it about fucking, I don't know.
Dick, something else.
Yeah.
Something else.
Anything else.
The Bocano-Pico opening.
I feel like we're off top.
I don't think what we're talking about is selling out.
We're talking about SEO optimization.
This is turned into a, like, a guide to selling out.
I want to get to, all I care about is me.
So do you, what about my system?
I definitely have the old school,
John Tron style of things where it's just my name
and branding.
You're telling me that it's a better idea to find
some sort of generic way of appearing individually.
Well, I think yours works too.
The reason I never, like, told you to stop,
because I think best anime ever grew on the gun,
like every single time, again, like what's in an OP,
it's always a title for that video.
It's never just, here's the name of my series,
and then also a video title.
Well, except that a lot of people,
a lot of people got really fucking angry at him
for saying the best game ever.
Best game ever Undertale.
Yeah, because they heard that from the whole internet.
Okay, that's a unique case in that one,
but I wonder if, I don't care if they get mad
as long as they come in and watch,
they can get as mad as they want.
That was what happened on our anime
is best anime ever, One Punch Man, got no attention.
It was like a severely downvote.
Everyone hated that, yeah.
Just because of the title.
No one watched the fucking video.
It was just they said,
One Punch Man's not the best anime ever, downvote.
It only works if it's either one
that people really feel is the best anime ever,
or one that people obviously know isn't
and they've realized it's a joke.
That's why I need to appeal to lesser known things
with that sort of stuff.
It only works once people know who you are.
Wait a second, Nate.
I just realized the whole subversion
is that no one cares about One Punch Man
because it's the best ever.
It called the best ever the same way
that Saitama himself is the most strong man in knowing.
I thought there was some sort of meta going on here,
but not really.
I'll find it later.
What were you saying?
Wait, hang on.
I was saying the difference between
Jeffson Nate's thing is that
Nate is making a statement with his
if you put like a question mark
at the end of Best Anime Ever,
that might rectify the whole thing.
No, that would totally change everything.
No, I can't do that.
That's fucking gay as shit.
Best anime ever?
No, I can't do it.
I'll let him do it next time.
Nate, next time you got to do that.
I wouldn't work with it.
I'll kill that for the ever.
Oh my god, it would work.
Maybe I could squeeze a tilled.
I can't do a question mark.
I can't live with myself.
I don't know what the tilled is going to do.
I don't know what to do anything.
I think it worked out really well with the first two
because Gurren Lagann,
a lot of people legitimately feel that way.
And then Monster Musume, like you said,
it was so obviously not the best anime ever
that people got that it was a joke.
But with One Punch Man,
it's too relevant and too contested
where people really are out there on the internet
arguing about whether it's the best anime ever.
And it's the same deal with Undertale.
It's like, even though that is the best game ever,
some people don't think so.
Some people think Uncharted is the best game ever
and are wrong.
I was thinking about doing a separate section
for modern things.
Maybe I'll give that some more thought.
But anyway, we're off topic.
We're talking about my shit.
I'm trying to think about
whether I need a good name for mine.
Because all I do is,
for my ones, I just say the name of the game first
and then hit the critical review afterwards.
Yeah, I mean, you're definitely...
It's okay.
I mean, you do very John Trani videos like I do,
which is just like, we take the thing
and then we just say whatever we want about it.
And it's not like exploring a specific theme.
John Trani's very old YouTube, though, man.
I know.
And then to his formula, totally, like,
no one should try to take the John Tron path.
Nobody should do it.
It's not viable.
The John Tron path is get lucky,
get successful on Reddit one time.
Yeah, that's right.
Not to say that it's not good,
but he definitely was one of the very few
to succeed in that way.
And I think it all really comes down
to him singing firework at the end of that video.
That's the entire reason that John Tron
is as big as he is now.
It was his hard-hitting analysis of DiCatana
that really propelled him into fame.
It was his Yonkers, man.
I don't know if you guys know about the...
It was Dino City?
No.
Bro, like, that's the one.
Yeah, it was Dino City.
No, that's what I'm saying.
I was saying it was his Yonkers.
Yonkers is a song by Tyler the Creator
where he had a music video where he, like,
ate a live cockroach in the video
and it got, like, super viral.
Yeah.
And that's why he's famous now.
Oh, I gotcha.
So it's just like one random little thing he did,
like, completely sparked his whole career.
Well, I'll just say, I've got a video cooking right now.
I've got some big plans for it.
I think it might be the one.
We'll see in, like, six, seven, eight months.
Let's talk...
Let's shift gears for a minute.
Yeah.
Let's not talk about how we can sell out.
Let's talk about other people who sell out.
Hmm.
I just...
Before we move from us to other people,
I just want to say...
Yeah.
The only time that I've ever been accused of selling out
was when I started putting annotations
at the end of my videos,
linking to other videos that are mine.
And then again when you joined this call.
And then again when I joined this call, obviously.
Yeah.
It was like a Vietnam flashback at starting this call.
But, you know, I mean, that's a totally bullshit criticism.
There's nothing wrong with linking to more of your videos.
You have to assume people want to watch your content
if they're watching your content,
so you might as well make it easy for them.
So, fuck them.
Backwinks are really important.
That's another thing that you learn from text journalism
and common sense.
So, you know, a thing about other people who are, you know,
big YouTubers who do things that are pretty shallow to get hits,
I think the reason that a lot of people don't like them
is that they don't respect their work ethic.
Because I...
Whenever my friend comes over
and puts on a normal boots or a hidden block video,
I'm like,
man, why do these guys get out of video every two or three weeks?
And I told her one time, like,
dude, if I were doing videos like this,
I would have a video out every other day.
You know, like, at some point...
Alright, you know what?
You've got me devout.
You've got me by the hooks.
I've got to give this rant.
This rant has been brewing inside me for a while.
Okay, let's hear it.
Alright.
It's called Fuck Movie Bob.
I've titled this one.
Alright.
That's a good one.
So,
Fuckin' Movie Bob, right?
This fucker.
Right.
This dude,
he's been around for a long time, right?
He used to do the Game Over thinker series,
originally on Screw Attack.
Originally on YouTube, and he got on Screw Attack, yeah.
Which was terrible.
Yeah, it's terrible,
and it went on forever.
I had this weird, stupid narrative.
It was bad.
But, he also made movie reviews and analysis on The Escapist, right?
And it would be two videos a week.
He had his Escape to the Movies reviews,
which were just pretty much standard movie reviews,
and his The Big Picture videos,
which were like these interesting looks into the history of film,
talking about specific stuff,
and they're really cool,
because he has a lot of knowledge,
and so it was like learning cool, interesting facts about film history, right?
Two videos a week.
So, he gets fired from The Escapist,
alongside a bunch of other people, right?
Too fat.
And, yeah.
Couldn't fit in the damn door.
So, he goes to YouTube,
and he starts doing two different series.
He's got one called Really That Good,
and one that's just his normal reviews.
Yeah.
His normal reviews are the most, like,
click-baity, possible things in the universe.
It'll be, he'll cover a new movie,
the instant it comes out,
and he'll just, like, if it's bad at all,
he'll make it out like it's the worst movie of all time,
rag on it incessantly, obnoxiously.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Which is pretty cathartic,
if you're, like, wanting...
Well, that's the problem.
If you want pixels to fail,
then that review is...
But back when he was doing regular reviews,
every week, talking about a new review,
a new video, a new movie,
every year, there would usually be one movie
that came out where he was like,
this movie's so bad, it's a big piece of shit
with a cunt and a face and a fucker,
and I hate it, and it's dead,
and it's a big pile of duty shit pits,
and that's, like, the whole video.
And now he's doing it all the time.
And now it's every single review he does
is written like that.
Right.
It'll be, like, because he did pixels,
and it was just like,
this is the shittiest cock bullshit.
It's written, like, old AVGM from 2005.
Old AVGM ripoffs.
Very important distinction.
Right.
Like, the people who were just,
who just slammed a bunch of swear words together
and they think that makes sense.
And I think he would put whatever...
And I think he was even more inelegant
than any of the ripoffs.
It's, like, just stop interrupting my damn rant.
I just want to get past this.
I, he's, this...
These reviews are shitty.
These worse than Chris Bors is that one.
I don't know who Chris fucking Bors is.
I don't care.
Let me finish my rant.
I have to keep going.
I have to keep my blood pressure high enough.
God damn it.
So he makes these shitty fucking reviews.
He's got these, this pixels review.
He's got his one for Fantastic Four.
He's got the one for the fucking, the visit.
Is that what the M. Night Shyamalan one was?
They're all the same review.
Copy paste.
He just gets mad at a movie.
Oh, so clever.
So, like, oh, we all get to hate this movie
because it killed our family.
He actually said at one point in the pixels review
that it felt like Adam Sandler came into his house
and pissed on his old toys or something.
Like, what the fuck?
It's a movie you paid to see, you fucking idiot.
So he goes and he writes these reviews
and they're always, like, the week it comes out
and they get really, they get a ton of views, right?
But here's the thing.
He's, even though, even though it's so easy,
he's doing the easiest reviews possible, right?
All he does is he writes a bunch of swear words.
He comes home and he just loops trailer footage
for six minutes while he just rambles.
His audio is garbage.
He fucking records into, like, a headset.
He cuts himself off at the end of words constantly.
I don't understand how he does that.
Like, he takes a week to do something
that I can literally do in 45 minutes.
In 45 minutes when I come home from the movie.
Like, pounding the render.
Yeah, and he'll come, he'll do these movies.
Like, if I did reviews like he does,
I could get them out literally five times a day.
I could do that.
I could review, I could review,
it would take me longer to watch the movies
than it would do to make those reviews.
They're just basic barebones shit.
And yet, somehow, he only makes, like,
one or two a month of those standard reviews.
And then he's got the really that good series
and these only come out, like, quarterly, right?
And they're, like, 45 minutes long,
they're heavily edited, you know,
they're good analysis videos,
but they're rambling.
He repeats himself constantly.
They're all 20 minutes longer than they need to be.
All of them could be cut in half.
He needs an editor.
He needs a fucking editor bad.
His audio is shit, so it's always like,
when you're listening to it,
it slowly grains on you, right?
Like, it slowly becomes tiring because it's so long.
You have to understand, Digi,
that if his microphone was better,
it would just pick up the sound of all of his fat jiggling
as he talks.
Yeah.
As he tries to squeeze out syllable
between the rolls and his fucking throat.
Here's the thing.
If MovieBob was just a channel
that put out, like, one review every month
and one really that good every quarter
and they were exactly what they were,
it wouldn't be a problem, right?
If that was all it was, if it was just some guy,
some YouTube guy doing that, right?
But it's not.
It's MovieBob.
It's MovieBob who has a lot of Patreon money.
Yeah.
A lot of Patreon money.
He has financial incentives to do nothing.
All he does is get 3,000 a month,
regardless of what he does.
Right.
He doesn't even get, like, at minimum,
he should have one,
because he has a monthly cycle,
so he's not getting paid by video.
He's getting paid by month.
So there are months that pass by
where he'll put out one six-minute bullshit review
that you could make in 45 minutes.
And it's like, all month.
And get paid thousands of dollars.
He's living in a world of privilege.
I wonder what his creator goal is.
I haven't even gotten to the biggest thing of all.
The big cherry on top of this shit Sunday, right?
So I'm already mad at him
that he doesn't get really that good out once a month
because he should be able to.
There's no reason he can't.
YMS puts more effort into his videos
and he can get out one a month almost always.
You know, I could easily get a really that good out
every fucking week if I had the material
and I wanted to do that, you know.
Well, you have DeVoo to do your...
I don't even need DeVoo.
I did 30 videos in a month
last August to October.
No one needs me to do movie Bob's level of editing.
Yes, true.
And here's the thing.
He put out this video.
This video made me so mad.
I almost shat a brick in my chair.
This dude puts out a video
where he literally says,
the next really that good is on the way.
It's a text video.
It's like, you know, epic music and text coming onto the screen.
It's like, but you know,
these, you know, I really have to fund these things.
So if you guys give me more on Patreon,
maybe it'll come out sooner.
Oh my God.
He really legitimately did that.
There's a whole video on his channel.
This nigga, right after that, he called up Domino's
because he's a pizza shit.
He made a whole video.
Like you said, he used to get out two videos a week.
I guess back when the escapist were constantly hounding him
to get off his ass and start doing things.
Everything I know about the escapist business
is that they're fairly cutthroat for internet standards.
But now he's just on Patreon.
What kind of work does he have?
What are even his creator goals?
$5,000 a month.
I'll finally put in a channel banner.
$7,000 a month.
I'll have a new avatar that is in a shitty selfie of my fat face.
Does he really say that?
Wait, is that for real though?
He doesn't have a channel banner.
$3,000.
No, but it doesn't actually say that on his Patreon.
No, but it should.
That's probably what he values.
He really had to be going for a second there.
You know, he probably got that.
This goes back to what I said before.
Davoo, I think it was, who said that, you know,
I hate people, things that make people money.
No, I only hate it when people make more money than they deserve.
And this is a case of a guy who I actually like movie Bob kind of.
I really like Really That Good.
I think it's a good series.
But I don't think he should be making $3,000 a month
to put out like four in a year.
It's outlandish.
It's fucking ridiculous, especially because like I said,
I like Really That Good too.
But again, I'm looking at it from the perspective of
I'm also a content creator.
And I can legitimately say I think I'm a better writer
than movie Bob in terms of like revisions.
Well, that's not hard.
I mean, I don't think he's bad.
It's just that he repeats himself too much.
Look, Digi, all we have to say is that you don't constantly
inject 9-11 into your writing, which actually,
that's actually the best thing I've ever done.
That doesn't bother me.
No, no, I think it's hilarious.
I love it.
Everyone should mention 9-11 for unrelated reasons.
He does it in his book.
He says, when I first saw Super Mario Brothers 3,
I thought it was the most impactful moment of my generation,
just like the shooting of JFK was for my parents,
and then 9-11 was for the next generation.
I thought it was amazing.
What the fuck?
I just can't believe that he has the gull to make a video
saying like, give me more money so I can finish this video
that's already a series I've already been doing.
And like, and what does he need more money for?
He's making $3,000 a month to do something.
Dude, I'll tell you exactly what it is.
He's living a life.
In his life, he needs some more money,
so he's saying, okay, they'll give me more money.
Bob, stop eating so much and you'll be able to fucking
afford your life!
He said fuck!
Even though like, this is why there are a lot of people
who are pretty click-baity or don't make a whole lot of
deep content, but we really respect like Anthony Fantano,
who proves those people exactly wrong by getting out of
video every day, right?
Yeah, and by the way guys, by the way,
I'd like to suggest that for our selling out purposes,
we should title this video The Movie Bob Rant.
The Movie Bob Rant, yeah.
I don't know if you don't want to start eating drama with
Movie Bob, but I imagine his fans would be terrible.
No, no.
But we do because that's the ultimate way to sell out drama.
Holy shit, let's talk about drama now.
Let's talk about that.
There is nothing more clickable.
Leafy is here.
Before we move on.
Yeah.
Go on, Ben, finish your fork.
Before we move on from Movie Bob, I just want to say that
I am about 75% certain that I saw him at the South Station
train station in Boston a couple weeks ago.
I mean, I was at like this station restaurant.
I saw him sitting there eating food at this train station
restaurant, but you know, I can't be sure because it could
have been any other big fat guy with a goatee.
I have food, big surprise there.
It didn't look exactly like him.
I am 100% sure.
And he is a Bostonian.
Yeah, right.
He is a Bostonian, so it's not entirely inconceivable.
But Ben, I am 100% sure that I saw Movie Bob on Google Earth
while I was browsing over the city of Boston.
What?
Were you zoomed out like eight times?
This was not street view.
He was just visible.
No, I was looking at the topography of the entire
Massachusetts area.
I was like, oh, hey, Movie Bob.
By the way, if you're a viewer of this show and you're fatter
than Movie Bob, we love you, and it's not a problem.
It's only gross to be fat if you're also Movie Bob.
Yeah, that's right.
No, Movie Bob is gross because he's Movie Bob,
and the fat is part of that.
I don't know, Movie Bob's easy to make fun of,
but I don't really mind him that much, except that I think
he should make less money.
No, don't get me wrong.
I'm with you, Ben, because I've been a fan of Movie Bob
for like five years, and I've seen all of his videos.
I think I've watched every single big picture.
I've been a fan for like eight years now.
I've watched all of his videos when he was on The Escapist.
Oh my God, the funniest thing ever was when someone,
he was doing like a Q&A video on Game Overthinker,
and someone asked him, when will you stop putting
in these terrible skits and just talk about games
like a journalist, which is the only thing you're good at?
And he answered like, yeah, maybe when I decide
that I'm okay with putting out an inferior
on total lack of self-awareness.
Okay, you know, that's really interesting.
It's really interesting, because the way that people,
there's such a weird dualality.
Yeah, exactly, he doesn't understand,
but you know, a lot of people are like that,
that they do these things because they're,
you know what, I don't want to shit on him,
but Jesse is kind of this way,
and just that he's so dead set in making his videos
in a certain way, even when other people,
even if he's good at it.
He's good at it.
I mean, it's not that he's bad at it.
It's not that he's bad at it, but like,
you look at him like the bloody dead man.
Jesse's good at it.
And I agree with that some of the time,
maybe most of the time.
Where is Jesse, by the way?
I don't know, he's out.
He's fucking his secretary, probably.
Movie Bob Skits are the greatest argument
against him as a film critic, period.
Yeah.
The fact that he can make that and think,
yeah, that's a good argument.
It's also the greatest argument against
personal artistic integrity.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
That's true.
Some people need to sell out more.
Some people need to sell out more to improve their art.
All right, yeah.
Let me get into that.
I want to, rather than drama,
because I don't even want to talk about that.
That could be its own podcast.
Yeah, fuck it.
We all get it.
We all do.
Like, so for me personally, like,
I grew up with lots of like weird ideas I wanted to do.
Like, most of the stuff,
a lot of the reason I never decided to work for a magazine
is that to me, being able to do what I wanted to
was the most important thing.
And I didn't want to have any rules or limitations
on what kind of stuff I was allowed to write or publish.
So I would look at all these, you know, online magazines,
and they all have like a very specific style,
a very specific formula.
I mean, Jeff, you had the nightmare experience
of you had to change your scores
to reflect what the site wanted you to give the score.
Oh, man.
Holy shit.
Let me tell you a thing or two about Steve Hanley,
that piece of fucking garbage.
Yeah, I'm saying by name.
That dude.
Could we get his home address?
His home address and phone number in the description.
Who is this we're talking about?
This is the editor-in-chief of Hardcore Gamer,
who, you know, I'm far enough out from that
that I have no worries about him attempting
to tank my career at this point.
At this point, I get...
I get more views on an individual video
than the entire site gets for a month.
So...
The best revenge is living well, as they say.
Yeah, and I mean, like...
Oh, God, there's so much wrong with that fucking website.
And it's not even a question of selling out,
because he didn't...
He had this weird sense of integrity
where he didn't understand what it meant.
Like, he wanted our reviews.
He wanted our review system to stay pure,
and by pure, I mean, ripping off IGN and Destructoid
and everything else on the internet.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I tried to make interesting reviews
that people would click on.
Like, when I reviewed one of the shittiest games on the planet,
Magus, I...
This is obviously ripping off something Jim Sterling did a long time ago
with Deadly Premonition,
where he gave that game a 5 out of 5 on Destructoid.
But I wanted to give Magus a 5 out of 5,
because that was a 5 out of 5 experience for me,
where I turned into a little leprechaun using a magic spell
and ran around like fucking Benny Hill,
circle strafing the final boss until he died.
That was fun times for me.
And he's like, no, we gotta give it a 1 out of 10,
because that's more true to what reviews are.
And it's like, okay...
Oh, yeah, let's just define our reviews
by what all the reviews say about the game,
instead of objectively abusing our own personal...
There was a moment...
What the fuck?
There was a moment I reviewed Stixmaster of Shadows,
which is the best stealth game to come out
in the last generation, period,
because all other stealth games are fucking garbage,
except for New Hitman.
Even Splinter Cell?
Yeah, even Splinter...
Especially Splinter Cell.
Splinter Cell is responsible for stealth games.
Don't get into a stealth rant.
What happened with it?
So I did a review of Stixmaster of Shadows.
He said I could put it on the front page.
I was the features editor at the time,
so I had the privilege to click...
Add this to the front page on my back-end thing.
I did that.
He took it off because the score was too high,
and he didn't want to make the site look bad.
And he said we could only put it back on.
I shit you not.
He said we could only put it back on
if another website gave the game a 4.5 out of 5.
Brilliant.
So just make your own website called Left Jew,
and then make a review.
He didn't understand remarkability at all as a concept.
You have to do something different from other people
in order to get people to click on your shit.
Because everybody writes game reviews.
Working for this guy didn't seem like it was a great time, was it?
And now you're reaching more people independently.
That's an interesting thing about selling out.
This is a very recent update in the world of selling out.
Normally it's like you get a dang publisher,
or label, or a manager, or an agent.
That's your key to sell out because back then
everything was made out of $1,000 analog equipment
that you needed to rent out in order to even use it.
And you didn't have the internet.
Today, working with other people
unless they're the exact right kind of people,
like all of us here, we're like so synergetic.
We're all really great people.
Synergistic.
We can work together and result in better and more product,
like this podcast you're listening to right now.
But by default, the idea of getting a manager
or a dude to do some things behind the scenes isn't necessary.
It increases the overhead.
It makes profits less likely, bogs things down,
makes things less interesting.
And I actually, just a couple like a month ago,
got an offer from a guy who runs a game publisher.
And they've developed some games themselves.
And he was like, hey, man, I like your videos.
So you're looking for a job.
And he wanted to offer me the position
to be a video game consultant of design.
Like basically just do game analysis,
but just tell them as it's being developed.
Wow, I didn't know a job like that existed.
And he also wanted to offer me...
That's a very profitable job, actually.
I have friends who do that.
Wow, I didn't even know it was a job until he told me.
And he also offered me to be like a podcast host
and also do game analysis for like their YouTube channel and stuff.
I'm like, you know, and if it weren't for the fact
that I was already doing the Digi Bro thing,
I may have more seriously considered it.
But then when I finally was able to put to finagle the conversation
into him into asking him how much he was going to pay me,
he asked me how much money I'm already getting paid.
I should have lied and said three times more than it is,
but I, you know, unfortunately told the truth.
Worst thing you want to do if you want to get big and sell out, by the way.
Never tell the truth, but more anyway.
So he's offered to basically pay me what I'm already getting paid,
but what I'm already getting paid is going up.
And so it's like Digi Bro's Patreon, which is indirectly paying me,
is going up at like a higher rate than this company is getting big.
And he even told me, this guy wasn't even like a great salesman.
Like I was doing a better job managing my PR than he was.
He was saying, yeah, we here at our company are pretty financially...
are pretty strapped for cash financially.
So not only are they strapped for cash, but financially so.
And it's like that was what really made it sink in.
Game development, especially indie game development,
is a giant death pit of money full of aides.
Like it's just not a good idea.
It's an over medium that's on the way out in terms of profitability
because everyone knows how to develop a game now.
You can't shake a stick without hitting an expert game designer
or a game developer.
Whereas YouTubers who really, really know what they're doing
are pretty rare for now.
And working all alone is actually a better system
because all your managers, your bosses, your agents, that's YouTube.
The YouTube algorithms are your managers.
And you have to work with them.
That's one thing.
Don't sell out by working with people unless they're the exact right kind of people.
This is the hardest thing, I think, for older people to understand
and why it's so hard for everyone who does this to explain to your dad
what you're trying to do.
We've had so many conversations with our dad trying to explain...
Nate, you need to go out and network with people.
He's always telling me to go to nearby colleges and find art students to connect with them.
I don't understand it.
I'm always asking them, why do you think that would help me?
It's because that's what he did to be successful when he was a kid.
And it's totally understandable, but...
I went out to buy a shirt with my mom and she was talking to the shirt guy
and she's like, hey, he does YouTube.
He could sell your shirts like a local shirt store.
Like they don't understand.
Yeah, it's totally different.
That happened to me at one time.
Well, parents will never get it.
My parents were at a GNC and the guy behind the counter,
he was a YouTuber who was trying to become a YouTuber.
The guy was working there.
And they were like, oh yeah, our son is a successful YouTuber.
They basically gave me his card because he had a card and everything.
This dude is not successful at all.
He's like a couple hundred subs, maybe like a thousand.
He's trying to do parkour and variety videos.
Oh yeah, you showed me this guy.
All of his content was just kind of weird and not really stuff that would get big on YouTube.
And this guy was in that mindset of like, I need to network.
I need to know people. I need to get my name out there.
He had the business cards.
He was trying to contact me.
He's taking the Mad Haas zone parkour pickup game.
He was trying to contact me because I'm popular and he was trying to find a way to network with me.
And I'm like, dude, I talked to him and I was like,
I think the problem with your content is that it's confusing.
People come here and they don't know what it is.
You haven't made anything that's going to like, none of your work is tied into anything.
There's no reason people would click on this stuff.
There's no reason anyone would seek this out.
And I was like, there's nothing me and you can do together because I do my work by myself.
You are not involved with anime at all.
Parkour is an urban colloquialism which is used for shortening.
It really interests me how outside people will hear that like two people work on YouTube
and assume that it's like at all similar.
It's hilarious.
You do the same job.
Hey man, I don't want you reviewing this movie.
Oh, not you again.
I don't want you reviewing this movie with me.
Well, I mean, look at all of us.
We barely collab and we're all best friends who do the same thing.
Like we all cover video games and anime and even we don't like leave it for the podcasts
because it's not something you want to do.
It doesn't make good content, you know?
And like, the funniest thing for me is my dad has it in his head.
Like, because he's always been supportive of what I'm doing.
He kind of gets it on some level.
But he has it in his head that I'm eventually going to end up on TV.
Like, he really thinks for some reason that I'm...
Oh, just like my hero, Jon Tron is going to do well.
Yes.
Jon Tron was on TV.
Yeah.
What?
He was on a commercial once.
No, but like, I think...
Okay, but the comparisons...
No, my dad thinks I'm going to become a TV personality.
Like, my dad thinks I'm going to get hired by a news network at some point and be like a TV guy.
And I'm just like...
The local news anime review guy.
That actually is a thing.
That actually...
There was one time, for a brief period,
we had the Hampton Roads show, like the local area news,
and they had like an anime block for like a short period of time.
Late at night at like 3 a.m.
I saw it once and I was like, what the fuck is happening?
It was so weird.
They were probably copying the Dolce and William or something, I guess.
No, it wasn't shows.
It was like talking about anime.
Like, local area.
Here's a way that maybe would work with some people's dads is explain this.
About half the people who watch YouTube have ad block and therefore don't see the ads, right?
Right.
Whereas 100% of people who watch TV fast forward through the ads now.
So there, there's the business discipline difference.
Can they do that?
And also no young people watch TV.
Oh yeah, that too.
Yeah, that's true.
So here's like a thing.
It's pretty bad when your parents are like, oh, you're going to be a TV person someday.
As a way of justifying to themselves what you do for a living.
My parents are very accepting of what I do and they think that it's, it's really cool
and they, they understand that I know better than them that there is actually a future in it.
That's nice.
But the other thing that you get all the time when you're a YouTuber is people giving you suggestions for shows.
Oh yeah.
And they're all terrible.
They're all bad.
So you did like, what if you went to like restaurants and did reviews?
I'm like, cause they're all in Virginia Beach and no one who watches me is in Virginia Beach.
You know.
What if, what if, what if you, you know, you're called mother's basement.
What if you gave your mom a vlog show?
I bet people would watch that.
Oh my God.
Mom vlogs.
Mother's basement's mother.
There was one time, one time I was babysitting my aunt's kids and she was telling me that
she really wanted to start up a vlog channel where she just like ranted about stuff.
And I was like, about what kind of stuff?
And she's like, I don't know, just stuff.
She doesn't have a TV, like a, like a presence for camera at all.
She talks really slow.
Well, hey, that's like a big fat old lady.
Oh, you guys show her Angela at all.
That's the only president I know for that on YouTube.
I mean, there are, there are like older people who are on YouTube doing rants.
Like I wouldn't be surprised to see a 40 year old mother on there.
Just, she doesn't even watch YouTube.
So like this whole idea is like, what do you think you're going to do?
You don't know what the trends are.
You don't know what you're trying to do.
Hey man, nothing's impossible.
Go watch the new Storyteller.
She didn't know what she was going to film it on.
You know, anything.
Anyone could be a YouTuber.
Yeah, the new Storyteller is so successful.
Yeah.
But like the procrastinators, that's a pretty big plug if I do say so myself.
Yes, true.
If that's the, if that's the highest that you've reached, then that's a very sad statement.
But you know, it's, it's not even that my dad,
Not that I don't love your new Storyteller.
My dad thinks I'm going to end up on TV because that would be like, you know, like what he wants from me.
It's just that he thinks of that as like the ultimate version of what I do.
Like TV is the, the final frontier, you know, and I'm like,
As opposed to your dying competition.
Right.
And like for me, I'm thinking like TV's on the way out.
It's going to be done.
It's not going to last much longer.
And like, you know, you'd have to be like, think about how like you get a guy like a,
Who's the dude who hosts at midnight?
Chris Hardwick is like the host of at midnight.
He's the host of several other talk shows.
He does the talking of the dead.
He does all these shows.
And I'm like, that's one guy occupying like over an hour of TV every night.
Right.
So that means that the talent pool is pretty small.
If you're at the top, you're in all kinds of stuff, you know, because you're the best guy.
Everybody wants you.
So there's only like a couple hundred people who are like TV hosts who are making real money.
And everyone else is on a local news station and they're probably making less than I make now.
You know, I'm making like over $40,000 a year this year.
If I make the same amount I have been making so far.
That's a damn good salary.
Yeah, I'm making fucking, you know, gotta think middle-class wages.
I think PewDiePie has really helped to evolve everyone's understanding of YouTube, including other YouTubers.
Because so many people know him.
Most people know he's a millionaire now.
And also the fact that he's like a real guy who doesn't feel like a shill.
And I think that's probably, I bet PewDiePie single-handedly has, or single-swededly progressed YouTube content so far.
What?
Because he's made, you can be like a real guy who's actually kind of charming and become the biggest guy.
He does create sort of an inverse problem though where people are like, oh, you should have 100,000 subscribers.
Well, you want people to think that, especially if it's like a girl and you're trying to like pick her up.
I guess if it's a girl, then yes.
That's very true.
You want to make that.
No, I, yeah, it's, it is a problem that people think you're rich just for having like a certain amount of subs.
But like, and it's also really fascinating to see like what people, what kind of selling out people think will work and what kind doesn't.
Because like, I want you all to look up Daim Drops, D-A-Y-M Drops, and look at-
I know about Daim.
Have you seen his Patreon?
It is the most hilariously depressing thing.
Because Daim Drops is a guy, he's this big fat black guy who sits in his car and reviews fast food from outside of the point.
Oh yeah, that guy.
He jumped.
That's a lot more.
That's a lot more than he was making when he started it.
Like, here's the thing.
Daim Drops started, he got big because of the Daim, Daim, Daim, Shmo Yoho song, right?
Shmo Yoho is huge.
Yeah, right.
So he gets pretty big through that.
He's got like over 100,000 subs, I think, right?
Where the heck is he?
He's got like 18 fucking dollars?
What the heck's going on?
He makes-
Take his word for it.
He has a pretty high subscriber count, right?
And he's considered like a part of the YouTube club kind of thing.
He's been out to the YouTube space, he's been invited to Taco Bell to do tastings of their new products for videos and stuff like that.
He's done endorsements and shit like that.
Guys, I think, and one of the factors that he doesn't seem to link his Patreon anywhere.
I had to just-
No, no, no, let me get to it.
He has a Wikipedia page, guys.
Let me get to it.
He's fairly well known as a YouTube personality, but here's the thing.
His videos are like five minutes.
The first 40 seconds is,
What's up, YouTube?
Facebook?
Twitter?
It's a main man, Dave Drost with another super official food review.
Can you take it, baby?
I know you can.
Hey, listen, man.
That's his intro.
Every video.
I can't believe I could still do that.
Sounds like a Hodge Twin sort of thing.
Yeah.
Well, he'll then, he'll get his food and he'll eat it and he'll talk about it and he'll give it a ranking out of five, right?
It is-
There's not a lot to it.
It's something literally anybody could do.
Like, yeah, he has-
But he just delivers his opinion on said food with so much personality.
Right, yeah.
He has a lot of gusto to it, but like, every video is the same thing.
If you watch one, you get it, you know?
And it's fucking fast food reviews.
And they're like three minutes long.
And so he makes a Patreon at one point.
And part of the problem here is, and I'm also giving this as advice to everybody,
your Patreon rewards, no matter what they are,
the numbers that you mark are like really psychologically controlling to your audience.
Yeah, yeah.
Because if you set, like, if you have it going, if you have a $1 tier,
like on mine, I made one that just said, for the longest time, all it said was $1,
and it said, I will love you forever.
And just by having that $1 tier, it makes people realize that they can give you $1,
and so they will, you know?
Yeah.
They have shit tons of $1 patrons because of that.
Whereas Daimdrop started off, and his first tier was like $40.
Yeah.
Because he was giving out like a lot of stuff,
but it was like a $40 tier and like $100 tier.
Oh man, you know what I saw?
And so as a result, he gained zero patrons for a long time.
A guy with over 100,000 subs had zero patrons.
You know what I've seen is that there are some people,
some patron pages where the first reward is like,
I'll thank you and also like, I'll give you a sticker
or I'll say hi on Twitter, and it's $2 as the first reward.
And I don't know if Patreon is still like this,
but at least earlier before the redesign,
when you go over and click on the Become a Patron button,
the number $1 is already in there,
but if it starts out at $2 as the first reward,
the default will be $2.
You sneaky bastards.
Me and Ben did that for our T-Bat patron
because there were two of us.
Was there justification?
I mean, I didn't do it for any sneaky reason,
but my first level is $5 just because.
So my Patreon is, I think, pretty successful.
I think it's the second most successful of ours
out of after-digies.
True.
Well, I don't think you make as much as Jesse makes
just because he patrons a lot more stuff.
Yeah, probably.
But because I'm on a monthly basis because I don't want to.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I just want people to be like,
I know how much money I'm paying each month.
Right.
But so I went to people I know
who have successful Patreons at the very beginning
before I even put it up, and I asked them for advice.
So the extra credits, guys,
and I think I asked you, Digi,
for at least input on my reward tier.
And I actually got put through to somebody at Patreon
who gave me additional advice.
And you were talking about the psychological priming
of your reward tiers.
Oh, yeah.
Essential.
Yeah.
So what you want to have is you want to have five reward tiers
between $1 and $10.
Because that creates like...
People at every level.
Yeah.
So that creates like a breadcrumb trail effect, right?
Where people will be like, oh, well, I mean,
I'm pledging $1.
I pledge two more dollars.
Exactly.
I get my name listed in a video at the end of the year.
I pledge $2 more than that.
I get to...
I pledge $2 more than the monthly Q&A.
Suddenly I get to join you for an anime night
where we hang out.
And it's really fascinating to see like
what people will pay for just because it's listed.
If you have a $15 tier and it's got...
And it's like limit 10 or something,
it could be fucking anything.
Just the fact that it's there means certain people
who have the money will pay that amount.
I think very, very few people really are interested
in the rewards most of the time.
It's more about suggesting to them that...
When people pledge to a patron, what they're really buying
is like a place in the narrative of the person.
But it's just funny because it's not
that they're going for the higher rewards
because I think there's a lot of people...
If you have...
If you're highest reward, mine goes $1, $3, $5.
So there's not a lot of stuff.
And most of the pledges I get are either $3 or $5.
Since implementing those ones, I mostly get stuff on that level.
There's probably a lot of people who if I had a $10 reward,
they would just raise it to $10 just because it exists.
And they think, oh, there's a reason to be 10.
Even if the $10 reward was nothing all that special
in relation to how much it costs.
It's just that I don't want to offer anything.
You only need the big rewards when you get to $80, $150
somewhere around there, which I've got people
who've bought into that from the beginning.
And I'm really grateful for that because it's helpful.
Although it is a lot of work to get that stuff actually made.
And big level patrons are scary because if they leave, you lose a lot.
That's true.
It's nicer to have a lot of $1 guys who can come and go.
That's why it's smart to limit your big level patron tiers
because then if they do leave for whatever reason,
there's somebody else who wanted that for a while and will buy in there.
I only have two levels of pledge rewards
and neither one of them is really a reward.
All you get is $5.
There's no real benefit except I post my stuff there first.
So in the long run, it doesn't matter.
But I didn't design them as rewards.
I just designed them as pledge this if you want to support me,
pledge this much if you really want to support me.
And that's it.
And I think it's been pretty successful.
I'm actually kind of surprised it's gotten as high as it has.
Funnily enough, once again,
we really haven't been talking about the concept of selling out so much
as this is now a guide on how to sell out.
I'm about to sell out.
So I'm going to give a piece of advice for the mindset.
So hang on.
Hang on.
I remember.
Just real quick, sell out mindset.
So there's this band called Clipping.
They have two songs that you need in your life.
The first one is a song called Outro from their first album, Mid City.
It's 10 minutes of a guy going,
Get money, get money, get money, get money, get money, get money, get money.
But it's two audio tracks that slowly desynchronize and over the course of it
and then re-synchronize at the end.
So it's just this chaotic train of get money.
It's like a hypnotic drug.
Play that when you go to bed.
When you go to bed at night, listen to the outro and just leave it on repeat.
And you'll easily pass out.
It just sounds like my choice.
Then here's the better part, though.
They also have a song called, I believe it's Get Up, something like that.
It's a song where it's the lead singer rapping over an alarm clock as the beat.
The beat is just,
And then he starts,
So set this as your alarm because the first lines in the song are,
Game, don't wait, hold up, wait, eyes on the ground, motherfucker, can't be late.
And so when you hear that, like, it wakes you up.
And then the first thing you hear is like, game, don't wait.
You're like, oh, shit.
And I always just jump out of bed and I'm like, all right.
It's time to fucking get money, get money, get money.
Use these two songs to program yourself.
Absolutely.
I'm working on a video.
I'm getting tired.
I'm getting weird.
I'm getting delirious.
My eyes start to go down, but then deep for someone within me, I'm just like,
Get money, get money, get money.
I come back up and I keep on going, get money, get money.
So I think the reason that this has become like a how to sell out video is because all of us are in favor of it.
Yeah, we all agree.
Except for maybe Jesse, but Jesse's style.
Maybe he is.
He just has the hardest time coming around to doing it.
Yeah.
Well, I don't think we're in favor of selling out.
We're in favor of like...
Monetizing our work, our fucking brutalized work we put thousands of hours into.
Getting money for your work and trying to get money for your work is not the same thing as selling out.
All right, listen to this.
Listen to this.
Let me break it down real quick.
Because there is abs...
If you want to spend your time, if you want to go to your nine to five and survive on that
and then come home and be your pure artistic ivory tower guy who doesn't involve money,
who doesn't corrupt your art with money, then that's fine.
You can do that as much as you want.
But if you want to be able to do that as your lifestyle, you have to monetize it.
You have to be able to survive by doing it and you need to come up with strategies to do so.
And that is why I want to say like when a while back, before Matthew Matosis made his Patreon,
he was expressing, and several people do, was expressing concerns.
I think Jeff was doing this too, about like, oh, if I make my Patreon, will people not like it?
Will people think I'm a sellout?
But to me, there is no case whatsoever to be made for something like a Patreon,
because it is purely a voluntary thing that people, based on love for you and wanting your content.
And that's why I really like the model of Patreon where you don't actually give them anything
other than like Ben said, a place in the narrative, and they're solely there to support.
To sincere thank you and like the right to call themselves like a true fan or whatever.
Exactly right, exactly right.
And so, but the core issue here is that there is nothing at all to be ashamed of monetizing your hard-ass work.
And I want that meme to die big time.
My Patreon has a ton of perks, but all of them are nothing.
They're just weird little words.
Well, I actually made some of my rewards.
I've changed them a couple of times. I don't even remember what they are.
But I remember specifically trying to make big level tiers that make it to where I am going to do things
that I want to do anyway, but can never justify the time for it otherwise.
That's a good reward.
I'm gonna talk about something that I think Jesse would be in full support of if he was here.
Jesse, if you're here, we're talking to things relevant to you.
Jesse's secretary, please get Jesse in.
Jesse's talked before about how like, for instance, when the whole where's the fair use thing came up,
Jesse was like, none of this really affects me because if we lost, if we lost the fair use battle
and I can't use footage of my videos anymore, I just have to become inventive and figure out how to make it work, right?
And like that mindset is kind of how I feel about like all this monetization stuff
is that to me, it's not about compromising my art and now I have to sell out.
Now it's a challenge. How can I uniquely work this into my narrative?
And so like, I have a Crunchyroll link where if you go to crunchyroll.com slash digibro and sign up for an account,
I get $5, right?
So like, I already had a series that was five must see anime you can watch right now,
where I talk about five shows that are available for free legal streaming.
So like, it was totally obvious to make that into now a Crunchyroll ad basically, right?
Because it's already what it was, is just, here's five cool shows I want you to watch.
Now I have also, you can make me money by doing it.
But that even was, that was like a little successful for making me Crunchyroll money.
Made like, you know, $75 or so.
But then I made way more because of the asterisk where sucks videos,
because I'm going on this epic tirade about how shitty this show is.
And then I managed to work in, right?
Well, no, it's even better because there's a part in part two of the asterisk where sucks.
This is when I first had gotten the Crunchyroll thing.
I do this thing where I say, you know, if you're watching this show on Crunchyroll,
you can easily click over and there's five other shows that have all the stuff this show has and are better.
Right, right.
And I go to this whole thing and you don't know that it's a setup for anything.
Like, I'm just talking about like, you know, even if I, I said like,
even if I was only allowed to watch anime on Crunchyroll and I couldn't click on anything else,
my browser was locked there.
I still have six other shows I can watch.
By the way, you can watch those shows using this Crunchyroll link that gets you to my account.
It was one of the smartest things I've ever written.
And people loved that.
I made way more money for Crunchyroll subscriptions than I did for that
than by an entire video just advertising Crunchyroll.
People thought it was so, I actually had people commenting like,
I signed up for Crunchyroll just because of how clever that ad was.
Yeah.
And you know, if you want to get like a master guide on how to always do a sponsor,
but always make it seem natural without seeming awkward.
Biggest problem in the universe.
Go vote it up.
Go listen to them.
Yeah.
They always, they only have like, they only have Harry's, Razor's and Casper mattresses
and sometimes Audible.
That's all they ever do.
It's been a hundred episodes, those same three ads of same three sponsors,
but they always segue into it interestingly and funny.
They always have like some funny thing to say about it.
It always feels good.
Right.
That's cool.
I'm a fan of how the two best friends guys do that on the super best friendcast.
Like they're, they don't do the ads live while they're podcasting.
They have them sort of pre-recorded, but they always have them like funny
and they have them be conversations that they would have on the podcast
that just happen to relate to Casper mattresses usually or flower ordering.
Right.
You know what we should do is we should monetize this video and put eight in video ads
every like 15 minutes.
Right.
That's a great idea.
Oh, that reminds me of.
So I had an idea to effort how to sell out and get the procrastinators podcast
to be the most successful podcast on the internet without, without any effort
whatsoever on our part when it comes to editing.
And that is, that is take our overlay with our faces on it.
Right.
And then just put that over extended footage of somebody playing counter strike go race
maps.
Yeah.
Just do that.
Oh, oh, what a great idea.
You know, I, I, I me and Davud did a commentary on this recently where there was a Pokemon
video I made and it was 15 minutes long.
And right in the middle of it, I did a who's that Pokemon.
And then I put an in video ad there so that it would be a commercial break.
And then after the video ad, it goes, it's onyx or whatever.
And so I was like, you know, on the one hand, it's a clever joke, but it also makes me more
money.
Yeah.
That's the best kind of joke of all.
That's the best way to do it though.
Like if you're looking at, if you're looking at the sell out stuff, you're like, uh, I
just had to force these ads into my videos and it always looks like that you don't want
to do it.
That makes it doubly.
I don't want to see it.
Like, like, you know, uh, like at the end of a, like a Tommy Oliver video or something,
if he's like talking about some service, he's clearly never used and doesn't care about.
And I'm just like, well, you obviously don't even buy into this.
You know, like for me personally, and the biggest problem in the universe is like this
as well.
They only endorse products that they use where they all got the Harry's razors and they all
love them.
Maddox has a Casper mattress, you know, and so, and I, I have both now as a result.
I've actually bought both because I trusted Maddox's word on them.
And you know, I know he's a guy who would want a high quality product.
So mattress is really that good.
They're pretty good.
I would say it's better.
Like, Earth, can I get these magical mattresses?
Oh, if only we actually, if only we actually got a promo code.
Right.
That would be excellent.
That would be getting paid for this shit.
I actually, I've, I've been prepared, like I was going to, um, like make a video of me
like whenever I shave, I'm going to do like a Harry's promo and just save it so that if
I ever get a Harry's endorsement, I'll have a video of me shaving with the razors to use
a promo.
You should get a victim film that.
I had that idea for ever.
Right.
Yeah.
And it is that I have to do it shirtless and that's creepy.
So, but, um, but anyways, like for me, the reason I waited until crunchy rolls, because
I actually use crunchy rolls.
So it's like, when I talk about it, I know everything about it.
I can tell you what shows are on there and what's worth watching and what are the pros
and cons of using it.
And, uh, you know, I don't like taking up endorsements with shit that I don't, that
I wouldn't use.
And you'll see this in my fucking hilarious videos about like those random boxes where
I had like two different, two different random box companies send me them.
And I, I, I did the videos on my after dark channel, which I didn't tell them I was going
to do, but like, you know, they offered me, I don't know.
So they sent me a box and I sit on my after dark channel and I, my conclusion is always,
well, I would never pay for this, but since I got it for free, it's kind of cool.
Like if you actually think this is worth your money, here's a link, you know, because like
I'm not going to lie about it.
And I think people really like that and it, they might even be more likely to buy it if
it is something that they think is interesting just because, you know, I'm not being like
so like, like when fucking, uh, George Weidman did that Luke crate ad, like there was a little
bit in there where you could tell that he was kind of like whatever, you know, like
he, he, he pulls out this shirt and he's like, there was more than a little, he was like
this, uh, labyrinth t-shirt cause, uh, David Bowie is cool, right?
Like, you know, that's the worst, shut up, George, shut the fuck up.
But I thought that was funny.
It was, it was humoring to show like he didn't pretend that he loved it.
You know, he didn't pretend like, oh, it's so worth it.
I got all this great stuff, which like whenever those companies like ask you to do something
for you, they send you other people, like other YouTubers videos who have done it and
they're always so full of shit.
It's always a guy who's like, oh wow, I got my new crate box.
It's going to be so cool.
I got an offer for this recently.
David's job.
I want to say a relevant thing first.
The documentary thing, right?
I got an offer from this, uh, the documentary company.
They sent you the video where the chick has these giant tits.
They sent me the one of the, the massive chick, the massive tits chick.
And she's great.
She really sold the shit out of that product, but, uh, I could never, I could never, I honestly
think that all the views.
I would die if I tried.
That video, it's like this woman with giant tits and she's just like, it's just a straight
up like six minute advertisement for this documentary company.
But like, it's only got like 5,000 views.
She's like a vlogger anyway.
So I feel like all the views on it are from other people that they sent the video to.
Yeah.
But you know, that really works for her cause she's like a vlogger anyway, that I don't
think people really care about anything other than her massive tits.
I also, uh, have taken that endorsement from the documentary company.
They are sending me a, they're sending me a pillow and a mouse pad and, uh, what?
They said they wouldn't send me a fucking pillow.
No, no, no, no, not the, not the inner pillow.
They're sending me the case.
Like, I want a fucking case.
Give those guys, I offered to use one in a fucking video and they were like, well, maybe
tell those guys about me.
Did you?
I want a documentary.
I'll do it.
It was, you know, the thing is though, and here's how I'm going to do it though, because
I'm like a hundred percent certain that that side is not legit at all.
Like it's, none of those are official documentary.
They're all for shows that don't have them.
They're super racing.
They're all way cheap.
So like in my video, I'm going to be like, so is this legal product?
Probably not.
Do you want to pay $50 for a hot, uh, lolly on your bed?
It's really up to you, man.
Yeah.
I, yeah.
So here's my question for you, Digi.
Did you ever, uh, actually accept that polygamy website, uh, promotion?
Oh shit.
And do, do a video about how to have your own harem.
Yeah.
I usually just forgot about that, but yeah, that would have been a great idea.
I have had that on my mind forever because I wanted to see that fucking video.
Dude, dude, work that into a review of like high school DXD or like something, I don't
know, whatever.
The problem is I get so many offers from stuff all the time that I, that I ignore that like
I just really don't, because most of it's shit I would never want to advertise.
Like there's this one dude who keeps fucking emailing me about like a, it's like some browser
based, uh, game site where it's like one of those where you buy coins.
It's like it's free to play games, but you buy like currency and they're, but they're
like anime themed and they've all got like really nice looking, like cute girl, anime
art, but they're all like these really shitty, weird tactics games, dude, the other day that
just reminds me just yesterday, I was at work, like finishing up some shit and, uh, like
all the, I get a pop up.
That's just like literally honey pop only like re skinned and like with, with like, you
have to like buy, like it's, it's like a Facebook game.
So it's like you get energy and you use it up and you have to buy more to keep playing.
Like, and it was just in a fucking pop up.
The entirety of honey pop was there.
Only someone in fucking stolen.
And you see, I think this is why, um, there aren't that many big advertised, uh, sponsored
people out there.
It's just audible and a few others is because most YouTubers who are worth a damn, uh, have
too much integrity like compared to anything else we've had before.
Well, it's also, because like you can't have like any, like you're, you're so much more
that, that's one of the great things about YouTube is that everybody is so much more
accountable than they were back in the days of TV.
If you were a big shield, you're going to have a lot of explaining about it.
And I think that might be why they're social sponsors.
You're kind of right and kind of wrong because a lot of these guys, a lot of these guys
who, who approached me, they do get a lot of people, but they're all small YouTubers.
And the reason is that they usually don't really offer you that much.
Like all those, the reason I made those box videos on the after dark is because they didn't
actually pay me.
They just sent me free boxes.
The box is worth 20 bucks.
You know, like for me, a full video on my main channel, that's worth like, like, you
know, now what, $800 almost, like for, for, for Patreon.
So like with the, like the Campani girls, which is that, uh, browser game, they were
like, if you advertise us, we'll give you like $350.
And I'm like, that's not worth, like I make more than that.
Like if the amount of time I would spend on your video, I could spend making my own
video that would make more money for people trying to sponsor things are very strapped
for cash financially.
They're, yes, they're all very shady and strapped for cash.
And like even the documentary guys, like they offered to send me a pillow and a mousepad.
And that was like, I actually haggled with them because like initially they were like,
we want to send you, uh, we want to send you a pillowcase and we'll send you the inner,
or they said, we want to send you a pillowcase and you'll make a video about it.
And they had like all these bullet points that want to be to address.
And I said, how about I just work it into a regular video?
Cause I already had this plan in mind that I'm going to get a pillowcase for a show
that I plan to talk about in the near future.
So I'll just bring it up in that video like I did with the crunchy roll thing.
It'll be hilarious.
And that'll sell way more.
And they were like, well, if we throw in the inner pillow, will you make a video?
And I was like, no, I've got an inner pillow.
It'll be fine.
Right.
And then they were like, well, how about we throw in a mousepad?
Then we're like, they just said, how about we throw in a mousepad?
Okay.
Why do they want a worse marketing?
Why do they want worse marketing?
Well, they don't want to chase.
Why don't we throw it out about the fact that they're broke?
Like you're not supposed to do that.
Well, no, no, no.
Then they said, how about we throw in the mousepad and they just want me to make
like a full advertisement so they could show it around.
You know, so like, so they're like, what if we throw in a mousepad?
And I said, I'll tell you what, if you throw in the mousepad, I'll make a video
on my after dark channel, which has 30,000 subscribers.
And so they agreed to that.
So I'm going to do like a regular ad video for them on after dark.
And then I can just promote it my own way.
Now they are giving me a discount code.
I actually don't know if they plan to pay me based on that code.
Like if I'm going to make any money from them having this discount code.
Yeah.
Well, what else would the point be?
Well, they said that they were going to like track the metrics and they would
keep sit like basically they'll keep sending you more shit if you if you're
successful, like if you drive more traffic, which for me is like, all right,
I'd rather have money, but I will never spend money on these
anime pillowcases, but I would love to have them.
So like this is a it's a fun way for me to get a bunch of cool pillowcases,
you know, like that I wouldn't pay for because they're not even legal fucking,
you know, like they're not making any money for the people who made the shows.
So like so it's it'll be fun for me.
It's something I want.
So I'm willing to accept it.
But like, yeah, most of these advertisers, they make it out like
they're going to give you something special.
But they're really like for someone at my level, it's not even worth it.
Whereas with like Crunchyroll and Audible, they give you like a lot of money
for those refer like Crunchyroll gives me $5 for everyone who signs up.
You don't even have to make a paid account.
You just sign up at all using my link.
I really need to get on the people I know at Crunchyroll to get the fucking
crunchy code. No.
And the problem is that everyone's doing it though.
H3H3 has it.
John Tron has it, you know, same with Audible.
But the reason people keep still using Audible is that I'm pretty sure they
pay even more because it costs like a they give you a free month.
But as I found out the hard way, it doesn't.
It's one of those that auto refreshes at the end of the month.
So if you don't unsubscribe from it like I didn't, you end up paying
$15 a month for eight months and then you have to make a large
splurging day on audiobooks, which you had already realized a long time ago
were not your thing.
So now I have eight audiobooks I haven't listened to and like a hundred
dollars that I accidentally spent on Audible.
But those things are really successful.
And that's like, I realized how much they must make when it was
because I watch Bro Science and he's always had an audible thing.
And at the end, there was one video where he said,
use my audible link.
It makes us a frankly unfair amount of money.
And I was like, oh, like, yeah, if he's
subscribing to unfair, it's got to be he's got to be making like a thousand
dollars a month or something off of it.
You know, he's like a million subscriber channel, I want to say.
So yeah, yeah, it's got to be a lot of money.
That's dope as fuck.
Well, I don't know.
We exhausted a shit.
I have been.
It was like, I have to say about this conversation for quite a while now.
It's great. Everyone should do it. I don't know.
Oh, you know, I do.
I do have one more point I want to make about it.
And it's just that and it's pretty much just a summation of what we've
been saying up to this point.
It's just you shouldn't view people like tailoring their content
to to attract larger audiences as like inherently a selling out sort of thing
because no, like you're there's always going to be an artistic process
involved when you're making something.
And there is a line that you can cross, which John Tron class long ago.
I just want if you don't cross that line, then you're all good.
You should be. It's all great.
My my go ahead.
Yeah, my opinion on like tailoring content to what will get seen.
As far as I'm concerned, my videos don't actually exist until somebody watches them.
You know, sure. Yeah, like that that is when they actually start to matter.
So to me, the idea of, you know,
making stuff in a way that will try to get people to see it
is inherently part of the process of actually making the video.
Yeah, because like if I just make a video and I put it out and like 100 people see it,
like, yeah, it it's it's cool and that's good.
And I applaud people who do that.
But to me, part of the reason that I do it in the first place
is because I I I'm one of those crazy people who actually likes to hear
what people have to say about what I've had to say.
So I read comments, which is not a terrible idea.
I accept compliments, but I don't give a shit what people actually think about it.
Yeah, well, to an extent, I mean, I I'm already right all the time.
So what do these people have to offer to the conversation?
I was just checking through my YouTube messages to see examples of spam I've gotten from companies.
And somebody, yeah, somebody.
That's all the messaging system is used for, really.
Like somebody like the occasionally like occasionally some fan
who's telling you that you're the greatest thing in their entire life.
And then like nothing but like MCM spam and MCM spam.
Like I've got a lot of that.
But yeah, no, I found a thing where somebody made a video reply to one
of my sort of online video, which I will take a look at.
But yeah, like I do like seeing people who have different opinions to me.
And I like getting more comments.
And that's a big part of why I went to YouTube from text blogging,
because I get no fucking comments on any of the game reviews that I wrote
because nobody reads anymore.
Readings for fags.
Yeah, nobody reads.
Yeah, yeah, it's essentially the trajectory I had.
I think I was I feel like I started talking about this earlier and I got sidetracked somehow.
But like, you know, and I made this video called Invitational Art.
It's a vlog on my Digibro of the Dark channel that talks a lot about this,
how there's there's sort of like boogie art and pop art,
where pop art is something that's trying to appeal to everybody.
And boogie art is just trying to appeal to yourself,
just stuff you made just basically for you without too much concern.
And boogie pop is what like bridges the medium.
That's what the ideal.
That's what the concept was of the boogie pop novels,
was that it was the author trying to after years of not getting published
because everything he wrote was too weird.
He tried to make something that was weird, but had just enough pop appeal
to succeed and it did.
And like that, for me, has always been like a great thing
because to put it simply, if you don't,
if you think that selling out is a problem,
don't post your fucking shit anywhere because there's no reason to.
If you just want to make stuff that's just for you, that's fine.
You could probably make a fucking masterpiece that no one will ever understand.
But the second you put it out there,
you're saying that you care what other people think.
You care that other people see it.
And if you want other people to care about it,
then you have to, on some level, make a compromise and invite them in, you know?
So like you're it's a it's a give and take.
Now, you you don't have to compromise all the way.
You can be like Jesse, who makes videos that are primarily for himself
and mostly for himself, but he likes it when people do get it.
And, you know, and he is actually able to make a living
off of the few people who get it because they get it so hard
that they really want to support it.
Whereas, like for me, a big part of the appeal of making videos
is like, how big can I get?
How how can I how much can I
Coto to what the masses want without making something I wouldn't want to make?
You know, I'm sorry.
How did you pronounce Coutou just now? Coutou, you know what I mean?
Jesus Christ. OK.
But like there's there's there's channels out there.
Let's say you get to a discussion.
There's channels out there like this, you know, barely speaks fucking English.
I've said it before.
What makes you think I want to speak English?
Yeah, yeah, fuck you about you fucker.
We got to get a boot.
Anyways, that's Scottish.
You know, as Canada, Christ, I say about about.
That's not a boot.
If anything, it sounds like a boat.
A boat is the fuck.
Go back to the ground.
I don't remember what I was saying anymore.
Yeah, I just I couldn't.
I could never do like, you know, Misty Kronexia level of like and and don't get me wrong.
I don't think that guy is like just doing it for hits.
I think he legitimately likes making that kind of video.
And that's just the kind of guy he is.
And it just happens to be as popular as maybe you couldn't make as much of that
as he makes if you didn't enjoy.
I will say, though, that glass reflections like and I just heard this here say second hand.
But like I was saying how I once criticized him as his videos are like
if you took every like mal review and Reddit comment and just like
constructed them into a video of like whatever the most common opinions
that people has are, you'd get his videos, right?
Like it's like he he somehow manages to reflect the like the lowest
common denominator opinion of a show.
And I was told are you saying that I mean is wrong.
Are you are you having a double standard here?
Are you saying his opinion is wrong?
Are you saying he's wrong?
I don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
He's saying his opinions, not his opinion.
Are you?
Yeah, I'm saying that I I've been told that he's doing that on purpose,
that he deliberately tries to have the most what he thinks people want to hear
review. I don't know how true that is, but that's also how it feels.
And whether he's doing it on purpose or not, that is what the what the result is.
It's it's always the most like this is what you would expect everyone to say.
And that's why he's so agreeable and why people why he's like the biggest guy
because he writes the most agreeable videos.
And I could never do that.
I could never try to like meter out what I think people want to hear.
And it's not a good idea to anyways, because appealing to one extreme
or the other is is even more of a way to get attention.
Like if I make that video about a race, like if I had just made a video
that was like, here's what everyone thinks about a race.
Yeah, that would get a lot of attention if I was a big channel,
like, you know, Glass Reflections, but having an extreme opinion means
that while one sector is really pissed off, the other sector thinks
it's the best possible video about a race and they they worship it, you know.
So like same with Sword Art Online, that's why that video.
So those videos are so popular because the sect who hates it loves those
really hate it. Yeah.
Right. Like, I mean, I've got I've gotten the same benefit from Sword Art Online.
I'm trying to see if I can get the same benefit out of hating Uncharted
so far. We'll see. Going OK.
It's my it's like my I think too many people love Uncharted.
Well, yeah, but there's there's people who don't.
A lot of people really loved Bioshock Infinite
and a lot of people continue to really love Bioshock Infinite.
But for some people, the Matthew Matosis video is the most cathartic thing
in the world, right? And yeah, that's true.
Yeah, this is my fastest hit getting
video game video of all time.
And I'm not sure how much of that is down to me having gained
40,000 subscribers since I last made probably a little bit of a video about.
Well, actually, no, I made my hitman video.
I think after I started my big climate subs.
Oh, no, I made it right.
Yeah. Now, you know, I had gotten like
not to hold on.
There is one thing I definitely got to say about because we've talked all about
talked about personal satisfaction with your work,
monetary success with your work.
But then there's also fame and acclaim.
We haven't really talked about that yet.
One thing you guys got to know is because I think a lot of people
like there's a lot of great YouTube content creators who have over a million subs.
But I don't think there's any.
I don't know of any great YouTubers who have 10 million subs, right?
I think that tier is.
Oh, really? OK.
Well, at least, it's very true.
Who, who? Who, who, who, who, Gib?
Oh, you know what? I agree.
Yeah. Yeah. He's the one exception.
He's the one guy.
There's only like 10 shadows with more than 10 million.
But still, the thing is, well, here's the thing, though.
Right? Are you are you saying that Taylor Swift Vivo is
not a killer?
Is going to play play, play, play, play.
Because in regard to the subject.
OK, I heard that in a story.
In regard to the subject.
It's on fucking rules.
Everybody doesn't agree that shake out was the greatest artistic masterpiece
of all time is a fucking idiot
Is that's another thing that about that you're gonna use to evaluate your decisions just keep in mind
I just love party music 10 million
Those though the ultimate biggest big big big big people
My ex-man called his new girlfriend. He's like, oh my god devil shut the fuck up
Can we wrap this thing up, please aren't going to be as famous in the future the people who are going to be
Respected and remembered for decades into the future are people like cg3 or us or people like us or people who are
Not quite at that highest level. They're gonna be the people who are seen as like the Star Wars of this era
So if that's what you're going for remember, you don't gotta be the most famous now
Star Wars was the most famous when it came I know
It's not exactly one-to-one parallel, but it's going to be like Blade Runner or something like or the thing
I could have said Van Gogh, yeah
All right, that's it. Yeah
All right now guys Jeff would say as Jeff would say thank you for watching this podcast about
Selling out. It was a good podcast
Why does your Canada spoof sound like the fucking anime snob?
Give him like a
Montral voice or something. Like I thought I was going for Quebec. I don't I don't fucking
All right, thanks for watching
Everybody
Money