Hello, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Poopcast.
I'm the best Poop ever. I'm joined by Mumkey Poop, Munchy wears tiny craps, Ghostbusters
2 is better than Ghostbusters 1, also I like Poop. So today, as you can tell, we're talking
about a very serious topic. One day we have to do the Poopcast, but for now, we need to
don't see the smoke when the person exhales. Now that's a ghost. Oh god, I love you Urban
Dictionary. What about Ghost Poop? Do they have Ghost Poop on there when you let out a
turd and then you look in the toilet and you can't see it? You can't see it. No, none
of this. Oh, but you know, Mumkey, you were right. Number two was Ghost to avoid someone
until they get the picture and stop contacting you. So that's basically what you were talking
about. We've all been there. Of course. So we're dealing mostly with number one here,
Ghost. I thought it would be dealing with number two. Plop. Where's Jesse when you need
him? Ghost, the Discarnate. Discarnate? I guess that's a word. Soul of a deceased human
being or animal. Or animal. We're dealing with animal ghosts. Still occupying the physical
realm. These spirits may or may not know that they are dead. They can also be called forth.
They can also be part of the definition. Oh my god. Oh wait, wait. Okay, number two. There's
like four definitions for this. Number two is residuals. Residuals is a ghost, I guess.
Okay. Number three, a demon, angel, saint, or Christ himself. Jesus is the most powerful
ghost, no demand. And number four, a poltergeist. Okay, there you go. We're like a polter cost.
Like a holocaust ghost, like a ghost of Auschwitz. Okay, cool. Wait, so who wins in a fight? Danny
Phantom or Jesus Christ? Are we going to record that right after this? I think we probably
should. I think while we're in the mood. Well, I'm down to clown for that. Okay, we're going
to go ghost. So, I mean, how should we just talk about that right away? Because actually,
we had planted a ghost episode before some recent events transpired, but there's sort
of a new context to discussing ghosts and going ghosts, you know, in today, the news.
So I don't know if you folks have subscribed to a little channel called Mumky Jones, but
I mean, I know it's not very popular. It's not very well liked, but it's not at all.
So there was a mass shooting recently by, what's the dude's name, Mr. Staircase? Yeah,
Randy Staircase. That's right. Randy Staircase, a silly boy, decided that he was going to...
Yep, that's what he is. He's a very silly boy. For some reason, I'm sorry, I miss gendering
him. He identifies as a woman. He identifies as a female ghost because he loves Ember from
Danny Phantom so much. So at some point with logic, I didn't quite follow. He then decided
it would be a good idea to shoot up the supermarket that he works at and he killed like three people
and then himself and he went ghost. He has gone ghost now. So I guess we should discuss
our plans to do so as well, you know, like when we'll be also going ghosts to join Ember's
sick band and remember the name. What do you think, Mumky? When's your plans for that?
Well, first of all, I don't think this should have been a surprise to anybody about his
mental state because he was a diehard brony. So we already knew he was mentally unstable
and a childish. But as far as me going ghost one day, oh buddy, unfortunately I don't plan
on taking other people out with me like Mr. Staircase did. I'll probably end up going
ghost in my bedroom closet with a noose. My question is, when we all go ghost, what ghost
activities are we all going to partake in together? Are we going to do a PCP ghost?
Like a ghost version of the PCP where we're all recording a podcast as ghosts?
Yeah, I think so. With ghost microphones and ghost wires.
To the ghost internet, which is like they're drawing a new book for ghosts.
Yeah, right. That makes a lot of sense. But Digi will be too much of a pussy to kill himself
now that he has all that money, so he'll have to join in via Ouija board.
That'll be a good way to bring in our patrons, our patron supporters who give us real money.
We communicate via Ouija board. We only need ghost money at that point.
As for what I'm going to do when I'm a ghost, two words buddy, global warming. I'm going to
think global warming is real and it happens swiftly. I'm going to put all my power into
warming up the atmosphere with my ghost body. How does being a ghost do that?
I'm just going to get up in there and I'm going to be all spiritual and shit and it's going to
just happen bro. If you're trying to turn up the heat, I've got the ghost for you.
Okay, we got the song out of the way. I just turned all our audience to ghost. That was painful.
I'm running out of steam on this Ember trick. So maybe we should actually go to our ghost
stories because we are going to, I think like the general through line here is we're going to talk
about our views on ghosts themselves and then yeah. This is one of our ghost stories and my
Ghostbusters 2 is the best movie ever made. So should we start with what we think about ghosts,
our beliefs in ghosts and all that shit. I'm just going to start off saying that ghosts are
literally not real and there is no, they are 100% do not exist. If you think so, you are a fool.
And any explanation for a quote unquote supernatural event that you think could be
attributed to the supernatural is a billion times more likely to be caused by some sort of
physical phenomenon that you just aren't aware of or don't understand. So are you really prepared
people to like invent a whole nether world as the explanation for why like your chair shook
once as opposed to, I don't know, fucking tectonic plateshifting dude. I don't fucking know.
Nate, are you talking about ghosts or about the Christianity religion?
Well, you know, they're related. They're kind of really souls. We just said Jesus was a ghost.
Jesus Christ is the most powerful ghost. Here's my case. Ghosts aren't real, but they should be.
And I'm willing to, I need to become a statesman. I need to study the art of statecraft so I can
get into president and I can use my executive power to make ghosts real. I'm 100% behind you on
this one, dude. Right. Every time that I remember that ghosts aren't real, I want to kill myself
so I can become the first ghost and start the first ghost nation because every every like
ghosts are the only thing that I think matter in real life because they're fake and fake things aka
are better than real things because they're fake and ghosts are fake. That's my logic. You know,
before we get to off track, I did want to ask. So like Randy Stairs, right? Was he, did he actually
like believe in ghosts? Was he like, did he think that Danny Phantom was real? Like, what was his
headspace at? So he legitimately thought that upon death, you would enter the ghost zone from
Danny Phantom where you could be and do whatever you want. I mean, that sounds really cool. And
that's pretty much Christianity there. That's what I want, bro. That's what I want. The great thing
about the, the great thing about the ghost zone is that unlike with Christianity, you can commit
suicide and still go there unlike in Christianity, which has that annoying clause of you have to keep
living and paying, you know, dividends to the church. Right. When I'm a ghost, all I want to do
is heat up the earth, cause global warming and you know, maybe fuck a few star systems while I'm
at it. Not anyone in it, but in the solar system. What's up hippo buddy? Hello. Oh, I hope you enjoy
Doctor Who, you fucking non-ghost. Yeah, piece of shit. You fucking physical form being. Yeah, we
started. Yeah, we fucking started. We started on time, goddamn you. Why weren't you? Yeah. I don't know.
Well, fuck you. If you're lucky that Major was having mic issues or you'd be, you'd be shit dead. Oh,
yeah. Ghost, you'd have gotten ghost right now. Oh, no. Would I kick Major off by coming in? Oh,
my God, you left so many messages. She had technical issues. Yeah, that was some of me
spamming that hypocrite. Yeah, we almost got Jeff in here. The ghost of the PCP.
Well, okay, what else we got? Gib, what do you think about ghosts? Tell me what you think about
ghosts. I think they're pretty cool, but they're, you know, they're not real and that's pretty,
that's basically a real, you agree that they should. Okay, okay. I believe in the dream bubbles. Yes.
What if a ghost fought a skeleton? Who's more powerful between you? A skeleton, of course. A
skeleton is a raggedy, dingley, dingley dangoy. He's got little rattly bones and he can play
xylophone and impress them into, into disaparating them. Like, you can't, you can't destroy a skeleton.
He just puts himself back together. A ghost you can put into a vacuum, it just, they're just,
there's just so much worse. Well, okay, I don't know about that because while skeletons do have
that raw physical manpower and then that raw horsepower and the unbridled consensual sexual
ability that skeletons possess, you know, at whim. Ghosts, they can cause global warming.
They can walk through walls, disappear and fly. They're much more unique than the other guys.
Yeah. And. Who's ever knew what he had to do to stop all the ghosts out of coming through?
He's here to fight for me. Not only that, but they cause slime, the most important thing a man
could ever drink. I'm so glad you brought up the ectoplasm thing because I really want to get deep
into ectoplasm. Yeah. Oh yeah. Basically, all I think about is ectoplasm. This is where my love
of slime comes from. Really? Is that the genesis of your slime love? Say that again?
Is that really the genesis of your slime love? This is deep lore. Yes, exactly. Exactly. One time,
you know, I thought about ghosts and I thought, oh man, I love slime. Just like that. Yeah, oh man.
Slime. Yeah, slime. Slime. I hate slime, dude. I don't like slip and slide and I don't like soap.
I don't claim myself. It's disgusting. Why would you even give a low-crash coffee? I want to try out
my whole skin. I want my skin and organs and blood to drain away so I can become a skeleton,
the driest, bestest friend you could ever be. Oh my god. A skeleton versus ghosts is like yin and
yang. It's like the ultimate slime versus the ultimate not slime. The ultimate drive. Drive versus
slime. Drive versus white. Can someone clarify for this for me? Okay, so do ghosts produce ectoplasm?
Like when they touch, then there's goop there. Or is like ectoplasm like what a ghost is? It's what
you make when you see a ghost. Okay, what it is is like ghosts are not of a material of this world.
So when they try and interact with like a physical object, like a wall or something,
then like they're like atoms fuck up the real world and not imaginary things. And they turn
into fucking slime, which you think can then turn into a delectable drink and then drink and then
turn into a super Saiyan yourself. So you're telling me, okay, so ectoplasm is kind of like a
waste byproduct of a ghost's existence in the physical plane. Is that correct? Exactly. Yeah.
Okay, awesome. Awesome. In Danny Phantom. Slimer is literally me. He's literally me. There's not a
single more character that is more like me than Slimer. When you look at Slimer, you just think,
yep, that's munchy. If you were to try and argue that Slimer is not me, I think you'd be way off
base and you'd probably be wrong on every level. I think Slimer should make a cameo in My Little
Pony. I'm just throwing that out there. Oh, remember that one time Curry made an appearance of My Little Pony?
He was a little pony, My Little Pony. That was a slime character in episode something or other
season six. Oh, Hugh Jelly. Hugh Jelly was a slime boy, right? Yeah, dude, Hugh Jelly.
There was a literal slime guy and he came to the party and he had a little bow tie.
I don't remember that. He was a friend of Discord. You're a little My Little Pony
faggot. You don't even know. Oh, no. Okay. So can we all agree that we don't believe
that ghosts are real? Yes. Are you on board with that? I'm 100% on board. But they're all great.
Okay, so has anybody interacted with people who legitimately think that
they do? And if so, what's the story? Because I have several people in my life.
I do as well. Go for it, Tom. Yeah, Tom. Yeah, you should talk.
I don't know. I mean, just like I come from like a spiritual household, like, you know,
people in my house, they believe in religion and all that stuff. And ghosts, I guess they're a part
of that. And it's interesting because like I talk with my dad a lot because we both work in that
abandoned building where like 100 people have died and there's like pseudo crazy shit that goes on
that place all the time. And like there I've had experiences that most people would attribute to
ghosts. But I know it's just like my primitive monkey brain having having a overreaction.
What's that supposed to mean? Well, I mean, I'm not taking it back. So you're just gonna have to deal
with it. I didn't fight alongside you in the great monkey war for this whole shit.
Well, yeah, I mean, so like, you know, my dad's kind of more of a spiritual guy. So he will say
like, oh, yeah, there's definitely like ghosts and stuff in there. It was like, and I'm just like,
no, I think it's probably just my my my brain freaking out on me. But I did have a weird
experience there a couple days ago. And I was I knew it was just like, yes, it's me just freaking
out. But it definitely felt like, you know, it's interesting how like the things line up. So
just like, oh, yeah, it feels like there's something going on, even though they're totally sure. So
he was really good at pattern recognition. It's our biggest flaw. Yep. Yep. Because it makes us
think things that aren't actually true. And then it becomes as big intercontinental religion. And
then people lose all their money. And it's bad. And that's how Jesus the ghost came to be.
Yeah, the losing of the money is bad. But it's it's the worst. Forget going. Well, I know, I know,
I don't know anybody who actually like believes believes in it. You know, as far as I know,
I feel like the people who say they think about ghosts, they just, you know, they're having fun
there and a bit of like, oh, I wonder what that could have been. Well, you know, you'd be wrong
because my dad thinks he's seen a ghost before. Okay, you know, right. I mean, I kind of I'll
talk about a story with my dad, too. That's not specifically about ghosts, but it's kind of relevant.
But like the thing about the thing about believing in things that you don't know are real, like I
don't really have a problem on its face with believing in ghosts if you just like want to.
But the thing is, like, what I think what you're actually doing when you like allow yourself to
believe that stuff is you're like, allowing yourself to be like intellectually lazy, and you're
just like assuming something that you don't know is true. And like, you're encouraging within yourself
a pattern of behavior to just like believe things without proper evidence for them. And like, that's
what I object to that kind of like intellectual laziness. I don't know if I go that far evidence.
They think that they've seen evidence. I think they're wrong. I think the thing about about ghosts
is I think people just like it's the same thing with like aliens and all that kind of paranormal
shit. I think it's just fun. Yeah, exactly. I think it's just fun to to. It's fun to believe in
God. Well, it is. It is fun for forever. I think it's just people looking for comfort and for
religion. It's definitely a come more of a comfort thing. But I think for like ghosts and like
Bigfoot and like all that kind of shit. I think it's just fun to think that there's more to the
world than what we figured out, you know, that have this a mystery left in our otherwise predictable
and mundane existence. You know, I'm totally cool with that. And I okay, go ahead. Go ahead. I just
want to say I love how fucking terrifying God is like he's the scariest fucking guy. I'm so scared
of the ultimate ghost sending me to fucking hell. It's it's real fun. Are you going to join us for
the bonus episode we're doing who wins Danny Phantom versus Jesus? Yeah, yeah. Okay, you can
decide that later. But you know, the thing you know, Christopher Hitchens always had a great
line I loved about God, which is just or not, you know, about like Christianity in general,
where it's like Christianity is like, oh, no, he might have been about Islam, but it's all kind
of the same thing. Any monotheistic religion, they're all like they are, it's like you and these
people who like are all about it and like are so happy that they have God watching over them,
and then judging them if they should go to heaven or hell. It's like wanting to live in a
celestial North Korea, where like all your your inner thoughts are judged at every moment. And if
you go against the great leader and what he has decided is correct. That's you like you're gonna
fucking go to hell and people who are like, yeah, God, he's got my back. That's you being like, yes,
treat me like a slave, treat me like an unthinking automaton. That's what I want. And I don't even
believe in free will, but these people claim to and so they're really going against their own
fucking message here. But forget that, Tom, please continue. Wait, wait, just to interject
here real quick, because I think it's really important. You know, I was a non-believer a
couple days ago, you know, I didn't believe in the holy book, the good book that is. And my name
wasn't in the book of life, but ever since I was called an abomination yesterday, and I was gifted
Titanic and The Peacemaker, my two favorite Marvel DC comic books, I hope get him meditation
soon. I'm just gonna read you a little bit of a quote from these heavenly books that
they restored my fate. Oh, shit. That old hand, she never leaves me alone. I hate her and her Jesus.
I wish she was dead, dead, dead. All right. Yeah, you could see more of that on the given,
given gaming stream of Minecraft featuring Munchie becoming a licensed guy ever. I'll end you,
but you came later. You came after the Jesus. I came to chill, Hillary. Okay, all right, let's get
back to God. Damn it. That's what I did. Watch those live streams sometime, monkey. You will
hear the most blue-pilled man in the world. Okay, go on. Go on, Tom, please. I don't even remember
what I was talking about. I was more just like, you talked about, I guess, any specific spooky
stories or paranormal event. Like you said that you had an event the other day, and I was curious
what the incident was. Yeah, okay. So what happened the other day, and it was easy for me to just
kind of like, yeah, this is just me being dumb, but still, at the same time, your primitive brain
definitely fucks with you, is that at my job, for people who don't know, I work as a quote-unquote
security guard overnight at this abandoned mill. It's like a couple hundred years old. It's been
hollowed out for like a hundred years. There's nothing in there. Do you live in a Scooby-Doo episode?
You know, if I lived in a Scooby-Doo episode, eventually I get to the point where I take the
mask off and realize my evil boss is behind everything, but I haven't gone to that point yet.
I perpetually trapped in the middle of a Scooby-Doo episode, which I'd argue is worse.
So, in between, like every two hours, I got to go do a round. So I go around the entire building
and like make sure nobody's breaking in, because the worst thing that happens in this building is
like, you know, skateboarders come in and try and break windows or whatever. But it's overnight,
so nobody comes in. So I just basically sit there, breathe asbestos, and long for death. So
I wish I was joking. So in between like the two rounds between like 11 and 1,
half of the lights on the second floor just all went out at the same time. So when I go up there
and like I'm trying to like go through the building and I get to the part, like usually when I go
through at this point and do my round, I just I'm not even paying attention just on my phone
doing whatever and just like walking through the motions. But like I get to the point where the
lights are off and like instantly the entire energy of the building like shifted. And I knew
it was just like my brain fucking up. But it felt like there was like some presence in there.
There was like a super loud bang next to me and I looked over and nothing's there. And I'm just
like, Oh, it's fucked up. So it was it was really fucking weird. And then like, there's the worst
room in the building, the whole building leaks, and it's perpetually just like wet and soaked and
there's like moss and shit growing in there. So there's just one room that's like it leaks so
bad, it's always flooded. And like, my body like refused to go in there, just because I was getting
like super bad vibes. And I'm usually not somebody who listens to vibes. And I'm just like, you know
what, even if there is like no ghost in there, whatever, it's pitch black, and there's holes
off throughout the floor. So I don't want to fall like two floors down. So I'm just not gonna fucking
go in there. So I didn't go in there. And it was fine. And and but yeah, it was like it was it felt
like just it was like my brain playing tricks. I mean, it literally felt like there was something
like evil in there just because like my brain was going haywire. And I told my dad about and he's
like, Yeah, I've definitely had experiences. There's definitely like, there's definitely like
spirits in there fucking the shit up because like over 100 people have died in that building,
apparently. So crazy. Tom, that is the source of global warming. You found the one room where
global warming is being impetuated. You have to go there. It is it is like a perpetual warming
ghost machine. It is a perpetual greenhouse in there with like the way it's always like hot and
gross and sticky. So maybe it is maybe that is the the the bed of global warming right there.
And we need to know I feel like it'd be relevant to read another definition relevant to that story
that I didn't read at the beginning. So let me just read you the definition for ghost anal real
quick. Okay, God ghost anal happens when you are fucked in the ass by a huge dick and it leaves
you feeling like you still have a huge dick in your ass, even though the guy left about an hour
ago. And let me read just the little example here. It still feels like I'm being fucked in the ass.
Woman B, do you have a good case of ghost anal woman a no I have a job beating in 30 and it
feels like my shit is going to fall out. There you go. That's we've all been there.
My life is another quote from Titanic. Oh, you can't do this to me. It's not fair.
Just what I had it made. I hate you for this. God.
Inside of you, it's a flash of the things you've changed, while the cues are real rain.
And bright green eyes. Okay, now glowing green eyes. Oh, fuck. Okay. You're not a real fan.
You don't get to join Ember's Ghost Squad with me. Oh, yeah, you'll be in there for sure.
Okay, let's go to our next champion. Unless you have more, Tom, do you have any more stories?
No, ghosts are gay. But they're cool. I don't know. I'm conflicted.
Oh, fair enough. Give give what's the spookiest ghost story you are?
Well, the thing about ghosts and stuff is that I'm skeptical and I know that there's,
there's, you know, logical explanations for things. So when I'm in and like out in the dark,
in a spooky area, and I and I hear something and it's for it spooks me and I'm like,
but I get all excited. I'm like, okay, let's think what, what could that have actually been?
And I go through in my head like, oh, yeah, science and reason and logic and, you know,
facts and shit. And I'm professor ladies like equations flying around your head.
And I deduce like what it probably could have been like, oh, there's probably an owl like falling
over, you know. A very loud thing and owl falling over.
Well, you know, it's like something, something strange that you can easily like wave away.
Maybe the owl got scared by a ghost and fell. Oh, yeah. That's right. Yeah. So, so I'm very
into like ghostly places, but I know it's not ghosts. I just like being a little frightened.
There was this one time when I was on a goonery, which is like a week camp out in a country place.
I go there and I, and you know, sometimes at night, well, I'll just say it's, it's a scout
group for like disabled kids and I help out and I'm a volunteer. But after lights go out,
after you put all the kids to bed, you can just walk around and it's usually on a school premises,
you know, we hire out of school ground and stuff. And there was this one time it was dark,
and I went into the school building and you're not really supposed to,
but the doors open. So I'm like, shit, let's go. And I brought my brother, we went in there with
a torch and there was, you know, it was the scariest thing I've ever seen, but it was so funny
because the next day I came in and I realized what it was. There was this giant, I guess it was
like a school mascot. It's a giant ceramic gorilla wearing a school uniform. And I just went on
there. The floors, the floors were creaky. They were like renovating parts of the building. So
there was like, like those buildings where like the floor was all ripped up and there was nothing
in it. And then there was just this in the foyer. There's a big old fucking gorilla.
Fucking spooky because I thought there was something there. And I love, I love thinking,
what the fuck could that be? I really got to go in there like when it's light. And yeah,
so I like spooky, spooky places. I like being spooked. And I like thinking about it, but I don't
really say I don't really mind like people being like believing in it. I just think they're
a bit stupid. Yeah, yeah. Here in America, the only time we get spooked by gorillas is when we
go visit Compton. Oh, no, guys, I don't know if anybody saw us on Twitter. I just the last week,
I went to the zoo. They had just the day before I went, they had reopened the gorilla exhibit where
that shit went down with Harambe, literally the place where it happened. I stood there. Oh my
God, you see the ghost of Harambe running around in the water. He was, he was like, I know who did
9 11. It was like, I know who did 9 11. It was and then he fades away and you're like, who, who
wasn't Harambe? No, I'll never know. Yeah, technically that gorilla got more votes in the
last election than Bernie Sanders did. Oh, it's so sad, but it's true. Is that really true? Is that
actually true? I mean, do you think Democrats wasted their vote in the election on Bernie?
He wasn't allowed. They killed it. You can write in any name you want. You can write in any name
you want in the election. It doesn't count, I don't think, if they're not registered, but you can still do that.
Well, yeah, I guess you wouldn't think to burn. Okay, well, in any case, there's only one thing
scary than a ghost and that's a black person, fat. Yeah, you can't even see them in the dark. What is
that? What's going on there? Oh my God, imagine if there are black ghosts, dude, like twice as
I'm gonna steal my ectoplasm. I've seen what you called ghost addicts. Ghost dad, ghost dad,
ghost dad, my favorite racist. He's gonna rape you. No, he's gonna quailude the shit out of everybody.
Okay, um, he's gonna have a hung jury. I want to talk about my experience with ghosts because,
unfortunately, they have alluded to me all my life except for when I was a baby. And as we all
know, babies and ghosts don't mix because ghosts are just too sexually aggressive and babies just
don't know how to contain their raw sexual ability. And they just lead the ghosts on to the point of
absurdity. So when I was a little kid, I was just, you know, I was just running around. And then I was
just, you know, just fucking around cartwheeling all over the place, which, you know, you do kicking
the shit out of plants. And then, yeah, and then I just started screaming at the top of my of my
fucking lungs, which, you know, I'm known to do, right? I started screaming bad man and pointing
at like nothing. And so my my fucking mom came out and she was like, Hey, how's how's it going? Why
you screaming? Shut the fuck up. Get my bell. And then and she was like, Oh, man, I felt weird that
day. I could almost see God himself staring down me and telling me to leave because I knew there
was a bad man there. And then and then later, after I was told the story, I was like, You're
fucking stupid. Kill yourself. You should make you should make a hit movie called The Bad Bad Man.
And that's about yeah, that's good. And ever since then, I've liked ghosts. And so I tried to go
like I live in San Diego, and there's like a really historical famous ghost site place holy
site called the Whaley house. And this was it's supposed to be mad mad spiritual bro. You're mad
consciousness up. If you know what I mean, lol. So I went there. And I was just like, Hey, if you're
a ghost, I'm gonna fucking kill you if you don't get out here right fucking now, bro. I'm gonna
post all your nudes on Snapchat if you don't get right now, bro. You know, bro. So no ghost came
not even not even like a ghost dog was there is a ghost dog there. There's a guy who like stole a
boat. He attempted to steal a boat, but he didn't like successfully steal the boat. And he was
captured and hung for almost stealing a boat. And now he just walks around fucking with people.
And I want I wanted to see him. I wanted to see fucking the dog almost the little little children.
So I so I could whisk them away with, you know, it would be really, really, you know, great aesthetically
to those children capture a ghost like an infinite slime source available at any time that would be
really convenient for you. I mean, that's a side project. That's a pet project I'm working on right
now, where I just have a bunch of souls, not only producing more and more heat to, you know,
admit the atmosphere, but producing slime for me to drink daily. Learn the mad truths.
As I say before, I'm reverse blind. And the way I can, I can, you know, keep up my all seeing
eye and all my, you know, hide and senses if I drink a ton of slime, which, you know, I need
ghosts for. So I go around all the time hunting ghosts, not too successful lately. I think the
ghosts of, you know, they've been on the down though. I wonder what's stopping them. It's probably
the global warming. That's, you know, you know, like, like global warming is caused by ghosts,
but also harmful to ghosts. It's like, it's a lot like poetry, you know? It rhymes.
Munchy, do you know what the two scariest ghosts of all time are? The ghosts of those two kids
that Gal Gadot fucking killed. Oh, no. Where did she do that? Where did she do that?
You'll have to tell me you're the expert in this field. My favorite ghost is both the ghosts of
the Twin Towers. Those guys. They still haunt that place. If you go there and you're like,
you know, you're like hovering on a jetpack. In the Freedom Tower? Yeah. Yeah. If you're hovering
near where they were, like 70% up at the top, you can feel the concrete. You can feel it.
I know every single time, you know, if I'm ever low on ghost power and I always, you know, if I
just want to get shooed, if I just want to take the easy way out, I'll just prance along the trail
of tears and I'll just get my butterfly net out and I'll just fucking swing it all up in the air.
And I'll get that mad slime, bro. I'll get that mad slime. It'll be really funny.
I want to say, like, I'm thinking of like the way people talk about like spirituality and being
connected to the dead and how you're so dumb. They're not real. They're not real. Dead people
are never, they didn't exist. They just, they didn't exist ever. And, you know, they're talking
about that. And I'm like, I completely get it. I just use different language. Like if somebody
says, Oh, there's a guy who died there. I don't feel nothing. I do feel like, Oh, there's a guy
died here. There's a guy died right at my feet. Like, like, like 10 hundred years ago. And I'm
like, Oh, and really what it is, is that I'm feeling, I'm feeling like empathy for a human being
or sympathy or whatever it is. And that's the feeling I get. And they're talking about that
feeling being something else coming at them. Like they can't produce some external spiritual energy
and not like an internal kind of psychological reaction. Yeah. That's funny. It's funny that
when you find out somebody died, you feel like empathy or sympathy because I just feel envy.
Of course. Of course. Lucky motherfucker. Gotta do what I've always wanted. Before, before
monkey goes into his ghost story, I just want to bring up real quick. What do you guys think about
about spirit mediums of people who talk to the dead? Because I'm the greatest con artist retarded
or both, you know, to their credit, I think some of them might just be delusional. They think they
have powers. They're they're they're con artists. There we go. Oh, that's a good one. That's a good
one pending. You know that you know that Long Island spirit medium lady. I hate her so much.
She's like, everyone just fucking eats her shit. They're like, oh, yeah, you're talking to my dead
grandma. Oh, I feel so good. I feel so like cathartic that I got to talk to her. She's dead
and she's dying in hell. Thank you for letting me know. Stop. Everybody stop. It's not it's not
real replaced with a sans who just says she she's burning in hell. Don't worry about it.
Sands will be straight with you on that. Okay, so okay, mediums are shit. They're all garbage.
Okay, all mediums and psychics are just con artists. It's true. Yeah. Yeah, I yeah, they are
con artists. They're con artists and stupid, but they're aesthetically really pleasing and and
like spooky and like I always want to get my I want to go and get my magic ball read and so I
it can just be like some things will happen in your future. I can feel it. It's shit.
You know, not just just things will occur. I guarantee it. Have any of you guys gone into one
of those because like your parents were there and just like hey, let's do it. This would be fun or
like a friend or something and you go in there like and you're like you are the the stereotypical
I don't believe in this ghost stuff the whole time. Yeah, yeah. I don't know. I don't think I've
actually done that, but I've certainly felt it. I certainly thought it while I was there. I hope
they picked up my I feel like I feel that in church and ironically do you stop to go to church
I used to until until I until I broke my conditioning. Yeah, I didn't let the Zionist
control my brain anymore. I went till I was like 16 or something. I got confirmed. So
isn't it crazy that people like like when you're a child, they try to like get you wedded to the
idea so that you can't leave. You know, it's like it's the whole thing with like a thing with
if you're a Muslim and you try to leave like, you know, it's not good. They downvoted on Reddit.
Yeah, they'll shave your beard. Yeah, really close. A very close shave like
Sweeney Todd. Yeah, okay, that's I love you ghost. Monkey, tell me your spook stories.
Well, first I wanted to say about these mediums and these psychics back when I was doing a video
over a documentary called My Monkey Baby, there's a scene where a psychic she's like an animal psychic
who can talk to the woman's monkey and tell her if the monkey ate her pills and all this
I remember watching this. Yeah, so I wanted to prank call one and all the places I called,
of course, like didn't answer, like they didn't put up with my bullshit. But I looked at the prices
and they charged these motherfuckers, these con artists were charging $25 for every 15 minutes
of advice. I thought you're gonna say hour and I was gonna be like, that's not that bad, but okay,
yeah, fuck that $100 an hour to talk to these con artists. If you're if you're gonna manipulating
people, that's the career field to jump into hell. I want to go do that shit. It's just such a
parasitic thing to take advantage of people's like gullibility. It's not I think it's just
natural selection at work, though. But the problem is like because of our goddamn welfare state,
the dumb people keep living and breeding and we're going to get overrun with shitty people who
believe in Jesus. Nate, isn't it your responsibility then to believe them out of their money so
they have no choice but to die in the streets after they floundered even their state given money?
Aren't you doing God's work? But they'll get on fucking welfare and they'll drain it from the top,
they'll drain it from the earners. Okay, I'm getting on a weird political rant. Let's not
get into that shit right now. What are you saying, Gib? What's up? I was saying, I feel like it takes
a certain special type of person who does kind of believe in it to calm these people because
I can't imagine somebody who does know that it's bullshit actually making any money doing it.
Not due to guilt. No, no, no, no. I feel like you have to kind of believe it too much because the
way it is is that these people, they keep it up like so much that it's hard to imagine that they
don't believe it. They indoctrinate themselves. It makes sense to kind of condition yourself to
unbreak the conditioning. You have to be a really good actor and if you're doing that.
But they know that there's not a ghost telling them things in their ear. They're just making
shit up. So how can they have that cognitive dissonance? They're making shit up but they believe
that the thoughts that they're making in their heads are things that are being planted by spirits.
I think there are definitely people who do that. Humans are really good at tricking themselves.
I was going to say, no, I think there's both. I think there's definitely people who think
that the random thoughts that come to them during those whatever encounters are actually
the dead. But I think there are other people who are acutely aware of like, I'm fucking this person
over for $25 every 15 minutes. I feel like the ratio is more in favor of people who believe that
it's working. Because to be successful in doing that, you have to be a really good actor.
And I don't know how many good actors there are doing that.
I'm inclined to believe, Gib. I agree. I think people are really good at doing that. But even
if they don't actually believe, there's also like, they could think that like, because I've heard
some people say that they are like entertainers. And so like, they're here to like-
That's the legal defense they have to do.
I fucking hate that so much. That fucking cowardly, just admit. Just say you're a goddamn actor and
it's all a lie. Don't be like, oh, I'm an entertainer. Like, it's up to people to believe what they want.
Like that dude who wears that weird giant like blonde wig, poofy hair thing, you know that guy
who was in that H3HC video. Oh, those fucking cowards, bunch of fucking cowards.
Yeah. There's a Dateline NBC special about this where they went undercover and like,
they paid this psychically thousands of dollars for crystals and magic rocks and all this bullshit.
I can't get it on that, bro. Yeah, you should. It's the perfect job for Munch.
And of course, like for, I mean, I'm just going on a thing, but like there's the James
Randy Foundation that for like decades was offering like a one million dollar prize.
If you can just prove any of this shit's real in any way and nobody ever fucking did,
nobody took the million dollars because they fucking lying. They're all fucking liars.
Of course. What can you do?
All right. Here's my dad's ghost story. Word.
So it's a tragic story because when my brother, or I guess when my dad was 15,
his brother was fucking shot to death on the street by some, yeah, it's pretty sad.
This gang banger piece of shit. And no, I'm not just telling the story of that movie again.
Oh, that's the first thing I thought you were going to do. I'm not telling Moonlight again.
This is real life events. Okay. All right. If you say so.
So it's a year later, my dad's 16 on the one year anniversary of his brother being shot to death.
He is driving to school with his friend and they look, there's a big semi truck like behind them.
They see in the rearview mirror and they swear to God to this day, my father still believes this,
that the guy driving the truck was his dead brother. So what do they do? They're driving to
school. They turn that fucking car around and they spend the next hour and a half following
that truck trying to catch up to it when they finally do they look in the window. No, it's just
some old guy. It's just some old man. Some of my dad now thinks that it was a ghost. His brother's
ghost was driving a semi truck and I'm like, okay, dad, I'm not gonna make fun of you to your face,
but that's retarded. That's a bit silly, but yeah, you know, that seems like the kind of stuff
people believe. Yeah, it's kind of cute. I mean, both him and his friend swear they saw the brother's
face and it was the one year anniversary. So can you even blame my dad for believing this shit?
It's like too much of a coincidence that they both saw it. My dad has a story where he, you know,
he backs it up by saying, yeah, it was him and his sister, they both saw the same thing and it was
like a spooky man or something. And but at the same time, he tells that story and then at the
end he says, but it was probably just, you know, a car passing by and the light shining through
the window somewhere and going down the hallway. So he knows that it's probably not real and it's
just something, but he still likes the freakiness of it. How two people saw exactly the same thing
and thought it was this exact same thing. And then they were like, ah, so yeah. Yeah, I mean,
that does make it weird. It makes it seem very convincing if two people come to the same conclusion
about something. There are, though, I mean, just, you know, again, to beat my own dick about this
stuff because I've done a lot of reading about it. Like there are tons of things that have happened
historically. Like there are phenomenon where I think in like there was a South American village
one time where like the entire village witnessed like something happened, like the sun, like they
saw the face of God like over the surface of the sun, like everyone in the village did this the
exact same time. But like there are there are many ways to explain it besides like God exists and
decided to look at this village from the sun one time. It could have been like a sunspot or
like some sort of visual phenomenon. It also could be like the power of, you know, if everybody says
they saw something and then you feel like, well, I saw it too. Yeah, they just want to be part of the
group. Yeah, see, there's just so many problems. You have to like isolate. If you want me to
believe any of this shit people, you got to make a fucking proof and there has never been any ever.
So good luck with that. But yeah, okay, cool.
One time I was possessed by the devil. How'd that go?
Besides like continuous one that continues to this day. Right now I'm just being possessed by a
lowly ghost, but I was once at Bealzebub's court himself. I was over to like like test out my
cousin's new house that they bought a while ago. It's like, you know, you know, bash some shit in,
you know, break some windows and get it home broken as in breaking the home. And I became
like incredibly ill for no reason. And they live in the high desert. So everything's like super dry
and in like hot all the time. So I got I got I got a mad fever, a delirious fever. And I
could barely see it was all like fuzzy, like even fuzzier than if you like took off your
glasses and then like poured Clorox in your face, which I do every single day to practice my religion.
But it was it was awful. I could barely hear anything. And I slipped in and out consciousness
a ton. And you just thought, well, you know, this is probably the devil. Like that, like, you know,
I have a fever. The devil probably gave me a fever. That's probably what is occurring right now.
So I might as well be possessed. I might as well go out and just allow myself to be possessed.
So I was just like, All right, prove to me, God, if you're real, make the devil be real, too,
please. And so I like to think about like the next like out like like day, like a day was just
about how like, okay, the devil is in my head now. And he wants me to fucking kill all my friends
and family. That's what he wants. And I couldn't move or anything. So all I could do is just like
watch Isle of Lucy and like think about how the devil is commanding me to like just like fucking
get a knife and kill everyone near me and what and then watch more Isle of Lucy and Fresh Prince
of Balair and like transformers. And it was the greatest experience of my life. And after my
fear went away and the devil's subsided, the devil now like lives inside my body, but he doesn't
have full control. Every once in a while, he'll come back into my headspace. He'll become he's
one of my most prominent headmates and every every every smile to his little friend. And it's
pretty great. And I would recommend to everyone, please let the devil into your heart. This is all
I have to say on the matter. All right, well, sick dog. Let me Okay, here, let me tell you my the
only story I have. It's not me against my dad. And it's about the Holy Ghost. It's not about
Yeah. So like, have you killed your dad yet? My Well, I mean, he didn't even put in those terms.
He like my dad is a religious guy, which I continue to find baffling because he's so
wanted. Don't I don't I don't understand how anyone intelligent believes. Okay, but but like
one day while I was grill them, I'm like, dad, you got to tell me like, I don't understand why you
believe in any of this shit. You got to tell me because I'm see I'm drawing a blank here, dad.
What's the deal? It's like, okay, Nate, I've had some experiences in my life that made me think
there's some spooky shit going on. And here's here's here's here's the one that that he chose.
This was his best example. Okay, so it was he's he's with like, I believe my mom and
her sisters like my aunt don't don't remember which one. And they were hanging out and they
were like in a city somewhere. I don't know which one. And like, oh, so they're just they're back
to cross the road, right? They're just standing there, ready to cross this fucking road. And like,
like, so my my mom and her sister like start to walk across because they don't see a fucking car
coming. And then like, according to my dad, he felt something he felt a presence, warning him
specifically warning him that like something bad's about to happen. Stop them, you know,
pull them back. And he listened to it. And he grabbed them and he pulled them back. And then
like a car came by like, oh, shit, they would have died or something. That's been a bit of an
intuition. That's I mean, that was of course, I didn't challenge him because I could tell he
was you know, he's deep into the shit, unfortunately. And there's no way I could convince him just by
arguing. But like, yeah, I mean, they obviously there are plenty of other things that could have
been going on in the man's brain. I just feel like like something like that you said you could have
thought to yourself. Yeah, I'm so cool. And I have spidey senses. That's why I saved their life.
No, it was some other guy. It was just some gods. He did it. I'm not actually cool. Why do you have
to do that? Why can't you be spider man? I don't think they're not spider man. I think the only
reason the emphasis I got from it was like that it was like a voice that he heard. Like that seemed
to be like the impression I got from how he told the story. And that's why he like attributed it to
like God. And I asked him, so like, why into Christianity? Like what's, and he's like, well,
I'm not really, I mean, who the fuck knows if that shit's real. But like, I did feel like it was
like a godly presence or something. So, so that's good. Because like, why would you ever believe
that like one specific religion is true if you don't have any actual evidence for it guys? So,
you just remember guys, you happen to be in the religion that your parents are, because it's a
fucking cultural thing. You just raised that way. It's not fucking real. Break the conditioning.
Okay. Break the conditioning. The whole like hearing voices in the head thing. I think a lot
of people who say they hear voices hear a voice, which is them with that, which is that in a monologue.
And the only reason they say the words out loud in their head is because they've read that people
hear voices and that's what they think God is. So they, when they, when they have an intuition
and they think, I should probably change this, they think to themselves, you should stop doing
that. I'm God. And they're like, Oh my God, God's speaking to me, but it's just them. But they just
put the voice in their head because they think that's what a voice, you know, that's what's
supposed to happen. I'm telling you, man, it's that it's that human, like we humans have an
incredible capacity for pattern recognition and like anthropomorphization. I love thinking about
it. I love thinking about why people do it. I love thinking about ghosts. I love thinking about
spooky shit. I love it all. It's so cool. I don't even hate it. I don't even think it's stupid.
It's great. Can the thumbnail for this, can the thumbnail for this episode be Danny Phantom
tipping his fedora? If such an image exists. No, hippos are going to draw it for us.
Yeah, I will draw it by copy pasting a fedora onto an image of Danny Phantom.
That sounds perfect. That sounds perfect. If we're talking about our parents now,
my mother is a goldmine of gullible actions and insanities. You convinced her to let you go to
fucking Brony Connellone when you were like 12. Absolutely delusional. You know, completely out
of her mind. I'm sure she's just putty in your hands. Oh, you know it, bro. I have those mad
manipulation skills, bro. I'm mad. Absolutely mad. I can imagine now. Mom, where are my tendies,
mom? Where's my slime? Where's my ecto coolers? Okay, go on. Go on. Where's my fucking juice?
My soup, my correspondence. Where's my crystals? I need them to do a baptism over the internet, mom.
I'm going to a J.O. sesh right now, mom. I need my crystals. Okay. Okay. Anyway, tell us the tale.
So we never, she's never been that religious. She grew up religious, but it's not that she
doesn't, you know, she isn't the religious herself. She's just too lazy to convince me to be one.
That's good. That's preferred. So we go to church a little bit, but you know, not too often,
mostly just for each certain, you know, big events. But anyway, she had a sort of like,
like second wave, you know, like second wind, like, oh, I'm going to, I'm going to be religious
again. It's going to be really, really going to be it like a couple of years ago. And instead of
just like getting back into like a church, she started researching online for like, what is Jesus
really? What is like real Jesus? Okay. All right. All right. She's breaking the conditioning a
little bit. Yeah. Oh, dude, the conditioning is fucking shattered by the point, by the end of the
story. That's not existent anyway. So she, so she finds out like all the, the, the mysticism,
the, the, the modern mysticism, you know, like you're, I'm talking, you know, you got your
cosmic beings of light powers. You got your, you know, church of euthanasia. You got your fucking,
you know, uh, what's that guy's name? Something, something Apple white. You got those kind of
people. You got that one, uh, uh, Colton, Colton Tokyo that tried to, you know, raise the sarin
gas on the bus. That kind of shit. You know, uh, like, like crystals and all that kind of stuff,
which is where like, I was, you know, I had known about that culture, but from my mom,
you know, starting to practice, I really got like a taste for it. And I realized it was my
favorite thing in the entire world. Oh, okay. Okay. And I, you know, I, I love crystals and I
love chakras. They're my favorite. Let me find spirit science. My greatest discovery of all time.
Yep. And the rest is history, but from her, uh, she created a sort of like monument to Jesus,
but not like, when you like, not like Jesus, Jesus, more like, like slime, like ghost Jesus,
like, like the soup, like super Jesus, basically. Right. And it was, it was basically just like a
bunch of J pegs of Jesus, like super cross posterized. So it's just like fucking undecipherable.
And a ton, like, like it was just like neon green, uh, cardboard, like slab, I guess,
with a ton of J pegs of Jesus, you know, pasted on. And just some like, um, if you believe hard
enough, Jesus is real. And, uh, and, and, and like fucking like in like Microsoft word, like,
like word art, like change it to like make it look cool. Your mother is a master of aesthetics,
dude. This sounds amazing. Okay. Okay. It's incredible. And just a, just a ton of crosses,
but like most of them are broken and they had, and she had to glue them back together.
And, uh, it's just, it's a bunch of like literal just rocks, but like somewhat,
somewhat sparkly if you put them in the right light. Uh, and yeah, just a ton of shit like that.
And she hung it like over her wall. Uh, and the way the house is positioned, she hung it like,
her door would always be open and like you could like see, trust me when you say, uh,
every time I go to the kitchen, I had to look at that fucking poster of Jesus. Okay. Uh, you know,
Jesus, just, just believe hard enough and Jesus is real. Jesus is magic. You are magic. And if,
and if you just fucking align your chakras and go vegan, then you'll be able to see the spirits.
You'll, you'll be able to see in 4D, bro. You'll be able to get all four dimensions. Yes. Yes.
And she was super into it. And she, and she kept, when, uh, when we visited Denver a while ago
to visit family, she was like, you know, this is pretty good, you know, being with family,
but, but I buy the seminar I need to go to and, you know, you just hang out, just hang out around
Denver while I go to this, this cool ass seminar where they, the Dalai Lama, you know, jacks off
all over me and I'm able to find, I'll be able to speak, I'll be able to speak to Nazis in their
sleep. I'll be able, I'll be able to find out where Hitler stashed his fucking ghoul and where,
and where, and where Hitler's like personal fitness trainer, like, like, like, got all the
crosses in the nation together and made like one supercross. And I'll be able, I'll be able to
know everything, bro. I'll be able to, I'll be able to personally fund global warming myself.
I'll be that ghost powerful. And, uh, she did it. And this continued for a while until I was just
like, uh, you know, you should probably, you know, that's not really a good idea. I don't think.
So she went to like a bunch of seminars or was just one? Yeah. Okay. No, a bunch. Like, yeah. Well,
by a bunch, I mean, like, one time my mom went to a Harry Potter seminar in Canada. That was pretty
cool. Yeah, by yourself, by yourself. I mean, I mean, I mean, that's going to give her mad
spirituality. No doubt, dog. Which isn't shit, bro. Yeah. Shit's crazy. But, uh, yeah, eventually
she kind of tapered off because, uh, she, she, she read something like one of like the leaders
she was like listening to about spirituality had like raped like 70 children. Yes. Yes. Yeah.
He's got to absorb that ectoplasm from him. He's got to do it, dude. Ghost should leave
it inside children's testicles. He just needs to get inside, bro. And, uh, okay. And, and she was
like, uh, well, you know, I guess it's still, it's still like real, but I, you know, I might get
focused on other stuff. Yeah. Anyway, great. Thank you, mother, for allowing me to understand
spirit science, the only thing that matters in the world, and align my chakras to such
decent that I have. But dude, if you think my Christ consciousness is like high, her talk was
or so fucking bliss that it was hard to even look at her. She was just like a glowing, a glowing
white fucking like spectacle to observe. Fuck, yes. To the level like eight, bro, like level eight.
Holy shit. All right. Well, you got to get her on one day to really weigh in on this shit. Yeah.
When, when we start our long awaited, uh, spirit science analysis series, uh, you know, we'll
get the expert in. Well, that's, that's dope. Um, yeah, it's great. Well, shit team. Uh, well,
can we come to any conclusions here? What, what have we learned here today? The parts of the
Caribbean, the first movie with a heart ghost is really good because they also skeletons, but
I was about to say, they're skeletons and ghosts. They're not even ghosts. They're not even dead
for real. They're all dead. They're just they're cursed. They're not even full skeletons. They're
barely even. We're all full skeletons on the inside. That's true. They're fake fans, if you will.
They're fake fans of being a ghost, not of like fans of the idea of being a ghost, but they are
fake fans of like being a ghost that they are a ghost. Right. Okay. Yeah. All right, boys. My
belief ghost of all time. Oh, Moaning Myrtle. Wait, did you say worst? Worst. Yeah. Moaning
Myrtle. Worst ghost of all time. She's pretty bad. I mean, I was never, I was never too oppressed by
Casper's. All right. You know, he was plucky. He was adventurous. Yeah. Friendly punk ass bitch.
He didn't tell me where all, he didn't tell me where all the gold was.
He wasn't a 40 year old woman pretending to be jailbait floating around a girl's locker room,
for sure. Well, that's why I like Moaning Myrtle. You know, I know, I gotta say, I've never been a
fan of nearly headless Nick. Like, okay, he's a nice guy, but like, I'm never going to get over
the fact that he got cucked out of the whole headless thing. He's just he'll never, he'll never
be a full headless boy. He will never achieve that. But yeah, I'll always make him the worst.
Because he sucks because he can't even do it right. He can't do anything right. Instead of
tipping his hat, he tips his whole fucking head. It's amazing. You could do that if you were headless
to him though. He's played by John Cleese, the famous John Cleese. Yeah, he was in Rat Race.
I love Rat Race. And nothing else. Rat Race is my favorite movie. Me too, dude. We should listen.
Give me your Rat Race episode. We absolutely have to. I love Rat Race. It was my favorite movie
growing up. Yeah, me too. Well, that's what we learned, guys. Rat Race is the greatest movie
ever made. It's the best movie. It's so good. I think my favorite ghost is myself in the future,
when I become a ghost, which will happen. Oh, wait, wait. I have the worst ghost. Arania
Circuit? What have you said? Oh, Arania Circuit? It might actually be Arania. Okay, whatever.
We know the one. Spider bitch number two, right? Yes. Yeah. I mean, she was hot. She was really
sexual and Jake should have fucked her. I don't know. There was something wrong with her. There's
something wrong. I don't know what it was. I mean, what was wrong about her was that she turned
into like this evil psycho for no reason. Yeah, but even before that, she was just sort of like,
I'm so smart. I'm so smart. All of the dancers are the worst character ever made. That's not true.
Every single one. Mina sucks. Wait, wait. Who's a good one? No, Mina's all right. No, Mina's the
literally the best character. You take that back, you piece of shit. She sucks. She sucks shit.
She is only number two to Roxy in terms of girls and homestuck. She's great. She's fantastic. I love
her. Dude, just because you're a race trader doesn't mean we're all race traders, Nate.
Look, just because Vriska couldn't hack it and got blown the fuck out by how badass Mina was,
and Vriska was like, no, why don't you love me? I'm just going to pretend I'm as cool as you,
Mina. God, that was so pathetic. Vriska trying to be cool like Mina all along. Fuck you, Vriska.
Do you remember when Andrew Hussey got literally cucked in Canon and he watched them have sex
and wasn't literally cucked? I do remember that in general. That was great. Upvote.
We should probably stop talking about stuff that Monkey and Tom have no idea what it is.
Yeah, you're right. Okay, let's go to our questions here. All right, it's time for questions.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Before the questions, I got a bit. Go for it.
We did a very official Twitter poll who is the worst PCP member and we've got the full results.
How many votes? How many votes did we get? Man, I didn't even get to vote.
We got 850 votes total. Okay, pretty good. That's pretty good. Should I go in order from
most hated to least hated or least hated to most hate? I mean, let's go from least hated
and then go all the way up to our winner, the most hated member. Okay, so with 16 votes,
the least hated PCP member is Hippo. Hey, what do you know? Who are those 16 people?
I'll kill them. That's an easy amount of people to kill. 16, I can do that. Those are all my alt
accounts. I'll turn them into ghosts. Okay, keep going. Who's next? Next we have with 21 votes,
Mr. Best Guy Ever. Yeah, all right. Yeah, I'm actually shocked. I'm actually shocked by that
because I talk so much. You just think that's a lot of material for people to hate me with,
but hey, thanks guys. Appreciate it. Then we have Mage at 55 votes. I guess they don't like
women because there's nothing to hate about Mage. Those are the 55 misogynists in our audience.
Yeah, okay. Oh, there's a small number. I know, pretty good, pretty good. At 73 votes, we have
Mr. Tom Oliver. Yeah, I'm an easy hate. So you might have noticed, most of the least hated people
are on this podcast and I have a feeling the other two participants might be on the other end of the
list. Let's find out. All righty. I think this is, it's like sixth place, whatever. It's Digibro
at 73 votes. Digibro and Tom are tied at 73 votes. Oh, really? Oh, shit. What do you know?
Their destined bond continues to this day. It's true. All right, the fifth most hated member
is Endless Jess at 85. You know, Jess was leading that poll for a while, so all things
considered, I think he came out pretty, pretty well, pretty well. Good job, Jesse. We have
Davout at 92 votes. What can you hate about Davout? These are all, so far, those are all
people with less than 100. Now we go to the people with the big votes, baby. I'm ready,
I'm ready. Lay it on me. Tied for second place at 133 votes each is both Mr. Ben Saint and Mr.
Munchy. Our union continues to this day. Our spicy bro pack. I was really sad. I was really
sad Ben didn't win this one. I was really rooting for Ben. I voted for Ben on all my devices that
I could. I really did. I really did. And the undisputed most hated PCP member with 163 votes
is Munchy Jones. I did it. I won. I'm so proud of this accomplishment. Is he just gone?
You totally cut out there. Just repeat that whole thing. Well, they all heard it, but it's me,
Munchy Jones, I won. Yeah, Munchy Jones did it. Way to go. You are. What our audience didn't
realize with that poll is that you're not allowed to hate any of us, so you're all dead. We're
going to kill you all. You're all turning into ghosts. You're all banned. You're all going
ghost. We should have done the second poll so we'd have the other results. Maybe this week
we'll do the opposite poll and see how that goes. That's good. Wait, wait, wait. Before we go to
questions, Ghostbusters 2 is my favorite movie of all time besides the other ones that I like a lot.
For a lot of reasons. Number one, Slimers there. Number two, there's a sea of slime. There's like
a ton of slime. Number three, they use slime to control the Statue of Liberty, much like how I
use my influences with slime to destroy and dismantle local government and slowly take over
the country. And control women. Yeah, and control women and blacks and whites, especially white
people. And, you know, I just control everyone with my intense charisma, my intense slime based
charisma. Dude, dude, fucking the Power Rangers first movie has so much slime in it. It was the
big giant slime man. Dude, I would probably love that. I would probably love that. No, you should
definitely watch that. Slime controls people and it's great. It wasn't slime though, it was ooze.
Our close allies at the very least. Yeah. By the way guys, if you smash centipedes,
then you'll get like a couple EXP and you'll get mad slime. So fresh all the centipedes you can.
Reach into your spine and then tear out the centipedes. Control on your thoughts. Oh no.
Oh God, don't. Don't pull out that Toblerone folks. Leave it alone in there. And Ghostbusters 2
is also good because like a baby almost dies. Fantastic. Yes. All right, let's go to our questions.
All right, here we go everybody. Here's number one at Adamualpha asks thoughts on crystal Pepsi.
Did you try it? Did you like it? Are you a fan of the concept of clear cola in general? Love
how specific this one is. This is a great question. He's really obsessed with crystal Pepsi. He
loves this disgust. I love the idea of crystal Pepsi of cola that is clear. I think it's the
coolest thing in the world. Isn't that what's seven up in sprite art? Well, those aren't cola. Those
are like fruit drinks instead, you know. Oh, okay. I've never tried crystal Pepsi, but I would love
to. Does it have a different flavor or is it the same thing? It's got to taste different, right?
Have any of us actually tried this? Has anyone tried crystal Pepsi? I have not. None of us have.
Wait, wait. I haven't tried it, but I would say to this person who asked this question,
check out the Examined Life of Gaming YouTube channel. He makes reviews of sodas. He's called
the new do review. I think he tried crystal Pepsi in a recent video, like it was a new thing.
And he tried it and he reviewed it. He reviewed sodas and video games and you might like what he
has to say. Pretty great. Fantastic. He's got a place to go for his crystal Pepsi fandom.
All right. Well, I have never tried crystal Pepsi. I have about, you know, I would say about 48 bottles
here all blessed by a priest. So they're holy holy water. Is this what you use instead of actual
crystals? Because you can't afford them? Yeah. Yeah, I can't afford the actual crystals. They're
too hard to mine from Africa and I don't want to wind up dead in a ditch trying to get them. So I'm
as old, you know, there's a body tone of crystal Pepsi. I mean, it has crystal in the name. So,
you know, it's probably the same properties. Yeah. So I just pour that all over my body
when I'm trying to get an extra boost. It's good plan. Good plan. Yeah. Okay, here we go.
Questions from the world's greatest procrastinators fan artist, Ms. At Jane Moreau asks, do you guys
like camping? It's Jane Moreau, yeah. What did I say? Did I say J? You said Jane. I said
why would I say Jane? Oh, I fucked. Okay, I'm sorry, Jade. I love your work, Jade. At Jane Moreau
says, do you guys like camping slash hiking? Who's who's a camp guy? No, are we all city boys? We
all city slickers here. I have camped. I have camped a couple times. Quite a few times in a tent
and shit. And I do love, I do love a big old, if I see a hill and I got some shoes and they're not
wet shoes and they're like good walking shoes, I will climb all the way to the top of that hill
and then all the way back down and be like, oh, I don't know why I did that, but I like it. So I
love hiking. It's fun because I just, you know, it's good. So I guess I do like it. Yeah, I don't
mind going for a nice little nature hike or to go exploring, but there's no excuse to ever
sleep anywhere other than my comfy bed. Why would I want to sleep outside in the dirt?
It's pretty not good, but I appreciate the feeling of waking up in really early two to the
birdsong and the cold air and it's like, oh yeah, yeah, early man. I'm like coming out of my cave
and with my sticks and stones, I'm gonna build my life. Let me tell you guys, I was in the Boy Scouts
for a thousand years, Eagle Scout represent, and I did a thousand camping trips, did a thousand hikes,
mountain climbing, skiing, all that kind of shit. I love camping. I think camping is super
fucking fun. The only thing that's kind of a pain is you kind of got to like put time aside for it,
but I mean, I'll take any excuse I can get to get out of nature because I just don't
experience it whatsoever. I fucking love going camping and sleeping in there. I mean, I'm a guy
who can sleep anywhere pretty comfortably. So like the whole sleeping thing is never a problem for me.
I don't mind the kind of fucking bugs. I don't mind. I like sitting on my tent. I like cooking
outdoors on my grill. I fucking love everything about it. I haven't done all that sort of like
intense like doing everything yourself sort of thing because when I go camping, it's like with
a big camp troop. Like I said, that's the agunary thing I was talking about. They have a kitchen
tent and they make breakfast for everyone and you have patrol tents and stuff. When you just sit
down, you can just play with a Rubik's Cube while you wait for the next activity or something,
but like literally going on a quest into the wilderness and living off like a can of beans.
I'm not sure I could do that, but I do that without going into the woods. I'm the bean boy. Yeah. Okay.
Well, when I was a little kid for like school, you had to like go on a camping trip like that was
like there was like a camping trip a week that everyone went to a camp. And one of the many
misadventures I had, the most interesting one was I, there was like a sculpture class where you
got like a rock and you were supposed to mold it into something. I got a twig, I got some tape,
and I just made a hammer and I threatened to kill anyone who looked at me. Well, that's sick dog.
Let's go to Jade's other question here. Hair goals. She simply states hair goals. Question
mark in one word. Who's got hair goals? Gabe, do you have any hair? You're a hair guy. What are your
goals? I have hair on my head. I, my goals are to keep it long until it starts thinning too much
and then shaving it all off because I don't want to be like a bolding guy. I just want to go straight
from having long hair to being bold. I don't want to go through that. That's going to be a big change.
That's going to be a transformation. Yeah. And then when I'm like got no hair, I'm going to grow my
beard out. So I'm going to be like opposite. I'm going to have a big beard, big bushy beard.
And that's going to be like my hair just, you know, swelled round. That's what happened. It's
like, it's like a 3D model that just sort of glitched out the hair bit. When Gib gets older,
losing his hair, he like a 3D model. Okay, that's enough of that. Yeah, that's a good song.
He'll become Heisenberg. Yeah. Anyone else have hair goals? I got none. I'm just going to do
exactly what I'm doing. It's fine. I don't care. I want to get better facial hair. I've tried
product. It doesn't work. My face is perpetually broken and it really pisses me off every time I
see Gib's glorious beard. I just want to like cut it off and tape it on my face and pretend
that's the best I'll ever get. It sucks. I hate it. I totally forgot about that. But yeah,
I can't grow a decent beard. So one day when I'm an old ass man, I want a big Dumbledore beard.
That'd be sick. I want that now. If I could go full Gandalf now, I would like not even. I could
potentially get a Dumbledore beard. Oh my God. Hey, you. Yeah. One of those 16 people who voted
it was me. It was me. I voted because you had the beard.
And like if we get soup in it and twigs and it'd be horrible, horrible.
Fuck you. I want to look exactly like Steven Sugar besides the beard part.
Is that Rebecca Sugar's husband? Yeah. Brother, but close enough. Basically the same.
They had the same sort of leadership. Hey, I've got a question
from at Bottle Cape. And I really wish Jess was here because he has the best answer,
but we'll do it without him. What do you think of your audiences and what do you think of each
other's? Uh oh. Well, I think my audience, the give and take audiences like that, they're nice
people that, you know, I like them. They're good. They're nice and the hypocrite audiences like people
who they don't really know anything, but they're not dumb, but they're just sort of like oblivious
to the internet as a whole. And I'm like, well, you know, you stumbled upon this because you're,
you know, the YouTube algorithm gave you my video because you're English and you also clicked on it
because it's like something you know. So I got a lot of English fans who don't really know the
internet very well. But yeah, they're cool. You got a lot of, you got a lot of like Mary Poppins
who were like, oh, what's this computer box? I'll try to click on it and watch the game reviews.
Oh, these are some silly children. Yeah, exactly true. Yes. If you look at your demographics,
it's like male, female, and then Mary Poppins is a third part of that. Yeah, epic joke. Okay.
Let me see. Monkey, your audience is full of misogynistic, racist, bigoted pieces of shit.
They're the worst people because they follow their leader. They know what you want and they
follow suit you. You did this, you're bad. If anybody here has an audience full of leader
followers, it's literally everybody but me. You think so? I click on any of your guys' videos.
It's an 80% like ratio to the views. That's true. Every comment is, oh, man, I love you. I can't
wait to buy one of your fucking stupid mugs even though the month was over. Oh, you go to my channel.
It's like almost no likes. It's probably 20% likes for the views. And every fucking top comment is,
hey, monkey, fuck you. Hey, monkey, this video is fucking shit. Yeah, I know. I mean, I encourage it,
but I'm not going to say that they're following the leader as opposed to your fucking,
your drones and your audience is over there. Your audience is, they suck your dick way too hard.
I don't get it. The thing with my audience, it's developing a bit like Jesse's where like,
the only thing I do is shit on them and tell them that they're gay. But I also
give them like life advice. So they, it's like a, it's like a push pull going on there.
And I think it makes, it endears myself to them, you know? I think there's some of that going on,
which is good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And I feel the same way about myself. Like when I see someone
who's got really great content, I'm like, yeah, I'm on board with this guy. I want to be like them.
Of course, I mostly overdoing that because I've been on YouTube for a while now. And
like that's that was with John Tron. And then, oh boy, then it turns out he's a goddamn bigot,
a goddamn racist. And no, I'll, all that matters is that his content's boring. That's the only
guy. Have you guys seen the rumors that he's working at Bed Bath and Beyond now?
That can't be true. What? He keeps posting pictures of products at Bed Bath and Beyond,
but he's behind the register. I'm going to go check this out. I don't believe that. He's got
three million subscribers for fuck's sake. All he has to do is just make good. That would be
unfortunate, but also rent is very expensive in New York. I was about to think like, oh,
that's funny. He's fallen on hard times. Wait, that's kind of sad. That is kind of sad. I don't
believe it. I don't, I do not believe it. How is he making money, Tom? He hasn't made a video in
three months. Okay, I was, I was actually looking this up the other day.
I heard he makes like, I heard he makes like $25,000 per video. That might be a totally made up
number, but like, he does a lot of like ad stuff and sponsorship, and he gets paid a substantial
amount per video that he does, as I understand it. I mean, that's made up number, so. I hate talking
about Jon Tron, fuck that guy, he's gay. Yeah, I mean, really, the only thing I care about is he
doesn't make good content anymore, so I don't care. So fuck that guy. My, my audience to go back to
that is like small and cult like and very devout and very like superstitious and easily manipulated
and just you're describing half of the PCP audience. I mean, there's a lot of overlap there,
you know, a lot of overlap. Yeah, when they say there's a new arm retrieval, they're like,
yes! Oh my fucking god. It's time. That's been like unironically like that. For a while now,
so I hope they're happy. I am unironically one of those types. For red matter media.
That's dude, I'm the biggest red matter media fan in the world. Yeah, it's pretty great. I love
them all. They're a little bit too meme-y for my taste, which may sound funny, but you know, I'm
not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm, I, contrary to popular belief, I'm not the biggest meme guy. I think,
I think they're fine, but I'm not, I'm not the biggest meme guy. Hillary, I love you.
Not Hillary. No. Uh, Momke, can you, I'm sorry, Munchy, can you just do me a favor? Can you give
us a quick average value? You know, don't acknowledge it. Uh, if you, what, what, what would you say is
the average Christ consciousness of your audience, you know, as, as a whole, what would you put that
pretty low, pretty low? No, they got some work to do. One or two. Okay. Okay. So maybe, you know,
like level one or two. Yeah. Uh, there's probably like a few fours in there. All right, you guys,
like, like a, you know, high five to a low six. Okay, good. All right, not bad. Well, cool. Um,
how about you, Tom? What do you think about your audience?
Mm hmm. Yeah, they got pretty mad at you. Hey,
hey.
Ah, yeah.
Mm hmm. That seems to be the way to go.
I'm, I'm just gonna be more potent, Tom. You're not potent.
You know, I've really been thinking about it and I've come to the conclusion that, um,
what's the benevolent fuck? What is it? It's like the benevolent dictator is really the best kind
of system of government you can hope for. And I've elected myself to this office. So I'm going to
use my, yeah, that's of course, of course. So I'm going to use my, my objectively best ideas
and create a cult like falling around myself and, and make and indoctrinate them with the best ideas.
They'll just be sheep, you know, they'll just be doing exactly what I tell them,
but little do they know I have their best interests in mind as well as the world.
And that's how it's going to go. And it's going to work out great.
I don't really want to get into a big thing, but every time I see like people saying you're like
literally like God and then like this into Jesse. Well, you know, like similar sort of things. I'm
like, why don't people do that to me? And then I see on my videos, they do kind of do that to me.
And I just realized that I look at other people's comments on their videos more than I look at my
own because I don't make any fucking videos. Yeah, you know, that's why I don't have like a fan base.
I have like a couple of people who are PCP fans on their occasion. They're like, Oh yeah, Gibb's cool.
Yeah, I like Gibb's stuff. And then, you know, they go back to not having watched any of my videos
because there are none. Yeah. Oh, okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It's it's kind of the kind of great kind of great people make PCP fan art, you know,
it's time. It's time to put the money where your dig is draw the shit. I think I think I think Tom needs
to Tom needs to be like in a in one of the many double podcasts that we have. We need we need a Tom
plus a one podcast. Me and Tom are going to do a depression suicide podcast. That's a good one.
That's a good one. Oh, by the way, before we get away from the topic, I just wanted to say that
about the whole like your audience really giving a shit, like I think that's a consequence of like
the audience reacts with strong emotions, too strong emotions like shown in the video. And I'm
a big like shouty boy and and like you're you're less of that. So like I'm a subtle boy. I love
your content, but I just think it's kind of like the nature of like people like, yeah,
oh, this guy's yelling, I want to yell my money right into his wallet. You know, that's that's
that's the way you can do like there's I it's working for me. Jesse was always like a big
passion guy and people got really passionate into his stuff. And like did did you was more of like
just like an absurdly prolific guy and people just like felt immersed in his content that like
achieves a similar sort of effect. And you know, if you could find you can do one of those and
I think it's a good way to go. And I and I'm sort of a chuckle boy, they come to me, they just
chuckle, they just type haha. And they leave. I think another thing more content. Another thing
to think about also is that like I'm a die hard red letter media fan, but I have never in my life
commented on one of their videos. So I mean, I think for every good commenter you get, there's
probably 20 people who love you just as much, if not more so, but they just they just don't
comment because they don't care about typing shit out. You know, I comment on like videos with
low numbers of comments, I guess, because I feel like I don't know that it matters more, I guess.
Like I've yeah, I also just I'm realizing I've never commented on one of their videos, even though
I consume everything they make because they're fucking love it so much. And yeah, that's interesting.
I have bought a bunch of their merch though, which I think is telling I was willing to spend money
on their shit. That's true. I think about that, like I wouldn't comment on one of their videos
because I don't expect them to read the comments at all. Yeah, yeah. So I don't think they would
ever get anything out of what I would put down. So I don't I mean, that's why I don't leave comments
in general. But when it's like, you know, one of you and I feel like, well, I could say this on
on discord or whatever, but it would make sense for it to be in public so people could see what
I'm saying as well. Yeah, I put a comment on there because I know that you would read it.
So I don't know. That makes sense.
Oh, yeah. Oh, that's nice. Comments are cool. The only comments I like are when Nate comments
on my Yu-Gi-Oh series. Otherwise, I don't give a shit. Monkey, you forgot you were distracted
from the tits. You have to go back. I commented like every day for like two weeks about that shit.
By the way, I want to real quick here encourage, you know, fan arts great. It's fine. It's I
like it a lot. But if you make songs or something, fan songs is greater than fan art objectively.
Most of the time. Most of the time. Sure. Sure. It's cool. I love that shit. I make them.
So yeah, fan songs are great. Any sort of fan project art is great. You don't have to just
be an art guy. If you anything you can offer is great. Anything that you can alter to the
alter of Munchie. You know those ring far like to worship me. I will appreciate those PCP
openings that those guys are making the anime openings for the PCP that were a big while back.
Those are great. Yeah. You know what? We don't have like a remix of our ending theme of the PCP.
Well, other than the ones you make, I'm supposed to be crapping my pants, you know, those.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's right. I forgot about that. Yeah. Somebody made like a I remember now
like an orchestrated version. It was great. It was good. It was good. It was uploaded by me on Reddit.
Well, I certainly would have if I had been aware of it. I don't know. We should check though.
That's true. Okay, let's go to let's go to some other questions here. Okay, here's one from
at strange CIG asks, why is Ben St. still alive? I don't know, dude. I've been worrying. I've been
wondering about that question for a long time. I've been worrying about that fact for a while.
Yeah. Wasn't that our $2,000 Patreon goal was kill Ben?
That's yeah, he's like a starfish. You break Ben in half, you just get two more Ben. So,
you know, I don't really know if we want to go down that road. He's trucking along,
bro. He's trucking along. He's trucking along. He's trucking. Oh my god. It'll be out by now,
but apparently the word on the street is a week ago when this comes out, the new fucking Nuzloc
ending to his genocide run is going to be out tomorrow for when we're recording this. I've
been waiting for it. I'm the biggest fan of that in the world. I can't fucking wait. Then he could
die. Then he could die. Imagine if that comes out and it's just like a HD remake of the first
Nuzloc you did. Like the back video. Gotcha. Yeah. That would be very interesting.
Well, I know that it's not because I'm a guest star on the episode. Oh man, I'm so excited.
Very hype. Ben and I had talked a bunch about it because I'd been like, oh, Ben,
I want you to do this. I want you to do this on the fucking thing. I've been being a creepy fan
of that Nuzloc. Okay. Okay. Here's the last question. We got one more from our good buddy,
the deadmine on Exilevich asks, oh shit, what are some of the worst jobs you've ever had? I know
some of Tom's. I don't want to Tom's. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Fair point.
Well, I am in between leaving school and going to uni. I had a year where I didn't know what
the fuck I was going to do. And I was just depressed. And I was forced to work volunteer work
to buy the government because that's how you get
because you're unemployed or whatever. And I had to sign an online form to like tell you people
sign up for this shit, idiot. I was a young boy. I still am really, but I typed in the wrong
county and well, not county, just sort of the wrong sort of area, the wrong town.
And they sent the forum online. Then they sent me because I typed the wrong town,
the commute was like a two hour bus drive all the way. Yeah, I told it before.
And working in that place, it was like a charity shop. And I had to like work in the back,
shoveling shit and deciding what the bags of trash that people send in, you got to
sift through it and find stuff and sort it out. And you know, that was boring. But that was at
least work. A lot of the time I was told to man the store, which meant just standing in the store,
there were no seats, there wasn't a seat behind the register. So I just had to just walk around and
sort of lie on the floor occasionally because my legs hurt. Yeah, I've been there. And I did that
for hours and I didn't like it and I didn't get paid and I ran away at one point. You don't get
paid for that at work? It was like the law was like, if you want job seekers allowance, if you
want grants for not having a job and you're looking for a job, you have to do a minimum of a
certain like, like three, four days of volunteer work a week. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. So it was, it was, it was my first real experience of like a nine to five. And it was
so boring just standing in that shop because nobody really came in. And I didn't really sell
anything. I was just sort of waiting, you know, waiting to die. I was glad when I just didn't
come in and broke the rules. Way to go, dude. Excellent. My hardest job that I ever worked was
not going, was never not having, I'd never had a job before. That was the hardest job I've ever done.
A wee lad, a wee lad. When the hell put you to work, boy? I'll put that butt to work. Oh no, dad, don't
get out your belt. Munchies. Munchie, for you. Specifically, since you're a school man, did you,
did you ever have like a terrible homework that you just hated so much?
Literally every single homework. Homework is the work, I would rather go to school all day. Like,
like for like, for like 12 hour school days than do a single piece of homework.
Okay, just imagine being, yeah, the homework is fucking retarded. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. I used to try, I used to try like when I first got into secondary school, I used to try
thinking, all right, I got to get on top of this homework. I hated homework all through primary
school. This time, I'm going to do the homework before I come, before I walk home, because I
walked home every day. And so, you know, the first few days I managed to do the stupid homework,
which is draw a page and do some words. And then I drew that and wrote some shit. And then I went
home and then, you know, obviously homework gets more and more and more and more. And I was like,
yeah. It just sort of became impossible to do it before I went home, because it would have been
like, oh yeah, just stay at school for two hours and have no friends. You know, I, yeah, I hear
you. I've had some shitty jobs myself over the years. I worked at Best Buy for a while. That
wasn't like that bad, but it was like retail and I hate, I fucking hate pushing things on people,
not downvoted. I worked at several pizza places. I worked at Papa Geno's, which is like a chain in
Massachusetts and like the Northeast region. Oh yeah. Nothing beats Papa Geno's besides an all-out
race war. I'm actually, I love Papa Geno's pizza. God, I would kill for some. It's so thin. It's
the thin. It's delicious. Okay. I know, I know. Gibbs is very concerned about that. I worked at
another pizza place that was like a mom and pop one that was, it was okay. It was kind of shitty.
I worked a bunch of like temp jobs, like after I, you know, the last like four years when I was
like doing stuff, when I was doing pony stuff, I worked at like, just like a temp agency being hired
for various jobs. It was never very good at them. Oh, it was all garbage. Did you demand they call
you keg? Of course. Okay. I'll just wrap up my point. I just wanted to say that like about my
current job. So my current job is not like the worst job in terms of like the hardest or I don't
know any of that shit, but like what makes it a unique challenge is like it's a real, it's a real
job. Like I'm a member of a team working on shit and like there are expectations of me. So like
when there's work to be done, it has to get done. Nothing else matters. Like there is no excuses to
like not do your shit. If you got to spend an entire weekend working on something to get it
fucking working for the Monday morning meeting, that's how you're spending your weekend now.
And that's exactly what I have to do this weekend and is what I will be doing as soon as we're done
fucking recordings. I have to fucking finish this program. It probably won't even be used in the end,
but I literally, that's what I'm getting. Yeah, that's like part of what I get paid for though,
that like I'm basically on call that I have to just do whatever. It doesn't happen most of the
time, but sometimes it does. And when it does, it's the worst and interferes with the things I
actually want to be doing with my life. But okay, whatever. That's enough of that.
Let me just quit your job and don't get on Patreon either. Just go away.
I'll just die. Yeah, patreon.com slash best guy ever. People set me free. Okay. Next is
what we say in time. What was your horrific nightmare job?
Hmm. Yeah, yeah.
That's cool. Yeah.
Oh, Lord.
Mm-hmm.
Cool.
Oh, at that point, tell them to fuck off. Yeah, that's too much. So how long did you do it for?
Just two weeks.
What the fuck?
These people didn't know what the fuck they're doing.
Yeah, that's uh, what the fuck? Okay. Well, cool. Dope.
Well, I didn't monkey have anything to say. No, he didn't.
The worst job I've ever had is, um, once every week or two, I get on this fucking podcast full
of these autistic little faggots. And I, I, I pretend to put up with their stupid bullshit
for like an hour and a half and then I get paid like what 20 bucks for it. Oh, whoop-de-dee,
what a great fucking gig. Kill me. 20 bucks for an hour ain't bad. Okay. Well, um, uh,
fuck, what was I gonna say? Something important. I don't fucking know, whatever I give up.
Subscribe to Monkey Jones. Yeah, that's, that's the thing to do. Do that. Uh, I guess we're done.
Subscribe to Monkey Jones. Hey, yeah. I just couldn't think of my own name. Shout out to,
shout out to everybody whose question I didn't read. Your questions were garbage. That's why
I didn't read them. So, uh, keep working, guys. Keep working on that shit. Shout out to ghosts.
Shout out to ghosts. Yeah. Yo, Danny Fenton, he was just 14 when his parents got a very strange
machine and it was assigned to you. You will remember my name. And don't forget to go on the
Patreon and join the exclusive Discord server. Tom didn't even know it was a thing, even though
he should have. That's the, well, we'll, we'll give you a link. Yeah, we'll give you one. Uh,
so yeah. My body is now your communion ghost. Please use me as you wish. Just be a patron.
Go to, go to patreon.com slash, uh, the, the Procrast news. Yeah, that's right. And uh,
if you join the Patreon lounge and you will become a ghost in due time and you'll be part of my
ghost harem. Do that and, and pledge five dollars and you'll get access to the bonus episodes,
including the one that we're going to do after this shit. So that'll like, get ready everybody,
get ready. Also, go on Twitter and tell Patreon that their new logo is shit. It's really funny.
They love it when you do that. Yeah, that's a good idea. Have they said anything about it?
Are they freaking out? I hope they're crying. I hope they're upset.
Oh my God. Yeah. Dude, I want that fucking PR rep lady to like respond to those.
Fuck you. That goddamn idiot. She's so much shit. Well, I think, I think if they actually be all
cheeky and coy with it, I'd prefer that to them like being sincerely like that.
Like if they're being sarcastic, like, oh, I love a fucking logo, you prick. If they're like that,
then I'm like, okay, they have like a soul, but I still hate you. Yeah. Go back. We have to go
back. Taren. Hashtag. We have to go back to PCP. Oh, your logo is so good. I mean, pod. Yeah, whatever.
We're still going to use that goddamn thing. It's going to exist. I'm going to sell it,
whether I like it or not. No, we have not. It's not been done yet.
I know we're letting it slip away. We have to do it like immediately. So we need to
fucking do this shit. Okay. Things are happening, folks. We're going to get on this shit.
Hopefully we'll have some updates. Oh, wait, wait, someone else did a question.
Shit. No, just let it out. Okay. This was just relevant. This was just like somebody
added a question. I'm sorry. I can't find it, but they just asked like, Hey, what's the status with
the iTunes? I just want to let everybody know like the iTunes thing. Okay. So we've had a couple
issues. There's been some problems getting it set up. It's entirely on me. I just have had
and had the time because of me and Mavin shit to fix it. So iTunes is coming someday soon. So
just stick around. It'll happen at some point. There you go. Okay. That's the end. Thanks for
the list, everybody. What's up? No, no, no. We'll say goodbye, but I need to sync.
Oh, okay. Yeah. We'll sync before we add. Okay. Thanks for this, everybody. We'll see you next time.
Make sure you send more questions. Use the hashtag. Hashtag ask PCP. Bye.