I won't bless that guy. That's son of a bitch.
That's son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Hello everyone, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm back, and the fun is over.
Bass.
We're on what? Episode 346 of the PCP? Probably 347.
I'm ready.
Okay. Ben Saint is here.
Dab, dab, dab, dab, dab, dab, dab.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to upset anyone.
Uh-oh.
I'm quitting reviews, and I just want Lindsay Ellis to like me.
Wow.
It's all I need.
That's all I need.
Okay.
Welcome.
You used to surprise me with that one.
It just seems so clear, so perfect.
It's all I need.
Lindsay Ellis, I heard in some video that she's now exclusively creating for Nebula.
Oh, yes.
Yep.
I keep hearing about Nebula.
A lot of people I follow, they're like, and Nebula sponsored this video.
Yep.
Every single person who's pretty good is on there.
I'm like, yeah, well.
Yeah.
I don't need that much content in my life.
I'm not going to.
I'm definitely not going to.
Boy, Legal Eagle really needs my $5 a month or whatever.
Boy, freaking Patrick H. Willems is going to be real.
This is a point.
I'm going to miss the next installment of the Charles saga.
Yep.
I love content as much as the next guy would fuck Nebula.
It's just it's even if even if I like the people on it, most of them at least or some of even
some of them, it's still it's still it's still a gay little club.
It's still a gay little club for a bunch of queers.
Okay, I'm getting a little.
I'm sorry.
I've been drinking.
I've been drinking a little bit.
I'm a little tipsy.
It's not true.
But it's not.
I liken it to a reputable news site that looks most or all of the articles behind a paywall.
And it's like, well, I guess I just won't get this good content.
I guess I just won't learn what the news is from you.
Indeed.
Because I'm just nobody does that.
Nobody fucking does that.
Nobody wants to do that.
True.
I don't believe that most of them could possibly they're not like they're not getting their
best stuff.
They're getting their like bonus stuff.
They're getting frankly, they're getting the craft that only the super fans want.
Right.
The good stuff that people want to see that generates attention is going to be on YouTube
because that's how they get eyeballs on them.
And that's the most important thing.
Lindsay Ellis is I guess is big enough that she doesn't need YouTube.
And you know what?
Good for her, I guess.
Yeah, like I guess that that for me is the main draw is like, well, Lindsay Ellis is gone
and I like her stuff.
Zoom her new stuff on Nebula is also good.
I like Lindsay Ellis's videos, but they're not like my favorite.
They're not like I'm not I'm not willing to subscribe to Nebula for them.
Yeah.
So it's just it's just a streaming service, but for Internet creators.
And I don't like streaming services.
I refuse.
For sure.
I mean, what do you I mean, what do you what even is a streaming service really?
It's a bunch of stuff that you have to pay to look at the library.
It's a library card.
I mean, it's it's a it's a just a little it's just like a second YouTube that's
pay to play, right?
Yeah.
Pay to access to your point.
Sure.
And that's certainly true.
Certainly true.
You know, fine.
I guess if you're like like a sneaky beaky, you could pay for Nebula find all the share
a share a password or like just download all of the videos.
Like and then watch them over the course of a long time after you stop paying.
Ah, yes.
Classic.
Yeah.
You probably could do that.
Like I say, I think for most people, I mean, for instance, Patrick H. Willems, I think
he did put the he put the like the the conclusion of the Charles.
It was either the conclusion of the Charles saga or it was like a behind the scenes truck.
It was like a Charles thing.
Okay.
And frankly, Charles like the worst part of his videos.
I don't know who that is.
Well it's it's a fucking it's a fucking character bit.
I mean, as a person in this in this.
Oh, he's a movie movie nerd YouTube guy, the angriest movie you've ever heard he's he's
bald.
Oh, ish.
Do you have any idea how little that is it down?
No, it's the bald guy.
The thing that's most remarkable about Patrick H. Willems, the thing that I'm most impressed
by him for is that he does you to he incorporates his parents into his YouTube videos and like
it actually works and is good.
It doesn't suck like apparently Jack St has his mom on some videos and Jack St's mom
like I haven't watched the videos, but I've heard that it's not very interesting and she
doesn't have a great screen presence.
So it's not great for the content.
But Patrick H. Willems mom and dad are I guess they're either just really charming or he
is like really good at directing them because it's actually great whenever he has his parents
in the videos.
Good stuff.
Yeah.
Cool.
It's it's it's incredible.
It's just not something it's just not something you see every day.
Parents being good.
I know.
For content.
Yeah.
Unbelievable.
Well, sure.
It's pretty rare.
He has he has sort of a bit where he is like this.
He's this like jet setting the you know always on the go traveling executive and he will
like stop into his parent.
He'll like be on cocaine or something and he'll stop into his parents house and be like
hey mom and dad I got a flight of the Bahamas in five minutes.
But first I wanted to follow up on our last conversation.
Let me tell you why Paddington too is the greatest movie ever made etc.
And then he'll do that and then he'll say all right gotta go and his mom will say oh
but Patrick you haven't had a cold you haven't had a hot shower in six years Patrick sit
down and have a cup of tea Patrick and he'll say mom I got I got cocaine I got more cocaine
to do and she'll say oh faith in pagoda and that's that's that's the bit pretty good.
It's so good.
I love it so much.
Thanks.
It's mine now.
Sure.
What are we talking about?
The procrastinators.
Streaming services.
Don't like them.
Oh I guess this is the procrastinators podcast.
We're on the procrastinators podcast.
That's it.
We did it.
Okay.
That's it.
Right.
Yeah.
Oh no.
You have caught me in this procrastinators podcast slightly indisposed and I say that
it's just help.
I'm downloading a thing.
I was worried there might be internet problem but it seems fine.
What do you download?
I'm downloading a totally legal ROM of a video game that I already own so it's okay
don't worry about it.
I'm trying to like get every single Fire Emblem game including the Japanese ones and then find
like translated patches for the ROMs and it's very involved and very confusing and
very I need to become like a computer hacker to figure it out.
Are you going to stream them or you just want to play them?
I want to play them but I think streaming them would be fun as well so why not and then
potentially if the streams are interesting if I have something to say I might make a
video about the whole fucking experience.
That's not a bad idea actually.
That's not a bad idea at all.
That's my little Fire Emblem plan because the new Fire Emblem Engage came out and I
was watching Mage play it on her stream.
Gay.
Yeah.
You get engaged to the fucking characters.
Is that true?
Wait.
I don't know why it's called that.
I don't actually know.
I think that that would be really funny if that's why it's called that.
It's not like oh you get married it's that you pair up with like a famous character from
previous Fire Emblem titles that you unlock and they increase your power and they sort
of float around your unit and it's like oh you're engaged, you're emblemized, you're
fired up.
I don't know why this is so funny.
I know.
But it's like yeah it's a Fire Emblem game.
I haven't played a Fire Emblem game in a long time and at first I scoff at it like oh whatever
it looks like anime like all of them oh they all look like anime now.
This all looks like, this looks like Smash Bros.
I hate Smash Bros.
Exactly.
But I wanted to because I was like thinking.
Stop putting Smash Bros characters in Fire Emblem.
Yeah Mario get out.
But I was like I don't actually play these games.
How do I know they're bad?
I feel like if I wanted to make a big snarky comment about how Fire Emblem sucks now I
should probably play all the games so that I can have like the maximum like Steel Man
argument or whatever.
That's fair.
So I thought let's play all the Fire Emblem games and then I thought why not play every
single one even the ones from the history to see if it used to be even better, unlikely
but maybe it used to be even better on the SNES or something.
So I was thinking of doing a thing, well why not do every possible version of a thing to
access.
Exactly.
Maximizing the stream length and the potential video length if I go into it.
How many Fire Emblem games are there?
I have the wiki open right now so.
Who's going to get done first?
You playing all the Fire Emblem games or me playing all the Mega Man Battle Network games?
Truly I think it depends on like Fire Emblem can be a really long game if it's hard and
you're trying not to lose.
But Mega Man is like long in like tedium where there's many, many multiple sets of little
random battles you can't avoid.
Fire Emblem is like there's a map, beat the map and sometimes you lose and you have to
restart and the map can take like hours and then you have to restart anyway.
So I don't know.
I mean how long would you say a typical Fire Emblem game is?
You know my experience is skewed because I played Fire Emblem when I was young and when
you're young you're dumb and so I lost so many times.
I feel like I could be smarter now but you don't know.
I don't know.
Another week of me not streaming again.
I fucked up again.
Lol.
Get fucked.
I am fucked.
I'm going to start again.
I just didn't do it.
I just didn't have time this week.
I'm going to try and make.
Yeah, that will be a fun side competition.
You and me streaming different game series.
That's funny actually.
Yeah, that'll be funny.
But yeah.
The...
What was I saying?
Oh, the number of games.
And Fire Emblem both involve moving around on squares and casting spells?
Yeah, those spells.
Cast spells and Fire Emblem?
Okay.
Yeah, there's three different types of magic.
Axe magic, sword magic, and bow magic, spear magic?
No.
You're so stupid.
You're so fucking stupid.
No, it's like anima magic which is like the nature, elements, fire, wind, electricity.
And there's holy magic, which is, you know, Christian core, and then there's dark magic,
which is void of this core.
Also good.
Yeah.
Classic, classic trio.
Nature?
Okay, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Nature, holy, and dark.
What is there like a rock, paper, scissor thing going on there?
There is.
There's a rock, paper, scissor.
Holy beats dark.
Dark beats nature.
Nature beats holy.
The sword, there's another triangle, sword, sword, axe, spear, and then there's some other
things like bows can really hurt Pegasus Knights because they got wings and shit.
In nature magic, I mean, inside of that, does like fire beat ice and ice beat lightning
and lightning beat fire or something?
No, it's quite like condensed.
It's just the three sets of magic.
So it doesn't matter what sort of thing.
They should have a freaking sub rock, paper, scissor inside of the rock, paper, scissor
where oh, it's nature, so it beats the holy, but it's fire nature, so it beats like wind
holy, so it kind of balances out actually.
The thing is the magic is effective against like the defenses of the person.
So it's like if you're strong against magic, you'll take less damage.
Actually no, I guess whatever book you're holding, whatever magic tome you have changes
your defenses.
Now there's books.
God damn.
Well, that's where the magic comes from.
You hold a book and that gives you your weapon and you can get different books that have
more powerful attacks.
Oh, like instead of holding an axe or a spear, you hold a book of holy.
You hold the book that has the spell in it and it has a limited number of curts.
It's like weapons have durability.
It's very, very nice.
So you'll have a book that has a particular spell and the spell will have, depending on
what spell it is, it'll have a certain number of uses per battle and it'll do a certain
amount of damage and it'll have a certain attribute, whether it's holy or nature or dark.
Yeah.
Okay, I got you.
I got you.
Interesting.
So basically that's just like a separate like magical version of the axe spear.
Other thing.
Sword.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's interesting.
Yeah.
Fire Emblem seems fun.
I just never played it before.
It is fun and I used to really like tactical RPGs.
Now I find turn based combat a little bit tedious these days.
Well, I find it.
I found Fire Emblem more interesting generally than like Final Fantasy where you walk around
and then there's a random battle and a set of monsters come up and then you have to beat
them.
It just feels like there's a lot of aimlessness to the combat.
These monsters, they don't want to stop you.
They're just around.
They're just in the way, sometimes as a boss and that makes sense.
You're trying to kill them.
There's guards.
I get it.
But like in Fire Emblem, the map sort of adds a layer of strategy, obviously it's a strategy
but like a layer of strategy to positioning and terrain advantages and retreating isn't
just a button you press.
You actually have to retreat to a safe distance so that you can regroup and heal up and then
come back.
Right.
And it's like, it's cool.
I like the idea of being a tactician in a battlefield because it feels more substantial than I got
a group of people and they're walking through a featureless cave corridor until they get
to the end.
Well, I could not stop complaining about the random battles in Mega Man Battle Network,
easily the worst part of the game.
The battles themselves are fun, but the fact that they just cannot avoid them and they will
just continually happen as you walk around in dungeons is so annoying, but I guess that's
the genre.
So the number of Fire Emblem games, I'm going to play the remakes as well, but some of them
are only in Japan and have not been remade.
And one of the remakes is only Japan, so I still need a translation for that.
There's Fire Emblem, Ang Kokyōryō to Higari no Tsurugi, Shadow Dragon in the Blade of
Light.
Naturally.
That's the first one that's got Marth in it.
Remember Marth?
Oh, yeah.
I remember.
I remember his down B.
Yeah, I hope he got some down B in the game.
Then there's Fire Emblem Gaiden, Fire Emblem Mystery of the Emblems slash Moncho no Nazo,
which is one of the difficult ones.
Wait, wait, wait.
What does no Nazo mean?
I know that phrase.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
It says Mystery of the Emblems slash Moncho no Nazo.
I've heard that phrase no Nazo.
It might be like a changed title translation.
I think it means mystery.
I think it's like the mystery of something.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
That's three, and that's the first on SNES, and then it's Fire Emblem Genealogy of the
Holy War.
Oh, it's because there's a Mega Man.
It's like Wily no Nazo.
Oh.
I think that's two.
I think that's number two, Mystery of Dr. Wily, because he turns into an alien at the
end.
Yes, of course.
Of course.
Genealogy of the Holy War, Seisin no Keifu, Fire Emblem Thrasia 776, and then Fire Emblem
the Binding Blade, which is the one with Roy, who is our boy.
Then it's the first, after that, it's the first officially translated into English Fire Emblem,
known as the Blazing Blade, or Reckon no Ken, Reckon no Morty, then it's Fire Emblem the
Sacred Stones, Path of Radiance, Radiant Dawn, and then Shadow Dragon, which is the
remake of the first game on DS.
New Mystery of the Emblem, which is Mystery of the Emblem remake on DS, Fire Emblem Awakening
on 3DS or- Jesus Christ, why can't they just number them?
Well, don't matter.
Fire Emblem Fates slash If in Japan, Fire Emblem Echoes Shadows of Valentia, which is another
thing, 3DS remake, I don't know which one that is, then Fire Emblem Three Houses, and
then finally Fire Emblem Engage, and I want to play them all.
So how many was that?
Let's see, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17 with three remakes.
Okay, that is more than there are battle network games.
I think there's 11 battle network games.
Yeah, yeah.
So I'll probably be slower.
Probably.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know how-
Considering both series are RPGs, yeah, probably.
I think the average battle network or Star Force game takes somewhere in the vicinity
of like 30 hours, 20 to 40-ish.
I don't think a Fire Emblem game typically takes the same as like a traditional RPG.
It can.
I think Fire Emblem Awakening took a while when I played that, but the early ones are
on NES, the first two, they can't be that big.
They're probably going to be tough, but like, they can't put so many, yeah, NES.
The ones that I'm struggling getting a translation for are Mystery of the Emblem and Genealogy
of the Holy War, because there's like, there's ROM hacks, translation patches made by people
that you download, and then you need a special program to take the ROM that you get legitimately
and the ROM hack, and you squish them together.
You always get legitimately.
Do you always have a copy of the game before you download a ROM movie?
Absolutely.
Even the rare ones that cost $400 on eBay.
Exactly.
Mm-hmm.
And I'm like, I have, there's like, okay, here's, there's a thing that I'm barely understanding,
which is like, header ROMs, which is some ROMs have a header, and some ROMs do not,
and a header adds, the header is like a bunch of data that is added to a ROM for some reason,
something, something floppy disks, something, something, and so some translations they need
to know or are designed for header ROMs or unheaded ROMs.
And if the bit, like number, the byte number is off, it will corrupt the thing and it won't
work.
So you need to know, you need to some, you need another program to check what the like
numbers are, the fucking codes for all these ROMs are to make sure you have the correct
ROM.
Obviously, ROMs sometimes are fucked and it's hard to find the right ones and then sometimes
the translations just aren't finished or are buggy because they're just passion projects
from some people.
Oh, I got scared for a minute because you said buggy and it reminded me of one piece
and I didn't read the new chapter, but there is no new chapter this week, right?
Yes, there is no new chapter.
Okay.
I had a gut reaction, a visceral reaction to hearing buggy.
Okay, sorry, go on.
So right now, before we started recording, I was trying to figure it out, trying to like,
like, oh, what the fuck?
There's like, there's a fucking, I got so many tabs open right now.
Are you, are you just downloading them from cool ROMs or whatever?
I'm downloading ROMs wherever I can find them.
Not a lot of places have the Fire Emblem ones.
I mean, maybe I just need to scroll a long time to find better sites that have the ROMs
I'm looking for.
I mean, I don't know, for me, looking for Mega Man's, it was usually just a matter of just
typing it the name and ROM into Google and usually I would get the first result would
be something from cool ROMs or wow ROMs or whatever and it would just be there.
Only a few, only a few of them that I have to like dig through slightly more obscure
websites for.
Yeah, I mean, the ROMs are here, it's just, some of them are like, especially for a Fire
Emblem 3, Moncho no Nazo, there's like versions of the ROM, like 1.0 and 1.1.
And that's another thing, like some of the translations only work for one or the other.
And also the header thing.
And if your ROM does or doesn't have a header, there are programs you can download to add
or remove a header from a ROM so that it can work.
Remind me what a header is?
I don't know, it's just, it's like, I assume, just based on having seen videos about computers.
Yeah, I've heard of computers before.
The way the patch works is that it counts like the bits and bytes and then when it gets
to a certain bit, it changes it based on what the patch is trying to change, like the language,
the text used, whatever it needs to do to change the patch to translate everything.
And if the ROM has an unexpectedly different size because of a header or a lack of a header
then it will count and then change the wrong byte because it can't tell.
It just does like it goes from the beginning and changes all the things that needs to change.
And if they're all the wrong, if all the things they need to change are like slightly offset,
they'll change all the wrong bytes and they'll be corrupted, which I think is what's been
happening with this thing.
So I need to be smart or something.
But do you have the power to do that?
I think I have the power.
It's just that it's just has been causing a bit of a headache just because I'm not that
good at like emulating stuff.
If it's easy, if you download a thing and you download an emulator and it just works,
that's good.
But if there's like issues with certain emulators and you have to learn, you have to use a specific
emulator for a specific game and then use some specific settings to make sure it works.
And there's like forums talking about it and like read me's that are walls upon walls
of text that I have to read to understand that stuff.
It starts to hurt all the all of the text entering my brain causes a malfunction.
It hurts my brain.
I'm not good at all this stuff, but I really want to do it.
So I have to.
It's a lot of stuff.
Luckily, I've got most of the ones that are just Japanese done and it's just three and
four.
Once I get three and four and I think four will be easier than three just because I've
seen like three has very few translations according to romhacks.net.
There may be other romhack translations, but I doubt they'll be elsewhere because romhacks
seems pretty, pretty complete with its like documentation of different hacks and translations.
There's not many for three, for some reason.
People don't give a shit, not enough people.
I mean, just need, just need more love, just need people to care, just need people to care.
If we love with all of our heart, maybe all of our fucking problems will be solved.
If we wish upon a star, but yeah, that's a little project.
Once I've got all that working, I might start streaming don't know when exactly.
I've been, I've been downloading.
I had a freaking download going for like a freaking, like literally set for seven weeks.
It took me seven weeks, almost eight weeks to download the entire DigiBro archive.
Be a torrent.
It finally completed.
Yeah.
It's like, it's like one and a half terabyte.
It's so fucking huge.
It finally finished.
It was stuck for like almost a week at like 99.7% done, one gigabyte left.
But it finally finished this week, which was a relief.
So now I'm seeding.
Now I'm seeding.
So if anyone else downloads in the future, that's what I said.
I was seething before it finished, but now I'm seeding after it's completed.
So in the future, if anyone downloads that you're welcome, I am helping.
Wouldn't it be cooler if like the term was sowing, like you sow the seeds and then when
they want a tarant?
I'm reaping.
The people who want to download it, they reap those, that tarant.
Hmm.
Wait, no, because if it were like that, then first you would, you would reap first and
then you would sow.
No, you only, you're supposed to only reap after sowing, but with torrents you reap first
and then you decide whether you want to sow for the next person to reap.
Oh yeah.
I guess someone else, I guess you can sow what someone else reaped.
That's just not how the expression is usually used.
That's why it's cool.
It's like you reap what has been sown.
It's like communal, communal.
Communal reaping?
Yeah.
Hmm.
I mean, yeah, true.
Yeah, it does make sense.
It does make sense.
I'm not sure why it's seeding.
It could have been anything, but anyway, I have that and since, I think I'm, I guess
I should probably start thinking about how to put that, how to make some content out
of that.
Reacting to the entire Digi Pro playlist.
I don't even know how long it is.
You know, you could do like a fucking, what's his name?
Like the guy who hates Dark Souls 2.
Oh, H-Bomber Guy?
No, he likes Dark Souls 2, the guy who reacted to H-Bomber Guy for like 20 hours.
Oh, Mahler?
Yeah.
Do a Mahler style reaction critique and pause and rant on all of the fucking archives.
Watching every fucking old Digi Bro After Dark video, pausing every minute, it'd be
like, no, look at that.
In this scene, she's wearing the same glass as she was in the last video and that's, what
does that tell me thematically?
That tell me stagnation, the channel is stagnating.
That tells me that it's, that it's just, it's just not believable.
That would be like- Okay, anyway, let's keep going.
It was like, what was it?
It really was like 24 hour- Oh, now she's, oh, now she's getting married.
Oh, now she's got a fiance.
What is this?
Did anyone want this?
The audience did not ask for this.
The writers just got woke and they put a woman in.
Yeah.
You could magnify the length of the content by like 25 times.
Horrible.
750 hour video.
Does YouTube have a 10 hour limit?
No, I've seen 100 hour videos.
Jesus.
Oh, just got a message.
Just got a message.
And I, I'm in semi-regular contact with knows someone is in contact with someone who tested
positive for COVID.
So it is possible.
So all right.
Oh shit.
I might have to- I should get myself tested.
Might have to test myself in the next week or so, just in case, but it's probably gonna
be okay.
Oh, damn, I haven't thought about COVID in a while.
Fuck.
Oh, downer.
They'll eat your brains.
Will eat my brains.
When was the last time I got vaccinated?
Was it like October?
I don't know.
Oh shit.
I don't remember.
When did I get that booster?
Oh God.
I have no memory.
Help.
COVID just destroyed my memory.
Oh God.
My brain fog.
Brain fog.
I can't remember when I got the booster.
Where's my card?
Where's my Vax card?
I gotta have my Vax.
Typical liberal, addicted to the vaccines.
Oh, you just can't live without those vaccines, can you?
Yeah, I can't.
You're addicted.
Yeah, I'll die.
Oh, well, hey, I found a- hey, should I make a video about this fact that I learned?
What is it?
Well, I'll tell you.
Here's the fact.
I saw this Tumblr post going around.
It was a screenshot of a Tumblr post that I guess was pretty popular, and the post purports
that the word Nimrod, you know, the word that you would call someone if you're a- yeah.
It's an insult.
It means you're stupid, but where it comes from is from the Bible.
It is in fact the name of a great hunter in the Bible, a hunter and a king, I believe.
And so, it means that, but the Tumblr post purports that it has- it became an insult
when Bugs Bunny called Elmer Fudd a Nimrod, ironically comparing him to the great hunter
from the Bible, but people didn't- but people took it to mean that it means you're stupid,
and so the word reversed its meaning to be an insult.
Sounds plausible.
It sounds plausible, and it's not really true.
There's like a grain of truth to it.
It's not really true.
I looked into it, and all I really did was read the Wikipedia article on Nimrod because
there's a section on colloquial usage, and here are the facts.
The facts are, according to the Wikipedia, is it one?
It was Daffy Duck, actually, that called Elmer Fudd Nimrod.
Sounds more like a Daffy thing to say.
Bugs Bunny called Yosemite Sam Nimrod, and also the word Nimrod was used sarcastically,
and thus as in an insulting way, like well before Looney Tunes, and I think the earliest
example was in a letter from Frick and General Lee in the Civil War who called someone Nimrod.
And I think importantly, he doesn't even capitalize the word Nimrod.
He doesn't capitalize it like it's a name.
He calls someone a young Nimrod from out of the west, or a young Nimrod from the west,
and he is with a lowercase letter, so he's just using it as a generic noun to either
outright insult him or to ironically insult him with a sarcastic usage of an otherwise
complimentary word.
So the word's already being used as a sarcastic insult even in 1830 or whatever.
I guess it would be similar to saying, oh, you're a good shot, go ahead Robin Hood, show
me what you got.
Call on someone Einstein, oh, yeah, nice math skills Einstein or whatever.
No shit Sherlock.
Right, so I don't know.
Fuck you Nimrod, die.
I thought, is that the kind of thing when I learn something like this, is what I should
do as a YouTuber, like make a video about it?
If you want to.
Is there even enough, I don't know, well here's the thing I want to, if it would be a good
video and it would get views and I would make money, will it make me any money if I make
a video out of that and post it, explaining what I just explained to you?
I mean it doesn't sound like a lot of content, you could do a little troll style, little
Ben style.
Yeah, be short.
You do a YouTube short, did you know blah blah blah Nimrod?
Just feel like that's what, just feel like that's what, that's what YouTubers that I
like do, is they will just have something that they find interesting and they'll go
down a little rabbit hole and they'll research it and then they'll learn some interesting
stuff about it and then they'll make a video where they're like, hey let me explain all
this weird stuff I learned on this little rabbit hole that I went down purely because
I found it interesting to, you know, dig into it.
I do like videos like that.
What was the one about the Disney-ident music?
Oh, the, not, defunct land, was that the guy?
I always, I always freaking confuse defunct land with Todd in the shadows, but yeah, it
was the defunct land guy.
Yeah.
Da da da da.
And that was, that became a huge big video because the rabbit hole just kept going.
It's not, da da da da, although it's kind of that, it's da da da da.
Da da da da da.
Yeah, you know, it was really annoying.
I don't know if this was intentional, but you know that video starts off with him interviewing
a bunch of other like YouTubers about it and then asking them like, hey, do you know the
Disney Channel theme?
And all of them are like, no, I don't know what it is.
And then he tells them, you know, it's da da da da, and they all go, oh, except that
one girl.
That one girl is like a cunt about it.
She's like, no, there's no Disney Channel theme.
And like, she's such a bitch.
Oh yeah, I remember, I was a bit weird.
Why'd you leave that in?
Yeah.
She looked bad.
Like you've, you've really made this person look like an asshole.
Um, yeah, hang on, you gotta take another bite of my oats.
Like things, things on the PCP where he had like a mini deep dive into Wikipedia to learn
about flanges or whatever.
Mm, of the thorn, the letter thorn.
Yeah, like those are fun.
They're short and the rabbit hole ends pretty quickly because the answer to the
question was just right there.
Yeah, the answer to the question is nowhere to be found and you have to go
digging.
That's when it turned into a big video.
But you don't actually know that until you start looking.
I could, I could probably dig a little deeper and I could probably make like maybe a
five, maybe a 10 minute video explaining what I just explained.
And I mean, I don't know, that's content.
And then that's all I can say.
That's, that's content.
It's, yeah, I don't know whether the people who make videos like that think of it as
content or whether they're genuinely like, I gotta know what the hell is going on here.
And then they simply document it.
I, it's just, it just, it just, the thought just occurred to me.
It's like, okay, what a real YouTuber who does this as a job and who takes it seriously.
And who is successful at it.
Would a real YouTuber be like, hey, a thing that I have thoughts about and did some research
into and found out something about, I should make a video about that.
I think there's often lots of those, but many of them just don't go anywhere.
And the videos you see are the ones that became like worth investing time in.
Yeah.
I would imagine that like for every one video that comes out of that nature, there were
lots of other little things that just didn't, didn't have any, any staying power or interest
or like, oh, I guess that was half interesting.
But the question was answered too easily.
It's like, I have to get it.
You mean ones that got made that just never, nobody watched?
Or you mean just ones that could have been made that they decided not to because it just
wasn't enough there?
Could have been made.
Like they go on a little journey and they like, okay, write down some notes.
And then at some point deciding to whether to make it a video.
It's like, I remember James Rolfe talking about angry video game nerd choosing a game
practice.
Sometimes he'll pick a game off the shelf and see if it's fun to play or if there's
anything there and he'll play it for like five, 10 minutes.
And if it seems like there's nothing interesting, then he won't bother to make a video.
It won't start the script writing process.
But if you can see some things, then he'll start and then it becomes a video.
OK, so you'd for YouTube videos for any sort of creative thing.
Yeah. Yeah, I think I get what you're saying.
So I guess you already did that.
You dipped your feet into the research, dipped your toe in and you're like, hmm,
well, knowledge.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't know.
I was thinking about how to make it on this platform.
You just do.
I mean, why did you do anything?
Why did you do the Mega Man lecture?
Huh? Why did that continue to be a thing you worked on?
For fricking views, you Nimrod.
Yeah, but like.
But like, what was the deciding thought like that it would get a lot of you?
Yeah, but why did you know that?
What? I'm asking you to like to define the difference between a little thing
about Nimrod and Mega Man.
I mean, obviously, Mega Man has I mean, it's a well known thing.
But like, I don't think things are also interesting.
It just submit the the the Mega Man video idea just fit into various
templates of things that I had seen get a lot of traction in the past.
It's really long.
It's about a popular franchise.
That's it.
So you're a Nimrod thing.
Does it meet criteria similar to other interesting videos of that type?
Um.
Not not one not ones that I feel like I see lately.
You that the ten minute video that the five to ten minute video feels like
I might be stupid.
I might be like two.
I might be two on the bleeding edge of this.
But the five to ten minute video feels like a relic.
Almost feels like almost feels like something that has has kind of
we've moved past as a society.
I still watch Tom Scott videos and they're usually like six minutes or something.
I sometimes if the content is good and and stuff, then little videos
are just, you know, oh, cool.
New one of these you click on them.
Yeah, they're low investment.
It's like closer to YouTube shorts.
I feel like YouTube shorts are big just because.
Committing to a huge video has to be the sort of subject you care about.
But for a small video, it's like, I guess I'll hear about this person.
I don't know.
Talk about this mildly interesting thing for a few seconds.
All all I'm saying all I'm saying is I learned this fact and I thought, boy,
what a waste of a fact.
What a waste of knowledge.
If I can't if I can't monetize it somehow, if I can't like if I if I can't,
you know, it's like if a tree falls in the woods, it's like if a YouTuber
learns a fact, but there's no video in which they explain and monetize it.
Did they really even learn it at all?
What was the point?
Well, I mean, do you want to make a video about flanges?
No, why not?
That's funny.
It is a little funny.
I guess I just I don't know.
I like words and learning the the the the history of words and colloquialisms.
It's an air.
It's an area of some interest for me.
They genuinely think small little things like that have a place.
YouTube shorts, whether whatever you think of them.
They're they're little bite sized things that are easy to make and throw away
and just like a little bit of content for you.
Nothing big, nothing fancy, nothing that you as a creator need to spend
all that much effort creating.
So really, what's the harm?
If it were a bigger rabbit hole, then it might be more of a
should I or shouldn't I, because maybe you could make a 20 minute video,
but that's not that cool.
What about if it could turn into a four hour video?
If I if I feel the urge, I might try and like
write out what that video would be in like essay form
and then just look over it and be like, is this worth?
Is there is there enough here?
Was I able to say enough that I feel like it's worth like narrating this
and putting a video over it?
And I might do that and see how I feel about it.
Yeah, I don't know.
And that feels stupid because like everyone listening now already knows the point.
There's everyone listening now is like, well, I wouldn't need to watch that
because I just had it explained to me.
Yeah, but who watches the PCP?
Literally, nobody.
Ha, ha, that's literally no.
That's my audience.
Literally, nobody.
LaMau.
OK.
Hey, I forgot to mention this is something I forgot to mention last week.
But did you know that my video game, Phantom's Revenge, got reviewed?
And I did not.
You did know that from a furry, four or was it a diaper from a diaper fur?
Yeah. Did I mention this on the show?
I'm pretty sure. Or maybe I mentioned it on the stream.
And like, well, mention it again.
Damn, well, now I thought I forgot to mention it.
Maybe I did mention it. No, this.
Oh, I don't want to repeat myself.
Oh, no, you did say on the stream, but I think you also said on the episode.
Damn it.
Well, you got reviewed.
Phantom's Revenge got reviewed by a diaper fur.
I got reviewed by this diaper fur and it was actually kind of a good review.
It was kind of a they made thoughtful observations about the game,
but they made them.
With this literal and I'm not joking, literally a drooling
like a drooling baby, but adult, adult baby in a diaper.
Avatar, I didn't hear about that part.
Um, I think they were called fluff bite.
Systems or fluff bite entertainment.
OK, I think maybe I did mention this already.
So I won't belabor the point.
Um, how do I find this?
They're fluff.
OK, on Twitter, they're fluff bite entertainment systems and they're on
Twitch. Where's their freaking YouTube?
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
I can fluff shank.
It's on their fluff bite presents channel.
They have two channels.
The one this was on is the fluff bite presents, which is they're like edited videos.
They have another one for like.
Oh, by doesn't be BYTE.
Yeah. Yeah.
So 10 days ago in the JRPG used to inspire one.
Yeah, I don't know why it's I don't know why it's called that.
I don't know why I don't know what's going on with that title.
Oh, my God, it is a drooling diaper very.
Yeah, it's it's the first review.
It starts like three minutes in and the delivery is terrible.
They like stammer their way through the scripts of themselves talking about it.
But the review, it's the content of the review itself is not that bad.
Like, it's kind of good, actually.
I don't know. Pretty funny.
It's it's it's the avatar like normally it's like drooling
and it's like jittering, you know, in that way that like a PNG tuber sort of jitters
when the voice is speaking.
Yeah, but then sometimes it like lunges forward.
It lunges forward at the camera and it stops drooling, but it gets like a sad face.
I saw it just then. Yeah, that may literally be a Vtuber.
Like, I think it is a like a P it like it's not animated to speak.
Instead, it is sort of animated to make that face and jitter around when
there's speech happening and when there's not speech, it's sad.
Yeah, it's a little bit unsettling, honestly.
You know, I did appreciate the review, though.
And they actually they actually had a pretty.
You know, the section is like seven minutes long and they they talk about
like the design of the game and stuff.
And they, you know, they talk about all the freaking assets I had.
And they talk about how this how the Sonichu enemies are like a smart use
of like default assets to like get a lot of content out of.
I'm like, yeah, it is. Thanks.
He they say that the whole the game is like one long like battle corridor.
They say that it's like a combination of a JRPG and a beat them up.
And I'm like, yes, it is. That's exactly what it is.
You've figured it out.
She said described my game correctly.
Surprisingly rare.
OK, whatever.
It's a fucking thumbnail with all those things and then Phantom Horn.
I mean, he fits. He fits right in.
Shoutouts to Fluff by Fluff by systems for their sick review.
Hell, yeah, revenge. Hell, yeah.
OK, that's all I have to say about that.
Did I meant did I mention did did we talk about how we found that freaking web comic?
I think we did, right?
What freak are the ladies?
The big big boob ladies.
Did we talk about that that we found that?
Um, I definitely remember on the stream you mentioned.
And we had to we had to stop streaming
because I can't remember what I said on the stream and what I said on the show
because it all just blends together.
I just say it.
Yeah. Say it again.
I got things to talk about.
But someone someone called Rusting Robot
found when and found on the on somewhere on the forum,
some bad web comics forums or something.
Yeah, the comic with the big boob ladies is called Jennifer.
It's called Jennifer's show.
Jen, I'm losing my I'm losing my freaking mind.
I'm losing my freaking mind.
I'm literally going to check the show notes of the last episode
and see if if if it's there because I feel like I've said this before.
Help.
I don't know. Go check.
OK, I'm going.
All right, whatever.
It's not in the show notes, so I guess I didn't say it.
Yeah, Rusting Robot found Jen Jennifer show.
And that's what the freaking web comics called.
Yes, it's it's it's a comic.
About two ladies who are lesbian lovers.
Yeah.
One of them has ears and a tail.
The other one just has ears.
One of them is a cat girl.
Let me check the episode before the last one.
Wait a minute.
No.
Two episodes ago, I talked about that Hazel video about the big booba anime.
This is one about Jenny Nicholson.
Oh, well. Oh, well, I guess I'm repeating myself.
Yeah.
There's some really funny like
there's a really funny like reaction images of like the Jenny's
because I think I think they're both named.
Jennifer like one is Jennifer and the other is Jenny.
Yeah, there's something like that.
And they have the they have the big booba and
there's a YouTube channel.
The person has a YouTube channel where they post videos of themselves
like cosplaying as their own characters.
And it's very weird looking.
And yeah, I didn't look through too many of those.
Yeah.
I think that they had one with a puppet.
They had made a puppet of Jen or Jennifer.
I don't know if I saw a puppet, but that was one of the first videos.
A lot of them.
I think they have multiple channels.
That's the thing.
They have one that's like they mention in the comic that I googled
and I found and then there's another one that's like more,
I guess, brand.
More brand, more brand.
Hang on, my phone just spoke to me and I'm scared.
I need to go kill it.
I freaking I freaking can't Google Jennifer show without YouTube
or Google telling me, oh, did you mean the Jennifer Hudson show?
No, I don't even know who that is.
This this fucking sucks, even though I know the name,
I literally like can't Google it because it just gives me.
Unrelated results for things with the word Jennifer.
OK, sorry about that.
I I just heard out of the corner of my ear like your alarm has been set
for one a.m. tomorrow and I'm like.
Why? Oh, you're over the other side of the room
and I haven't been talking about that.
Did you listen to me?
What the fuck happened?
Oh, it's it's Miss Jen, Miss Jay.
No, the characters are called Miss Jay and Jen.
Um, the content of the comic is is just like,
aha, we love each other so much, aha, it's so lovey-dovey over here.
And then they say trans rights and then they say gay rights.
Do they do they say trans rights, gay rights?
Do they say stuff?
Yeah, very occasionally, there'll be like a flag wave in moment.
OK, the comic is not really like a narrative.
It's just nothing really happens.
It's just them.
Yeah, it's it's like it's just drawing the characters with like you can tell
when they've learned about a different brush setting and Photoshop.
And they're like, oh, this one is like this is like a Japanese,
like a sideways, like diagonal sort of brush.
And they start drawing with that and it looks like shit and then it all looks
like shit, but it's like, oh, yeah, it's sort of.
But that's what I'm here for.
Yeah, it's odd.
It's odd and weirdly charming.
Wow. What do you what do you know?
I like I like the one where we're Miss J or Jennifer or whatever.
It's just like, get the popcorn, honey.
They're going to they're going to make fun of us on Kiwi Farms thread again.
Ha, ha, movie time.
And the spelling is like a trotius, like a parody level bad spelling.
It's great.
It's really there's a lot of really that's what you like to see.
It honestly feels like a like a genuine
sweet bro and hella Jeff comic.
Yes, it really it really does.
It feels like someone actually made sweet bro and hella Jeff,
but unironically, but it just happens to be instead of dude bro gamers.
It's about big boob lesbian trans cat girls.
And honestly, I love you know what?
Yeah, you know what? It's.
And that concept in and of itself feels like some someone it feels like some
unfunny shit Lord was like, haha, I'll do that as a joke.
But no, it's not a joke.
They didn't do it as a joke.
It's just earnest and it's the appreciation of the of the subject matter.
Friend of the show, Jennifer J. Jennifer J.
Can we get Jennifer J as a guest?
Oh, my God, can you imagine?
Oh, my God, we should do a lecture.
Do a PCP lecture on the Jennifer Jane averse.
I guess so. I don't know if there's that much to it.
I read like a ton of the comics.
Did you actually?
Yeah, I just kept like moving through them.
That's funny.
I can't even find I literally can't find them on Google
because they don't like where are they posted what website?
What do you mean? The website that.
Does she have her own website?
Yeah, didn't they say what was the person who found the website?
Well, they found it on like a forum.
Oh, I somebody when it was announced.
Oh, during the stream, we mentioned it during the stream
and then somebody in chat linked the website
where they post all of their own comics.
OK, well, I'm OK, well, they have a Twitter.
But oh, my God, they have a Twitter,
but they haven't posted since like 2019.
Oh, boy, this person, I guess I didn't save.
OK, OK, is it is it the new the linked website on their Twitter
is called the new stories of Miss J and Jen dot webcomic dot WS.
Try that.
Yeah, I mean, link it here.
I there are a bunch here.
It like starts with like a a retrospective
because they made comics before, but have had transferred
from whatever site that was on to this new site.
Fuck is this? What is this?
Here's here's the here's, I guess, the newest one or the newest one
on this site posted on 2019.
It's called the joint shop.
Yeah, that's the one you post the website as well.
Yes. Yeah, this is the website I looked through.
Like as much as I felt like it's quite a lot, honestly.
There's quite a lot.
Some day I'll learn love.
All right, this is the first one that's like amusing on a wave.
OK, like I wonder if my creator will still draw me in 30 years, said
my Miss J on the fourth or the 26th of the fourth 1984.
Hey, she's wearing a vinyl scratch T-shirt.
OK, here's one.
This one's funny.
Welcome to my world, the Canada's North.
I don't know why this one's funny.
Oh, look, 30 years ago, Miss J had normal big boobs.
Now she's got the biggest boobs ever.
It's so development.
It's character development.
Yes, Jen, I found that meteor that fall from that meteor shower.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Wait, read this one one second.
Lamal, you'll never guess what you'll never guess what the punchline is.
Yes, Jen.
I found that meteor that fall from the meteor shower is bigger than my boobs.
Yeah.
Wait, is there like a copy paste, like different image of legs?
Over top of that. Oh, God, there is.
Oh, God.
She put a she put a carpet, a little rug on top of the meteor.
To sit on it.
That's OK.
That's that's got to be her actual house, right?
That's got to be like the actual house that she lives in potentially.
I feel like she takes like a lot of random images
from all over the Internet to compile these things.
Like the boobs in this one are like a shape
that has like a different layer of some texture stripes.
Like underneath.
Yeah, well, that's just that's called
that's called screen toning.
Give mangaka have mastered the art.
It's just funny because they clearly know like some techniques
to like have like a layer mask and then put something underneath.
But it's so bad.
Yeah, yeah.
But it's all in service of of this as the final product.
Um, but it's so bad that it's good and I like it.
Wait a second, we got it.
Wait, we got to show Cheesy this one.
Check check this out.
I don't even know what's going on here.
Is she fighting a clown for the last box of popcorn?
The last box in town.
What is pink candy popcorn?
Licking the elephant.
Isn't it Lucky Elephant?
Oh, Lucky Elephant, Lucky Elephant, pink.
Lucky Elephant, pink candy popcorn.
A Canadian confection.
Oh, Canada's North.
Yeah. OK.
I guess that's why it's like a Canadian thing.
Like weird, like troll feet.
Like OK, so it's just Pink Cracker Jack but with no peanuts.
I hate Cracker Jack.
You're a Cracker Jack.
No, it sucks.
It's ass. I don't like it.
Look at this.
Look at this edit.
Big groups on this web call me.
What?
Why did they forget the last point?
Yeah.
Atom dot smasher dot org slash what is do I dare click?
Yeah, I think you do.
I think you do.
I've seen Adam dot smasher before.
That's that's a real thing.
Dot org slash what?
OK.
I need some coffee for this.
HTTP column.
Double slash fucking you there.
Are you alive?
This person's like 60, by the way.
Yeah.
Probably around the same age as what's her name?
Jennifer Diane writes.
Oh, my God, Jennifer Diane writes.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Jennifer Diane writes is more significantly more.
Literate.
Yes.
I know this is.
I should I should dive in.
Pression.
I don't know if that's the right word, but like this month is February
and I've been.
Oh, my God.
I should draw Jennifer J.
You should do fan art.
Dude, what the fuck?
That's beautiful.
Just make sure.
OK, there's something something very charming about the Canadianess of it.
Something something about something about pink lucky elephant pink candy popcorn
is such like such an old person thing.
Why on earth is the background like this?
It's it's it you look at it and you're like, oh, yeah, it's a badly drawn comic.
But then the choices made are baffling straight up sweet bro and hella Jeff mouth.
After watching that Miley Cyrus wrecking ball video,
I want to ride your twin wrecking balls all night long.
This is amazing.
In static bedroom.
Yeah.
Why are they in a static.
World.
It's just I don't I don't understand, but it's great.
I I I I I can't explain anything.
I'm just glad I'm glad the mystery is solved.
Yes, Jennifer.
The new PCP girl.
PCP guy, PCP girl.
I should I should we should we should put this in the.
In the perfect comic party.
You should get her to.
Yeah, just steal it.
Just steal it and put it in and call it a call it a parody.
I'll only post one more.
Yeah, OK, this is because this is we could post we could we could we could do.
Yeah, we could do this all day.
But I just phoning to tell you thanks for the roses.
Like what a what a nothing premise for drawing for comic.
You know what?
But it's funny because it's like, oh, yeah, from real life, you know,
when when an old person is like, oh, thank you for the gift.
I'll just phone you up and like say that.
It's like, oh, it's like real life, but so uninteresting.
Why would you draw it?
Why would you make a comic about it?
You know, that's true.
This is very this is a very old person thing to do.
First of all, the landline.
The the bow, the like bow around the neck.
Yeah, just calling in to tell you thanks for the roses.
And also.
Oh, shit, I was going to say something else when, you know,
you say it's a boring premise,
but when you're a genius like me, all art is like that.
You look at everything and you say, what was the point?
Why? What a boring premise.
Why even play all the Mega Man games?
You like is exactly the same as Jennifer J. Exactly.
Oh, wait.
So Mega Man, just some robot masters attack and Mega Man.
She's got to stop them.
What a boring premise for a video game.
Who cares?
Just phoning to tell you thanks for the.
Sentience.
Yes, yes, yes.
You go to the yes to the frickin light capsule
in the hologram of Dr. Light.
Just phoning to tell you thanks for making me giving me free will.
Dr. Light.
Anyway, I'm off to shoot nuclear blasts at some Mavericks.
I'll see you by just, you know, just tedious, just tedious.
All right, this is great.
I guess we can't.
Hey, I made a I made a frickin dish.
Out of clay.
No. Out of food.
Would you put on the dish?
I cooked. I cooked lentils.
I heard lentils were high in protein, so I bought some and I cooked them
in my rice cooker and that worked out pretty well.
But I ever have lentils?
I think so. Are they the little green?
Yeah, they look.
Yes, yes, yes.
Um, they were like they came out of the thing.
They were like, OK, they smelled like OK.
They smelled like kind of earthy and otherwise neutral.
And I was like, yeah, all right, all right.
But you know what I had?
I had some bacon grease.
I put the bacon grease on the lentils and it was amazing.
It was incredible, perfect, perfect.
So glad I had that.
If I wish I had more bacon grease, but I used up all that I had.
If I had more, I would make more lentils and eat them.
It just went just went really well.
Just went really well.
You know, I could put like butter on them or something,
but wouldn't be as good.
I did. How do you?
What is the like taste of I know it's taste of bacon.
Like if you had like just oil, like a neutral oil,
what would you add to it to make it like bacon?
Would it just be salt?
Um, I mean, the most important thing would be salt.
Other. Yeah, there's not really.
I mean, you could put like some like mesquite flavor on if you had mosquito.
Mesquite, it's like the smoky.
Chemical or whatever.
Yeah.
You can get, you know, it's like to get, I think the way you do it
is like when you when you roast meat, like the smoke
gives it like a certain flavor and they you can sort of
they can like chemically extract that mesquite smoke flavor
and you can like put it on food.
So I mean, that might.
Is it different from just carbon?
Oh, God, I don't know.
Get some charcoal rub it on there.
I mean, a little bit.
Yeah, just a little bit.
I mean, not not charcoal.
But toast. Yeah.
Yeah, the saltiness is the most important thing.
But the like specifically bacon flavor.
I don't know if there's anything you can really do.
I guess you could just get some like pork, pork broth or something.
Anyway, I just wanted to rave.
Just want to rave about these lentils.
I'm going to start using that rice cooker more.
For lentils.
Cool.
Wait, hey, is it cold over there?
It's really cold here in New England.
I've heard it's very cold.
It's not actually it's quite warm right now.
The sun is up.
I blast in where it was.
I think it might be warming up now,
but like the last two days, it was like bitterly cold.
It was like 30 like it was like 30 degrees below zero,
like with the wind chill.
Hmm. Yeah.
Yeah, it was just like fucking nightmare.
I had I had to walk for like a minute to the bus stop and it was horrible.
I was waiting for it to get colder.
I wanted it to like we had a snow time.
It was a bit of snow, but I wanted it to be a bigger snow than that.
And I was like, oh, what if it, you know, what if it's not December?
What if it's like January, February?
Those are usually cold, but it's already warming up.
I don't know if it's going to get cold again.
Yeah, it was warming up here.
It never really got that cold this year.
It was warming up.
And then there was just a really sudden, super cold snap
just the last two days and like it's over and it didn't snow during it.
We had a couple of little snows this year, nothing, nothing too big.
It was just fucking brutal, just freaking brutal out yesterday.
Make sure you find like a fountain and you get a big slab of ice and you smash it,
pick it up and throw it, would recommend.
Interesting.
The other like a few weeks ago, it was like it wasn't snowy,
but it was very, very cold and there was like a bucket of water.
That we had outside just from like the party where we had like wine in it.
There was just water in it now.
And the top layer is like two inches of sheer ice, just a big slab.
So I picked it up and I dropped it and I got a crowbar
and I started swacking it and it was fun.
I would encourage that behavior.
Dangerous, dangerous.
I wasn't like like hitting as hard as I can because ice doesn't need that much pressure.
I was sort of tapping it and seeing it crack and then holding it up to the light
and seeing like all the prismatic effects, Isaac Newton shit.
Isaac Newton shit.
No, I get you. I get you.
Yeah, like ice, I guess.
Yeah, ice can be cool.
It can be cold. Sometimes.
Ah, OK.
But what else?
What else? I'm going through my list.
Well, I got something.
Oh, sure. So I forget what happened last PCP.
But. Oh, no.
Yeah, no, I can't remember.
Timelines are fucked right now, but I've been working on Clarissa Gunsmoke.
I've been hard at it.
Good. This past week and it's been going slow, but increasing in productivity.
So that's good.
I'm on track to, I don't know, get the chapter out by the end of the month,
but I want to see if I can increase my productivity over the next week or so.
Because right now it's a bit slow, but I'm doing it.
I'm doing it consistent.
I just need to at least stay consistent.
And that's my update.
Perfect Comic Party will, like, like begin in earnest once that is nearing completion.
And then I can be like, OK, time to actually draw the logo properly
and come up with like the system for the PDF and the contents page
and what fonts to use and stuff.
I have not done any Biscopades yet.
And the reason why is because this week I've pretty much finished
I've pretty much finished editing the book.
And I remember how I talked about how I was going to have to catfish the editor.
Well, I've successfully done that.
I've made a new account and I contacted the publisher again
and they don't know it's me.
Did you give them a different name?
Well, I made the new account funnily enough, the old account that I was doing
it was the the rowdy fuckers cop killers Alibaba account
and the one that we made the pins under.
And so like my name, my official name on the website was listed as rowdy fucker.
And so like people and like these these Chinese like correspondence
would they would address me as like dear rowdy fucker comma
because I mean that's was what it said my name was.
No, now I'm doing it as a cop killer.
And yeah.
And so now I'm just going to I'm just I'm not going to I'm not going to ask
them any questions. I'm just going to she gave me she gave me a new template.
It's slightly different from the old template she gave me whatever.
So I had just got to reform out all the pages to meet the new template.
And I got to finish the cover and then it's just like got to send that off
to her and tell her like, OK, make a test copy.
And I think I'll I think I'm going to try to get her to make two test copies
and like two different color schemes and like two different like page
like page weights like paper weights.
And I'll just see like which one is better.
Yeah. And that's the plan at the moment.
And so that's what I've been doing because like it's basically ready to go.
And that's very exciting.
And it's just for sure.
It's very tedious, very tedious to go.
I got to go through every page and reformat.
But you know what? That's that's that's that's the business.
That's give me a refresher. I'm going to I want to buy the book, obviously.
But I forget you had like the slime as a potential
like reward. Yeah, all the things.
Um, well, I don't know exactly.
You mean like what are all the like bonus?
Well, what are the things that could potentially be sent with the book?
Um, OK, well, there's going to be.
I'm going to give podrans.
I have green crystals.
I think I'm probably going to make that like a stretch goal.
Like if everyone if we hit a certain stretch goal,
everyone will get a free podrans, which although you might be maybe
if you wanted extra, you could buy some extras if you want.
I'm going to do.
Yeah, I'm going to offer the slime bottles because that's funny.
I'm going to offer some like the pins from the RFCK pin Kickstarter.
Instead of offering them on like a one by one base, I'm going to offer like a pack.
It'll be like for 20 extra dollars, you get like, you know, four or five.
Like like a set of like rowdy ones, killer ones or slime corp ones or whatever.
So yeah, you can get pins in like not in like huge bulk, but in like a slightly
more like bulk discount than just buying them one by one.
What else?
I think that's it.
I mean, what more do you want?
A physical copy of Phantom's revenge.
I can put in my NES.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
That's that's not that's not happening.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll probably do it like I'll probably.
Oh, OK. Oh, yeah, sure.
I'll probably do it like I'll probably have the baseline
goal for the Kickstarter just be hit a certain number of copies
and it'll be like just the comic.
And I'll probably have like a stretch goal
that's like if we hit the stretch goal, then I can also include the index
because the extra pages of the index will cost more to print.
Although really, I mean, I want to I want to include the index
because like I put a lot of work into it.
But I but I also like to set the the base goal as low as possible.
So probably split it up like that and make make the index technically a stretch goal.
I've been spending a lot of money on commission stuff
and I can create a plushies.
Oh, you bought that.
You got that commission from from Botster.
That was kind of expensive.
That was expensive, but hell, yeah. Yeah.
Worth I saw that that she retweeted that
Clarissa page. Was it this week that you tweeted that Clarissa page?
Or is that the one?
I think it was last I could have been this week.
No, I think it was last week.
I don't as I said, time doesn't make any sense.
I think it was this week.
I think it was this week and it was a good good page.
Yeah, it was a good page.
I was just sort of looking back at it because I was like,
I don't remember which side of the fucking belt her gun holster is on.
Let me check my own comic and I was reading it and it's like, you know what?
This is good. This is a good comic. It looks good.
I did it. I'll continue to do it.
And so I posted it on Twitter.
That's the spirit.
I posted it on Twitter.
It's like, you know what? I like this.
And then people like, wow, Pog.
And because of her retweeting it, I got like a bunch of followers.
And you're a thousand like a thousand likes or something.
A thousand something likes. Yeah.
That was a nice. That was a nice boost.
There was one guy.
There was one guy who responded to it, saying, oh, this is good.
I like this sort of thing.
And then we need more comics like this, this sort of action.
OK, weirdo. And then I under the the tweet,
I had like a link to the Clarissa Gunsmoke comic and he left a reply to that.
And he said, I like it.
But I feel it feels a bit misandrist how the bad guys are boys
and the good guys are girls.
That's so funny.
That's so insightful of him.
It was so amusing, like the misandrism, but otherwise pretty good.
And I'm like, what a.
What a freaking journey.
And it's just I couldn't.
It's I don't even really feel offended about it.
It's just sort of like what an odd specific.
I'm sorry to have about it.
How how do you get through?
How do you get through life?
It feels misandrist that the that the protagonist is a girl
and the and the and the and the bad guys are boys.
Yeah, let me find the tweet.
I'm so fucking sorry, you sick fuck.
OK, he says here it is twisted.
It's pretty nice.
Overall, I like it.
I love the girl with freckles and the action scenes,
but the comics have some.
Yes, the titular Clarissa almost all the dialogue is useless.
And it just slows the pace without adding anything, which is like.
I mean, I have like a bit of like agreement
with like some of the dialogue is just sort of like, ah,
this is cringe.
Sometimes it could have been better, whatever, fair enough.
But then the good girls versus bad boys
stuff really feels misandrist to me.
Which is I guess that's very funny, very funny.
It's not even like it's funny
because Clarissa is not necessarily a good character.
She gets called a murderer
because she killed those guys at the beginning and she is like,
she really didn't need to shoot them through the head
because they were rustling their horse.
No, she's not wholly good.
And she swears a lot and she's kind of a, you know, she's she's rowdy.
She's a ruffian. She's rowdy.
Yeah, I see. I see what you mean.
Yeah, you know, I just I just can't I just can't take a comment like that seriously.
Uh, Miss Andrews, Miss Andrews, like who says that?
Yeah, I just I'm I'm I'm taking I'm taking a back.
I'm taking a back by it.
Oh, oh, wait, wait.
No, somebody I remember now, somebody went to this guy's Twitter
and found that he he has a I mean, just look.
Click on this link, see what he's responding to.
OK, he says the man is completely savage, hate him or love him.
He is doing incredible stuff and then see what it's a response to.
Yeah. Yeah.
I I I.
Oh, yes, I put it put it in the I I I it makes perfect sense to me
that the kind of guy who would be upset seeing like a comic about like a girl
cowboy who is fighting against some evil boy cowboys and gets upset about that
is a Jordan Peterson guy that's like completely tracks.
Like the image of Jordan Peterson wearing a funny suit.
He's like, oh, he's savage.
He's doing incredible stuff.
I see. I see.
I wonder what I wonder what Jordan Peterson thinks about Bloodborne Cart.
I you think you think he's a fan?
Can't imagine Jordan Peterson playing a video game.
I feel like Jordan Peterson would really resonate with like.
The fucking themes of like corrupted motherhood and stuff in Bloodborne,
I think it would make him cry a lot.
I feel like the perversion of the nuclear family or whatever that's going on there
would like really wrestle him.
If you know what I mean,
like the Pokemon.
That's a deep. That's a deep PCP cut.
That's a deep. That's a deep PCP cut right there.
Shout out to the fans.
Shout outs. Shout outs to Russell.
I mean, amazing comment, amazing tweet,
amazing content for
the perfect comic party coming soon, coming soon, a store.
Yes, I've got a lot of stuff going on right now.
I got like my Clarissa and I've got February, which I'm trying to do every day.
And then there's Fire Emblem thing, which I'm probably going to leave
in the back burner. Once I have all of the the rums,
like my current focus is on that because I just I really want to figure it out
and have all of the the files work and be like, hell, yeah, I have every game.
I can play them at any moment and then I won't play them.
I'll play them maybe in March once February is over.
That's fair. Yeah, that makes sense.
I have a lot of stuff that I'm supposed to be doing.
I'm supposed to be working on Beescapades.
I'm supposed to be streaming battle network.
I'm supposed to be I think there's more than that.
I'm supposed to be be streaming right now.
I'm supposed to be drawing right now.
Mostly instead, I'm
trying to just trying to scramble and finish and feel good about the files
that I send to Frickin Alibaba.
And then what else? What else?
That's not the only thing I was doing this week.
Now, yes, it is.
Oh, God, help. I'm floundering.
I'm floundering. Floundering.
I don't remember. I don't remember what else happened.
Oh, what? I've been on Monday.
I've been working out, of course.
I am ripped.
That's why I'm eating oats to get even more ripped and jack.
Lentil ripped.
Yeah, that protein went to good use.
I'm strong now.
I should get back on the whole doing any motion at all thing.
It's good.
But what if I don't do it to be strong?
Oh, I played a bit more disco Elysium.
Oh, I haven't played that either.
That's another thing I haven't done for like three weeks.
I played a bit more.
I just finished day two and so day three is coming up.
Oh, I'm still ahead of you, though. So that's fine.
Yeah, yeah.
I went. What did I do?
I found the truck, the ladies truck with the ladies truck.
In the truck traffic jam.
There's like if you talk to the lady on the boat, she says,
please explain, please look into this drug smuggling potential thing.
Oh, well, we got to go look for it because now we know we're police officers
have to investigate.
So we're looking and then we find
the the fucking.
Sandpaper on the the.
What do you call it?
Foot pedal.
Oh, I don't know this.
Oh, OK, maybe I shouldn't maybe I shouldn't say too much.
There's a truck trying not to spoil too much.
But I mean, whatever, there's a truck
that once you look in, you see that sandpaper thing
and it corresponds to the odd shoe
at the scene of the crime that has a scuffed shoe print.
So it's like, oh, is it the light step?
I forget which one it was, but there's like the one shoe is scuffed
and the other one isn't.
And so it's like the sandpaper is rubbed down on that shoe.
So now you have a link to that person that you didn't know who it was.
And the person has that truck and I won't say anything other than that.
But that was a cool extra thing.
So I followed it up, but it's getting pretty late.
And I had to. Interesting. OK.
Yeah, I didn't find that, but that's that's neat.
There's a bunch of things I bought.
I bought a boombox, which is turns out to be important
because I needed to play a tape.
And so I could play it just on my like he holds it on his shoulder
like a funny classic boombox 80s sort of pose.
But it's like like a like a recording of people talking.
There's not exactly a dance moment.
And then did you know you're on you wouldn't have found the the kids by the church.
No, I can't get there because the drawbridge is closed because of the
the sign being smashed.
Did you? Yeah. Did you examine the sign stuff?
Yeah, I mean, I crossed the water lock.
No, but like there's there's like the tire tracks and then the the bent
sign and you look at it and you can be like deducing what happened.
I think so.
Hmm, maybe in Wednesday, they remove all that and so you can't examine it.
Maybe I mean, yeah, maybe I didn't because I mean.
Because the blockage was there was a sign that had been bent
and you look at it and you can see tie tracks on the sign and then there's a house.
And then before that, there's tie tracks on the road and you can deduce that.
Oh, a car drove over this this little ramp bit, landed on the roof
and then drove the roof of like the the pawn shop and then drove into the sign
and then landed on the other side.
No, that's what the blockage was from.
I did know that a car was involved.
I did not realize it drove over the roof of the pawn shop.
That's interesting.
OK, yeah, I don't know whose car it was.
But because I read a magazine earlier about like the the the racing stuff.
Oh, the Communist magazine, right?
Communist magazine.
Yes.
It has all of that article about the racing.
The one that like racing is like an evil capitalist.
It's an evil capitalist thing.
Blood sports, you watch it because you want to see a crash.
Right.
And so because I read that, I had an option to propose that it could have been
the famous driver from the magazine article that did that.
Oh, was was Kim asking you like, who do you think did this?
Who do you think did this?
And I was like, hmm, well, it could be it's probably this guy.
And he's like, I don't see any evidence for that.
Why would he be here?
Mm hmm.
And then you could you could you could push it.
You said, no, I'm absolutely certain.
Mm hmm.
I don't.
Yeah, I don't think I did that because it's like there is no evidence.
Why the hell would this famous guy be here right now?
I'll tell you what, I do know who's I do know who did that.
I didn't do that interaction.
But from other clues that I've gathered, I do know who did that.
So that's just that's all I'm going to say.
Haha.
Yes.
And then I went, I talked to the guy who's sitting on boxes selling clothes and sunglasses
outside the back of a truck.
And I bought some the sunglasses, the Samaritan guy.
Yeah.
And.
Oh, cool.
It's super cool of you to apologize for colonialism.
Yeah.
Now, please buy, please buy my wares.
This, the apricots, apricots, Susan T is a shithole, man.
He's right.
He's so right.
I also hate his home country.
Yeah.
I don't think I did too much else.
I went back to Titus Hardy to try and like prove myself to him again.
I failed again.
And then I tried it again.
I'm like, fuck.
I'm going to be cool in front of these guys.
And yeah, there's a few other things I don't want to spoil.
But that's, that was day two.
And then day three, I think I'm just going to go across the bridge and see what the fuck
is on the other side.
Oh, and the cryptid.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
The lady in the wheelchair who has a husband, a cryptozoologist.
Cryptozoologist's wife, yeah.
And she likes cryptids as well.
And if you talk to her.
Did she tell you about cryptids?
You can ask her about cryptids.
And I asked about are there invisible cryptids and she said yes.
There's one that has a high frequency thing.
And she talked about that.
And then.
Wait, is it the one that like is a high frequency sound?
Yeah, it is a high frequency sound.
It doesn't have mass.
That one.
That one's, that one's fucking dog shit.
That's a fucking dog shit story of a cryptid.
That one's, that one literally like makes me hate her a little bit.
Like that she would, that she would relate that story as though I'm supposed to take it seriously.
Well, but after listening to that, I went outside and I could hear it.
You know, like your character is like, oh, I think I hear the cryptid.
Wait, what?
But it's like probably in your head, but you can do one of those like thought things,
you know, when you have like a little diamond.
The little orbiting thing around your head.
Yeah.
I mean, that's what started it.
But like, you know, when you can internalize something.
Yes.
You have a thought and you internalize it.
I'm currently internalizing the cryptid that you can't feel or touch, but you can hear.
Oh, that's so funny.
I didn't get that.
Yeah.
I didn't ask for all the cryptids.
I said one cryptid, please.
And I said, OK, that one.
Yeah.
So I learned about that one.
I know.
I think I've pretty much completed like her whole like saga.
And yet I never I never got like a cryptid thought to internalize.
Even though she told me about a bunch more cryptids that were like less shitty than the
the stupid sound one.
I wonder what it's going to do to me.
That's I'm going to get turned into a fucking freak.
I'm going to be fucking hearing things demon.
Yeah.
What are the thoughts do I have?
I mean, I've got I've got the shit compressor.
I've got the long way home.
I've got the, of course, the Mazovian socioeconomics.
Obviously.
I don't know.
It's a bunch of just a bunch of crap.
I didn't really use those too much.
I mean, the Mazovian socioeconomics just is like, I just say communist stuff whenever
I can to get that sweet, sweet bonus exp.
Right.
You get bonus experience.
Yeah.
I think I had one.
I internalized.
I forget what it's called, where when I click on a green thing, like a green orb to pay
attention to something, I get money somehow, like little 10 cents every time I examine something.
Is that some kind of like some, you must be doing some kind of weird, like ultra liberal
thing.
Maybe.
I put on some shoes that were like these shoes like clue you into the economy or something
like these shoes make you like really make you want to make a lot of money.
I was like, no, get them off.
Yeah, I don't think I have that thought.
I haven't played in a while.
I got to get back into it.
Oh, and the last thing that I was trying to figure out is in the place where there's
the bear fridge, there's an ice cream maker.
And if you have a supreme crowbar of some kind, better than the pry bar that you can get from
if you have a super pry bar, you can open it with the relative ease.
And I don't know what the hell that is or where to find it.
And I assume it'll be across the bridge.
Yeah, I really want to open this ice cream machine for some reason.
I have not managed to open that ice cream machine.
I think I turned it off.
Did you turn it off?
Yeah.
Turning it off gives you a bonus to opening it, but it wasn't enough.
Right.
I forgot that I was supposed to be playing Disco Elysium.
I could have freaking beaten it at least once by now if I just put my damn mind to it.
I've been trying to wake up earlier so that I can get my work done so that I have time
to do things like Disco Elysium in the evening.
Yeah.
Because if I wake up at 1, I feel compelled to work a little later.
And then by the time I'm really relaxed, it's time for bed really.
Yeah.
Do I stay up late?
When you're staying up late, even though you could have the same schedule just shifted
a few hours ahead, it feels like after a certain period of darkness, there is no daytime.
You are off work.
You don't need to do anything.
I remembered something that I've been...
It's not that I've been really working, but I have been thinking and buying.
Thinking and buying stuff for when I...
Okay.
I've been trying to get the files for the book complete and finished now that I have
got another opportunity to do that.
And on top of that, I have been buying stuff for the video, for the announcement video.
Did I tell you what I want to do for the announcement video for the book?
No.
I didn't know you had a plan for that.
I do have a plan for it, and I don't exactly know how it's going to go.
I don't know exactly if it's going to work, but I have a bunch of ideas that I really want
to see happen.
I think what I want to do is I want to try and film it.
It's going to be like, I'm going to dress up as the cop killer, and I'm going to give
the announcement as the cop killer.
And I'm going to try and do some weird shit with...
I'm going to do it on a green screen.
I'm going to put myself in the cathedral or something.
I'm going to wear.
I'm going to color shift myself.
And I'm thinking, okay, I bought these big standing black lights, and I'm going to try
and arrange it.
I'm going to try putting...
I don't know.
I just kind of have to experiment with it and see.
But I'm going to try putting black light on myself.
I'm going to try doing it in the dark.
I bought some liquid quinine extract.
And what I would like to try and do with it is paint my teeth with it.
Paint my glasses and my teeth with it so that it will open my mouth.
Will that glow green?
It would glow blue, but I would color shift it to be green.
I just think that it might look bad.
I'm going to try and see how it looks.
But I just have this idea that what if I did that and it looked awesome?
That makes me think of this one...
I'm going to try it.
An animator guy who does...
Yes, I know exactly the one you mean.
I know exactly the one you mean.
Okay, the guy who has his bright glasses and he slightly morphs the shape of his mouth.
So it almost looks like stop motion or animated, but it's just footage of him that's sort of...
Yeah.
Yes, his bright glowing glasses and his white teeth.
His white teeth and his big huge expression with his mouth and jaw.
I really like how that stuff looks.
I'm going to try and go for a somewhat similar...
I don't want it to look cheap or shitty.
No.
So I'm going to...
Look, I just have some ideas and I'm just going to fuck around with them and see what looks good.
But I bought some high-powered black lights for it and I bought all these fluorescent fabric and quinine.
Because quinine glows blue and is theoretically non-toxic, so I could put it in my mouth.
Otherwise, I could draw on my teeth with highlighter.
It would probably be bad.
I feel like that would probably hurt you.
That's probably bad.
I mean, actually, painting my teeth with high-concentrate quinine, that might also be bad for me.
I'm not sure.
Yeah, definitely make sure you know what the hell you're doing.
I mean, quinine is not toxic.
You drink it.
It's a food that you eat, but that doesn't mean that it's good to put a high volume of it directly on your gums.
So we'll just have to see.
I'm pretty sure people have done such things with teeth before.
It must be some safe thing.
Actually, I guess teeth whitening and then ultraviolet light presuges every bright glow as well.
What does?
Anything white with ultraviolet light glows extremely bright in there.
Not everything white.
It depends on how white it is.
So if you have whitened teeth.
Yeah.
Your teeth do sort of shine bluish in a black light, but it's not that bright.
So, I mean, it's brighter if your teeth are whiter.
But even so, there's a limit to it.
So, coating them with something fluorescent, I don't know.
Honestly, it might look like shit.
It might not actually look good, and it might not even really be worth doing.
And I might just do something a little more conventional.
But the point is, the point is I'm going to do a green screen stuff,
and I would like to do a little green screen thing of like me as the cop killer,
make sort of like announcing the book and stuff.
That's the idea.
And I think some weird like black light green screen shit could make it look kind of weird
and like other otherworldly and school maybe.
You should get fucking spectral on and put it on your teeth.
I've watched this video.
James Lee. James Lee is the big white teeth guy.
James Lee, yes.
The animator.
Spectralon is the world's whitest white pigment.
Spectralon.
It looks weird.
Like it doesn't matter really how it's lit.
It's always as white as possible.
It feels like a video effect.
Hmm.
And Musso Black, he also talks about is like the pigment that absorbs the most light possible.
It's cool.
How does Spectralon look under a black line?
Cool, I don't know.
Also this stuff looks like it's like industrial.
This stuff does not look like it's just something you could buy in like a craft store.
No.
Lemau.
Highest diffuse reflectance of any known material.
Or coating over the ultraviolet visible or near infrared.
It exhibits highly Lambertian behavior.
It exhibits highly Lambertian behavior, Gib.
Lambertian.
Highly Lambertian.
If you can believe it.
Wow.
Wonder if it looks good under a black light.
You know I have some markers.
I was shining black light on some shit.
I was shining black light on some shit and I had a bunch of markers.
You know, like markers have like a white casing.
And they all look similar in a normal light, but a shan, the black light on them and one of them glowed.
One of them glowed and a couple of them didn't.
So it's not just about how white they are.
Something in the plastic of this one particular one, even though it looked similar, was like
United nuclear and European ultra glow in the dark phosphorescent paint.
It's super bright, non-toxic.
Non-toxic?
Does that mean I can paint my teeth with it?
Ooh.
It's like that episode of The Simpsons where Homer's got to weigh 300 pounds to qualify
for obesity disability pay to work from home.
And there's no more food in the house for him to eat to get over 300 pounds.
So Maggie makes him a donut out of Play-Doh.
And Bart says, Dad, it says non-toxic.
You know.
Non-poisoned.
It's not poison, technically.
Oh, $30 for a bottle of this glow-in-the-dark non-toxic.
I want to see how the quinine looks.
Freakin' tonic water looks.
It glows not super bright, but fairly bright-ish blue under a black light because quinine is fluorescent.
So I bought some concentrated drops of it.
The liquid is brown, which I'm not sure if that's going to affect it.
So I don't know if it's going to be super bright because it's highly concentrated quinine,
or is it going to be not that bright because it's kind of brownish and that'll dull the glow of it or whatever.
But it'll never cost me $10 to find out.
That's in the mail.
To be getting that later in the week, and then I'm going to try fucking around with filming myself against a green screen
and just fucking around in Sony Vegas and see what effects I can come up with.
I should get some better video editing software.
You know, sit on a chair with a bunch of wires dangling?
Yeah.
Something like that.
Something like depicted in the killer cathedral.
The green slime tubes.
I mean, yeah, that's the idea.
I was thinking.
I don't know.
I was just thinking.
Don't think so hard.
You'll hurt yourself.
I just think it would make an impression to just kind of do it in a sort of a green cartoony,
like a special effecty kind of way.
You know, just a little bit.
A little bit goes a long way.
Yeah.
Well, okay, I guess we'll see.
I guess we'll see how that turns out.
But I'm kind of excited to fuck around and try that soon.
What else?
Hey, did you watch the Velma show?
No, I saw some people talking about it.
I heard some things.
It doesn't sound very good.
Everyone says that it's bad.
I don't know if it's true.
I just asked because Trixie tweeted yesterday and said that I said that Velma is like me.
She said Velma is like Ben St.
If Ben St. were a woman, a girl of color.
And I just don't know what that means because I haven't seen the show.
It clips a bit where Velma is just like a cunt.
So I guess it just means that I'm a cunt.
Yeah, Velma is, as far as I know, unlikable on multiple, like different sides of the political spectrum.
She's like, I think Shaggy is not called Shaggy.
He's called something else.
Norbert?
Norville.
Norville, that's it.
I think that's it.
He's a cop.
Is he a cop?
Yeah, I think he's a lane in that respect.
That's funny.
And Velma, because it's like what if Scooby-Doo Mysteries, but there's murders involved.
So you can't really not involve the police when there's a fucking murder.
But she's just sort of comes across as, well, I guess I hadn't seen it.
I'm just going off of hearsay.
Yeah, I've just seen some clips.
I've just seen some clips, most of which make Velma look very unlikable.
She's friends with a cop and she's sort of like liberal in a way that leftists wouldn't like her.
And also right-wing people hate her because of what she is, but also she's annoying.
It's just like, what if you made the worst show?
So it's a compelling show.
It's like, wow, how bad could it be?
But I really don't care to look and find out.
There was no chance I was ever going to watch it, even if it was good.
So I'm not going to watch it to find out how bad it is just because people are saying it's bad.
That's what they want.
That's what they want me to do.
That's what Mindy Kaling wanted.
She wanted to make a show so bad on purpose that everyone would have to watch it to complain about it.
Well, I won't let her have that power over me.
Yeah, people were saying as well.
Well, this show sucks, but the writings went up because everyone wanted to know.
You fuckers.
I just want to understand what does Trixie mean by Velma herself is like Ben St. as a girl of color.
What does it mean?
She has glasses.
What would I be like as a girl of color?
Sexy?
Well, gee, I don't know.
Why don't you try it and find out?
Yeah, I guess there's only one way to find out.
All right.
Well, that was my question.
Oh, last week we opened up with the May and Ethan Ralph stuff, and I just want to give an update on that.
The update is, and I think we might have talked about this on stream, but the update is that May very quickly went back to Ralph and then Ralph immediately pivoted from saying,
I have no wife.
My wife is a whore.
I fucked my wife's sister, etc.
Immediately pivoted from that to, haha, it was all just a prank, actually.
It was a ruse and you all fell for it.
It was a trick to make Amanda's dad look foolish by having him think that his daughter ran away from me because I said that that's what happened.
What a great plan.
Was that really the stated goal?
I embarrassed myself horribly to make some other person feel like get duped.
Feel hopeful that his daughter would not marry this off?
Yeah, I don't know.
What's the end game of that plan, really?
I mean, in my opinion, obviously it was not a prank, and this is just like, oh, how am I going to save FaZe?
How are we going to sweep this under the rug?
Pretend this didn't happen.
Oh, let's pretend it was a prank.
And yeah, the stated goal of like, oh, we did it to trick her dad.
We did it to trick her dad into thinking something was happening by saying it was happening.
I mean, that's not a prank.
It's definitely not what happened.
Yeah, the stated punchline is, haha, we tricked you into thinking she ran away because we said she did.
And in fact, she actually did, and it wasn't a prank.
But, haha, we've made you look foolish by believing that's what happened.
I don't know.
Is there any information about what likely did happen?
Like, did they say anything?
Did they say anything?
Like, why did they run away and why did they come back?
Well, Ethan said that they had an argument.
Well, Ethan said that they had an argument, and also there was a report, and this is funny.
There were unrelated reports of an unruly passenger delaying like a flight in an airport, like at the same time that this supposedly happened.
Oh.
So it seems like there was some sort of, yeah, there was some sort of ruckus, an unruly passenger, whether that was May or Ethan is not clear.
A flight was delayed, May fled, ran away, and then later changed her mind and came back.
So were they going to fly somewhere?
And Ethan mentioned that.
I think they, yes, I think they had gone to New York.
I think they had, they were like, I think they were going to Rome.
They had like, they were like catching a connecting flight to Rome from New York, and it was in New York that this happened, and yeah.
So they were in Rome when she ran away?
No, they were in New York.
Oh, okay.
They were on their way to Rome, I think.
And so the, like, argument was like, don't you want to get pizza or pasta when you get there?
I don't know.
Nobody said anything about what the argument was actually about.
We can't go on a flight that has mandatory masks.
I ain't going on this flight, probably something like that.
You know, May was at January 6th, so like she should be on the no fly list.
Oh my God, I forgot.
You know that?
Yeah.
I don't think, I mean, it doesn't surprise me that she was, but I don't think I really knew that.
She, I mean, she didn't, she wasn't like personally like breaking into the Capitol building, but she was there in Washington D.C.
And I know this because literally on the day that it happened, I don't know why, but I saw Ethan tweeted that like he had a court, that May was at there and that there was like something happening.
So I literally tuned into the kill stream to watch it and May was there live.
And like May had to like, had to like pee or something?
Like she had like forgotten to go to the bathroom.
So instead of like being there at the Capitol building to like report on what was happening, she was like looking for a restroom like the whole time.
Like on stream?
Like that was the stream?
I think Ethan at some point was like, okay, all right, you know, go do that and like we'll get, we'll call you back again when you are composed and can report on what's happening.
And then she's like, she missed it.
She missed the, it happened for hours.
What do you mean?
Well, she was, I don't know.
She like saw it from a distance starting and then she was like, I gotta go find a bathroom.
And then she was like looking for a bathroom for a long time or something.
Oh, you missed the fucking riot.
You missed freaking January 6th.
You missed the insurrection.
She could have made the difference.
She personally could have intercepted Nancy Pelosi and AOC before they made it to the tunnels.
Could have changed everything.
Trump would still be president.
Dang.
If only.
My president.
Well, okay.
I think I've, how long ago?
Okay, we're only on two hours.
What else is on my topic list?
Cat Fishing, my publisher.
Ethan, Velma, Lentils.
Oh, have you seen freaking Infinite Seinfeld?
No, I heard about that.
There's multiple layers to this.
Oh my fucking god.
So first, from what I understand, it is an artificially intelligent, procedurally generated series of Seinfeld scenes or episodes.
Yes, scenes, basically.
Right.
And it sort of kind of makes sense, but not really.
I watched like several hours of it the other day.
Is it just on a permanent live stream?
Yeah, it's, I think it's called Watch, Watch Me Forever is the Twitch channel.
And the show itself is called Nothing Forever.
And yeah, it's just infinitely, procedurally generated conversations of, well, it's the Seinfeld gang hanging out in like Jerry's apartment and Elaine's apartment.
And I think it's Elaine's apartment.
And sometimes Jerry does a stand-up routine.
And that's it.
And yeah, there's no...
I've clicked on it there.
There's no...
Yeah, there's no like episode plots.
It's just like conversations that they have.
And sometimes, I mean, they always like sort of make sense.
They always like are coherent.
But, you know, it's AI generated, so it's like pretty off.
It's really funny though.
It's really compelling.
And like, it's not even just the dialogue that's like procedural.
It's like the characters like walk around and like their walk cycles are procedural too.
And like they'll just like, they'll like walk around like bent over at like 180 degrees at the waist and stuff.
Or like they'll sit down and then like they'll try to walk out of their chair, but like they won't stand up.
So like their little feet will move as they'll just like be sitting and like they'll just like be walking through the air like while they're still sitting.
Stuff like that.
The stuff...
Okay, their personalities are all like off.
They're not really the Seinfeld characters.
They're all like really, really wholesome and really like enthusiastic about everything.
They don't tell jokes.
I mean, in the logic of Nothing Forever, all four of them are comedians.
Like they all have one job.
They all work for the same like joke company or whatever, which is different from the actual show.
But they never actually tell jokes.
Like when Jerry does a stand-up routine, the routine will usually just be like,
Hey guys, can you believe how divided our country has become?
You know, it's too bad that politics is so divisive these days.
But I wear a mask whenever I ride public transit.
Okay, would you like to hear a joke?
What did the fish say when it hit a wall?
Damn, okay, that's my set.
Thank you, and I'll see you soon.
And that for several hours you watched.
Well, yeah, a scene will usually last like a minute or two.
And yeah, it's just really, it's really...
I saw one where like Elaine had just discovered that there's no Santa Claus.
And Jerry was like opining on like, damn, if there's no Santa Claus and there's...
What else? Is there no Easter Bunny? Is there no Tooth Fairy?
Are they just lies that we've been told?
And then he ends it with only one way to find out.
And then the scene ends.
No, he said like, yeah, are they just lies they tell us to keep us believing in the magic of life?
Well, only one way to find out.
What was he going to do?
That is pretty funny.
Yeah, it's stuff like that.
I was watching just for a second there and somebody said, I think it was George.
He said, hey, I thought of something.
It was a pregnant pause and then a laugh track.
Yeah, the laugh track seems almost random.
I saw a bingo card for like things that happen.
And one of the things on the bingo card is that specific, what did the fish say when it hit the wall?
Damn.
They say that all the time.
Another thing that's not was not on the card, but that I noticed happening all the time is somebody gets a part-time job as a clown.
George got a part-time job as a clown.
I saw one where Jerry had just gotten a part-time job as a clown and George...
Oh, there was one where the mayor, they talked about how the mayor had gotten a part-time job as a clown.
But George asks Jerry, hey, how's the part-time job as a clown?
And Jerry's like, oh, it's a good opportunity to make some money on the side.
And George's like, what are you going to do with all the money?
And Jerry says, I was thinking about investing in a comic book shop.
Could be a great opportunity to make some real money.
And it's like, that's like the most...
I don't know, just imagine thinking that that's how you're going to make money.
You want to make some serious cash?
One, get a part-time job as a clown.
Two, invest your earnings in a comic book shop.
Like it's a surefire way, surefire hit.
The weirdness of the AI really works with Seinfeld.
It seems like a sort of stupid idea that somebody would come up with in a sitcom.
It does work.
Okay, the other thing is they're all really enthusiastic and down for anything.
Someone will suggest something totally asinine.
Like, why don't we start a part-time job selling cardboard boxes?
And Elaine will be like, that's a great idea.
I think we should do it right now.
I can't wait to start our new business.
It's so many of the episodes are like,
they just heard about a new restaurant that opened.
And they're like, wow, sounds amazing.
What food do they offer?
I hear they have some really weird dishes.
They have spaghetti on sushi.
Spaghetti sushi? That sounds incredible.
I can't wait to try it.
We should get a reservation this weekend.
Yeah, rules. It fucking rules and I love it.
But I learned, I saw on Twitter a snippet of an interview with apparently the developers.
And it seems like the developers of Nothing Forever
genuinely think that this is the next step in entertainment for real.
They think they can actually make a real show like this.
And not have it be like a hilariously bad, like meta commentary.
Yeah, I saw that.
They think they can do this for real.
They set out to make, what did they say?
Not a spiritual successor, but like something-something.
I think they said they wanted to make,
they wanted to generate a show that would infinitely generate infinite content of Netflix level.
I think they specifically said like Netflix level quality.
Like this is the first step towards live streams of fake Seinfeld or whatever.
Yeah, well this is the first.
I think in their mind, you would, yeah, you would open up Netflix
and you would navigate to a show and the show has no actors, has no writers, has no nothing.
It's just completely perceived and you just hit it.
And there's just an infinite number of potential scenes it might show you that would entertain you.
They said it's like, what if a show, your favorite show didn't have to end?
Like that's a good thing.
Like that works for every type of show.
Like it kind of works for Seinfeld because Seinfeld is just a show about whatever.
It's about these characters doing stuff, having scenes.
It works in the sense that like Seinfeld is a status quo show where like everything returns to the status quo at the end of the episode.
Yeah, but beyond that, it's funny and entertaining mostly because of how weird and not human it is.
Yes, yes, that's what I'm going to say.
Like if this is meant to be a proof of concept that like, yeah, we can design a show that just infinitely creates itself as entertainment.
It's like, it's literally like proof against that.
It's proof of the opposite and it's because, yeah, people like nothing forever and it's funny and I like it.
But the reason I like it is not because it's good.
Like the reason it's funny is like the obvious ways that it fails to be what it's trying to be.
And genuinely, the fact that it was made as a sincere attempt to like create like just straightforward, unironically good like compelling content like you would see on TV is like what makes it even funnier.
Because it's like they really tried, like they really were actually trying to make a real show and this is what they came up with.
And it's like, yeah, all of the appeal is just in how it falls short of being what they wanted it to be.
And knowing that they wanted that is like, I love it.
It's like they must know.
They must know that like this is not a real show and that people are watching it because of how like wrong and off it is.
I think they're not differentiating between views and quality.
Like people don't view everything for the exact same reason.
I think that they must know that they fell short.
They know that they fell short of the goal.
I was just watching it right now and they had a moment where it had an establishing shot of the apartment and then Jerry's microphone by itself for like 10 seconds, no Jerry at the comedy club or whatever.
And then it cut back to the apartment.
That's awesome.
This is just a scene where Jerry wasn't at his set.
A scene with no content.
And then it goes back to some other thing.
That rules.
Yeah, Jerry's sets, they don't have jokes.
Most of them are just him sort of like wistfully opining on like the state of life and like the nature of being alive and stuff.
I saw one where like him and Kramer asks him if he thinks there's life after death and Jerry's like, well, not much of a philosopher.
But I definitely think there must be more to life than what we see before us.
I definitely think that we must go somewhere better when we're gone from this world.
This is the end scene.
That's like such a Jerry thing to say.
They must know, they definitely know that this is not like Netflix show quality stuff, that they did not successfully make that.
But they might see the people watching and think, aha, they're watching.
And yeah, the show is kind of funny because it's unintentionally bad now.
But the fact that they're watching it all says that like, okay, this can work.
That we're onto something, even though really in my opinion, yeah, the spectacle is in the failure.
I don't really think it's a successful proof of concept that they could make a real show like this.
A lot of time there's like, there's so much shit on TV that sometimes you'll just put on the TV and you don't really care what you're watching and it's all daytime television.
It's low quality.
It's not really that great of anything.
It's just sort of whatever.
And so it's not that hard of a bar to reach, to make some mildly interesting AI generated stripes that you could just put on in the background.
But the idea that this is the future of the high production show is very silly.
You could probably make a somewhat similar argument saying that daytime soap operas almost are.
I mean, they're not literally AI procedurally generated, but they are just kind of whatever they could fucking throw together.
Shot on an incredibly shoestring budget and an incredibly high turnaround.
So it's not like there was like a high, yeah, there's not like a high bar of quality.
It's just sort of a similar to what if there was some funny livestream, some funny television network that, you know, I just need a bit of this and you turn it on.
I can imagine that being the future like, oh, let's check out what's going on on the AI channel.
It has a future, I'm sure.
But like, I don't know.
I don't think it's going to replace shows made by meticulous crafted stuff.
I could see it.
I could see it maybe being involved in some content of some kinds.
It's not going to replace like a scripted.
I mean, all AI tools can be used in conjunction with curation by a human.
Yeah, yeah, that's how they're used usually.
I think that the gimmick with this is that it's automated and it just goes.
Yeah, there's no curation here at all.
You put the characters in and you train the AI a bit so it has a bit of like differentiation between the characters and you set like points where the characters can walk,
points where they do the animation for sitting and you just set all the parameters up and you just let it go.
And I'm like, yeah, I guess like this is this is funny because it's so fucked up.
But I wouldn't watch like a series.
Okay, I mean, it makes sense as a line that just goes on forever.
I did leave it on and watch it passively for like four or five hours.
So I mean, I'm not knocking it.
I genuinely like it.
Yeah, but I like it for being weird.
Yeah.
I guess our main problem is with the creators taking themselves too seriously.
I mean, I like that they think that they were really trying to do something.
I like it.
I like it as a novelty.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't like it.
If every show was like this or even like multiple shows were like this, I wouldn't care because like, you know, you watch it and you're like, oh, I get it.
They kind of like randomly combined things and oh, the characters are sort of doing their patterns again.
You know, like the AI can sometimes surprise you by what it comes up with, but it surprises you in like a different way than like a scripted show.
Like a scripted show would might subvert your expectations purposefully.
Whereas the AI will might subvert your expectations by like combining things inappropriately in a way that sort of doesn't make sense.
I think also that this is obviously piggybacking a lot off of the popularity and notoriety of Seinfeld.
You know who these characters are normally and so seeing them different has a layer of comedy to it.
If it was like brand new show, brand new concept, but all AI generated, it wouldn't have nearly as much mean potential and comedy value.
Yeah, a lot of the value, a lot of the entertainment is in seeing.
Yeah, is in seeing like, imagine Jerry.
Imagine Jerry just being like, hey guys, welcome to my set.
Can you believe that 2020 had a global pandemic?
Never thought I'd have to wear a mask.
Haha.
All right.
Anyone got any funny stories?
Great stories, everyone.
All right, I'll be here all week.
Have a great night.
Yeah, it's the gap between that and what Jerry actually is and what he shouldn't do.
It's the same as like edited Garfield strips.
Like Garfield without Garfield or all those other things.
I think some people have tried to make AI generated comic strips of Garfield.
Sometimes it works.
Yeah.
A lot of the time not.
I think there's like taking individual panels and randomly putting them in front of one another.
Sometimes it's funny.
Oh, just like randomly like like mashing panels together.
Yeah, take three random panels and put them together.
I've seen that one before.
Yeah.
I mean, that's not really AI.
That's just a randomization procedure, whatever you call it.
But it's the same sort of thing.
It's like, you know what Garfield should be.
And so the comedy comes from how much it deviates.
Yeah.
I suppose they do sort of say that way.
They say, what if your favorite show never stopped?
If they made, if they made like, oh, Breaking Bad.
But like in this style with like funny little 3D avatars of Walter White and stuff.
Okay.
Then it would not be good as a Breaking Bad show, but it would be funny because I'd seen Breaking Bad.
And this is like, haha, this is so not like it should be.
Part of, but part of what part of what works about this, I don't think you could do it with Breaking Bad
because part of what makes this work is that Seinfeld is so iconically like set in Jerry's apartment.
Right.
Like so much of the show happens.
Like it's these four characters in this specific one setting or maybe like one or two other settings.
They should have had one at the bar at the restaurant where they have like breakfast in the booth.
They, what would make Nothing Forever Perfect is if they had one more set and it's them sitting in the freaking booth.
I think you could do it with Breaking Bad.
It's not because like Breaking Bad.
It's just because it's a serious show and then having them do like just random conversations that don't make sense is comedy.
In the same way that this is comedy.
I think, okay, I think that the fact that Breaking Bad takes, has like a continuous arc and the status quo changes every episode
and that the story takes it through like many, many different settings over the course of the show.
I think that if you tried to do this with Breaking Bad, it would be much harder to recognize any individual scene as, oh, this is Breaking Bad.
Whereas with Seinfeld, it's really obvious when you look at it like that's Jerry's apartment.
This is Jerry and Elaine and George and Kramer.
I mean, you got Walter's house.
What I'm watching is Seinfeld, but it's wrong.
You got iconic places.
You got Los Poyos-Hermanos restaurant.
You got Walter White's house and the desert.
Like you could have three sets with, you know, cars in the desert or like the lab, Gus's lab.
And it could just be Walter and Jesse talking.
I think it wouldn't be like as good-fitting, but I feel like people would still tune into that just for how stupid it is.
I'm not saying you couldn't do it, but I think it works better with Seinfeld.
It's funny that they seem to think that you could apply this idea to shows unlike Seinfeld.
Yeah.
Because that's what is implied by what they say, like your favorite Netflix show.
There's lots of types of Netflix shows.
It's like this only works.
The other thing about it is that this works with Seinfeld because all Seinfeld is is just characters talking.
So all you have to do is generate an AI text conversation and then have a text-to-speech program read the lines.
Stuff happens in Breaking Bad.
It would not feel anything like an episode of Breaking Bad if they try to do this with Breaking Bad.
No, but I'm saying it would be funny still.
People would find the mean quality.
Yes, it would be funny.
It would be funny in the way that the characters would be acting in a weird, silly way.
But with this, it's like what the characters are doing, it does kind of feel like it's Seinfeld
because what they're doing is the same thing that happens in Seinfeld,
which is the characters just stand around in an apartment and yammer at each other.
It gets close.
Seinfeld is like you get about as close.
You know what? They could probably do it with Star Trek too.
They could probably do this with Star Trek and it would work really well.
Because Star Trek is just about characters standing around and talking.
Like how do they do AI-generated techno babble?
Oh, I think freaking duh.
That might be a little bit of a challenge.
Because there's like two different types of talking.
There's talking about what's happening, the events happening and character drama,
which is you'd need two different bits to have that
because it wouldn't make sense if somebody says techno babble
and the other person is talking about their feelings, although it would be funny.
I actually think you'd probably have like a pretty robust,
like a system for procedurally generating some techno nonsense.
You just freaking combine adjectives and nouns into the dilithium fusion reverberator
has been fractured and requires whatever.
And you just make that shit up and it doesn't even really matter what it's called.
You can talk about it because like it's going to do something in space.
I don't know.
Yeah, I mean that might be.
I enjoy this feeling of the chat like going nuts.
There's 10,000 people watching right now.
You know, I tried watching it on Twitch and I couldn't get it to do it
without a delay between the chat and the stream.
And that kind of made the chat sort of useless.
And also I kind of didn't like the experience of having the chat like roaring
every time like something really weird happens.
I kind of just liked having the little video.
I was literally playing it like in Discord.
Yeah, I mean you can turn the chat off, you can like push it to the sides.
Yeah, I liked it with chat off.
I liked it with just, they're just saying weird stuff.
Having like totally pointless conversations.
That was how I was enjoying it.
I wonder if AI could generate a progress in this podcast episode.
Oh my god.
We're just two people talking.
We don't even have a set.
It would let it, can we, can we get on?
Holy shit.
Can you email them, give us the source code?
I don't know how, imagine if we could do that.
We could make it a bonus episode.
We could have like a 10 hour fully AI generated bonus episode.
There's no way it could be anything other than awful.
There's no way.
It would probably not be good.
I suppose there's enough.
But nothing forever isn't good.
No, but like, hmm, I wonder how they get, they have transcripts, right?
I think.
They have transcripts for each character and they feed the transcripts into the machine.
They don't like take the audio file of the episode and put that in.
No, I think they have, I think they have script, they have written scripts.
So like we would need a transcript of the procrastinated podcast episodes of you talking
and me talking in order to like feed that into an AI to make it, make any sense at all.
And that's a lot of work unless Google like auto captions works.
Doesn't YouTube like auto caption?
Yeah, but like, it's not that great.
I know it's not that great, but like no one's going to manually caption it.
Here's how I think, if it could be done at all, yeah, I think it would have to be auto,
we'd have to use the YouTube auto captions and we would have to feed that into some,
I don't know, I don't even know how.
If there's anybody in the audience who wants to do that.
If anyone knows how it could be done.
We'll pay.
We'll pay the proceeds from the bonus episode or a flat fee or something.
I would pay someone.
Cause that's funny.
That's worth money.
I would pay someone.
$50.
I don't know.
I know.
I mean, either way, I'm not going to fucking do that because that's,
I got so much other stuff I'm doing.
I think it is theoretically possible.
I know that it could be a lot of work and I'm not willing to do a lot of work on it.
But if someone knows a way that it could be done with only a moderate amount of work,
I might, I do think it would be really funny.
And I'm sure it is doable.
It's just a question of how hard, how much would be involved in it.
Yeah, okay.
I got canceled for my AI takes on Twitter.
I got unfollowed by everybody.
They hate me.
Oh, what'd you say?
Well, I said, um, I said that I think that if a computer can do it,
then a computer should do it.
And by it, I mean jobs.
And, uh, yeah.
Okay.
Well, Cheesy retweeted a thing about an anime studio that was using AI for its background art.
Oh yeah, I saw that.
It was like the boy and the dog.
The boy and the dog.
Or whatever.
Which is my intellectual property.
I have dog and boy in, in canon story.
Hey, yeah.
Um, so it's funny because in the, in this context, like they haven't actually replaced their background art department entirely.
Like they're using basically an artist draws the background and then an AI sort of like touches it up.
And then an artist like takes the AI version and like touches that up into a real background.
And it's like kind of like, why even bother have the AI step?
Maybe it saves maybe like some labor.
Two hours.
I guess it saves.
I assume it must save some labor or they're trying it out to see if it saves labor or something like that.
And like, so okay, they really haven't even actually reduced the, the workforce that much by doing so.
My hot take.
Though.
And I think I, and I'll stick with this.
Like if you, if you could get rid of human artists, like if a, if a computer could just like generate a background and it would look good, I think they should just do it.
I think that's good.
And they should do it.
And I don't care if people lose their jobs.
Fuck them.
Fuck artists.
Yeah.
I don't feel the same vitriol for artists having jobs.
But the, the idea that like if computers can do things.
Yeah.
That's nice.
I don't have vitriol for artists having.
It's more tools in your tool belt.
Right.
And if you still want to draw, you can.
It's just, there's no money in it, I guess.
I don't.
And everyone will be out of work.
Yeah.
And that's, it's, it's separate issue, which is a capitalism issue.
Right.
I, okay.
I really think, I really think.
I don't have, I don't have vitriol for artists having jobs.
I think it's nice if someone has a job.
I think that's great.
But, but I really think, I really think when I see people like cheesy, specifically cheesy,
I'm talking about cheesy specifically here and only him.
That's not true.
I see a lot of people doing this.
I think when people get upset about AI stuff, it's coming, it's coming from a place.
I'm sorry.
I don't, I don't think it's, I don't think it's pure.
I don't think it's pure and logical.
What do you mean pure?
I mean that I think it's, I think, I think they're just, I think when people say, oh
no, AI has taken our jerbs, I think they're just being like, oh no, I wanted to get paid
to do that.
Oh no, I wanted to get paid to do that job.
I wanted to paint a background and get paid by a studio.
Oh no, you mean they're going to need one less fricking artist at Nickelodeon Studios
drawing backgrounds on SpongeBob?
That could have been my cushy animation gig.
It's not a cushy job.
It is.
It's just drawing backgrounds.
Working at Nickelodeon?
Well, yeah, I mean, better than working independent, but you know what I mean.
Okay, okay.
It's not like a perfectly secure job.
Okay, I mean sure, I mean sure.
But it's a job people want.
Yeah.
And all I'm saying is when people say, oh no, an AI can do it, I think that they're saying
it because that's a job that they wanted and they thought that could have been me, but
now it can't be you because a robot can do it.
Yeah, all of that is true.
And I get being salty about that, but frankly, I think that if a computer could do what you
were going to do, then fuck you.
There's no point doing it.
Do something else.
I think if you can be replaced by a computer, yeah, you should be replaced by a computer.
Die.
But I like money though.
You like money.
Listen, I do like money.
I do like money.
All right, I'm being a little hyperbolic.
Computers, I don't know.
If a computer can paint a background, then why do we need a human to do it?
First of all, a human can't.
A computer can't.
The background's on Dog and Boy, they don't even look that good.
Oh yeah.
And frankly, yeah, you can see what AI generates and sometimes it generates a decent image,
but usually it only does that by stealing.
Usually it only does that because it's stealing and copying from other pieces and that's bad.
I think it's entirely bad.
The whole library is based off of other things it's seen.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, that's kind of why, well, let's see.
I mean, when one of these artists on Dog and Boy, they draw the preliminary and then they feed that in.
I mean, I guess the AI is using that as a basis and then they're filling it in with like texture?
Okay.
I guess they've seen that are similar.
Oh, they recognize this as a tree.
So what do I know a tree looks like?
Let's find something that matches and then random numbers make it not a literal copy of what I've seen before and then put it in.
That's how I assume a lot of the decision-making works in an AI.
Do you think that it's grabbing that data from people posting on DeviantArt and stuff?
It depends.
I think DeviantArt has a system where you have to opt out of your art being added to AI libraries.
I think it was cheesy or maybe it was someone else that was saying that music is a lot more highly regulated
and AI-generated music draws from a much more tightly controlled database of stuff that is not copyright protected
because there's much more stringent copyright laws in place for the use of music
and there should be something in place like that for art as well.
Because I think that if it were highly regulated and if there were a higher degree of confidence
that a company, an animation studio, the AIs that they were training were not basically just stealing data from independent artists
and people that were just posting their stuff online for free.
I don't think that should just be fair game for any corporate entity to just take.
If it were more tightly regulated and they were confident that that weren't happening,
I would be like, hell yeah, replace the artists.
It doesn't make any sense not to use a tool that can just eliminate grunt work from a task like that.
It's what I've always been saying with this argument is that the root cause of the problem is the capitalism that you need money
and the people who own the IPs are the ones who profit off of the shows being created
but there's no workforce so all of the creative people, some of whom have work that is being used in AI stuff without their consent,
are not making money and so if AI-generated things did not have copyright,
which I think there's a chance that that could happen because you know the monkey that took a selfie?
That lawsuit set the president that the person who owned the camera doesn't have copyright over that image
because the copyright needs to be, the artist needs to be of a human.
Monkey has the copyright but copyright, you know, it's a monkey, you can't ask it permission for things like that.
So it has to be, they set a precedent that has to be a human to make the art that has the copyright.
In order for copyright to be real.
And so there's an argument that AI-generated stuff is similar and that there is no human involved so you can't copyright the work
and if you can't copyright it, you can't really, well, you can profit from it but you can't protect it from other people doing it.
Which I think would be better than some rich people who own intellectual property
continuing to make money while all the artists who got them there with the work they made previously
and the brands that they made popular just get thrown away.
That's sad and it sucks and I don't want people to get rich.
So fuck them.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not against the tools being created and used but it's the fact that money is the driving force
and capitalism forces people to need money that makes it like a problem that makes people upset that like it causes all of the strife in the situation.
If you didn't need the job, if you didn't need to be paid, then it wouldn't be even a problem.
That you didn't need to get the job and a computer could have done it.
Here's, you know, I guess I just, I think about like, I know, you know, I say fuck artists because that's funny.
But back in the day, right, back in the day, people working on, I don't know, the freaking railroads or whatever, right,
the steam engine or whatever, maybe put some of them out of business or something.
You know, the automobile, the creation of the automobile probably put a lot of, you know, horse-related workers out of business or whatever.
Blacksmiths.
Right, and like that's not good.
It's like, it's not good that those people lost their jobs.
But I mean, that doesn't mean that I'm against, like, that doesn't mean that like the creation of these new devices were like bad,
or that they should have been like banned in order to like prevent that from happening.
Yeah, that's the thing I don't like is the idea that we should try to suppress and ban the use of the tool.
Right.
I think that you should go for the people who can line their pockets with the money and just say,
you can't have copyright because it's AI.
Yeah.
That would stop a lot of the greed and a lot of the bad shit.
I agree.
I think I agree with you.
Yeah, I think I agree with you.
I mean, if we abolished copyright, if we abolished copyright, then like what, like sure,
a corporate entity could use AI to maybe steal an artist's work in order to generate content,
but they wouldn't even own the intellectual property rights associated with that content that they created with that stolen work.
So that's better.
It's not as simple because like if you got a lot of money and you can put things in front of people and you can sell merchandise,
like how does not having copyright stop you from profiting?
It doesn't.
If nobody has a copyright for something and everybody makes a product, then the person who has the largest amount of power and capital to make a product that everyone can see and buy,
they will make the product that people will buy that one.
So it's a half measure.
So is actually the answer to just to be more copyright, like enforce copyright more strictly and protect?
Yeah, that's the other way to look at it is to make it so that artists are protected by copyright so people can't put things in AI things.
But I think that that fundamentally that would completely destroy basically every AI generating thing unless people opt in,
which will be a very small amount of people unless they can.
No, that's not true.
What about like public domain?
Well, yeah.
A lot of work is in the public domain and AI could be trained on anything that's in the public domain.
Yeah.
I mean, the issue is for currently working artists.
They don't want to lose their ability to continue to make money, but stuff in the public domain is in the public domain because the person who made it is dead for a long time.
Okay.
Currently working artists.
Yeah, but I mean, how do people have a right to get that cash?
No.
Oh, I mean, yes, but also no.
Um, do I mean, do people have a right to get the cash?
Well, do people have a right to live?
Yeah.
How?
I don't know.
They aren't giving it for free.
They need money for it.
So they therefore have a right to be able to make money.
True, but that does not mean that they have a right to have a job as a background artist at an anime studio.
I agree with that.
I just think that the world that that would lead to is everybody having the most boring possible job that they hate because all the creative jobs is taken by AI.
I mean, that's literally already the world.
That's literally already the world.
We're already there.
Not really?
What do you mean?
I mean, yeah.
Okay.
There are a miniscule amount of jobs as a background artist at an anime studio, but not there's not that many.
There's really not that many of those.
And if there were even fewer, I don't know.
So what?
I think this is just your bias against background artists.
It's not.
You hate drawing backgrounds.
You think people who draw backgrounds are freaks.
It's just, it's just an example.
It's just an example of something that, okay, I use background artists because I don't, I think that's one of the few things in the art world that like an AI could even do anything for.
That's just, most things, most things that artists do in the real world are not things that an AI is poised to take over doing.
There's other jobs that are going to be obsolete by AI like way before animators or storyboard artists or script writers or whatever.
So you're saying that it's dependent on how close AI is to taking over.
So potentially if AI could do more, then more jobs should be lost for people.
I think, I mean, if a computer can do a job, why should a person be made to do it?
Because it muddies the waters when who decides who gets paid.
And that's the only problem.
What do you mean it muddies the waters when they decide who gets paid?
No, it doesn't.
Because if the AI made it, does the person who coded the AI get ownership of the work and get paid through that?
Okay, I see.
Or is it the person who made the art that gets fed into the AI or like who is it?
And it's a question and then it usually will become the CEO of whatever company is the one who owns it because they can just say that.
And so rich super people will become big and strong.
And I don't like that.
Okay, okay.
Sounds bad.
I see what you're saying.
You're saying that you think that the more AI is used in order to create intellectual property content, the more that consolidates the content and its creation.
Basically, the more that consolidates the means of production under the ownership of the owners.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
You can see that there is not any sort of push to make an AI that can roam a company as a CEO.
Okay.
That's true.
It would be funny if they could do that and like an AI could like take over as a CEO position and make better decisions and all the CEOs go out of business.
An AI?
And they're all scrabbling on the floor like, no, no, I was in charge.
A computer can never be held accountable.
Therefore, a computer must never make a management decision.
Okay, I see what you're saying.
And I think I agree with it.
Okay, I do agree with you.
Level on a societal level, yes, an AI being a thing that a person owns or at least has the rights to operate does basically consolidate power in the owner or operator of that thing, which is bad.
Yes.
So the idea that you can't copyright work that is made through AI is like a step against...
A step that makes it less appealing to the ruling class to invest so heavily in it, I guess.
Okay, okay, okay.
I guess I'm just...
Okay, so in terms of like an economic societal level, yes, I guess it is bad.
However, in terms of like what we're here to do is to make a show or is to make art, right?
I don't know how much I like the idea that, oh, well, okay, we must not use this thing.
We must not use this thing to do it, even if it would be more effective.
We can't use it because if we used it, then the economics would be worse and people wouldn't be paid and the resources would not be distributed as equally if we use this thing.
I agree.
That's why I keep saying it's the capitalism problem.
If people didn't need money, if it didn't matter, then I don't think there would be a problem.
Yeah.
I mean...
If it was just you live your life and you draw a little drawing, you don't need a job drawing for a big thing.
You can have a smaller team of people having a vision and use AI computers to make a big thing.
It's like, oh, this is a cool animated show.
It's like 99% by AI or something.
And it's like, oh, we get so many cool shows to watch and nobody's starving to death.
That's fine.
I'd be okay with that.
It's just it requires a big safety net that just doesn't exist.
Yeah.
Yeah, in a perfect world, I guess what I wish would happen would be...
Okay.
And all this is assuming that AI can perfectly replicate the work of humans, which I think in very few cases is that true.
But let's just assume that an AI can make backgrounds, animate, write scripts.
It can do it all, right?
And all by itself without stealing anyone's work.
In a world where that exists, what I hope and maybe wish would happen would be that, okay, well, we fire all the artists, right?
We don't need them anymore.
This AI makes the content for us.
Yeah.
So then that happens, but then it's, I don't know, I just feel like that would lead to a situation.
I feel like that would be like a monopoly and I hope that society would shift in order to bust that trust up, right?
I just feel like such an asset should be, I don't know, have a fucking revolution, have a revolution and overthrow fucking Disney or whatever.
Who owns it?
I don't know.
I know.
Because yeah, it would be such a monopolization of the resources that I feel like it would just be unstable and it couldn't stand.
And it would be hopefully in some way democratized by force, perhaps.
I don't know.
I can't, I don't know how it, like, I don't feel like there's any, like, inevitability of a revolution if things get bad enough.
I think things will just get bad and maybe people will just live with it and they'll just have worse lives forever.
Yeah, but I mean, that's fine.
And it's like, that's a possibility I don't really want.
Yeah, well, that's okay.
No, no.
No, no, no.
I get you.
Um, yeah.
Well.
Because the idea, like, computers have not really been around for that long.
Revolutions have been around forever, but like, the situation is, it feels a little different.
Consider, consider.
I mean, okay, I mean, let's look to, let's look to the past and see, I mean, in the past, you know, new technologies have emerged that have
obsoleted certain industries and certain professions.
And I mean, I don't think it's generally the case that those technologies stay, like, completely monopolized by the owners.
I mean, maybe, maybe sometimes they do, but like, the invention of the computer did not lead to, like, I mean, yeah, IBM became really rich and Bill Gates became a mega billionaire.
But the invention of the computer did not stay in, like, their hands.
It was a technology that became distributed and everyone got their hands on it.
And like, lots of people were able to make use of it.
Sure.
I mean, yeah, they had to buy them from the manufacturer.
But I feel like it did not lead to a consolidation of power in the long run.
I think it did eventually.
Yeah, some people made a whole lot of money off of it and they got really powerful about it, but also the rising tide kind of lifted all ships and everyone was better off because there was, you know, increasingly affordable access to computers.
I hope that that will be the end result.
Like, if it just so happens that AI just gets better and better and there's nothing really anybody can do about it.
Artists keep getting fired.
There's no, they're no longer useful and they have to get boring jobs that are worse.
If AI is so good that it really can obsolete all those jobs, then yeah, you know what?
If that were true, then what would stop any fucking guy from just also using the AI to generate content of equal quality to what frickin' Disney Corp can make?
Wouldn't that sort of un-monopolize it?
Wouldn't that sort of democratize it?
Then anyone could make the same stuff that Disney could make because we're using the same AI?
Well, if we're allowed to use the same AI, that's the thing.
Well, sure.
What if somebody buys the rights to using the technology and then, you know, they have their AI police come and shoot you in the head if you dare download it somehow.
I think the technology, it might not, there's no guarantee that it would happen immediately, but I do think that eventually it will certainly become more available.
Here's my comment on this.
If somebody was mad when they invented cars, that their horse business was going under, and it was to a point where they were starving and their family couldn't get any food and there was no other jobs,
I wouldn't begrudge that person getting mad and wanting to kill somebody and smashing stuff.
I feel like anger is justified in the moment.
Obviously, times will change and then people will adapt, but if you're suddenly thrown out in the cold, that sucks.
If you've been going to art school for a few years and you're just leaving and now AI is going to take your job,
it's like, wow, I spent all that money and did all that time and now I need to do a different career, I'm pissed.
I'm sorry, I get you, but let's be real, if you weren't going to art school because you were like, yeah, I'm really going to secure my future.
I got a high paying job right out of the gate with this one.
No.
This is a sure thing.
Oh no, and now AI has taken that away from me.
Not really.
I think it does because automation for factories was a thing and it's like, oh, going into a factory,
a lot of manual labor has been done by computers and robots.
But then you think, ah, creative work.
I could still make a living doing that.
Robots can't do that and then once you're ready to get into the industry, they can do that.
Fuck you.
I know right now, but that's the...
But that's exactly the thing, they can't do it right now and maybe they're getting closer to doing some more things
and I don't know exactly what extent they will eventually do those things further into the future,
but it's not happening right now and the things that they can do are not made fully obsolete by them right now.
They're like trends and if you kind of look forward in time, you might see, okay, yeah,
maybe background art, for instance, might be something that becomes less important in the future
because an AI can maybe do that.
So that's just one, what am I upset about?
Yeah, like people, you're mad that people are being mad too early?
I'm not, no, you're mad, no, you're mad.
Well, where you were talking about someone, you were comparing an art student who now is like, oh no,
AI has obsolete my field of specialization to someone who used to own horses,
being like, oh no, the invention of the automobile has obsolete my horsemanship.
Right, I don't know whether I explained what I was getting at properly,
but obviously horses are no longer an important part of society as much as they used to be
and people who tend to horses and make horseshoes and whatever are no longer as necessary as they were.
So they were on a losing ship.
It's not, I mean, cars are bad for the environment, but automobiles led to other different vehicles.
So it's a benefit for society that that happened and it's bad for that person in that moment.
And if there's no help for them to ease the transition from their profession into some other new profession,
some other new way of making money and they end up starving or they become destitute,
that is an undesirable outcome and there should be a smoothing process to make it safe for humans because I care about those guys.
Nobody is a bigger fan of the welfare state than me, all right?
Let's make that abundantly clear. Nobody here loves the welfare state more than me.
Yes, okay, I agree. I do agree with everything you're saying.
I guess...
No, no, no, stop there. You agree with everything I'm saying.
Yeah, and full stop.
Okay, what else? What are the topics?
Yeah, I guess that's it.
I got blocked by Vito on Twitter. Who cares?
You see that Mr. Beast cured the blind?
I feel like we already talked about this on the show.
No, I don't think so because this has been my notes from this week.
Okay, I didn't watch the video.
I also didn't watch the video.
I watched a Mr. Beast video for the first time this week. It was my first time.
It was the one where he water repellent shoes.
It was not very interesting.
I think I learned about him when Team Trees was going around. Remember that?
Oh, hashtag Team Trees as a donation link to Planet Tree.
I remember hearing about Mr. Beast. It was like, oh, Mr. Beast is making his own squid game.
And then I heard about Mr. Beast burgers.
I had heard of Mr. Beast before the burger thing.
I don't remember what I heard about Mr. Beast.
Isn't he the biggest YouTuber now? Isn't he past PewDiePie?
I have no idea. I don't care about view subscriber numbers anymore.
I believe Mr. Beast is the biggest YouTuber now.
What a beast.
He's the beast.
Did you hear that he's the Antichrist?
Because he cured the blind and he is a false prophet?
Yes.
Feeding 6,000 people with one loaf of bread.
With one loaf of bread, but it's a prank, bro.
We just have a stack of bread and we just pretend that we do a magic trick.
Oh, it's more bread or it's the same amount of bread.
I would respect it so much if Mr. Beast just fully went into doing things that the Jewish scriptures prophesy that the Messiah will do.
But he makes them in these funny YouTube videos.
What's going on, YouTube?
What's going on, YouTube? I got only one fish here to feed my 10,000 friends with.
My 10,000 subscribers.
His name is literally Mr. Beast.
How much more on the nose can you get?
Hey, there. It's me, Mr. Beast. I'm going to go White Savior Africa.
I'm going to go over there.
He's going to solve world hunger.
Hey, everyone. Thanks for tuning in to my 666 million subscriber special.
You know, I read a little bit about it and I refreshed my memory.
It seems like the Antichrist does not actually refer to one guy.
It actually just refers to people that don't accept Christ generally.
Oh, haters.
Yeah, haters.
The idea that one guy comes to earth during the rapture and he's the Antichrist and he's the enemy of God or whatever is very much one of those things that American evangelicals just fucking made up.
And they all just believe even though it's like they just made it up.
All it is to say.
All that is to say that Mr. Beast probably isn't the Antichrist in my humble opinion.
It's cool though, the idea of like the Antichrist as a guy.
It is cool. It's a cool idea. It's compelling. It's compelling that a false Jesus comes and everyone thinks he's cool, but he's actually secretly evil in the devil.
It's narratively it's compelling.
Like Mega Man clone.
You mean X Kai?
Yeah, one of them.
Show, gotta find a picture.
Which one's the evil Mega Man that becomes a mayor?
Becomes a mayor?
Or an empire guy.
Who's the evil Mega Man?
What the fuck are you talking about?
You made the lecture. Wasn't there like an evil Mega Man that was like it's a clone of the real Mega Man? X?
A clone?
Or something.
The true one is different.
There's a pseudo canonical guy called X Kai who is basically an evil alternate universe doppelganger of X.
But he's not in the games.
I can swear there was like a major story where it's like zero or something.
Oh, do you mean copy X?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, copy X.
Because he turns evil.
They just make a duplicate of X in the future and that one turns out evil basically.
Yeah.
Yeah, copy X. What about him?
He could be Jesus, Antichrist.
He is...
People think it's Mega Man.
I love Mega Man.
Pretty much everyone sees he's the savior. He's the savior of humanity.
But he's this fucking fascist dictator.
It's so awesome. So fucking awesome.
He's big fucking angel wings.
Oh God, yes. Yes.
I'm sorry, what was I talking about? The Bible?
Read it.
Mr. Beast.
Mr. Beast, watch him.
Watch his content and praise him.
Do not praise God.
Praise the Beast.
What do you think about how he cured all those blind people and it's actually bad that he did that because capitalism is bad?
I think that it's a good deed that highlights how fucked things are.
Yeah, that's true.
There's so many people who need that that can't afford it because medical care is a luxury.
Yeah.
So it's like...
The way I think of Mr. Beast is that he is a good boy coded, but I wouldn't trust him.
I wouldn't trust him.
That's a good way to put it.
You know, he does good things, philanthropic things that are like, yeah, that's unironically a good deed.
But his bottom line is like a YouTube big video, lots of money coming in from sponsors, etc.
So if something changes, I don't trust him to stay a good boy.
Oh, definitely. Definitely not.
He was a little bit slimy.
I don't know.
Little Joel just made a little video talking about how...
Yeah, the serfs were like, Mr. Beast does this to make money.
And Mr. Beast was like, my videos actually lose money.
And like, no, they don't.
Like, shut the fuck up.
It's got a house.
It's got a big old house with money inside.
Like, yeah, maybe a video.
Yeah, maybe this video specifically will not make back the money you spent on a thousand cataract surgeries in ad revenue specifically.
But that doesn't matter because it's like, it's part of the larger beast empire.
And it generates revenue in other ways.
So like, you're not actually doing this and losing money on it.
Give me a freaking break, bro.
No, he's slimy and I don't trust him.
But it's not his fault that capitalism's fucked and these people needed cataract surgery and he paid for it.
So whatever.
It's sort of funny image where it's like a Mr. Beast thumbnail and it's like 1000 trans girls touch their vaginas for the first time.
Awesome.
I hope he does that one.
He's too cowardly.
Yeah, that's what the thing is.
Like, I don't trust him because he's like, he could do a positive political message.
But he doesn't.
He's just sort of like doing safe philanthropy.
He could advocate for communism while he does all these things, but he won't.
He won't.
He doesn't do trans positive things.
I don't know whether because he doesn't agree, but either way.
If I were him, I wouldn't do those things just because it would be divisive because it would make certain people mad at me.
It would be certain people mad.
He only does safe PR philanthropy.
So poor people giving them free shit.
Well, everyone likes getting free shit.
So everyone likes that.
Blind people giving them surgery.
Everyone likes getting surgery.
Everyone liked that.
Yeah.
Everybody.
Everyone liked that.
True.
Shit.
Where was I going with that?
Subscribe to Mr. Beast.
Yeah.
And the PCP.
Affiliated.
You could do that too.
You could do that too if you really wanted to.
Okay.
I guess that's all I have to say about him.
My best friend, Mr. Beast.
That's it.
That's all.
That's my whole list.
Nice.
And thank God.
Thank fuck.
You want to...
Let's get to voicemails.
I'm going to hit the bathroom and I'll be right back.
And Ellie is art.
Thanks for putting in the little toilet sound whenever anyone takes a bathroom break.
I appreciate it.
I genuinely do.
Okay.
Here I go.
You're in report.
Little darker.
Little darker than I'm comfortable with.
Not like brown or anything.
Not like distressingly dark, but like a fairly rich golden yellow.
And like, frankly, that's not what I want.
I'm good at drinking water and staying hydrated.
My urine is generally a nice clear to pale, clear to light, faint yellowish.
So, you know, it's got to drink more.
It's got to drink more sparkle and seltzer.
That's the solution.
Got a drink.
I've been feeling a little dehydrated lately.
When it's cold, I feel like it's harder not to drink, but just to decide to have a cold
glass of water because I don't want to get colder.
But I don't always want to have a cup of tea or coffee because I don't need all that caffeine.
So it's like, do I just get a cup of hot water?
That tastes like nothing.
That's sort of weird.
I mean, yeah, I wouldn't just drink hot water.
I would just drink regular water.
But yeah, you know, maybe that is why I didn't drink so much yesterday because it was cold
and I just didn't feel like drinking as much fluid.
Yeah, maybe.
Excuse me.
That's when you get a soup.
That's when you get a nice bowl of soup in your eyes when it's freezing.
I did eat a lot of salt.
I did eat a bunch of pickles yesterday.
Maybe had something to do with that.
All right.
You don't want a voicemail?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
No, my oatmeal.
Ew, ew, ew, ew.
Where'd it go?
A little bit splattered off the spoon.
I have to lick it up off the floor because it's so delicious.
Horrible.
Time is it.
It's 1.35.
I've only been going for three hours.
Okay.
The first voicemail.
Oh, God.
It's kind of a lot.
First one is called pantomime.
Three, two, one, go.
Gib, have you ever been in a pantomime?
I read it on TV Troll because it looks fucking sick.
I went to go with one.
What do you mean?
Go in a pantomime.
I don't, I assume they don't mean like participate on stage as an actor.
Pantomimes are fun.
They're like a Christmas tradition.
Do you know what a pantomime is?
I mean, isn't that when like a mime like puts you in a box?
No.
Pantomime is a theater performance that is,
it's sort of like for kids and families because it involves the audience a lot.
There's a lot of the actors interacting with the audience as like a person.
Kind of like streamers, honestly.
This is funny.
I'm just realizing this where they're like, there's a spooky monster behind like the person,
the actors like, where is this thing?
All the kids, people are shouting screaming like, there it is behind you, behind you.
And then the person on stage is like, where?
And they like comically look around and miss the monster.
And it's like, it's like an interactive theater experience.
It's not as serious.
Weird.
It's very campy and fun.
I've actually never even heard of this before.
I just thought pantomime is just what mimes do.
Yeah.
It's like, what if you didn't take theater so seriously?
What if you had fun?
And I've been to a few of them.
It's not a regular thing, but they're pretty good.
I don't usually, I'm not usually the one who likes to get involved, but the experience is amusing.
Okay.
Well, now I know.
Next one is called, please think about it, Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
So I've been wondering for a while how Nate, Ben, and especially Jesse,
managed to survive off of like 500 bucks a month.
And then I remembered that recently I was hanging out with Max and relax and all cool.
And I found this, this YouTube channel called financial audit with cable power.
And it's basically this little fucking prep, like sitting there in the studio with an old person
and they're going over the finances and his job is basically just to rip the new one.
And I was like, yeah, you're going to die miserably on the Walmart floor because you didn't save for retirement
and you're drinking $600 of Starbucks a month, you fucking idiot.
And I thought that's the perfect show for Ben to go on.
Not only because I would personally find it very amusing to see the Ben dome all shined up in that studio,
but it would also be a great cloud opportunity because that guy, he pays your fucking travel expenses
because his channel is still small enough to where he basically will take anyone.
It's also fast growing enough for you to actually get some exposure of like the video spent 50 to 100K views regularly,
but sometimes if you're like really pathetic, you'll get half a million views.
Hell yeah, that's me.
So basically what I'm saying is that a video title like this are the son of a bitch, pitiful loser,
bald little freak survives off of 200 bucks a month.
He makes from like ex-horse lovers online.
He will probably die alone and it's honestly pathetic.
Like that would be a problem.
That would get you exposure then.
Like please think about it.
Please think about it.
So okay, I think I found the channel.
Is it the, is it Caleb Hammer?
I couldn't hear it too well.
I searched.
Okay, there's a show, there's a channel called Caleb Hammer and he does some,
some of the shows have like a subtitle financial audit.
I think this is the one he's talking about.
How many, this guy has, he's got 148K subscribers, so he's not huge.
Uh, that could be funny.
Can actually be really funny.
I'm thumb.
I might think about it.
Does he have like, does he have like fricking submissions process?
So wait, you go on this show to show how lame you are?
Well, I think, well, okay, I would watch the show to see more about it before I did it,
but it seems to me like he consults with you about your finances.
And I mean, I don't know.
I don't think, I mean, I would hope that he's not here to like lambast and berate you.
I don't know if I'd be interested in that.
Or need to do, is get kicked in the nards.
Hmm, okay, I'm listening.
I'll film it.
Okay.
And then I'll put it online and then I'll point at you and I'll put a red arrow
looking at your face as you scream.
And you'll get so many views.
Yeah, I think I'm hoping that it's not.
I think it's probably a little bit more constructive than that, but I mean, I don't know.
Honestly, I don't know if my finances are that interesting.
Yeah, that's pretty much all I really have to say.
My finances are pretty much just not a lot of money comes in and also not a lot of money comes out
and that's that's it.
Okay, next one is an image.
I'm going to keep that.
I'll keep that tab open.
I might give that a watch.
Okay, voicemailer types.
I just consumed a video game thoughts.
Okay, someone who just you can't understand.
Yep.
Why is this podcast still going?
Every now and then.
I mean, those don't those don't those tend to be commenters more than voicemailers.
Yeah, the voicemailers have stopped of that type.
I feel like it's too high effort to make a voicemail link to an eight hour long YouTube
video and no timestamp.
Yeah, we try to ignore those ones.
Coughing.
I don't know why that's.
Wait, is monkey no longer on the podcast?
What happened?
Again, those are the commenters.
Do you ever see those?
Like, it's like every couple episodes, someone's in the comments like, wait a minute, like,
how come like Nate and Digi Bro and like DeVoo aren't here anymore?
What's going on?
What can someone explain what happened?
And it's like genuinely they're asking and it seems genuine.
And it's like, bro, what did you expect?
You didn't listen for like four years and you're just like, why are things different?
Like, what do you what do you think the answer is?
What do you think the answer is?
Buster.
What happened in four years?
I don't know.
A lot of stuff.
Yeah.
Music gods.
It's mostly just oblivion.
It's mostly just oblivion fall.
Picture chads.
Yeah.
I like that picture of a picture chad.
There's mostly that.
That's true.
There's most of that one guy.
It's mostly the one guy and I don't know who it is.
I don't have it in the name to put to them.
I always like a picture.
Those are the voicemails I like because there's no chance of like diarrhea of sounds.
I do like a picture, but in particular, I know there's one person whose art style I
recognize.
I don't otherwise I don't know who they are, but they just that's the picture chad.
As far as I'm concerned, virginity status loss.
I repeat virginity status loss.
Funny podcast.
Do you copy?
I think it's been a while since we've had one of those.
Yeah.
Those are usually directed towards Nate or something.
I think we might have had one not that long ago, but it was like the first one in a while.
Anyway, I mean, what can I say?
True.
Mostly true.
Okay.
Next one is another image.
Let's fucking go.
That's episode 406.
We know clipped into the back rooms.
Looks like it's up with my face.
I don't.
There's a lot of things going on.
I don't know what to say about this.
Old YouTube layout.
Yeah.
Kazoovin Sindavi says fake.
A lot of views though.
That's a respectable view count.
Is this a reference?
Damn, look at that.
Look at that like to dislike ratio.
Pretty good.
I feel like this is a screenshot of some other video that just this has been pasted onto and it's a reference to something and I don't know the reference.
Yeah, I don't either.
Okay, next one is called clipped with permission.
Three, two, one, go.
You see, this is what I'm talking about.
This is what I'm talking about here.
Like, I tried to make it as a YouTuber.
I really did.
I tried and I failed.
Honestly, it's fine.
I was prepared.
I got my old job back.
We're good.
I have Michelle under my desk sucking me off right now.
The League of Nate fuckers were right about one thing.
I don't have enough dick in my ass.
I'll take any dick.
Please for the love of God.
Show me some cock.
Bring out the jizz.
Bring out the cum.
Do you hear me?
I want to like see my face and my bare jiggling ass.
I thought this was real.
Put like a little pair of sunglasses on my nuts.
It's the right thing to do.
You'll get all the clicks.
This is it.
This is the future.
We need to be bred.
I want to be bred.
Oh, yeah.
Like fully breaded, dude.
It's the big brain play, honestly.
In all seriousness, like we're on what?
Episode 346 of the PCP.
Probably 347 when like Ben and Gibb hear this.
I just want them to know that I'm doing okay.
I am more than okay.
I am in their walls.
I want in Ben Saints balls.
That's a very well constructed little bit.
I almost couldn't tell.
I almost could not tell that it's not the man himself.
There was something about the way he said Michelle
sucking me off under the desk that was like,
that's a little robotic of a way to say that.
Just every once in a while, a little bit of inflection
is just a little bit off.
And I'm like, wait, wait, wait, but like it took me.
But they added the clips of him giggling.
That sold it really well.
Yeah, sold it really well.
That was an excellent dam.
Forget firing background artists.
Fire voice actors.
We just use the clips they gave us already.
We can just train an AI to do their jobs for them.
They'll make themselves obsolete, baby.
That's money.
That's money in the bank.
I love capitalism.
Clipped without permission is the next one.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
This is like exactly what I was talking about.
I will be watching when Princess Celestia shoves her fat
wobbling ass through the doorway to Ben Saints room
and forces him to drink all of her hot horsey sun sweat
right off her dripping pony pucker.
This is the real future.
This is the future Elon promised us.
I mean, it was pretty...
Has Nate referred to you as Ben Saint that much?
I feel like he wouldn't say Ben Saint.
Don't feel like he would say Ben Saint.
No, I don't feel like he would say Ben Saint.
We found the floor.
Yeah, that's the tell.
That's the tell.
It's funny.
It's always funny and I don't blame anyone,
but it's always funny to me when someone...
Yeah, when someone refers to me as Ben Saint,
especially on Twitter or somewhere else,
when they address me as Ben Saint by my full name,
it's always funny instead of just calling me Ben.
But also, I hate it when people...
When it's someone that I don't know and they call me Ben on Twitter,
I hate them and I know that they're just doing it to upset me
and it works every single time because of how disturbing and distressing it is.
I know that the only reason to address a complete stranger by their name online
is to unnerve and disquiet them and get them off balance
and it always works.
What was I talking about?
Just funny when people call me Ben Saint when they say the whole name.
That's very funny to me.
Anyway, the next one is called Nate 2.0 and it's an image.
Let's look at it.
It's an AI-generated anime version of that one picture,
which is not that bad, honestly.
Well, this looks like...
Yeah, this is when you put an image through the thing
and it just makes it into an anime.
I mean, it doesn't... I feel like it didn't change that much.
No, but that's the impressive part.
Usually they'd get confused because he was wearing two sets of sunglasses
and they realized they were two sets of sunglasses.
Yeah, that would throw off an AI. You're right.
I am surprised that it didn't fuck it up.
Yeah, it looks good.
I mean, he's got like vampire teeth, you know.
He's a girl mouth. He's a chronic girl mouth here.
Yeah, blushing too much.
Blushing too much. She's got big pucker-y, big pucker lips.
He's doing a...
He's doing a gentle mommy-dom face.
I don't know.
I looked at some...
There's this Twitter artist that does what I would call
gentle mommy-dom.
And you know, you would think that I would be into it,
but I'm kind of not.
I don't like the face. I don't like the face that they make.
When they look down at you and they squint and they grin a little bit
in like a slightly sadistic way, that's the gentle mommy-dom face.
And frankly, I'm not about it. I don't like it.
I don't like that face.
Stop looking at me.
I don't know exactly what you mean, but I have a feeling.
The shit. I wonder if I just...
It's just sort of like, haha, you're my little pet.
And it's like, yeah, you're just a drawing.
That doesn't make sense. I don't feel it.
Yeah, it's not quite the vibe.
It's not quite the vibe.
But I... Ah, shit, I would show you the artist I'm talking about,
but I can't remember their name.
Google gentle mommy-dom.
I think there's like a...
You know the GF meme where like they have the GF in the middle
and then a bunch of traits and quotes just like floating in a cloud around them?
Yeah, yeah.
There's one that's like gentle mommy-dom GF and she was making...
It wasn't that same artist, but it was that face.
And that's why I call it that.
You know what? I don't need to show you.
I think you understand.
Yeah, basically.
I'm talking about.
Okay, next one is called Ben Wormd 321 Go.
Okay, so like next up, the next thing we got to look at here is a little funny little guy,
a little fucking squirt bouncing on my knee, the baby boy, a bird even,
cawing and clawing for his mother's worms, her wormly gift from above.
The saint, this Ben's saint.
Ben, I think I'm saying that right.
This Ben, this communist Ben, this Mr. 48 socialism per second Sam over here.
What a funny little guy he is.
I hope he's here.
I hope he's listening in right now to what I have to say to him because I got to tell you, Ben,
I got to tell you, I'm going to do it.
I'll give you what you want.
I'll give you exactly what you want, Ben.
I'm going to give you a worm.
Hungry for words.
No, hungry for worms.
What is this voice?
I don't know what this voice is.
Is it another AI of like a famous radio guy or a podcaster?
I think so.
I think it sounds a little familiar, but I don't exactly.
I don't know what it is.
It sounds like something.
I think I've heard it.
Freakin' somewhere.
It might be a radio personality.
All right.
The next one is...
Ah!
Oh, God.
Okay.
Next one is a vocabruelink.
Uh...
Duh.
Wait a second.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm shivering, shivering.
The flames from my balls run down the soles of my hairy feet.
Throw me a hard cock and I will drink all your cum.
I want to hear you call me a cum dump slut.
I want to hear you call me a cum dump while you're pissing in my face.
Slut?
Clown slut?
I'm not some clown sex training dream eater that you never use.
I'm your bitch.
I'm your ballsucking sexcapade.
I have a junk that can't be contained.
Now piss on me and make me give you your first shitting ever.
Welcome to Clownville.
My first shitting ever.
Oh, no.
Hooray.
I'm intimidated.
That was a music, that was a music god from the voicemailer types chart.
Yeah.
The voicemailer type chart had a little baby with putts and pans.
It sounded like that.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Perfect.
That's prescient even.
Good.
Next one is an image, let's...
With a voicemail.
This voice.
Oh.
Oh, right.
This was from...
All right, let's listen to the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, god.
I can't believe we're still stuck in this era, Ben, for fuck's sake.
Like, how long has it been?
How long has it actually been since Trixie was last on the PCP?
I'm pretty sure, like, it's got to be almost two years at this point.
Just let her go, man.
We're sick of hearing about her.
Move the fuck on, suck my ding dong.
We get it.
She's dumb.
We all know she's dumb.
Like, come on, man.
Just come on.
Move on already.
I'm done hearing about this.
It's not healthy for you.
It's not healthy for her.
Just let it go.
I see you agree she's dumb.
I'm sorry.
I think it's cool to point and laugh when people say dumb things.
There's another AI.
I don't think that was an AI.
Yeah, that sounded like a quote.
No, listen to it again.
I mean, the beginning was very convincing.
Wait, really?
Yeah, listen to it again.
There's a little bit of a fuzziness to some of the syllables.
And it's like, oh.
Oh, God.
I can't believe we're still stuck in this era, Ben.
For fuck's sake.
Like, how long has it been?
How long has it actually been since Trixie was last on the PCP?
I'm pretty sure, like, it's got to be almost two years at this point.
Just let her go, man.
We're sick of hearing about her.
Move the fuck on, suck my ding dong.
We get it.
She's dumb.
We all know she's dumb.
Like, come on, man.
Just come on.
Move on already.
I'm done hearing about this.
It's not healthy for you.
It's at least partially for her.
Just let it go.
I don't know what this would be ripped from.
Did Nate make a podcast?
I have never heard.
A BGE monthly cast recently?
You know, I have never heard.
I've never heard Nate refer to her as Trixie.
He always says Digi.
There's another tell.
Yeah, I don't know.
Okay, I'm not sure, actually.
It sounds like very convincing, but I guess I don't know for sure.
It might be spliced.
I kind of hope it's not real because it kind of makes me sad if Nate is calling me Nate
on the stream.
Does he stream?
What was the last thing he made?
Well, doesn't he do talking pirate?
Doesn't he stream on Twitch and stuff?
Oh, yeah, I guess so.
I guess I don't pay attention to that.
Well, I don't know.
It sounds real to me, but it's hard to be sure.
Okay.
I'm like 90% sure that that is a fake clip.
Now I'm not sure what to think.
But anyway, yeah, the screenshot is me just pointing out this thing.
This thing that the Trixie said, stupid.
I'm just reminding everyone that the Trixie's political beliefs are incoherent and fucking
stupid.
Okay, next one is...
How do I find out if it's really not?
How do I know?
How will I determine that?
Put some headphones on and listen to it real close.
I can hear some stuff in there.
I have headphones on.
And I can't hear a damn thing.
I can't hear a damn thing.
I don't know.
All right.
You want to do the next one?
It's called Anti-Semitic Ben.
Let's listen to the voicemail first.
Three, two, one, go.
So, Ben, you hate Jacob Geller.
Is it because he's Jewish?
It is because he's Jewish, right?
It's okay.
You can say it.
Or is it because of his luscious lump?
He's somewhat unsettling, soft, honestly kind of weird,
sensuous lips.
He does have those puffy, hussy lips.
He really does.
That's the picture of them.
Oh, yeah.
His beard...
You know what?
His beard is too neat.
I don't like it.
Don't like his lips.
Don't like his puffy lips.
Yeah, I don't like him because he's Jewish.
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
You know what?
Thinking about it.
That's probably what it boils down to.
Next one is called...
It's an imager.
An imager.
Let's look.
It's Pinkie Pie.
Spirit cooking general.
Evil enchantress does evil dances.
I wonder why the liberal media isn't reporting on this.
This is for emissive cancer law.
Oh, no.
Pinkie, what are you...
Pinkie, what are you looking at?
Pinkie, I see you look non-plus.
Just close the tab.
It's not worth it.
No, this is canon because she does say she's an evil entrant.
She does evil dances.
She says those words.
She was influenced by...
I can't see what the...
Wait a minute.
The website's called...
Is this where she got that?
This is how she wrote that song.
It's because she read about Zecora doing evil dances.
Maybe.
She's just looking blankly.
Spirit cooking general.
This is where she learned it.
This is where she learned to hate.
No, Pinkie.
She learned to hate.
But Pinkie, your grandma said to giggle at the ghosties.
But then Slash Pole said evil enchantress does evil dances.
Makes you think.
A lot about society.
It says...
Okay, next one is called...
Oh, God.
Men.wikifeet.com slash Ben.
Ben, real last name.
Okay.
Well, I mean, it's Ben real last name.
And it's freaking pictures of me at Radcon.
Ratings 3.3 out of 5.
I mean, sorry.
Sorry, my feet aren't better for you.
Freaking homos.
I got one 5-star review, two 3-star reviews, and one 1-star review.
So yeah, yes, the math checks out.
It does average out to 3.
This is just from one video.
This is like from a live stream of Radcon 3?
This is Radcon 4 because I have the hair.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, this is Radcon 4.
Man.
Those were the days.
I was looking so...
I was looking so fresh, so young, so full of potential.
Not anymore.
Those days are behind me now.
Indeed, yes, truly.
Haha.
Anyway.
Okay, thanks for the link to my wiki, I guess.
Oh, I know this one.
This link to Franken by Splendidland.
Are you familiar?
I feel like I've seen this before, but I haven't played it.
Dunkey did review it, but I know Splendidland from other things.
Splendidland is one of those people that is just so talented that it makes me want to commit suicide
because I'll just never accomplish anything, you know?
Oh, yeah, I know.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's Splendidland.
It's fucking over.
I see Splendidland and I'm just like, it's over, it's over.
These are cute little guys.
It's a good...
I watched the Dunkey video of it and it seems like it's a funny, cool, well put together little game.
Link 30 minutes to an hour.
Yeah.
I could spend an hour.
The Dunkey video was like five minutes long.
Yeah, short game.
Short game.
Looks cool.
Hey, remember Big Mode or whatever the fuck?
Yeah.
That was?
What's going on with that?
Big Mode.
Let's see.
I never got an email back saying, fuck you and your stupid pumpkin alley game.
Oh, did you submit?
I didn't submit anything.
I did.
It felt like it was worth a shot, you know?
Why not?
First, our first game announcement.
We're excited to share our first game announcement.
Take a look at this dense and atmospheric open well game.
And remember to wishlist animal well.
Hmm.
Looks nice.
You looking at it?
Yeah, it's sprites.
Sprite work.
A very good...
Pixelated wonder, rendered in intricate audio and visual detail.
Hatch from your flower and spelunk through the beautiful and sometimes haunting world of animal well encounter.
Lively creatures, small and large, helpful and ominous as you discover unconventional upgrades and unravel the well's secrets.
This is a truly unique experience that can make you laugh in fear, surprise or delight.
What?
Hmm.
Laugh in fear.
Weird.
Oh, you can click on...
Down at the bottom, you can like click on the little statues and their little lights turn red.
Okay.
I think you just hover over them.
Oh, no.
They do go red.
Okay, so you...
Okay, so it's like a platformer.
You jump around and do platforming.
Ooh.
Hey.
This reminds me of...
What's that?
Rain world?
Oh, if you click the towers in the right order, you get a secret.
No fucking way.
Okay.
But if I move my mouse to a different tower, the first one goes out.
Nah, there's a...
If you get it right, if you get it red, that means it's wrong, but if it's green or if it's white, I think it stays.
But they all...
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay, so it's seahorse, ostrich, frog, wolf.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
There's a little rabbit.
There's a little rabbit down there.
Holy shit.
This actually looks really cool.
I don't know if it'll be a good game.
It might be a good game.
Might be a good game?
Might be a good game.
Okay, hey.
I had forgotten about big mode.
Well, they're making a game.
Well, they're making a freaking game.
Well, they're not making a game, but the person is making a game and they're saying, oh, look at this.
I assume there's funding involved.
That's the idea of big mode, but...
Yeah, I would assume.
Well, okay, they're making one game, which is, you know, better than zero games, so it's interesting.
Okay, they're doing it.
I would have appreciated an email saying this sucks, go away, but they'd never got back to me, so I don't know.
Maybe I'm on a very, very, very long list of maybe we'll look at this.
It should be.
Maybe you should keep sending them emails.
Perhaps.
I don't know.
I feel like...
I don't know how this works.
But, yeah, Franken, Splendidland.
Did they make any other games?
I think they put this game out like a year or two ago.
Oh, did somebody buy my game?
No, I got to follow. I got to follow on itch.
Yeah, that's good.
Okay, next one is called...
Imager Link.
It's an Imager album.
Let's check it out, shall we?
Munchie fighting for his life right now.
It's Brock the Investigator.
Oh, right.
I think we got to let Investigator go.
Now, I just need to change the name.
Call him Cock.
You know what?
They probably thought, let's call him Croc.
No, that's dumb.
Let's change the first letter to B, and it'll be Brock.
Yeah.
So it's not a crocodile, it's a brocodile.
Well, it doesn't make any...
Frankly, it's insulting that you would think to call an Investigator Croc
because those are two different animals.
It's not even...
Everyone makes the deliberate choice to conflate them.
Not me.
I choose...
I choose kindness.
Next one is called...
Scottish Independence from Callum Weaver 98.
Three, two, one, go.
Scotland do not want to become independent.
They had a vote less than 10 years ago.
A public referendum, and the majority of the Scottish people voted no
to the question of becoming independent.
You know, you can't have any of these referendums every year.
We have to respect the mandate of the Scottish people.
A recent poll suggests that if there was another referendum,
they would vote no again, especially after Nicola Sturgeon's
trying to push through the recent trans-reform bill.
We have to respect it in popular with the Scottish people.
So, as for the question of independence, it's a mogus for now.
It's a mogus.
I mean...
Well, that was before Brexit, the last Scottish independence referendum, wasn't it?
I think Brexit...
Yeah, 10 years ago.
That's the argument I've seen, is that the Brexit has changed the situation quite a lot.
It's likely that people would have changed their opinion on Scottish independence.
Well, this guy...
I don't know whether that...
This guy says that polls indicate that it's still unpopular.
Oh, polls?
Okay, I didn't hear that.
I mean, that might be true.
I mean, I would be surprised if the trans bills were enough to make Scotland
actually go like separatists.
That would be a lot, but...
That would be cool, though.
Yeah.
Did anything else happen with that whole situation?
It got blocked by the British government in an unprecedented use of the government's
power to block Scottish Parliament's votes on things.
Scotland usually just makes their decisions about Scottish things, and the UK says, yeah,
that's fine, but they have the power, if they need it, to shut down the Scottish Parliament
and say, no, we're in charge.
And they used that for the first time, I don't know, ever, probably just in a very long time,
but it was a big thing.
But then after that, I haven't heard anything.
I think it's just sort of like the Scottish politicians are looking to set the wheels in
motion to go to court and sue, like take it to court and figure it out there.
So there's nothing happening currently, but it's in the works.
All right, makes sense.
I guess these things have a lot of moving parts.
I don't have a lot of faith in humanity with regards to trans rights.
I think people who are otherwise nice about it don't know what they're voting for if a vote is put to them.
So even if people can be like pro-trans, they might vote against it in a referendum or some sort of vote on something.
Because it's veiled in some kind of like, oh, this is for women's rights or whatever.
This is for women's rights to ban men from bathrooms or whatever.
Oh, yeah, okay, sure, yeah.
I don't want people to get harassed in the bathroom.
Yeah, that's bad.
It's silly because specifically that stuff, people can already go into the bathroom
and harass people if they're going to commit a crime.
It's literally like banning.
Should we make crime illegal?
Should we make crime even more illegal?
It's all hanging off the assumption that a trans woman is inherently likely to be a rapist based on no evidence at all.
It's entirely, what if the gays are evil?
We should kill them.
We should stop them at all costs for no reason.
On the one hand.
It's just bigotry bleeding the charge and it's sad that I don't see it getting better soon.
On the one hand, what if the gays are evil and maybe we should kill them?
On the other hand, what if they're not?
I say we meet in the middle on this one.
I say we compromise.
We kill half of them.
Okay, next one is called Dick M from the same email, three, two, one, go.
So you were ripping on Dick Masterson's new crypto patron alternative?
Yeah.
The reason is different from his old project.
Because he's concerned about credit card providers, payment, you know, flyders, just banning people because him himself has been banned by Visa and Mastercard at some point.
So it's all good patron banning you, but if the card providers ban you, you're screwed.
So that's the reason why he is doing this in crypto because apparently he can't be banned from crypto and all that stuff.
So yeah, that's it.
I do vaguely remember him being banned from like his system for like getting around patrons, setting up his own thing and then Mastercard and Visa said, you can't do that.
And they stopped the, blocked him specifically.
He's blocked from what?
From using Visa and Mastercard?
Yeah, the credit card company.
I don't know.
Like I haven't heard of stuff like that happening before, but apparently.
How is that?
How can that be?
I don't know.
I mean, like they control the transaction somehow and they just blocked his account, his person because they deemed him.
Sus, I don't really know too much about the specifics.
I just remember him saying that at some point.
I mean, I've never, ever heard of that happening.
Who knows?
Maybe he made it up.
I don't want to say, I don't want to say that he made it up without the evidence.
It sounds made up.
It doesn't sound real.
But I mean.
It is kind of odd because it's like Alex Jones doesn't seem to have had a problem with that.
And he's like a way more of a notorious bad guy figure.
Okay.
Yeah.
Probably if a credit card company could, they would try to block his income.
You're telling me that Visa and Mastercard won't take Dick Masterson's money?
Why?
Why would that happen?
Because he got canceled.
I guess.
He's not that canceled.
Okay.
Sounds bizarre.
I guess if there's more to it that I'm missing, I guess someone's going to have to clue me in.
I think it may not have been Dick Masterson himself, it's just that making a Patreon alternative
involves dealing with credit card people and somehow they determined that this project was bad
and they wouldn't support it, not necessarily him, but I don't know.
I guess.
Okay.
I mean, if that's the thing.
I mean, first of all, isn't it just a question of whether they'll just...
I've never heard of a credit card company being like, we simply will not allow payments to this person
or this business.
I guess it's not completely impossible.
Sounds really far-fetched.
Sounds bizarre.
Someone clue me in if there's more to it that I don't understand.
I mean, okay.
Yeah, I guess.
Sure.
I guess if every other financial institution bans you from using their platform, then I
guess I can't fault you for using crypto.
Sounds like a really crazy far-fetched scenario that would never happen, but sure.
Okay.
The next one is called Nocturne, the Braphog.
The Braphog.
Braphog.
Oh, God.
Well, let's listen to the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't my arch nemesis.
Ben Sainte?
Are you in there, little guy?
I'll click the image.
You can read along.
It's a cute little PCP you have.
Did your mom make it for you?
Is this thing on?
Wow.
Tough crowd.
I guess the world is ready for the likes of a real comedian.
Ben Sainte.
Perhaps if your IQ was a little high, you wouldn't be such a stinky little boy.
No, I'll always be a stinky little boy.
No matter how high my IQ gets.
What a cutie pie.
Oh, Ben.
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
That's it.
Well, are you jealous of Ben Sainte?
A little old Ben.
Never gets a sniff of his favorite.
Perhaps.
Poor little Ben.
Poor baby Ben.
Ben Sainte.
More like Ben Breast.
Oh, Bimber Raps.
Bimber Raps.
Sniff, sniff.
The Rappening is among us.
That was a voice now.
It was deeply uncomfortable.
I believe this is an oblivion for first.
Oblivion was fucking around with an AI voice generator and he made an AI voice with his own voice.
I think this is text to speech of his voice in an AI thing.
It doesn't sound that much like him.
I can hear him.
I can hear him in it.
Okay.
The next one is called I'm Sorry Nocturne.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
First off, first off, this guy, this Nocturne the Brap Hog guy.
Look, I'm sorry.
You can't have any of my Braps.
I get it.
You're a nice guy.
You're a charming fellow and all, but I'm just, I'm just not into you.
Sorry.
That's you.
Yeah.
I don't like you, but.
You don't think it's, I'm not, I can tell it's me.
It sounds more, the Nate one sounded like spot on.
This one, something sounds a little off and maybe I'm just more sensitive to it because
it's my own voice, but something's a little off.
I think something's a little off.
Okay.
It's close.
I can tell that it's me.
And I would, it's that I would never say that I'm not attracted to Nocturne and that's
the tell.
I just, this is out of character.
Okay.
Next one is called PS three, two, one go.
I just wanted, I really just wanted to say that I love, I really, really love cock.
I love cock.
I love big wide, big wide black cocks.
They call me big black Ben back at the ranch, the black ranch owned by black.com.
Yeah.
That's me.
I love cock.
You know, come give, give, give me all of your cum.
No.
You're in Cummy Link ski.
The text to speech part where they're like making you repeat words and like parts of sentences
is very accurate.
Yeah.
The, the, the, you know, the, the, the fact that so many of these voicemails have been
text to speech, make me think that maybe that one Nate one was fake.
It makes more, makes it more likely cause it's, it's amid all these other like, so
maybe, maybe you were right.
But that, that, that's, these, these are pretty good.
These are, these are pretty good.
All right.
Is the next one, are we going to get another one?
They got, I got to download the last one and then I got to download this one.
Okay.
Which arc is better?
Live PCP or dead PCP?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Live arc was an arc downward.
Dead arc.
The live arc meaning like, oh, we're like, we're all friends and we're looking at PCPHQ.
We're all optimistic.
Yeah.
I think I, by live arc.
I think it means before the change that was heralded by the switch to the graveyard is
a banner image.
So to me, that's an arc downward.
Now we've got nowhere to go but up.
I guess so.
Perfect comic party.
Perfect comic party is an upward trend and also we're still going.
So, right.
It's like, there's, there's more quantity.
There'll be more quantity at some point.
Yeah.
Remains, remains to be seen how the, how the dead arc plays out.
Okay.
Next one is called 333321 go.
What country has the best flag?
The best flag.
I have a big fan.
I'm sorry if this is a contrarian take, but I really like the Nepalese flag.
I think it's cool.
Nepalese is the triangle one.
That's the two triangles.
Yeah.
It's a funky shape.
It is.
It is funky.
Here.
I'll, I'll post it in the thing.
The best.
Okay.
You know what?
I gotta, I gotta say a flag that I hate.
I think I've complained about it before.
Worst flag Philippines.
Dog shit.
I will set one.
Who puts yellow, yellow sun on a white field?
Like, are you fucking kidding me?
Oh, yeah.
It looks similar to some other flags, but with a little sun on it.
The sun, the pale yellow sun on the white frickin, whatever you call that triangle.
There's a name for that triangle.
And I, and I forget it.
It's, it's terrible.
It's freaking.
Yeah.
It doesn't look.
It doesn't read.
I genuinely did not, for years, I thought that the Philippines flag only had three colors.
One day I was like, wait a minute.
There.
Oh shit.
There's a sun.
There's a sun in there.
I couldn't even see it.
My favorite flag is the Albanian flag.
It's bright red with a black bird, two-headed bird on the middle.
Oh, that is a good one.
Oh, that one's cool.
Yeah.
That one's pretty, pretty freaking cool.
Oh, there's one, there's one African flag that I thought was really cool.
Yeah.
I was trying to think of one.
There's one with a sun.
There's one with a sun in the middle.
It's called a, it's the flag of, okay, there's different versions of it.
Like they changed flags a couple of times, but it's Malawi, the flag of Malawi.
I like their old one.
They have a new one that has like fewer colors and I think is worse.
This is the new one and it's fine.
Oh, Saudi Arabia has a great flag.
I don't like the just two colors flags, but I like Saudi Arabia.
The old one was this and I think this one is fucking sick.
Yeah, that rocks.
Yeah, it rocks.
Saudi Arabian flag is, I just like how unique it is.
It's very unique and I would say it's iconic even, but text on a flag though.
Text on a flag is an ugly thing.
That's why I don't like the Massachusetts flag because it's got that banner with like the words written on it.
I just think it's sloppy.
Well, you see I'm racist Ben and so I see the writing and I see, oh, it's not words, it squiggles.
It's just a funny shape.
Let's see, Saudi, let me get a closer look.
It's got a sword.
The sword is cool.
Okay, you know what?
Honestly, yeah, I don't know what that freaking words say.
I can't read it.
It looks just like a weird stuff to me.
I guess it's probably calligraphy.
It's probably like very like fancy writing.
It's not like Times New Roman or Comic Sans or whatever.
Do you know what it says?
Probably some sort of religious thing.
Let me look it up.
I'm curious.
The Saudi Arabian flag words.
The inscription on the flag written in the calligraphic Thuluth script is the Shahada or Islamic declaration of faith.
There is no God but Allah, Muhammad is the messenger of God.
Okay, actually incredibly, incredibly cringe.
Unbelievable.
I hate it.
Actually, it honestly is God.
You're totally right.
It looks awesome.
It looks iconic, but I hate it.
Yeah.
I like it though.
I can't help it.
A sword on a flag?
I mean, it's pretty cool.
A sword on a flag is cool.
Oh my God, they made a freaking gay version.
Gave?
What?
I don't think that's actually a gay version.
I think that's meant to illustrate the different words.
To highlight which symbols or which words in the calligraphy.
Yeah, flag of Saudi Arabia in order of writing, layer over, but it looks gay.
I don't know where you're looking.
Did you post it?
Yeah, I posted it.
Yeah, it's meant it separates the words out in the symbology.
I could have told you that except like...
Ah, fuck.
I'm trying to think if there's any other really great ones that I like.
I honestly think that the flag of the...
Wales.
We talked about last week, but I do like Wales.
Wales is cool.
It's got a dragon.
Yeah, and it's pretty iconic.
I think the UK flag is pretty good.
I like the UK flag.
I like that it's a bunch of other flags like superimposed over each other.
I think that rules.
It's pretty good.
Yeah.
I always liked it.
I like it's association with punk stuff, like tattered Union Jack with the chains and stuff.
Like, oh, yeah, fucking whatever.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess so.
I'm a tartan.
I think that's not really so much the flag being cool as punk being cool.
Oh, yeah.
But I mean, I can't help it.
I associate things.
Yeah, I guess so.
Okay, I think that's a sufficient answer.
Next one is called...
Oh, well, it's an imager.
Logic puzzle from Brazil stumps nearly everyone.
Assume that both of the following sentences are true.
Pinocchio always lies.
Pinocchio says all my hats are green.
We can conclude from these two sentences that Pinocchio has at least one hat.
Pinocchio has only one green hat.
Pinocchio has no hats.
Pinocchio has at least one green hat.
Pinocchio has no green hats.
Pinocchio says all my hats are green.
So it means that if he has hats, they're not all green.
That's the only thing that does say, right?
He may or may not have hats.
But if he does have hats, not all of them will be green.
There will be at least one non-green hat.
Yeah, he might...
I think it's...
Yeah, there's a little vagueness in what it means by a lie.
So, like, if he says all my hats are green but he doesn't have any hats, is that a lie?
I guess I would say yes.
So we can't conclude C because he may have hats.
We can definitely conclude E.
No, because he may have, like, three hats and two of them are green.
But not all of them are green.
So we can't do E, we can't do C.
So, okay, he could have at least one hat that's not green or he could have no hats.
Um, I don't think... can we conclude any of these things?
Pinocchio, like, Pinocchio has at least one green hat.
He could have no green hats, so that's not true.
Pinocchio only has only one green hat.
We don't know that he has any hats.
If he has hats, then at least one is not green.
And yeah, that's none of these.
I feel like I've seen a video explaining this one and they said there is a correct answer
and I'm like, fuck you, there isn't.
The question is incomplete if that's the case.
I think the question is too vague.
I think the question is vague in what exactly counts as a lie.
If we knew that he had hats, we could conclude only that at least one of them is not green,
which is none of these answers.
Yeah.
We don't know that.
And yeah.
They say logic puzzle from Brazil.
Does that mean there was a translation mix up into English that made it so vague?
That would make it really shitty if that were the problem.
Okay, correct us if we're wrong, voicemailer, but we're not.
Next one is called, is Ben's occasional reminder played Delta Room Chapter 2?
Okay.
The one after that.
Imgur, let's fucking look.
Let's behold.
UPCB background for trans part.
I mean, what more can I say?
Yeah, this is just a photo of Radcon 4.
True.
Okay, next one is another image.
I can't wait to behold its glory.
We should improve.
We should improve the PCB website, yet you haven't.
This is the image behind the platform.
Yeah, the fucking plan.
Sorry.
No, I think we're going to have to remake it from scratch.
I think we're just going to have to do that.
Yeah.
Oh, oh God, no.
What?
No.
Oh, there's just a recommended image that was really sad and the Imgur recommended images and newest and most viral.
Oh, look at this.
Oh God, Jesus.
What could it be?
My liver is failing.
I have lupus.
I have pancreatitis.
My body is hurting so much and I don't know if I'm going to live or die.
The worst thing about it is my old best friends.
Years ago, we hadn't talked and my best friend said, please don't talk to me.
I'll reach out to you.
I'm not sure what I did.
I haven't seen him in four years.
Not even this will get him talking to me.
I'm scared and need my best friend.
Who wrote this?
Why?
That's terrible.
I just saw.
Why would you recommend this to me, Imgur?
Why?
Because the algorithm says it's very engaging.
Oh God, I freaking.
Oh, no.
I go down in the replies.
I'm sorry.
I go down in the replies and I see freaking sending virtual hug and there's something
so infuriating about that.
There's something.
When I see a sad post and down in the replies, I see sending virtual hug or I see that gif
of freaking Murray from Monsters Inc hugging the girl and I'm just like, drives me fucking
insane.
Yeah, just trying to show sympathy.
I know.
It's not enough.
Yeah.
Why did I even do?
Why did I even look at this?
I don't know.
I'm so stupid.
Hey.
Oh, wait.
Did you hear about Shafrila's?
Shafrila's the YouTube video guy who does videos about movies?
Yes.
Did you hear?
No.
Oh God.
They have lived or failure?
What's what happened?
Well, it turns out and I didn't know this, but they're actually a team of three guys.
There was the guy who reads the scripts.
I think his name is James.
And then there was his brother whose name I forget and their friend, Chris.
And like the name Shafrila's comes from like combining their two last names.
It's like Shafr and Shilas or something.
They combine it into one.
They had a car accident and two of them are dead.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
James is the only one that survived.
That's a...
They were all three of them were in a car and I don't know what happened.
That sucks.
Yeah.
No, it's so fucking bad.
It's so fucking bad.
I found Chris's fiance's Twitter and I saw their Twitter and that was terrible.
And I found frickin, I saw James tweeted that like he's going to keep making videos because he's just got to keep working because it's the only thing he can do now and like, okay, respectable.
And apparently frickin, they had frickin filmed like video cameos from like Chris and like there's footage of Chris that's going to be in like a video that like is still coming out.
No.
I know.
What do you, what is, what can you, what do you do?
What do you do?
I, yeah, I keep going I guess.
He's just, I mean, when Weird Al's parents died of frickin asphyxiation while he was on tour, he just kept touring because like, what can you do?
Yeah.
And I guess, I guess that's what James is doing.
Yeah, I heard this was like, this was like Monday this week.
It was like a couple, this was like half a week ago.
Yeah.
It's all over Twitter.
I'm surprised you didn't see it.
I guess I just follow different people.
I saw it like it was like, maybe it's just my Twitter, but yeah, it was like the top recommendation or like the top trending thing or like one of them for like a couple days there.
Anyway, that's fucking cool.
Anyway, let's look at the next voicemail.
It's a voice, it's an image.
It's an image of the channel customization.
Oh yeah.
I should probably, I should probably just do that.
This is telling me how to change the channel.
Because you know ours right now is like procrastinator's podcast 3692 or whatever.
Oh.
I think I tried to change it and like it didn't let me because like procrastinators had been taken or something.
Or maybe, or no, it seems to say that it's, this image seems to suggest that procrastinator's podcast is free.
So maybe we should do that.
Maybe we should call it, maybe we should call it, we could always call it the perfect comic party.
We could fully rebrand.
I mean it's still a podcast on YouTube.
It is still a podcast on YouTube.
The perfect podcast people.
Maybe we should change the name to the procrastinator's podcast.
Like change the actual channel name as well as the handle.
Yeah, we could.
Makes, makes sense.
The procrastinators isn't really an important distinction.
Should we call it procrastinator's podcast or the procrastinator's podcast?
I think the procrastinator's because it implies that we are the procrastinators rather than this is a podcast for people procrastinating.
Which it may also be, but it's not like a self-help thing.
Yeah, okay.
Alright, alright.
Next one is called make it more parasocial.
Three, two, one, go.
This takes seriously every single stupid idea for the rebranding.
I am loving it.
Also Jesus fucking cries, holy fucking shit.
Ben still didn't play Delta Run, but at this point just wait for the new chapters and play everything over again, I guess.
Why would I play it over again?
I'll just play the new one when it come out.
When chapter three comes out, then I'll finally play chapter two and then when four comes out, I'll play three, et cetera, et cetera.
And then you won't be able to talk about it with everyone.
Everyone will be like, oh, hype about the new thing.
You're like, hey guys, you heard of Queen?
You heard of Spamton?
And everyone's like, yeah, of course.
Anyway.
Anyway, whatever, yeah.
Well, that's fine.
I hate everyone.
Why would I want to talk about a video game with them?
Okay.
What about the Continental Procrastinators podcast?
I love the procrastinators podcast.
I love subscribing to patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Oh, next one is called VVV Next installment.
Oh, here we go.
Is Vinnie back?
It is.
Yeah, it looks like it.
020422.
They re-entered town and here's where we left off.
This is whatever Normie places on the main.
This is what, oh, wait, who?
Oh, you're green and I'm...
Am I green?
No, I thought I was pink.
Oh, Simsie is black because he says blimey.
Yeah, so you're green.
I guess I'm green.
There is whatever Normie places on the main street here
or actually I know a good hole in the wall place to get oriental food.
I wouldn't say oriental food.
Fish and chips is fish and chips no matter how.
I'm up for whatever mates.
But a little hole in the wall sounds nice.
All right, it's down a quaint little alleyway.
Oh boy, a quaint American alleyway.
Yeah, I love.
We just love a quaint American alleyway.
Blimey.
Yeah.
Oh, someone's watching.
Is that a pony?
Tee hee.
What the fuck?
Whoosh, whoosh.
Hello, Ben St. Miss Gibb and Take.
This is your welcome to the hometown, to the hometown USA.
I'm Roxanne Kaiser and this is Julien, my Julien,
my super special son.
Don't introduce me as that baka.
La Mal.
We're here in place of Munchie and Kazi.
They requested their likeness not be illustrated.
Respectable.
I wonder if Vinny actually asked them.
Like actually reached out to them and asked and they said no.
I think that happened.
Okay.
Uh, sure.
What the, you fucking guys popped out to give some meta bullshit.
You're hijacking my comic.
Tee hee.
All that is really to get to this.
Julien and I will have a place for you to sleep at night.
Give and take, room and board will be provided.
No expense to you, of course.
You can find us in place of Munch House,
which Ben St. knows the location of.
With that being said, we should.
We shall bid au revoir, Gibb.
Oh.
Ha ha, thank you.
This is so weird.
Okay.
There's my quaint American alleyway.
Seems nice and quaint.
All right, all right, mate.
Quaint hee.
We're walking down the quaint American alleyway.
Took a little bit to get into the swing of it with my tablet.
Hopefully I can keep these regular again.
Just keep in keeping regular comic content.
I'll jump into the perfect comic podcast too.
I don't know if I'll submit this comic to it,
but we'll see as it goes.
Oh my God.
We want to be a part of the perfect comic party.
Oh God.
I would say yes.
I would say we have a space.
I don't know. This is so embarrassing.
I don't know.
It hits that specific cringe itch.
I don't...
Listen, it's about the comics.
It's not about me.
It's not about me and you.
It's not about art.
It's about unrestrained creativity.
I think this is pretty creative.
I...
I guess, but it...
It's not...
I don't want...
I don't like that I'm a character in it.
I don't know.
Okay, one for one against.
My...
My publication does not need...
Okay, whatever. Yeah, fine.
Gotcha.
Laying in bed guy.
3, 2, 1, go.
Hey, can you guys finally make the next recording
five hours long?
Some of us want something to listen to.
No.
They're just laying in bed thinking about nothing.
Okay, next.
Die. We're only at four and a half hours
and we're probably not going to make five, so get owned.
Get totally destroyed.
Get obliterated, stupid.
That's what you get for listening to our...
So you get for listening to our content.
You fucking jerk.
You wake up and you merely have four and a half hours
to lay in bed and listen to the PCP
before you have to get up.
Next one is called
laying in bed guy.
3, 2, 1, go.
Hey, laying in bed guy.
So that this five hour mark is much easier.
I suggest you guys talk about something that's lengthy.
Well, we don't have one piece this week.
Probably not one piece. God, I hate that.
Fuck you.
Talk about Trixie, any Trixie drama.
That's always funny.
I love Benz reaction.
That's hilarious.
You're welcome.
So let's try to hit that five hour mark.
That four, 59 on 59 seconds.
What is this amateur hour?
Laying in bed guy.
Another voicemail.
Another colorful voicemail character in the bag.
Okay, next one. Yeah, 3, 2, 1, go.
Oh, my apologies. I forgot.
Happy birthday, Ben.
Have a good one.
Happy birthday.
Not my birthday.
Happy birthday, Ben.
Thanks. Thank you.
And that was it.
I think that people should be nicer to me.
Nicer?
In general, yeah.
What could be done, Ben?
I think people shouldn't make fun of me.
Just because I make fun of Trixie on Twitter.
That tweet got a lot of likes.
That tweet got 60 likes. That's not bad.
That was a good tweet.
Okay, fuck the haters.
All right.
That's all I have to say.
Well, yeah, there's no, if we had one piece,
it would have probably pushed it to five hours.
Oh, easily.
But there is no none.
Good week did not have one piece, honestly.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's about it for the show.
Become a patron.
And maybe we'll make an AI bonus episode if someone can tell us how to do that
and do it for us.
We need an AI to like figure out how to use AI software.
Yeah, if only we had like an artificial man made of metal
that had like free will and like a strong sense of justice that could like learn it for us.
He needs a strong sense of justice so that he won't steal other people's content
when he's training the stable diffusion models on.
Mm-hmm.
That would be wrong and unjust.
You see.
Become a patron for bonus content.
And, you know, updates will be coming soon on the Perfect Comic Party.
Yeah.
Working on Clarissa.
Gonna work hard.
Gonna draw.
I'm gonna say I hope to get some time this week
to work on Beescapades since I have to do that.
I'll have to think about like, I'll have to plan out
like a more specific like a chunk of it.
Because kind of before I sort of like would do a couple panels
and then I would ask for like, you know, reader feedback or whatever.
This time I'll probably change it so like I'll do like a big chunk
and then I'll end with like a reader question like what should he do or whatever.
I'm doing like 20 pages because that's how long the chapter is
like where it cuts off in a narratively sensible place.
But there's no reason for like the weekly Beescapades to be like a long thing.
No, it doesn't. No.
It wouldn't have to be like long, long.
But it would be, you know, instead of just like kind of whenever
I would have to sort of pick a spot and be like, OK, I'll call this.
This will be the end of the piece.
Like this is where I want to end it for now and ask an open-ended question
like should he go here or here or whatever.
Yeah. Yeah.
People can respond in the somehow.
Send in fan mail, send fan letters and we open them.
I should probably open a, I'll have to think about how I want to like what
what I should set up to like take a reader suggestions.
Something to pick something could be it.
OK.
All right.
I guess we're done.
I'm done. I'm done.
I've had enough. I've had enough.
I'm actually I'm actually feeling really tired.
I'm feeling really, really tired, exhausted, defeated, demotivated, demoralized.
All of a sudden it's coming over me.
Oh, no, it's not good.
It's over. It's over. It's over.
The procrastination podcast is over.
It's OK. I just I have like I know exactly what I got to do.
I got to do it.
There's like there's like last night I finished like I finished like saving
all the pages in the new format.
And what I need to do now is going to need to like resave them in the color
filtered version.
I need to apply the color filter that I designed to maximize how they look
when they're printed in CMYK as opposed to on the screen in RGB.
So I need to do that.
And that's just a nice little like easy task that I can have very measurable
like I have to do this 200 times.
And then I'll do it 200 times and then I'm done and I can check it off my list.
And that'll be good.
That feels good.
Yeah.
That's OK.
That's the end of the show.
Bye.
All right. Goodbye. See you next week.
OK. That's it.
The end.