I'm supposed to be working right now, I'm supposed to be working right now, but I'm not working, I'm doing nothing, my dick I'm jerking, myself I'm suiting, I am an asshole, I am a stupid, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I
got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick,
I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got a dick, I got
couple times. Maybe maybe had a larger health bar. Maybe CEO
shouldn't make all this money. If that's all they do is
welcome. No, they're welcome. Welcome everybody to the Amazon
Prime podcast. I'm your host, Jeff Bezos. I just made $20
million in the time it took me to say that sentence.
They're in a lot of zoom meetings, though. It's it's rough.
The life of a CEO. It really is. You don't understand. You
couldn't. You can't even jack off during them. Though they
can't. They can't. Yeah. They can't jack off because they
have their like hired whores sucking their dicks. I mean,
they can't. They can't. It's just a little risky, but like
that kind of makes it harder though. These guys are getting
off in ways that we can only dream of. We could never
understand the release. Well, we used to be able to not
understand. Now, now we know all about it. We know exactly
how they jacked off. We're jacking under the table while
in a call where if anyone discovers what you're doing,
it'll cost you the million dollar yo play deal is just
AK 0.0001% of your net worth. So you're risking really
nothing. Exactly. Exactly.
That's okay. Okay. Am I wrong in thinking 0.001 is still
like a lot of money for like a billion?
It is, but they don't care. I mean, 0.001 of a billion would
be a million, right? It's a thousand. So yeah, something like
that.
Did we start the podcast? I feel like that was the beginning.
No. Well, we can tell we can tell Elia's are to put it in.
Okay. Oh, because the Craig recording will have it.
But I just started Audacity. Do you want to, we can sync now?
Oh, I guess we probably should sync. Recording.
Oh, I wasn't, I was only recording with Craig. I just started
recording right now. Elia's are please and thank you. Make it
work. Just make it work. Fix it in post. Okay. That's what we
pay you for. Just make it work. On the count of three, say
sync. One, two, three, sync. Sink. Sink. One, two, three,
sync. Sink. Sink. Wow, you're like way behind. Am I way behind?
That was some buffering. That was some real buffering.
I think I heard you buffering, Ben. Okay, let's do it again.
Let's do it again. One, two, three, sync. Sink. Sink.
No, that's just how it is today, I guess. Yeah, we're just
getting that high ping over there from over the pond.
Based. Elia's are make it work. I told Elia's are the other day
that thanks for being the editor because you're a good
editor and you indulge my whims and when I say hey, make it a
new background, use new graphics, he just says okay and does
it and it's pretty based of him in my humble opinion. Thanks
Eleazar. Let's give a shout out. Thanks, Eleazar. And thanks, bro.
Okay, a mystery was solved for me this week. Have you noticed
that recent episodes have had a strange hashtag on them?
Oh, I think I know where you're going to go with this already,
but yes, the yeah, the hashtags Eleazar's discord handle,
right? That's what it turned out to be. Yeah, the episodes have
had this hashtag like they've been tagged like hashtag 7532,
I think, and I didn't know what it was. And it turns out it's
Eleazar's discord number, which he like he includes his
discord info in the description, which makes sense. But it was
showing up as a tag on the video and you could see it. So if
anyone noticed that, that's what that was. But he says he's
fixed it in the description and it won't show up anymore. Yeah,
lol, major, I mean, that's not so bad. It could be like a craftsman's
mark on each episode. Keep an eye on everybody for the Eleazar
discord t-shirt coming soon to the PCP. Yeah, we will we will
profit and not share any of it with him. And he will get it in
notifications. He will be, I mean, he'll get so much exposure
for people wearing his discord shirts. I saw a number on a
person's shirt and I'm crowded like in public and I just
thought I should say hi. I just thought I should contact Eleazar
for all my editing needs. That's what it made me think.
Yeah, so I don't know. This week, I think this week, Bitcoin
Bitcoin went well off down the tubes and it hasn't
been well. Welcome everybody to the procrastinators podcast.
We didn't even say that I'm to see you know now because I
said it before anybody else did. That's true. That's true. We
got Ben Saint and give and take on this episode. Anyways,
Bitcoin's shit now apparently it's down to 43k. Last I
checked it went it went down. Yeah, I bought this isn't I'll
just tell you I bought some when it was like high I bought some
at at 58k lol and then I bought some more after it fell. I
bought at like some more at like 40 48 I think I bought it
48 as well. Yeah. So they average out I think the amount
that I've got is averaged around like 52 and now it is down
to 44 and a half. So I mean it's not doing great but like you
know that's that's like a week. I'm like not that stressed
about it this time. I'm not well feeling as constantly
anxious as I as I was before. I feel I mean when it started
going down from like the peak the most recent peak mine says
like 41k as in pounds sterling. Yeah. So I don't know what it
is for you but like it started going down then it went back
up and I was just gonna come right back up and go even higher
and it has not done that. Yeah. So I'm losing money but like
I'm not cashing out ever so I guess I'm not losing anything.
I'm sad that Ethereum is down so much but I'm not super sad
because I haven't bought any Ethereum. I just got my
Ethereum for free. So who cares then. Dude 69 Ethereum. I want
that to be more. I want to get even bigger returns. It was
up to over 300. Now it's back down to 228 which is just
not. Okay. The worst thing that one voicemail said like
index funds is a good thing. Was that the thing he was
saying? Minerva. I forget who but was it an index fund?
Yeah. That was that was Minerva and I think she said it was
an index fund or something. Yeah. I was I've been meaning to
go back and listen to that segment again because she
seemed to have some good advice not for like from a vault
not for like fucking buy in the dip in a volatile market
like cryptos but just in like solid like long term
investing strategy. Yeah. Just kind of better like fuck this
up and down. I remember the name and I looked it up but
I wasn't sure if that was the thing they said but index
funds are like kind of like a stock that replicates like
sort of mimics the market as a whole. So if it's not one
particular thing. So if things are it's really safe bet
because it's very unlikely that everything goes down
such as in a 2008. Well, I think it kind of did like I
think I think like this week this the market just kind of
took a hit and sort of took Bitcoin down with it. That's
what I was reading. I don't actually know if that's true.
I could be totally wrong. That's what people on our
slash Bitcoin were saying. I will have to mention that this
is not a money show. We never understand money ever and we
will never understand Bitcoin. I understand I understand
money and I don't even don't even pretend that we're
trying to be smart about it. I'm not the worst thing that
happened this week though. This made me so angry. It was so
infuriating. I finally sold my GameStop only for it to
suddenly shoot up again. I had finally it was no like days
before like you know I bought it like at the beginning of a
month and I was like okay it like rose for like a couple days
there and then it settled back down and it had like not moved
and I was like okay it was just a meme. It's not going
anywhere and then like later that same week it suddenly
shoots up to like 180. Literally it went up to 200.
Yeah I would have I actually would have made money. If I had
sold to 200 I actually would have made money but no I lost
like most of it because I sold it 50. I sold it 160. I bought
it at 210 so I still lost a lot of money but like way better
than like I was considering just like getting rid of it.
So I'm like uh no but I was like no I'm going to hold.
I did just because you got to hold and in the game of Stonks
you either hold or die. No I don't believe you have to sell
eventually. You have to sell eventually. The key is timing
when and yet and I fucked it up. I just there were no
indications that anything else is going to happen with it.
I know because like because like they they had the the trial
or whatever or the the hearing with that guy with deep fucking
value and like I saw a little graph like when he said that he
was still bearish on GameStop apparently it had like you know
I was still even saying oh the the the stock shot up the
stock shut up and it looked and it went up by like eight
dollars. I was like okay so it's not really moving that much
and I was like fucking I'm selling and that only for to
like quidruple overnight. Yeah I was watching it happen in
real time like what is happening because like I'm in like I'm
in a discord server with like Saber Spark and a couple other
guys just talking about the stock stuff we're all just like
what is going on right now just watching it go up in real time
was crazy. Just. We decided that the stock market's not real
and it's fake and it'll never be understood ever by anyone.
I mean it's it's like it's it is gambling the whole thing the
Bitcoin the stocks the whatever you put in money. Saber was
mentioning something like options like do you know anything
about options? I think it was who's called option that I was
only half paying attention because like I used to know
you make like a bet that a stock is going to be at a certain
price by a certain time or you lose your money. I'm like how
is that not like why not just why not just invest in the
stock? I don't I don't know I don't get it but like just
explaining the concept I'm like isn't this just like like
betting on horses or something but you're just betting on
stock like literally I guess I guess people would bet that
the stock would go down and so they wouldn't want to have the
stock. I don't know. I don't understand. Well, she's short
it then. Like over that over that. Somebody in the in the
chat who's smart explained to me what why how that's not
gambling. I know in way too smooth brain to understand. I
know in theory how shorting a stock works. I have no clue
how one would actually go about doing it. So I don't know
maybe that's like an easier way of you just need a big bunch of
money. You you buy a bunch of stock. Okay. You buy a bunch of
stock. You borrow the stock and then you borrow it. The the the
key is no so that then you have to I hate you. I hate you.
You're explaining what it is in theory but how do you actually
do it? How do you actually do that? Just go to Google search
how to short stock and I'm sure wiki how will tell you exactly
how to do it with pictures. No, you don't know. I have no idea.
Yeah. Of course not. Yeah. Yeah. I wouldn't imagine that's what
I'm saying. I'm on a podcast on the internet. You think I know
anything of substance? If I did, I'd be doing that instead of
being on the procrastinators podcast. Okay. Well, you're
right. Obviously. The thing with all of this though is it's
like I put the money in and yes, technically it's you have to
cash out but I don't see any reason to cash out until you
can make a profit. Like if it never because if you die, I mean
it's so you can make a profit. Yeah, but like I don't know.
Whoa. It's like imagine if you spend like like like I don't
know a hundred pounds, a hundred dollars on food and then
that money is spent, the food is eaten, life goes on. In this
situation, you throw it down a well and in the future, it may
come back. I don't see much of a reason to like it's
reductive. I don't know. The reason is because there are
people who put money into stock market, they can't afford to
lose. That's why. It's all about opportunity cost, right?
Because like, okay, say you have, I don't know, Bitcoin and
Bitcoin is going, I mean, if Bitcoin goes down and Ethereum
goes up, then hypothetically, you would have made more money
if you had sold your Bitcoin and bought Ethereum. So like even
if you weren't like even if you were selling the Bitcoin of
the loss, you could be reducing your loss and maybe turning
loss into gain if you sold at the right time and did the
right thing with the money. It's about maximizing.
I know that the min-maxing of it is much more efficient at
like actually making the gains, but I don't like the lifestyle
and the, you know, I've said this before. Like to play it the
way I'm playing it, it's only useful to take out money when
there's a profit. Until then, it's gone and that's fine, but
it's like a ghost. You could revive it.
But if you, but only if you expect there to eventually be a
profit, right? Yeah, that might be, and that might not be, but
like, yeah, I invested in the first place on the assumption
that it would make a profit. My assumption, okay, I have, I
am not worried about the dip because I invested this, this
time I bought some Bitcoin with a solid, wait, who just left
the fucking call? Was that Craig? I fucking hate Craig.
Did Craig just abandon us? I, like he always does, yes.
He always, he always does this. Craig's the worst guest on the
PCP. He just doesn't work. Why doesn't he just fucking work?
Oh boy, I'm mad. He comes on here and he doesn't say
anything. Freeloader. And then when we, and when we have to
pay him, and we have to pay him 25% of the, of the, of the
cut, because he's so big. Man, it's a good thing we don't
rely on Craig and still record locally. Imagine if we just
lost everything. Lol. Yeah, I mean, yeah, sure. And then we
won't even, okay, whatever, we got the beginning. Okay, I'll
try and get him to come back in. It doesn't matter. Um, was,
wait, he's messaging. Oh, he said, okay, I fucking, I say,
hey, Craig rejoined the call and he DMs me to say, I'm already
recording that channel. No, you're fucking not Craig.
You're a liar, Craig. Fail to join. This is gaslighting.
I hate you. I hate you, Craig. I hate him so much. I hate his
stupid fucking bare face. It is like the worst illustration
ever. That's not true. But it's up there. It's up there.
It's very, it's poor. It's a poor. Um, okay, anyway, whatever,
I'll try and get him back in. If, uh, what was I saying? Fuck.
Something, something, something money, something, something
stonk, something, something Bitcoin, I don't remember.
No, no, no, I had a point I was gonna make. Uh, we were talking
about, what did you just say, Gib? I just said that there's
no reason to, like, like, you should always only sell it at
a profit and never sell it before that point. I remember.
I remember. Okay. I bought Bitcoin this time because I had
a notion and I still think it makes sense and is probably
true to some extent. And that is that everyone said that the
stimulus package, the money printers go, is going to, if
not cause inflation, it will at least create concern about
inflation and Bitcoin is seen as a hedge against inflation.
And therefore it makes some amount of sense to think that the
price of Bitcoin will rise in response to the stimuli and
also that people will be putting their stimmies into Bitcoin
because a lot of people want to invest and that'll be their
first opportunity to do so. So I think it makes logical sense
and I could be wrong. Well, it kind of did. I guess I think it,
I think it kind of did happen with previous stimmies, but so
I'm expecting that it, that, that there will be a jump in
response to the stimuli and I, I, I'm just going to hold it
until then. And if it crashes to zero and I lose everything,
well, fuck it. I won't starve. So, you know, it's fine. It's
fine. But it is, I do think it'll, I do think it'll crash
eventually. It won't stay at like 40 or 50 forever.
I think it might, like, my imagination really is just
saying, oh, patterns, huh? It went up real big from nothing.
And then it went back down and stayed down, but then it went
back up again and it went even higher. This means it will
absolutely go even higher than this time. And that's like my
stupid like a monkey pattern seeking brain is like, yes,
there's absolutely a chance that it will get even bigger than
this.
Yeah. You know, I did, I was, because I watch a YouTube
channel called Clear Value Tax where Brian explains how to
make money to me. Thanks, Brian. Love you. And he, this is
Donate to my Patreon and I'll tell you all about it. In
hindsight, in hindsight, I'm so infuriated because there was a
video that he, that he put out advising like how you should
like invest like specifically it was called When You Should
Sell Bitcoin. And basically his thesis was this thing about,
in response to the stimulus is probably gonna, he says like it
lines up timing wise with the time frame of like previous
Bitcoin crashes. And also the stimulus seems like it's a
promising thing that'll cause a rise. And so he's planning to
like start trickling his out around then. But he released that
on February 8th, literally the day that Tesla spent the like
billions of dollars on Bitcoin and it exploded. Like he
released it that same day. But I didn't watch it then. I
didn't watch it until several weeks later. And when I
watched it, I was like, he's right. And I invested and that
was the day it fucking crashed. It was so bad. Always. I hate
you, Brian. I hate you. You betrayed me.
Uh, brutal. Absolutely. I feel like the the Bitcoin era of
the PCP, um, it was pretty stupid. Oh, yeah. We never talk
about it ever again. Ben, you're just too lefty for stocks
that they just they just inherently it's like oil and
water. They hate me. Every time you get into the market, it
just pushes away from you. I I hope that's true. I wish I
had the power. If I if I had known that, okay, if you had
told me Ben, you actually have the power. If you invest in
Bitcoin, it will go down. You will lose your own money, but
it will destroy Bitcoin. I would have done it anyway just to
fuck Elon Musk over. I would have considered I would have
considered it to be a worthwhile investment. So in that
sense, I'm not too bothered about it. That might have lost
tons of money on Bitcoin, but he has the moral victory and
that's all that really matters. If if I had known that it
would have happened, I think I would have done it. Of
course, in reality, the drop would have happened without
me investing. So I wish I hadn't. And then I could have
just laughed at the dip without cringing in pain. But
it's not a perfect world. It's not a perfect world. I'm not
a perfect person. Oh, God. In a perfect world, men like me
would not exist. In a perfect world. You wouldn't exist.
What is that from? It's from the potion seller guy.
From what? He made a video where he was like, oh wait, the
thing you said? I don't know what that thing you said. No, what
you said. I was talking about the thing I said. Is it a
YouTuber? It's it's the guy who goes, you know, with the
funny face filter thing and he's like, potion seller, I
need one of your strongest potions. It's like my potions
are too strong for you, Trevor. You know that guy? I think
I know that guy. I think I'm only familiar with it second
hand. Oh, well, he's funny. And he makes those videos all
the time. Like just like fucking around with face filters.
And he did one where he was like, let me just find the
link. You can put it in the description. I learned a lot
today. Yeah. Post the link. Is Craig, Craig says he's in
here. What is he? Craig, we came and left like four times
during your tirade on easy Bitcoin. It was very strange. Oh
yeah, I've seen this video. Here's here's the video. It's
53 seconds long. That's too long. That's one whole voicemail
we could be listening to instead. It's not a perfect
world. Okay, okay. It's like pretty old, right? I remember
watching this seven years old. Yeah, okay. That's about
right. Oh, 2013. This filter is really good. It's really
working for me. That fucking Mac webcam filters going on
right now. I told Craig to join again. If he tells me he's
already recording, I'll know. I'll know that he that I
succeeded. He says he's in the call. He says a lot of
things. Not a very trustworthy narrator. No, terrible.
Yeah, go on. Funny videos. I think I was gonna say I think
okay, fine, okay. No, it's it's because of the lag. Like
every time I open my mouth, you have begun something and I
was like, oh, I should stop speaking and then every time
you hear me going, you're like, oh, Gabe wants to say
something. I should stop speaking. Look at this. I tell
it's it's in the call. I tell it to leave the call. It says
I'm not recording. It's not in the call. I say join the call.
He says I'm already recording. Curse him. Okay. We need to
stop talking about Craig. I'm sure the audience is not
super invested in our frustrations with a 12th member
of the procrastinators podcast, Craig. Or are they?
The commenters, let us know. Yeah, I guess so. I don't think
I've seen a single comment talking about Craig. The Craig
is in full swing. Bummer. It's like a sleeper arc. Yeah, I
think I am done. Not done, but I think I'm over my my deepest
obsession with Noida at this point. I think I've I think I
was going I think I was way too hooked on Noida for a
little bit there. But I had a I had a run I got them I got
one of the endings. I got the not the like get every orb
ending, but the get every orb just from like the normal
world ending, which is like almost the best ending. It's
like the second best one. So I feel like I've done a lot
with it. And maybe I can be a little free of its malign
influence now. I was I was trapped in its world, like
Jumanji. But now I was in there, mixing potions and
shit. Building wands. I was today I was today I was rambling
in my discord server about a wand crafting theory. No one
was interested. But I just wanted to explain about how an
autocast laser wand is actually really good because that
applies. It's a cast delay modifier without its mana
consumption. So just just think about that. Think about
that if you will fast. I'll think about it. Okay. Okay,
good. Okay, good. Well, that's me. That was that was my
week sick based. Love it. Me too. I have this music club
thing, where in a discord, we say to each other, let's
listen to these albums, we like bring an album forth, and
we vote on which ones we want to listen to, and then we
listen to them, and we talk about them. And the last
week, a pro mayor. Like the anime? Like the yeah, like
death note, like, like, like, like Naruto. He was a Naruto.
She was a Kunuichi. Could it be anymore obvious? I love that
song. He was a Naruto. She was a Kunuichi. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, stuff like that. I was like, I really
like that. I've heard that. I have no I have no idea what
you're talking about. Promare is like emo girl, singing
about feelings in the early 2000s band. Wait, isn't
pro-marine? Isn't pro-marine? Paramore. Paramore.
Okay. Paramore is a band. I know, sorry. It is an anime.
Okay. All right. I know. So, Paramore. So, Paramore AMV2
Paramore. Make it happen, people. Yeah, and if I can, it's
like Gun Girl Accord. It's like, that's good. That's what I
want. I want to be into that. I think the greatest human
achievement I can ever like achieve is to be unironically
into like Paramore and Evanescence and just be a big
actual fan of those sorts of things. That's a really lofty
goal you've set for yourself. I know. I'm trying. I don't
know. I'm struggling every day. I support this. I mean, it's
about the journey. It's about the climb. If you never make
it, it's okay. Yeah, so I listen to that. That was good. Do
you, like I, I, I, I, I missed out on, oh yeah. I, I, I don't
know much about that sort of music other than I've heard
bits of it in YouTube videos and I knew that emos were a
thing, but I never really saw any at school and I sort of
missed the boat on all of that stuff. I mean, but I kind of
feel like I like it. I kind of feel like I wanted to be that.
I, I not ironically enjoyed Evanescence first album and
even listening to it recently, as in recently being a few
years ago, still slaps, still like it. Did they not have,
were there no like emo or goth kids at school, Gib?
No, there must have been a few. There was one guy. But they
were all black so you couldn't see them. They were invisible.
Well, not, not like they wore all black. Yeah, that's what I
mean. Oh, the, the African American students. Oh, the
African American goth. They're completely invisible. That's
why, that's why they're so rare. It's a rare sighting. The
African British population just loves Paramores. I don't
know why even if they're wearing black, they would be
invisible because the, the world is like, it's the sun's out.
It's daytime. Um, you can see them. Only really. Maybe that's
why I never saw them. There was a girl in my photography
class who had like, seen girl hair without the, uh, like
hair dye. Yeah. And I was like, oh, she's, uh, pretty.
Yes. But she was a lesbian apparently. Of course. They
all are. Fuck up. She was, she was really cool. You can't.
That's the problem. No. No. But that, that was the only
person who was even remotely in that sort of thing.
Cool woman. Pick one. That's what I'm saying.
How about both? That's my official statement. No.
No. What if Dora the Explorer was a goth? Yeah. What if she was?
What then? Dora the Explorer, goth blingy gift circa 2001 on
MySpace. It exists somewhere, I'm sure.
Yes, I'm Dora the Explorer. Yes, I'm goth. We exist.
We should be, uh, goth. We should like do a goth rad con.
I already was. I already was goth. I mean, we're, we're, we're
like tombstones right now. Right now we're dead. Like tombstones.
We should be skeletons as well. There should be bats and spiders.
Think about the Halloween episode we're going to have with
these images. It's going to be so aesthetic. Oh my God. Yes.
The Halloween episode, we're going to be like fucking
Five Nights at Freddy if I'd.
Ooh. Do you see that new Five Nights at Freddy's game for PS5?
It's like full 3D now. Like it's pretty weird. It's pretty crazy.
Uh, no. Yeah, I saw that. There was a Sony, like Nintendo Switch
Direct, but Sony version. They should make the Five Nights at Freddy's in VR.
I mean, I'm sure they have Five Nights at Freddy's. They already do.
Oh, well, you know, it was really strange about that new Five Nights at Freddy's game
that like fucked with me. Is that like they had like actual,
like human characters in like third person you could see the people
and they looked like cartoons. I'm imagining they look like the doll people in Toy Story,
like Andy. Yeah, it kind of was like that. And I'd always just kind of assumed it was just like
photo realistic humans and only the animatronics. That's, that's why they're animatronics.
That's why Five Nights at Freddy's like works and is good because you don't see any humans.
And the only characters you see are the animatronics, which are made according to
what's his name's like, what's his name is just he's only, he's only good at making like terrible
looking animatronics, which just happens to work with a game that's about being hunted by evil
animatronics. Yeah, if, yeah, there's a reason it's minimal. That's terrible. I didn't,
I didn't think, I didn't think that was a good call. I think it should have,
should have been real looking humans, but you know, it's like, yeah, so they don't care about
what I think, I guess. Yeah, it should have had like FMV actors or something. That would have been
sick. Yeah, that's what I, that's what I would have done. 480p, 124p, video file, human actors on
a green screen. Yeah, like a Sega CD. Yeah, like 12 FPS. Sega CD shit should come back. It was
terrible, but I like looking at it. Yeah, yeah, it's good stuff. But good, I mean bad. Yeah,
because the only human you see in a Five Nights at Freddy's game is you. Well, I mean, and you
don't see yourself. So it's just assumed that you just look like yourself. And you're just in this
place with these robots. And the robots look like they look because they're designed to be like
cartoony looking. And yeah. And then they got blood, they got red blood coming out. And it's like,
it's like a creepypasta. And they got big teeth. I've probably talked about, I've probably talked
about it before, but when I get, I get inspired whenever I think about that, how like, I mean,
you know, like his Scott Cawthorne's game, like before Five Nights at Freddy's, like the kind
of stuff he made. It's like a cute animal platform where they got tore to shreds because it looked
creepy. So he was like, all right, let's just roll with it. And he made it creepy. Yeah, because
when he tried to make animal characters in 3D, his aesthetic was just like just bad and looked
gross and creepy. So we just leaned into it and made a game about creepy looking animal characters.
I like unironically love stories like that. Yeah. It's like, I'm bad at everything. I'm bad at
everything except this one thing. So let me make a game that's completely about that and it works
and it's genius. A story that vaguely reminded me of that because like, you know, like Daft Punk,
you know, you know how Daft Punk, like they're dead, they die, they're gone. I heard they're dead.
Yeah. Sad face, press F in the chat for Daft Punk. I was reading an article about like Daft Punk,
because, you know, in regards to them, like no longer being a thing. And I guess like before
Daft Punk, they had like another like band with like a third guy and they got a really bad review
and someone called it like Daft Punkish or something or other. And they took that and made
a new band called Daft Punk and it blew the fuck up. That guy must be like an idiot.
That's great. That guy, that guy is the is the TJ Henry Yoshi of music reviews.
You know, he said an A-press is an A-press. You can't tell it's only a half. Well,
shows what you know. An A-chord is an A-chord. You can't play only a half A-chord. You can.
I saw a gif or I saw a video showing the original song that the one more time
chorus was sampled from and like how it was. Yeah. Yeah. It was like stretched out and like
pieces cut out of it and, you know, cycled around. Super cool. I kind of, I mean, when has
Daft Punk like put out a new album in years? I mean, I know they weren't dead. Random Access
Memories was the last one. They felt pretty dead to me for a long time.
You know, they felt like something that used to make, somebody that used to make music.
Yeah. I mean, I wasn't, I wasn't, they weren't really on my radar until Random Access Memories.
I think I'd maybe heard of them before once or twice. I love to describe it.
And then that was like an incredible album that's like, oh, wow. I can't really see if they do
anything more. And then like that came out in 2012 or something. Have you seen, have you seen
Interstellar 5555? Hell yeah. Love that movie. Yeah. It's great. Do you know what it is?
Is it when they go back in time because there's this space and there's a time vortex and they
No, they don't go back in time. They go to like a different galaxy or a different universe.
They get like abducted for something, right? Yes. They get abducted from like an Earth guy.
Abducts these alien, these aliens of bands. Daft Punk made an album called Discovery and
Interstellar 5555. And like Discovery is like their big one that has like one more time and stuff.
Yeah, that's the album that this movie is based on because they took the entire album
and they animated like an anime movie to all the songs in succession.
And the plot is like, it's like these alien band and like they get abducted by some Earth
people and like reprogrammed to think they're like an Earth band, like they look like humans.
And it's a lie. Literally this guy, he's just a music executive and he's like, hmm,
I gotta chomp on his cigar. I gotta find some talent. I gotta moichandize something.
It's like Space Jam, except it's at a basketball. It's music.
It's like Space Jam in reverse. Pretty much.
Oh, she's like, oh shit, but the best band in the universe is on another planet.
Can't make money from that.
I know, I'll steal him and I'll paint him to look human and that's what he does.
It's really a euphemism for capitalism and how it's exploitative when you really think.
Doesn't he? Is that the blue people in the music video?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
It was on that tsunami back in the day.
He literally like puts them through a machine that like splats them with like human colors,
skin, goo and makes them look like humans.
Harder, better. I don't forget what it's actually called.
Yes. Oh God.
I think it's called Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger.
Yeah, Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger.
It's legendary. It's great. Definitely worth watching. Check it out.
The best one. I like the one where the space, the alien like army guy who is sent to rescue them
is like looking at the poster of the girl and it might not be the right one.
It might not be the right time, but there's something about.
Yeah, that one's a, I'm getting, I'm getting, I'm getting all emotional.
That's pretty good.
What interested me about the Daft Punk like epilogue video was the,
you know, the two guys Daft and Punk.
Daft kept walking and Punk was just like, no, I've had enough. I want to stop.
And then the other, you know, Goldilocks, Golden Manhead, he,
he blew up his friend because he wanted to stop making music.
Obviously the metaphor is that I want to stop being in the band,
but the other guy just keeps walking.
So I wonder if like there's going to be more of his music.
I didn't know there was a video. I haven't seen this.
Oh yeah. Oh, it's, it's a really cool video.
It's super cool. It's like a little short film.
Oh, okay.
To like announcing there.
Yeah, they put it up on YouTube.
Yeah. It's, it's, it's a wordless announcement.
Like it's, it's very well put together.
It's just like body language tells the entire story.
And one of them blows up.
And an explosion, a very sick explosion.
Completely final, like, like the helmet is destroyed.
It's gone. He's gone.
Oh.
Say my final message.
It's actually like, maybe feel a little bit.
Maybe feel a little bit.
Watching the Silver Man get blown.
It wasn't good, but like it was well done.
I was like, oh man, goodbye.
He like takes, he like stops and like takes his jacket off.
And there's a self-destruct button on the back.
And like the gold guy presses it and he just walks.
And there's this long shot that lasts way too long.
And then he blows up.
It's fucking sick, but sad.
And made me feel like really like bad.
Gold guy has to go on to join a steam powered giraffe now.
He has to join up with the only other robot band in existence.
It's the only place for him.
He keeps walking in the desert and he bumps into,
can guess it on the lizard wizard.
Gold's going to make a cameo in the Five Nights at Freddy's
video game coming.
He's going to come into like the next Gorillaz album.
Got to make money somehow in the interim.
He takes his like dome screen face off
and it's just teeth under there.
And he used the Five Nights at Freddy's all alone.
That was Freddy.
Oh, he was Freddy.
Of course.
Freddy Fazbear under there the whole time.
Doftpunk at Freddy's.
Mm.
I'm glad we figured that out.
How unfortunate that our specific expertise,
we can figure out that deep mystery,
but we can't figure out the stock market or Bitcoin.
It's because there's not enough funny things
in the stock market.
It's just numbers.
Where's the pixels?
Where's the fucking high res bloom effect?
I don't like looking at it.
Where's the contrasting colors?
Oh, never mind.
It's here on my price chart.
There's the red candles and the green candles.
It's a masterpiece.
Yeah, never mind.
Never mind.
Bitcoin is actually the greatest work of art
of the 21st century.
It's true.
I think those like fake like CG renderings of a Bitcoin,
if it were physical, does a lot to sell people on the idea.
Like way more than people would imagine.
You mean the one that the slime coin is based on?
Yeah, those like fake like, what if Bitcoin was real?
I mean, there are real coins like that.
They're like, they're just collectible.
But like, the idea to make that at all
is like a really good publicity thing.
Because I don't know what the fuck a graph coin looks like.
I mean, I watched it.
I think I mentioned that someone sent me a video explaining
what it actually is and it's not what I thought it is at all.
It's literally a Bitcoin is literally like a record of transactions.
Basically, that's encrypted.
It's like the very basic version that leaves out a lot.
There was a guy linked me a really good video about it.
And I think I mentioned it on a previous episode,
but now I forget what it was called.
Yeah, it's hard to visualize and it doesn't matter really.
Because like at the end of the day,
it's just the same as any other stock.
Like I pay money in and the number goes up or down
and then I get money out and it's more or less and yay.
That's all it really means to me.
Yeah, I guess it's better than trading with loaves of bread
because those go moldy.
I can't store those in a bank.
Those aren't a secure store of value.
You got to read debt.
Gib, did you ever read debt by David Graber?
No, I heard about it.
I was in the book reading club with Munchie and I was like,
ah, you know, this sounds like something I should do
and I didn't do it.
Debt is one of the most interesting books I've ever read.
I recommend it to everyone.
It's fascinating.
I feel like it'd be a huge downer if I read it though.
It's not that much of a downer.
It's not even that like.
But I'm in so much debt, Ben.
Would that make it a downer?
Oh, um, I mean, yeah.
You're a downer no matter what.
You know, that's fair.
That might be a little upsetting.
That might be it might be a little irritating.
But I mean, what it what it really does is it like money
doesn't come from where you think it comes from basically.
And like the the idea that like the idea that like.
It's a talk about fractional reserve banking
and how the U.S. government buys bonds
from the Federal Reserve in exchange for reserve notes.
And then a little banks can like loan it out.
But every time they make a loan,
they actually can like loan out 10 times the amount of money they have.
Well, I mean, it's it's more about like the historical like development of it
and how like pre industrial cultures have things that are like money,
but are really not used in the same ways that we use money.
And and how like people just kind of assume that like before money,
there was a sort of there like the barter system was used.
And there was like an exchange, you know, a certain like number of loaves of bread
equal like a number of, you know, like clay bricks or whatever.
But like, it's not really that simple.
And like the idea of like payment and exchange and owing sort of like came after money,
like the money was invented and it wasn't like there was no.
I don't know.
It's more complicated than I'm I mean, that that would be interesting.
Like the fucking missing link between bartering and money.
Like yeah, like it's not as it's not.
There was there wasn't it's not like, oh, we used to barter,
but then money was invented.
And that just simplified bartering like no money kind of came first.
It's in a in a way.
It's pretty long book.
There's a lot I should reread it actually,
because I'm sure there was stuff I missed on the on the first go.
Not as long as, um, oh God, what was that other one?
Oh, fuck, there was one like 17 hour one was like an old historical book
by a guy like a nobleman who visited the United States in like its slavery times
and wrote about it.
Oh, that one was boring.
That one was boring, but I stuck it out.
I listened to the whole thing and now I can't remember what it was called.
No, sorry, I fucked up.
How unfortunate.
Very sad, sad.
Wow.
What are there?
What else happened this week, guys?
Any any news?
Do we want to talk about?
No, OK, go on.
Go on.
I was just going to talk about how I'm really sad that computer parts are forever
gone.
Like it's never going to happen.
I wanted to buy a new graphics card.
I wanted to play some new video games and super high frame rates.
And you just can't you just can't do it.
And it really sucks.
And it's really bothering me because I keep thinking like, oh, I can't.
How much longer can it last?
How much longer can this chip shortage last?
How much longer can these scalpers continue to win?
And now everyone's saying like it's probably going to go through 2022.
I'm like, oh, I didn't know.
I didn't even know that was happening.
It's so bad.
So like there's there's been like a huge shortage of just like like chip manufacturing
because like basically everybody gets their chips manufactured through a company called
Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing or TSMC.
So they're getting slammed with all these like orders like you got to make the fucking
all the new consoles.
You got to make all the fucking Apple iPhone things.
You got to make all the AMD process.
You're going to make all the Nvidia graphics cards.
And like, well, actually, Nvidia makes goes to the Samsung.
But that's besides the point.
So like there's just a huge shortage of just like chips, like computer components.
And so we're at the point now where the shortage is getting so bad
that even like car manufacturers can't finish making cars because like the computers that
run cars like you can't make them anymore.
And so like new graphics cards and stuff launched like six months ago and they're
still impossible to get a hold of.
And it's at the point where like at first, like there's like this whole like
gray market of people who would like buy shoes with like like computer like algorithms,
like immediately buy all the stock and then flip them and like scalp them for like way
higher prices.
And I guess someone, some of them figured out, Hey, why don't we like start scalping
video game consoles and computer components because they're way more expensive.
And so all these cards are being immediately bought by like algorithms
and sold for like triple to quadruple what they're supposed to cost.
And it's been that way since like September when all the shit launched.
And now like they just released new cards, like a $300 graphics card and video did.
And now the stores are just like, fuck it, we're going to scalp it.
So the stores are listing them at $600.
I just cut out the middle man.
Like this, the retailer.
So now selling them for double the cost of what they're supposed to be.
And it's just like the nightmare is never going to end.
And it's like, I just want a PS5 and they're still not in stock and they won't be until next year.
That sucks so bad.
No, you know what the worst thing is?
You know what the worst thing is?
I had a 30, 60 TI in my house.
I bought one.
I paid $200 more than I should have for it.
And it was broken.
I had to send it back.
The one card I could actually get was defective and I had to return it.
And New Eggs specifically was like, we don't have a return policy on this.
You have to get it replaced.
I'm like, good.
I want it replaced.
And they're like, we don't have any stock.
Where does she find you?
I'm like, fuck, it's gone.
And now I'm not going to be able to get one until next year.
It's truly a nightmare.
It sucks.
How can anybody be letting this happen?
Like so many people are involved in computers.
Well, how do you stop it?
I mean, increase the supply, I guess.
But the scalping thing is like, you take all of the stuff away from the hands of the consumers.
Yeah, you would think that market forces would increase supply in exchange.
Like this obviously represents a surplus of demand.
Well, the problem, I guess, right now is because of COVID and shit.
And because there's only like all these all these fucking companies use one company to do all their
manufacturing TSMC does like all the manufacturing for AMD, all the manufacturing for Apple,
you know, like even even like, I think even Intel now, they usually do their manufacturing
in-house, but they're starting to move to TSMC as well.
So like they're just like slammed and there's just too much demand and there's not enough supply.
And it's just bad.
It's really fucking bad.
That one guy who like he had like 500 PS5s or whatever, he was going to scalp them for
higher price and then he got robbed.
I remember that.
It's pretty funny.
That was based.
It was pretty based.
There was like a thing for a while back in like I think December.
I don't know whether I like the idea that like this situation should be happening at all.
No, it should.
Scalping PS5s doesn't bother me as much as like people that were scalping like toilet paper
and hand sanitizer because those are like those are like necessities.
Yeah.
Yeah, but like still, I mean still fuck scalpers, but like, you know, not as much.
I'm more insulted that stores are just scalping now.
I'm just like, yeah, it sucks.
It's super gross.
I just like this is a serious problem because like if people need stuff and there's just some
like a very small minority of people who have all of the things from the stores,
then the stores are just what they're going to.
This can't be sustainable.
I mean, Nvidia is now selling like five year old graphics cards again,
just to have something to sell.
And those are selling for way more than they cost when they first came out
because the demand is just there and people are just buying whatever is there.
It's really dumb.
But I don't know.
I guess I guess cap free markets.
Like if they'll pay for it, let them buy it.
Question mark.
Like I bought my old ass graphics card like three years ago for like $180.
It's selling for like 400 plus used right now.
Hey, I got good news though.
Bitcoin, Bitcoin's up to 45.
Oh God, fuck you.
Holy shit.
That rose a whole five hundo.
1.28% according to Robinhood.
It's up.
Very nice.
Oh yeah, I can see it.
It's interesting how like all crypto moves at the same time.
Like I'm looking at Dogecoin, Ethereum and Bitcoin and like the trends are all identical.
Like the market moves together for the most part.
It's very strange.
Seems to you.
Too large.
Dogecoin is still just kind of, how is it?
It's fucking around.
It's just kind of tipping off for a while.
Yeah, it's just kind of hanging out.
My investment in Dogecoin was pretty good.
I'm up 100% on Dogecoin still.
I invested a little too late.
I have, what do I have?
Like 600 Dogecoin or something?
I have 5,597 Dogecoin currently.
I mean, I would say I wouldn't expect it, but you know,
that's coming from the guy who sold his GameStop.
So what the fuck do I know?
Did you, someone was telling me,
I don't remember if I mentioned this last time on the podcast,
how Elon Musk wants saying like,
Oh, I want to send Dogecoin to the moon.
I want to invest in it big time,
but it's really kind of not cool that a small amount of people own almost all the Dogecoins.
So you got to sell off your Dogecoin first, then I'll invest.
And it's like, says the richest man in the world.
Like what are you talking about?
What a fucking dick.
I hate him.
I hate him so much.
I only heard that second hand, so it could be completely full of shit.
I will believe literally anything you tell me about Elon.
There's nothing that I would put past him.
He's a good guy.
You're right.
There's a fucking thing that Ben won't believe.
Yeah, I think I saw those tweets.
He was just, I didn't, maybe I didn't comprehend it correctly,
but the gist I was getting was like,
he was hyping up Dogecoin like,
Hey Dogecoin, and everyone was like,
Oh yeah, Dogecoin, then it went up.
Wait, so he's saying sell your Bitcoin so he can make it.
Sell your Dogecoin.
What?
Yeah, so we can make it go up.
Why?
I don't know what that was.
I think that narrative is that it's supposed to be like the people's crypto
because it's so inexpensive to get into as opposed to something like Bitcoin.
But if you heard that, why would you then sell it?
I don't know.
He's saying he's going to make it go up.
I don't.
So sell it?
Like no.
I interpret it as him like super transparently just trying to make money
of the people who he knows he can influence to make something go up.
That's what I figured.
It seemed like if selling it, because if you sell,
if all the people who hold Bitcoin sell, the price will go down,
then he can buy it all up and get rich.
Yeah, I swear to God with what I remember seeing.
But I don't know.
I'm making things up.
I don't know.
It could be totally wrong.
When I encounter an Elon guy on the internet,
and once in a while I find them and they are, they're just Vincent,
and it makes me so mad.
I'm so angry every time I talk to one.
Like they're not human.
They're subhuman.
They're monsters.
They're demons.
I think they're the worst.
If it's the next issue, the vapor is going to be all about
Vincent investing in crypto.
I kind of thought that like, you know,
maybe Vincent would be an Elon guy.
I don't know.
Maybe there's a story there at some point.
No.
No, thank you.
Love it.
What else?
Okay.
I guess now's a good time as any.
I want to talk about yesterday in the Radcon.
Yesterday in the Radcon of Discord server.
Last week to everybody listening.
Because it's last week.
This would have been a week in some ago.
Yeah.
This was a Saturday.
So we had been talking to Trixie about the Brony lecture.
And without going into too much detail,
Trixie adamantly would not said no,
she will not release the Brony lecture as it is.
Not only that, she will not allow the raw footage to be seen
even by backers.
And we said backers should maybe see it
because it's like behind the scenes footage.
And that's kind of it's rad content.
And she said no, no, I won't do it.
And she made a number of statements in the Discord server,
which made me very upset.
And I in which I want to disavow specifically
as not representative of the PCP ethos.
And here are some of those.
Oh, you have them prepared.
I have them prepared.
Oh, God, all right.
One, I'm trying to do a Trixie voice.
And you won't tell me what to do
because I don't respect you on the basis of having given me money.
I think that's disgusting, reprehensible human behavior.
I believe, I respect you a lot if you give me money.
Let's see here.
A backer says, we were invested and we trusted you.
Trixie responds, yeah, well, guess what?
I can't afford to make good on your investment.
The fact you made a faulty investment
doesn't fund me to pay for it.
I would disavow that.
You giving me money to do something does fund me to do the thing.
I said, this is just kind of a big middle finger
to all our supporters.
Trixie said, if this is how they act, then yes,
I am giving them the finger.
I don't have to respect people just because they gave me money,
to which I would say I do respect you if you give me money.
There's a lot of that sentiment.
There was a lot of that sentiment going around
that like, fuck you if you give me money.
I just want to say, no, please, please give me money.
Fucking aside, please.
The general consensus here, I believe,
is that we don't really stand by anything
that was said in the heat of the moment yesterday.
No, it was a shit show.
It was a real shit show.
It was not good.
It was bad and then I went to go play D&D
and then I came back and I realized
for like the four hours I was there,
it was still going on and got worse.
I'm like, oh my god.
I kind of saw it going on and I did,
but I didn't say anything until someone like added me
about something in the conversation
and then I felt obliged to enter into it and I did
and I got very upset and I said some things
that I don't apologize for, Lamal.
I mean, I think it goes without saying
that everybody here wants to get everything
that was promised from Radcon delivered
in a timely fashion as best to our abilities.
Unfortunately, the Brony Lecture may be trapped
in a way that we can't access,
but everything within our power will be released
in A's timely fashion as possible.
Yeah, I mean, you made the Kickstarter update post today.
Yes, and I have breaking news
that the animated OP is done.
So the OVA can get finished.
Literally like an hour after I posted the update
when I said, because you had just said that's right.
It'd be like a month and change and like literally an hour later.
You said they said before, like maybe end of February
and yeah, it's the last day of February and here it is.
So good on them.
Yeah, but now we've got a-
It looks pretty cool.
It looks good.
I mean, it looks better than I think it's-
Better than it has any right to be.
Yeah, yeah, for real.
I'm excited for people to see that.
I'm not sure if there's anything we need to release before
that comes out like the Brad Lecture.
I think-
We'll have to double check the order,
but I think the OVA was like in terms of the editing things.
That was like the biggest roadblock
because that was something we couldn't do ourselves.
But like the OVA and the Brad Lecture
and even the music video for the diss track
are all, we can do all those directly.
So hopefully-
I think, wait a minute.
I think that the OVA isn't like canonically,
doesn't the OVA immediately follow the Brad Lecture, right?
I believe so.
Oh, wait, the Brad-
It's been a year.
No, no, it's the music video for the diss track
that follows the Brad Lecture.
Yeah, it's the Brad Lecture, then the diss track,
and then the OVA after.
The OVA is the story of what happens
when we go on summer break from the lectures, which is school.
That is true.
Wait, yeah, but the last lecture was the Brad Lecture.
Okay, then is that, I don't know.
Yeah, I haven't looked at the footage in a long time.
I mean, me either.
I haven't looked at it at all.
I just lived it.
No, you don't want to look.
It really does feel like a fever dream.
I mean, that was-
It can't possibly have happened.
It's strange to think that the last thing we did in a pre-COVID world
was fucking RatCon 4.
I'm convinced it caused COVID.
Yeah, I mean, we used COVID's name in vain quite a few times
and summoned its wrath.
We upset it.
We didn't think it was real.
We thought it was just a joke.
I don't want to say anymore to spoil it.
But I think it has only gotten funnier in hindsight,
in my opinion.
Unfortunately, we are the reason people are dying
in more ways than one.
No, well, maybe.
No.
No, no.
Rat COVID-19.
Yeah.
Rat.
What you said, you hit the nail on the head.
What a joy.
You know, I'm so excited.
I'm so excited for it to come out.
I really do think it's even funnier a year later.
I really do.
Yeah, the joke's old and nobody cares anymore.
And that just makes it better.
Honestly, I mean, it shouldn't have taken so long.
But I kind of, with the COVID and everything involved
in between in 2020, it's a little understandable
that it took so long for all this stuff to get
to this point was really done.
I think when people see the OP,
they will understand why it took this long.
Yeah, I mean, it was a double whammy of adding
so much stuff at the 11th hour that's
beyond the scope of what we usually do for these
and COVID being a thing.
That's true.
So, you know, we're still making it happen,
though.
Progress is being made.
We have not abandoned anything.
So, stay tuned, my dudes.
Yes, yes, yes.
You heard it here first, folks.
Ben's done with Noida.
That means CWC 102 any day now, I'm sure.
We respect you for giving us money.
No statements to the contrary apply
or are officially acknowledged in any PCP context.
I mean, unironically, it's really humbling to think,
like, oh my God, that was a lot of fucking money.
Yeah, no, it was so crazy.
It's crazy.
I couldn't believe that it was still going out.
So, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, that livestream was-
There's a huge, like, humbling and responsibility
to make sure that this stuff is done
to the best of our abilities.
So, for sure.
I mean, I mean, I don't know.
I think it's, I think we've hit a point where,
I mean, there's probably a lot of people,
honestly, a lot of people that probably, like,
haven't even kept up with the PCP since then.
And I think a lot of people might just not expect
of it to come out anymore.
And I feel like when it does come out,
and there's like, oh my God, there is actual content.
It was produced.
It does exist.
I think people will be shocked.
And I think we've hit a point where now it will feel
like it's just free, like they had already given up on it,
but now it does exist.
And it's like, oh, this is just free.
I expected nothing at this point, but now I've got this.
Yeah, the Kickstarter backers,
they backed the crypto, the PCPenny,
and it crashed immediately.
It's been low the entire time.
But now, now it's going to surge.
It's going to go right to the moon.
Just like, good ol' XRP.
It's time to go to patreon.com.
That's the procrastinators and invest in the PCPenny.
You will not be able to exchange it for USD.
You won't need USD soon.
When the entire American economy crashes,
you're going to be happy that your assets
are locked and safe in PCPenny's.
It's a great hedge against inflation.
The People's Currency.
That's what the PC stands for, the People's Currency Penny.
People's Currency Penny.
It's the People's Currency Penny, Penny,
because it's a...
Wait, no, it's PCPenny.
No, I'm sorry.
It's not the PCPenny.
Yeah, you got it.
You got it.
Do we want to go to voicemail?
Is it too early for that?
I mean, we'll be going for like an hour.
Yeah, we'll be going for an hour.
Hmm.
Do I have anything else to say?
I could read more shitty stuff that Trixie said.
I mean, I've got more screenshots of shit that made me mad.
I feel like we've made our point.
As much as it was like a shit show.
Oh, but there's some good stuff here, though.
Oh, but there's some real infuriating shit here, though.
I mean, it's all in the chat
if anybody really wants to dig into it.
Well, only Kickstarter backers are in that chat.
So, like, we're broadcasting it to a large audience.
I guess I just assumed everybody
who's listening to it at this point is a Kickstarter backer.
Somebody said, like, this is the content we paid for.
And you know what?
If they feel that way, then I condone that.
Enjoy it.
Lol.
Okay, all right.
Pulling victory from the jaws of defeat.
I like that attitude.
That's, yeah, that's really making lemonade, you know?
It's true.
Yeah.
Like that girl with brain cancer.
Uh...
See that?
There was a...
I don't know if it was in Brain Can.
There was some feel-good story going around Twitter
about, like, this girl needs, like, multiple brain surgeries
because she's got, like, horrible seizures
that are going to kill her if she doesn't get them.
So, she's selling lemonade to pay for the operation.
What a heartwarming story.
Wait, what?
Yeah, this was, like, all over this week.
This week?
Yeah, brain surgery, back lemonade.
Is terrifying.
Alabama girl, seven years old, selling lemonade
to help pay for her brain surgery.
Holy shit.
Liza Scott.
Yeah, I hope, quote, I hope I make it.
Yup, me too.
Fuck yeah.
You can't see it, but I'm, like, I'm making a very shot.
USA.
Fucking epic.
US game.
I can see it on, like, ABC.
Like, heartwarming, you know, and then the title
of the article.
That's what you call picking yourself up by your bootstraps.
You know what else is heartwarming?
An iron, like, heated, what do you call it?
Swarm.
An iron poker to the heart, like, stab?
Like, it's heartwarming.
Okay, that was, I failed the time.
No, I got it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I get it.
No, it was good.
No, no, no, no.
No, it was funny.
No, it was just shivering.
Come on, it was funny.
It was good.
No, you did.
No, I got it.
Now I'm going to cry.
I'm gonna cry and it's your fault.
Yes.
Um, voicemail?
We could start.
Yeah.
Okay.
Are you ready?
You got them up?
I gotta go get a speed pipe.
Okay.
It looks like the first one here is called Dag the Food Science Guy Solves Your Gummy
Worm Woes, which I hope to God means he's going to tell me where I can affordably purchase
some fucking-
Oh no, I'm not logged in.
Uh.
I am you fuck.
You bitch.
Yeah, no, it's completely warranted.
I'm sorry.
Eleazar, put some cool elevator music while I'm trying to get the password again.
This always makes me chuckle.
Put in um-
Please add more storage to your account.
You've used one gigabyte of the 100 megabytes total.
Eleazar, put in the song with me and Gib samples.
That one.
Play that.
That's the waiting song.
Remember that one?
Huh?
The one that's like, I don't even remember what we're saying in it.
Yeah.
All right, I did it.
I did it.
I found it.
Okay.
Okay, Dag the Food Science Guy Solves Your Gummy Worm Woes in three, two, one, go.
All right, when people are giving advice and they wait until the very end of something
like this to give the useful bit of information.
So right up front.
Oh, you?
Okay.
All you need to know is that, Ben, your gummy worms are not coming out consistently because
you are measuring by volume and not by weight.
Conceptually, it's kind of hard to wrap your head around at first.
No, it's not hard to wrap my head around.
I understand the differences.
Different substances are going to be ground to different levels of fineness.
I hate you.
And so more, the finer it is ground.
I have a fucking degree in physics.
I understand the difference between volume and mass.
Bits.
To be fair, that is hard to believe.
Things can affect this.
Like, if you live in a particularly humid climate.
No, okay, that's it.
No more particles.
No more.
I get it.
I know the difference.
Was I being sloppy?
Yes.
We got to be more science.
But if I'm using, okay, if I'm using the same like brand of sugar, say, same brand of sugar,
for instance, and I, and I'm at the same altitude, right?
And I take like a scoop, like a half cup of sugar is not going to radically change you
like one day to the next, like what the mass of that is, you know?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just making excuses.
Yeah, just put in a measuring bowl, idiot.
Well, that would be fine.
Not a measuring bowl and a scale.
I do actually have, I did buy, I did buy a new mini scale, not for worms.
Actually, I bought a scale for weighing packages and envelopes so that I would know how much
postage to use for RFCK merch stuff and vapors stuff.
So I have a scale.
So, you know what, Dag?
I'll give it to you.
You're probably right.
You're probably right that I should be measuring by, by mass.
Yes.
Fine.
Very well.
Next one is called Origin of Lol Cow.
Three, two, one, go.
The term Lol Cow actually comes from farming.
You see, there's this thing called the rape rack or they used to call it that.
Now they're shifting to more PC terminology, but you know, it's the rape rack where once
a year dairy cows, they're tied to it.
The farmer forcibly impregnates them, shoves their whole arm inside, you know, squeeze
a little syringe of bull semen.
And you may think, oh, it's a little harsh to call that rape.
I mean, like technically, and you're right to say that actually because when it happens,
the cows go, lol, because they think it's really funny.
That's where the term Lol Cow comes from because cows like it when we rape them over,
over again every year.
Wow.
And what's even more funny to them is that once the calf is born, after like three days
or not even, sometimes immediately, we just take the calf away and the mom is like,
wailing.
But it's not actually wailing.
It's that she's laughing really hard because she thinks it's so funny that we do this to
them over and over on an annual basis until they die.
That's cool.
Pretty funny.
Pretty good.
I'm all on about it.
I'm having a, I'm having a sensible chuckle over here.
The more you know you, I'm looking at this diagram like Googled rape rack.
I guess it is a thing.
Why?
Why would you?
And this is a diagram of a cow's innards.
That just seems like a dangerous term to search for just in general.
You know you're right, but it's too late and I can't unring this bell.
Thank you.
Thank you for posting that in the chat.
I didn't need to see it, but.
Amazon's already like suggesting you to buy your own.
My own what?
Rape rack?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, hmm, you know, I mean, well, I mean, maybe if I make enough Bitcoin, uh, profits
than, uh, okay.
Next one is called Ben.
This is an intervention.
Your alcoholism is killing you.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, this is an intervention.
Your alcoholism is killing you.
If you die, it won't even be based.
I feel like this is old because I have not been drinking, uh, recently.
Like a few months ago, I was drinking a lot, but mostly this year I have not been.
So.
Sounds like, uh, like an alcoholic in denial.
Ben.
No, no, you gotta, you gotta be lucid to make those like quick trades, uh, for Bitcoin.
You got, you guy comes in.
He's like, Oh, I haven't been drinking and you're just like, Hmm, this is an alcoholic
in denial.
Quit denying it.
Don't hold them down and pour a beer down a store.
Accept it.
Accept your alcoholism.
Stop denying it.
So you're doing right now.
Don't accept who you are.
Exactly what an alcoholic would say.
Just be the best.
If I drink in a beer.
Just be the best alcoholic you can be.
Uh, next.
Drink all the alcohol.
Next voicemail is called, I, I was tempted, I was tempted this weekend.
I was tempted this weekend.
Want to drink heavily.
Ben, I kept.
Yeah, I was tempted to go get another, another, my, my classic two bottles of barefoot bubbly
brute cuve.
Fucking alcoholic.
I didn't do it.
Something distracted me.
Probably, probably Noida.
You know what?
I, I is Noida.
Well, you know, now that I'm over Noida, um, back on the sauce, I'll probably get, I'll
probably get back on the sauce.
By the way, um, tectonic improv.
Uh, recommended me a video by a discount gum shoe about Noida where he talks about
it and its themes.
And I thought it was a good video.
And so I guess I might as well shout it out.
Um, go, uh, it's, it's called, um, I don't remember what it's called, but it's by discount
gum shoe.
Uh, I liked it because he was like, lol, good game.
Sounds good.
No, cause he talked, he taught, he talks about, I mean the, the, the, the, the coolest thing
about it is he says like, yeah, I was playing the game.
I was trying to win.
I was trying to win, but then it was too hard and I gave up on winning.
So I just was like, fuck it.
And I didn't go down the main path and I went exploring again and I went like, hmm, what
if I don't go into the mountain?
I'll just go left.
Oh my God.
What the fuck is over here?
I'll just go right.
Oh my God.
I can go up like, oh my God, there's shit up here.
Like what the fuck?
There's so much more to this game than I thought.
Like this, this world is like bigger than I thought it was.
And now like the next time I go and I go down the holy mountain, it's like, I have a completely
new outlook on it.
I, I Google one that is like, uh, discount gum shoe on YouTube and I can't see their
account.
Is there a way to spell it?
Um, I think it's all one word.
Oh, maybe that's it.
Oh, there it is.
Yeah.
It's, it's called, wait, no, I didn't mean to make this like a whole diversion, but
now I'm, I'm irritated.
Wait.
That was a year ago.
No, it's the author as God.
Yes.
That's it.
Um, yeah.
I didn't, he made that video.
It's from like, like early 2020, uh, I guess it's been out for a while.
I see videos sometimes talking about like features and like, yeah, I guess it was like
an early access for a while and I guess it's been out for a bit.
They keep adding stuff, uh, and actually there's more stuff being added now, like on the beta
branch, there's all these new like structures that are being added to old biomes and there's
like new spells and spell modifiers and stuff.
And there's like new secrets and, uh, it's pretty cool, but I'm not playing the beta
branch.
So I haven't really fucked with any of it.
Um, okay, uh, no, no more noise to talk enough, enough.
Um, this next voicemail is called PCP crunch mail three, two, one, go.
Okay.
So I don't know if I'm a bigot, but something about Digi not wanting to be called Digi anymore
and deleting all of her videos makes me like viscerally angry.
Like no, you're dumb.
Just be called Digi something Digi.
Nay.
I don't care.
I'm going to end this voicemail by eating chips.
Nice.
Very good.
Um, well, the, the, I think the only thing that's bad about the taking down of all the
videos is that she said three weeks and it wasn't three weeks.
Oh, that's really bad.
Yeah.
She said that happened.
She said, she said three weeks and then after like 11 days or something, she just like,
ah, fuck it.
She just did it.
Lol.
Which is like the, you said, you just, you said it like you give people the time.
And then, okay, since, since you bring that up, I got to mention the thing she said in
the radcon server where someone was like, Hey, you said that and you broke your word.
And she said, uh, she said, uh, uh, you should never take anyone at their word.
Like why didn't you just like, why didn't you just expect me to lie?
Like what are you stupid?
Like it's your fault for believing me, idiot.
Lol.
Uh, really cool.
Disavow.
It was, it was just like, I don't know, the, the taking down of all the videos because
you don't feel right having them.
I always, I'm always on the side of the person to be able to do that at any time.
There's no, there's no like, um, you know, obligation, moral or legal or anything to keep
yourself broadcasting forever.
You can just stop and delete it all.
Um, I just disagree with the whole not doing the one thing you said you would do to allow
people to save the videos they like.
I think, I mean, I think deleting the videos is cringe.
It's not that she can't, it's that I think she must not do it.
I think it's cringe.
I also think it doesn't make any sense because it's going to cost her a lot of money for
no gain at all.
Uh, and I mean, that's, those are my thoughts on channel deletion.
We don't know exactly what the gain is in, in like, I don't know, mental state or whatever,
but you know.
I suppose.
Yeah.
That made sure whatever.
And I mean, uh, she, uh, I don't, I mean, I disagree that she doesn't have to keep going
by Digi if she doesn't want to.
You know, if she, I mean, I can understand if they're named people change their brand
all the time.
Yeah.
I mean, if like, it's a, it's a brand that's been around for like what, like a decade at
this point.
So of course, like if you've been following, you know, Trixie's content for this entire
time, like it's probably going to be weird to be like, Oh, like, like I'm just mentally
like associating this person with Digi bro, like that's just just, that's just ingrained
in my head.
But like, that's not too hard to get over, um, you know, like we've been saying Trixie
this whole time and like we've known them for like 10 years, like literally talk pretty
frequently.
So, um, but I don't know.
I mean, in terms of like deleting the videos and stuff, like that's obviously, you know,
her prerogative, do whatever you want with your content.
I think it was probably not a great call to delete it early.
And I'm also not really sure why, like a lot of people were saying, like in the comments
of that video, why not just start a new channel?
That's what I would have done.
And I don't understand the, I don't, because you just want to keep that sub number around.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sure.
I understand that, but it's like, okay, I want to shed my old audience and get a new
audience.
It's like, well, then what is more sensible audience that you are?
Cause like the only thing you're doing is inviting, inviting, you know, people to like
react badly to the new content.
Whereas we have a new platform from scratch.
You're starting fresh.
Yeah.
That's literally saying I want the old people to see the new content by putting it here
where they are.
Maybe there's something I'm missing, but it seems like it seems we're going against
the stated goal.
But like, I mean, it's nice that 300 K numbers really comfy and you don't want to let it
go.
So I get that.
Sure.
But functionally at this point, it probably doesn't mean much, you know?
I mean, practically, if I were just trying to, if I were in that situation and I were
just like, okay, I don't want to be Digi bro anymore.
I don't want to be Digi anymore.
I want to rebrand.
And I also don't want to be fucked.
What I would do is leave that channel, could just, just continue to accrue, you know, ad
revenue from views on that old channel and start a new channel and just like leave it
there.
Like, yeah, that's Digi content.
That's what it was.
I'm not Digi anymore.
I'm over here doing this thing.
But like that stuff is still benefiting me.
I mean, even if like you're uncomfortable, like with like that, you know, phaser life
being active on the internet, like you can, you can private all that still, but like I
would still start a new channel as opposed to like trying to keep that one going at this
point.
I gotta say, I agree, but it's hard to get that being said, hope it works out.
Like I think maybe it was like, oh, in order to get a monetization on a new channel, you
have to get a certain amount of views and over a certain time and it was just easier
to use a currently existing channel.
So I don't know.
She could get, she could get thousands of views, which is what she's getting on her void
gazer stuff on the old channel.
She could get thousands of views on any new channel she made just by tweeting about it,
just by like saying or making a video on the old channel saying, I'm here now.
Like I don't know that audience, that core audience that will watch that will follow
her to any new place she goes, it is there.
So I forget the point I was making.
It doesn't matter.
Is it?
Yeah.
Whatever.
Was there anything else about that voicemail?
No, I think we said it all.
I'm glad you enjoyed your chips.
I'm like he was enjoying those chips at the end.
So I got some, I got some chips today.
I got some Parmesan crisps.
Oh, I had some of those literally earlier today.
Are you keto?
I'm back on keto.
Yeah.
Nice.
I got.
Okay.
Last time I ordered from Costco, I got some stuff that I'd never had before and it was
really good.
It was called moon cheese.
Do you know what that is?
No, I've never heard of that.
It's literally just like freeze dried cheese, but it's not cold.
You know, it's room temperature, but it's like dried into these sort of little like
puff like balls, but it's just cheese that's been sort of like flash frozen into these
little like crunchy pieces and you just eat it and it's good.
But then they were out.
I tried to order some again and they were out.
So instead I got these Parmesan crisps and they're pretty good too.
They're good.
The next voicemail is called bane will find him three, two, one, go.
You're probably wondering who would come in a man before throwing him out of a plane.
That would be the league, of course.
Oh, no.
No.
No matter who we are, really, what matters is our plan, our plan to fuck Nate.
You see, once I find him, it will be very painful for Nate.
These guys are always talking about their plans to fuck Nate and they haven't done
it yet.
They haven't even approached him.
Are these guys just at the league of incels like Nate incels?
Where's their game?
You know?
Where's their result?
If they want to threaten Nate, shouldn't they be like messaging content?
Nate's not around these parts anymore.
We've been sending them over in like paper or plain form.
I don't know.
I'm wondering now if maybe it is, maybe it's all just a bunch of empty posturing.
At some point, you have to put up or shut up.
After a while, if Nate remains unfucked, I have to question your dedication.
There's a whole league behind this and he's just too, like, too.
What's the word?
He's unfuck, he's unfuckable.
He's unfuckable.
He's like the Chastity Belt, like is like like 10 psych locks.
Nobody knows that reference.
I don't.
Damn.
People in the comments say, say, lol, if you, if you lulled.
Do you want to?
What is it?
It's Phoenix, right?
Psych locks?
Phoenix, right?
OK, like a personalized, then the psych locks.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah, I remember.
I remember.
We got to grab, we got to grab one of my thirty five cans of Coke Zero that I got
from Costco today.
This is number.
Oh, God, I'm on five already.
Hmm.
Yikes, Coke Zero.
Ben still does have a drinking problem.
It's just not alcohol anymore.
Glad we cleared that up.
Absolutely.
He just loves those liquids.
You can't get enough.
Oh, I bought.
I bought some.
I keep going on these keto tangents, but I ordered some like non-sugar candy from
a brand called Behave.
I ordered like a box of them and didn't like them.
Smart sweets are better, I think.
So Behave is like, it's fine, like it's OK.
I try not to buy any specifically keto branded product because they're always way
too expensive.
Well, these are not called keto.
They're just low, low sugar.
But I mean, they are overpriced for what they are.
Yeah, it was it was literally it was like $48 for like twelve bags of the stuff.
Oh, my God.
It's like, have you seen the ads for that like keto cereal that's like seven
dollars for a tiny box?
And I'm just like, how dare you to sell my intelligence?
I haven't seen those.
And all I can think is like boxes of cereal are so small to begin with.
Right, like I in the past I have bought a little box like you can buy the big
like family sized ones, but if you just buy like a normal box of cereal,
like the meat, the normal size, that's like three bowls for me.
It really is. Yeah, it's not much.
And I'm sure that these fucking keto cereals are even less.
So I can only imagine like spreading that across like two breakfasts.
It's probably like two bowls at best.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, the next bowl.
This is this capitalism, am I right?
Yeah, fuck them.
Next voicemail is called Jenkins jinkies three, two, one, go.
Shekels for heckles when asking for a friend.
Oh, we haven't done one in like three weeks or something.
I'm so busy.
Oh, I mean, I can I can always do one, but I haven't been thinking about it.
I haven't been thinking about it.
I think I said this last time.
How did you play so much?
Noida and not Shekels for heckles it at all.
You know, you know what?
You know what?
I would love to do a Noida Shekels for heckles.
That would be fun and cool.
Let's do we want to do that maybe this week?
I don't have the game, so I'll just be sitting in the cool watching.
But yeah, I can I can stream it.
Yeah, I mean, it's a single player game.
Uh, if we want maybe if we want to do it this.
Should wait, we should say let's say that we'll do it the week after this comes out.
All right. Sure.
So we want to say like the the Wednesday after this episode airs,
we will do a Noida Shekels for heckles.
I can I can.
So the 10th, March 10th.
Yes, March 10th.
Noida Shekels, baby.
That's so far in the future.
Ha, ha, I'm going to sneak up on you.
No, no, no, never forget, never.
I can never forget Noida.
By then, I'll be a God.
I'll be such a guy.
Wait, I got to tell you about this one.
I got to tell you about this one I found.
Got to save it for the stream.
No, OK, I will probably rave about this.
This was like this was an incredible early game find.
And I still lost.
Well, next voicemail is called Blingus Keningus.
Three, two, one, go.
Konichiwa.
During last week's episode, it seems our friend
Kringus Bingus was facing a bit of an existential struggle.
Ganbare, Kringus Bingus.
Yeah.
Questions you pondered once stuck out to me.
What do Martin Lawrence and Sonic the Hedgehog have in common?
Well, Fred, no more for this is one predicament I can lay to rest.
What Martin Lawrence and Sonic the Hedgehog have in common
is that they have both starred in a feature titled The Black Knight.
Anyway, pledge to my Patreon at Patreon dot com slash PC Minecraft
and follow me on Twitter at Procrastinator's Minecraft.
Until next time.
Say, oh, no.
Oh, no.
Nala, what was he saying?
I don't know.
I guess they were both in Black Knight.
He said Martin Lawrence, but I pictured Lawrence Fishburne,
who is basically similar, essentially.
PC Minecraft, guys, I don't want to alarm you.
OK, forty five, forty five, three fifty five.
We're up another three hundo.
We're up another three hundo, baby.
Wait, huh? What?
Bitcoin, Bitcoin.
Sorry, I'm not glued to the Bitcoin screen.
I'm glued.
Thirty thirty five, thirty five.
Look, look at this.
Look at this.
Oh, yeah.
Look, look, look at this.
Look at this.
Until it's breaking fifty K again, I'm not interested.
Let me know when it hits fifty K again.
When I'm making a profit again, look, look at that meteoric rise.
I mean, look at it in the context of the week, though.
And it's like it's a snow.
I'm not going to do.
I'm not going to look at it in that context.
Like you, I choose not to do so.
Even for today, it has fallen so much.
No, shut up, shut up.
Wait, is that true?
What did it start the day at?
The day it started at fucking.
No, it's about it's about where it started.
It's gone down, but yeah.
Yeah, next voicemail is called Brony lecture correction.
OK, three, two, one, go.
Just want to clarify the voicemail I said last week
about the releasing the original blown in the lecture.
I didn't mean now and I didn't mean unedited.
What I meant was just don't get rid of or throw away
any of the original footage from what was recorded at Radcott.
That's all I was referring to,
because it's I'm sure that it's good shit and it's yeah, it is good shit.
We want like that's what everyone wants.
Everyone wants to see it is what everyone the lecture
that was recorded at Radcom with all of you guys there
listening in on the lecture.
That's what we want.
That's what it means.
Yeah, don't get rid of any of that shit.
Yeah, I'm I'm sorry.
I don't know what to tell you.
I've even I'm sorry that I can't do anything.
Yeah, I mean, it feels like that battle has been lost.
Digi has not in any way implied that she is getting rid of
the original footage that she she said over and over again.
She's going to no incorporated into a second video with new footage as well.
Lol, I don't know exactly what that's going to look like.
But you know, well, it won't look like the original,
which is what everyone wants.
I guess I guess the and also it will never happen.
Lamar, it's confusing how it's like all the original footage
is going to be in this new version, but you can't see the original footage.
It's like it's it's it's it's I mean, literally.
It doesn't make any sense.
We still don't have what these edits are totally insane.
So maybe it'll make sense five years from now.
When there were actually comes out.
But if it were ever going to come out in any form,
there would be no problem showing the backers the raw footage, you know.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sorry, everyone. I'm sorry.
I wish I could do something, but I can't.
Well, next voicemail is called any hole is a Smeagol.
Three to three to one go.
Words to live by.
My precious.
Oh, my precious is gone.
I miss my precious.
I know where this is going.
Yeah. Miss you, Nate.
You're delicious.
Vain cook.
I miss it.
I'm shaving pure.
It's really sexy.
My precious.
Nate, I miss that one stray hair
hidden underneath the hood.
I miss the crustiness of the forest.
It's too real.
If you're listening, please tell me.
Do you want my pinkies in your urethra's?
Do you want me to slide my
ricofinger into your cock hole?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's see where this is going.
A precious cock wheel for Nate.
The one you mean.
My anus
forged in the fires of Mount Coombe.
That was too good of an impression.
I'm saying all of that.
Oh, I could see it.
I can see him saying it.
Yeah, unfortunately, I can see it.
I could smell his breath
and crawling all over me and delivering this monologue.
It's like all the voicemails to be highly produced
that had to be that one.
It's like it's like that ride at Disneyland
when the Disney World where the alien breaks out of the thing
and like the like the the the the leathery wings
and like it breathes on you.
It's like that. It's like that.
Thanks for the voicemail.
You know, he didn't he didn't say he was part of the League, though.
That's true.
He could be a competing force.
Smeagol and Gollum.
They were always on their own.
Yeah, I select it.
Yeah, renegades.
Precious cock ring.
Like my anus forced in the fires of Mount Coombe.
Mount Coombe's pretty good.
Salvaged it right at the end.
That was pretty good.
Yeah, a real cherry on top.
No pun intended.
I just want to listen to it like a sex ridden load of the rings.
No, no, no, no, get out of here.
No, it's just you really want that.
I'm sure it already exists,
but it's just so silly.
OK, fine.
I don't I don't I don't plan to enjoy it.
I just is funny. OK.
Sherry, I just want to watch it ironically.
Promise. Hmm.
Next voicemail is called you're the reason I can't stop stealing.
I'm not meming three, two, one, go.
Hey, I just wanted to let you know,
Ben, at one time that you talked about a shoplifting
made me rethink the way that I go about my spending my money.
And now, whenever I need food,
I tend to have a kleptomaniac problem.
So, yeah, ever since then, I haven't spent any money on food.
Any. See you. How?
I mean, that's that's a power move, my dude.
If you can if you can steal all of your food,
I'm impressed. Yeah.
I I mean, I have I have not been in any like stores in a while.
So like, I haven't stolen anything.
Yeah, for online shopping, you you go to checkout
and then at the last second, you like
void your credit card as as you do the thing.
And then it's like it goes through like, oh, oh, it's already being shipped.
Just like you place order and then you immediately go to your bank
and with half an A press, you file a fraudulent report
and you get your money back.
You have to hold down the mouse click
between when you say buy and then you go and you hold it down to your bank
and you say like dispute transaction.
It's got to be in one swift motion.
You have you have to do it in a single frame. Yeah, yeah.
Stealing stealing all of it.
Like, how do you do that? Like is he just eating like an apple?
That's it.
I mean, I mean, don't steal from mom and pops, preferably.
Yeah, don't I mean, don't get caught, I guess.
And if you can do both of those things, I say steal away.
Stealing is good. Thumbs up.
I was thinking about this.
I was thinking about this
just like yesterday, I was like,
I've talked about stealing before and how it's good.
I should say that again.
I should reiterate that, by the way,
don't forget that I think stealing is good, but I do.
So thanks.
Thanks, caller, for giving me the chance.
Next voicemail is called.
No, it's good. Not not.
Hey, no, what are you? What are you chicken?
What are you, pussy, huh? We not cool.
I think it's like morally OK to do that
if it's a large food business huge thing as opposed to a proper store.
The only like moral qualm I have about saying stealing is good
is that I worry that someone like this, who has by his own admission
was inspired to steal by me, might get in trouble if they get caught.
Like, I would I would really feel terrible if that were to happen.
Like, please.
Yes. Well, the more you say it, the bigger the chance
of that happening becomes.
So I know. And I'm saying like.
The most important thing is don't fucking get caught.
La Mal. Just just eat it in the store.
Yes, it's true. It's not a bad move.
Next voicemail, microphone, Michael, three, two, one, go.
Well, if it isn't me, microphone, Michael.
Damn, what a mic on this guy.
Am I right?
Me microphone named.
Michael. Yeah.
Microphones are slightly phallic shaped.
And you know what rhymes with shape?
Ben, shut the fuck up.
I'm going to fuck you for ever.
You're going to regret letting me on to this show.
I will fuck your brother in dough.
Oh, my God. In what?
Microphone, Michael turned into a fucking Palpatine at the end there.
He seemed like such a nice guy at first.
But then things took a turn.
Turn for the mic.
Give a shout out to the original microphone, Michael.
Mike, the microphone of Brony fame.
Oh, is that a musician?
Yeah. Yeah.
I remember the name.
I don't even.
It rings a bell.
I've heard the name, but I can't say I've ever met the man.
Remember, remember that?
Remember when that guy said that?
I remember somebody referencing it.
I don't know. It's from.
That's that's what that's what someone that's what Dr.
Wolf said when someone asked him about Endless Jess, he said, I've heard
no drowning in horseshoes.
I have heard the name, but I've never met the man.
I feel like he would have been referencing something else.
That's oh, my God.
You know what we didn't talk about?
Have you guys seen anything about G5?
G5 exploded this week.
Oh, wait.
I think I saw the like a screenshot and I hate how it looks.
There's tons of animated gifts and everything.
Yeah, I hate that it just it just looks like any.
It looks like some your normal Pixar shit.
Everything looks like that.
Every fucking movie looks like that.
And I hate it.
There's like one artist in the industry that does the eyes for every 3D thing ever.
They're exactly the same.
They did it to VeggieTales.
They gave them those same eyes.
It's fucked up.
There's do you remember?
Like God, this is going to be such an obscure reference
because I didn't even remember till someone pointed out.
Do you remember that like that like weirdly detailed painting of like
Celestia with like the really derpy looking face from like way back in the day.
It kind of had this like God, I'm never going to be able to find it.
It just like looked really stupid, but it was like a overly detailed painting.
God, I don't know. Maybe.
I'm not going to be able to find it.
I don't remember.
All I know is that the person who made that painting
worked on designing the ponies and this G5.
So let me we've really gone.
We've gone places.
I guess it's not that crazy to imagine.
Bronies from Gen 4 will be working on Gen 5.
It's been a 10 years.
I'm never going to be able to find it.
I'm really mad.
Yeah, but it was on Twitter and now it's just gone.
The I was looking at the they said there's a movie I'm right.
I'm right, though, right?
Like G5 just looks really generic, right?
It looks way less, way more generic than than G4, that's for sure.
The they had like a small post exclusive to some website.
And they had like a brief little bit of information
about the fact that there's going to be a movie coming out
and then a series to follow in the same animation style.
And the director is the guy who made cop out or something.
Cop out?
It's I don't know.
The movie, I think so.
I was looking at the names of the people involved.
The one the one that Mr. Plinkett like shield that one time
for the check in that joke with the fucking.
Oh, yeah, that was the one.
Or is it like a cop cop dog more like cop out?
I don't even know what that means.
Here is my only that's my only touch.
That's my only touch point for cop out.
Yeah, so I just wanted to know if like if there's any chance of it being good
because the only reason the Gen four was good was because Lauren Faust
really wanted it to be a good show and she pushed hard for that to happen.
So without her, without a similar voice in the next one,
it's probably just going to be exactly the same shit as, you know,
the the unwatchable garbage that was, well, I don't know, Gen three.
I never watched it, but I caught glimpses and it was not interesting.
I mean, I mean, it looks it looks it looks in motion
just like I thought it would from the screenshots.
I don't like the 3D look nearly as much as the 2D.
Oh, I don't think anyone would say that this looks better than Gen four.
Oh, found it.
All right, this is the picture I was talking about.
Let me get this, please, please.
I feel like I can almost picture what you're talking about.
I had to scroll up through another chat, but yeah, here we go.
That image.
Oh, my God.
That was wasn't that the the the logo for some musician, right?
I think it was at some point.
I don't know. It was that the fucking double chin or no chin, Celestia.
Some it was that one musician that Trixie was a big fan of who deleted
all their so powerful.
Yeah, yeah, so maybe I don't know if that was their icon,
but that so gap was the one I associate this image with that person.
But I could have misfired somewhere, I don't know.
Neat, neat.
This is like a haunting image, actually, it's great.
It's really good.
I unironically like it.
It's a little bit like, I don't know, like Richard's scary.
It's got that cursed image kind of vibe to it.
It just looks like deliberately made to be a little unsettling.
And I'm like, hmm, yeah, well done.
You did it like cryptid Celestia.
Yeah.
But yeah, like the response is pretty good so far.
Like people are making fan art for everything.
Like the fandom may rise from the ashes or the show could suck.
It'll be a fan.
I mean, it looks.
You know, I mean, it looks to me like it's high enough quality.
And it like, no, I can totally see the old bronies just jumping on this new bandwagon.
I don't. Yeah, like, why not?
Maybe.
Hmm.
I mean, if I were if I were still a brony and I saw this, I'd be like, yeah,
it's different, but it's still more pony stuff.
I'd be I'd probably be into it.
Yeah, it makes sense.
I really, really don't like the Pixar look, though.
I really hate that.
I might check out.
Shit, I might check out.
It's very derivative.
I want to I want to know.
I want to know if I like the new one just because why not?
Oh, I'm definitely going to watch the movie for sure.
Like I'm contractually obligated.
Why? I don't know.
Hey, though, I'm curious.
Brony curious.
I'm for you.
Yes. Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
It's no shame.
There's no shame in watching a pony show just because it's an extreme.
No, there's no shame in it, but I wasn't going to do it.
Maybe it'll be good.
I don't know.
No, it's not.
Why would you think it would be good?
I've why would it be good?
There is a statistical chance that it could be good as small as it may be.
Yeah, we don't know everyone who's working on it.
It could be the people from the show or us.
I mean, actually, I don't know.
I think it's a different animation studio, a different studio altogether.
Yeah, last time a pony movie came out, we did a a PCP episode about it,
where we should we should do one about Gen five on our own.
I'm I'm ready.
I'm ready and willing to do another one.
When is it coming out?
I don't know, actually.
I don't think there's a really state is so little information.
I think it's soon.
It sounds like they're ramping up advertising, assuming it's not too far from now.
Fascinating. OK, well, we'll have to.
Offer roll up the old OCs for that one.
Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah.
We should make three.
Tom, you can make 3D version of your Bernie Currier.
So see tall tales. Yes, yeah.
You can do that. You can make them all of us for free.
All right. Correct.
That's that's how it works.
Yeah. Nice.
It's like a low poly tall tales makes 3D video like with 3D glasses.
But then you I will pay you by the polygon.
OK, I'll just make a really low poly throw like a sub div on there.
Multiply it by like 15 X and charge you per polygon.
Just just make it a perfect sphere.
OK, that's still a lot of perfect smooth.
Yeah, exactly. That's how you would maximize profit.
You just make the smoothest sphere you can.
But I don't have my RTX 3060 Ti.
It won't handle those polygons. God damn it.
Oh, you're that's you fucked up.
You don't own the means of production.
Yeah, I know, production.
Yeah, you've been you've been hamstrung.
Scalpers is what globalism is bad.
It's time to next voicemail.
Yeah, let's let's go on.
Next voicemail is Error Array and Bear Investment Classroom.
Help. He can't count three, two, one, go.
He's nice.
Spare the bear.
Making investments in teacher callers.
The bear needs more than just table manners.
How can I teach him about investment?
Why is this a song?
Well, it's just how they speak.
Yeah. Why would you be asking us for how to learn about this episode?
This episode is proved definitively.
We are not the people to talk about this with.
I've just do the opposite of what we say.
Lost hundreds of thousands of dollars every second.
I'm like the I'm like the reverse Jeff Bezos.
I lose ten million dollars a second by not having been part of the original Bitcoin people.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, I like that.
I think that's a funny that's funny.
I like it. I'm very proud of myself.
Good job.
Thanks.
Next voicemail is from Keyblade Spirit.
Well, I like that he invested in t-shirt callers, not in t-shirts,
specifically in t-shirt callers.
That's called Division of Work.
That's called Division of Labor.
That's a post industrial society.
That's called technology.
Next one is Keyblade Spirit.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, here's how to truly enjoy Mindsweeper.
But first, a brief history lesson.
Oh, you see, Mindsweeper and all the other default games that came with Windows, whatever.
Those were designed specifically to teach people how to use the mouse.
And this is crucial because in order to enjoy Mindsweeper in the form that it was originally intended,
you just have to completely forget every single thing you know about using a mouse.
And that will make it a perfect 100% keynote experience.
I know this because this is how I learned how to use a mouse in Microsoft Windows back in the day
when I was a toddler.
I don't.
Good night.
Okay, I do not follow the logic of why do you why do you need to forget everything about
how does that improve the Mindsweeper experience?
Is it because the wonder of being able to affect things on screen with a mouse,
that's where the true joy of Mindsweeper comes from?
Is that what's being applied here?
I can't unlearn it.
My mouse is a wireless Bluetooth mouse.
I need to go get a ball mouse from 1995 in order to truly enjoy Mindsweeper as intended by this logic.
The tactility of the little rubber ball moving the X and Y values
is the only way to play Mindsweeper properly with original hardware,
this emulation with Bluetooth technology, you're just not cutting it.
I must acknowledge that I made a complete fool of myself last week in talking.
There were comments addressing this and Gib, you explained it to me as well,
that you can in fact deduce a lot more about Mind Locations than I was seeing at the time.
Obviously, I am terrible at Mindsweeper.
But now I get it, if you're like cross-referencing multiple squares with numbers,
you can give it, oh, if this one's got two next to it,
but that one's only got one next to it and it can't be either of these,
this must be a safe square and the mind must be here, if these both are next to one.
I just wasn't thinking.
You just thought it was too much like a real Mindsweeper, in real life with a mind detector.
Where you just go willy-nilly and just jump wherever you are looking.
Yeah, they get all that expensive equipment, they just like long jump into the thing, see what happens.
I think it's just because I played Mindsweeper since I was a little baby,
and I just thought it was like a baby game, and I didn't think about how like, no,
it actually is kind of like a puzzle, sort of like PyCross,
where you sort of like logic it out.
I just have never approached it that way, and I've seen it for so long.
It was a different way of conceiving of the game.
You know, briefly, mentioning like the Windows, like the game package with Windows,
to teach people about the mouse, I remembered the joy of turning on the mouse trails,
so that when you move the mouse, like a after image of your cursor is left,
and I found the settings in Windows 10, so now I can just, I have thing now.
I remember.
Why would you want to do that?
Because I remember it, I remember like moving it one pixel at a time,
and you can like make it look cool, like it's 3D, or like a mouse-shaped prism.
Ooh.
I'm making swirly's right now.
Wow, that's amazing.
Fuck Mindsweeper, fuck playing Mindsweeper during the podcast.
I'm just gonna make mouse swirly's.
Just make mouse swirly's.
Is better.
Uh, next voicemail is called Max L Clutch.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey PCP, it's time to shift these voicemails up a gear, with me.
Max Clutch!
Oh my god.
It sounds like he's actually-
All right, give me your fastest speeds in the car, each of you.
Adam up, divided by three, that's the speed I'm going on my next voicemail.
Wait, your fastest speed in a car?
No, he says give me numbers, and then I'll calculate them,
and that's the speed I will go in my next voicemail.
I don't want you to die though.
Oh, I kind of want him to die though.
Wait.
He said, yeah, give me your fastest speeds in the car, each of you.
I don't know what the fastest speed I've gone in a car.
I mean, I've definitely done over a hundred.
I might have done-
I feel like I might have done 120 one time.
Is that a thing you can do in a car?
I don't-
Yeah, in some cars.
I've gone on a motorway.
What is a motorway?
I've definitely done at least 90.
I think I've gone up to 110 at one point, but never more than that.
I've definitely gone over a hundred.
I'm not sure if I've ever actually done 120.
Maybe.
If we've all done a hundred, this guy's pushing a hundred next voicemail.
There was a-
I drove from Idlewild, California to Las Vegas and back one time,
and that is a bunch of long, featureless roads through the fucking desert.
And I did it in just a fucking sedan, and I shit you not.
There was-
I literally raced a guy on the highway.
My car was not cut out for it, but there was another guy in-
I don't know what model it was, but it was a red-
It was a sports car, and he was passing people.
He was ducking and weaving, and I just did it.
And I followed him, and we just kind of stayed neck and neck.
We kind of stayed neck and neck with each other,
and just kept passing people together.
And I think I eventually just let him go, because I didn't want to keep doing this.
But I did that one time, and I went really, really fast.
Pretty zoomy, I hope you-
Next voicemail is called-
Wait, I just want to say 17.
I've been- I haven't driven a lot, but I have taken some lessons,
and I went on a motorway once, and it says,
Do the motorway, 70 miles per hour.
Okay, I said, tears running down my face, expecting to die every any second.
So that's my number.
Cool.
Do you not drive?
I don't, no.
There's no reason to where I live.
I mean, I don't really eat anymore.
I used to, because I used to live in places that required it more.
God, I'm jealous of your ability to not need a car.
I hate driving, it's the worst.
That, well, that's why I wanted to live in the greater Boston area,
which was great until COVID, and then I don't want to take any transportation,
any public transit.
I just had to pay my excise tax, and every time I have to pay my excise tax,
I see the with rage.
What is an excise tax?
An excise tax is a Massachusetts only tax,
where they tax your vehicle for using the roads, and we're the only state that has it.
So it's a tax on your car, basically just for having a car.
Correct.
Okay.
And it's really, it's not expensive, mine was like $50, but it's just like,
it's the principle of the matter, that like every year I have to pay an additional tax,
just for having the fucking car, and where the only stateship does it,
yeah, yeah.
And it's just like, fuck you.
Yeah, like auto insurance, and like all the associated,
even if you don't use the car, it costs you money, plus it's expensive just to buy one.
The problem is if you don't use the car, the car will break down, and then it's dead.
So like, it's a liability any way you cut it.
I hate it, I hate car ownership, and I'm glad that I don't do it.
Uh, well, although sometimes I do,
sometimes I think about maybe getting a Vespa or something one day, I don't know.
I could do that, I could get a Vespa.
It's tempting.
Might be funny, might be funny.
Finally live out your FLCL fantasies, all those years ago.
You know, you know, the thing about it though, is that
Haruka rides the Vespa like you would ride a motorcycle, like she does it cool.
But like a real, like that's sort of, I didn't really think about it at the time,
because I had never really seen a Vespa in real life.
But sort of the joke of that, is that an actual Vespa is not cool, and like doesn't
fucking do anything, which, yeah.
An anime Vespa, in all sense of the word.
You should never, never the less, I mean,
never the less the idea of like a small motorized vehicle still has its appeal,
even if it's fucking dweeby and doesn't go fast or anything.
Like still, maybe.
I'd think about it.
Moped's can be cool, in a cringe kind of way.
Night based.
A next voicemail is Cross, literally my first acapella, but I think it's okay.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working, I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking, myself, I'm suiting.
I am an asshole, I am a stupid bomb.
I got a deadline, don't want to do it.
That was pretty good.
Yeah, that should be the theme song for this episode.
I agree, I was gonna say the same thing.
Eleazar, make it happen, make it work.
Cut it, crop it, chop it, and send it to the press.
Next voicemail is called, hey, a couple of questions.
Three, two, one, go.
You guys like macaroni salad?
Yeah.
No.
I don't know what that is.
No?
Shit, just dropped some on my floor.
Fuck.
Only one question so far, genius.
You know, isn't Speakpipe supposed to be like charging you money?
You just never did.
I don't know.
That is correct, and that is technically a couple of questions.
Okay.
We do know that, yes, it's funny.
I'm shocked that you, Tom, don't like macaroni salad,
and that you, Gib, don't know what it is.
I know what macaroni is, I think.
It's like a little pasta shape.
Okay, if you told me that you didn't know what macaroni was, I would freak out.
I think I've had macaroni before.
What do you mean you think you've had macaroni before?
Well, I mean, I've had pasta before, I don't know.
I think, like, think back to it.
Wait, pause.
What?
What is happening?
How do you not know what macaroni and cheese is?
Is that like an American thing?
That's impossible.
It might be an American thing.
I've never heard of it growing up until-
What?
Okay, Radcon 5 mac and cheese.
I don't like cheese.
That's unbelievable.
I'm just trying to think of like times where I,
like I know it's like small tiny little bits of pasta as opposed to like-
No, literally having a mental breakdown right now.
What is so strange about this?
It's like saying the sky's blue, I never knew.
That's literally, that's like, you know, bread?
I think I tried that one time and it was like, it was decent.
No, that would be like saying, I've heard of pasta, like as a whole food group.
Okay, yes.
Macaroni is a food group in America, let's be real.
I mean, okay.
It called it macaroni.
That was the first time I heard the word, but I didn't know what it was.
I mean, macaroni and cheese, other than like spaghetti, is like the most common pasta dish.
Spaghetti is the most, yeah, that's, that's like, if I said, I think I've had spaghetti, like-
No, no, no, it's the same.
That's, that is what you're saying.
I guess I can understand if that's-
That's literally on the level, that's literally on the level of what this feels like to me.
Not over here.
Okay, yeah, macaroni and cheese is like a, is like a staple over here.
I mean, it explains a lot.
It's very American, high in fat, high in carbs, not good for you at all.
When I think of like default pasta, I think of spaghetti and then I think of frisilli,
which is like the twists.
Those are like the number one and number two normal pasta things.
I mean, yeah, I mean, macaroni is probably not the most common pasta that I eat.
It's just, it's just such a staple of the, because it's macaroni and cheese.
According to Wikipedia, it's called macaroni cheese in the United Kingdom.
So it exists where you are.
Well, they cut out, they cut out the and, oh, they're too good for the and, okay.
I mean, I mean-
Wait, no, I haven't had these little, these little tiny tubes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I don't think, I haven't had macaroni and cheese because I just, I don't like cheese.
Practically speaking, macaroni and cheese, I mean, well, technically it's, you know,
traditionally made with macaroni.
I mean, if you made mac and cheese with fusilli, you'd still call it macaroni and cheese, probably.
Yeah, cool.
Kind of like how you still call it Jell-O, even if it's something else,
even if it's some other brand, or you still call it,
they still call it Coke, right?
Like in the South, is that where they call it Coke?
They call it every soda Coke?
Yeah, some places.
Some places they call every soda Coke.
Um, what was the other-
I mean, macaroni salad is like, it's cold, it's like cooked macaroni, but it's cold,
and it's usually got like a mayonnaise-based kind of sauce with like herbs maybe in it,
and like vegetables.
Yeah, I'm not a mayonnaise fan in general, so.
I, I like, I like mayonnaise, so.
You know, it's like a, you know, it's like a barbecue staple, you know, like you go to a
barbecue and you got like, you know, your dogs and your burgers and maybe like your ribs and
your sausages, and then you got your side dishes, and you maybe got like your potato salad,
and your macaroni salad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I love, I love potato salad.
It's, it's usually not macaroni, but I, I think I've had salads like that at barbecue and things.
Yeah, it's, it's, it's okay, I can't do the mayo, just not a huge fan.
I made a, I made a BLT the other day.
It sucks, it's keto, it's good keto food.
It is, I made a, I made a BLT on some keto bread the other day, and it was, uh, it was, uh,
have you, have you found keto bread?
Have you been, or have you looked for any?
I've seen a couple, but they all have like still a lot of carbs, even net carbs.
It's like over 10.
I'm just like, no, die.
And that's for one piece of bread.
I'm like, that's my entire day's carbs in one sandwich, not worth it.
If you can find, if you can find love and fresh, love and fresh is like all wheat,
like wheat starch, it's all, it's all fiber, like it's all fiber.
Okay.
And it's good.
If you can find it anywhere.
Where do you get it?
Aldi.
Oh, wow.
Didn't you say that like they just closed the Aldi near you?
They don't, they don't deliver it.
They, yeah, they'd close it temporarily to remodel and then they don't deliver it anymore.
But I go there and like their selection has shrinked significantly in the last like couple
of weeks, which really sucks.
I feel like I've said this before, but I'm shocked.
I'm shocked that they have it at my Aldi.
Cause when I think of Aldi, I think like kind of a crap selection, uh, place.
And yet they have these like very specific like specialty breads
that I can't find anywhere else.
So it's really just the best of both worlds.
Yeah.
It's, it's cheap and exactly what you need.
Cheap and niche is not usually something that goes together.
Spag ball, spag, spag ball is, is what people call it.
Whoa.
Spag, spag ball.
I never called it that.
What is it?
Spaghetti bolognese is like the colloquial term for that.
Oh, spag ball.
Wait, spag.
Okay.
Spaghetti bolognese, bolognese is like a tomato meat sauce, right?
Yeah.
That, that's what I think of like is maybe the equivalent of mac and cheese.
Like in terms of like ubiquitousness among English families.
This is weird.
I mean, we have, like we have spaghetti bolognese, but I mean most we, I mean,
spaghetti and meatballs would be more classic.
Yeah, maybe that fair.
Yeah.
I mean, I would, yeah.
I've never heard anyone call it spag ball, but I guess it's.
It was a few people at school called it that.
I was like, wait, people, that sounds gross.
Why would you call it that?
It does sound gross.
But it does sound gross, but I like it.
I, um, I like a good spag ball.
Um, I don't, uh, yeah, it's good.
It's probably not something I would like make.
I mean, not, I mean, I'm keto now.
So, uh, I've never been much of like a spaghetti guy.
It's fine.
It's okay.
I'll take it.
Um, next one.
Yep.
Yeah, suit up.
Okay.
Next one is called mentally challenging game.
Three, two, one, go.
So Gibbs said she wanted a game that can mentally challenge her.
Yes.
You know, look no further than Phoenix rights trilogy.
It's just been released on the PlayStation five and switch and PC.
Or you can just emulate the original Game Boy or DS games.
They are fantastic.
I, I don't know if I talked about this on the PCP,
but I had recently booted up my old DS and replayed the original trilogy just for,
because it was, I felt like it, and it was great.
It was so good.
I did.
I think this guy's, this guy's recommending games and his
and his recommendation is just, oh, games on the Game Boy.
Like no, that's not specific enough.
Say Phoenix, right?
I guess he did say Phoenix, right?
But series.
I mean, it's on Game Boy and DS.
So like, but Gibbs already played all those.
She's like, she's talked, she's talked about it many times and she's a big fan of that series.
Yeah.
I guess, right?
I guess he just didn't know.
Maybe he didn't know.
Um, I mean, I don't know if you've played it,
but like a game that I remember being like kind of like thinky and heady,
even though I haven't played it in a while.
I played it after Phoenix, right?
It was Hotel Dusk Room 215 for the DS.
Oh, is that the guy with the meme face where he's like smiling and he's like, yeah.
I have no idea.
It's like, it's like a, you hold the DS sideways and you go through like a 3D rendered hotel,
but all the characters are drawn in like pencil sketch looking things.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hotel Dusk meme face.
What's the one?
Nate used it in one of the Smash reveal videos.
I can't find it, but it's fun though.
It's a good game.
Yeah, I think I have that.
I don't remember beating it though.
So I could, I could boot that up.
It's this guy.
It's not that.
That's not the face that is the meme face.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the guy though.
Oh, there it is.
It was a fun game.
That's it.
That's my recommendation.
That's the one.
There it is.
He's so satisfied with whatever that is.
Someday I hope to feel satisfaction to that level.
Oh my God, I just got a fucking, this sucks.
I just got a fucking notification that I guess there's,
I have a family Zoom meeting at 5.30.
What does that mean?
What the fuck?
I mean, I'm glad we're almost done.
I guess, I had no idea, but I guess I'm supposed to have a family conference call
with my family in eight minutes.
They really need to sit down and talk to Nate
about this league of Nate fuckers.
It's just, it's getting a little out of hand and they're concerned.
No, they've joined the league.
Okay, I'm going to tell them that I'll be there soon.
If I'm a little late, it's fine.
Sorry, I got a little distracted there.
Next voicemail?
Yep.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's called Love the New Segment 321 Go.
Hey, it's that part of the podcast
where Oblivion followed those funny voices.
Yeah.
Smeagol must have been Oblivion's fall, right?
There's no way to know.
Who's Smeagol?
I mean, like in this, in a voicemail.
I mean, no, Smeagol, Smeagol.
Smeagol.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
No, actually no.
That was Smeagol from Lord of the Rings.
It was just Smeagol, yes.
Yeah.
I mean, it is a good new segment.
I enjoy Smeagol.
What?
I don't know, what is this?
Is this a joke?
Like, yes, I ironically do love the new segment.
Fuck you.
This guy thinks he's too fucking cool for school.
Yeah, yeah.
Next voicemail is The Lord of North Fearwell 321 Go.
The Lord of North Fearwell, it has come to our attention,
that I'd like to say, does the Dark Lord have to play mine, Smeagol?
I know.
I think this guy chooses his way in the game,
instead of improving his skills.
This guy, this like the lot of girls suck.
If it was a day, so early on the walking day,
and the Lord of North Fearwell 321 Go.
Shut up.
Who fucking cares about mine, Smeagol?
Apparently, it's a big deal.
I don't give a fuck.
It's a baby game for idiots.
Stop.
No.
No!
We are the Lord of North Fearwell 321 Go.
I'm so scared.
I hate you.
Is this a little too thick on the effects now?
I could not understand most of it,
but like the point came across loud and clear.
It's like if a Dalek was at the bottom of a well.
He's so upset that I didn't play minesweeper, right?
He's just like incoherent with rage.
Really?
You really stuck a nerve with the minesweeper community.
I did.
I triggered them, you might say.
I trolled them epically.
I was only pretending to be an idiot,
and you are the fool for being upset about it.
Next voicemail is called TheMainAlien at MoonAnion.com.
It's called AmoonAnion 321 Go.
Oh, Christ.
MoonAnion, mainly AmoonAnion.
I can't hear them.
No, you know what?
You know what?
MoonAnions are the most numerous of the aliens.
You could even say that mainly MoonAnions are the main aliens.
Look at what we've cultivated.
Oh, my God, why?
I'm going to brownmate in his butthole.
Night, night, boy, pussy, night, boy, pussy, oh, wow, yeah, boy, pussy, boy, pussy.
Oh, my God.
You know what?
Oh, my God, there's so many of them.
They really are the main aliens.
You know what?
That Love the New Segment guy, he was prophetic.
He knew exactly what he was talking about.
He had it exactly right.
The New Segment sucks, and I hate it.
Thanks.
I like the reference to the MoonAnions.
It's a Gib reference, a very ancient Gib reference.
Wait, is it?
Yeah, mainly MoonAnions are the main aliens.
It's from a video where me and my brother were in the park late at night hunting ghosts.
Ghosts?
Ghosts.
We're ghosts watchers, and we were in the park, and we found evidence of alien life forms,
the MoonAnions.
Yes.
Nice.
That's good.
Okay, you know what?
That does ring a bell, actually, vaguely.
Um, well, thanks for the fucking voicemail.
I liked it.
Next one, wait.
Yeah, it had its charms.
Next voicemail is called Bward Co-op number three, and this time I remember it's Ben,
weekly reminder to catch up on One Piece number three.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, Ben, Ben.
Here we are once again.
I'm disappointed in you.
Once again, it's Ben.
You can weekly reminder to catch up on One Piece.
How do you know?
Maybe I caught up on One Piece.
It's very good, and should only take a few days.
Thank you, bye.
A few days.
Very presumptuous of him to assume that I haven't caught up on One Piece yet.
Are you presumed too much about Ben's reading level?
No.
Take him a lot longer than that.
I am very stupid.
I'll get around to it.
It's fine.
It's good.
It's the best show on the internet.
It's the Procrastinators podcast.
That's it.
That's the end.
We did it.
Oh my god.
Right?
We made it.
We made it to another end of an episode.
You procrastinated with us for two hours and change.
How does it feel?
We listened to all the voicemails.
Go to patreon.com.
slash dprocrastinators to get value for your money.
The new bonus episode is out.
It's finally out.
I said it was out before, but I was misinformed.
But now it's out really.
I feel like I've said that every week for years now.
It's the behind the scenes episode.
But actually it's out now.
Thank you, Tom.
Check us out.
Check out Shekels for Heckles.
We'll do the Shekels for Heckles this Wednesday, March 10th.
In the evening, probably like 6 p.m. ish EST.
I'm sure we'll have a more solid announcement on Twitter.
Patreon or the TP Crastinators on Twitter.
We'll have an actual announcement.
I did it.
Speakpipe.
speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail.
If you want to annoy us on the show with some stupid bullshit that just wastes our time
and the time of the audience and we love it.
Thank you.
And go to kitco.com slash bitcoin price charts usd.
We are at 45331.
Okay, so we've pretty much just hung in there for the last hour or so.
That's fine.
That's good.
Is that everything?
Are we done?
Yes.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Follow us all on Twitter.
Give us all money in addition to the procrastinators podcast.
Follow all our projects, read our comments, play our video games, all that shit.
Yes, yes, indeed.
Okay, bye.
Thanks.
See you later.
Love you.
Love you very much.
I disavow this podcast.
You're very special.