Hello and welcome to episode 5 of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We're back again this week to talk about a new topic.
I'm your host, Guy, the best guy ever, your anime man extraordinaire, talking about all the hypest, kawaii shit that you need to have in your life.
And I'm here with my internet people once again. Let's go down the line. Ben, who are you?
Ben Saint, SaintComics.com. I'm a mangomancer.
Don't forget that Patreon link. That's what the people want to hear about.
No man, I'm playing it close to the chest this week. I'm keeping it cool.
Listen to this guy. Alright, Digi.
I stay hype! I stay hype!
There you go. Jesse Wood.
I'm Endless Jess. I review cartoons every week, but I forgot to this week.
Oh!
Ashy as fuck. Gibb, Hippocrit.
I'm Hippocrit, and I'm taking a shit.
And the Davoo.
I edit Digi Bro videos, or make my own videos. It depends on what gets the most patronage.
There you go. And we're back this week to talk about Hippocrit.
I think this is going to be the best podcast we've ever had, ever recorded ever.
Yes, I think that's crazy.
It might just change the entire podcast landscape, rock the whole industry to its core.
That's right. There's no doubt about it.
Oh, I get it. It's a joke.
That's no joke. You can take that to the bank and make 1.1% interest dividends on that motherfucker.
You thought that was great. Just wait for the next ones.
I don't know how you guys are thinking about doing this, but I think all I've been thinking about in preparation for this was just all the examples of hype
that have ruined my life over the years, with a couple examples of things that have come out relatively okay.
Because in general, and I think we'll probably all agree on this,
hype is the worst thing ever.
It is cancer.
It ruins my life all the time.
I don't like it. I don't like it.
Yeah, it's terrible.
It is.
There are occasional things that we can talk about when things actually live up to the hype,
and when you are hyped for something and it lives up to it, that's great.
But when it actually goes beyond your hype, that's when shit gets absolutely crazy.
And the most recent one that comes to mind for me is Undertale,
because everything I expected with Undertale was achieved at the end of the pacifist run,
and then when you get into the genocide stuff and all the stuff beyond that,
it went shooting way beyond anything I thought it would do.
I have a problem with people who say that Undertale was overhyped,
because it wasn't hyped at all. There was nothing official.
All the hype was word of mouth.
There was the demo, and I was super excited for the demo,
but yeah, everything became word of mouth after the game came out.
I mean, as someone who played the demo and then jumped on the game almost as soon as it came out,
like for me, even I was hyped for it just because I love the demo.
Yeah, me too.
I mean, but now look at the internet.
Now if your friends with anyone on the internet, they've told you you've got to play Undertale,
but don't look up spoilers because it'll blow your mind.
Well, you can say that the fans have overhyped it,
but I mean like when people blame the game for being overhyped,
when there was no marketing behind it whatsoever in the first place.
Right.
It's not like Watch Dogs where the hype was completely generated as a marketing thing beforehand.
There's one very big distinction to make with hype,
and that is a very specific kind of hype, which is pre-release hype,
which is mostly what we're going to talk about that week.
Corporate.
Sure.
Well, we'll talk about both.
Well, I mean, look at something like...
The actual hype that's good is like when you're actually having the thing that hype I love.
I don't know about that all the time because something like...
That kind of hype can be bad too.
Yeah, like a game like Final Fantasy VII or something,
if you want to play that now, there's no way you're going to go into that without bad news.
Everyone's got bad news now.
Let's take a step back.
Let's explain.
I want to explain hype before we get too deep into this.
Okay, good idea.
It's kind of what we do on this podcast.
Where's our Urban Dictionary, Nate?
That was the one that you had one job.
Yeah, I actually did.
I opened it, but the description was lackluster, so I didn't even buy it,
but I'll read it to you right now.
And I'll just do my own...
I'll just define it myself.
So hype basically is when you're getting excited for something.
When something is generating a lot of attention and everyone's looking forward to it,
or in the aftermath of it, people are making it out to be something amazing.
So hype can't...
You can never be hype for something that you've seen.
Hype is something that you either project to other people or receive from other people.
You almost verbatim quoted hype on Urban Dictionary,
which is when someone gets excited about something.
So good job.
But I think hype as an experience, once you've seen something and you think it's great,
you can hype it for other people, but I don't think that counts as you feeling hype.
You're now creating hype.
Hype is what people feel before they see it.
Other people hype something up for you, or you hype something up for other people,
but once you've seen it, you can no longer just be hype for it.
Let me put forward a somewhat counterintuitive notion,
which is that I believe that all hype negatively impacts the experience
and that generally the better you think something's going to be, the worse it actually is,
even if it's good.
There's something to that.
And that if you think something's bad, then it's going to be bad,
then it ends up being better, regardless.
And that hype is kind of like spoilers for overall quality in that if you're told something's good
and that it ends up being good, it's like you've sort of been spoiled on its goodness already
and it feels less significant.
I don't know if I agree with that.
I know what you mean.
I sort of agree there.
I think there's a lot of overlap.
I think that hype serves a purpose in that in order for you to go out of your way to seek out an experience,
you need to have experienced a certain amount of hype for it.
Yeah, that's the thing.
But if you get too much of it, then it's going to, but the hype itself negatively impacts your experience.
I would say that I have had more things ruined for me with hype than by spoilers,
where oftentimes if I hear a spoiler for something I didn't even care about,
it might get me interested because I'm like, whoa, that happens.
That's kind of like, maybe there's a show that I thought looked dumb,
but then I found out that one character dies and I'm like, oh, that's actually kind of cool.
Then I watch it.
But when people hype something for me and they make it out like, oh man, you're going to love this.
My immediate thought going into it is I better love this.
Am I going to love this as much as that guy thinks I'm going to?
Let's find out.
I'm really with Ben on that one.
In my bizarre, puritanical view of spoilers definitely crosses over into hype.
You need that little bit to get you to even play it in the first place,
but I don't even want to know if something is good or bad or when good things happen.
How many times you play in a game next to someone and they're like, dude, next part is the best part.
Get fucking hype for it. You're going to love it. It's the worst. I want to kill that man.
It's usually the fact that those people exist that they think hyping something up is a good idea.
Dude, let me tell you.
The hype itself is just sort of like sometimes it can be good.
It's not that they think it's a good idea.
It's that they want to do that to vicariously experience it through you as they can.
It's for themselves.
Let me tell you this little story about this guy I went to school with named Jarvis.
Jarvis? No, it was Jarvis.
This guy, he was in the anime club with me and he just loved.
Yeah, it was great. He just loved.
We always come up to be like, yo, guy, what are you watching right now?
And I'd be like, I don't know, Tsukuyomi or something.
We watched that one time and he was like, dude, that show is fucking great.
What episode do you want? I'm like, I don't know, episode three.
He was like, dude, episode four where, and he would describe the events that happen in that episode.
He's like, get ready for it, dude, you're going to love it.
So not only did this guy spoil everything that happened in every,
and he would insist on telling me these things every time.
I had to go out of my way to avoid him.
Like, this happened with every game, every show,
because this guy was an ultra-weeb.
He knew it all. He knew every single thing that I'd watched years before I'd seen it.
And just would insist.
It was this bizarre combination of trying to hype me and enjoying watching me be spoiled,
because I told him over and over, I didn't want to fucking know anything.
I think he had a massive impact on my viewing of spoilers and hype in my life in general overall.
That's understandable, man.
I do not relate to anything that's being said here pretty much.
Really? Interesting.
Get the hell out, Davoo. Who invited you anyway?
I think that the more familiar you get with a medium or a craft or a scene,
the more that you can manage your hype emotions.
And with video games at least, I've mastered the arts of no matter what I'm told,
no matter what expectation I have, no matter how I feel going into it,
I'm able to jujitsu everything around to maximize my enjoyment levels every time I play a game.
I don't buy that.
I think, I totally do.
People told me that Undertale was like, this cool game that's coming out and like, I don't care.
People can tell me something is a 12 out of 10 and it doesn't resonate with me at all on its own.
It can depend on who it is that says it.
And with Undertale, people told me you, Davoo, will like it because it's like Mario and Luigi in those kinds of games
and has similar elements.
I'm like, whoa, that got me interested.
When I went into Undertale, I was kind of in a downer mood.
I'm like, I'm going to try to dislike this just to see how much I like it.
Well, that's having an effect on you with that right there.
Within 30 seconds, I was completely into it.
Yeah, but what if you hadn't been though?
What if you had gone in with that same attempt to be like, I'm going to,
because I also played Undertale like, I'm probably not going to like this.
Everyone else is hyping this.
I'm just going to fucking shit on it.
And then I played it and I was like, that's pretty all right.
But like, I think that just speaks to the strength of the game,
whereas if it had been a weaker game and I'd went in with those expectations and I would have come out hating it,
even though like, I think there's plenty of stuff that's not that good that you can go in underhyped
and because it exceeds your expectations, you like it more.
Yeah, that's the great thing about being underhyped.
All that lower expectations, everything above that just makes it better when you finally see it, usually.
Which is a great thing.
Like, for instance, the show that me and D'Vu just watched because he had two for my series,
Raku Dai Kishi No Cavalry or Chivalry of a Filled Knight,
which is like a show that I dropped after the first episode when it was airing
and I thought it was, you know, pretty shitty.
But like, people were telling me, oh, it's better than Asterisk War,
because it's like kind of the same show.
So I was like, well, I'm going to watch it just so I can talk about it in my video
and I had no expectations.
And so when it turned out to actually be kind of okay,
it was so much better than I expected it to be.
Right.
That it was like overall a positive experience.
Whereas I've had times...
That was an anti-hype effect.
Yeah, whereas I've had times with shows like that I would give like a 6 out of 10,
but because like, my overall feelings about Chivalry were positive,
even though I'd give it like a strong 5 to a light 6,
whereas say with the Madoka Magica 3rd movie,
like, you know, I expected it to be something cool
and then I just kind of thought it was a 5 or a 6,
but it was such a let down that it then was...
I'm going to let you finish about Chivalry,
but Bushido is the best code of ethics to live by of them all.
Best of all time.
Yeah, well, let's talk about that only after they make an anime about it.
That's true.
Gabe, you were saying something.
It's hard to put into words what my argument is.
I'm trying to think because, like, things are hyped for me a lot,
but I usually only listen to the people I trust the opinions of,
like when you guys would tell me to say,
this game or this anime is great, you should watch it,
and I go watch it, and I have a good time,
even though like you said, like, you know,
you especially hype things up a lot.
I say everything's the best ever.
You say everything's the best ever,
and you're like, it's the greatest thing I've ever seen,
and I go and see it, and I'm like, yeah, you know,
I don't really feel, I don't ever get, like, disappointed
that something is not the greatest thing I've ever seen.
That's because I have the best taste, but, you know.
Are you saying, like, here's the thing though, Nate.
Like, I naturally don't feel, I don't get disappointed like that,
the other person to me.
I think, Nate, that the problem with hype,
because, yeah, now that Hippo mentions it,
it's super ironic that you are anti-hype,
but you hype people up all the time.
I don't want to be hyped.
I don't care about other people.
They can deal with it.
The problem is that I think everyone has that same mindset though,
that everyone thinks that their taste is great,
and that everyone's going to like the stuff they like,
and I think that's where a lot of hype comes from,
because, like, for me, you know, sort of like DeVoo,
I'm pretty resistant to hype for the most part,
where, like, I only really get hyped for stuff
if, like, people who really know me are hyping me for it, you know?
Because of the fact that I don't think many people like the things I like,
or dislike the things I dislike,
where, you know, like, with the current season shows,
like, erased, where there's all these people hyping fucking erased,
and everyone's shitting on me for not liking it and stuff,
and it's like, yeah, but if you knew my taste,
then this should be obvious.
Like, everyone should know that I'm not going to like this show,
so when people hype it, I wasn't buying into it,
because I'm like, what do you like?
You know, what are the other shows you like?
They obviously are not to my taste.
It's one thing if, like, if someone who likes all the same shows I like,
you know, hypes me for a new show,
and I'd be like, well, you know, I'm generally in my experience,
we've loved all the same things, so now I'm excited, you know?
Well, that's the thing, that's why I so look forward to recommendations from DeVoo,
because DeVoo likes tons of shit that I like,
and too, it's in terms of games.
You guys both seem to like really unique games.
That's true.
Really, like you were saying, there's kind of two different ways of being hyped for something.
There's like personal accounts of people you know telling you how good it is,
and that kind of shit, and I guess the lines are kind of blurred
since we're online figures who get comments from people,
but the other one is the endless cascade of people talking about shit,
like the new Star Wars or whatever.
There's literally no way to not be hyped for it,
because everyone in the fucking world is talking about it.
I think I generally take hype not very seriously at all.
I see that there's hype for Star Wars, for example,
and then I would go to all the reviewer and analysis people that I know
if they're talking about it and what they think,
and then I would form an opinion based on that.
The fact that there's hype on something,
like everybody's raving about this new thing,
I would look into it before feeling excited at all,
even if it was like a sequel to a game that I really liked or something.
Let's talk about Resistance 2 and or knowing how to manage hype
versus just being jaded generally.
Resistance 2 Fall of Man for the PlayStation 3 is the greatest game I've ever made.
Because I would say I'm somewhat resistant to hype,
but I think I would just say that's more that I'm generally jaded,
because when someone tells me something's good, I just don't believe them.
Even if I'm just...
Fall of Man was Resistance 1. I'm just pointing this out.
Glad we established that.
I've never played those games, and I think that I hate them actually.
They're all right.
If I saw all the Undertale hype going on now,
and I hadn't played it yet, I would think,
oh, that game looks stupid.
I'm sure it's not as good as everyone says it is.
I have this friend who recommended me this manga called Helc.
Have you guys seen this manga, Helc?
Anyone know what I'm fucking talking about?
Oh, man.
You told me a little about it yesterday, but no.
Helc. It's great.
But I have one friend who just said,
read this, it's awesome.
And I was like, okay, one person says it's awesome.
That's like...
No matter how highly one person praises something,
that's still just a little tiny blip on the hype radar,
no matter how glowing the review is.
So I don't know.
But I read it, and because I only had that little tiny bit of hype,
I thought it was pretty good, and I was like,
oh, yeah, okay, I actually like it.
Anyway, I guess the point I'm trying to make
is that I just don't believe anything is going to be good,
no matter how many people tell me it is.
That's good.
And in fact, the more people tell me that something's good,
and I don't know for a fact that it is good,
the more I start to be like, no, it isn't.
No, it's not.
No, it's not in my head.
They're clearly lying.
They're clearly just bought into the hype.
I feel very differently that I accept that sometimes
my taste might be very normal.
So if a lot of people like something,
I might like it as well.
I'm not as much of a hipster, I think, is the terror.
That's true.
I don't think you are.
Ironically, despite everything I just said,
and despite how much of a fucking hipster I am,
I still find that when lots of people like something,
I tend to like it too.
Yeah, I think it's pretty good.
And it makes me really mad.
It's pretty gay to...
I hate people who instantly have this knee-jerk reaction
of, if everyone is saying it's great that it must be terrible
because people are all secretly sheep and they're stupid.
Jesse, I feel that way.
Intellectually, I feel that way.
If everyone likes something, I feel like I'm going to hate it,
but in practice, it always ends up being
that if something's wicked popular, I end up liking it too.
Yeah, there's usually...
Like, home-stuck and undertale.
And I'll bet if I saw the new Star Wars, I would think it was fucking great,
even though I want to hate it so much.
There's usually a reason why a billion people like something.
See, that's the thing, though.
There's an interesting correlation here
between marketing and hype.
Because on 4chan, all the time, you'll see false flaggers
who just make threads praising something,
and they do it in a way that's obviously like a shilling sort of way
of praising it in an attempt to draw hatred for that thing.
And then there's...
This has happened many times.
There's been actual shills on 4chan who just come in
and are like, guys, how have you not bought a PS4 yet?
It is by far the best system.
I'm playing it every day with my hot girlfriend.
What are you doing with your life?
I got to...
In response to what Ben said, though,
I think it's sort of a...
I don't know if false positive is the right phrase for this.
Anyway, I think that you're looking at it backwards,
because...
I am?
Yeah, maybe the things you like tend to be popular,
but that doesn't mean that the things that are popular
tend to be things that you like.
For instance, if we measure just sheer popularity,
like Assassin's Creed and Call of Duty
are the most popular games,
and I don't think any of us give a fuck about them.
I have never played any of those.
Maybe I'd love them.
I did a huge research project four years ago,
or maybe even five, on my anime list,
where I was looking into all of my favorite shows
and trying to measure how my tastes stand up to everyone else's,
because I consider my anime list to be a really good gauge
for the common man anime fan.
A lot of the stuff that's the highest rated
or the most popular on the site is stuff I don't care about.
However, all of my favorite shows were well rated on the site
and were pretty popular.
None of them were something that no one had ever heard of.
None of them were below a 7.5 rating.
They're all pretty well liked and pretty popular.
It's not that I like everything that's popular.
It's just that the things I like do align with some other people.
Nothing I like is so out there that no one else knows about it
or no one else cares about it.
I guess I would say I'm in pretty much the same boat there.
I think the big thing that I don't relate to
is this idea that your different perspectives
have to blend together into one overall.
There's something that's talked about
in the beginning of A Book of Lenses by Jesse Schiel
about the art of game design, about how to analyze a game while you play it.
It's called the Holographic Experience,
in which you play the game purely while simultaneously
you're like a ghost looking at yourself
and studying it at the same time.
It sounds very Buddhist.
In becoming an analyst, I'm able to do that.
I'm able to look at all these different perspectives
at the same time.
I'm able to think about its cultural perspective,
my baggage going into it,
because baggage can be interesting.
Baggage can be from Louis Vuitton.
It can be really luxury.
I can enjoy everything simultaneously.
I don't need... I really think that my experience...
These Time Cube references are very distracting.
I can't pay attention to your point when you keep saying simultaneously.
Basically, it's about the Time Cube principle.
I'm looking at four different timelines
of my experience at once.
You can't say the top and bottom are sides,
so obviously they don't count.
They're not part of the queue.
I'm looking at two Radgai Kishinokavari, whatever.
I was like, oh, I guess it's going to be decent.
I really think that my opinion of it
was not overall changed by my expectations.
Episode 11 happened and I'm like, oh, that was terrible.
I don't like this show.
I don't think it's that your opinion is swayed by your expectations.
I don't think that's necessarily what we're arguing.
It's more the overall experience.
Like I said, Cavalry and Madoka Movie 3,
I would give the same score.
It's just a matter of one I went into with no expectations
and because it exceeded them so much,
then it was like, wow, I experienced something that was better
than I expected it to be and that makes me feel good.
Whereas with Madoka, it was like,
I expected to see like a seven out of ten
and I got like a five and so it was a disappointment,
even though I like both shows the same amount.
Do those feelings last at all
or are they just like memories of having feelings?
I think they continue to last
because I still have a sour feeling over the Madoka Movie
just because I felt like it should have been better.
So in that way, it would be like,
the best idea would to be to assume that everything is shit.
Yeah, pretty much.
But I can't do that though.
That's what I'm saying. All hype is bad.
Negative hype makes you experience a work more positively.
I can't do that like legitimately.
I can pretend to say, this is going to be bad.
Well, nobody can force themselves to think that way.
I usually have a very positive outlook,
but I don't have a very high one.
My point came out a whole lot less cogent.
But I never get really blown away either.
My point came out a whole lot less cogent
because I was sitting on it for 20 minutes
and when I sit on something for 20 minutes,
it comes out really uncogent.
That's what your mom said about my dick.
I just get really anxious when I sit on it for too long.
It wasn't cogent.
If I interrupted everyone at the beginning,
it would have come out really eloquent.
Well, here's something I've been sitting on for 20 fucking minutes.
It doesn't affect my enjoyment level.
It can make it better and it never makes it worse.
Here's something I've been sitting on for 20 minutes.
It was at the risk of bringing this up too early
and it would have just ended the whole conversation.
I wanted to detail Yahtzee's feelings on hype
that he shared in a video once.
Are you talking about the Punnett Square?
Yeah, it's the square where he says
if you go into something with high expectations
and it meets those expectations
then it'll be great.
If you go into something with high expectations
and it doesn't meet those expectations
then you'll feel like shit.
If you go into something with low expectations
and it turns out to be shit
then you won't lose anything.
If you go in with low expectations
and it turns out to be amazing
then it will way exceed your expectations
and it will be great.
Expectations nothing can ever hurt you if you go in with high expectations then sometimes you'll get burned
Sometimes you'll get that transcendent experience like I did with undertale where you have hype and then it's better than you thought and like
What do you want to do? Do you want to spend your life avoiding harm?
I just think I think that when you I think you should just manage your hype
Carefully there are there are movies. I've seen where like okay
My brother Victor has a tendency to hype things like when he likes it because yeah, like like like all of us
He's fairly jaded and fairly, you know critical
But he also has pretty different tastes from me and like it's funny because it's weird to him
Like he's so used to us having the same taste that when he likes something that I don't really care about then
It's like he doesn't expect it and it's kind of jarring
So he'll hype me for stuff that he likes and then I'll watch it and I'll be like I
Didn't really like it just seemed okay to me and he'll be like what like I can't I can't grasp that you didn't like this as much
As I did you know so like I have had times where like like we watched this movie
Confessions which is like one of his top three favorite movies and like I watched it and it was just kind of like I
Expected so much more just because he kept talking about how much he loved it and then I was like I don't like I don't get it
You know
So I feel like if I had just seen it with no expectations
It would have probably been better than then with the ones I did have but like I do think that there is some value in like
Managing your hype and like getting if I think if you know you're gonna love something then yeah
Let yourself get hype for it. Like I but can you ever really know that?
I think you can because I think there's times where the hype is like it doesn't matter
It won't change it like for last year the most hype
I got about anything was for the video game dengeki bunko fighting climax
Oh, right out in like September no October and I was hyped for it for like six months because it's a game where you play as
Characters from dengeki bunko light novels and it's a 2d fighting game and like I love 2d fighting games inherently
I'll play any of them, you know, and I love that I got to beat up all these characters that I hate
You were in this game
I get to beat up Kirito and Shana or play Shana and beat up Kirito
I get to play characters. I like characters. I hate and like it didn't even matter to me if the game was going to be like
Legitimately good or not like it was gonna be worth the price of admission just for the experience of a 2d fighter where I can beat up
Kirito, that's true. That's a pretty safe bet
Yeah, no matter what it was gonna be cool
So I got really hype for it and it did end up being as good as I wanted it to be like it was every bit as fun as I
hoped it would be and so like I felt like it was money well-spent
Well, you know, did you an example that involves you actually for me was when I
Tried to watch log horizon because this was after seeing your like 10 out of 10 video and I was like well
I have to check this out. This sounds exactly like what I like
and I think that I would have liked it more if I hadn't had these crazy expectations and
Like I got specifically I was looking forward to like the arguments you made of like the whole food thing
How it like changed the world and everything it does to the story and that stuff was in fact interesting
But I really was just on the lookout for like, okay, this is a 10 out of 10. I need to study it
I need to be looking for why this is the case
Yeah, and as a problem like when I watched along horizon
I had only heard that it was mediocre. No one ever told me it was good
We came in with totally opposite expectations. Yeah. Yeah, I think your relationship with hype
Can needs to be changed and evolved as your relationship with that medium or that genre
Changes, I think that I think hype is very important to get someone into a thing
You keep talking about anime. I didn't have enough people
Hyping me up to anime shows. I I didn't all the people who I talked to even if they were anime fans
They were way too polite. They weren't if they had jumped down my throat. You had the weirdest anime fans around you, man
I've never met an anime fan who was like that. I've only met like a evangelical everyone must watch Naruto
Or else kill themselves
evangelicals and
I and so as a result I didn't get into anime until like I didn't really get into it until like two years ago
I didn't I didn't I wasn't gonna get into my little pony until a friend of mine said you've got to watch this
You gotta watch that and thank God
Yeah, Ben Ben told me to watch Milo, but Jesse would you describe it? Yeah, it was the best thing I ever did for you
What's going on? Are you are you an evangelical Jesse?
Never mind. You're you're not a fast enough move on
I think that hype is really important to get someone into a thing and that as you get more familiar with it
You can learn more about it or is that my knowledge that it exists and that it's generally okay
I do think it's hype
I think that I think I've when when I want people to get into anime
I do involve hype although at the same time when I'm trying to like I
Lately I try my hardest to not hype people when I introduced into something, you know
Like I'll say like when I tried to get you into a shield hero yesterday. I was just like it's a good manga
I think you'll like it. I did that I read the whole thing yesterday. Yeah, I saw you reading it
But like I was just like yeah, it's pretty good. Like it's not amazing, but it's pretty good. You should read it
I think you will like it. I don't think yeah, I think it's a 10 out of 10
But like yeah, you know
I think my expectations were just a tad bit above where they should have been I did read it
I liked the whole thing, but nothing like
Super-duper amazing happened which was what you were saying, but I didn't calibrate my expectations quite properly
All of your like 10 out of 10 recommendations can be a great
Proof that I am good at not being overhyped or underhyped or anything at the time
You gave like an 8 out of 10 to kill la kill and so I watched it
I was like this is a 10 and then you gave like a 10 out of 10 to log horizon and I watched it
I'm like I have some problems. So I give it a 9 you gave a 10 to ghost in a cell standalone complex
And I watched it and I was like I agree
This is a 10 you gave a 9 to serial experiments Lane and I watched it and like I don't get it
So I gave it a 6 and so like I think that there's I think I'm able to
For some reason I am making my points so much worse than I thought I did I think I'm getting overhyped about my own points
I legitimately think that's a thing that you go through a lot
I've watched you overhype yourself for your own points in the past in
Conversations, I've also watched you overhype your own abilities where you're like
I'm gonna have this done by the end of the day and then and the funny thing is
Every time DeVu has ever told me when he's gonna finish a video. I always tack a day on in my mind
He'll always say like I'm gonna have this done by like 10 p.m. And in my head. I'm like tomorrow, you know
He's like, okay
It's gonna be a few more hours cuz my internet died or because this or that went wrong and I always I never let myself
When the video is gonna be I
Lots of people do it lots of people do it, but guy is particularly bad not to overhype myself
But I am the best in the world at missing my own deadlines massive
Yeah, I've got like like there is one medium that is ruined by hype for me and that is analysis videos because
What the fuck those things don't I mean hype they do I hype them
Nobody else in the world
Aside from this group of people
Okay, nobody else goes holy shit guys, there's a new mr. Beaton
I was like guys you have to go fucking. Yeah, and then I ultimately don't care if I agree with anyone's opinions on any game
Any movie any show but if one of us thinks that some analysis is a 10 out of 10
And I don't or I do and that bothers me it bothers me that did you like nerd writer so much and won't
Criticize him as much as I want to and that bothers me
Wait, how much do you think I like nerd writer? I have no idea, but you gave me a top
You praised him pretty glowingly. I mean he is making
unbelievably consistent videos every good. Oh, they're consistent
Oh, I can do their kids. Oh, they're consistent, and they have nice down quality
All right nerd writer has made about a hundred fucking videos last year
Like and all of them have a little bit of intrigue in them
And that's a lot of intrigue when you add it all up if you watch all of this
I'm sure I want to watch all of this even if he only makes one point per video in the end
He's made 52 points Nate put out one video last year. Yeah, and I fucking crushed that
But you didn't put out any other fucking videos
So I think there's a value in something like I am way
I am more likely to stay
Excited for someone's channel if they keep putting out content all the time and I'm like oh man
You're hitting me with every different side nerd writer puts out videos on paintings never seen someone
Obviously on YouTube
I've never seen someone analyze poetry on YouTube before he covers
No one covers comics the way he covers comics. He makes videos but every subject matter in existence
That's what interesting about him
They're all too short and they all feel like they stop short of saying anything really substantial about whatever he's talking
I mean, that's true
But they still make a point in the end like there's still something interesting in there like we made the video about the
He made a video about the the painting that says this is not a pipe and he's like the point of this painting is that it's not a pipe
It's a representation of a pipe and therefore, you know when we look at images
We describe them as that's a like if I showed you a picture of a pipe, you'd say that's a pipe
But it's not a pipe. It's a representation of a pipe and it's a study of language interesting point
I hadn't not that interesting because that but what you just related to me is information that is obvious to any thinking person at a
Glance and I do not need to spend two minutes
Painting I would never have thought about that. Did you that's very obvious. That's literally the entire point of the painting
I've never seen the painting, but okay, here's the thing
Writer makes videos about things. I've never seen before is interesting enough in itself
I've never seen any of the movies. He's talked about except like children of men. I've never seen any of the paintings
He's talked about
Except maybe nightcrawlers, but I didn't know what it meant. I just seen it
I don't give a fuck. I've never thought about a painting before nerd writer has taught me to think about a font about a painting
Don't understand paintings at all. I just look at him. I'm like what the fuck is that? It's colors. I don't care
It doesn't move. It doesn't have dialogue. I don't fucking. I don't want to look at it
You know it really into the fact that he's had would you look at a painting if it had subtitles?
Well, they were Japanese this is not a pipe has subtitles and I still wouldn't have thought about what it meant, you know
I like I just want to go back to
Managing hype because that's the topic. Yes
The way the way that I manage hype
I've realized is that I base it completely on research for example
Dark Souls 3 is coming out soon and I'm extremely hyped for that because I know that the director is the same guy as Dark Souls 1
Miyazaki I forget his first name
Yeah, that's actually wrong. You know what that's that's actually that brings me to a great point though
Here's something we've all been skipping out on and Nate you kind of touched on this with like a risk in feeling
I I do think that there is a value in
Experiencing extreme disappointment. Yeah, I think that there are some things that you should just go all in
Let yourself get hyped for and just be crushed by because it can it can lead to
Years of you cathartically bashing it like Dark Souls 2
Very true
You know like with with Demon Souls because I don't know but I'm sure you guys probably played Dark Souls first
But like my friends were hyped for Demon Souls before that even came out because one of my friends is a huge from software fan
He was into armored core and all that shit and he was really excited for Demon Souls
So that came out and it exceeded everyone's expectations
We were super excited and then they were making Dark Souls and we all got like really hype and it came out and everyone was kind
Of like undecided at first like no one could decide if it was as good as years for people to figure out
Yeah, well cuz it you know at first it it had like a little bit more cheapness to it
And they also ironed a lot of stuff out in patches, you know, that was a problem
Yeah early part, but like, you know, it was kind of tepid but then people were like oh man
Dark Souls is the greatest game ever and then people got really hype and then they're like Dark Souls 2 and we're all like
Oh fuck yeah, and at this time no one knew about the like how important he did Takamiyazaki was or how like you know
Changing directors would change everything or any of that we were just like it's another Dark Souls
You know and then Dark Souls 2 came out and everyone played it and they're like oh, yeah, it's pretty it's pretty good
But it's not as good as Dark Souls one and then over time it just like you know
It just right people think about it a huge issue right and then like when Bloodborne was coming out
Then it was like well should we get hype like I want to get hype
But yeah, that's gonna be like Dark Souls 2, but Miyazaki's directing it again. Maybe it'll be amazing
Maybe I should stake it all on the line, you know
It was great. You're like all right. Well Miyazaki's never disappointed me
So surely Dark Souls 3, surely surely Dark Souls 3, surely
That's where I am right now. Yeah, I'm actually considering buying the collectors edition for that
And like if Dark Souls 3 turns out to be a huge piece of shit
We will talk about it for ever
It will be legendary if we like we will never shut up about it
You know and like I think there's some value in that worth like because when I think about
Hype and the dangers of hype the biggest thing that comes to mind is watchdogs because it was a game that was
Way overhyped for years all the trailers completely were misleading
They all made it look like it was gonna be this really deep like next-gen game
No one had ever seen like this level of like polish in a game before going by the trailers
Which were completely false, you know, and then it came out and it was just kind of a shitty talking about right
It wasn't even interesting. It was mediocre
So then and the thing is that game had sold so many like pre-order bonuses and special editions and everyone who got them got
Burned everyone special edition was like I shouldn't have got the special edition
It wasn't that good of a game games these like a lot of triple a games are more about the trailers than the game right
They're about establishing pre-order while like generating hype for the people who felt all that hype and then were let down
Like I'm sure that they they hate it and they wish they had that money back
And they wish they hadn't played that game
But like as a cultural thing it was kind of awesome to watch because it was like, you know watching this mighty like
Opening of the the fjord of people realizing that oh my god
Hype is bad and I should stop buying these expensive like you know, I my friend
My friend Josh who buys like special editions of everything like he was so burned by watchdogs that it made him rethink his buying habits
You know and like what what was in the special edition of watchdogs. I don't fucking know. It's probably like $95 though
It has Aiden's iconic hat. Oh good
I
Wanted I want to do we stop coming over on the topic on a cat nice while we're on the topic of our personal
Stories and personal and like particular height. Yeah, I wanted everyone to share a horror story
I want to talk about my own personal hype tragedy, please which was spore. I was gonna say I bet it was four
Yeah, yeah fucking spore tell us when the original trailer for spore came out. We'll write
You know what I'm talking about. Yeah, I know about I was big on this for hype
Lots of people were people all over. Yeah, will write came out and demoed this version of spore
Which was so fun
It looked so fucking robust and it looked like it just it made it look like anything was possible
And it played this this little like dinosaur man
And he just like twisted it around and like gave it three legs and it procedurally generated this perfect-looking walk cycle on three legs
And then he showed off all these other hypothetical monsters and they all had
Like yeah, they all like wobbled around realistically according to their weight and like he
It all just looks so real and visceral and like nothing that had ever existed before and then he zoomed out and you saw the solar system
And he zoomed out and you saw the whole galaxy and it was like oh my god
There's so much possibility and it's all gonna be procedurally generated and there's gonna be so much emergent content
And it's gonna be amazing and for two fucking years people talked about this shit for two fucking years
People said oh, here's what I'm gonna make in spore. Here's what I'm gonna make in spore
It's gonna be the greatest thing ever and then it came out and it looks nothing like the demo
It doesn't work. It doesn't it doesn't even behave similarly
I mean it kind of superficially resembles the demo
But it's not the same game and it doesn't have the same tone or atmosphere or capabilities
Yeah, and the whole thing was clearly just a fucking fabricated farce of a goddamn pre-rendered trailer because there's because there's no dang
Way you could do anything in the trailer that was in the dang final release, you know
And gosh, I'm still so salty about I'm with you
I think that will write in this case had the absolute best of intentions and thought he'd be able to do it
But I think when reality that's that fucking Peter Mullin. He was he was just channeling Peter Mullin
He's he really was that's the thing though
These people have really lofty goals put Peter Mullin you especially and will write in a lot too in this case
They want to do all the stuff and they they plan as if they'll be able to do it and they market it on these
Hypothetical like we'll definitely be able to do this and then like when they don't respect that in principle
I don't respect in principle at all
You cannot tell people that you are going to do X if you don't know for sure you can do it
I mean, I think what they should do though is if I think when this is the problem with the games marketing is that they will never
Admit it when it's not that you know like if like when fucking
When Peter Mullin you hypes up fucking fable 2 or whatever and says all this shit
Then when the game's about to come out and it doesn't have those capabilities. He should come out and say by the way
It's not gonna be like that. It's gonna be like this
We couldn't we didn't have the budget to make it as
Here's what Peter Mullin who does fable 2 comes out and it's a piece of shit, but he doesn't admit it
Until he starts hyping fable 3 right? Oh, yeah, great
You know I know we I had such great hopes for fable 2, but it ended up it was nothing like I wanted to be
It was basically a piece of shit, but I'm gonna accomplish everything I set out to do with it
And more and fable 3 fable 3 will finally be the great game
I've been promised then they come out and the same fucking thing when will they learn
Triple A the video game big budget hype machine is the worst type machine. Yeah, especially
There's a huge issue of like I don't know
Really deception like something like Dark Souls 2 does not look anything like the
Videos that they show it looks like shit compared to the video all they had to do it
They knew it right like I'm sure because the thing is with Dark Souls 2
I'm sure that they did intend that system to be in there because if you look at Bloodborne
It does have like the torches and the lighting right like that was supposed to be in Dark Souls 2
But yeah, they should have just put out a statement. Hey this trailer no longer represents what the game is, you know, right?
It would have been so easy and and you you know, it'll disappoint people
But like at least it'll be honest and they won't fucking hate your guts from that on
Everything you say, you know hide behind shit like oh those trailers like they were just in development
But they never show you what it's actually gonna look like once it comes out
All you've got to base your thoughts on are the demos that they showed where it looks good or whatever
But you know like we're talking about how like companies literally just lie about what things are gonna be in regards to hype
But like that's like the worst case scenario. That's not even what you should normally is normally the issue with hype
There's it's it's it's everything before that about like expectations being set too high and then them not being met or you know
That that whole gamble you're taking me to do that the whole business is lying to you thing is the worst-case scenario really
I'm trying to like think of what my most like
Hyped up for something and then it wasn't yeah, it's a way to I think it's like I think for me
I would I would say that like
Because I'm so slow to actually get around to stuff my hype usually like just diminishes over time where like for instance when I was
Like a teenager
I was really into JRPGs and I just kept buying JRPGs because I was excited for all of them
And I just kept buying them
But I would never beat them or I would never play them very far and then it was just kind of like as I grew up
I sort of realized that those games were probably not gonna be fun
You know like a lot of the ones that I thought that like you know like I bought all the knee-punny
Gucci games at one point like cuz those have diminishing returns hard
Yeah, you go further in the series like cuz you know this guy a one everyone loved it
I had played a bunch of it
I thought it was pretty cool
But then like just because of like the idea of the company that it was like this this small
Publisher of like really interesting tactics games that no one was talking about you know and that were often hard to come by and I bought like you
know
Like lapissel tactics and fucking
Lapissel tactics was such a snorkel. Yeah, I gave up on that within like the first couple of hours
I bought lapissel. I bought fucking phantom brave
I bought Makaya for real and I bought this guy
And like I had all those games for a long time and like I played the first like a couple hours of lapissel as a kid
And like I just didn't understand mechanics
So like this is something I did a lot when I was younger
I would buy games and then play them and not really get them and that'd be like well
I'll probably get around to it in the future and I just hold on to these games forever
And then finally like ten years later
I put in lapissel and tried to play it and I realized it's just boring, you know
So like I feel like my hype back then was like all of these games are gonna be great one day
And then eventually I realized that I was just deluding myself and I don't know where I got this hype from you know
I hate the waiting sitting around waiting checking every preview that comes out waiting for it to come out
I ended that personally in 2008 with brawl because I was waiting for that so intensely and the delays
Killed my soul off in half so much and I played it. I'm like, oh, it's it's just like melee
You you sit down and have a good time for for infinity. It's not something
Yeah, I've never had like like a lot of I've never waited for a thing to come out like I I've I
Want Dark Souls 3 to come out really soon and it is and I'm happy that it's coming out
But I haven't been waiting for it. You know, I haven't been looking trailers
I don't really care to look here's here's what like information for man. That was for me
I just want to buy it when it comes out. Here's what more than years
I spent crawling around on spore forums just like fucking hyping myself up
Oh, no more than I don't get about waste of my god cycle is like most of these games are
Are going to be like a week of your life not anything past that like yeah
All the time you've already put in right people spend like years hyping themselves for a game
And then you beat it in like, you know 20 hours and it's like why did you like was that really worth that level of hype?
Like, you know, and then people get let down and I watched like my brother victor
He always lets himself get into the hype cycle because like he'll you know, he'll he only plays games once usually
Like it's very rare only like the souls games and like, you know a few other like games that he really truly loves
Well, he played more than once most games. He'll just get it and forget it
But he'll let himself
Like, you know constantly watch trailers and watch all the nintendo directs and get like all excited for games
And then like he spent like two and a half years being hyped for zeno blade chronicles x
And it came out and it was complete like, you know, and the thing is he'll you'll trick yourself
Like he spent the first like 35 hours like trying to convince himself that it was great
And then in the end just realized it was a huge disappointment. You know, I just I just remember the best example of all time
Final fantasy 13
Like i'm the biggest final fantasy fan in the entire universe and I too spent
You know 60 hours trying to like that game either writing was on the wall before 13 came out
So I didn't allow myself to get hyped for that one because dude. I loved 11. I loved 12 was a good game
But like
Now 12 was a good game but 11 was like an mmo and then there was advent children
Before that an advent children was like the thing that hurt me more than anything else ever to the point where
For years after advent children came out
I would like lie to myself and I still wouldn't want to admit how much I hated it
But then like every time I saw it subsequently
I I had to admit a little bit that's the thing
I I followed the chronicles of the compilation of final fantasy 7 shit so tightly like every scrap of information
Was like gold to me was like pure orgasm through my whole body
And like only this year have I finally realized I was I was just being fucking duped a whole fucking time
And it was so like and it was so like
Real and like such a juicy betrayal to me because it was because back in those days
Like I put my heart and soul into that series. It was like I was like
Like 14 or 13 when advent children came out or something. Yeah 15 16 hours
Fucking the baby, you know, like it was like before I had access to the internet or anything
So to me final fantasy 7 was just my thing and it was this beautiful thing from my childhood and no one else could ever
You know tarnish it and and oh my god. They're they're making a sequel to my game
And then I and then it's not just a ever made like a
Philosophical thing like on principle. I will heighten myself down
The more you learn about the context of the way things come out the more, you know
Logically it is most likely not going to be like there's nothing that can logically make you guaranteed
That something is going to be great. I don't know if that's true game series any game developer
Any place that a game can come from that will guarantee it being good
Yeah to me and did you I remember you saying that you're like that with anime your last bastion was
Tell you had a one last bastion of like this is definitely going to be good, but it got broken recently. What was it?
No, I don't even like most keo any shows. I don't even like half of their shows
Um, but there was probably something that was oh, yeah shinichiro watanabe because he what do you mean?
Because he made fucking zankyo no terror and it was complete garbage. Oh, that's right. That's right
Like it was he was like the one director who had only done three shows and they were all amazing
And like everything he'd worked on otherwise was like little artsy stuff and like, you know
It was like he could he couldn't possibly do wrong
And then zankyo no terror came out and like the first three episodes or first two episodes are like amazing
And then they're it just spirals down and it's a piece of shit
The only thing that I can rely on to be good is when I know that the people in charge of creating it
Have the same tastes and roughly the same vision as myself
Which is why I do get hyped for some analysis shows because I for one thing
There's almost no waiting it comes out and I get hyped in three seconds to watch it and I know where they're coming
But you know the scary thing is that over a long period of time how the people behind the work change like
Like with with square enix and like how final fantasy has evolved and morph like it's the same series
But it is not what it once was
I think the internet has helped us a lot because now we can look into that shit. That's true. That's very no
I think I think with
I think every year we get closer and closer to people are paying attention to developers like specifically the people
We're like, you know with dark souls again
No one knew who hitataka miyazaki was until dark souls two sucked
No one no one knew who he was when dark souls one was great
People knew who he was when dark souls two sucked and we went for an explanation and the explanation was it wasn't the same director
You know that was when people went oh
Like that matters, you know like hitataka miyazaki's clearly the guy who's important here, you know
And then it became like well bloodborne's got his name on it. So maybe that'll be worth it
Oh dark souls three has his name on it. Maybe that'll be worth it
You know, but like I think every year we get we get more and more in the internet age
Like we're paying attention to that shit where um, you know, uh, I think that's good. It's true
It's it's a it's a hopeful sentiment and I I think yeah, but even then
I would be for the next the next thing that toby fox makes right sure
Absolutely
I think the more people are involved the more you need to look into it because like with
What davoo said about shinichiro watanabe like I just assumed everything he made would be good
But then like, you know
The writing staff and the people behind zankyo no terror were not the same people who wrote his other shows
You know, we're like he used a lot of the same staff on cowboy bebop and on uh and on you know
Samurai shampoo and it's like the writers for this show
Were the problem like the directing was not the problem with zankyo no terror
He did his job
It's just that the show had a terrible script and like on you know, he was a failure for not correctly assigning
I mean you could say so but like I think because it was his concept of a show and I get why he made it and like
What he was going for it's just that the writing did not deliver on the idea
And I think there was probably a point where
They maybe recognized that or maybe they didn't maybe they just thought it was you know
Maybe they thought the message was more important than that
Or they just went ahead with what they had because I don't you love that when people decide that the message of your show
Is more important than the entertainment value. Love that. Well, I I just think that like
I think with that particular show it was partly just they wanted to give him work because like
You know like Masao Mariama had been saying that he'd been trying to get a show with Shinichiro Watanabe for years
But it's just that it's too expensive to work with him because he's he's a really ambitious director
And he's going to make stuff look good. And so like I think you know
Mariama is the one who runs mappa and mappa was a fairly new studio
They hadn't really done a lot of work and they wanted to do something with Shinichiro Watanabe
And I think that was that's a nice goal. I think that was more important to them than making a well written show
I think they just wanted to make a show with Watanabe and that's why they succeeded
The thing with tobi fox because like at first I was like, oh, yeah the next tobi fox game
I'm probably gonna like that right because not only did I love undertale, but I loved
But like the ways in which I really liked it felt like tobi was doing things the way I would do them
Like I've made games
A couple years ago
What you only like things that are the way that you would do them well in the sense that he said trash in the sense that like
It makes me think he comes from a similar place. Obviously. He's better
But he comes from a similar place with similar tastes as me
It's not someone who made something that they like that I think is amazing for different reasons, you know
And well, I think that I think that what's good about undertale
I think or or I think I'm kind of agree with you
But for different reasons like I think that the ways in which undertale is good
Suggest a development philosophy that I can write. Yeah
Yeah, I think that you can tell that the way he went at it was to think of concepts first and then flesh to think of
Original concepts first and then flesh them out to a mechanic explain that something
I would like to see more like using an opposite like if you
Love sonichu
It's not because you think christian has similar intentions to you
Like you love sonichu for reasons that have nothing to do with why why christian like
I love sonichu for the emotional arc
So of the author right that you can glimpse the things you like about sonichu are not what christian intended
You to like about it. Nope. And therefore you could never look forward to his next work in that way
Whereas yeah, what's the shirt on my new level I can look at almost any detail and think
I think toby put that there and did that that way for this that and this reason
Don't know how accurate I am though because toby his his persona is so
Um timid he like acts like oh, I don't I didn't know
I was just trying to make a game with stuff that I like and everyone loves it. That's nice
I think he's probably like yeah, I'm a genius. I know exactly
I don't know what you're getting that. I mean, I'm sure there's some level of of confidence
I'm sure he's like that only because that's what I would be like
I too would project a facade of like not thinking I was the shit
But then secretly think he literally said all these people giving um 10 out of 10s
I got I you know some people give him an eight give undertale an eight like I expected
But then some people give it a 10 and I'm like you like it that much
Wow, we well frankly toby has absolutely no business trying to judge his game
In the in the world of all games out there and trying to decide where it belongs
Absolutely, yeah, I think it's fine. I'm just saying that it makes it a little bit harder like
Is he just accidentally a genius because I don't know what I really need to do
Is play other stuff that he's made play his earthbound mods and really get where he's coming from
On the subject of like there's no guarantee
That that like your hype will be justified like you can never know for sure if like the next output by someone's gonna be good
Um, I'm not gonna like the next toby game if it's like an undertale rehatch
I was gonna say yeah, I don't think it will be because what I think was good about undertale was the ways it experimented
So it's gonna be totally I'm gonna be looking I'm gonna be looking for like the new ideas that toby has right
And those things are gonna be new and therefore they're gonna be a risk
So there's only a chance that it'll be a really great game if he takes risks
But those risks are gonna come with the possibility that maybe they won't work out as well as they did an undertale
So there's there's really no guarantee. That's what hype is all about. I think it's it's more of a guarantee
than like other like just thinking of like it's it's better to think of like, you know, it's not I know but like
It it's better to it's more trying to think of the words
Well, you shouldn't you shouldn't get hype for a company's game. Yes, you get hype for the individuals who are making sure
I want to address like ironically the like the fact that to the fact that I expect toby to take a risk
Right in in being creative in in his next game like like taking that risk is a
Better is closer to guaranteeing that something will be good
Then not taking any risks because that guarantees that it'll be bad to address like devu's point about toby's like attitude
I think, you know
You might think that the things he did were genius
And like you might share the same ethos as him like I'm sure he put all those things in his game on purpose
And that they all serve the purpose he wanted them to but that doesn't necessarily mean that he thinks that that is genius
Like maybe he thinks that all those points he was making are like pretty clever
But like, you know that he doesn't think that it's worth a 10 out of 10
We're like, you know, and it comes down to personal values
Like devu you clearly value the things he did so much that you think it's a 10 out of 10 game
I don't you know, like I appreciate all of it and I think I understand all of it
But my values don't mean oh, that's automatically a 10, you know
And I think his surprise is that so many people value that and I'm surprised too
Like I would never have thought looking at undertale that it would get these
The sheer level of like game of the years that it got, you know, like yeah, like uh, well, you share nobody's because I definitely think
There's plenty of things that aren't great about it in one interview
He said, you know, I came up with the whole mercy system
And you know, it's kind of it's not that great because it's basically just a bunch of trial and error
But I wrote some decent dialogue to make it good and I read that I'm like, yeah
I agree the the mercy system for most regular enemies is not like that in in
In thralling all the time, but it just goes back to I don't think that something needs to be
Objectively perfect to be a 10 out of 10
Yeah, wait
You have to look at the way that he used it because like what my favorite example
I think of that in the whole game is the way that you have to that you mercy
The tsundere plane which involves like you have to come close to it and like brush against it
Which relates to its personality and is like the most genius thing I've ever seen
That's the thing like all of that is genius
But it's not necessarily something that you expect people to value where like sure like in a games market where you know
Because if you look at like
Game spots game of the year list like that's the one where I what I would have expected where they put undertale at like number 16
You know and like number one is the witcher 3 which is this huge
Oh, it's like everything that games journalism seems to value in a game is what the witcher 3 represents
You know what it reminds me of the way that like the oscars judge like best editor
It's not like who made like the highest quality game. It's who made like the most game
Who put it like the most that just tends to be what most people value is people tend to value like
What's the biggest bestest most insane thing that had to happen?
You know like the the one that's the closest to the gold standard and like you would never expect that a fucking
A game that looks like it was on the goddamn
NES would be the you know would be anyone's game of the year pick from like a professional journalist
You know you can imagine I think the point I was trying to make earlier. Yeah, I get
the the point was um
You shouldn't ever think that a person
Being on a team or like a company making a game would guarantee
Even if they have a good track record
You should never think that it guarantees it to be good, but it can it's okay to like
Feel a little better about all this discussion and no one has mentioned metal gear solid 5 which burned all of you
I was trying not to mention it and not to think about it. So thank you so much. I totally forgot about that. Yeah
Oh, Jesus christ. I didn't even remember that. Yeah, it's same director who made all the other games
Now there was a lot of drama around it when it came out which kind of maybe sort of absolves him a little bit
We won't know exactly whether
Kojima himself is responsible until we see his next game and if it's really good then
I am well you actually
You can look closer and you can see patterns here because he didn't write the games himself
Alone until metal gear solid 4
Everything 1 2 and 3 were written by some other guy who's much much better at writing
And that's why like the writing in those games is worlds better. So it does
It was nano machines kind of thing. Yeah, it's clearly a george lucas thing
He he got more control and as a result thing
But like the biggest problems in five the biggest ones are that the game just isn't finished
And I think those come down to konami issues with them not giving him the budget to finish the game
It's deciding. You know what? We've spent enough money put it out the door. It's playable. That's it
We don't we don't completely know and I think it's I think the danger with that game was that there were four
Like I mean there were there were three amazing metal gear solid games and one pretty great one
And then you know, you have no reason to expect it's not going to be great
You have no there's no one that you notice has changed because the only name anyone knows is hideo kojima
He plashes it all over everything. So everyone sees him as the guy the beginning of every mission guys
Guess who made the game
But like is he what a fucking guy was he the only one responsible for all these games being great?
Or is it clear that he was not one of the guys or that there's more going on that we don't know and like yeah
Even with the name recognition like
Again, or whatever you shouldn't get you shouldn't just immediately be like. Oh my god. It's a kojima game
It's gonna be amazing. It's well a lot of people work on those, you know
I think we also have to go ahead whatever
No, no you go. Oh well going back to hype. I think that uh
I think that hype affected how the game was developed and designed
negatively in a way because
It reeks of that
Philosophy of everything needs to be open world and appeal to everyone in the world and right that kind of thing and it's just
That's just the game hype cycle and it's how all games are made now
This is an all new thing to talk about is how hype will affect the development of the thing
Which I think is has way more of a direct effect than how it affects my experience
Okay, yeah, maybe for someone like you who says that it doesn't really affect him
That's totally true because like look at look it's god
It pisses me off so much that like the audience has now become part of the process of making the game
It's like our reaction to these trailers like like street fighter 5 right too much ass on on cammy and uh on mika
We got to get rid of that shit and like the the guys didn't intend that from the start or they would have made it that way
They change things to and it's I don't know if that's you can like that or just like that
That's just the audience it's the audience's response right, but I do think that like hype
Creates the danger of every installment has to be better than the last and it makes people
Like if you make something successful, then you always feel like you have to one up yourself and like
It it kind of disgusts me because everyone
Talks this way and I mean everyone even people who hate hype who say this and that like if you make a new game
And it's not as good as your old game people are going to say so constantly
All anyone's gonna like uh bastion versus transistor right like bastion came out and it was super hyped because like
It was a you know game that nobody expected
But it was really great and it had this great narration and everything and then transistor came out and all anyone talked about
Was how it compares to bastion. Oh, it's right. It's it's kind of the same
But it's not it's not quite as good the narrative isn't quite as interesting
Listen that and it's like dude. It's a different game like forget about fucking bastion talk about fucking transistor
You know like totally different art style different story different characters
It's not a sequel in any way
But like you know, that's what the hype cycle does to people is they always expect the next one to be better
And to be this huge evolution. Yeah
And what if it's just good, you know, like that's like the issue with something good
Yeah, people aren't judging continuing works by if they're good or not because they kind of can't until the game comes out
Uh, they're judging it by how how much it is is what they were hoping for in this series
Well, I mean if you're reviewing a game, right you're reviewing a game
Uh, to hopefully to someone who hasn't played it right the reader is someone who is perspective and like considering playing the game
What is there to talk about like like hopefully I mean there's you got to talk about something
They are familiar with and like relevantly that's going to be previous games by the same
Right, but I think like I mean you got to compare it to something and that's like a pretty good starting point
Saying it's one thing to say. Oh, it's kind of like bastion, but then to be like
Oh, it's you know, it's like bastion, but it's not quite as good and it's like this and that and
I just feel like it's divorcing it from being its own game
And and I'm making it so the developer can never make anything that's not better than bastion, you know
It's the same. It's we have a problem. I like the the w
Go on Gabe go on
This is why I like the the w2 wtf series
By total biscuit because when he talks about a game he does like at first impressions like a 30 minute video of and he just talks about
What what he likes and how he feels that it you know, how good it is and it's just it's it's a nice introduction to
like your own
Research into that game because he talked about transistor and he didn't mention bastion
And he talked about how cool all the things were and I was like, yeah, right, you know
I I I didn't think it was my kind of game, but
That's the sort of review that I prefer and I don't follow people that talk about things like
Like if if somebody's going to compare two games from the same developer
They better be making a video about the developer
In general instead of just reviewing the game that just came out
Well, there's times when it's appropriate and times when it's inappropriate. Yeah, devu was starting to bring up hiruki and maishi
And I'm guessing you were going to talk about kill a kill versus guru in the gond
Uh, yeah, of course
Sure, like, you know guru in the gond came out and everyone thought it was the best anime ever
And then when kill a kill came out all anyone talked about was how it compares to guru in the gond
And you can't bring it for years. You could not bring up kill a kill
Well, I guess it's only been out for it's been like two years two and a half years
But like you could not mention it without someone saying guru in the gond was better
And it's like it's who the fuck cares which it which it is which it is
But I would say it is narrowly better
But like I don't think it I don't think that matters like it doesn't it does not is no relevance to kill a kill
What guru in the gond was other than the fact that it was made by the same people
Do not agree that guru in the gond is necessarily better than kill a kill
I think that you're clearly mistaken, but go ahead and make your case
I think that you're a big giant faggot
Well, what on what basis on what basis okay, I uh guru in the gond is better. I don't know
I just like the uh dark souls tune. That's true
Well, the fact that we're even arguing about this is missing the point the point is that it doesn't matter which one's better because they're completely different shows
But I want to argue but it's kind of interesting but it's kind of interesting to talk about which one's better
But like I think I just think that when that becomes all the conversation is then it's like why can't
Emiishi just make another show and we judge it on its own merits and not worry about whether it is good
I never bring up because it's an interesting question. It's an interesting question
Which of these two big budget releases by the same producers is it is an interesting question?
But it should not do it should not dominate all discussion of kill a kill
Well, here's my only problem with this discussion is that I think it's vastly mistaken to consider either of them big budget
Or from the same producer
Listen, I think I do like the gond ligand kill a kill discussion more if it always involved
Panty and stalking as well because that really completes the picture for me
Right because that because I'm much more interested in Emiishi than the guy who wrote gond ligand kill a kill
I really resonate with his
Animation style. It feels like the thing that I want animation to be
Since I was like born and saw animation
Emiishi does the kind of animation that I want to exist
It's a similar kind of resonance to toby fox where I feel like he comes from a similar place
As me and that's why I mean if he comes out with another show that's going to be animated with him in charge or him directing
I will be hyped for it
Though not necessarily for whatever the narrative is and I'm almost certain I will enjoy it as a visual experience because I feel like I
Understand where he's coming from
Thank you for the creepy dramatic
Downward I don't know why that was just that was a very it was it was your your way of speaking was hypnotic
It was really quite hypnotic
What do you what do you guys think are we are we hitting the limits of what we can say about hype and the hype?
Well, we could talk about you think we could go forever
No, we could talk I mean at this point we are talking about arguing over shows
So, yeah, I don't know whether we have much to say
Well, I think I think it all involves hype because I think that the I think you know again
It's I think the problem with it is that people always want everything to constantly be amazing
Everyone and people expect everything to constantly be amazing
And I think that's the problem we're running into is that people aren't just like letting things cut like I think you should go in
And just like let things come to you and then make a decision, right?
Like sure you can know things about it beforehand and maybe set up like, you know
If Kyoto animations making a show I'm going to expect the characters to look a certain way
I'm going to expect the animation to look a certain way because I know that's what they do
But like that doesn't mean it's going to be good or bad or whatever
Like I'm just going to wait until it's there and then I'll look at it and I'll say
That was good or that was bad. Like I'm not going into Kill La Kill thinking this better be better than girl in the
Gone this better be as good as girl in the gone
Like, you know, then you just set up this weird expectation that has nothing to do with the intentions of the show
That I highly doubt anyone involved in Kill La Kill went into it saying we got a top girl in the gone
Hang on. I don't I don't I don't agree because I think it is fair to say I want this to be better than your past work
It's not saying this should be like your past work in in all these ways only done better
It should just be something that's it's I think it's reasonable
I don't think it's unfair
But I think it I think that it it's not like I think you're going in with your intentionality
Not necessarily matching what the intentions of the series are and that can be fine in the long run
But I feel like you should go in like like because hype is all about the beginning. It's not about what you feel in the long run
It's about what you feel going into it
And I think when you go into a show like Kill La Kill thinking this better be as good as girl in the gone
Or else I'm going to be disappointed then you're setting yourself up for disappointment
Whereas if you watch kill and you just enjoy it and then you go well
I didn't like it as much as girl in the gone
But it was a good time then like you know like that should be something you think about after the fact
That should be like the I agree that it's reductive
I agree that it's reductive and kind of nonsensical to go in with the expectation that something will be better than something because like
How can anything be better? How can anything be definitively better than something like okay?
I mean, this is just my opinion
But something like girl in the gun which was basically perfect at what it did like right any like
If something could be better than it in a certain way like if like something could be better at making you cry
Then girl in the gun because girl in the gun didn't do that. But like you have no soul
But but like um, maybe uh, I don't know
You told me you teared up when comedy didn't show up in the opening of the next episode. You know what you're right
You're right. It actually did make me cry. But other than I mean, it reaches its own top
Right doesn't need to be done better. And you know, yeah, or even just as well
Yeah, when comedy didn't when comedy didn't show up in the opening video. I think that like when he was gone
Like, you know, I'm a big proponent of like I think that all things I think all art can be compared
And I think you can select scores based on like I can look at girl in the gun and I can say that's a 10
And I can look at kill a kill and say that's a 9.75. That's what I would score both of them on my current scale
You know and like I can look at them and I can say that but like that to me should be after the fact
It should not be going in thinking this better be as good as girl in the gun
You know, it should be a consideration you make later like when you're I think I think
You should start judging art after you've seen the art, you know
Not like beforehand with the hype and like oh, this is going to be amazing or this is going to be terrible
This is going to be the best thing ever and then like you watch it and then you you select
It's like you're you're deciding how the game or the the anime or whatever compares to your hype
Instead of just looking at it and then making a decision about it. That's why hype is a destructive force and needs to go
I mean, I think that I mean, I believe in a holistic grading system
Like yeah, I believe that you can more or less assign a score and a value to something
But I don't think there's any good comes out of going in with like a rigid scoring system
Like oh so many points for this category so many points for that
It's all about just like
Once you've watched it and you're done and you're there and the aftermath thinking about it like how did you feel watching it?
What feeling did it leave you with?
Afterwards I and you know but on the one hand
I think that hype does affect that because if you went in with really high expectations and it didn't meet them
Then it could leave you with that sour feeling. Yeah, I score things based on the amount by the level of enjoyment that I have
Anything that I give a 10 is something that like I'm stewing over it
Well after the fact and like this it's just so good like I can yeah, but a lot of people's enjoyment is affected by
Randomly like see a kill lock kill picture and be like oh, yeah, and then all of a sudden I like spend an hour
Check off immediately and and just looking at fan art and just dwelling on checking in it and how good it is
Just constantly checking your and that's the kind of thing I gave a 10
And I recently made a list of all the games I have played that I can remember and I gave them scores if I could
and
You know undertale ended up being the only one at this moment that I gave a 10 to I gave dark souls a 9.9
Uh and but the fact that distinction though, what an asshole
The fact that I gave throw it a fucking bone
The fact that I gave undertale a 10 the fact that it's the highest scored one
Isn't nearly as interesting
As the fact that I gave so many 9s and the fact that there could be so many different games that could be a 9 to me
So many different ways of video game
Yeah, I think there's a 10 is vastly more interesting than what
That I had like is a 10 out of 10 because I hate nuance
Yeah, I feel like I feel like a lot of ten or zero. That's it. I feel like for a lot of viewers of stuff
There's like a like a zero some game. It's like everything's either a fucking 10
A six or four, you know, like those are the only or not even a six. I should say a seven
Everything's a 10 seven or four, right? It's all I've gone on record is saying that's how I view most things
Right, it's like either a 10. It's either the best thing ever or it's mediocre or it's shit
And like and and those are the three scores people would use to denote those because nobody cares about the other part of their
Fucking 10 scale, you know
But like I I I'm with devu that I like the nuance of like, you know
Not everything has to try to be a 10 a nine is also really interesting, you know
Hang on. What what is this? What is this you keep bringing up about how a show shouldn't try to be great?
No, I'm not saying it shouldn't try to be great. I'm saying I think anything above a seven is great
I think if you make a show that's an eight out of ten that gives me tons of stuff
And I think like, you know, if even if kill a kill is like
Even if you thought kill a kill was an eight and you thought guru on the gun was a 10
That's still incredibly impressive that it's an eight because to be an eight
It has to be better than 80 percent of everything else out there, you know
Like it's still something that has so much value
And it's in the parts of it that it has and I think that value is so much more interesting than why it's not a 10
You know, like like the things when you're like when you're like, oh guru on the gun is a 10
Because this is in this and kill a kill is not quite as good and it's like, yeah, that's fine and all but like
Look at all the stuff that is in kill a kill. That's all all great
And I think like it's so reductive to be like well, it's not as good as guru on the gun
So I don't care, you know, like I'm I'm with you on the idea that you should
I'm with you on the idea that you should appreciate what is good in kill a kill and just think about what is there in kill a kill to appreciate
I think that's cool. However, if guru on the gun like fucking
Emotionally like did something crazy to you and left you with an impression that lasted for years and years as it did me
And kill a kill didn't do that as is the case for me. Then I think it's worth asking. Okay. Well, why did that happen for?
Yeah, I mean, of course, that's one question you ask. I think that's worth asking
But I think it's I think that when we talk
The answer may simply be because you're older and you already felt that with guru on the gun a million years ago
There is that there is that I don't know. I don't think it
I don't think kill a kill that would have done quite the same thing
Well, I don't think it has the same intentions in the first place
So I don't think it would have done the same thing for you but like
But you know, I just think but that kind of I think the danger again
I think the danger with that again
I think it's cool to do that after the fact
After watching girl in the gun after watching kill a kill deciding how you feel and then being like
Kind of interesting that I didn't like that one as much as that one
But again, I think the problem because this is about hype was what this podcast is about is going in
thinking
This better be as good as girl in the gun or constantly comparing it or thinking about why it's not as good or why it's better
You know a bad place to be and on that note. I feel like we've
Said our piece. Yeah, let's wrap it up. Sorry. Anybody failing so much. I don't know
I got so busy. Hey, don't worry about it. Davoo. Stop me. Let me just end
Let me just end on the note that I want to say that we've talked a lot about people over hyping things in their mind
I think that my problem is the opposite. I really think that my
Hype problem is that I underhype everything and I'm skeptical of everything and I really believe that everything will suck
Until I see it and improve and otherwise and on the one hand
This does lead to me being more often pleasantly surprised when I do see something and it's not as bad as I think and it's actually pretty good
I'm like, oh, it's pretty good
But it also causes me not to seek out media and I don't watch as many movies or listen to as many music or play as many games
I probably should and probably would enjoy if I know what actually I just remember sometimes hype is good
I just remember another thing about hype that can be good
um
Because best guy ever here
Names his channel best guy ever
And all of his videos best anime ever best game ever
And I think that I think your channel would immediately be the worst channel on youtube
If you ever failed to live up to the hype of your video titles
It's it's hyperbole. Give me a break. Look. Okay. The thing is
Because I hate that I I usually hate that persona. I hate when people like say i'm the best ever
I think it's unless you don't even do that because the second you don't live up to it. It's well
It's in your name. It's inherent you've named yourself best guy ever and the second you don't live up to it
It's gonna look like a farce and you know
I I took that that girl in the gone video the first one part one
Yeah, I posted it up and uh, you know my friend ghost lightning who also like me and him
We used to always talk about how much we hated like that kind of persona and like I post on twitter
Like the best guy ever just made the best video ever, you know, he started watching it
And he was like I thought it was gonna be shit because of the the the title and everything and the way you started
But then of course it's a bait and switch it turns out to be like awesome
You know when you watch it like you deliberately made it start off shitty and then it becomes amazing, you know
Right, which was and if you look in my I don't know that's in the other video too at the end
Like I took I took painstaking ever to take as faggy a picture of myself as was possible
Right to show what an asshole I really am and then I hope people get that
But like what I what I love about it though is that the hype what it's done for you as a creator is you have to
Live up to best guy ever every time you cannot make a video that doesn't live up to your title
I mean you can make some I suppose I'm open to more criticism for that reason. I suppose that's true
I don't know about that. I mean, I think that what saves guys best guy ever persona is that there's a little bit of tongue in cheekness there
It's like kind of a good
It's like kind of a healthy mix of like serious hype like I am the best person
Yeah, but I'm also kind of I think you can figure that out in the videos when he sort of like reveals that he's a nerd
You know, but like and yeah, he doesn't play up the persona nearly as much as a lot of other people would
But I do think that if you name yourself best guy ever and I watch one of your videos
And I'm not interested immediately then it's going to be a bad time
But if some of the comedy of the video comes from him sort of poking fun at himself
And sort of like pulling the rug out from under his own
Okay, if you clicked on his video though
If you clicked on a best guy ever video and you didn't know who he was and you saw the name best guy ever and you clicked on it
And it was not an amazing video
Would you not then be deeply mad that he named himself? I'd probably be a little no
Not not if the comedy of the video came at the expense of the supposed best I guess I can agree
But like I think that
I that would make it not a bad video
Like I think that I think that you're already like if the fact that that's happening already makes it
A good video
I'm saying if the video was not good if it didn't have that and the guy was called best guy ever
Would you not then be that much more mad like if someone made it if someone made a video and they're called best guy ever
And they started out the video like I'm amazing
I'm the coolest and then their analysis was completely like not interesting
Would you not be that much more mad that he called himself that I'm really interested in and I really want to talk about this
It's the how a creator can manage the hype levels of their stuff and that's very interesting to me
I know we were trying to end this podcast
But that is its own interesting topic that I like to do in my own videos when I did my
Willa Cooster tycoon one versus three video was this huge production and I'm like
I don't want people to get hyped up to think I'm always going to be this big
So right afterwards I did a two minute video about trampolines
And later on I was doing this I did this 20 minute critique of big hero six
I did this 35 minute break down
You did these things not because you super
Wanted to talk about these topics immediately
But as a as an effect to bring down the expectations of the audience. Yeah, and I was making I made a well
That's part of it. Like I made a 20 minute video
I made a 35 minute video. So then I made a seven minute video
And so like my idea is to like to kind of dress people down from their high
Like sometimes that's a pretty good idea if I'm really into like really intricate really deep music
And I'm on this big kick. I'll like listen to some really stupid mucor stuff that like lowers my class
Brings me back. I I kind of do this
Mucor is not low class
I I do the same thing as devu where I try to manage expectations a lot and like especially when I first started doing anime videos
Like I tried to get out as many videos as possible so that people would get like
Like I didn't want people to think that I'm only into this type of show or that like if I only talked about sci-fi shows
I didn't want people to think I was a sci-fi channel
I didn't want people to think I was like, you know only gonna make big videos or small videos
So I tried to mix it up and have like every video
I did be something different from the last and make it like, you know
And now I'm at a point where I can do anything
I could just make nothing but big videos
But people would know that I could change it, you know, like people wouldn't expect it to all be that
Whereas I think like I think mr. Plinkett videos for instance because he set the bar
Said they were always going to be big and I think that's why there haven't been anymore because like always
Beg them for Plinkett videos. That's what people really want a couple of smaller ones
But no one like, you know, everyone complained about yeah because they were small
And so like he could never make Plinkett a video series
I could do everything because so many of them were big so early
But even with stuff like Plinkett like managing expectations
Happens in the script where like he'd used that voice
Specifically because it was boring to listen to someone talk about that kind of shit and it's just too nerdy
So he wanted to make it something that you would expect like you go in and you're like
What the hell is this, you know, and then it's like then you pay more attention to the points
Which is why you know like film crit hulk does his all caps thing
Which I don't think is as effective
But like I get that he's doing it so that people think it's stupid and then they read it and they don't think it's pretentious
You know, I don't think it works when I do it. I make a video about undertale
I'm going to tell everyone to rip it off and then everyone took it literally and then mr. Beetsong like
Is the expert of this where he always like he'll he'll he'll like the biggest difference between like the truth is
I'm engaging in calculated sophistry for the sake of
The difference between Beetsong and and errant signal, for instance
Is errant signal will pull out some huge word out of his ass and just run with it
And you're just like what the fuck are you talking about where Beetsong will be like
I'm about to make up a really stupid word and I'm a complete idiot
Here it is. If you're interested then keep watching, you know, like he downplays
What he's doing so that you don't think
While this pretentious fuck like you do when you watch errant signal videos, you know
If I were in toby fox's position because I I wish I have even
Like named him on twitter with the at symbol to like hope he reads this because this is my advice to him
Because he has probably enough money to live for a couple of years without publishing anything for sale
Make a bunch of really short
Little games about random things that are off the top of your head
That way people who are fans of you can think of you not as the undertale god, but as
This guy who comes out with shit
You know, I don't think there's any way of avoiding him being undertale man for the duration
I like that idea to do. I think that's a good advice
It was greatly diminish it would give him this fan base of people who follow his stuff
Not when will be the second coming of toby, right?
Because that way when it's time like say in three years to make his next big game
It'll cost especially if it does take three years because by then people will will have like, you know
Any time I think the I think people build up in their heads when something doesn't come out for a long time
It automatically means that all the time was dedicated to it, you know, like for instance, uh, the band agilosh
Agilosh only puts out an album every four years and like their first four albums were all like incredible
So it always felt like man, they really ruminate on this stuff for four fucking years
And then they put out their fifth album and it was kind of like mediocre
And it was like, you know, the the first impression you get is did they really spend four years on this?
But then you think about it and it's probably more like they were just doing normal shit for three years and then decided
They wanted to do like I don't think that they're professional musicians
Like I don't think they have enough fans that or put out enough content that they get paid just for that
It's probably a side job. They probably have normal fucking jobs, you know
So like yeah
So I can't help but imagine that it's really more like every four years they go
Hey, what if we put out another album? That would be fun, you know, but like to the fans
It's like, oh my god four years of waiting has finally paid off
You know, this this has to live up to those four years of expectations and you know, and then you get middle year solid five and
Yeah, what a what a disaster which was like what like eight years seven years something like
Well, well, wait years hands are on came out in that time too. So that's you know, there was something there
Yeah, red line. Well red line was awesome and red line wasn't even was red was were people super hyped
No, no one knew and no one watched it once it came out. It was totally later on like it was completely
Did not sell no one cared about it and madhouse went bankrupt and
Okay, but but I guess at least it's become kind of a cult hit now, right?
I guess you can call it but I still don't think it's as big as it should be
It's actually it's on youtube now for free. Anyone can watch it. Yeah, like uh fucking. Oh, shit
Maybe I should go buy it on dvd. Yeah, dude the dvds lately. I've been lately
I've been really feeling the urge to buy things that I like I went back and I bought I bought a
Highlyx that claymation game because it was only three dollars and I thought he deserved three dollars
I went and bought lisa for a friend because I really wanted to spend more than the three dollars
I spent have you come into some great wealth that is prompted such uh such kindness
Medline blue rays were seven dollars within like a year
Like they immediately were on sale like one dollar for each year that it was there
You know, let's look talk about talk about not having hype when I saw a red line
I didn't know what the fuck was gonna happen. It was like the best movie I've ever seen. It was so fucking good
I'm so glad that we've all hyped the shit out of red line
Everyone listening should go watch it with totally high expectations
Expect it to be the greatest movie ever
Which incidentally if you go one of those expectations, you will be let down because the plot is not that interesting
It's just a really cool movie
It's it's but that that comes right back to the problem with like managing hype
We're like it's so hard to talk about red line because your instinct to talk about it is
It's so mind-blowing that you're like this is the greatest thing ever
But then you actually watch it without hyping it. I don't think it's anyone's favorite movie
But it's something that I think everyone should see and I think that's a problem
When you say something like everyone should see this movie then they're like, oh, it must be the best ever
And it's like well, it doesn't like the bestness is not what makes it worthwhile
It's the intrigue of seeing that this is real that like this is the thing that happened
You know, it's fascinated on like a cultural level that it exists that was produced
That's too to go to go back to the thing about how I underhyped things in my head
And how
A having hype is bad and it makes me like things less and going back to undertale too
Let me draw all these threads and please wrap it up this time to go. I gotta and tell the story if I played the demo
I loved the demo. I was like, I'm really excited for this game
But due to my proclivities in my head. I'm like, okay, that demo was really good. He probably used all his good ideas for the demo
The rest. Yeah, the rest of the game will probably not be as consistently good
So I actually kind of dehyped myself for the rest of the game didn't expect to like as much
Then went in
Found that the game continued to get better and better and all had all these other great ideas in it
And ended up being like, hmm, you know what? It actually was pretty consistent in quality
It didn't it didn't blow me away. It wasn't better than the demo
But it was all I'd say all of it was consistently as good as the demo
So my expectations and the reality ended up it ended up being like a very
Fortuitous like they came into alignment in a way that it all really fucking worked out just just beachy for me
So that was a very rare case. That's the thing. That's didn't end up
But it was because
But it was because I was managing my expectations in that way because of my skepticism
The hype didn't end up hurting. Well, that's good. Okay
Good anecdotes. Everyone. Good talk. We're done. Oh
I'm glad. Yes. Thanks jester for that contribution. Uh, we're uh, thanks for watching guys
We'll be back next week. Leave your comments in the thing below if you got any more suggestions for topics you want us to cover
Feel free to leave them. Thanks for joining us everybody. Everyone say goodbye