I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Okay, hello, welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's Gibb's
not here today, I don't know what she's doing. Some nonsense I guess.
God rest.
Got ripped, but we've got Tectonic Improv, and Gamer's Tavern, aka Chrono, here in the
studio, here live in the studio, live studio audience.
Woo!
Yeah, alright!
I'm back!
Woo!
Yeah.
Yeah, it's been a while.
True.
I should start this off with one of my customary jokes.
God.
Yeah.
Of course.
Let's hear it.
Let's have it.
Ham sandwich walks into a bar and orders a beer, and the bartender says, sorry, we don't
serve food here.
Well, that?
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll play devil's advocate here, and say that that request is more than reasonable.
Ham sandwich, come on.
He can't even, he'll just get all soppy, like wet bread is gross.
That's just racism, because there's no law, like there's a law against serving minors.
He'd get in trouble.
There's no law against serving food, so that's just victory.
Yeah, but it's for some good.
It's foodism.
Oh, just like Jim Crow, right?
Yeah, exactly.
Ham sandwich loss.
Separate but equal, right?
Yeah, okay.
I'm going to spoil something that's going to happen later on in this podcast.
I think you might have heard that the Speakpipe mailbox finally filled up.
Congratulations everyone.
You broke it.
It was supposed to only hold like a hundred megabytes, because we have the test, what
do you call it?
The trial period.
Yeah, we have the trial period free membership.
It should have filled up like years ago, but it just kept letting us do more and more.
But at some point, a couple people messaged me and said, wait, and yet we got a new one
just yesterday.
How can this be?
I was going to say, I was hoping that meant that we would have less voicemails this time.
That's what, yeah, we would all hope.
Yeah, maybe, possibly.
But I'm looking and, yeah, actually we do.
Yeah, we have fewer than usual.
So I think, but here's the thing.
I will just go back and I will delete old ones from the, yeah.
So next week, by the time you're listening to this, it should be okay to send more.
But between then and now, the box will be full and I'm sorry about that.
The, yeah, trial period is 100 megabytes free.
Our current storage uses 1.86 gigabytes.
So we really, yeah, storage use 1.46 gigabytes out of 100 megabytes.
So we really got a ratio.
All I can say to that is ratio.
Do you like know for certain you have a trial account?
Maybe like Nate or someone just sprung for like a full account and you just never noticed.
I don't know how this works.
I don't, it's possible.
It says, it says this is the limit.
Wait here.
Fair enough then.
Yeah.
Here's our little, here's our little sidebar.
You can see for yourself.
I swear I'm not bullshitting you.
There's the blam screenshot down at the bottom, storage used.
I don't know.
Yeah, that's 1.46 gigabytes out of 100 megabytes.
Yeah, I wasn't lying.
Oh, that's up to me.
I don't know.
I don't see anything wrong here.
You know, for those who don't know, one gigabyte is 1000 megabytes.
True.
Because you know nowadays a lot of people don't know that.
You know, zoomers probably have no idea what megabyte even is.
Because the units just don't go that small?
Isn't it like a little different from like 1 to 1000?
Isn't it like a slight discrepancy?
Yeah, it's like maybe 1,024 or something like that.
I remember.
Wait, why?
I fucking computer code shit.
Who cares?
Okay.
I remember looking something up about it.
Because when I made my Super Mario Land video, for some reason I put a little diatribe in about the difference between a megabyte and a megabyte.
A megabyte.
Yeah, like what's a megabyte?
Is that a pun?
No, it's just a different type of measurement.
I'm not going to speak on exactly what it is.
Is it something in like base 64 or some crap like that?
I think so.
Maybe.
I've never heard of it, but I have heard of megabits.
Yeah.
A megabyte equals two, oh it's two to the 20th bytes, or it's just over a million bytes.
So it's slightly more than a megabyte, but it's in base 64 or whatever.
I've got to wonder where it's used, or if it's like...
I think it's very base.
Very base.
I think it would be used in a context in which you are using binary code, because it's base two.
I think that's probably why it exists.
But yeah, it just happens to be functionally almost the same size as a megabyte.
I'll be darned.
Yeah, that's funny.
I wonder if they sound similar on purpose.
Well now that we know that gender isn't binary, I think we need to retire binary code.
Yeah, I think it's got to go.
It's off the spectrum.
True.
Very problematic.
Ones and zeros.
We've got to do quantum computing.
It's kind of like how the hard drives, they used to be masters and slaves.
Yeah, oh yeah.
RIP.
You have male and female cords, or outlets, or whatever.
What did I see?
I saw a really funny meme that I thought was very clever, and here's what it is.
It was a Mr. Incredible face.
The happy one, and then the black and white scared looking one.
It was jobs in which...
When at your job, someone asks you to do...
Someone, jobs that require you to work with male on male or something like gay.
Work for gay, right?
And it's like, baker, good.
Yeah, make a cake for the gay people.
Something else, wedding planner, blah blah blah.
Last one was electrician.
No.
Oh yes, oh yes.
You see, the comedy came from when one frame of reference suddenly came into unexpected conflict with a second frame of reference that used the same vocabulary.
The joke was very human.
It caused a surprise reaction in me that gave me a sensation of delight and caused laughter.
Very human podcast.
It reminds me of that clip that you tweeted ages ago where Trixie was explaining some kind of joke.
Oh, I vaguely remember that.
I didn't remember what the joke was, but it was something like...
I don't know.
Do you remember what the joke was?
Oh yeah, I think it was something about majors and minors, and I think it was a quote on the album.
It was a rap verse, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Oh, she was explaining that somehow you see the...
Yes, yes, yes.
It was a Mr. Girl lyric about sex with minors, but he meant the joke was it was a play on minors as in children versus minors as in people that work in a mine,
which has never been done before.
Never heard that one before.
Yes, she was like, oh, here's why this is genius.
Here's the brilliance of this pun.
You see, it conflates the meaning of two different words that sound the same but are written differently.
Very human.
Well, you know what they say, you should never explain a joke.
Never under any circumstances, even if asked.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
See, if you have to explain a joke...
Explaining a joke is like saying the n-word, you should never do it.
In...
What's the...
Ronald Reagan, in politics and comedy, if you're explaining, you're losing.
What's the actual quote?
What was the actual thing he said?
I think he said, oh, oof, ouch, oh, it hurts so bad.
Take me to a hospital immediately.
Oh, the hellfire is burning.
Margaret Thatcher, my friend, saved me.
Actually, speaking of Reagan,
did you guys see that the guy that tried to assassinate Reagan has a YouTube channel?
John Hinkley Jr., that's right.
Oh.
He's been making music recently.
He just recently, I think last June, got taken off his probation, so he was looking to tour.
Looking to tour?
To a couple of venues, but like every single venue keeps canceling on him.
Because he's John Hinkley Jr.
But that's fucked up.
Let the man play.
It's all I say.
He served, he served.
He did his time.
He's rehabilitated.
What is this?
Yeah, I think he did like 40 years or something.
Too much.
He only got out a couple of years ago, and only just recently his probation came out.
I think he's just recently able to post online.
I think he had someone else doing it for him until then.
When will, god damn it, when will they let, when will they let freakin, oh no.
I forgetting their names.
Molly and Orissa.
The Slenderman girl.
When will they let them post online?
I don't know.
They're not serving time, are they?
Because they're like writers.
One of them was let out fairly recently.
But I think she is still on probation and not allowed to use the internet.
Morgan, justice for Morgan and Anissa.
Oh yeah, because it wasn't one of them.
One of them was sort of the ringleader and the other was just kind of like a follower sort of thing.
So they were more lenient on the follower.
I know you talked about this last week.
I haven't listened to the episode.
I don't know what the official conclusion was.
From their testimony, they both kind of seemed to suggest the other one was in charge.
But I'm pretty sure that Morgan is the one that did the actual stabbing.
And Anissa is the other one.
And so I think it was probably safer for them to get her out of there.
Whenever you're in trouble, just blame the other guy.
Yeah.
Seems to be working out.
They're already on probation maybe.
It worked for Anissa. Anissa, I don't know.
The kid they stabbed didn't die, right?
She could have. She was pretty close to dying, but she did not die.
Yeah, they came pretty close to severing a fairly major artery, but they didn't.
Yeah, that story was fucking crazy.
Little known fact about me, I fucking loved Slenderman YouTube shows.
I watched all of them, even the really bad ones. I watched them.
Are you talking about like Marble Hornets?
Yeah, Marble Hornets, Evermint Hyrid, Tribe 12, Dark Harvest.
I watched some Marble Hornets because it was recommended to me.
I watched a bunch of it.
I wasn't around for when it was like popular.
Yeah.
I got the DVDs, baby.
They did. They had a Blu-ray too. Unfortunately, the Blu-ray is sold out.
I don't think they make it anymore, but yeah, I got the DVDs.
The menus are really good.
DVDs of Let's Plays.
It is kind of like that.
Oh my god.
It was kind of like Marble Hornets was like what, 2009, 2010?
And the DVDs I think were like early 2010.
So it was like one of the first ever YouTube things I ever got as physical media.
It's on my other shelf, so I'm not going to grab it and survey it right now.
It was pretty good.
The DVD menu was pretty well made.
They had a commentary for all the episodes.
Aren't there like a million episodes?
I think there's like 60 something.
They span it over three seasons, quote-unquote.
So they did like creator commentary tracks.
They did, yeah, for every episode.
That's amazing.
Yeah, that's cool.
That actually sounds great.
And that should be done with a PCP as well.
Did you guys do that a couple of times?
That's a great idea. We did it once.
I think we just did it once, but yeah, the creator commentary track.
Actually, I think you did it a few times.
Patreon.com. That's procrastinators.
If you want to hear the director's commentary of...
I don't even remember which episode we did it of.
I think it was an early one.
Probably the first one, right?
Yeah, it might have been the first one.
It was an early one.
I think you did it a few times and I was on for one of those.
One of the episodes was the first episode I was on.
No, what? You're right.
I think we actually did it.
I think we did it twice.
That sounds right.
Yeah, maybe one of them was the first one.
Anyway, it worked great.
It made perfect sense in an audio medium and nobody complained.
Yeah, that's how I remember it.
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway.
It doesn't seem like that terrible of an idea.
It's a bit...
I think some people said it's a little confusing because you keep hearing the same voices.
Oh, sure.
One is past Ben and one is future Ben.
The one is commentating on the other and it can be a little hard to keep track.
I think...
Well, whichever one doesn't sound like he's talking through a tin can is the normal Ben.
That's true.
Also, my voice just changed over the years.
My voice became higher pitch for some reason.
Did you originally record lying on your stomach or something?
Do you know what?
Actually, I think I did.
Not all the time, but I think I probably would record lying on my stomach.
Yeah, there was a time when I did that.
That might have something to do with it then.
It's a very Ben core thing to do.
Yeah, now that you mention it.
There's that Let's Player streamer Northern Lion.
I watched him for a really long time.
In the early days, his voice is a lot deeper and a lot less animated, I guess.
Nowadays, he sounds different.
You could chalk that up to just like,
Oh, well, he's been doing this for a long time.
He's more comfortable.
It's also because I remember hearing that he used to record lying on his back with his laptop on his stomach,
playing the games.
That's going to change how your voice sounds.
Even if I stood up instead of sat down when podcasting, it sounded a little different.
That's a strategy.
There definitely were episodes where I wouldn't lie on my back with my laptop on my stomach.
I would lie on my stomach with my head in hand hanging over the front edge of the bed
with the laptop on my floor in front of me.
Oh, wow.
Voice actors need to take notes because this is how you really do it.
This is how you get range.
That's the professional podcasters tip right there.
That one's for free.
How do you think Mel Blanc did it?
All those amazing voices.
Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck, Marvin the Martian.
He was lying on his stomach for a lot of them.
Yeah, he's lying on his stomach on his back doing pull-ups.
Lying in different positions.
They never got back to me about my voice acting audition for that stupid deaf Pina cartoon.
Oh, I'll never make it.
Is there something happening with that?
I haven't been listening to the PCP for a while.
I fell off the wagon.
I'm recently catching up.
Weeks and weeks ago, he just put out a casting call for voice actors for some cartoon he was making.
I said, sure, why not?
I just recorded some lines and sent them.
I didn't hear anything back.
That's fucked up.
Do you have any nepotism you could use?
Do you have a cheesy note or something?
I don't know.
I guess I was like, if on some chance he knew who Ben St. was,
if he'd seen the Sonichu lecture or something,
maybe that could have helped me name recognition-wise,
but to my knowledge, nothing came of that.
And it's probably been too late at this.
Either the project's canceled or he picked someone else.
Surely, surely.
Which is not okay.
So I'm not cool with it.
I'm going to be very mad.
I'm going to dislike bomb the video.
I'm going to lead a social media campaign against it.
I'm going to make it personal.
I'm going to make it his problem.
And then he's going to rue the day.
Yeah, I mean...
That guy has some controversies under his belt, right?
Yeah, probably.
I don't think I've ever seen a Daphne video.
He's fine.
I guess he calls people out.
Oh, that sounds great.
Yeah, his shtick is that he's monotone.
Oh, that's a great shtick.
Yeah, it's a good one.
Yeah, I know that shtick very well.
Speaking of voice acting, I wanted to briefly mention
that infamous scene in Mega Man X4.
I think you talked about it before.
I mean, this can't be happening.
Oh, there's no more point going on in this world.
What am I fighting for?
I skipped a line, didn't I?
No, Iris, no.
Don't hate humans, Zero.
You can't hate humans.
I agree with the colonel.
We must fight for our independence,
for we are the replifors.
I'm a fucking good game.
Well, I just wanted to mention that
I was curious about listening to the original Japanese version
because I heard it was better.
How could it not be?
I looked it up and it does sound way better.
Here's the link to the clip if you want to listen to it.
It's kind of a shame that the US version
got really bad dubbing
because I think the story to this game
would have been pretty good if the dub didn't suck so bad.
I agree.
It completely turns Iris' death into a huge meme.
That said, Iris was introduced in this game
and I feel like I wouldn't really care about her regardless.
The way they handled it,
I don't think there was anything they could have done
with the presentation to salvage the character of Iris.
The performance here is actually kind of impressive
because I don't know the Japanese voice actor's name,
but his screams were like gut-wrenching.
I was surprised by how good this performance was.
I'm almost there.
Yeah, that's a good anime scream.
I love a good anime scream.
Yeah, that's good.
It's totally good.
Have either of you played Mega Man X or Maverick Hunter X for the PSP?
Is that the remake?
No, I have not.
The voice act?
Well, I don't blame you because it was only on PSP
and I don't think they put it on any PSN store.
I just philosophically disagree with the idea of going back
and remaking the game because it wasn't good enough?
I agree with that.
I feel like it's not...
I would never really say it's definitively better than Mega Man X.
It seems more like they're trying to reboot things
because you've probably seen...
I remember you talking about the Day of Sigma OVA or whatever.
There's slight story discrepancies between the games,
but I like the voice acting in that game a lot.
The English dub.
In Maverick Hunter.
The thing is though is that that came out so much later
that dubbing standards in anime just was way better by then.
You have to remember that Mega Man X4 came out in 97
and most anime back then were dubbed horribly.
If you watch a lot of anime from the time, this dubbing sounds pretty familiar.
Yeah.
I think some anime had gotten a cut above this at this point,
but when video games...
I took to Final Fantasy X for voice acting and video games to be not fucking terrible.
I learned from Mage that we didn't really get this in America,
but in some countries, dubbing simply...
They didn't even take out the original audio.
They just...
One person just narrated the subtitles.
Yeah, Mage said that when she watched Dragon Ball Z,
it was just have someone's voice recorded over the unedited original Japanese audio,
just sort of repeating the lines but in Lithuanian or the native place,
the native language, the vernacular.
That sounds interesting.
I want to check out Lithuanian Dragon Ball Z.
Yeah, I mean, it'd probably be easier if it were a language you understood,
but yeah, just imagine like...
Japanese is still there.
Just someone is just one guy.
It's saying the lines.
It's like the PCP commentary tracks.
Yeah, it's like...
I should do a solo Ben.
I should do a solo Ben?
Wait, you know what?
I'm going to do that.
I'm going to do a solo Ben cast commentary track on one of the solo Ben cast.
I'm doing it.
No, I'm doing it.
I'm writing it down.
That's a great idea.
I'm 100%.
Yes, thank you.
Excellent.
Okay.
I'm trying to think of some early video game dubs that I think are pretty good.
Like Metal Gear, Solid is good.
Yeah, it's probably one of the best ones.
You know, I'm playing the old Resident Evil games,
and I actually kind of like the Resident Evil 2 dub,
even though it's corny and cheesy.
Yeah.
Other RE games, although RE1 is kind of...
I have never played Resident Evil, any of them.
But I have, you know, there's sort of a...
I've heard people say, I mean, sort of the goofy, like, wrong...
No, it's Silent Hill.
Silent Hill is the one that I hear people say that, like,
James is, like, stilted and kind of objectively bad delivery
actually sort of increases the uncanniness.
Yeah, I've heard people talk about that as well,
that, like, because Guy Sihi, I think, is his name.
He wasn't, like...
He wasn't a voice actor or, like, a professionally trained one.
There's, like, this funny story where he was taking his daughter to a rehearsal
or an audition to play the little girl in the game, Laura, I think, is her name.
And she didn't get the part, but they asked him to try for James,
and he got the part.
And I've never played Silent Hill,
but I did watch a Let's Play of it years ago,
so I basically know, like, the story, and I can comment on the performances.
And I think the voice acting in the game is actually really good,
because, like...
That's Silent Hill 2 or the first one?
2.
2, yeah, I should have clarified.
Because, yeah, it does sort of sound, like, sort of stilted and odd,
but in sort of a more, like, a homely way than, like, an incompetent sort of way.
I don't know.
Because, like...
Can I have something about it?
Silent Hill, either, so...
But I've seen that...
I've seen that... is it that Twin Perfect series?
About the...
The games.
What is that series called?
That second thing, Silent Hill or something?
I don't think that's it.
Two Peaks?
That's where the name comes from.
Yeah.
I've actually never seen those Twin Perfect videos,
but I have watched another video a couple years ago,
basically talking about how that Twin Perfect series
is inadvertently responsible for putting a lot of the blame
onto this one Silent Hill producer named...
Yes.
What's his name?
Tom Hewlett.
Yeah, they go pretty hard on Tom Hewlett in that...
I might...
Yeah, okay, it's called The Real Silent Hill Experience.
Nate recommended it to me years and years ago.
I have kind of come to...
I kind of think the guy's evil.
I kind of think the guy is evil a little bit,
the Twin Perfect guy.
He seems like a douchebag.
That's perfect, isn't it?
Aren't there two people?
There is, but the other one quit,
and I think has apologized for a lot of...
I think specifically for the harassment that Tom Hewlett received.
But the other guy has not.
That's a shame because...
I've never even seen those videos,
and I remember back in the day that a lot...
I remember people blaming this one producer dude, Tom Hewlett,
and I watched this video a couple years ago.
It's a two-part, but whatever.
I think you or someone else might have shown me this one.
Yeah, because I didn't know anything about it.
I saw the Twin Perfect one, and the Twin Perfect puts...
They say they're not doing this, but...
And then they name-drop on it.
You come away with the impression that basically this is Tom Hewlett's fault.
I assume that that is not entirely their invention.
I assume that probably a lot of the community put the blame on him, too,
and they sort of echoed that sentiment.
But then it just reinforced it.
My outside perspective is,
oh yeah, Tom Hewlett, that guy who ruined Silent Hill.
And I don't even know anything about any of this.
It seems so weird in hindsight
to foot the blame at some dude who may have had
some small amount of creative control regarding the series.
When it's fairly obvious that,
since it's a Konami game,
who the fuck else ruined Silent Hill but fucking Konami?
They ruined everything.
I was under the impression that every Silent Hill game
was handled by a different team.
The first three or four were done by an internal team
that disbanded shortly after, I think.
And then the rest of them, yeah,
they got done by different teams at Konami
or outsourced from Konami.
Way forward actually did a couple of Silent Hills, I think,
which Tom Hewlett works at way forward now, by the way.
What else did way forward do?
They make a Chante series, I think, right?
Oh yeah, yeah, okay.
They're fairly well known for making licensed games
that are better than you would expect.
And then every once in a while they do an original game
that's like an indie darling.
They were supposed to make that Advance Wars remake
that Nintendo delayed because of the Ukraine crisis
and is still not come out.
Advance Wars?
Yeah, they were remaking Advance Wars 1 and 2 for Switch.
Are they like in Ukraine or something?
Is that why the...
The...
I've never played Advance Wars, but from what I understand...
I did play it back on the Game Boy Advance
and I could ever beat the Final Stage.
The Black Hole Army, Sturm is too fucking hard
on the Final Stage for Kid Me.
I think they delayed it partly because, I mean,
there was a big war in the news
and the game's called Advance Wars.
Oh, because it's about war and war is bad.
War's bad, everyone's like, wait a minute.
We don't want to advance war, we want to reduce war.
It's stupid.
But also, the villain,
the main villain faction of the game is a Russian analog.
So I guess they wanted to avoid all controversy altogether.
But it's silly.
The game is apparently completely done
and has been done for months.
They should just release it.
That's the thing, if you're going to wait for a moment
and there's no war to release this game,
then you're going to be waiting a long time.
Honestly, I feel like...
Yeah, some people might get mad,
but I kind of just feel like nerds who are into war stuff
would just be more excited
if it reminds them of a current ongoing conflict.
I feel like that might move units, I don't know.
Ha, move units. No pun intended.
Yeah.
I think it's, since Advance Wars is made by a Japanese company,
they have maybe weirder views on this
compared to other developers.
Possibly.
I don't know.
I can see why they would want to do it,
but it's not like this crisis is going to end.
I mean, it's not over still.
What are you going to do? Never release the game?
Because a war happens?
A silly little war? Come on, we want video games.
Exactly, exactly.
Let's not lose perspective of what's really important here.
Video games.
I think also it has to do with Nintendo specifically.
They're very adverse to anything that is controversial.
They want to be family friendly.
Yeah, I mean, I guess that is true.
You want to know what a real...
It's actually kind of weird that they even have a war-based game at all.
Do you know...
Well, it's kind of cartoony.
I feel like that's how they get away with it.
Until that one on DS when it's not.
It is very cartoony, but at the same time,
it is about just regular people fucking killing each other
in a fucking field of battle on operations.
But at the same time, Andy doesn't know what an airport is.
I vaguely remember that.
There's something really funny.
A really dark coincidence with Advance Wars
and the original Game Boy Advance game.
It came out, I believe, September 10th, 2001.
So...
No!
I'm pretty...
Sturm used Meteor!
I'm looking this up to get specific.
I know it came out right around 9-11.
Are you saying that Intelligent Systems did 9-11?
I'm not saying they didn't.
No.
We couldn't prove that.
Ah, jeez.
September 10th.
Yep.
That's crazy.
If only...
You know what?
If only they had just done for the war in Afghanistan
what they are now doing for the war in Ukraine
and delayed the game,
and we wouldn't have done 9-11.
So maybe they're right after all.
In honor of Operation Iraqi Freedom
we are delaying Advance Wars.
It will release when all the troops are gone
from the Middle East.
Nintendo should have used their power.
We could have ended the war so much sooner.
Because Osama bin Laden's like,
Well, fuck!
I wanted to play that!
George W.
It's just like, ah, come on.
I love Andy.
That's exactly what would have happened.
Meanwhile, Saddam Hussein's in his little hidey hole
playing elite copy
with his little head sticking out or whatever.
Just think of what...
All of this could have been avoided.
If Nintendo was just a little less callous
with their video game releases,
I think this is the learning lesson.
Nintendo needs to use their platform for good.
They need to be better.
Instead of cancelling,
instead of copyright striking YouTubers
for using video game footage,
they should be copyright striking
the United States government
for conducting various CIA-backed coups
around the world.
They need to DMCA the United States government
for committing wars.
I believe that is our intellectual property
that you're infringing upon.
You're emulating wars?
I don't know.
They didn't buy the hard copy.
They copyrighted anything that has to do
with advanced warfare.
Speaking of the Game Boy Advance
and speaking of Mega Man,
I played some zero games recently.
My feeling from my adolescence
was that they were the best,
and I'm happy to say I was right.
They are still the best Mega Man games ever made.
The Zero Series is a big blind spot for me.
I know Chrono likes them,
and I know you like them,
but my experience with Mega Man Zero
was walking into a GameStop
when I was seven,
and then in the GBA kiosk...
It would be very challenging for a seven-year-old.
Yeah.
As you'll see shortly,
I think it was 0-3
was in a kiosk thing.
It's just a good-ass video game.
I was playing it.
I think I got to a boss and then died.
I was like, well, fuck me. This is way too hard.
Had you had any experience with Mega Man before that?
Yeah, I played X back in the day,
and Legends.
I feel like if you can beat the X bosses,
you can beat the Zero boss.
I never said anything about beating it.
I just played it.
I could probably beat it nowadays.
I know there's a collection that you can get.
Yeah, the Zero and X.
I'd be curious to try it.
I've never played ZX.
It's so good.
I know that...
Are you playing it through an emulator
or just that collection thing?
No, I'm playing on the Visual Boy Advance emulator.
Word up.
I actually prefer Gameplay-wise.
I prefer the X 1 through 4
to the Zero series.
But I think as far as the story is concerned,
the Zero series is definitely...
It's more cohesive.
Yeah.
What really stands out
is just the fact that
in the Zero games,
when you're not on a mission,
you're in the base
and you can just walk around
and talk to the other people
who live in the base and the other people
who are being affected by the war
that you're fighting.
It's such an obvious thing
to include.
It just makes the game a million times better.
Yeah.
And in the first one,
you can actually go to the missions
from the base directly without warping there.
They kind of pulled Dark Souls
where they made the first one
and they gave it this really cool
connected, continuous world
that was really cool.
And they were like,
that was hard.
Kind of is hard, I guess.
I guess it's hard.
But it was appreciated.
And they didn't do it again.
Which is fine.
I guess.
From a story standpoint,
the events of one game
lead into the other one.
And it feels like the world
and the characters are changing
from a game to game basis
that carries over.
The problem
with the X series story-wise
is that every time you beat one game
the next game starts and it just feels
like everything resets back to
the default values.
Pretty much.
Well, we beat Sigma,
but he's a freaking ghost in the machine now
and you can't actually beat him.
So I guess he'll be back.
I know that Dr. Wiley
always came back in the Mega Man series
but it always rubbed me the wrong way
that Sigma would come back in every game.
For some reason, there was a disconnect there
that it always seemed kind of cheap.
Like the second time in the second game
when he comes back, okay, that's fine.
Because he turns into a data thing.
That's interesting.
There comes a point where
they should have stopped.
Yeah, bring him back
every couple of games, I guess.
I haven't played it,
but I think in X7
or X8, he comes back
and he's all
fucked up looking and mutated because
he's like, yeah, he just keeps coming back.
I think that was X6.
He comes back as a zombie.
But he's not the same.
It's like they knew. We really shouldn't keep
dragging this guy back, but we have to do it.
Actually,
X6, technically, Sigma wasn't
the actual final boss
even though you fight him as the final boss.
Yeah, he was that gay guy.
He was a scientist.
He was some red-white scientist.
Yeah.
He was the main one putting the strings
and he revived Sigma for some reason.
Well, because you need to fight Sigma at the end.
Yeah, literally.
Sigma has nothing to do with that one,
but then at the end he's like, okay,
hey, you beat me.
My machinations have been unraveled.
Final note, I did revive Sigma just in case.
So go fight him as well.
Okay, thank you.
Crazy about that is the
final battle with Sigma in that game
is probably the most unnecessary in the series
so far. The music is probably
the best Sigma battle out of any
of the Sigma songs. It's like a remix
of the first three. It's really good.
I don't remember the music.
Actually,
I don't know if it's a spoiler to reveal it,
but at the very end of X8
you don't fight Sigma, surprisingly.
It's Luminae, right?
I never played X8.
I have not...
I haven't played that one either.
I know who Luminae is.
I always heard that it was better
than 7, but like
better than 7 is not
really a high bar.
Yeah.
But I think it's better than X5
and 6 as well.
Oh, yeah. X6 is kind of...
X6 is bad.
I would say 5. I don't really like 5.
I think 5 is where
it kind of went off the deep end for me.
Yeah, I consider 5 bad, to be honest.
It has an interesting story, but everything else
about it sucks.
5 is pretty whack.
He's the bad guy in 5.
You know, the whole cannon thing where you have
a random chance of getting a different ending.
Oh, yeah.
You can fire the cannon whenever you want,
but if you beat all the stages
you have a better chance
of the cannon being successful.
Even if you beat all the stages,
you can still lose, lol.
And you can still get the bad ending.
Why not?
It's right there.
If you beat all the stages,
you get the good ending.
I don't know. Come on.
Why would you make it random?
It's bizarre.
Yeah, the Zero Games.
I don't think this is the case,
but the story is tight enough that you would
think that they went into it planning to make
4, and they were like, here's the plan.
1, 2, 3, 4, done.
Apparently that's not the case.
Because I guess I read in an interview
or something that, like,
after X3, they were planning on making X3
the end.
But then, like...
But fans wanted to know what happened
with Dr. Vile.
So we had to make 4.
Dr. Vile?
Dr. Vile.
And it's like...
Oh, zero, zero.
I thought you were talking about X.
I was like, who the fuck is this?
In Zero 3,
they ended it,
and it literally ends with
Dr. Vile is back,
and he's in charge now.
And that's the ending.
And we were surprised.
Fans were unsatisfied.
Fans wanted to know what happened
and it's like, yeah.
What did you think was going to happen?
Ah, jeez.
And then they fucking made it,
and 4 has the best fucking ending.
4 has the best ending, the most definitive ending.
They brought it to a conclusive,
satisfying resolution.
Yeah, I watched Gamer and Savarin's video
on that ending. It seemed pretty cool.
Right, right.
I remember first experiencing
that ending back when the game came out,
and I beat it.
And then back then, I was like,
this is a really great ending.
So then, like 10 plus years later,
I was still thinking about that ending,
so that's why I wanted to make a video on it.
Yeah.
Literally,
the best ending that any Mega Man game has
because it actually has one.
Yeah, they actually had the courage
to end things
for certain,
not leave it up in the air with all the other ones
that they usually do.
How tied in is the ZX series?
I know it takes place like...
Isn't the plot of ZX is like, it's like
years and years later,
and like kids,
they get data of
0 and X, and like, where them is like,
armor, basically.
Yeah, they do a funny...
Kids in the future do a funny fusion dance
to
call upon the power of the ancient
Reployed Heroes
and become superheroes.
Well, when you say it like that,
it sounds kind of stupid.
Oh, sorry.
I haven't played it myself,
but yeah, the plot seems very
very Saturday morning cartoon.
Like, they wanted to make a Mega Man game,
but they were kind of embarrassed about
what they were doing, so they tried to
make it distant.
It's...
But also, pretty much the whole ZX
story sounds like
just a big pastiche
of homage. They're just like,
let's make it a...
Yeah, the stories in those games are kind of
underwhelming, but I like
the concept of
humans that can transform into
the X
and zero heroes and stuff.
I've always been a sucker for
the Super Sentai or Power Rangers
concept of superheroes.
I think it's a very
silly place to take the series,
but I'm not like...
completely against it.
I'm just kind of...
I just kind of find it
amusing, like, hmm, okay.
Really? That's what you're going to do
with it? I mean, alright.
Sure. Well, it's never going to be as cool
as what the Mega Man Zero series did.
It's hard to imagine.
I think...
I really just miss Mega Man.
Having played through
Legends and Legends 2 recently,
yeah, Zero used to be
a far and away favorite. I thought it was obviously
the best game. I think it probably still
is, but I think Legends is probably my second
favorite. Legends is a really...
Legends
accomplishes what it sets out to do.
It succeeds at being the kind
of game that it's trying to be. I would say
I would say about as well.
It's not around the heart. It's not around as well as
the Zero's game. They do have a lot of heart.
It's really well realized. I love
the aesthetic.
They figured out Z-Targeting
in a 3D game.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I realized
as I was playing through Zero 2
that it really reminds me of Phenotopia.
You know that game? No.
It's an indie game
made by some guy.
It was released on Newgrounds.
It was published by Newgrounds.
It's a side-scrolling platformer,
but it's pixel-arc based.
Oh, I heard you talking about this.
Yeah, I used to compare it to Cave Story
because it sort of looks like
Cave Story side-scrolling pixel-based,
and it is an action game, but
the combat is really clunky
and the moment-to-moment
gameplay of it
is about
a lot of it is about finding
objects and bringing them to the
people that want them in exchange for stuff,
which feels like
Mega Man Legends a lot.
And it's also,
thinking back on it, the story of Phenotopia
is about delving into ruins
of a mysterious origin
and nobody knows where they are,
and it turns out your protagonist
has a secret connection to the creators
of these ruins.
That certainly sounds familiar.
Very, very similar.
Now that I've
played all of it.
Legends is just one of those games
that indie developers really like.
Yeah, I think
probably if I went back
and read that guy's blog, he probably
would mention Mega Man Legends somewhere.
I feel like the connections are pretty similar.
I like Mega Man Legends, but
I do have issues with the controls.
It has those old-fashioned
tank controls
from a PS1 era.
I like Legends 2 controls
much better.
I think the reason I bounced off Legends as a kid
was because, yeah, I liked the
sort of twitchy action
of Mega Man, and so I picked up Legends
and I think I found the combat really slow
and clunky, and I was like,
yeah.
It's really hard to turn
around and target enemies
and actually attack them effectively.
It's interesting because
I'd say Mega Man
on NES,
Mega Man probably has some of the best feeling
like platforming
games on the entire library
and same with X on Super Nintendo.
Yeah.
Legends would be the best
of the cream of the crop feeling
3D games,
but even Capcom kind of stumbled a little.
Not even close.
Their priorities were completely different.
But it still sort of pays off
because people really,
really like Legends regardless
because the aesthetic and the world
and everything else
is top-notch.
Yeah.
I do like everything else about it.
The voice acting is pretty good
and the cutscenes are fun.
It is.
That game has pretty decent voice acting,
I'd say.
You know, I'm thinking back to it
and I can't remember any times
when I thought the voice acting was bad
in a way that stood out,
so I am forced to conclude
that the voice acting was good.
There you go.
It's a little cheesy.
It's like a Saturday morning cartoon.
Um...
No one sounds like they're asleep
or are
asking what they're fighting for.
It's way better than
Dr. Light from Mega Man 8.
Zero.
If I become one of them,
you have to finish me, Zero.
Don't be ridiculous, X.
I'm cutting off communications.
If I were you, I would fight Dr. Huawei.
A lot of them.
When I was a kid,
I didn't realize how bad voice acting
was in X4, so I actually kind of
liked it back then.
Now I can see it's
horrible. I still like it. I think it's pretty awesome.
If anything, the only problem with it is that it's too quiet.
The voice acting is too quiet.
I can't hear it.
It's so quiet.
I think they should have just left
the Japanese voice acting and added subtitles.
Oh, like X6?
Yeah.
If they were too lazy to get to dub it,
then just do that.
No dubbing is better than bad dubbing.
Exactly.
It depends on how story heavy
the game is, but
I guess if the dub is bad, then yeah.
Something like a Mega Man X game,
I don't think it really matters.
It doesn't necessarily need an English dub,
but I did think it was really funny
that they just didn't even bother
to dub X6 because they knew the game
was a fucking trap.
The issue with X5 and X6
is that they didn't even have anime cutscenes.
They just had static
images.
They put no effort at all into the cutscenes
in those games.
I didn't really even mind the static images as a kid,
because
all the art in the cutscenes
or the stills are on model
well enough. That said,
it is kind of lame that what is supposed
to be like Zero's final
hurrah is just resorted to
stills.
It just stepped down from the anime cutscenes
of X4, which were
impressive to look at.
They look really cool.
The Sigma Zero fight
is really badass.
It's like
the reaction to the cutscenes in
4 was bad, so instead of
improving them, we're
not going to do cutscenes anymore.
I don't think they were aware of
the reactions back then.
They probably didn't know the reactions
until after the internet became
more popular.
That's true, and it was just
the English that was terrible.
Probably in Japan, it was fine.
I think it's just budgetary reasons.
They just kept getting lower and lower
budget.
It seemed like for X4, they had a pretty big
They wanted to go big with that one.
It was X5 and X6.
They just wanted to make it
really cheaply.
I'm looking this up.
Apparently, the
Phenotopia remake
was released on Switch last year.
I saw. I was looking that up.
It's all steamed, too, I guess.
I knew that they were making
Phenotopia 2,
but apparently, they were
being developed at the same time,
but apparently they have stopped making
it when they're doing something else now.
I don't know what that is.
At least they're still around.
I don't know
why remake it, though.
Artists
love
finding something they made early on
and then trying to improve upon it.
Yeah, like George Lucas.
God, I hope he didn't George Lucas
Phenotopia.
I would like to play the remake
just to see
what is different.
I know they added
cooking systems and stuff,
which could be fun,
but I don't know. I feel like Phenotopia was
I feel like it was just fine.
Yeah, that's the issue I had
was Maverick Hunter X
is that I felt Megaman X didn't need
a remake.
It was really, really good as is.
Well, I haven't played it.
The question is that it's there to
update the lore.
Sort of.
I feel like the lore didn't need an update
because they updated the lore
in the subsequent games.
I do like
the Day of Sigma
video,
but besides that, I felt everything else
was kind of unnecessary.
I think it is mostly
fine.
It's a good game on its own.
I would probably never play it over the original
X.
That said, it does have
some extra stuff.
The Vile mode is kind of cool.
The only problem with it is that
when you play,
you play as Vile,
instead of how X gets powers
from all the different Mavericks he fights,
Vile has
this equipment mechanic where
before a stage, you give him certain
pieces of equipment that
changes Musa out
around. Just pretty cool.
It's pretty cool.
It's a neat little addition.
The problem is that
he has this song
that plays
throughout the entire game.
They don't play the stage music.
They play some butt metal.
Wow.
They throw every level and you
get fucking sick of playing as Vile
two stages in.
It's really weird.
That really is a bummer.
I think it's the same song for all the stages.
Yup. It's the same exact song.
It's some generic
shitty butt metal riff.
It's so bad.
That is unfortunate.
There's no zero.
You don't get to play a zero. I know he dies,
but come on.
Vile also dies at the end.
Yeah. Vile dies too.
They could have done something to
play a zero.
Why wouldn't they make a zero mode?
That seems like such an obvious inclusion.
It does because when you play X,
there's a lot of moments where zero says
he's going to scout around or he's going to do
something off-screen.
That's true.
That would have been a perfect
opportunity to have a zero mode
where you get to see what he does off-screen.
At the beginning he says
I'll...
I'm going to find Sigma.
At Sigma's Fort, I think he says
I'll
make a frontal assault on Sigma
on the fortress while you
sneak in while I distract
the main forces.
It's something like...
I assume it was just
time restraints or something.
Zero was a staple in all the games at that point.
But if they had the time,
I think it would have been cool if
you get a zero mode and he goes through
remixed stages.
That would be different because
we got to get the game out.
I understand
that that's
gamer entitlement to ask,
why didn't you make even more game?
I feel like simply implementing
another character to play through the same stages.
I appreciate
the novelty of a vile mode.
I think that's cool.
Why would you not have a zero mode?
It seems like such an obvious inclusion.
Seems like it wouldn't have been that hard.
The intention they had was to
remake the entire X-Series
just like how they were going to remake
all the classic games with
Mega Man Powered Up.
It seems a little like George
Lucas-ing to me. I'm glad it didn't happen.
Yeah.
I think Powered Up is probably
a better
reimagining.
I'm sorry, Powered Up has Oilman
and that's racist.
Oilman? Yeah.
I don't think
they should have made Oilman.
They probably shouldn't have made Oilman.
I think they changed
them into purple in the US release
like with Janks and Pokemon.
They pulled the Janks, I see.
Yeah.
I don't really care for the cutesy
art style of Powered Up
either.
Again, I haven't played it, but I've seen it.
I don't see the appeal.
I don't like what I've seen.
What I think it does better than
Maverick Hunter, though, is that
it has a lot more bang for your buck.
It has a level designer.
Yeah, there's a level editor.
That's neat.
You can't play a zero on
Maverick Hunter X, but you can play
literally every robot master in Powered Up
and Roll.
That's cool.
If you could play as Chill Penguin
in Maverick Country,
that would be sick.
That would be so sick.
Yeah.
Imagine your plan is
Spark Mandrill trying to go through
the little boss doors.
It just has a little
discharge.
But obviously,
if you're going to play as any robot master
in Powered Up, you have to play as a oilman.
I just can't relate
to a character of a different race
than myself.
If you woke to play as an oilman,
I'm sorry, this is terrible.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Remake's bad.
Remake's bad and I disagree with him
philosophically.
Kind of, I guess.
I was playing the Resident Evil Remakes
recently.
I just beat Resident Evil 2
and everyone
really likes that one.
I just started three and I know
I like that one.
Having played
the older ones,
recently,
I feel like I have a pretty good frame of reference
to quantify
what is good about the remake
and what isn't, etc.
I liked Resident Evil 2 Remake.
I don't know if I liked it as much as the original,
but
it still kind of
justifies itself in my head
as a pretty
significant reimagining
of the events of that game
and has enough
where I can kind of see
them existing concurrently.
I would never say
don't play the original, just play the remake
for Resident Evil 2.
I would say play both
because they're both good games.
What's different?
Well, obviously,
it's a big
budget 3D
AAA game now.
It's got the over-the-shoulder camera.
The original
was pre-rendered
to tank controls.
That's a completely different
play experience.
It plays completely differently
and the layout of the police station
and the other levels are different
to some degree.
It's a lot like...
There was this section in the game.
Let's see how we can reincorporate it
in a new way.
There was a lot of stuff I was seeing
or I was like, oh, this kind of reminds me
of this part of Resident Evil 2
and now it's like this.
That's kind of cool.
It plays Resident Evil 4?
Here's the thing.
People always say that
and
I guess it's similar
in the sense that
it's third-person shooters over the shoulder
but the way
you're meant to play
in Resident Evil 4
is completely different from
the later remakes
because in RE4
the game
just showers you an ammo
at least on the normal difficulty.
It showers you an ammo
and it gives you all the opportunity
to shoot the guys
and then tackle them to the ground
and stuff. You're basically encouraged
to just kill everything
and it's fun.
I replayed Resident Evil 4 recently
and that game is so fucking good.
I remember Resident Evil 4
coming out and getting
10 out of 10s in Game Informer.
It was one of those games that got
critically acclaimed
way back in the day
and basically wrote the book
so like you would expect
you'd expect
it probably hasn't aged that well
it's kind of the first to really do
a lot of these things and it really hasn't
it just feels so fucking good.
I don't know how to describe it.
I have high hopes
for the
RE4 remake
and even if it
comes out and is great
I would still recommend people play the original because it's...
I feel like remaking
Resident Evil 4 seems kind of unnecessary.
Yeah.
It kind of is.
I'm not going to say it isn't because
the game holds up perfectly fine nowadays.
I feel like they're just kind of doing it to do it.
But if the game comes out good
then it's two good games, right?
That's
how I feel about the Pokemon remakes now.
I think that's a...
Do you really need Shining Diamond
and Glistening Pearl or whatever?
No.
The game industry is kind of headed
to where the movie industry was
where they're just remaking a lot of old stuff
because they can't come up with anything new that's good.
Is it like
the Squatters rights thing, right?
You've got an IP but if you don't do something
with the IP you can lose the rights to it.
Yeah.
I'm sure the Pokemon company doesn't have that problem
but...
You've got to keep the brand relevant
by releasing something every so often.
I'm thinking of Square
because they made a lot of Final Fantasy games
that everybody hated so then they were like
well everybody likes Final Fantasy 7
so let's just release nothing but
Final Fantasy 7 games until
forever I guess.
That's kind of how it feels.
I know that they...
I mean they do...
I guess a 14 is a pretty big hit.
Yeah.
14's its own completely different beast.
I think 14
initially everybody hated it
but then they were updated it
and massively changed it
and now it's people like it.
It got a new producer
and the guy basically turned the ship around
and turned it into their biggest cash cow.
It's wild that that is possible.
It's one of those
one in a million big success stories
for something like that.
I mean it's...
I think it's a more popular MMO these days
than even WoW
which is...
I definitely hear more people talking about 14.
Yeah, me too.
It feels like the first
time in a long time that
an MMO has felt like relevant
like people are talking about it.
Which is shocking.
I kind of never thought that would happen again.
It seems deserved.
Here's the thing.
Why would you name your MMO
Final Fantasy 14
and then release a single player game
that's Final Fantasy 15?
This had a chip on my shoulder
back when...
When 11 came out and it was an MMO
it always perplexed me.
They should have just called it Final Fantasy Online.
I know.
It seems so obvious.
It means that they thought it was a good idea.
They were just so committed
to the numbering system.
We can't...
Too late now.
Too late now. Sorry.
The other 11.
If we don't do it
people won't take the game seriously.
If we call it anything other than
Final Fantasy Number
people will think that's an admission of failure
for saying this isn't a fake game.
That was probably their thought process
when making 11.
I think so.
If we call it Final Fantasy Online
people will see it as a side project.
We got to get people to play it
by calling it 11.
You haven't played all the Final Fantasy
unless you've played 11.
Which is a shame
because from what I understand
11 holds up perfectly fine on its own.
It's a pretty well-liked game.
I don't think it really needed to be 11.
It's just a name
at this point.
It doesn't really matter.
But it is strange.
It is.
It's just so stupid from a marketing standpoint
because
Final Fantasy 14 is supposed to outlast
15 and 16
until it has an online one.
It seems dumb
to tie it to an old number.
I don't disagree.
If it's successful
I assume they intend to eventually
make a Final Fantasy 18
or whatever. That is another MMO.
They're going to continue
drilling into this bad idea
of, you know...
You think it's a bad idea?
Or are you in the numbering system?
I'm shocked they still...
I'm shocked they're still numbering them.
They're like one of the only companies
that still does that.
Yeah, at some point other ones
start to not hyphenate.
They start to use colons.
They get embarrassed of the number.
Final Fantasy 7?
Fuck, there's 7 of these? How embarrassing.
Final Fantasy...
Can't all be the final one.
Let's make a
control all delete webcomic
about that.
How can they all be the final fantasy?
Ahhhh!
Thank you Penny Arcade. Very cool.
What were we talking about?
Oh, a fucking
tie back to Resident Evil.
Resident Evil 7
is called Resident Evil
Biohazard.
But the VIL
in 7 is like
accented. So it looks like a 7
in the evil. And Biohazard is the Japanese name
to Resident Evil.
So what's the name of Japan?
It's called Biohazard Resident Evil 7.
Wow!
And then they have Resident Evil
Village
where they do the thing again
with the numerals 8 in the village.
Isn't that clever?
Wait a minute.
Yeah, it is.
It's cute.
That's pretty cute.
Yeah, they did it.
I think Japanese companies
are one of the only ones that
do this kind of thing
where they have a number
into like
they release so many sequels
with numbered titles.
Because I can't think of
like western
equivalence to that.
Well, you know, you got
the wizardry games. Those got to like 9
or something.
Same with Ultima.
But those are pretty old. I can't think of anything that got to
like 16.
True.
True, true. I think Final Fantasy might
be the one.
Unless there's like some obscure like
shitty shovelware game that's on like
Majang number 70 or something.
Bloons.
Yeah, Bloons got to like 6 tower defense games.
Okay, not even as many
as I thought.
Wait, what's that one?
What's that like
turn based flash game
with the anime characters?
You're gonna have to be a little more specific.
You have to be more specific.
It has the slimes.
Oh god, this isn't narrowing it down at all.
Adventure quest?
Oh, it sort of feels like Adventure
quest.
Oh god, this is gonna haunt me.
Ragnarok online.
Your main character
is like a blonde pirate guy
who like summons swords.
It was on
Newgrounds. He summons lots of swords.
Oh god!
That was like a combination of one piece of Final Fantasy
The side character,
the cute side character is a slime
but he's like a little cat
necko slime or something like that.
Oh no, sword
quest
sword adventure
anime
anime quest adventure
sword
I can't
I can't handle it.
Google. Google.
Pirate
anime
cat
slime sword
summon
quest. God help you.
Give me.
Please.
This is gonna be the hardest thing to find.
I'm not.
I'm gonna lose it.
I'm gonna freaking lose it.
Wait, I'll add Newgrounds to the list.
Battle
something
I never played
many Newgrounds flash games
back in the day.
I played my fair share.
Epic battle fantasy.
I think I actually remember hearing about that one.
Let me post the screenshot.
What a generic name.
Yeah, I think
I think that's the point.
Yeah, probably.
Is Cloud Strife unlockable?
I think you should win an award
for winning this one.
Epic battle fantasy.
Pow.
Blammo.
Oh, geez.
Hell yeah.
It reminds me of Maple's story.
It does.
It's a...
We have Dragon Quest at home.
Yeah, it's not really like that.
I mean, it looks like that, but it's got that
freaking chibi how to draw anime
style, but
it's just a very...
It's just a side-scrolling...
I mean, it's a turn-based...
It's basically just a turn-based
RPG, like battle
gauntlet with no...
I mean, there's a story, but
it's just about
using big magic to do big
attacks on enemies.
It sounds like Phantom's Revenge.
I was going to say, it's Phantom's Revenge.
But good.
Damn.
It's got...
Phantom's Revenge only has one sword.
Oh, man. It's been so long
since I've listened to the
PCP and I was catching up.
And I just recently got
past Ben releasing
Phantom's Revenge, so I got to ask...
That's like four months ago.
The post-mortem.
How does it feel four months out
from release?
The post-mortem is,
you know, it got the...
I think it got... It's a crude
like 500 downloads now,
which is, you know, that's nice.
Cool.
I think the game came out good,
came out pretty much exactly how I wanted it
to, which, I mean, what more can you ask
for? My
goal is...
You know, because I'm
still trying to get the book printed
and when I do the Kickstarter, I'm hoping
that the Kickstarter is
a big success and gets eyes on it
and maybe some more people check the game out
from
hearing about it through that.
That's my hope, anyway.
Are you still considering that idea
of like
scraping out
the Sonichu references to make it
more palatable, or was that just a slight
musing from months
gone by? That would...
That would be... If I did
that...
That would take a lot of work,
I feel like. It would...
I mean, it would just be a matter of changing
sprites and changing some dialogue.
If I did something like that,
it would basically be in...
I would basically just create
a sequel. I would just
make another game that
had similar, like, systems
and just different
enemies or something,
which I don't have any immediate plans to do. Yeah,
I did think about, like,
should I scrape this of Sonichu
because Sonichu is
brand poison? And I think,
like...
It wouldn't be the same game,
so...
Maybe I would come back to it
and make it
basically a different game or a different
version that is its own
thing. That is not
Sonichu related.
You'd be able to use a lot of the
codeface still, right?
I could... Like, assets?
Yeah.
Or just, like, the way the game works.
Yeah, I could definitely
recycle a lot of it
into...
Yeah, there's a lot I could reuse.
I don't see why you have to remove
the Sonichu references
since they're all, like, enemies
and bad guys.
I don't know. My thought
at the time, and I think it probably has some
truth to it, is just that, like,
any association with Sonichu
at all, to a certain kind of person
that's, like,
just so hideous.
Just so hideously off-putting and, like,
basically synonymous with
all sorts of
negative things.
I'm just thinking, it's like
if the bad guys were Nazis,
you wouldn't say, like, oh, man,
I gotta get rid of all these Nazis.
I don't want to have any references.
I don't think it's the same
because everybody
knows what World War II is.
It stands to reason that
if you are putting
Sonichu in your game, then you know
what a Sonichu is, which means
you know about Chris Chan, and some people
just, like, don't want
anything to do with that at all.
Yeah, everyone knows what a Nazi is.
Yeah, everybody knows what a Nazi is.
And Nazis are, like, a
relevant, historical villain.
If you're
making Sonichu-related content,
you are choosing to put this in front of people,
you're making choices,
and they're bad choices, and people don't appreciate it,
and that's what I did.
But to be fair,
you did it at a time, you know,
in a different time when it wasn't
four times.
I know what you mean.
I think
there is some cringe factor.
There's a cringe factor with
Sonichu that, like, if you are describing
the game, and it's like, oh, it has
Sonichu's in it, in any extent,
people will be like, oh, that's cringe.
That makes the game cringe.
Which honestly, I can't really,
I get it.
Wasn't that always the case, though?
Anything related to Sonichu
was always cringe, even,
you know, before current events.
Listen, there's people
I mean, you know
that Sonichu redrawn, someone
re-drew it from Rosichu's perspective?
No, I don't know
that, but...
Someone redrew, like, a chapter
of it from Rosichu's perspective, and
that redraw had good art
and it was, like, rewritten
to be good.
And it was, like, the person that made it
was talented and he did a good job
and it's a good comic. However,
it's still Sonichu
and it's still, like,
I don't know, I think
to a certain extent, it's like
this idiot wasted their time
making Sonichu content.
Like, what a freak.
Disgusting.
I feel a little part of me feels that way
about myself.
So, you know...
Well, shucks.
I contain multitudes, is what I'm saying.
Yeah, so...
Don't worry about it.
At least you didn't waste, like, 15 years
writing 500 reviews.
I
will waste my time
doing something. I swear to God.
Don't you, don't you doubt it.
I want, I want to talk about those
for a second, because I
I'm meaning to say this for a while, and since
you, Gamer's Tavern, are on this
podcast with me, I suppose I can
now.
I was, I actually went back
and I was looking at some of your, like, old
you're on your website, like, your old, like,
blog posts or, like, your reviews
or whatever. Just, like, your writings, I guess.
And, you know,
I guess I don't really know what I
expected, but
you're really mean in those,
I've noticed.
Really? Yeah.
It was a different time.
I haven't read a lot of your text
reviews.
Gamer's Tavern's
text posts were, like, because, you know,
you hear him on the podcast and he's a pretty
mild-mannered guy, you know, he's a little corny,
funny corny jokes. So, you know,
I expected, like, some
some, like, some dry
witty, sort of,
like, uh,
deadpan analysis of some
sort, but he's a lot fireier.
The fire in his heart burned
bright, I'd say.
I feel like that was, sort of, just
indicative of the time.
And, you know, just being younger.
Like, it was an era of angry reviews
and an era of, like,
insult, insulting something.
Yeah.
I mean, he's right here,
so I guess he could speak for himself.
Well, you know, that was,
I started the site nearly 20 years ago.
So,
you know, I was different back then.
Yeah.
You know, when I first started
writing, I kind of had a bit of
a persona on my website.
That's why I figured
that's what that was.
It was different from how I am
in person, so it was
kind of like a
Maddox, you know, Maddox.
It's kind of like
that kind of thing.
But I didn't
know who Maddox was at the time.
You know, so I thought it was being
completely original.
It's hard for
me to imagine you with, like,
a, I'm being mean
gimmick. That's crazy.
Yeah, it was being kind of
mean and cynical and
egotistical and narcissistic.
But I was kind of doing it
in, like, a self-deprecating
way.
It's part of the joke.
It's so funny.
So I did that for a while,
but then when I realized
Maddox already did that before
I did, I kind of stopped
because...
Yeah, I guess that is a bit...
I didn't want people to accuse me of copying him.
Yeah.
People probably accuse Maddox
of copying someone else.
Yeah, and there's a lot of, like,
Maddox copycat writers
that used to exist back then
in, like, 2005.
I'm sure Maddox wasn't the first
person to, like, do
comedy in a sort of, like,
I'm being an over-the-top
asshole on purpose sort of
way.
Yeah, probably not.
Yeah.
Who would contemporary critics
have compared Maddox's comedy to
at the height of his power?
Sean Baby, I guess?
Yeah, that's another one.
Did Sean Baby exist when Maddox
was writing the best page in the universe?
Yeah, Sean Baby was, like, late 90s.
Yeah, Maddox started, I think, in 97.
Was he? Yeah, I think so.
I'm not super knowledgeable on Sean Baby,
but...
I still don't know anything about Sean.
I've heard the name, I don't know who that is.
Yeah, he's, like, an old
internet writer. I'd say it's, like,
him and Maddox are, like, kind of, like,
old guard that are somewhat still around.
I think Sean... Didn't Sean Baby, like,
found Cracked or something?
I don't know. I'm not sure
what Sean Baby did later,
but I know, you know,
I think he used to write for EGM or something.
He used to be a video game magazine
writer, then he started writing on the
internet.
Are there any, like, stand-up comedians
that have a persona that's, like,
oh, I mean to children, like,
dead baby jokes? Yeah, all of them.
Yeah, basically.
I mean, dead baby jokes, that was
Andrew Dice Clay's saying, wasn't it?
I'm not familiar
with the man's work.
But, perhaps.
Yeah.
I think most male comedians, you could
probably find them making a joke about how they hate kids.
I'm just saying, you know,
the animatics stick
came... did not come
spring fully formed.
I'm sure he was influenced
by comedians and stuff,
but he was probably the first, like,
major internet person
to do that style of humor.
Because he started in the late 90s,
and, you know, the internet
barely existed back then.
I know that
my friends
were really into Maddox when he was
running the best page in the universe.
Well,
a lot of his old writing, I think,
is, you know, was pretty good for the time,
and some of it still holds up.
I don't know why he, like,
stopped and, you know,
started doing other weird
stupid nonsense.
Yeah.
I don't know, maybe he just
maybe he'd run that
stick into the ground.
I mean, he's doing it for a long time.
He's doing YouTube videos later,
and those weren't as good as the articles,
but, you know, some of them were fine,
I guess. They were pretty popular, though.
Yeah.
I don't know why he didn't continue doing them,
because they were getting good views,
and, you know, some of them were okay.
You know, some of them were decent.
I think...
He famously had that cuck one,
which kind of
started a lot of things.
Yeah, that one wasn't that great, but...
There were a couple of other ones that were
fine, you know.
I think just the issues he was having
with Dick Masterson
maybe
demoralized him, and he didn't want to work
on content anymore.
It's funny, I still see him
every once in a while,
just like on a scant
Twitter post every now and then.
I'm just like, oh yeah, he's still around, huh?
So, you know,
there's that.
I'm reading an article
by Sean Baby
from February 12, 2012
called four, quote,
geek humor books
by authors who understand neither.
I'm already laughing.
It's possible Maddox
was inspired by Sean Baby, you know.
Pure...
Yeah.
Let me see here.
I'd say they're contemporaries.
I've never heard him mention Sean Baby,
but
here's a sample
from this article.
I guess this is a real
book that's being
reviewed.
This is very,
it's kind of like Maddox's thing,
but Sean Baby did it first.
Hmm.
Write a book? Yeah, Sean Baby
already did that pal, sorry.
No, Sean Baby didn't write this book.
He's reviewed, he's lampooned.
This is a real book from
by some guy
and he's featuring.
It's being featured here.
It's like when Maddox
reviews an old book or something
and, you know... Oh my god.
Maddox did an article reviewing old
book covers, I think.
Yes.
Well, wasn't that one of the,
that was one of the
basis for his
one of his books that he sold?
Or no, he like, made fun
of kids drawings in one of them.
How do you get...
What do you get when you cross Pac-Man with a sweater?
An owl pack a
sweater. Ah, jeez.
Woo! I think we found
where Gamers Tavern gets his jokes from.
Yeah, pretty much.
Maddox was inspired by Sean Baby.
Gamers Tavern
was inspired by good old John Byrne.
Yeah, pretty much.
I mean, like a
Titan of the industry.
Uh...
Those were different times.
I gotta tear my eyes away. I can't read this
whole article right now. That's just rude.
That's just rude.
To my listeners and my guests.
I haven't been posting on the website much lately,
but I do make YouTube videos
sometimes.
I saw you made a video
talking about or
showing off all of the
enemy descriptions
in Mario RPG.
And you got Cybershell to voice them.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, that sounds...
That sounds great.
I want to see that video.
Yeah, that was
that was a very
time-consuming project.
I could see that.
That's in decent views.
Okay, I'm gonna check this one out.
Enemy thoughts
in Mario RPG.
That's awesome.
In Mario RPG, you have this ability
where you can see the enemy's
one-on-one. Yes, Psychopath.
Very interesting name for that.
Yeah, Malo's Psychopath ability.
You know, I remember
when I was a kid,
my dad is a psychologist
and I played that game and I saw that ability
and I didn't know what that word meant
and I asked my dad like,
hey, what does that mean?
He seemed disturbed by the question.
I
feel like it's some sort of mistranslation
because shouldn't it be called telepathy
or something?
Because Malo's reading the guy's minds, right?
Yeah, it would be...
Yeah, the name doesn't make sense.
What's the word when you read people's thoughts?
It's not clairvoyance.
Oh, not telepathy.
Telepathy is telekinesis, right?
No, telepathy is when you can
speak with your mind.
But reading other people's thoughts
is...
there's a specific word.
Is it clairvoyance?
No, clairvoyance, I think, is like
seeing and fearing at a...
No, it's seeing at a distance.
You're clairvoyant if you can like see what's happening somewhere else
from where you are.
I think so. Wait.
Clair...
clairvoyance is...
That's how it works in Psychonauts.
Oh, perceiving things or events
in the future or beyond normal sensory
contact, okay.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Okay, I guess it does include the future.
Regardless,
I saw the ability
Psychopath and Mario RPG
and I thought I was going to get some fucking badass
sicko mode move
and then I just got the
bestiary move, basically.
Okay, no, you were right.
Telepathy encompasses
both speaking with the mind
and hearing others with your mind,
so there you go. Yeah, that makes sense.
Telepathy is what they...
I don't know why it's called that.
It's pretty baffling.
But I actually...
I think the last time I was on
the PCP
I mentioned I was working on
a new project,
the video.
Yeah, probably.
And I don't remember if it was on the episode
or off the episode, but I described...
Let me see your channel.
I kind of, like,
described it ambiguously.
You know, so this is
that video I was working on.
That was months ago.
Because I basically wanted to make a video
that would contain, you know,
the old gamer's tavern humor,
but wasn't a let's play
video.
Because let's plays aren't really
that popular anymore.
So you mean it's this Mario one?
Yeah.
Listen, I'm excited
because Mario RPG
is one of my favorite games
ever, and I don't know,
just I want to
hear jokes about
the things that are in it.
I'm the market for this.
It was basically the inspiration
was to, you know,
pick a game that a lot of people like,
but show something off
about that game that a lot of people don't know
about, including people who do
like it.
I'm certain there are some messages
in here that I've never read before.
Yeah, and then also combine that with
the gamer's tavern humor
that everybody knows and loves.
Okay.
We'll link that
in the description. I will watch that
after the podcast is over.
I want to consume
that content. It was a pretty
ambitious project, you know, because I had to go
through all the enemy
dialogue, which was
I think there's around 210 lines.
Is there
I was going to ask how many there are.
There's 210. Do you do like commentary
on each one? I kind of do
like a quick rapid fire joke
or comeback on each one.
Hmm.
I don't want to spend too much time on each one
because the video is already 28 minutes.
I understand.
So I got a cyber shell to read
the enemy lines.
It's a good
that way it's a, you know, he reads
a line and then I respond to it.
Basically the gist of the
video.
Ah,
it's on my list.
He did. He did a
lot of work, you know, so
yeah, major thanks to cyber show.
Yeah, to read 210
line. So that's
quite an ordeal.
Man.
I want to read lines.
I want to read lines in people's videos.
And I was pretty
surprised how quickly he
got all the lines done.
Is that I kind of just ask them
and then by like a day
later, a couple of hours later, he was
done with all of them.
Oh, wow. Does
cyber shell just like
I see I hear his voice popping up in a lot of
videos. Does he just like
I don't know, does he
like advertise that like that's
something he does or do you just
a lot of people ask him to do that.
I think they can just ask him. Just because
they've heard him in other stuff and they were like, let's
get that guy.
I don't know, but I got
him because
first of all, I know him and
we know each other and
I was
inspired actually to make this video from one
of his videos. He did a video on
the
NPC dialogue and Sonic Adventure
and that's where I got the idea
for this video.
I'm trying to remember if I've seen
that cyber shell video.
I think it came out like last year or something.
I feel like I would have seen it, but I don't
really remember it, but
okay.
He just seemed pretty appropriate
and he's
pretty good at reading lines. He has a way
of doing it that's kind of funny.
So that's what I needed. I needed
a funny reading of enemy
dialogue and Mario
RPG.
What we need is a Mario RPG remake.
We need that
remake. We need an HD. We need Over the
Folder.
You know, actually
when I was a kid, I was really disappointed
that we never really got a sequel
to Mario RPG.
Paper Mario
is supposed to be like the sequel, but
it's totally different. It doesn't feel
anything like
the original.
I'd say Mario and Luigi series is closer
to capturing the Mario RPG
feel, especially since
Alpha Dream was made of
X Mario RPG
devs.
It doesn't play the same
because you play
Mario and Luigi instead of
Mario and Luigi.
It's still not quite the same.
There's something missing.
I always
was just like,
why wasn't there another one?
I didn't get a
N64 so I couldn't play
Paper Mario.
Was Paper Mario 2 on the N64?
It was on Gamecube.
I didn't get one of those either.
I'm a little younger
so I was more attached to Paper Mario.
I only played Mario RPG
when it came on Virtual Console
and I thought it was alright.
I did eventually go back and play the Paper Mario
games and they're good and I like them.
But they're not the same.
I do like the Paper Mario games as well, but
they lack the feel of
Mario RPG.
I did have
Game Boy Advance.
I did play
at least the first
Mario...
Mario and Luigi.
Superstar Saga.
That's good.
The good thing about Mario RPG
not really having a real follow-up
is that it will remain
forever distinct.
There's nothing like it
and it seems like
there will never be anything like it.
Can you imagine
I don't even know
if I would want them to
try to follow it up?
Yeah, that's a good point.
Sometimes a sequel or
a bunch of sequels can kind of ruin
the legacy of the original.
Especially now,
30 years later,
I just think
they couldn't do it.
Whoever
made that game
is no longer the same.
Those same people don't exist.
The world is such
a different place that it would never
be the same.
So whatever.
Just...
There's no hope
of ever fully
recapturing the magic exactly.
So just leave it.
It's always going to be different.
Yeah.
I think the reason for that is because
Mario RPG was co-developed
by Square
and Paper Mario
was made just by Nintendo.
Yeah, intelligent systems.
It lacked that Square touch.
Yeah.
There's no Qlix.
Yeah, Qlix isn't in it.
There's no Qlix. Mario's
Paper Mario is not the sequel
because there's no Qlix.
I mean, I don't know.
Did Square write
the dialogue?
I don't know how to...
It didn't...
Chrono, you might know this.
The Final Fantasy VI
localizer Ted Woolsey
write the dialogue for Mario RPG.
Well, you mean translated it, right?
Yeah.
I think so, but I'm not...
For all intents and purposes, his dialogue
in the English version.
Yeah, he's known for...
He did Final Fantasy VI
and also Secret of Mana.
Yes.
Maybe he did more RPG,
but I'm not positive.
Let's see.
I think... I know Ted Woolsey.
But I think
maybe Square wrote the script for the game,
the original Japanese script.
Yeah.
I kind of doubt that Nintendo did.
Yes, yes. He did.
He did...
He did translate Mario RPG.
Yeah, that makes sense because he translated
most of the Square's big games back then.
Yeah.
Seems like Mario RPG
was his last translation
job for them.
I think I read
in an interview with...
I think it was Shigeru Miyamoto
when Square wanted Mario to have a sword.
Yes.
It was against that, so he told them
to change it into a hammer or something.
Wait a minute.
The story I heard was like
he was presenting it at
like a conference or something and he
this sounds fake. This sounds like a fake story.
But he was like giving a presentation
to an audience and he showed
a slide of Mario with a sword
and a slide of Mario with a hammer.
And like
the audience cheered louder
for the hammer or something.
I swear I read that somewhere.
I didn't hear it like that, but I don't know
maybe that's what happened.
That sort of sounds like another story
with Miyamoto from around
that time when
Rare was making Donkey Kong 64.
They gave...
You can see this in previous footage, so this is real.
This happened.
You can see Donkey Kong
with like a realistic gun
because he has the coconut gun
that fires and spurts.
Well originally they were just going to be real guns.
And
when they showed it to Miyamoto
he was apparently really
surprised and offended
that they would give him a gun
which apparently...
Why would you do that?
So instead,
when he saw that
he came back with
a little quick drawing
of him with like a coconut gun
instead and they just did that.
So it sort of sounds similar
to that story. I don't know
if you got stories mixed up or anything
but I could totally see
something like that happening because
90s game development was fucking wild.
Yeah.
Hey, you want to know a fact.
When translating Super Mario RPG
Woolsey wanted to name
Punchinello James Bomb.
Though the idea was nixed.
One reference to James Bond
Punchinello introducing himself
as the names Nello
Punchinello remains in the final game.
I didn't know that.
It's pretty interesting.
I would be curious
to know
what...
if someone has ever re-translated Mario RPG
to be more
a more faithful translation.
And to see if the translation
is just like really dry and lame
and that like
Woolsey is what
kind of helped to make that game's
style feel so...
That would be really interesting
actually.
I heard that was a case for Paper Mario.
The original Japanese script was
boring and then the translators
they added a lot of humor
and references
that weren't an original script.
I...
I know there's a few stories like that
where like the original
the original
script was just kind of
bland and it was
quote-unquote punched up in localization
for better or for worse. Mostly for better.
I think that was
mostly in the thousand year door
sequel.
I could see that. Not to say
that the original Paper Mario wasn't funny
or anything or charming
as it was but like thousand year door
was a lot
quipier I'd say
in a good way.
I like thousand year door
who doesn't like thousand year door?
Also in the last few years I found out
something that I didn't know about Mario RPG
was that the soundtrack was composed
by Yoko Shimamura
I think her name is.
She's the one who did Kingdom Hearts
soundtracks later on.
And Street Fighter 2.
She's like
video game royalty.
She's very very good at what she does.
She's been doing it for a long time.
That's from what you said.
Sorry.
I used to think
that Mario RPG was done
by the typical square
composer of the time. His name is
Nobuu Umezu.
Yeah, Uematsu.
I didn't know it was actually
Yoko that did it
recently. But it makes sense
because it does sound like her music.
She has kind of like a signature
style.
Shimamura also did
what else did you say?
Kingdom Hearts.
That's what she's most known for nowadays.
She also did a Legend of Mana
for the PS1.
And actually there's a track
in Legend of Mana that sounds exactly
like a Mario RPG track.
Which Mario RPG track?
It sounds like the Mushroom Kingdom one.
Okay.
It's the magic city
track from Legend of Mana.
Let me see if I can find it.
I'm trying to remember how the
Is that?
I know that one.
Mario Kingdom or the Mushroom Kingdom?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's something like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, if you're playing a RPG,
fuck that chest
that you can only get in that one room
by jumping on that one toad's head
that runs through that room one time.
And you can never get the chest again.
Yeah, I remember.
And then your radar beeps for the rest of the game.
Okay, that always
stumped me as a kid.
I never know this.
Her first project was Live Alive.
She just got a remake recently.
What is Live Alive?
She did the soundtrack to that game.
Live Alive was a JRPG made by Square Enix.
It never came out over here.
It was only in Japan for Super Nintendo.
It was directed by the Final Fantasy IV guy.
That's what he did after.
And it's basically like you play as like eight different characters in different scenarios
and it has like sort of like a grid based combat.
I think you would like it then.
I beat this game actually on an emulator back in like two thousand and three or four maybe
two thousand five.
Yeah.
It's kind of one of those like great like top five RPG games you never got one of those
games.
I want to play it.
Yeah.
It got a fan translation years ago.
I am.
That's how I beat it.
I beat it back then.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty interesting.
I am listening to this track.
It does.
It does sound.
Yeah.
I can definitely hear the similarity with the Mushroom Kingdom.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Actually I played Legend of Mana when I was younger and I never made the connection between
this track and Mario RPG until now for some reason but it does sound very similar.
Legend of Mana is the PlayStation one right?
Yeah.
It came out I think in either 99 or 2000 I think it was 2000.
I always get Legend of Mana mixed up with Dawn of Mana which I think is the PS2 one
that's apparently really bad.
Yeah.
I never played that one.
I rented Legend of Mana one time and I played it a little bit and I didn't really get into
it and I had Sword of Mana on the Game Boy Advance which I think is sort of a remake
of like Seikenden Setsu one.
Yeah.
It's a remake of that which was released here as Final Fantasy Adventure on the Game Boy.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean it's a big remake.
They changed a lot.
Yeah.
It's pretty different.
Hmm.
Um.
Video games.
I love them.
I have to pee.
I will be back in a second.
Go right ahead.
Well you know Legend of Mana is pretty interesting because it plays like Secret of Mana but I
think the gimmick is that every time you beat an area or a quest you can place a building
on the map and you can choose where you place the building and depending on how you place
the buildings it affects certain elements in the game.
The Mana series always seemed really interesting to me but I only I've only played Secret of
Mana for a little bit and Secret of Mana is I mean it's a it's a it's a game.
But I also remember watching your Children of Mana review.
Yes.
I have very extensive knowledge of Children of Mana which is probably not the best first
impression to the series.
Yeah I um I played that a little bit when it first came out and then I think in the
last few years I went back and I beat it you know it revisited and it's a it's okay but
it's kind of repetitive I think.
Yeah.
The the gameplay is really it really wears itself out very shortly.
I don't know there is something sort of captivating about it or at least there was when I was
a kid and it looks really pretty but um uh I it was one of those games I beat because
they had not because I really liked it and it's a it kind of is pretty fun for the first
dungeon or two but then after that it becomes way too samey.
Especially since they expect you to do like side quests where it just go through those
levels again.
Yeah.
Which is like uh I'd rather rather rather rather rather rather.
It does kind of feel a little bit like one of those uh I guess quick cash-ins because
is like they worked hard on the assets and building the core of the game but then the
rest of it is just uh copy and pasted side quests.
Yeah and the story isn't really anything to write home about either.
But uh in my opinion one of the best mana games I think is Seikend Incense 2 3 which
hmm try to localize right as trials of mana here.
That was another one of those games that it kind of like Live Alive was one of those like
never ever games which is amazing that it got localized.
Yeah I uh I beat that game in 2014 uh because it got a fan translation I think around that
time maybe a few years earlier.
We hadn't before.
No actually I had an old fan translation from the early 2000s.
Oh that was like a shitty one though.
And I just didn't get around to beating it up to 2014.
Oh alright alright.
And I published a review on it uh on my website back then you know that's the only reason
I remember I beat it in 2014 because the review was written uh you know so that one is really
good.
I was very impressed by it.
It's something I want I want to try.
I bought that mana collection a couple of years ago and I played a little bit of Trials
or Seikend Incense 2 3.
I was playing with my uh with my brother though and you know to co-op in a game like that
you kind of have to like align schedules and then it's like uh if I want to play and he
doesn't want to play kind of shit out of luck so it just kind of never really got off the
ground.
Yeah that's right.
I played it.
Oh welcome back.
Yes.
That's the issue with these games is that uh if you can line up your schedule so that
you can play with a friend or two every time it's probably going to be like one of the
greatest experiences but if you can't do that you know most people can't do that uh then
it's not going to be as good but it's still pretty fun as a single player.
What are we talking about now?
You know uh Trials of Mana Seikend Incense 2 3.
It was uh it was a Mana game that came out on the Super Nintendo but never came out over
here uh until like a couple of years ago when Square like dug up the ROM and localized
it and remade it.
Yeah I'm not sure why Square did that but uh pretty nice of them.
Uh yeah it was surprisingly uh surprisingly out of character yeah charitable cause like
you know they were remaking the game so they really had no reason to bother localizing
the original.
I see.
Uh but they did so uh cool now we have two versions of the game awesome.
Okay all right all right.
Yeah and I uh I beat that one in 2014 and also published a review for it back then.
Yeah this is really it's a really pretty game too.
Hang on wait uh Trials of Mana yeah Trials of Mana there there's uh the the Super Nintendo
version the the 3D remake they made uh I think I heard it was pretty good but it's definitely
kind of low rent compared to like your Final Fantasy 7 remakes.
Yeah.
But that's okay.
This not not everything needs to be like a huge dick.
Well I prefer the original artwork I think the original art is uh fantastic.
Yeah because at the time this was like the big dick triple A uh experience because this
is like some of the best looking like sprite art on Super Nintendo yeah it's a square game
so.
And the music's pretty nice too.
Yeah I should give this a try.
Why did is this the one where you turn into a werewolf?
I think that's one of the characters yeah one of the characters is named Kevin and he
turns into a werewolf at night and he gets pretty strong.
Oh yeah what man I think wait yeah you made it did you make a video about this chrono
this this game uh no I just uh wrote a text review of it.
Okay because I yeah I've seen this and like yeah the sprites look so good why would you
not bring this that it was so good it's such a good looking SNES game what a waste.
It was in the middle of that like time uh where RPGs still hadn't completely uh captured
the west yeah or at least so they so square assumed I I think they did at least by the
by the Super Nintendo I think the RPGs were doing all right for themselves uh because
I know I know I was playing like Final Fantasy IV and stuff or at least my brother was.
Okay they uh they claimed that RPGs weren't popular in the west but they didn't release
a lot of them here until later.
Yeah and like you know mana is like it's kind of like an action RPG but you know it's not
like Zelda and there's scary numbers in it so I assume we wouldn't like it.
Have you uh are you do you know do you know Secret of Evermore yeah I was actually going
to bring that up because that's kind of that I was just I just saw it recommended underneath
in the Google image search I just did and it just I I've never played Secret of Evermore
I just reminded me that like I used to see it on like the blockbuster shelf and I thought
the cover art was scary.
Uh that game is weird because it's um I don't really know anything about it just I remember
seeing it and being intrigued because it's square soft but also being like I'm unsettled
by this creature uh correct me if I'm wrong chrono but I'm pretty sure this was made by
a western studio.
Yeah it was made by I think a square of America at the time.
It was American division.
It was sort of like the it has like a contemporary setting sort of uh or you like time traveling
stuff the the whole point of the game was that like we need something that American kids
will like and that's yeah basically the the hook of the game.
And actually a lot of people in the early 2000s anyway uh hated this game because they
thought uh you know it wasn't made by the original Japanese square developers so it
sucks but uh I don't I don't think it's that bad it's actually pretty alright.
Seeing seeing the the cover art with this like blonde kid with what is he holding like
a bone yeah like like for his dog a wrench or something yeah his first weapon is a bone
that uh uses it's actually in that cover it's awesome actually I like this really captivating.
Seeing that reminds me of uh of um Star Star tropics uh which was like they made they made
that to be another like oh let's make a game that appeals to Americans yeah so we'll we'll
set it we'll make the kid like an all-american football player and we'll name him like we'll
name him like John Henry or something his name's uh uh Mike Jones the same yeah yeah
Steve Smith is something yeah what is what is the name of the guy in this like the American
version of Secret of Mana yeah I think I saw the name and I think I think I might have
assumed that it was like a sequel or something to Secret of Mana uh those are my two favorite
games on the SNES as a kid Secret of Mana and Mario RPG then you probably like uh Trouser
of Mana because it plays it's like Secret yeah I think I would I think I would have
loved Secret of Mana I can't I can't believe they didn't let me play it yeah it's it's
frustrating there's a lot of cool games we didn't get ever I think like Front Mission
Gun has it the real reason probably didn't bring it over is because it had a large script
so it would have been really costly to translate and this was uh in 95 so uh it was towards
the end of the Super Nintendo's lifespan yeah I'm sorry how much how much could how much
could it cost how much could it cost to translate all the text in a SNES game well well believe
it or not back then uh it was pretty difficult to translate text and games because uh I think
the the western developers they didn't have the same two owns that uh the Japanese developers
had to change the text it was kind of uh from a coding standpoint it was complicated yeah
you couldn't just like you know find and replace Japanese text and paste in English script right
like Tim Rogers talks about that in that Final Fantasy 7 video yeah they sometimes would have to
hack the game's code in order to make it work with uh different font sizes and stuff he I've seen
I've seen Let's Mosey yeah I know he talks about like having to I don't know he talks about like
having to do it through on like a spreadsheet he doesn't really talk about like the the technical
aspects of it I guess it makes sense that you might have to do coding at some point you might
have to actually go in and like fuck with it to make it display properly and and and etc I think
also a Japanese text is more condensed than um English so whenever you translate anything the
lines are longer and then they don't fit and then you have to figure out a way to make them fit
which sometimes requires hacking the game's code yeah you need extra text boxes probably
uh and so I mean I get I get that yeah back then like uh you can even see it on The Secret of
Evermore uh case here they're like they don't say anything about the game they just call it a 24 meg
action adventure just to say like oh it's it's the file size is big that means the game's good
like uh Secret of the Trials of Mana was probably like a really big game like a couple megabytes at
least and you know like the more yeah it's it's like nothing now it's fucking don't even
no please the thought four megabytes Jesus Christ that's like million that's millions of
but like back then like the more the bigger your game was the the more it cost to make the cart
so I assume they just saw like how huge that's actually that was and like that's one of the
reasons why Japanese RPGs on the Super Nintendo are so expensive to buy now because they didn't
manufacture many copies of them back then as as it was so expensive to make those cartridges
they're pricier back then too yeah they were costly sometimes you would have to spend like
80 or 90 dollars just to buy brand new I mean Nintendo game back then did well I mean um am I
wrong do do all the uh SNES cartridges not all have the same chips in them uh some it depends
there's a lot of uh Super Nintendo games now they have different chips some of them they have a
specialized uh hardware chips like the Super FX chip which is it's like basically a graphics card
or a GPU built into the cartridge that would enhance the Super Nintendo's uh graphical capabilities
when attached yeah it's it's how you got stuff like star fox yeah that's how the Super Nintendo
could do 3d polygons with star fox and then there's also uh you know the memory like uh
this secret ever evermore was on a 24 meg cartridge when they say they mean megabit not
megabyte by the way oh okay okay so three three megabyte game right here big deal
yeah did um I mean we're like we're rpgs like more data intensive than other than like platformers
yeah because they were bigger yeah worlds with more graphics to store and stuff I think um
they could have just made a bigger platformer then and lazy it would have been nice I think the biggest
Super Nintendo game is either Tales of Fantasia or Star Ocean it's one of those because uh because
those games straight up have voice acting in them I never played either of those and uh I probably
would have been stoked too but yeah yeah I think how do you put how do you put voice acting on a
SNES cartridge all right well let me tell you why would you do that just the flex seems insane
seems completely insane I think it really is Star Ocean had a special compression uh technology
that allowed it to store more data into Super Nintendo cartridge it's called sd something
yeah it's it's it's a add-on chip I think and uh a lot of like flashcards or whatever couldn't
replicate it for years yeah but I remember reading about either Tales of Fantasia or Star Ocean in
Nintendo Power in the late 90s and um back then they kind of made it seem like those games were
going to get released in the US eventually and then they didn't so I was um I was watching
which I was watching some Kim Justice video about it was about RPGs in Europe but specifically
about like a magazine there was like a particular European magazine that covered JRPGs and that like
that sounds cool oh yeah let me try and find that video because it was pretty it was pretty good
I think the magazine I read this stuff in was like game players or something and they changed
their name later in the 90s to get to what uh they renamed themselves but there were a lot of
really cool uh gaming magazines back then oh here we go here I found the exact video uh
Kim Justice the story of JRPGs in the UK before Final Fantasy 7 Super Play magazine that is such
like a niche topic yeah that's that's Kim. The UK had really bad luck even worse than the US when he
came to RPGs because the the history the history of uh of uh of platformers on this on the ZX Spectrum
I've only seen one Kim Justice video and it was I'm sorry to make fun of her voice
it's just very funny but I like her videos a lot actually I like this great I like the one I saw it
was on um Oasis's Be Here Now album so I thought she was I thought she was a music channel no I
haven't seen that one but I'm curious because I've only heard her talk about video games
I found her through her Peter Molyneux uh like like basically like the biography of Peter Molyneux
which is I actually just rewatched that the other day it's good yeah uh yeah I'll have to I'll have
to check this out yeah I think um I think the UK didn't even get Final Fantasy 6 or Chrono Trigger
uh they did yeah they got some sort I think they were not officially released but I think
there were there were like uh underground there were like indie venues that could potentially
provide you with with with hacks of some some games uh uh they uh there was a scene I think they
didn't get Chrono Trigger but uh they did get uh TerraNigma which is kind of that's uh that was
unusual is a US didn't get that one yeah yeah I I really want to play that one I still haven't
played it yeah I beat that one a couple years back and I also reviewed it it's uh quite good
uh I've managed to remain unspoiled uh about the game I hear the story is really good so I'm
uh curious to play it someday yeah it's um it's similar to Illusion of Gaia it's yeah it's made
by the Act Razor and Illusion of Gaia Dev's Quintet okay uh oh yeah Act Razor is fucking awesome
it's really good Act Razor is the one where you play as like the angel like you're recreating
society or civilization yeah I've I like only learned about these games through like um uh
speed uh uh what's the the speed convention there's speed running game game yeah games
don't quit okay I've seen people play them as games don't quit I'd never seen any of these before
yeah I really like uh I really like Soul Blazer by Quintet I think that that's like a really uh
competent action RPG from like the early SNES and I uh Illusion of Gaia I don't like as much
honestly yeah though it's it's a prettier game it feels a little less uh good to play I don't know
something about it but I still haven't beaten it which is why I haven't played Terranigma yet
well most people prefer uh most people prefer Illusion of Gaia to Soul Blazer but um I like
both of them both uh pretty good I don't know something about Soul Blazer I like how simple it
I guess it is compared to Gaia actually Soul Blazer has a gimmick in it that's pretty similar to
something from Dark Cloud yes it is similar I I do like Dark Cloud a lot so that might be why I
like it more it's like in Soul Blazer you you start out with an empty uh town that there's like
nobody there and then you explore dungeons and as you kill monsters in dungeons the town gets
repopulated yeah and buildings appear in the town as well and by the end of the game the town is
huge and bustling so Dark Cloud had almost the same thing uh for some reason I don't know if the
two games are related Dark Cloud's also kind of similar to Actraiser too I would you know because
you can build stuff as well now something about uh I really I'm really fascinated with Quinta
as a developer because they made really weird games back then when a lot of people like were
still figuring out like even like how a platformer works well these guys were making like sim action
hybrid games and they just kind of dropped off the face of the earth after the 90s I always
wanted to make a video like kind of like dissecting whatever happened to them but I don't really feel
like I have the resources necessary to do that well I highly recommend uh you try Tere Nigma
because it gets really interesting towards the end you know it's a very uh it seems like a
really fascinating game I have this is a really funny story I bought a cart a Tere Nigma cart
uh a PAL version of it and I have like a I have a super NT so I can just play a PAL cartridges
just fine I thought it was the English translation but it's the German I have a German cart of
Tere Nigma so I turned the game on I'm like oh I haven't but that's fine you just have to
learn German no big deal uh yeah but my my German is completely ruined is over I have
not taken German since high school uh yeah man those guys were cool
well you know what they say um 2d beats 3d any day of the week I was 2d 3d pd I was uh
I was just looking at I I was gonna complain because I thought uh I started at Mega Man
04 and I saw some of the in-game graphic or some of the in-game cutscene images and I thought
okay they don't this is not Toru Nakayama this is not drawn by Toru Nakayama they don't have
the guy they lost the guy no but I'm looking at this article and I guess that's not true like
Toru was still working on it he still drew like promo images and stuff for uh uh uh ZX and stuff
but some of the some of the art in that some of the art is definitely not from his pen maybe he was
like more of a backseat for this one more of a backseat more of a concept art he didn't do all of
the in-game cutscenes probably got some some schlubs to do some of it Ben they were they were
so caught off guard about the fan demand for a new Mega Man 0 they couldn't they were like oh we
didn't tell Toru that he was gonna have to make a game that actually finished the story like we
were just we didn't think it's really unexpected uh we didn't we didn't renew his contract oh god
now we gotta give him benefits for another year of this bullshit oh we can't afford him
let's just get an intern to like kind of trace just kind of copy his character designs for some of
these uh for some of these uh in-game for some of these cutscenes uh you'll never notice
um you know what i did yesterday you want to know this is not video games sorry i'm sorry
i went sailing yesterday oh if you can believe it yeah i went on well i wasn't really sailing
because there wasn't very much wind there was occasionally wind mostly the motor was on for
a lot of it but i went on a boat my uh my dad and my brother went uh deep sea fishing yesterday
so they were also on a boat deep sea fishing yeah they didn't catch much kind of a bust
like of a trip how deep how deep are we talking uh they just go like a i guess a couple miles out
from the from the coast to i'm like i'm like some schooner or something i don't know do they uh
do they dive into the ocean and use spears or harpoons to catch their prey
we got to go down in the mariana trench and find like get the like you know in um in uh uh
in the harvest not harvest moon something valley stardew valley in stardew valley you
catch the deep sea fish when you go down in the in the submarine or whatever and you catch like the
weird uh lantern fish and stuff you gotta go you gotta go way down for the really deep fish
that's what you want see i always know trade them for more for more for more money i always knew
i was doing something wrong when i go fishing i don't have a submarine that's what i need
a submarine yeah exactly you cut yeah uh uh yeah i don't know i just i went on a boat that's all
i'm sorry that's all i have to say i was on a boat how how would you get the boat uh my my dad
and his friend co-own a small sailboat together and they love it it's like it's like my dad's
a hobby basically that's cool him and his him and his buddy sail this boat it's their thing
and i haven't been like christopher cross or something christopher cross yeah sailing
yeah forget it never mind i'm not i'm not familiar someone someone in the comments maybe
we'll get it forget it doesn't matter the uh i hope you had fun on the boat i had not been on the
boat for i've got to be like 10 years now the last time i went to this i didn't go on the boat i
didn't get on it but the last time i saw the boat actually it was a different boat because they
they traded they like sold a different boat and they bought a replacement uh but uh the last
time i saw the boat was like probably five or six years ago and it was to film nate's footage
for a best anime ever one piece oh that that'll chest not great video by the way it was to record
i i stood on the dock in a recorded footage of nate on the boat and uh still waiting for that video
uh that's a pretty good use of uh of a boat if i ever saw one right that's production value
that's production value right there um yeah it's like a it's like a jon tron video
oh yeah it's exactly like that me uh me and uh michael from reps to go where we're sitting on
footage of of something we recorded like a year ago now for basically use whenever we feel like
using it i guess so it's maybe not exactly the same as you want to give a hint uh no i i think
i've already said too much all right it's just it's something we uh we met up at like last year
we did some recording fair enough just as like uh well we're together we might as well do something
for the channel i guess you know i yeah good point you know you know i binged reps to gog uh a while
ago oh yeah i watched the whole catalog yeah excellent quite and it's quite enjoyable yeah
i'm uh i'm hoping i think i think michael's just about the finish uh the kingdom hearts review
that's been a millstone around his neck for a while now god that's like a game that i've heard of
yeah it's i don't come to reps to gog for games that i've heard of uh me neither sometimes
did the whole thing where you're trying to review every ps2 game ever yeah you review every ps2 game
oh god it's a quite a massive undertaking it is how many games are is that i think there's a couple
thousand okay and how many videos have you made like 20 hey gotta start somewhere yeah yeah the ps2
has like more games and almost any console and a lot of the games are really long if you that's uh
that's kind of why we we did it because yeah isn't it the funniest game to funniest console to review
every game for the the the the sort of uh what do you call it sort of the unofficial uh the unofficial
mascot of it is sisyphus pushing yes yes yeah that that was it was a very inspired choice there
in my in the time uh i think last time i was on here i was saying i was gonna do an enter the
matrix reps to god which came out i saw yeah yeah i was gonna say you did that one and uh i recently
finished the digital devil saga 2 1 and i've been focusing on doing a uh a channel or a video
for my main channel it's kind of a big video so it's kind of just like very slowly chipping along
at that just kind of like it it's one of those things where as i'm making it i'm like oh my god
can i like actually do this or should i just like i'm still in like the i can still give up but i
really don't want to i want to i want to get it done and that feeling yeah that's how i thought
when i was doing the mario rpg video yeah it's uh it's a it's a commentary video i think that's
the most i want to say about it like you know like the mathematosis commentary videos yeah those are
like bar none my favorite videos on youtube and i like i love watching those and i always wanted
a commentary video for game i'm making one on right now and since no one else is gonna do it
i will that's basically it that rules i'll watch it yeah unless it's a game unless it's a game that
i really hate now you'll probably it's a pretty likable game the only problem i'm having right
now is that like i'm worried that there's kind of been a bit of like a kickback or a pushback
against like the whole like big video craze that's kind of been taken over youtube the past couple
of years you think so uh i i you know i see it every now and then you know the only the only
reason people push back against it is because they're popular and people like them i i think so too i
i think so they get haters i think it's you know there's like some uh fair criticism there where
it's just like oh it's a long video you're just you're repeating yourself you're it's just uh
it you're just uh synopsizing what's what happens in the game or the show it really yeah there's
some it really depends sometimes they can they they feel padded because they're repetitive and
sometimes it's just synopsis and those are two pitfalls that those kind of videos can fall into
they don't they're not all like that yeah it's some some of them are for sure it's something
i'm really trying to avoid when making my video uh it's pretty difficult to write a script at the
same time it is for so many hours yeah i do think i do think that a video if a video is long enough
it's okay for there to be a certain amount of repetition because it's certain certain concepts
will bear repeating like when they become relevant in multiple different like times in the narration
i don't so i i don't i don't i don't think repetition is is like is it is it is a mortal sin
but some of yeah some some it's a it's a pitfall it's okay it's something i can see the criticism on
but i also kind of it also sort of feels like you know these like big videos that people make on
youtube are something that you could only see online or like on youtube like uh you're never
gonna watch you're never gonna see someone talk about x thing for uh for like like four hours on
like on like an actual produced television show just no you know it's sort of embracing like you're
never gonna see uh uh somebody like cyber shall talk about uh the chow garden for like one or two
hours in a video exactly exactly and that's something i think people should uh should embrace a little
more when dunking on quentin reviews for his really long boring i carly videos or whatever i
i think that i think that all the criticism of those videos is completely warranted and yet
i like them yeah well you know sometimes like i just watched like a fucking six hour video about
lost which is basically the bill the billiam one yes i'm halfway through the the new billiam lost
video it's this is my this is my genre i will defend the long video yeah format i think it's great
i like that video a lot because it wasn't i mean it was sort of he was just sort of talking about
the plot of the show and he did himself a bit a lot of that is synopsis something i did like about
it is he also manages to talk about the pop culture about lost at the time which is something that
people who binge watch it like what i did uh won't really know seeing that like hey they literally
made magazines about what happens on this one show it's so weird or like all like the press
junkets where it's just like uh so who's the hunkiest on the island i get i i mean i get that
they're i get that a little bit just the just the sheer scale of it though yeah yeah it was huge
and is is hillary hillary clinton like name dropping it so so funny yeah it uh in an alternate
timeline that would have been the the pokemon go to the polls kind of yeah i think so form a community
to to find out what's what the heck is going on in loss i don't know it in the the pop culture
sections almost sort of justify the length of um yeah of the video because it's sort of it's
inadvertently tells you that lost was this juggernaut that never that like had had so much of a
following that uh yeah someone will watch a six hour video talking about it it it's interesting
i like i like that video quite a bit yeah it's nice to have that uh cultural context
because that's not something you're gonna get to be watch it now yeah reminds i mean um the other
one that jumps to mind is the jenny nicholson uh vampire diaries video which kind of goes into
huh i haven't seen that one it's good i know about it and it it it does it does just it does
describe the plot of the show it does summarize the show but it also talks kind of about like
production production uh uh things like what was going on with like the studio and the cast
and crew and the deal with uh like the original author and the rights to the franchise and and
all that stuff it's great yeah um but you always have to uh give like a promise of whatever it is
you're talking about you have to always at least describe some of the plot yeah yeah there especially
for our television show uh i'm just hoping to get this video done because i would i would like it to
be like a big i haven't i haven't made a video since or on the main channel since october so
i feel i feel like i kind of have to be like here's here's my grand return or whatever i would like
i would like for it to be a nice statement you you and me are in kind of the same boat then
because i have not put out a video in a long time well you're not primarily a video guy you
you're still not really along with the comic i have yeah i have done some other stuff in the
meantime but still you know this is kind of my yeah it's kind of like my return to youtube like hey
guys i finally sorry i haven't made a video in a while yeah and and mine is also going to be
it's gonna be pretty large i think is the plan so so i hope i hope the video goes well yes and
you're not gonna tell me what it's about yeah uh maybe after the podcast i guess okay when do you
i mean do you have a do you have a time frame in mind uh i i basically like i want it
as soon as it's uh as soon as i finish the script like the script i'm uh i'd say i'm like a little
under a third done and uh you know obviously i prefer you and stuff but uh since it's a commentary
video uh that the video editing part of it uh goes by significantly faster than um a regular video
would all right just because you're just kind of talking over your gameplay footage right yes yes
yeah yeah this video is gonna be uh scripted it is yes aren't you tectonic improv yeah ha ha
very funny you know you know funnily enough you know you know actually i am a little surprised
that like you'd fully script out like a commentary um because okay i've done i've done a few commentary
videos before i did a cave story one and uh a one on super mario land and uh when i made my cave
story video i think i made i was making videos like a year at that point and um basically i was trying
i was basically like looking over at matthew matosa's homework and being just like okay well
how does he do it and then just basically trying to copy him and i'm pretty sure that his demon
souls and dark souls commentaries are not scripted yeah which it like you can tell because of how
natural he sounds when he talks but like that is amazing to me is amazing that that man you know
through like several takes obviously but like he was able to talk and talk and he just has he just
has that much to say yeah it's really amazing and i tried to do something similar when i made
my cave story commentary and i think i got five minutes into into the initial recording and
just kind of like i stopped it and i was like this isn't gonna work and i i had i had the scripted out
well you could okay i mean were you planning to like commentate over like the full unedited
playthrough no no uh the for how big the game is it's definitely there's definitely going to be
cuts like a lot of cuts but yeah the the idea is still i still want the idea to sort of be like
this is a a playthrough of the game you were getting you were getting like the game and not
yeah this this is a substitute for the original product this is not fair use yes yeah yeah i i
intend to be uh taken down by nintendo yes for this for this video but like uh i'm looking at the the
on just like the raw footage right now and it's like well over 10 hours and like fuck that i mean
couldn't couldn't get me to write write something like that for 10 hours and make it interesting
oh so the video so the game is one that's over 10 hours uh putting that down in my
on my little on my little checklist yeah just cross-reference how long to beat.com
every game that can be beaten under 10 hours but yeah it's uh it's a it's a game it's a video game
it's honestly cool i can't imagine writing a script for anything that's several hours long
you know that's uh must be real hard and um you know you know i i mean i was thinking about it
it's actually i was surprised to realize that like an hour narration is only like 1500 words no no
10 minutes sorry 10 minutes is 1500 words right or or uh something around that it depends on how
fast you talk obviously so an hour long video then is only maybe like like it's like 9 000 words
which i mean is it's a lot to write but uh i feel like on a if you're really feeling it and you
really have a lot to say i feel like i could write 9 000 words in a day yeah uh like well my
cave story commentary was uh it was like a little under two hours i think yeah and it's 19 000 words
yeah yeah that's like well that sounds about right novel it's well below novel length
mm-hmm and i guess uh i just find it really hard because all my stuff usually is uh jokes one
after the other yes so it's not easy to write uh like one hour worth of jokes of course well it
helps that i don't try to i don't try to be funny in my videos most of the time it's it's i think it's
easier to write uh more or at least for me i i find it easier to write more dry analytically than uh
than to really have like a lot of uh humor or whatever put in because i mean you know i gotta
think of a joke and like you know think of joke takes a lot of time gotta be clever my the video
that i of that will not be named is it's it's not scripted it's not like scripted scripted i have
notes i have many bullet points and i have any anytime i for a few for maybe a month or two now
i have been every anytime i think of something funny that is relevant to the subject at hand
i open up a little i have a little notepad and i just have like a list of jokes and i'm like okay
i'll just i thought of a funny a funny joke i'll just write that or a funny thing to reference
i'll put that in there in roughly the the period and i'll just when i'm recording i'll just okay
make make sure to make sure to mention that make sure to not forget to actually this is uh this
is how uh larry david does his uh does curb your enthusiasm he mentioned it in an interview
yeah he walks around with a notepad in his pocket all day and every time he comes up with a joke he
uh jots it down and then when he goes home he transports everything into a larger notepad
and then he turns that into an episode huh hmm hmm i'm a genius so this is uh how a lot of
professional comedians do their uh come up with their comedy well i guess maybe that maybe that
tells me that i've i'm not completely fucking it up yet because it's kind of hard just to sit down
and just come up with jokes in that moment yeah no usually you come up with them uh
you know uh while you're going about your day every once in a while i have a little thought
and i'm like oh that's funny i'll write that down and then i've let them i've let them build up
for that's actually how i i do my videos as well i have a giant uh joke uh text file on my computer
with like hundreds of funds and it's almost the rosetta stone it's almost like it's almost like
creativity is like a is like an ongoing process damn it's all it's almost like yeah
hmm this is just learning learning so much about about life and about the artistic method
this is just this is like old pcp when we talked about uh being content creators remember that
remember that they're really really old pcp yeah the the early days pcphq guys any day now
yeah we just have to move everybody to the same location yeah everyone was at virginia beach
we're waiting for you chrono give it it changed every like five months ever here uh
you ever hear asperger's digi bro rap no no i haven't but it sounds uh sounds amazing
it's um did you record it before or after uh the the beatings alleged beatings i should
tell you let the alleged beatings give me a break there's no evidence there's no evidence on the
books i don't i don't i don't want i don't want to slander the man yeah uh uh uh he's a good boy
good boy you did nothing wrong uh the uh some might say there's no there's no this i'm i'm not
trying not to get too serious but there is no there is no credible there are no credible yes
yes yes um but anyway but anyway um in the in the digi bro rap i don't remember the whole thing
off the top of my head but i do remember there's some bars in there about pcphq and how it's
fucking stupid i guess uh he does have a point he he did have you know what he he you got a
handed to him just like ices you got a handed to him uh what were we talking about before uh
before that um something about uh video game activity is uh i love video games and i love
video games as well i would play them all day well i i actually hate them oh no i'll do you
want better i hate everything so is that yeah that's uh isn't that a youtube channel i saw i saw a
tweet the other day that was asking like what's a creator who's like lost their fame or lost their
their uh their cloud or whatever you know lost their audience yeah and someone said i hate everything
and like i don't i don't think i guess i haven't heard much about him in a while but like he's
got to still be big right yeah he he has um he has that podcast with uh yms and Ralph the
movie maker and then like that other podcast with his friends jar media yeah i was thinking of jar
media what's the one with with yms uh the sardonic cast yes yes yes so like he's still around and i
think he's still i think i think he still has like a uh a a dedicated fan base he maybe but
does he not put out like regular ihe videos much anymore that's a good question i have not
been subscribed i hate everything i just i was surprised to see that because i i never heard of
any like downfall of that guy uh but only one that comes to mind it's not a lot of stupid answers
to that question he doesn't upload a lot yeah he hasn't uploaded since or seven months ago it's the
last time he uploaded so i guess he just focuses more on uh it's not as long as me so yeah yeah
his focus is more on side stuff i think he's still you know he hasn't fallen off in like a in
like a way i would use is that definition is like a big career i feel like i'm like a
and what i was gonna say that was a jauntron way well jauntron still gets views his jauntron
does still get his public perception i think has fallen in in certain crowds his public
perception has fallen and i i mean i just don't think he's funny yeah i haven't in addition to
finding him personally repellent yes well he's i would say like he used to be but for some reason
he still gets a lot of views he does oh great great a under a does that guy even post anymore
i think he does at least somewhat frequently hmm um haven't heard a peep about him in a long
long time that's who that's who i think of when i think of like big creator who's fallen off you
know it's not all like old-ass let's players like to buskis or something oh i mean i think the last
thing i heard about great a under a was like that he had done some covid conspiracy yeah i think he
was like an anti-vaxxer maybe i don't want to sound sounds believable yeah yeah yeah the only the only
one i can think of is uh digipro well of course whatever i got replaced by somebody else whatever
happened to him you know what what where did yeah like what like what is yig studio and who is this
and who is this weirdo and like the the halloween costume i saw i saw people commenting and
here discord about uh i hope giga released like a video talking about like a bunch of
prominent uh anti-tubers and how uh like a history like a history of anti-tube yeah and
i guess trixie is just like kind of footnoted which is pretty sad in the grand actually that's um
that's kind of interesting how uh it trixie isn't mentioned into big anime sphere anymore
you know what it makes sense to me because she was always like never like part of that
she heard her brand was always being like i'm set i'm not like them i'm better than them and
now she and she got what she wanted i guess yeah i i guess yeah uh don't like her no sir
there you go no sir you guys thought you were safe huh you thought you weren't gonna get a
trixie reference well guess what you did it took like two and a half hours is that a trixie reference
is that is that a trixie reference oh bad stop talking about trixie oh my god i can't i can't
i'm too angry my feelings were to her sad sad but true uh uh well hey i was gonna suggest
that we could start a voicemail if you feel like it unless there's anything else you'd rather do
before that uh well actually there's one last thing i want to uh i want to show you okay it's uh
it's not really much to say on it it's just uh this is a really funny song oh fuck yeah there's
an n64 game called buck bumble where you play as a cyborg cyborg bumblebee with guns and stuff
yeah the song kicks ass and the most notable thing about this game is a title screen music
uh buck to the buck oh it's pretty uh pretty interesting i recommend everybody listening
to this to uh check that out i'm cringe i'm cringing i'm cringing i'm bumping my head
yeah that's uh that's kind of the intended effect well i don't know if they intended it but uh
that's the effect it provides i remember uh renting this game as a kid many years ago and i uh i went
back and i beat it recently and the only thing i can remember about it is this song uh i have so
it's not that good i have never heard of it ever uh well it's not it's not horrible but it's kind of
like uh playing it's basic yeah you know there's not much to know about it it's like lover
yeah but uh i completely forgot about this song until i played it again and it's uh
it's it kind of reminds me of like the dk rap from donkey kong 64 it's not as endearing as that but
it's no i would no definitely not but it's still kind of weird and gringy it's hey hey
why why did they make this yeah that that's exactly what i thought
what i was thinking to myself as i listened to this this is like a 3d collectathon like platformer
like an action platformer no it's like an aerial 3d shooter you fly around and you shoot at stuff
hmm i think it's kind of like those uh star wars games uh on n64
you shoot around uh you shoot shield generators to destroy stuff
it's uh basic like search and destroy kind of gameplay you know the game itself sucks but the
song is i think worth listening to well i'm i i now i can never unhear it uh
uh who would you call this like it's like drasta so okay okay i know it's uh i don't know
a jive jamaican guy singing for some reason i don't know why they they thought that was very
european yeah what what's what's them what's thematically yeah it's it's very a year a european
trying to do jamaican drum and bass yeah it's really what what what's thematically relevant
about this song to the game is is my exactly what's what's well what's the motivation here
his name is buck bumble and he bumped to the buck to the bump to the buck buck to the bum
bumble so he like he he bumbles and he bucks his name's buck bumble
yeah that explains everything so it's drum and bass i'm getting there yeah okay it is the 90s
it is the 90s we are in the 90s we are living in the yeek era and uh and buck bumble instead of
yeah instead of uh gushing about like like uh final fantasy and legend of zelda in that game
they should have been like super excited to play buck bumble on the n64 yeah why not you know
with music like this um you know the the sad thing is the rest of the music at the game
isn't like this at all oh lamb the rest of the music is like generic
that was weak would have been nice if the entire soundtrack was like this
it would have it would have at least it would have at least
been something to say about about buck bumble um yeah uh the the speaking of long videos you
know who hasn't made a video in a while uh well i think everybody in this uh in this call
accounts long video long video man hasn't made a video in a while um you might get it i might get
yeah i know you know this person i got thumb through my five billion subscribers
bum to the bum to my bum to my bum yeah i gotta i gotta bum to the buck bumble gotta
gotta buck my bumble real quick well it can't uh it can't be cybershell because he made a dreamcast
video not that long ago i think no it is not cybershell and i did see that dreamcast video
uh and i was uh entertained the sneaker has been uploading recently so i guess it's not him
yeah no uh although i haven't seen his newest uh output i don't normally watch his yakuza videos
because i don't really i'm not in that space i don't play it's fine i don't play them but i
i did binge all of his yakuza videos at one point so i guess somewhere in my mind i'm like
i'll watch another one if he makes more of yakuza videos but i haven't done it yet
uh all right you give up yeah i give up it's tim rogers it's tim rogers actually
yeah doh doi what'd he say he was uh what did cypes i was gonna say cybershell uh cyberpunk set
2077 came out review came out in like october last year hasn't been like a year it's been it's
getting close to a year i i'm yeah well doesn't he take a while to do his videos he does sure
well sure and he also said he was gonna not uh overwork himself on the next one which this might
be why would it take so long it's it's just funny that like the initial the initial action button
uh model was one video a month and uh isn't isn't that cute isn't that what a card
yeah yeah uh i mean he described yeah that's what he says he's gonna do in the final fantasy seven
review uh but then no uh then did he say the next one's earthbound right i think he suggested
the next one would be earthbound for season two i think he said that he would do an earthbound video
but i think the next one i think he says in the cyberpunk video that the next the next next review
is is uh it's some playstation game called like something my summer vacation oh some japanese
yeah yeah uh yeah i don't know what that is i'm looking uh that seems like it could be cool i don't
i've never played the game i'm really interested he said he was going to review final fantasy four
and i'm really i really want to see that one because i love final fantasy four did he say he
was going to do six uh i don't think he said six hmm it's his favorite six would be pretty
interesting i think yeah he wrote he wrote that i mean he i know he wrote that article at one time
about like uh the time about the time he bought final fantasy six i did find that and read that at
some point i should i should read more of his uh his blog or like his website i haven't read that
much of it i wasn't aware uh then he had a website with written articles yeah he does yeah i should
probably him and some other people it's not he didn't write all of the reviews on there but yeah
i should probably check that out as someone who also did that for like you know 20 years
maybe i mean i i can't speak i can't speak to the quality of what's on there
i read i read some of his uh i think it's like his top 100 games of all time and uh you know
i obviously i read some of like the the higher the higher ones i think um i think he puts another
world at number one which is uh another world's a great game and it's nice people talk about it
but i've seen i've seen a lot of i use this phrase lovingly i've seen a lot of highfalutin
critic types uh praising another world it's one of those years it is yeah i've never played it but
in fact i never even knew about it like when i was younger i first heard about it super nintendo
uh like platformer out of this world is what it was called in super nintendo yeah oh yeah it's
is made by the um uh eric chahi the uh part of darkness guy right i i beat that one recently
it's uh pretty interesting it's uh well it famously inspired uh eco that's oh did it you know what
one of its claims to fame and i didn't know that but i it seems obvious now that you say it eco
convinced miyazaki to make games so eco is responsible for dark souls ergo and another world
is responsible for dark souls i didn't know that i i'll i'll it's it's like it's one of those your
favorite game developers favorite games yes yes it's it's also it was also made by one guy so it
has that like sort of auteur feeling to it it's a cool game you can beat it like an afternoon
i think i've seen him i think i've seen a matthew mitosis video about another world
and i've definitely seen a lot of video about heart of darkness i don't know who
matthew did one on heart of darkness i don't maybe that's on another world maybe but he
oh wait he mentions another world when he's talking about abes odyssey yeah that's that's
what i that's what i'm thinking of i did i oh sorry i did a uh i did like a short little video on a
on another world in the g video so you maybe probably also thinking of that i might i might
definitely be thinking of that are we now getting to the point that the new sorry i'm sorry that's
i'm trying to change the topic but you finish your thought before i go on it's it there's a
lot of reviews out there of another world you know yeah i was just gonna ask are we now getting to
the point that uh the wait for the next action button has now been longer than the wait for
cyberpunk 2077 no are we are we pat how long was the wait for a cyberpunk review
oh oh you mean the review i thought you meant the game itself because the game no like 2038
no no no uh oh that's you know it's a good point i think it was only like eight eight months i don't
think it was a whole year yeah token between toky meky memorial and 20 cyberpunk toky meky came out
in january and cyberpunk came out i think in october uh yeah so it's close i can't do the
math right now but uh i think i think oh yeah yeah yeah because it's august so oh yeah so so yeah
it would be to be 10 months i think the yeah i think it's the same i think we're the same yeah
yeah yeah amazing it's uh that's not really that much time in the grand scheme of things uh i mean
after all yeah not really once didn't upload anything for like two years yeah but here's the
thing though i mean when the cyberpunk review came out it was like i mean how many combined
hours is it like 12 hours it's like eight hours i think yeah seven reviews some of which
encompass like an hour and a half some of which are like 20 minutes i had thought
that the next one would not be that size i was under that impression as well and i don't think
it'll be as big as the cyberpunk video but are eight you know he also could be uh he could be
like backlogging them you know so so they uh like he's recording footage for a bunch of different
games uh maybe if we followed his patreon maybe he he's more specific about their reviews yeah
used to do that i know he streams every friday for some reason it doesn't i don't feel like the
weight has been too excruciating for a new tim rogers video i guess because i was i mean i was
surprised to learn to realize how long it has been yeah no i don't disagree because it has been a while
he just thought i i guess i'm just surprised i thought it would be sooner but uh what i mean
you know whatever these things they uh they take time yeah uh i just uh i just and i'm not paid
and i'm not paying any money so i have no i can't complain god damn you yep i'm consuming the content
for free uh all right what do you think about a voicemail now all right let's go all right
let's go there's only like eight or nine i think um was it because they they all got sent to the
incinerator or people just weren't so talkative this week i i assume that uh yeah they stopped
being able to send them because the inbox got full i will i will empty out the old voicemails
from the inbox man what uh you're you're doing the voicemails in like what 2018
is that when you started there's gotta be some old-ass voicemails in there i
i there must be yeah there must be oh no i almost i hate to do it i hate to go back and and delete
well how am i gonna how am i gonna sort through 1.4 gigabytes and and not delete any of the good ones
i can't do it it's impossible it's impossible no i'm gonna i'm gonna have to just select all
delete like half of them yeah well you know they're immortalized in the the the podcast
episodes so you know they exist still you know what here's here's the the silver lining there
back in the day when nate was in charge of it so many of them didn't get listened to and they're
i'm sure there's so many hidden gems in there that will just be right in the trash and i'll never
know and i'll never have to mourn them because i will i'll never experience what i uh i sent a
i sent the voicemail once that uh nate decided wasn't good enough for the podcast i'm pretty sure
do you remember what it was about nate uh used to screen uh the voicemails yeah he did yeah
good good old days remember that he would he would pick out like a handful of them
um back when we back when the pcp cared about quality
hmm right yeah that was a long time ago my voicemail it was uh i forget why it came up but i was
talking about uh i think tom tom tommy oliver for for all the viewers who forget who that is uh
was said on like a podcast that like heart gold and soul silver is just like better in every way
to gold and silver or just like gen two's the best gen and i i basically just i'm actually
in a voicemail which you know fair enough that you don't play that because i think it was kind of
long okay okay uh i don't even remember what i said i think i i think i agree with them i think i
kind of agree with them uh i if if i listened to the specific podcast again i could probably get
the gears rolling again okay uh i won't i won't make you try it out yeah uh your old uh grievance
i think i basically just don't really like the level scaling and joto or the uh well well that's
not really that's not a problem that's a problem with both versions yeah it's something they could
have fixed though uh you know i haven't revisited them in a while but i've heard i've been watching
of some flygon hg hd videos and uh oh he's a he's a nuzlocke guy oh okay flygon hg and um you know
he talks about joto he really dislikes joto i don't dislike it i think specifically the the the
post like the like the specifically for nuzlocking he says like nuzlocking through konto after the
end game of joto he's like a slot he doesn't do it he doesn't include it i could see that joto
runs yeah that's uh that's famously where monkeys uh pokemon crystal nuzlocke ended
got wiped out by i think sabrina oh yes i remember that when i yeah what i'll see in days
the the uh yeah the the run that i played that that brunswick was originally from
i i think it's pretty weak i think i wiped to the uh to the evi girls in in like ho oh tower
whatever right whatever tower but doesn't run so i get killed by a wabba fat yes but he didn't
but i didn't wipe to the wabba fat oh no like like i well like i went on to lose that run
to the fucking evi girls like a chump i doesn't come again with you getting i thought the comic
ends with you getting killed by uh claire and blackthorn yes am i mistaken or is this like
artistic license it does i i changed the yeah i i changed from real life fair enough
no yeah actually that's the good point and i forgot that i did that but yes in real life
i wiped to the evi girls but like i didn't want to draw that this is like uh this is like looking
up the wikipedia the wikipedia article to the biopic and finding out like oh wait a minute rudy
didn't catch the winning touchdown what the fuck they just made that up for the movie no
what do you mean remember the titans isn't real uh the first voicemail is not a voicemail it's an
image i guess so here i'm gonna post the link uh for that um okay so i hear what i'm gathering from
this is that greenhouse gases are just going to go down see i don't know the the guy just posted
the image so i don't know what he's trying or what they are trying oh wait wait there there's a
caption here in parentheses it says they it says they did it so i guess this is i still i
congratulating them on the reduction in greenhouse in us greenhouse gas emissions
i mean well it could also be ironic but i don't really know what i mean i know that this this
act this inflation reduction act just got passed by the house i don't know if that means i think it's
the last good that's senate doesn't it oh and it might just the trajectory down towards the
paris target yeah good just better than nothing i know that uh midgar produces a lot of greenhouse
gas emissions so we need to we need to do something about that city what uh here listen to the the
avalanche conspiracy theorists uh look the lifestream is perfectly renewable energy it's fine
we elected joe mansion because our mako reactors if we close down the mako reactors you know then
what about our jobs what about our jerbs we're gonna lose we're gonna lose all our all our all
industry to nibbleheim uh uh those the those god damn wutai soldiers they're gonna take all
our jobs this communist wutai you know the wood the wood the wutai are manufacturing eco we gotta
stay we gotta stay even with them they're gonna overtake us if we don't uh if we don't keep if
we don't keep sucking up the like sucking up mako we gotta keep we gotta keep the mako make
the mako flowing i stand with president rufus president rufus has said that he president rufus
has said that you know uh we as americans we have to embrace diversity and we have to really formulate
a strategy to form a committee to make an inquiry into the possibility of future greenhouse future
lifestream uh uh ref refinement uh reductions with targets set as as early as 2075 so uh you
know the leaders they they've got to handle don't worry about it it will be renew completely carbon
neutral by year you're never going to see like so like stop complaining we will be lifestream
neutral we will be we will be we will be putting as many uh dead people's souls back into the
lifestream as we are sucking up power but devouring them to create a materia
by the time it happens you'll be part of the lifestream exactly so so they say and that's a relief
and isn't that just a relief and that's a good thing you can you can peacefully go into the
lifestream knowing that you will uh your your contribution will offset will eventually offset
the amount that you used uh in your day-to-day life while you were alive before you yourself are
uh you know harvested to i don't know yeah power some power some fucking tube or gasket or whatever
your soul would be harvested harvested to power some guy's uh private jet to keep to keep uh to
keep to keep janova safely in that tube uh okay the next next voicemail is called uh uh where did
i put it here next voicemail is called owls there it is three two one go hello i am an australian
sorry on behalf of the great nation that is australia i demand that summer isama is made
voice grail what but don't just take it from me oh listen to my friend here yeah
you are
samurai's back i think it's the real i think it's the real McCoy you know what i
i i feel graced to to get a samurai voicemail i love i i'm an og samurai fan you know what
how is samurai not voice grail that's the only reason i'm confused i i said like last episode
someone pointed out samurai sama was not voice grail and i said well that seems like an oversight
i should fix that and then i forgot to fix it so uh no i swear i swear i'll do it you can forget to
fix it again it can be ben's weekly reminder to put voice samurai sama and voice grail uh okay
you know what good good good good message good message thanks samurai konichiwa uh next voicemail
is called um question okay three two one go hey new to the show uh wow i'm so sorry gib are you two
dating well hey aben and nate are you two like actually brothers or do you like just call each
other that because you're like black like what's going on there somebody asked that somebody asked
that one time he thought he thought yeah he thought that me and nate were black and that's what we
called each other brothers it might have been a joke it might have been a joke but like how can you
tell that's a good joke if it was a good if it was a joke it was a very funny one um but anyway uh
uh not yet wink not yet wink that's my answer long distance it never works never works but maybe
but it but it might for us but it but it might for us you know they're always just they're always
just diluting themselves you see once once you get work for us once you get php uh pcp a hq
going then it'll be possible then we can get then we can get married for the tax rate you know what
my dad asked me and this sucks i hate this but my dad asked me if i was gonna get married and i said
and i said i don't know and he said and then he pressed the question which i didn't like so i uh
so i responded with uh that i i that i would love to get fake married i would love to get
fake married just for the tax write-off and then my mom was like there's not really a tax write-off
i was like what i guess there's not there's really not that much benefit to it the best
the best benefit the best financial benefit reason is that uh you and you and a spouse together
might uh qualify for like a lower tax bracket but um there's not i thought there was like a
bigger i thought there was like a bigger standard deduction that you get if you're married but no
it it's it's you get double the standard deduction that's because it's two people filing jointly so
like it it's equal so what a fucking ripoff well just uh just remember if you do get married
be sure to livestream uh uh well it's i would say i would say the real the real uh reason
for you and give to get married is so like you could get the the green card right i mean that's
the real that's the real prize not the tax just like just like my conspiracy theory that raw that
the holly and ross's marriage was a green card a green card yes as far as i'm concerned it's it's
true it's it's true to me and that's all that's all i need that the the did i ever explain that i
probably explain i i vaguely remember this uh because ross is canadian right australian australian
okay well you know it's the same thing yeah yeah right my my my my my completely spurious uh uh
claims just based on like uh i don't know just based on that the i think i think holly described
herself as asexual uh before well so i remember i mean i mean i guess i know i know i know asexual
people can have sex and be horny and be sluts and and well i don't even i don't even mean that i
just mean like you know you can marry someone and still like like them love them i i i i i
my claim is not even that they don't like each other in fact you would have to like someone a
lot to uh marry them just to get them a green card i suppose you would yeah it's kind of
a commitment yeah exactly okay yeah sure you know what i don't know truly truly i am speculating
on matters that i have no insight into whatsoever but that's the fun of it you know that's that's
the best kind um next one is oh it's a vocaru link uh from fuck best guy ever dot mp3 at voicemail
dot doid it's it might be him the gas i think i think it's him it might be him uh before before
you you start this i i have a confession to make uh i'm sure your doid gazer they have right uh
okay i'll go on kb farms uh true true uh i actually asked to be on this episode because i got a dm
from doid gazer saying he would like for me to be on this episode really yeah really yeah because i
also uh i got a tweet from doid gazer asking me to be on this episode as well wait really curious
uh yeah i posted a screenshot of it uh earlier and uh oh wait oh yeah no i remember i i did
okay i mean so i did a big confession i'm sorry i ben i came on here for doid not for you no
well now now i know sam now i know same what you really think okay well let's i guess let's give
it a listen uh three two one go
hell he's our we want to cut this one out
mix with self shame and tip means my main man nates guy grow man of panelism
i've read your dog sesha over with birds prius i'd say for his death like i say for verge penis
you're getting into the protagonist of a jrpg and your content is worth less than ripple x rp
so kill yourself it's a critical responsibility go eat a can of beans like you cramadol and creatine
and cramadol down like a gonzo slam and mescaline oh shit right i said the word gonzo gonzo it's
better with nate gonzo gonzo gonzo it's better with nate gonzo gonzo gonzo it's better with
nate gonzo gonzo it's better with nate gonzo the gamer zone is just a version of pcp and talking
pirate needs to be flushed out of the potty me and my friend were stretching me to ask them
mindedly and we agile uh was just another scandal you couldn't keep but you don't get it you want
your normie life you want your age and wife that's some ellie roger looking tids man and that's all
right shit i get it not here to fight about who's wrong on the right but you voted for trump
twice and you mind all night your head would look good and paled on us fight with some sunglasses
your friend are left in hindsight screaming on your worst night keep that bestie boy butt
tight in the five inch joint pipe i'm sick of your glasses i'm sick of your tactics you're as
faking as plastic as the gas stations and glasses you went back to code because you blew all your
loans too quickly and burned out like an origami so i thought it was funny
fridely quick i'm fluttering gonzo gonzo it's better with nate gonzo gonzo gonzo it's better
with nate gonzo gonzo gonzo yeah bars bars with bars spit it you didn't even make a smash video
in corn not in what's wrong with you fucker or minecraft steve everyone complains about trippy
dropping off but you're worse can't wait for you to continue not acknowledging anything you
fucking coward you fucking make bit look good in comparison oh snap so that's good
fucking noro typical normie weight slaves cocked is come this has been a ygg production
baby do you have anything to say
say patreon.com slash
i heard something uh oh that was the that was his kid because he has a kid yeah yeah he he
he's every once sometimes he does that uh in more recent times he'll just give the baby a
microphone if you like say something this is a this is getting voice grail from me i yeah surely
he's already i think doid is already voice grail but uh if not yeah i mean he can he can multiply it
he makes a good point though why why didn't nate make a he should have made a kingdom heart
smash video i yeah i mean that's silly it's silly you should do that maybe it was uh too much
pressure because you know he's a kingdom hearts guy and he did those smash videos it makes too much
for him well he needs maybe he needs to take some personal fucking responsibility and uh and and
take up the mantle he needs to make that smash video before someone else does
now now it's timely before it's too late before it's really the clock is ticking sore has been out
for a year two years now yeah okay if it's five years i'll be too late yeah uh well if you wait
20 years then it becomes nostalgic again so maybe that's playing the long game playing the long
game he won't make it now he'll make it 20 years from now uh uh when the audience has aged up and
has uh and has more money you see hmm that's uh that's a ticket uh this was uh pretty good uh
pretty good rap pretty good bars uh i guess uh that's why uh uh mr doid wanted me to be on here
so i can uh be graced with this uh majestic work of art i'm uh i'm a well well known outspoken doid
gazer's fan yeah he uh yeah me too all farmers are bastards except one that's do it that's right
i think yeah yeah that's pretty much uh that's pretty much where i land on it uh
uh i'm i'm honored thank you thank you doid thank you doi i'm honored to receive this uh
this work everyone should follow doid gazer is it doid gazers on twitter at doid gazers
i think it's doid gazer yeah okay yeah uh anyway it's not should should uh should check them out uh
on uh i'm i'm trying to i'm trying to remember the lyrics and try and think about which was my
favorite was it was the funny it was the biggest laugh was the biggest laugh that got out of me i
can't remember sorry everyone my diss track against best guy ever has broken the bcp voicemails
prophetic that gets that gets me he was the last uh voicemailer
he was not quite there are a few more after but shortly after that i think yeah it ended
they were like they were like they heard that and they were like oh shit we've let these people
have too many voicemails over the limit we were we were being generous but uh no no more this this
can't this can't be allowed to continue all right uh doid gazer i'm giving him i'm giving him
that retweet again gotta get this shit and that's uh it's a tweet where he asked me to be on this
episode all right yeah i do yeah you did post it before i i forgot but um okay all right i'm
still real i'm still reeling from that last one but we've got a the show the show must go on uh
so uh let's take a look at uh okay this next one is is called there's 20 something images
oh this guy yes it's more of uh vinnie oh is he been posting them he has been uh yeah he's he
usually uh deposits them in a uh i like the tom and the wheelchair it's pretty funny he looks
like a home sir runner character but this is a this is pretty good artwork maybe you should hire
this person to do your comic for you you mean um is that still uh the dojin
yeah yeah drinking drinking moth drinking moth has has started uh drawing some of it
um and they're coming and they're really good they're coming out really good and i'm uh that's
good yeah yeah um sims is doing a page as well it's kind of a crazy that you're still releasing
radcon reward stuff yeah uh it's a little stupid it's a little stupid and fucked up but uh i won't
ever let it go until it's done so uh you know that's that's you're a man of integrity that's right
what does it what is what without his word you know what is what is a man even worth
wait a minute i don't mean to post that one there's there's 20 something images but some of these are
some of these are repeats some of these are like like zoomed in uh shots of larger pieces this one
i like the clipboard it adds a lot this i this one of uh of uwu poti is uh truly delightful
yeah these are good these are uh this guy's evolving oh yeah oh no tom no tom tom this
is i'm sorry but this is what happens when you this is what happens when you betray the pcp and
you run off to uh hang out with uh richard friends you know you uh you get you get fucked up
uh you get your legs broke uh uh what a shame what is what a shame yeah what a shame but uh you
know don't say it don't say i didn't warn you he was a good man uh for yeah he was you don't
know you don't cross the pcp because then uh that's something you're not gonna walk back from
what is this dragon i think they just he just gave tom a dragon i think i think he just wanted to
draw a dragon uh well this is the the sorceress that was lost i don't know i can't i can't i
can't think of it i was trying to think about tom references oh it's tom tom's jojo stand
spinal tap that's i saw i saw that that's clever that one's pretty good yeah
with each spine gained the user grows stronger and more mobile each spine adding to the arms of
the star and multiplying its strength by tenfold the limitation and release of this power is
is when the user steps on a crack so this has its own lore behind it this guy yeah he's he's
started uh he started doing uh jojo stands as well uh wait i'm just gonna post that i'm
trying to post like the most zoomed out versions of all of these sorry some of the some of the
the ones that i'm posting are repeats and then most of the man most of these are about tom
and that's lame what about me it's the tom arc
tom gets a heart because his spine sure doesn't does that make sense
hello yeah okay
he's uh tom's uh the pcp favorite
not anymore not anymore hey gib want to go with me and have a podcast together to tom i
i oh god i wish he would just post these all as one image tom i you you know i'm podcasting
with ben podcast with me and i can show you a world without an ounce of gas gas that is always
about another woman gas that heats that that heats ben to his core unlike anything anyone
any or anyone else in the world in our podcast it will be only you and me gib join me in podcasting
as my co-host with exclusivity to tom hey gib have you seen the new regional variant of whooper
look at this little guy yes are you okay gibbon tom isn't behind me is he no he's not no one's there
okay y'all you're gonna be okay yeah i just need a minute tom is so unsettling with his rippling
muscles i'll get you yet gib and take saver spark spaghetti supremacy will rise yet i don't get it
uh pokemon huff huff let's complain about these pokemon gib shut up ben but the pokemon's
okay um and then we've got one drawing of simsie fart ha ha how much of a simp do you have to be
to do something like that there he is uh i'll have to he did not include a single just big
shot of the whole comic so that's inconvenient i'll have to post this like a pcp fan fiction
yes yeah it's becoming more and more common for some reason more and more of the voicemails are
i think this but this must be inspired by by new the comics about me and gib with the
sounds like a real pcp episode if only um okay uh delightful uh tom is strong and scary and that
is what we've learned today uh the next voicemail is another vocaru uh three two one go my hope is
that that you know that kind of frequent content thing like best ever will be the things people
are really hoping to see for me uh and then like the pcp the potty cast uh and of course
content being like the new place for the faster content the stuff that's about you know timely
releases that me and digi can whip up stuff about um i mean yeah you could probably find a gold
mine of uh of old pcp episodes where yeah things someone said did not exactly pan out as planned
plan oh wait a minute are you telling me are you telling me that these that these plant that
these well-laid plans gong agree what the fuck next you're gonna tell me that the best laid plans
of mice and men often go awry that doesn't know i wouldn't i wouldn't uh uh that's funny to hear
the um uh i mean content was frequent content was frequent when it happened
yeah i guess i don't really remember but yeah it was it was it was frequent ish
i can't it's hard hard to hard to really i would lay the blame on nat not for ending
content but for beginning it uh i would say it was the mistake there uh uh and then uh and then
you know everything else oh oh yeah potty cast dead uh law okay what was the other one he said uh
did he say bestie boy the side channel i don't know if anything's uh he said the pcp was uh
oh the pcp oh that's that's you know he's he's extricated himself i don't know i mean uh
listen i can't explain why people do the things they do i'll never know and neither will name
and he not he just he just refuses he will simply he will simply refuse to speak on the matter
uh you get it like a another job again recently no one knows you want to explain uh i don't i mean
to be honest i don't i don't really know like i don't really talk to him about it much he doesn't
like tell me things i don't know i i do kind of know what's going on with him but i feel like
he wouldn't appreciate me like divulging what he's up to and stuff i just uh it's nothing
remember he made a big i don't i don't really have it i don't really have anything like a
super interesting to say but uh just remember uh when he started doing a bunch of youtube videos
he made a big deal about how he quit his job to do youtube full time um yeah and then but then he
doesn't really upload that frequently anymore and then people people said he did less videos
after he went full time yeah so i just assumed that he got a job again later but uh i don't know
um i i don't feel like i should you don't have to confirm one way or the other about it
i mean honestly he doesn't really owe us i feel like and i feel like he would he would
he would tell people what he's up to if he wanted people to know what he's up to
yeah i um i respect that you know i kind of uh i don't divulge many details about myself
and and unlike and unlike stuff like the pcp uh like rad contenters unlike that like that's not
that's his business so like whatever yeah i'll i'll leave it to him to talk about his life
if he wants to also nice try chrono we all know that you're a head executive at a pharmaceutical
company wait why i don't know yeah you gotta you got me is that just one of my silly little eyes
remember that one oh i get it i get it uh yeah um dan you know what you you i think your output
your video output would be a lot higher if you weren't like you know if you weren't working
in mergers and acquisitions at like tesla corporation like that must that must be really
like really putting a lot of pressure on you and the he needs to get the hyper loop yeah it's um
it's a lot of work going to the bank and cashing checks and stuff
it's it's it's a lot of work uh it's a lot of work um you're in charge of going going to court
to argue yes i know yes elon said he would buy twitter but he didn't mean it he didn't mean it
when he signed all those documents your honor he was a joke look he put a little he put a little
420 next to he drew a little he drew a little cool s next to his name that's this that's an s for
sarcastic he did a backslash s what more do you want what it's right there it's right there on
twitter sir you can see it see it all the post history is pristine uh the next voicemail is
just ben's weekly reminder play deltarune chapter two okay the one after that ben's weekly reminder
the one after that ben's weekly reminder get laid no way
uh i will not reminder ben by the way and casey forgot and you can't make me you can't make me
um yeah i assume this has happened for a couple weeks now uh i don't think i don't know if there
was a get laid last week i hope i hope whoever whoever like thoughtfully was making a voicemail
knows that uh the the weekly reminder to get laid i got it before you did i'm sorry yeah uh well um
this uh the there's one more and i think this is the last voicemail ever ever ever we will never
be another no i will i will make space um but uh wait i already downloaded it it is called
ethan ralph junior will kill you yet ben sains uh three two one go
i may be a baby but i pray to god and jesus with all my might that i may grow
and be powerful enough to kill ben saint if my name ain't ethan waltz jenia
that's the name amen
so all right so so so business is usual with uh with ethan or ethan jr um from what i
gathered when i was catching up uh this this guy called in and he started doing a samurai
thing right yes uh i assume he has stopped doing that and um no uh well i think the i think ethan
ralph is the samurai reincarnated actually yeah but yeah i think this is technically a continuation
but from what i understood that the guy who did that one was not the same person who does the uh
the other samurai sama voicemails so it's sort of like a non-canon it yes continuation
yes that's correct but it seems like there's no samurai mentions at all in this one so maybe
this guy has spun it off into his own it's it's now just the adventures of the baby that and great
now a samurai and a baby wants to kill ben well which which uh which one aren't there two babies
and the baby might also be the samurai depending on what you consider canon to these voicemails
oh god can we get a lecture on this stuff it's kind of it's kind of open to interpretation
honestly honestly pcp voicemail lore lecture i like what a fucking like masturbatory lecture idea
i've heard i've heard stupider ideas uh i guess um wait a minute wait a minute
earlier in this episode
oh no i would know it'll not a lecture i just remembered i feel like i had a good idea for a
video and i remembered it was uh it was um wait was it phenotopia yeah yeah you what would i make
a video about why did i think oh i should make a video about that like what would i what would i
say about uh the aesthetic of the game reminds you of megaman legends yeah i guess like games like
that maybe huh maybe maybe something maybe i was thinking like the history of the development
of it or something because like that guy's been vlogging not vlogging that guy's been
blogging his development for like 15 years really uh yeah uh shit i forget his name
i think he's like i think he's korean or something uh but uh whatever um
the uh no it's good legends is uh is a legend at this point
hey there we go there's there's a there's a chrono a chrono ism it's about 25 years old
now at this point megaman legends yeah i think so would it come out in like late 90s 97 yeah
yeah okay wait same year as something else my birth yes megaman x4
maybe 97 that's uh yeah someone would be x4 someone said that something else some other game
came out in 1997 earlier on this podcast final fantasy seven was it i thought that was 99
no that one 99 was eight yeah oh okay um i don't know whatever uh i'll listen back to this episode
and i'll recall everything that i forgot in the course of making it of course yeah actually listen
back to this stuff sometimes sometimes i do on it not never uh it's impressive is it
or is it sad uh i guess the listeners can decide that one that's right as as they will
as they want to do uh but i guess i guess i'm done uh i've i've talked about all the video games
that i have opinions about ever no more no more uh i'm done the voicemails so i mean uh i'll open
the floor back up to you guys if you've uh had want to share anything with the class
uh okay well
i don't obviously like i said earlier i don't have any videos coming out anytime soon
i imagine but uh so i will instead um you know check out reps2gog obviously but i also i want
to i'm just gonna show a completely unrelated channel so we review every playstation 2 game
oh god yes reps2gog rex reps2 dog should you should be able to find it pretty easily it's kind of
it's kind of the only thing quite like it yeah like when you search it but um i want to recommend
another channel i found just uh it's a small channel and it is basically reps2gog for playstation
and this guy it's a guy who commented on i think it was my digital devil saga review
basically it's like oh wow this is a really good video i just stumbled you know it's like i just saw
this is very similar to something i'm doing and i checked them out and uh he's actually really good
his name is blue bidya game and here you go blue bidya game this is the video first video of his
eye watched and uh yeah he seems he seems like a really cool guy i was talking to him a little
while ago i just uh seems pretty interesting i might uh check it out later yeah you should
it's uh i'll give it i'll give it a view he give it a listen he is already he is way
fucking more prolific than me and michael are like like how many uh how many uh let's he started
less than a year ago and i think he has about as many videos as we do how long have you been going
at least two couple couple years yeah okay i see i see i see playstation games are a little
bit shorter i think than ps2 games so maybe it's easier to get him out faster maybe yeah but there's
two of you so no excuse tell me tell me something i don't know that's a good point but yeah that's
that's all i'll say i recommend you watch this guy he seems cool sweet and i recommend you watch my
super mario rpg video i most i most definitely will i i must not have seen when that went up
because i i definitely would have watched it the moment i was aware of it so i'm gonna do that today
and uh if anyone listening to this uh doesn't like me uh you can still watch it because cyber
shell is in the video yeah it's yeah got something for everyone really yeah yeah yeah exactly the
the duality of the duality of man are you are you a chrono or a us hi rachel whoever wins we lose
yeah pretty much uh uh what do i have um that's it that's it nothing thanks i'm glad you guys were
on uh i feel like we could i would not have had that much to talk about this week other than that i
was on a boat oh that's no problem you know yeah i'm always uh i'm always happy well happy to be on
actually i shouldn't thank you i should thank doid geyser for uh very true for tricking you
thank you thank you doid geyser for making the podcast happen but we're all just pawns in your game
uh yeah okay well uh i soon i will do soon i haven't forgotten soon i will record
the uh solo ben commentary on the solo ben cast i will put that on the patreon patreon.com slash
the procrastinators for that as well as um i made that uh i made that uh uh uh nasty slanderous uh
tricksy gossip video uh that's up there it's up there for the bonus and also uh there was another
behind the scenes uh collection uh uh off the wreck off the books chatter uh did is an hour or so
of that was recent was recently posted another one so there's like 55 or 58 or something bonus videos
up there for patrons patreon.com slash the procrastinators send us a voicemail at speakpipe.com
slash pcp voicemail uh once i clear the records which i will which i will have done by the time you
listen to this once he cooks the books yeah once i once i just um smooth out some of those
wrinkles on the brain if you know what i mean uh and that's all i'm done yeah and i also go to
gamers tavern.com right tectonicimpro.com st comics.com we've all got .coms here
yeah all right i guess it that's the end of the episode uh good bye see you farewell everyone