Now, since the last time I've rolled through these parts, and I do roll through with some frequency,
I'm a little bit like herpes, I keep coming back.
But since the last time I might have seen some of you folks, I have had my 70th birthday.
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm now 70 years old, and I like 70.
Not as much as I like 69.
Well, 69 was always my favorite number.
Now I figure I'm 69 with one finger up my ass.
But now that I'm an old fuck, and that's what I consider myself to be, an old fuck.
Old fuck is a very special term. It's not like old man. Old man is different.
Old man isn't really a time in your life or a period of years. It's an attitude.
Old man is a point of view. It's a way of looking at things.
Some guys are old men when they're in their 20s. You've met guys like that.
They're just wired like old men. Not me, not an old man, and not an old fart.
Because an old fart is kind of...
What I am is an old fuck. It's kind of like a fat fuck.
Fat fuck, tall fuck, skinny fuck, short fuck.
Old fuck. Who's the old fuck? That's Georgie. Georgie's the old fuck.
In this respect, fuck is actually a synonym for the word fellow.
But now that I'm an old fuck, I'm beginning to notice there are some advantages to putting on a few extra years.
The first one is, you never have to carry anything heavy ever again.
Everybody wants to help an old fuck. If you've got a big suitcase or something like that,
you know, you just kind of go like this a little bit.
You say, yeah, could you help me with this?
Yeah, hey, how far are you going? Indianapolis.
He wants to help. Fuck him, put him to work.
Take advantage of people.
Another nice thing about getting old is you can leave any social event early just by saying you're tired.
Works great with family members. Just turn to the person next to you and say, jeez, I'm getting tired, you know.
Oh, you're tired? Come on, grandpa's tired. Grandpa's going to bed.
Someone else is, but it's 7.30 in the morning.
There's always one asshole in the family.
But the best thing about getting old is you're not responsible for remembering things anymore.
Even important things. But it was your daughter's funeral.
I forgot. You can even make believe you have Alzheimer's disease. That's a lot of fun.
You look around the dining room table and you say, who are you, people, and where is my horse?
Then you stare at your oldest son and say, Agnes, I haven't seen you since First Communion.
Fucks them up. They don't know how to handle it.
It takes them a week to get over that shit.
And they start listening to you a lot more carefully from their own.
So don't be afraid to get old. It's a great time of life.
You get to take advantage of people and you're not responsible for anything.
You can even shit in your pants.
They expect it. I haven't tried that yet, but I don't rule it out.
I'm keeping my options open. Everything is on the table.
Perhaps that's not the figure of speech I wanted.
Welcome, one and all, to the Procrastinator's podcast episode I don't know.
Today with me is, I'm Hippocrite by the way. Today with me is Nate.
Hey guys, I'm the best guy ever. What's going on at your house?
And Ben.
My house is pretty good, Nate. How about yours?
It's okay. I have to move in like three weeks though, so that's kind of stressing me out.
Oh no. Oh no.
I kind of forgot shit out. Oh no.
Meanwhile, on the Procrastinator's podcast, we're talking about...
That sure is an adult problem you have, Nate.
It is. It is.
Meanwhile, on the Procrastinator's podcast, we're talking about people complaining about getting old and how they're stupid for doing so.
I was trying to segue there.
Oh, well, I'm the guy saying the intro, so I got offended.
I respect that authority.
It's the old cast today.
Yeah, and how everyone's always, a lot of people are like, oh no, I'm getting old, I'm fucked.
Or like people that really dread getting old.
Here's what's interesting about the thing about dreading getting older, is that it happens at every age.
That's true. Every single age.
I mean, some kids can't wait to grow up. I was not a kid like that.
I was a kid who was like, man, I sure don't want to be an adult.
And you know, once you're an adult, you're like, oh man, I don't want to be an old adult.
That sounds bad.
But to me, it's like, it's like, my experience has been, whatever age I am, that's like the right age, the normal age, and I'm scared to get older.
But like, I don't, I don't know.
It's like, you're old to any, you don't want to be old, right?
But whatever age you are, you're not old to yourself, because you yourself are the reference point, right?
Like, no matter what age you are, you're old compared to the people younger than you, and you're young compared to the people older than you.
That's always true. That's always really what it boils down to, right?
Yeah, I mean, a lot of the time I think the fear of getting older is fear of the unknown.
You're like, yeah, I don't know what's going to happen soon. I'm scared about it.
Which is a pretty reasonable thing to be afraid of.
Yeah, I guess. But I don't know. I don't feel like that.
I'm not scared of getting old and dying as much as other people seem to be.
Like the whole like, oh no, one day I won't be around.
Oh man, I'm pretty scared of that.
Whatever. I'm pretty scared of death.
I've already got more, like, recorded stuff of me, more than most people.
So people will remember me more than the average person.
Right, but I think about how like, you know, I mean, what if, you know, Google or whatever goes out of business
and like all the YouTube servers go away and like all our videos are going to go away at some point
and that will be forgotten. So I think about how long this legacy will really last.
What I'm thinking more on that is people, like there's a guy 500 years ago thinking about the same thing
and nobody knows his name and nobody cares and all of his family is dead
and that's just how it is.
I just feel like eventually I'm going to be that guy 500 years in the past.
You're going to be that guy.
You're going back to the past, baby.
Yeah, you know what I mean.
I know exactly what you mean.
I feel like worrying about it is just a waste of time because it's not really, I mean,
there's all that talk about plugging your brain into a thing and living forever.
I don't care. It's a hassle.
What the fuck is a hassle?
I don't care.
I probably get annoyed with the instruction booklet and technology sucks by the time.
It's like a VCR programming thing you're talking about.
But what a hell of a fuck this. I'm not dealing with this today.
I'll just die in my chair.
He's getting up and plugging your brain into the machine.
I'll be like 90 years old and I'll already hate new technology and all the kids and everything.
I'll be like, why would I want to sit around with all these weirdos?
Yeah, God, I mean, you don't want to be that technology, right?
That would be suck. That would be the worst.
Technology's gay, so being it would make you be gay.
It's like all those kids with polio who refuse to use the iron lung because they just hate a technology.
Man, fuck it. I'm not getting in that man's machine.
I'm going to live my own life.
I admire those kids resolve.
They lived and died according to their principles and I really respect that.
I got to respect that.
They died the way they lived, not in an iron lung.
It's true.
So yeah, there's that side of the whole thing, like I'm scared of dying.
But then there's also the more annoying aspect of complaining about getting old is that there's people younger than you saying,
oh my God, Pokemon's 20, well, you know, Pokemon's not a good example,
but like something like Pokemon like, oh my God, it's 20 years old.
I feel really old.
I'm going to post on Facebook and get loads of sad clicks from people my age.
Yeah.
That's just, I hate it.
It's one of those things where I only think that you should,
okay, like everyone has that experience.
Everyone gets old and there's no avoiding it.
There is one way to avoid it.
Yeah, to put both in the brain.
But the only way that you should be allowed to complain
is if you're actively working to combat it by researching like genetic aging
and like, you know, if you're one of the people on the forefront trying to fix this shit.
Not everyone can do that.
Well, exactly.
So you should shut the fuck up about it, you know, because we all get it.
We all understand we're dying slowly.
We got both feet in the grave.
I think there's half the people that are just sort of saying it for frivolous reasons.
They're not thinking about death.
They're just, yeah, they just want to get...
Yeah, it's relatable.
It's a relatable thing to say.
It's like nostalgia and all that.
I mean, it's old now.
Yeah, these sorts of things look really good on a Facebook image macro.
Well, if you're an idiot looking at the macro, then sure.
Have you seen that vine of like, it's like some shitty comic of a guy like tucking the sheets under his feet
and then it's like, I sleep this way and then it cuts to the guy reading the comic
and he's like, I do that.
And that's the funny thing.
I have it, but that sounds amusing.
I've seen that a lot. I like it.
Sorry, I interrupted with my shitty anecdote.
Go on, Gib.
I don't know.
Let me say, all right, I think it's Harry Potter 6 at some point.
I think it's when it's like the attack on Hogwarts like that,
that shitty, that werewolf guy gray,
gray wind, lol, cross-reference.
Grimjaw, yeah.
Yeah, sure.
And those two, like the Allister siblings, I think?
I don't know, they're there and they're attacking Dumbledore.
And I think one of them calls them old.
They're like, ah, fuck you, old man.
And they rebate him a quote from the series.
And Dumbledore is like, I forget his words,
but he's like, yeah, I'm old.
You will be two one day if you're lucky.
And it's like, shit, man, you're so right.
And that's what it's like.
Like you said, there's no getting around it.
And in fact, it's way better than the alternative.
So looked at through that lens, it's nothing to fear exactly.
I definitely look forward to the position of being an old man
who specifically can sit on his porch and yell at people.
But even aside from that, being distinguished,
being able to grow a beard is something I dream of doing one day.
I assume that'll happen as I become an old man.
There's perks to being an old ass man.
As you get older, you look more distinguished.
Men get pretty sexy when they get old.
So I look forward to that.
There's ancillary benefits, they do.
Gay right now.
I have a keenly honed appreciation for the male form.
Like no other.
I do agree though.
Old guys, they're cool.
Even Dumbledore looks badass.
Yeah, because he's like in a movie, right?
Like they made them up to look real.
I don't know, I don't agree with...
Okay, senility is not cool, but like...
I mean, some people, I mean...
Alright.
That's the only thing I'm actually afraid of is like...
What?
Going senile and not being able to tell people to just kill me.
Fair.
I don't want to be in a position where I'm just shitting my pants all the time.
And that's it.
I think a lot of people share that.
When they say they don't want to, you know, they fear getting old,
I think that's probably a lot of what people are talking about.
I wouldn't be so bad, like if I was just old and I don't know,
I couldn't walk very well, that's fine.
You know, I can get over that.
It's just having my brain become mush.
That's the worst.
But you know, people aren't talking about that when they post like...
Oh, I still like Pokemon, I'm so old.
Of course, Pokemon Go has made Pokemon like hugely popular once again.
But before that, it was like, I still like Pokemon.
I played Pokemon Red, I feel so old, I don't know these new Pokemon.
It's, shut up.
Shut up.
Yeah, fuck you and appreciate the new gens,
or I'll come to your house and kick you in the knees.
Yeah, especially...
I really appreciate when, like, all the guys get into, like, young things.
Like, um...
Like young women? Like children?
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
I got you.
Little children.
What I'm talking about is, like, when they can get into technology,
like Steven Fry, he adopted Twitter,
like, really early on, and he's like a big advocate for new things.
But then he quit it because he got mad.
Well, yeah, but...
That's a separate issue, yeah.
Yeah, I'm just...
I want to be an old guy that's cool with new stuff,
but at the moment, I'm not actually cool with new stuff.
So what you're telling me is...
Yeah, I've been behind the technological curve my entire life.
I only started using Twitter, like, this year.
Yeah, me too.
So, Gabe, you want to be a sexy grandpa?
I do.
And you want to, you get the t-shirt now,
and you'll be ready in a hundred years.
A hundred years.
Or whatever.
Well, maybe.
Hey, yeah.
I'm pretty good, you know?
Yeah, I guess.
Good medical technology is getting.
I'm pretty excited about...
All right, here's a tangential thing.
With all the...
You know, you get in old parts of your body, stop working.
People are getting replacements.
They've been getting hip replacements for years.
What if, when we're old,
we can have the opportunity to just become a cyborg?
Would you do it?
That's the Ghost in the Shell dream, man.
I wouldn't put my brain into a computer,
but I would get an iron leg.
That would be cool.
Well, like, as opposed to dying?
Would you go full ride in
and just be like a brain in a fucking robot suit?
As opposed to death?
Absolutely.
All right.
Just think of the adventure.
Think of the extended adventure your life becomes.
Would you become a cyborg ninja with your bare ninja?
There is a song by Jonathan Colton.
It is covered by Imagine Dragons.
It's called The Future Soon, and it's a great song.
I fucking love it.
But the chorus has this line
that brings me to tears.
It's about this angry nerd,
and the whole song is him fantasizing about his ideal future.
And he says,
It's gonna be the future soon.
I won't always be this way
when the things that make me weak and strange
get engineered away.
That's a good line.
Yeah, like, holy shit.
That's what I want.
Man, I could feel his insecurities
and he's like,
The robots are gonna fix me.
They'll improve me and make me a strong handsome boy.
He's like hurting inside.
He's putting his only escape
from his self-imposed hell that is his life
is this thought that maybe one day
science fiction will come true
and everything will change
and he'll be at the forefront of it.
Oh my god.
I'm quivering.
I'm quivering just thinking about it.
I like the idea of being a physical being
with a brain with robotic eyes,
robotic body, the whole thing.
I don't like the idea of being a brain in a jar
hooked up to a simulation world or whatever.
Well, let me just play devil's advocate for it.
No, I'm just gonna explain my reasoning
is because as a physical being
you can still decide to end your life
whenever you want by jumping off a cliff or whatever.
You can take your brain out and kick it.
I don't know.
Oh, so you mean like being kind of like in the matrix?
Yeah, I don't want to be stuck in a matrix.
The year is 2167.
A renowned internet hero and cyborg,
Hippocrite, ends own life
by drop kicking own brain out.
That's the headline.
I've seen it writ large.
Yeah, on all the banners and all the top of Twitter
turning on Neo Twitter.
Brain lands in nearby baby carriage
leading to hilarious mix up.
It's a hilarious British antics.
What's that song?
Yakety Sax.
Yeah, that's the one.
People just hot potatoing the brain around.
Oh man, and like it would be like
the brain would be like all cute,
like looking around like, oh no.
I'm still a brain flying around.
Alright, I was gonna say though,
because if you think about it,
our entire existence, you know, there is a distinction,
but our entire existence is basically the brain in the jar.
Because all we are is a brain hooked up to a robot
that is just our shitty human body
that perceives stuff, however.
And you could argue whether it's real or not.
Let's just assume it is and that you can end your own life.
But like even in the matrix,
you can kill yourself and you can still end it if you want to.
So I guess you're saying,
what's the issue?
Like if you killed yourself in a matrix,
you'd be a responder?
Well, I don't think I remember the matrix very well,
but if there's like a thing where you're hooked up
to a computer that you know is built by people,
like I know that people built this,
that they could do stuff to me.
Like I'd be paranoid that I know that they made something
and they have complete control over my consciousness.
And I don't like that.
They wanted to torture me, they could.
How do you know you're not right now?
We have no way of knowing.
Well, I'm not going to torture you right now.
My point is why worry about it.
There's no way to know anyway.
Fuck it.
Yeah, but the thing is, I don't know now,
but like in the future,
if there is a big computer that I could hook myself into,
I would know that there is a chance that they can do stuff to me.
Right now I have no idea.
But if I had the choice,
I'd rather be a robot than in a machine,
in a matrix.
Oh, I got you.
You'd rather be a cyborg than a matrix, man.
Okay, that's cool.
I agree.
Ghost Michelle, make it happen.
I think we're a little bit off topic now.
We're talking about the trans symbolism and post...
It's not related.
What's the word? Post-singularity?
Post-singularity was the word I was looking for.
Oh, post-cyberpocalypse is a way better word for it, though.
Let me...
Okay, okay.
Going back to what you said about
old men being sexy,
or men being sexy when they get older.
Now, I think there are men
that look good at most ages.
I don't...
I don't know.
That is one of the things that does bother me
about aging is that, like,
you get ugly.
Not everyone, but most people get ugly.
I mean, I'm...
I don't think I'm a great look.
I think I'm pretty average-looking,
so, like, I don't know.
I certainly don't want to get any uglier, right?
That would just be rough.
That would be a death sentence, for sure.
Yeah, it would. Once I dip below,
once I dip down to the other side of the bell curve,
I'm just done.
And I'm right in the brink.
I don't feel like young people,
because you don't look ugly now.
You wouldn't become more ugly when you get wrinkles,
but people who like old people
don't mind the wrinkles.
But you guys know, like,
it's not weird to people who...
I don't know.
Some people look really weird when they get old.
Maybe those people were generally weird looking
all along. I don't know.
Okay, but the thing is...
Do you mean, like, celebrities where it's like,
oh, I know them as a young person,
and now they're old and it looks weird?
No, I mean, like, people that I see on the street.
I mean, like, normal people.
Okay, all right, that's true, Ben.
I see them and, you know, they look ugly or whatever.
And that's fine, but, like,
it's not like that gives you an understanding
into what their life is like, because really, as you get older,
like, your appearance, honestly,
appearance really doesn't matter that much
on the grander scale things.
If you can, like, do the things you want,
you know, like, nobody's going to say,
like, oh, you're an ugly man,
you're an ugly old man, so, like,
your life must be shit.
Well, it's not about inferior.
It's own...
Yeah, like, two of these ugly people,
like, we're talking about older men, right?
So, like, two ugly older men,
I really doubt that it's that big a deal.
Like, Rupert Murdoch.
It might. It might.
And he's the ugliest motherfucker in the world.
Well, like, if you're that rich,
then probably it doesn't matter.
Okay, maybe that's a bad example, because he is super rich,
but I just don't think it's really, it really matters that much
past certain points.
I don't think it matters too much, either,
but I have a slightly different perception,
in English, and there's a thing that I've noticed.
And you want to talk about ugly, the English.
Yeah.
No, no, really, it's true.
The English, there's,
we have more of a tolerance for ugliness,
which is why ugly people
appear on British TV more than
they would otherwise in America.
Which is why there's that stereotype
of British people having bad teeth,
because if we have bad teeth,
you know, if you're like,
you got bad teeth, but you're a good news reporter,
you still get on the news,
and then Americans come over and say,
oh god, everyone in Britain's got fucked up teeth,
and that's why there's that whole thing.
It's just because we don't care so much.
I respect that.
I wish everyone were like that.
I wish I were more like that.
I mean, yeah,
I guess I'm pretty shallow.
Like, I don't like ugly people,
but I also hate beautiful,
I also hate beautiful people.
I hate everyone.
Yeah, I do. Anyone who's more attractive
or less attractive than me
is just always done.
They just get out of my fucking sight.
And you know, I don't want to exaggerate.
Like, there's a point where you're beyond
what's a comfortable level of ugliness for sure.
That's what I mean, right?
Like, if you get old,
well, I'm not even that far.
I don't know. If you get old,
and I get ugly,
and I become,
you know, unlovable,
I don't want that.
I don't even think there is a level of unlovable.
You can always find somebody,
even if you're like a freak.
Like, it's just a marathon
of looking past. I'm talking about, Nate,
I'm talking about bitches, Nate.
I'm talking about hot, young sluts.
I don't think
being...
I mean, some girls like older guys,
but not all of them.
So what I'm saying is, when you get older,
I think it does limit,
I think fewer...
Like, not none,
but fewer girls are going to be interested in you.
Like, the older you get.
Wouldn't those girls also not have been interested you
when you were young because they're into older guys,
so it kind of equals out?
Maybe. Maybe. I don't know.
But I still think the pool gets smaller.
Um...
I think it'll...
I've noticed this about myself.
You can overpower women.
You don't need to look...
You can just physically overpower them.
That's a good point.
But I just mean that,
as you get older,
I felt this about myself.
I just feel way more...
Don't give a shit, because I think
that I'm a cooler guy just
by having done more stuff in my life.
So I'm not really as concerned about
being able to physically impress people.
I just think, I know that I can...
I'm way cooler than these people.
They are going to be interested in me.
So I'm not...
You're already quite physically handsome, though.
I guess.
Not in a gay way.
You are a handsome boy, Nate.
You know those things?
Yeah. Well, that's good and all.
He kind of shrugs, no?
Well, you know.
It's hard to respond to something like that.
Because you're already attractive,
it's easy for you to say,
yeah, I don't really mind about my attractiveness.
Okay, let me flip that around.
People say that to me sometimes,
and it really does not
make a difference when you're out there
trying to get coups.
When you're in a club,
it does not matter
if you're in the top 10%
of attractive people in there, or whatever.
All that matters is if you get in there
and do what older guys
are better at of getting
attention, lording the club.
Lording the club.
And whatnot.
That's what it's about.
I think being attractive
does increase your chances,
but it's not the most important thing.
It's a small thing.
No, there are definitely girls
who will go for you
if you are handsome
that wouldn't if you weren't good looking.
There are definitely girls like that.
I would just argue that's a small number
by comparison to the people
who are just interested in meeting
an interesting individual who's fun
and exciting, whatever.
So my point, and the larger scale here
is just that there are benefits
to getting older that I think
kind of outweigh being younger.
I do completely agree with you
that the older I get, the less of a shit I give.
Yeah.
And that does kind of trump.
That's a big one.
That does kind of trump everything else.
Getting older gives you
perspective.
Ironically, I worried about
getting old way more when I was young.
Yeah.
Because back then, you thought all these...
You had less perspective, so these things seemed
like a bigger deal back then, probably.
Right. His part of
the whole getting old thing
is a...
believing that you...
This is what I did. I didn't worry about getting old
because of death.
I worried about getting old because
I was not skilled enough
for my current age, and I should have been doing stuff
earlier. Oh, yeah.
That's why.
If only I had... I was like this kid on YouTube
who's like five years old, and he's a really
really good guitarist.
He's like, holy shit, I'm not as good
as him. I should have been doing it from
earlier age, and now I'm fucked for the rest of my life.
That's a tough one. That's a tough one.
That really gets me a lot, but I tried
over the years to forget about it.
Here's the thing.
I have thought... I have thought
that I should be better than I am now
my entire life.
Yeah.
There was never a point where I was young enough
that I was like, you know,
at this age,
it's okay to be bad.
There's no... there's no being
young enough for that.
You should always be better
than what you are, right?
I mean, you always can be,
obviously, and there's always going to be somebody
better than you, so I guess I'm just saying
don't worry about it too much.
Just do what you can do right now.
I don't worry about it all that much,
but I still see people worrying about it
or just feeling like I'm not progressing
or I've waited too long and it's too late to start.
It's never too late to start.
I'm not saying that because it's like it's a big old
you can do it sort of message.
It's just literally not... it's never too late
to start. You can learn something
like a skill at 40 years old
and you can be really good at it
after 10 years.
There's another post I see that goes around
that lists like famous pieces
that were accomplished.
Harrison Ford's first acting gig
was when he was in his 30s
I think it wasn't Hansel.
Yeah, it was Hansel.
It was his first big thing.
Alan Rickman's first role.
He was like
an artist
or a programmer. I don't know.
He was some totally unrelated thing.
He just totally switched careers and became an actor
Wow, awesome.
Oprah Winfrey got fired from some
TV correspondent job
when she was like 30 something.
You know, there's a whole list
of...
I like that.
I just turned 26
and that's on the latter half of 20
so Doom begins to set in.
Sure.
People comment
sometimes that I sound younger than I am
or when I say that I'm 25
or 26 now.
They'll be like, wow, you're old, dude.
I did not expect her to be that old.
It's like, okay.
Some people
thought we were teens
when they heard T-Bab.
I remember when we did our Q&A
people were like, you guys are like
in your 20s, what the fuck?
Well, our audience
was pretty young.
On the net balance it was pretty young
so they probably assumed we were close to their age
because we shared their shitty...
No, not because we shared their interests.
Man, you know, even back then
I remember never saying that I was a brony.
And I, you know,
I was never one of you people.
Just letting you know.
Just putting that out there.
Anyway, let's move on.
God damn it's phone.
Just destroy the phone.
Ben, are you getting messages?
Are those threatening messages you're receiving?
No, there's updates for his age.
He's getting older by the minute.
Because, you know, guys,
we've been getting some weird messages lately
from these guys calling themselves the CMC.
The Crow...
The Crow Masticators, you know.
They've been...
Wait, wait, the CMC?
Dark Reflection.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you sure you don't mean the Cutie Mark Crusaders?
Oh, no.
Cutie Mark Crusaders have teamed up
with a murder of crows
to undermine our whole operation.
The CMC, the Crow Masticators
are a flock of vicious,
carnivorous birds.
Yeah, a murder, you might say.
A murder of crows.
They've set out to devour
our YouTube subs
and our flesh.
Yes.
And right now,
their current attempt is to just...
Both of which we are rich in.
Yeah, that's right.
It's just to ping Ben's phone mercilessly
to undermine our brilliant...
Let me check my text.
Come outside, Ben, we're hungry.
All day and all night,
this keeps up.
The Crow Masticators, yeah.
One day I'll...
One day I'll get old
and decrepit and slow enough
and they'll catch me and they'll be able to catch me
on the street, but for now, I'm safe.
You see, that's why it's all related.
We can't get old because then the fucking crows
will devour our bodies.
All it takes is one slip up.
Let your guard down for an instant.
This is PCP cannon, people.
Put it on the books.
Put it in the wiki.
We've got an evil...
Evil alter enemy
guy, Crows.
A murder of crows, yeah.
Yeah, they are a murder of crows.
That wacky CMC.
Oh, and also, they're forever young.
It's terrible.
They found the fountain of youth.
As one crow dies,
it's simply replaced by a new crow.
It's a constantly...
ebbing and flowing cycle
of death that's
trying to devour us.
I totally forget where we were.
Goddamn it, me too.
Because your goddamn poem was interrupting us.
Fuck.
Let me completely segue.
I watched this...
show. It was a Japanese...
I guess you could call it a documentary.
Where this one mangaka
he, like,
puts cameras in other mangaka's
studios
and films them working
and then, like, a month later,
him and the other guy watch it together
and, like, talk about their workflow
and process and stuff. Oh, that's cool.
It was very cool, but I was shocked
at how fucking old they all were.
All these... they were all...
Like, the youngest guy
that I saw on there
was the guy who did
motherfucking...
or, I assume, a poon-poon.
And he's, like, phone
and he's...
And he's, like,
35.
He's been at it for a while, though.
And, like,
the guy doing the show is, like,
in his 50s and, like,
the...
And he's still going at it.
They all looked really youthful.
They all looked really vigorous.
Well, they're Asians, you know.
Yeah, maybe. But there was one guy
one episode of it
was this one, like, older guy
who did this famous thing.
Gogo9?
I don't know it.
It's about this assassin.
This, like, really tough assassin guy.
And, all right, this guy was, like,
78, right?
And he got on the show
and one of the things that they talked about
were, like,
yeah, people say I don't even draw anymore
but that's totally not true.
People say,
sorry, that I only draw the eyes or whatever.
And everyone's, like,
well, we'll prove them wrong with this footage.
And then, okay,
all the other footage of the guy
showed them, like, working, like, you know, all day
drawing, like, page after page, right?
This guy, this 78-year-old guy,
he goes into his desk, he sits down,
he draws, like, two pictures, right?
He does, like, he draws, like,
one portrait
of the main character from one of his series
and one portrait of the main character from another.
And that's it.
And then he draws, like, a storyboard,
but it's super bare bones. It's all text, right?
Like, this guy is not working
at the same rate as the other guys.
And he takes these super bare bones
storyboards and he hands them off to his assistants
and they give him back, like,
fully finished pages. And all he does
is he doesn't even
just draw the eyes, like the rumors say.
He just goes in and he just draws in, like, the sound effects
over the fully finished, that's, like, all he did
on the fully finished pages.
So, alright.
The start off being, like,
people say, I don't still draw,
but I do. And then he kind of goes in,
draws these two pictures, sort of makes a show
that he can still draw. Like, obviously, he can still do it.
But then they show him actually working
and he doesn't. He isn't.
The rumors are completely true.
He doesn't, in fact, draw his shit, but...
So what you're saying is
old people don't... In the end,
in the end, I think what the impression
I came away with is that, like,
these rumors that he doesn't draw
seem to be completely true
and founded, but it's
cruel to, like,
hold that against him because the guy
was, like, 78 years old.
The guy had to, like,
really slow walking around.
He had to, like, take naps in the middle of drawing.
Like, you know, yeah,
this guy isn't putting out work
at the same rate as these younger people.
But, like, seeing him in action,
why would you expect him to, right?
And, like, the guy is still
putting in... The guy is still working
to the top of his ability. I don't know.
I guess... It was interesting.
And I guess that brings me to,
yeah, one thing that I do worry about
with getting old is that, you know,
you're less capable and you can't do the things
that you want to do anymore.
As I recall, there's a great line that I...
This guy was definitely slowing down.
Did you watch Shirobako, Ben?
Yeah. Well, yeah, yeah, I did. I did.
So there's the... I didn't finish it,
but Digi has just told me this line
and really made an impression on me of this old dude
who insists, and I think you talked about this a bunch, too,
who insists that you have to get fast
at drawing when you're young, because as you get older
you only get slower. So it's important
to turn that skill up.
That's the kind of line
that really gives me fucking
nightmare triggers.
That's the kind of thing that someone can say
that really fucking shakes me to my very core.
Yeah.
That is, like, the big thing that's, like,
the antithesis to the idea that you can start
a skill whenever.
Like, some things you literally can't
because of, I don't know, your hands
gets too shaky that you can't draw.
But I like
to think that
as long as you, you know, try
you can be decent
enough from any age.
Like, if you do start
when you're, like, a teenager,
you start doing a skill and you do it forever,
you're gonna be one of the best in the world.
You're gonna be, like, one of the Beatles
or something.
Even if you
say you start really late
and you're slow and you never get fast,
right?
That's not a death sentence.
Like, some people can be slow,
but good, right?
Like, some people can be successful
despite being, like, George R. R. Martin
is not a fast guy.
Yeah, right, right.
Though it did take him, like, 30 years for anyone to give a shit.
I mean, on a large scale.
Yeah, but still.
I mean, he was making a living off of it,
like, his whole life.
That's true. So, I mean, really, that's, I'm sure,
his larger goal, just to be able to do it.
And he did it, so, you know.
He's fake. Like, I just remember
really liking that he struggled with his speed
for a long time, and it took him
years to achieve
a speed he was comfortable with. And even then,
he didn't get as fast, ever,
as A.G., as the, like, the genius did.
Yeah, yeah.
Crowman. Oh, my God.
The head of the CMC, the head of the
Crowmasters, A.G.
from Bakuman. Oh, my God!
That fucking
bitch killed that guy.
Yeah, I just,
I'm glad that the series
touched on that. It didn't really
to my satisfaction address
how he got good, other than he just kept
doing it. He just kept doing it,
which is good, and I guess probably
is all it takes. You just keep doing it.
You're gonna figure out tips and tricks
to one weird old tip to draw
fast. Yeah, like,
you don't get to,
this isn't really an age thing,
but just in general, you don't get to choose
what you're good at and
what your strengths are and what capabilities
you have. Like, by doing
the work and starting things
and doing things, you have to discover
them and then work around them.
Yeah, definitely true.
I think one thing,
yeah, go on, go on.
One thing I've, with regards
to being slow
if you start late
or never being quite
the best ever is something
that I've always, like, I don't like
the idea of not being the best, because I'm very
competitive. I always want to be
the best at everything I do, but I'm obviously
not, you know, because I don't,
I try lots of different things.
Well, I don't necessarily agree with that.
I mean, I think you're,
at what you specifically do, I think you
are the best, because
only you can do exactly
what it is you do. That's too
your narrow definition.
What I mean is,
like,
I forgot.
Sorry. What I mean is
something about
being not good
at all. You're saying you want to be the best.
Yeah. Like no one ever was.
Right. No, well, okay,
sure.
I want to be really good. I want to be the,
jack of all trades, that's what I was going to say. I'm more
of a jack of all trades. I do, I dip
my fingers into a lot of different
pots. And a lot of
pussies.
Wow.
Yes, great.
Draw that fan artist.
Yeah, yeah, draw it.
So I'm good at lots of things,
but I'm not, like, really, really good
at one thing, which is what I want,
because I feel like I want
to be better than everyone in one field.
Yeah. And there's always somebody better
than me, and it didn't always be me.
You know, I get that.
I get, you know, people say you got to pick one thing
and be the best at it. And that's,
I understand that.
I,
I mean, I think, I think that my
specialty was probably
is like, you know, would be art,
and like actually like, like actual drawing
part of the art is like the thing that I'm
best at. But I'm not the best at it.
But I am comfortable
with not being the best at that.
I am, I'm, what I was saying before,
I am comfortable with being
the best at, you know,
my own particular blend
of, you know,
writing
slash drawing, slash storytelling,
slash directing, slash humor,
slash, you know, whatever.
I'm, I think that's all,
that's all I want to be is just,
you know, it's like, it's like Jesse,
it's like Jesse always says, I'm the best
at what I do, even if what I do isn't very cool.
I, I'm totally cool
with being that. Yeah.
I mean, I'm not cool with that,
because that's a boring, dumb definition
that is useless because
it's too specific. Well, but that's the only definition that you'll ever get
to be the best at, so.
Yeah, but that's dumb. You should aspire
to greater heights to be the best.
But you're always competing with yourself.
When I'm watching like your, your draw vlogs
Ben, I see yourself,
I see you drawing and like, and you're like,
I don't know about this, this, this
doesn't look good. And I'm like, hmm,
I want to be a drawer guy. I want to make
a comic just so I can say I'm better
than you. Not because I have,
not because I'm being
That's a fine motivation. I just, I,
watching you work makes me want to be
better. I don't know.
Watching anybody do anything wants me,
wants me to feel like I,
because I'm really competitive. I really want
to just beat everyone all the time.
It's good to watch people working hard
at things that they want to do.
So it's, it's not like, um,
I feel like you suck
because you don't. You're really good.
It's just, I want to
I want, I want to make a comic
god damn it. And I know
I need a lot of practice before I can really
do that. Back when I, no, you don't.
I don't, you don't. Just do it.
Just, I'm sorry.
I'll do it. Sorry if that was
patronizing. No, no, it wasn't.
Okay. Um, back
Speaking of patronizing, everybody
head on over to patreon.com
slash best guy ever. The only place
to give me all your money.
No, it's mine. You failed the meme.
I'm modifying the meme to give me the money now.
You know, you know, Nate, I heard that if you pledge
now on best guy ever, you get
50% off on plates and silverware at Target.
Is that true? That's, that's, I can confirm
that that is indeed not true, but
you can do it anyway. Oh well.
If you go and tell them that, maybe they'll fall
for it. Yeah, sure.
You can't afford
me.
Viewers, you can't afford
not to pledge or can
you?
A brilliant marketing strategy.
Hey, you know, I was going to
say before, I just wanted to clarify
that I don't think it's
like bad or anything to
to be the best at what you do. It's just
I also see myself as the
best at what I do and I just
don't find a lot of usefulness
from that mentality just because
like, yeah, people generally
seem to like what I do, but I
looking at myself, I see all the ways
that I'm inadequate in other things
that I need to improve on. We all do that.
We're all thinking like, I'm great
but I could be better than me.
I have to set my own bar
higher. Well, I like to compare myself to
other people in the ways that they are good
that I want to, you know, do
like Digi's work ethic and just his
his rate of output is
something that I want to achieve or, you know,
get closer to because that's really
important on the market of YouTube and, you know,
just things like that are what I
think about when I think about this stuff.
Was this on topic?
I'm with you. Actually, no.
Kind of. Okay.
Who cares? Well, okay, let me
kind of segue into something that is a little
related. I
used to watch, like a couple years ago,
I was watching a lot of like
drawing tutorials or like, you know,
draw
vlogs or things, kind of like what I'm
making now. And
I watched this. There was one guy in particular
named Sycra that I watched a lot
and, alright, Hippo, you said
like when you watch my draw vlog, you feel
like, oh, I want to be as good as
that guy. When I watched Sycra,
there was a bit of that, like, oh, I want
to be this good, but it also gave me
a sensation that was like
I am
this good, like when I
and at the time he was way better than me, like when I
watched Sycra draw,
I would feel as though I was
drawing it and I would be like, oh,
I've seen how he does it. Well,
I could do it too now. Like there's
now like now that I've seen it, there's nothing
to it. Yeah, that's a lot.
A lot of it is just knowledge base and under
when you can break down something like what's somebody
like like Brian Leo Malley or something
and like watch him draw something and you see, oh,
there's nothing magical about this.
He just went through the steps like everybody else. That's
a useful thing, I think. On the one hand,
it's true. Like there's no trick to it.
You just do it. On the other
hand, I was totally wrong because
like I felt like I could go
and draw this thing because I just seem, but like
it wasn't true. I definitely could not
have done what he was doing
then and probably still not now because
that guy is really great.
But anyway,
yeah, Sycra, now there's a guy listening to
his life story. They told
him he
he's kind of like me.
He was, I mean, he drew a little as a kid
but then he was like, he was in, I think
he was like 21 or 22
when he like decided to
he went and found like a tutor
or like a personal art like mentor
and was like
I want to learn how to draw and be really good at
drawing and they told him at the age
of like 22, like you're too old.
What a fucking bitch.
Like you've passed the prime
time in your life to like become
good or fast or whatever, like
if you really want to do it, you can
do it, but like, yeah, and he was like
I don't care.
Good friend. I think he's like
he's probably maybe like 31 or 32
or something like that now.
It's not even old at all.
Yeah, and that was earlier than me.
I mean, I drew a little bit, but I didn't really
start taking it seriously until I was
like 25, but I don't know.
I'm happy with the progress I've made
since then. Yeah.
Getting
never too late people, you know, like
I said, like, like
and my whole life, like even in like
high school, I would sit down and
sometimes I would I didn't draw that much back then
but I would often like want to
I would like think about doing it or maybe I would
start and then I would be like, oh, this isn't
coming out good immediately. I give up
you know, like in a second
and even back then
when I was like 16, 17, I was like, man,
I could have been drawing my
entire life. I could have been drawing since I was
10 years old. I could be like good right now
but I'm not. Yeah.
So, you know, I've fucked it up. I've wasted my
time. I've wasted my potential.
Fuck it. I give up.
Yeah, I think everybody has those feelings.
Yeah, yeah, but it ain't good.
And moreover, it's not
true.
It's not true. I don't believe that anymore.
You know, I remember when we were young and
we were both in high school, I think, at the time
and you drew like everyone's
D characters in this like
particular like RPG based
style as I call it. Yeah, on like graph
paper. Like you're a little tiny
like RPG maker sprite looking
dudes. Yep. That was awesome.
And I gave them all, you know, they were
I gave them all little
color scheme, little
individual color schemes, like elemental themes. They were really
simple. And then someone like
at school, someone like
accidentally like ripped it, like
like it got like a rip in it because like
someone like was being careless with it.
And I was like, and I was like,
dude, you just rip my drawing
and he and he looked at it.
Yeah, this was not a guy I respected,
by the way, his opinion did not did not
hold much weight for me, but he he
he got defensive about it. He tried
to like play it off like, oh, it's not a big deal.
Why are you mad? I didn't do anything wrong. And he was like,
dude, do you know how easy that would be to
draw? Well, I wasn't
even mad. I was just like
I didn't say this at the time because
I had no idea how to respond to this, but like,
yeah, I do because
I drew it and like, sure
it's simple, but like I spent time on
it. You ding it. There was
like 12 characters on there, like 10 of them
or something. I wasn't it was
so stupid. It was such a stupid thing
to say that it didn't even make me mad. I
was just like, how can he
that there's how that's a guy
right there without a creative bone
in his body or at least not thinking about it
in those ways. I don't know. He was
thinking back. He was deaf. He was definitely
like making sort of a knee jerk
reflexive defensive thing, like
trying to deflect.
At that moment, he wasn't thinking about
what it means to be a creator. So fuck that guy.
Oh, definitely not.
Do you know
how easy that would be to draw? Yes, I do
actually.
There's a sort of
a related thing
in that
the not not finishing
projects is something that I've struggled
with a lot. Oh, man.
Not finishing projects.
But I feel like a lot
of the time, the projects that
I wouldn't have done much with anyway, like
when I did that homestuck
fan comic. Yeah.
I was going to have the whole of the horseshoe
crew as characters and do a whole
thing. But then I realized
why would I spend so much time doing a homestuck
comic when I could just make a real
comic. Yeah, fair point.
Agreed. As much as I hate
unfinished shit,
there's probably better things
you could be doing. Though not to discourage
people from, like, if you're starting from zero,
go for it. Like, take your time
and go ahead and do that shit. Like, I mean, I
did, like, that illustrated homestuck
RP, Spurg, and
I spent, like, it went on for like
two years. But I stuck
with it and I fucking, because
I had put so much effort into it
by the, by the end
I was like, I can't give up.
I have to finish it. And it was
wicked hard. I really had to fucking
kick myself to do it, but I finally did.
And, and it's good.
Um, Jeff.
Finishing things is so important.
Finishing things is, is, it
makes you feel good, you know, even if it's not
very, like a, like, I've,
I've had multimedia fusion too, which is
like a video game creation
application thing. And I've
made tons of games.
One or two that I actually finished
and hundreds that are just like,
we've never seen any of those, man. I want to see
them. Yeah. If I, if there was a good way
to record them and if I could find them
then yes, I'll try and do, I kind
of want to make a, a hypocrite video about
them. Yeah. Great. I'd love that.
Yeah. But yeah, I've, I've
done loads of things. I've tried writing
songs. I've recorded like hundreds, well
not hundreds, but like lots of songs,
lots of different guitarists, never any
lyrics. But the things
I have completed, like that one album I
did when I was sick, I, I stuck with it.
I made a song every day
for seven days until I got better,
which just so happened to be an exact
week and, and ended on this day
Homestuck ended, which was weird. Oh yeah.
And I liked that album and I went and fucking bought
it. I bought your album. Something I
have never done is buy an
album, but I bought your fucking album
hippo. And it was worth it.
On bandcamp.com
slash Hippocrite or something. Yes.
Yeah, but
that, that album, because it was finished,
it's like, I like it, even
though some of the songs are kind of whatever.
Yeah. It's cool. Yeah, it's great.
I mean, like,
you're never going to, you're never going to be totally
happy with the work of art, but
it's fine, right?
Like, you still, you still got to finish it.
I think the first real creative
endeavor I did was in college
when me and my buddy Rich, just
you know, we, we both wanted to make video games.
We were programming guys. We just decided
to make one. And we
just spent the next year slowly chipping
away at this RPG maker
like puzzle drama
kind of game. And we finished it.
It's called Bell. Man, I bet I have
a download link. I could probably put it in the fucking
description of this if I can get that shit. You know, I never
actually finished it. It's really
hard. It's really hard and like
not super clear. But we made
it that way on purpose. I would have played that game again though.
Oh yeah, I did some sprites for that, didn't I?
You sure did. You made like a blanket that was
folded on itself and like I think like a paper
plane or something. Yeah, you made stuff. And Grace
our sister made some shit for that
and me and Rich worked on it for a million fucking years.
She like painted the backgrounds, right?
She made some art
that there was like cut scene art that's
not so great. But I remember
thinking it was not that good. No offense to you, Grace.
It's not very good. It's not
She's done, she's drawn way better
stuff. She's much better now. Yeah, this is
this was years ago. But yeah, like
just the fact that it's done, I've got a finished
game that's just out there that people
have played, you know, not many of them and it's not
great, but it's constantly
giving me a source of joy from like ever since
it's been done for the last like eight years. So
you know, it's not eight years.
Oh, maybe like six.
We did that sophomore year
of college and it's been like, that's
like six, probably six years, maybe five.
That does not feel
like it was six years ago that I drew this.
Yeah, I know. Well, oh,
I feel so old now.
There it is.
Yeah, we're way off topic, but
while we're on this on subject of finishing
things, I have two things to say. One,
I think that finishing things,
just the act of finishing things
is a skill in and of itself
and you need to practice it
by finishing things, even if they're bad.
Finishing them is important just
to fucking get
just to, you know, get experience points
to put into your finishing things skill
because finishing things is the most
important thing. Because if the experience points don't go
to that, they go to the giving up on
shit skill and you don't want to train that
too much. Yeah.
They're learned. They're both learned. Giving up
and finishing things are both learned behaviors
and you need to practice.
You got to like, like your brain is plastic,
right? Like the more you do a thing,
the more your brain synapses reroute
themselves to like more easily
like route you towards doing
that same thing. Yep. So like the more
you do a thing, the more you're
going to be inclined to do that
same thing. So you need to not give up.
You know what it's like? You need to finish a thing
in order to change your brain.
Life is an RPG
and like most RPGs, it's hard
to reallocate your stats.
Specifically, it's like Final Fantasy 6
where you've got the chicken knife
and the brave sword and when you run
from battle, when you run from battles
your chicken knife gets way more powerful
and that's giving up. But if you stay
and fight every battle, your brave sword
never gets less powerful and it stays
one of the best weapons in the game
and that's finishing stuff. So don't run
away from battles, people. Don't raise that
chicken knife, even though in the game the chicken knife
is way more powerful potentially. Keep your
brave sword strong. It's not a perfect
metaphor. It's not a perfect metaphor.
It's a terrible one. It's in fact the worst
metaphor. It's the exact opposite.
Alright. Wait, wait, there's one more thing
I want to say about that. The reason why
you've got to learn to finish things is
because finishing things is the most important
because as Brian Leo Malley, creator
of Scott Pilgrim once said on his
Tumblr or something
or something, he said
anything finished
is better than anything unfinished.
Like no matter how bad a
thing is, if you finish it
it's something. If you don't
finish it, no matter how good it could
have been, it's only potential.
It's nothing. It's garbage. I like that
message. Yeah. If you don't
finish a thing, it's garbage.
If you do finish it, it's
at least a non-zero value.
You've at least created something.
So that's the most important thing.
Thanks, Brian Leo Malley.
That quote is really stuck
with me ever since I read it. I don't
know, however many years ago.
It's so important. I'm going to go make a comic
after this. I'm going to make it. It's going to be
10 page comic. That's my goal.
That's your goal. That's a good goal.
We could probably do that in a week.
The page is going to be one pixel
wide.
You could do that in one minute.
You broke the system.
Well, that's good, Gib. Yes.
Do that.
After you both finish the project
that we're working on aside from this shit.
Do that first. Actually, we can't do it
until Ben does this shit, but whatever.
I will do my shit. We're so
off topic. We haven't
even been talking about it. It's sort of an inevitable
sort of thing from
complaining about getting old.
In itself,
people who complain about getting old, that
is not really much of a topic.
I don't like when they do that.
It's silly. I've got so much more to look
forward to. You shouldn't be sad.
Yeah.
When I was
where you were
saying before, Hippo, about
comparing yourself to people's
ages and being, oh, this person
was this far along when they did this.
I should be doing that at that age too.
Like Brian Leomali,
I think he was like 22
when he did
Lost at Sea, his
first full paperback that nobody fucking remembers.
And then I think he was
doing Scott Pilgrim between the ages of
like 23 and 27
or 8
or 29 or something like that.
So, I don't know. Think about that guy.
I mean, that guy had been drawing comics
since he was a little kid, but not anything
like publishable. And he'd only
really been working in the field.
I don't know, maybe when he was like 20 or something.
He was doing a little bit for some website or something.
So, I don't know.
I mean, Andrew Hussey. Andrew Hussey had been
drawing for years
and years. I mean, I think all of his old
black and white comics, like I think he did
whistles in his late 20s and I think
maybe he was doing things like
a steep price for
pie and like humanimals he was doing
maybe his early 20s and I think
I think he was maybe late 20s
when he did problem sleuth and I think
he was, I think he's maybe like 34
now. So, oh my god, I guess
he was, wait, maybe I have this all shifted
because I guess maybe he started
home stuck when he was like late 20s
or something. Well, do you know how old he is?
Yeah, the guy. He's like 7 years old.
Yeah, so I guess
I mean, I think he's like 33 or 35
right now. So, I don't know. So, he probably started
home stuck when he was about my age.
Although, I mean, he had been doing a lot of other stuff
before. Oh my god, jeez, that's
shit. He's, shit, he's younger than I thought.
God damn it.
Yeah, but we can't, you know,
we can't let everybody else who's older than
you when they started. So, you know, I'll just
think about that like, I'll just think about
that the 50 year old guy who was doing
that manga documentary.
By the way, that documentary about the
mangaka is called, it's called
manben, M-A-N-B-E-N
and you can find it on Dailymotion.
There's like 7 episodes, I think.
That's cool.
The best one is about the Oyasumi
Poon Poon guy. And it's like,
I don't know, the guy
the 50 year old guy who's
a host who's like, he's still totally
active in the field. He's totally, you know,
vibrant and vigorous and working away.
He like talks to this like 35 year old
guy like, oh, you know, you're a young guy.
You're like part of the new guard. I'm like, that guy's
like 10 years older than me. Awesome.
I can still be, I can
still be like a, I can still be
like a young, like, you know,
part of the new guard
when I'm like 35.
Like that's normal. Cause like I'm saying,
no matter what age you are, you're young
compared to those older than you. You know what I always thought was weird?
You know how Blackbeard
in One Piece is like an old ass bitch
and yet he's part of the worst
he's like a new hot pirate
despite being an old ass man.
That's inspiring to me. He's like the most
powerful man in the world and he's an old ass bitch.
He's, he's, he's older.
Well, no, I think some of the other
supernovas are kind of old.
Like Uruj, he's kind of, you know,
30s. Yeah, like, like
what's, what's the gang beach
is like. Capone gay. Oh, that's true.
Capone gang is pretty old. I think Drake
is probably in his 30s or something, whatever.
Yeah. Um, yeah.
Like it doesn't matter what age
you are really. Yeah. Like their age doesn't
matter. It's the fact that they became relevant
at that time.
And like, you know, like, we're saying before, with like Harrison
Ford and, and the guy from
Die Hard, Alan Rickman.
Bruce Willis. Oh, no, yeah.
No, and Alan Rickman. But he started kind of late, too.
But whatever. He did, yeah.
You can, you can,
it's never too late
and people can become relevant
at any stage of life. It happens,
you know. Like sometimes
you might think, you might think
that just because you're not where you want to be,
you know, creatively
financially or you know relationship wise or in any aspect of life you might
think you're not where you want to be at whatever age you're at but like you know
I'd say it's pretty safe no matter what age you are it's pretty safe bet that
someone has succeeded later then yeah say once you pass age a hundred you can
probably say well then you can get some yeah then you can give up but at least
you're gonna agree news and you're gonna get a letter from the Queen and it's
gonna be interesting do you get a letter from the Queen when you turn a hundred
yeah whoa you got right why doesn't Obama send send me a letter from the
queen yeah yeah I know I don't want Obama I want Obama to just ask the
Queen for one yeah that'd be nice yeah all right I think we've wrapped it up in
a nice little Queenly bow here but do we have any does that do we have anything
else to say on the subject of being an old-ass bitch I think I said my piece I
don't think I'm gonna be old like and I don't think I'm gonna consider myself
old until I'm 60 until then I'm just a guy yeah I mean you know you could start
I'd start worrying about it at like 50 then you can start to think about it but
don't really worry about to your 70 70 is the bridge to real you know you can
worry about shit that that older mangaka who was getting slow and who was
like past his prime he was like 78 whereas like these guys in like their
50s and even like this other lady who was 60 something they were still chugging
away yeah they're fine exact doing exactly what they wanted to do with their
life and like you're doing what you want to do you're you're as young as you
need to be mm-hmm there's one thing from the movie up that sort of struck a cord
with me is that the the kid watching that guy the pilot guy or the explorer
the explorer guy was like in his 20s or something and the kid you know I forget
his name oh yeah and then it cut at the beginning forward yeah and he's like
he's 60 or something and the guy the explorer is still out there he's like
he's in his 80s yeah but they're both considered old but like that's like a
20 year difference that's a lot of years yeah the guy still be doing things yeah
the guys like still I mean you there's plenty of time to be old you know like
you can be you can be you can be kind of old for a long-ass time and get a lot
done in that time you know it's very true it's very true so everybody thanks
for listening I think I find I think that is I've said I agree with so we'll see
you next time watch out for the crow masticators the murder of crows in your
in your area remember viewers if you see a crow kill it it might be it might be a
spy it might be an enemy enemy to yeah send us send us send us send us dead
for every 10 dead crows in the mail get a free you a shout out max you have free
we'll give you a doctor pepper 10 10 refreshing Calorie there are calorie per
crow the crow masticators are enemies of procrastinators all across the globe so
we need to unite against them all right thanks for watching everybody we'll see
you next time goodbye I'm supposed to be working right now I'm supposed to be
working right now my self I'm sucking I am a stupid I don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong with me I'm supposed to be making money I'm supposed to be
creating funny people gladly will pay for artistic genius that's what they came
for instead I'm tweeting that's why it's quite the burden it's a hard-knock life
being a genius