Hey, what's up, everybody? It's Digibro. I'm not in this episode. I don't even know what this episode's about, but here's a rant I gotta give you.
I'm sick of half measures by society when it comes to germs. Everyone washes their hands all the time after they take a piss.
You don't even really touch anything, but you feel the need to wash your hands. People wash their hands after they touch this and that, when they touch trash, they touch this.
But yet everyone goes to the grocery store and pushes around carts that a thousand other people's hands have been on, and no one washes their hands afterwards.
Or even worries about it. No one puts shit on their hands to grab the cart, even though every fucking sick motherfucker who's been in that place has touched that cart.
If you're touching carts, then you're doing it wrong. You're fucking up, and you're washing your hands after... I don't know what I'm talking about. Here's the episode.
Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of the Procrastinator's Podcast. I am back. It's just me today. Nobody else is here. I'm the best guy ever.
Creek, it's me. I just walked through the door.
Oh, I didn't... Oh, hey, what do you know? It's, uh...
Don't tell me, but I'm hiding under the table. He doesn't know I'm here. I'm here with the fool.
Oh, is that him? Are you under the table? Is that you?
No, no, I'm not.
Oh, you up-ended the table, god damn it.
Yeah, I see you guys.
Here comes the crappy pants, man!
Everyone's favorite character.
I'm a superhero. No one knows my secret identity. You don't know who I really am. I'm the crappy pants man.
Who could I be? Which mysterious member of the PCP is actually me?
AKA the Pooper Tailor.
Fill it with a shit. The crappy pants man can't do that.
Hey, you kids. What are you all getting up to? It's me, your dad Ben... Your dad Ben St. here, and I've got my... I'm getting my fucking belt off, kids.
No. Okay dad, I'll do our homework. Don't take my belt off. My pants are the only things keeping in my crap.
My pants are the only thing that set me apart from the animals in the field. Please don't take my clothing. They're my badge of honor.
Okay, anyway, we're here at Procrastinate's podcast, and we're talking about some shit.
Okay, so we got a topic to Justin from a while ago. Oh, and DeVoo too. Of course. DeVoo encompasses the rest of us.
The furtive DeVoo.
So easily forgotten.
That's actually hilarious.
Except I made that same fucking joke about myself last week, and no one left any of us.
It wasn't hilarious when it was about Ben, because Ben's not cool.
No, that was a lie.
It was harsh, harsh justice.
Okay, we got a suggestion here for a topic from our buddy. It's Mun Keh at Mun Keh Away, who I think has asked a question before.
Is that my secret evil twin brother?
Probably, probably. But here's what they got to say. It's not Mum Keh Jones, it's Mun Keh Away.
He says, are there any art mediums you think are crap? I, for instance, share Digi's views of disliking visual novels.
So this guy's asking a question about the inherent worthiness of different artistic mediums, basically.
And a couple of us had been discussing this topic amongst themselves already, so this was a very apropos of a suggestion.
So Ben and Mun Chee, I believe. You got things to say about this, right?
Well, kinda. Kinda.
Like, okay, if by medium you mean like film, the pros, then I would say no. Probably not.
Well, I would say yes. However, continue Ben.
I was gonna say, but there are, I think there are genres that are inherently worthless.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, this guy's talking about like visual novels, so I think we can define it however we want, it doesn't matter.
We'll run the entire game, but we'll go medium or genre.
We'll go fucking art itself being worthless, which is nice.
I'm just saying.
I'm gonna jump right into this and say that I think any medium or genre can be good, but not necessarily any...
Yeah.
Like, there may not be a good one in that genre yet, so they are using that.
I think anything can be good, but I think that being good, I think that like a porn, for example, that is good
is just inherently worthless than like a real book that is good, or a real movie that is good.
There are definitely tiers of goodness, depending like a sign to each class or medium.
Well, hang on.
Yeah, it's interesting.
And you will not go above that stat.
What if there's a book and there's like six in it at some point?
Yeah.
Well, it's not primary purpose is to be porn then.
What is it?
There's this really great anime called Kite, I think, and it's by some director who's really famous, who I forget.
And it's beautifully animated, and he's got a couple things like...
Nezo Forte is another one that's like that, that has some of like just the best hentai fat material in the game.
And yet, it's just in the context of this other story where there's just like...
It's like a detective sort of story where there's, you know, spies and it's adventure.
And yet, there's just these incredibly detailed sex scenes that are...
They're just super fappable.
They're just incredibly fappable.
And they're just in the context of this bigger piece of art.
So I don't even know...
It feels kind of separate.
It's almost like in Fate Stay Night, like the sex scenes feel very like removable from the story.
In the same way, these scenes...
Like, it's funny because most of them are just like dream sequences, at least in Mezo Forte.
So they're like completely removable.
But in Kite, the other one, they are actually kind of a characterization of this woman who like...
She's like a secret agent spy lady, and she is, you know, being controlled by this like evil policeman.
And you know, he has sex with her.
I feel like we're getting a little off topic here.
What exactly is it to you, Ben, about porn that makes it not valid?
It's not that it's not valid at all.
It's just less valid.
Because it all falls back on the same fucking...
It all amounts to the same thing in the end.
It all comes down to the same exact emotional response being evoked in it basically the same way again and again.
And it's cheap and it's tawdry, and nobody learns anything.
But if you, in theory, if you want to make like an artistic porn and try to evoke like other emotions, why can't you?
And also, I disagree.
It all comes down to the same feeling.
Like, sometimes I feel it more in my ass sometimes based on the context of the porn.
That's gross.
You feel it in your ass when you're watching the porn.
The idea of porn is to usually get your rocks off.
And if it's distraised from that, then it's not really porn.
Yeah, if you take a porn and you fucking just...
Well, that's like a no-true Scotsman for artistic mediums.
Yeah, you know, I guess it is.
And yet, if you take, I don't know, fucking, I don't know, porn of the week number 77
and you slap fucking Catcher in the Rye in the middle of it.
Like, have you made, have you then created a thoughtful and engaging work of pornography?
I would say no.
So you're saying that what you don't like about pornography is that it's just, you know, it doesn't matter how it gets there.
If it gives you an erection, then it's done its job and that's what it means to be a porn.
Yes.
Well, it just so happens.
That in itself is not artistic.
In order to be artistic, but to have something else would change it from porn into something that is not porn.
Look, that's an important question because the question here is, are there art mediums you think are crap?
If porn serves one, if it is a tool with which to get off as opposed to learn anything, then it's just not art.
It's not art if all you're getting from it is this one function.
It's very simple, please.
There is an artistic quest in making something that you can enjoy and also fab to at the same time.
I agree.
Why did my game keep going up?
I don't know.
It is art and there is artistry involved in it and I have read porn that has impressed me artistically
and yet I just don't think that it can ever exist and be worthy on the same fucking level as, you know, other stuff.
I'll tell you why.
It just so happens that there is a porn that was specifically made to confront this theme of whether or not porn should be considered art
or should be discussed in artistic circles and it's a comic called Lost Girls by Alan Moore, the creator of Watchmen.
And then the premise of the story is that all these public domain characters, Dorothy from The Wizard of Oz,
Alice from Alice in Wonderland and Wendy from Peter Pan, is during that era of like World War One,
they meet up together in a hostel somewhere in Europe and they get to talking and they talk about their sexual awakenings
and the whole story is about, you know, the stories of these characters retold through the lens of pornography of them
finding out about their sexuality and getting fucked and sucking cock and it's these underage girls sucking cock
and that's the porn aspect and it's hot and sexy.
But the whole reason that it was written is because Alan Moore felt like sex is underrepresented in literature
and he felt like it should be...
Because sex is...
What is like...
Even if it's just there to come, what's invalid about that?
Like coming is the most important part of human existence.
It's just as human as any other emotion.
You know, I kind of agree and like I think that like a work of fiction or like a work of prose or literature
can have like explicit sex in it and be good.
I don't think that makes it porn.
But it is porn.
Jack off to run and it's cool.
If the purpose of it is to make you jack off...
The purpose of it was to have sex in it.
Listen, if the purpose of that, of Lost Girls...
I've heard about Lost Girls, I haven't read it.
If the purpose of it is to get you off, then it's porn.
If the purpose of it is to confront themes of is porn art and it's not porn, it's art.
Why can't the purpose be both?
I guess...
I guess it can be both.
I think it's just how you're defining porn.
I have a question for Ben.
Is part of this resentment towards porn part of...
Is it your virgin rage?
Well, no.
Maybe.
No, is it part of like your disdain for artists who just make loads of money by just appealing to the lowest common denominator
slacking tits and making the tits bigger and then they get millions of pounds?
Is that the thing?
Yes!
Yes, that makes it mad and I think it's wrong and a sin.
Making something that I find hot enough to want to download is like...
Everyone should be in jail.
Everyone should be in jail and in hell.
Everyone should go to jail and then be put into hell jail.
You know, making something that I find hot enough to actually want to download is like always an exciting thing.
Like, wow, this is a thing that really appeals to my interests and aesthetic sensibilities so much that I'm going to revisit it.
And it's like they have so many specific tastes and interests that are like so underrepresented
and I find that finding people who actually make that product to be really exciting
just as much as someone making a video game that does what I want a video game to be.
I don't even disagree with any of that.
But it doesn't change how I feel.
What about for example...
For example, Playboy has always made it a sticking point of having tasteful nudity
as opposed to porn, like hardcore pornography, which is so prevalent.
Like, Playboy always talks itself up as a little bit artistic
and it kind of is.
I don't believe anyone has jacked off to a Playboy since the internet was invented.
It's the most unarousing, like, tame.
It's basically like looking at a girl's ankle at this point.
But like you still...
You can rip out pages from a Playboy and you can plaster them all over your wall.
I have a wall of beautiful naked women.
What's wrong with that?
It's tastefully nude photography and it's artistic because I say it is.
Well, this really all hinges on the definition of art.
What purpose does art serve and does porn meet the qualification?
Enough!
I've held my tongue for too long.
Welcome back to Listen Buddy Episode 3!
Sex Redux with your host, Munchy wears tiny hats.
As you all know, I hate sex with the passion.
And you will learn soon enough, sex is gross and I hate it with all my bean.
That's why I hate porn because it makes me think about sex.
I hate it so much and you don't even know.
Are you just being selfish and short-sighted, Munchy?
Because other people might enjoy porn.
No, I hate sex.
No one can like sex because it looks gross and it feels gross.
It's not even good.
It doesn't have any artistic merit and it's not cool.
I don't think people are cool who have sex.
Anyone who's ever had sex isn't cool.
Every time I go down in a woman and I get over zealous and I get way too toothy,
she goes, I hate sex with all my bean.
That's disgusting.
Overall, I'm sort of on the same wavelength as Ben is.
In general, with thinking of certain mediums as superior to others.
The whole everything is art and it's all subjectivity and stuff.
That is really fascinating and really inspiring when you're 15 learning about art and shit.
By now, I'm totally bored of all that subjectivity.
Everything is relative stuff.
At this point, I just have to come out and think that video games and animation
are two mediums that are cut above the rest.
And sequential art is a cut above the rest.
When Munchy is talking about how he's planning on making a comic or something,
I'm like, yeah, when you make a comic,
you will have produced a work that is of significantly more value
than any individual set of drawings that you could make.
And like me myself, I'm working on learning how to make video games
because I think video games as just the most powerful medium in existence.
Why would I not want to do that?
Why would I be stuck just making YouTube videos?
I agree, kind of.
Well, I don't agree with all of your categorizations,
but I do believe that there should be a hierarchy.
And you know what?
I honestly think that sequential art is at the top
and then animation is below it
and then video games are way below that.
What a surprise.
The comic boy thinks that comics are the only thing there.
Yeah, I know it's obvious.
Wait, no, no, no, pros.
Pros is better than video games, but below animation.
This is the stupidest shit I've ever heard.
I don't know.
We should get too much into the hierarchy
because I have a very well-defined tier list that I will bring up.
Well, hang on. What was Hippo saying?
Well, I mean, if we're going to just say,
well, I like this one more than that one
and then just have a list and then we're all going to disagree.
I mean, what's that going to do?
Yeah, that's bullshit.
It's going to be fun and we're going to argue about it.
We're going to yell, we're going to scream,
we're going to cry about it for an hour and a half.
No, are we done?
Are we done with porn?
Because I wanted to talk about porn.
I like really, really cool castles.
I like architecture.
I like medieval architecture.
That's my favorite art form.
Castles are way cooler than Homestuck.
Architecture is the lowest.
Castles are fucking gay. They're overused.
They aren't even cool.
They're always gray and dusty.
That's why I hate Dark Souls.
Architecture is the best man and utilitarian.
Yeah, that's the thing.
Dark Souls is only one step above analysis.
Really, architecture is just pornography for manual labor.
Here's the fucking...
There we go.
Animation, video games, movies, comics.
Munchy, calm the fuck down from it.
Let Hippo finish this goddamn thought.
The only reason Dark Souls is good is because it evokes
imagery of castles and medieval weaponry
and I really like all those things.
So people who make physical, real things,
3D sculptures, sculptures, architecture,
that's the best, that's the coolest stuff.
Physical objects are the worst.
Do you ever just go on the internet
and shut the fuck up
and never speak to me ever again?
There's no internet.
Physical objects are inherently inferior
to digital and intellectual.
This infuriates me about
fucking art fags.
You're always thinking about if I just draw all these great pictures
think about all the great things I'll be able to do.
No, don't you understand that the entire purpose of art
is to make real life better
to improve our actual tangible lives?
That's the whole point.
The purpose of art is to be itself
and be cool.
We're gonna run up against a wall.
We're gonna reach the end of that journey one day
and then we're gonna say,
well, let's make some more pictures.
I don't give a fuck about pictures anymore.
We're gonna reach the end of the journey.
We're gonna hit, we're gonna be Starfleet
and then everyone's gonna be like, there's nothing left to do.
There's nothing left.
There's no point.
So life, humanity is doomed.
There's no point to anything.
Art is meaningless.
We're gonna get to the end.
We're gonna be Starfleet.
There's gonna be nothing left to do except fucking art
and it's just gonna exist for its own sake
because there's gonna be no other purpose
that it needs to fulfill.
I like standing in a place
that's really cool.
Looking at a mountain range is cool to be there
but it's not cool to look at a picture of.
It's cool because you know how cool it is to be
looking at a mountain range in real life.
Feeling that wind on your face.
Art replicates life, right?
Art is just derivative.
Art is all not real.
Everything that's real is cool.
I like going outside, I like looking at mountains,
I like seeing bricks, I like looking at rocks.
Literally nothing that is real is cool.
Nope.
I love everything that's real.
Never before in the history of the PCP
have I felt more like I'm just in a room
with insane people yelling at me.
Everything that's being said by everyone
is completely insane.
Like you yourself consider the mediums
YouTube and critique to be inferior
to almost all the other ones
and you dislike having to work within those mediums.
You make the same value judgements.
Yeah, obviously
it's all relative
there's no medium better than the other
but on a day by day basis
everyone has these preferences.
I hate YouTube because everyone on it sucks.
It doesn't mean I don't think it can be great.
YouTube can be just as great as any other medium.
Every medium has potential to be
astounding.
The medium of web video
is just as good as any other medium
but the format of
for example
video game analysis
or anime analysis
or any form of video criticism
is inherently low and piss porn.
I believe that criticism is not art
and should never be considered art.
Of course.
This is why I didn't give a fuck
about the whole discussion of porn really
because
is like a bullshit
genre of film
that we arbitrarily have decided
what defines a porn
and as we just saw with our whole argument
people value those things differently
and our definition can change
but none of that matters
because the point is
it's communicating things
and it's either going to do that or not
and then each of those ideas can be weighed for their value
or if they don't fucking accomplish anything
then obviously it's not worth having it
saying that like
French 19th century film
about the Alps
are like
that's my favorite genre
that's the best art form right there
that's equally arbitrary to me
is saying porn is all
whatever
but we can fucking define
we can define what porn is
even though the lines can be blurred
we can say porn is art
whose purpose is to get you off
and like we can take that
and go from there
and let me talk for a second
you know how like movies
are like they do like shit
and you're like happy about it
and you're also sad sometimes
they can make you feel different emotions
porn only makes you feel one emotion
and if it doesn't then it's not porn
I've decided
you know what
I don't know
I feel like there's a lost art to porn
I feel like there are things
I feel like what I value in a porn
is a rare is rare
and might actually be art
is it blacks?
no
I just go to black.com dude
I think that like the ultimate porn
would probably involve
some like deeply personal
emotional arc
that led you through all these characters
like innermost feelings and like culminated
yeah but Ben
if they made that you would just say
well that's not porn then
you're right
I think the ultimate porn
is the one that most speedily and most efficiently
gets you to orgasm as quickly as possible
that would be the ultimate porn
and whatever that requires
it's cheaper to have any merit cause it's gay
if there was porn
that made me like literally fall in love with people
and then like
just made me like cry tears of joy
seeing them have sex with each other
I would be like this porn is art
even the greatest film ever made
has never achieved that
there are some that aspire to that
but dude even the greatest drama
that's not what porn is at its core
even the greatest film
has never achieved that for anyone ever
so how could like porn
a sub genre
a small niche thing within all the film
possibly accomplish that
like I think you're setting your expectations way too high
through the media
my point is what it aspires to
most porn at its core
doesn't try to do that
porn at its core really just tries to get you off
every single artistic medium
or format
is all just a set of guidelines and boundaries
of what we decide that that format can be
and sooner or later by the very nature of it
someone in that little
in that box of guidelines
is going to make something that pushes on those boundaries
and possibly even breaks them out
so you can't just sit there
and as soon as something breaks those boundaries
say that it's not that thing anymore
if it started as that thing and pushed on those boundaries
then that makes it totally
just as valid as anything outside those boundaries
you fucking clods
it can still be valid without being
the thing
it's like a similar thing
but it's not quite the thing
but it's so easy to say that I don't think that this medium
is as valid as that medium
but then when this medium impresses you
that's not this medium anymore
that's completely recocculus and cockamamie
I have a very narrow definition of porn
any sex ever
so that can be applied to any movie or comic
and I'll always be upset
and when they leave those peer views
then I'm happy about it
and then it's fine
Game of Thrones literally shows you goose dicks
that's porn
yeah
I'm just saying you see
no one hates a sex as much as me
they get known throughout the land
I am the ultimate anti-sex crusader
does that make you redpilled
or bluepilled
have we discussed before?
I'm a green pill
Munchy is the leader
ever since Count Graduon was defeated
Munchy is the new leader
of the private villa of corrupted citizens
preventing Christian West and Chandler from getting laid
of course
I've expanded the group's ambitions
to not only Christian West and Chandler
but the entire universe
you're doing God's work
I really feel like I can't relate to this whole
talking about the
artistic endeavors of porn
because most porn is about sex
and sex is very normal
it happens a lot
so it's really easy to justify a context for it
I seek out porn where not normal things happen
so there's a lot of questions about how to make that
narratively occur
and so I get really excited with
this is an incredible context
to make this, that and that
happen all in the same narrative
god damn
I completely get where you're coming from
but does that have to occur in porn then?
is that related to the act of having sex?
it sounds like
let me backpedal
and be like okay
there have been pornographic stories
and materials that have actually really impacted me
and left me with a lasting impression
and been like wow that was art
but
there have been way more
that has just been hot
and has gotten me off
and what I would consider
good porn
and yet I don't think it's art
so it's like porn was just
an extra layer that may as well
didn't have to be there for that story to be told
it was just there
exactly
there have been some that have done both
it has happened
would it be smarter of us to define porn
to use what the word porn
as sort of an attachment
to a piece of artwork that can exist independently
or with this extra label of porn
it's obviously not a medium
no I don't think so
we'll see where that's what we're arguing about here
it's much more genre
I think it's a porn if it's purpose is to get you off
it can be anything
it can even be actual sex
and I will consider it porn
like medium I believe used to mean literally
are you using a paintbrush or a chisel
so obviously porn is not a medium
real life for example
is a totally crass
and commercial and artistically
worthless work of pornography
of course
you guys are overcomplicating it
it just has sex therefore it's shit
well none of us agree with you on that
you're all just weird puritans
I can't believe I've been friends with you this long
now I mean
we're arguing about artistic merit
what is the
I don't even know
I don't know what art even means
what has more artistic merit than fucking
in life nothing
define art as you say it
artistic merit
what does that mean
art is stuff that's good and I like
sex
anyone if you want
if you have something that you want to create
and then you create it then you have made art
and if that art
if I watch that art
and I go wowee
you've made great art and there you go
holy shit Jesse thank you
that was a definition I've always come with
by that definition are fruit roll-ups also art
because they make me say wowee
made of fucking like melted shoe bottoms
I know but I love that
that's my favorite thing
if two people come together to create human beings
is that art
that's building art
I would say yes
the fact of raising a child could be interpreted
raising a child
we're getting off top
we're not supposed to be talking about what is art
because that's a nebulous fucking means nothing
we're talking about like the hierarchy
if one exists
let's talk about other things
like we've touched upon
the medium of web video
and whether it's valuable
and we've touched upon
oh god what was that other thing
there were some other things that was brought up
I don't know
I guess I've been arguing
analysis and critique
it is analysis and critique art
yes it is
it's definitely art
you know what it's exactly like porn
you can have an analysis
or a critique
that has elements
that are artistically valid and valuable
but the critique itself is not art
well okay I guess if critique
literally just means placing judgment on a thing
like if you do it with no creativity
whatsoever
then it's not artistic
but any review is going to be artistic
on some level so that's why it's called a medium
well any pornography is artistic
on some level you kind of like where do you put the camera
what music do you put over it etc
there's this general sense of
if a medium is largely bullshit
then it's lower on the hierarchy
because like porn
a lot of porn is shit a lot of reviews
are complete garbage
that are good so like the medium itself
is fine all the mediums are fine
no it's not what I'm saying
I think that it's not about the
it's not just that most of it is bad
I think that it is inherently less valuable
yeah I agree
when I watch a really great anime
porn and criticism this is true of both of these things
okay you know what we should frame this
the idea of them isn't good
I think we should frame this
I think it makes a lot more sense
we're going deep but it makes a lot of sense
to do it from the way that Ben was initially talking about it
like there are people out there
who make tons of money drawing porn
and then there are people who make
you know like much more
I just like there's much more
thought put into like your average
comic of you know X amount of like
they're just like a picture
of a porn that is drawn with great technical skill
like I drew a monster girl she has big tits and a big dick
give me a hundred thousand dollars
that person is rewarded more by society
in the form of they get more money
to make an impact of porn
as opposed to just porn itself
well that's the whole thing the artistic mediums
that we think are crap is the question
so it's about our perception of
I just think that
medium is
it's just a way of expressing yourself
and you have preferences
depending on who you are and what you like
here's what I think about
well here's what I think about
criticism
aside from any other like artistic
considerations or additions
to a work of criticism the criticism
itself derives
all of its value from an existing
work of art being criticized
therefore it can't
the criticism itself yes
therefore it can't ever be
as valuable as the work of art from which
it derives its value it has to
be inferior
listen Ben listen to this great example
right here I forget what but there was some
movie you'll probably know the name of this
there's some movie that was made
it was like a Hollywood movie it was a complete
bust everyone working on it got fucked over
and nobody liked it
maybe you've heard of it its name was Star Wars
there was a
there was a documentary made about
this film that I can't remember the name of
that is like
much more celebrated
of a piece of
of art that was about
the making of this film
that details like the crazy experiences
that were had by the people trying to make
it was a troll too
it's very similar to that I think it's a
different movie but it's
talking about the making of
it's like the artistic value
of this no no no
yeah that is right that is not
a criticism of the movie
it is in part that is one of the things
that's when it started out as
now we're talking about all the other stuff
that's ancillary to the actual criticism
here's a here's how I think
I can't add anything to a criticism
other than just the criticism of the piece
which is obviously not true
that's not true
specifically in the case of Sonic the Hedgehog
a series where
god damn it Tavu we're not talking about Sonic the Hedgehog
we're talking about this other example
about uh
you know
has resulted in lots and lots of amazing reviews
and analysis from which I derive
so much enjoyment and indeed
all of the criticism that that franchise has seen
it all comes from details present
in the games themselves
if you want to use a metaphor you could say it's like
um cooking raw ingredients
that have these like flavors
that are trapped inside of them that you couldn't just
eat right off the shrub
it wouldn't be able to get the enjoyment but when processed
correctly by a critique
it draws out those uh those ingredients
and that's
that's something that was in the original piece
similar stuff like
the huge uh analysis
of the enchanted series
is much more entertaining than playing any of the
uncharted games
at least the first one
and also the game grumps let's play of Sonic 06
is obviously much more entertaining
than playing the game
so derivative things can be better
than the original
I think there's something misguided
about trying to argue this on the basis of
you can make a good criticism
of a bad game
that doesn't really seem to be answering the question
I have solved this
dilemma about critique and criticism
and everyone needs to not say a single
goddamn word until I finish making this
point
we're all talking about critique and
criticism as though it has
lower value as art than other art
but the fact is critique and
criticism should not be considered art
and therefore it's worth
is irrelevant to this conversation and also
fucking
ugh
the way I see it
I agree that it's not art
you can't disagree
because the point is not finished being made
I thought you finished
rather than
seeing critique and criticism
as
artistic mediums we should see them
as what they are which is artistic
tools they are not art they are tools
to make art with
every work of art has some element of criticism
or critique or satire already in it
as part of its creation
so talking about criticism as though
it's a medium of art unto itself
is misguided and flawed and stupid because
critique and criticism
is essentially a paintbrush or a pencil
it's just another tool to make art with
okay yeah
okay with that
would you say that
wrestling isn't wrestling
that's a youtube video
that's a man making art
with the tool of critique
yeah so
would the medium be a film or a youtube video
or something what would you call that
any
great analysis video that you've seen
like a matthew matosis he's just making
he's making art
with the tool of critique
nice
if I make
if you make a parody of something
or a satire or something you're making
your own work of art with
your critique of another thing
I agree with this
so the art itself is the video
that's being made
the critique is just
something you're using to make the video
I agree with this but
and I guess the way to differentiate
videos from one another is to use genres
so analysis would also be
a genre of video
my point is I just don't think that it's relevant
or fair to
I mean I don't think the hierarchy idea is fair
in general but to put like critique
and criticism like at the bottom of the hierarchy
is not fair because it shouldn't be even
in the hierarchy at all it's a tool
well it's funny is that
to devils advocate this
as I said a little bit ago that
originally like medium meant
what tools you used
like the medium of a painting
versus a sculpture
so like you know
anyway I actually agree entirely
with your point based on the current definition
of medium but I just figure some people
are going to be pedantic about this
that's fair so it's like
saying that like if I am a
landscape painter
and I make the best landscape
paintings I can and you know people like them
or they don't that's one thing but then
if fucking Ben St
landscape painting critic
Waltz is by my booth
at the local art
landscape convention
yeah the landscape convention
is a youtuber who makes videos
in which he analyzes landscape paintings
that is like a whole different medium
that should obviously not be
directly compared to me
as a landscape painting creator
those are two very different types of art
they are very different
well yeah they're completely different
no they're yeah but they're not different
in the same way like a painting
and a work of prose are both
you know they're both aspiring to create
can you compare a sculpture to a video game
I think you can
I think you can more than you can compare
a criticism to
a book
it's just gonna be hard it's just gonna be really
like like state your case that
like the Venus de Milo
is a better piece of art than
Undertale you know whatever
like you know you can you can
I think you can argue that
the thing that we just just you know
discussed is that critique is not
an art form it's the medium
in which you're explaining
your critique is the art
so if you're making a YouTube video
you can compare a YouTube video critiquing
something else because it's a video
it's a thing in itself it's part of a
right right well anyway obviously
and I think it would and I think it would
come up short because
what it amounts to
is criticism
which is not artistically
on the same fucking wavelength
it's a video which means it can have more
than criticism in it it can have visuals and stuff
and it's gonna be really good it's gonna be the best video
you've ever seen so like there's no
you're right you're right and therefore it's not the
criticism that you like or that you
this is why and going back
criticism itself that's the art
right and going back to it like
a porn as in
a film with you know
sex for the viewer's sexual
gratification can in fact be
the best art piece in it because that porn
element is one element of it
and therefore as we've just discussed
it can have other elements as well
that may elevate it may synchronize with the porn
elements I actually think that
I would say that the porn
part is art whereas the criticism isn't
like I think that I think that
I think that like the sex part is like it's
more it's more comparable to other art
criticism is we need to
to make sure we understand
the difference between a tool used
to create art
you know a medium of art
if everything is a tool
to use to make a video like
the camera, the lighting, the people
having sex
the size of the penis, is that a tool
in the porn
it is
if those all go into a video
are we
arguing what tools
are better than others or what
whether videos are better than music
or whatever
like the current definition of medium
is the delivery method like if you were
to print out all of the assembly
code for Super Mario World on the paper
it would no longer be a video game though
it would technically be the same work
made with the same tools plus a printer
I'm lost
well anyway the argument is over
because video games are the best medium
because they have all the other mediums
but also interactivity argument over
that's dumb there's no the best medium
totally disagree
I'm lucky of mediums where I very clearly
well define
it's time for me to bust out
my fucking fallacy
I'm gonna bust out the fallacy of
saying that Davoo is wrong because he agrees
with someone who is bad
you know who else thinks that same exact thing
fucking Phil Fish, Davoo
therefore you're wrong because I've
associated you with a bad person
guilty by association
I've done it, I've succeeded
every single time I've heard people talk
about these terrible Phil Fish quotes
I'm like this guy is hilarious, this guy kicks ass
yeah
Phil Fish literally says in Indie Game the movie
that video games are the ultimate medium
because it's all the other mediums plus interactivity
yeah
I mean it doesn't like some they have the same
stupid facial hair
me too
I don't agree with that sentiment logically
it just like
emotionally it makes perfect sense to me
because that's why I like video games the most
it's like you know when I
I don't agree because interactivity can come between
an artistic message
as easily as it can
things will come between things in porn too
some games can use the interactivity
to make it better, some games have
an interactivity because it's a game
which makes the experience worse than if you're just watching it
yeah
it's true
I disagree
I want someone to program
the godfather with cut scenes where
you push like quick time events to make the scene
continue
interactivity is another tool
you can't like mathematically say
that a medium is better than others
because it comprises elements
of those other mediums
the best work of art
in any medium
is better than all the mediocre works
of art in every other medium
yeah
I know
I know you're right Jesse I just don't want to
quit being mad
well okay we've been talking about this a lot
I think that's the theme of this entire episode actually
starting from the
topic
it's animation, video games, movies,
comics, lists
wait much you start over please
start from the top and then going down
animation, video games
movies, comics, music
books
and then I would put
our books even above
zero or they under the zero level
I would say they're
they do more damage than good
oh oh oh sculpture is below book
I'm going to go with
so is individual paintings and drawings
okay
video games, then animation
then sequential art, then live action
film, then music
then books actually probably put music
above live action film
and I sort of think of youtube videos
as sort of like it's own like zero
place it's like I don't care about it
as much as any of the others and yet I care
about it more than any of the others it's like it's own
dimension
okay cool well I don't actually want to hear everybody
I want to say mine I want to say that
sequential art and pros are at the top
I would say that I would say animation
is underneath both
pros why the fuck would you put animation
below comics how can you defend that
I have my reason because it's gay
music is at the very bottom
yeah for some that I just feel that
I just feel that in my heart and so I'm going
to go with it uncritically
I would like to say that when I say sculpture
it's not just like things in museums
and whatever it's just like
the feeling of being in the presence of
something physical and real which no other
thing has
yeah Ben's talking about those 2D bullshit
that isn't even real
you know what
actually that's not sculpture and individual
paintings and drawings are the worst
yeah I agree with that
I just want to say that
I can't upload those to my soundcloud account
you know what true art
the highest form of art has an emotional
arc to it and a static
image I mean I guess it can
have an emotional arc to it but it usually
doesn't it doesn't lend
it doesn't lend itself to the having
of an emotional arc same with the sculpture
this whole conversation
music can have an emotional arc to it
and therefore it's better
this whole conversation is completely insane
there's no hierarchy
every artistic medium has the same
amount of prestige and value
which is no prestige and value
the mediums themselves have no goddamn value
the works of art within said mediums
are what have the goddamn value
this whole conversation is goofy
well the reason why I like to
hierarchy things like this is because it helps me
in making decisions as to what media
I want to consume and also create
and also promote it just makes it
like easy shorthand it makes it very
convenient for me I don't agree with that
because I don't actually want to consume
any works of art even in the mediums that I
purport to like so
well it's all fucking shit
there you go
good then you're a reasonable person
I just wanted to explain that I like
being in physically around stuff
rather than looking at a screen
that's just generally my preference
I think most of the art I consume
is manga
that's good that's high tier
that's high tier you're doing it right
hooray for me I'm glad I'm on your
that's around mid tier
you know what you know what it is you know what it is
you know why I put animation below sequential art
is because it commu
okay okay
you can communicate like
a little more through
animation you can communicate
stuff in a moving picture
than you can in a static one but not
enough more to justify
like the fucking like the amount
of extra work that it takes
oh so now it's an equation you have to do
of effort input versus what you're able to get
the work it takes to do something
and how much money it costs it doesn't matter to the art
whatsoever
okay that's true
fuck shit dammit
there goes your
I would say that like yeah animation
is like it has to like
it's sense of time has to be more realistic
which can be good but you know
when something is sequential art it can like
tell stories with a specific kind of
pace that doesn't have to make complete
considerations for the sense of time
digi actually has an old video about this
called the problem with adapting
shown in fight manga where it's like
the problem with pacing and so much anime
is that manga isn't written to like
make sense with time and that's a power
that sequential art has it can just sort of exist
in this nether realm of time
yeah that's an advantage I
acknowledge that that's true though I think you probably
could animate it
I don't know you have control
it wouldn't take too much to just make a brand new
medium by just changing a few of the rules
of any given thing that already exists
well like there's only so many senses
that you can appeal to at once
I mean we could add smellovision you know
suppositories
like animation and film
let's not smell them they all have like rules
they have like things they need money they need to be
on tv they need to be made for certain
things
and you can just take a medium
and fuck it up like that book that's like
all fucked up you know that one the house
leaves or whatever house leaves yep that's a
book that's not really a book
you just make it it's a book well guys
I know your point though
to I have actually
been lying this entire time
oh yes because
is that the kayfabe commander because
you there is
a specific medium of art
that I detest so much
that I view it as having inherently
less value than
any other artistic medium
is it and that medium
is slam poetry
yep yep yep
yep
now I've never
defined slam poetry I'll define it
for you and I'll clarify that I think
that poetry
itself is invaluable as art poetry
is
demonstrably valuable
but as a raps man I thought you would be
sort of in tune with your
poetic side slam poetry is not rap
slam poetry is a perversion of poetry
and rap it's like you took the worst aspects
of rap and poetry and combined them
into one and the one
depressing stew with a disgusting
the toxic brew that turns you
into a that video
I hate religion but I
love Jesus that's I'm gonna get to that
yeah that's what slam poetry
is poetry
which is fine which is which is beautiful
it's art there's plenty of room to
you can make a man cry with a good poem
someone writes a poem
but that's not good enough for them
they have to they have to get up
and they have to speak this poem
with all the all the bad acting power
they can possibly muster to try to
to try to force an emotion into you
by way of their voice yelling
it at you and they put
they put it on YouTube they put some cheesy
like some public domain music behind
to make it seem more inspirational
and they just recite their bad poetry
but they recite it in this arrogant
aggressive pseudo-intellectual
pompous pretentious way
that's just this is my poetry
and you will love my poetry
and you have to feel something because
I'm smart there's this one motherfucker on
YouTube who he does
this slam poetry shit about like
Christianity and God and shit
he's hugely popular he's got like
you know he's on Facebook all the time
by everyone's crappy religious relatives
every day on Facebook
it's just this like this
this dweeby fucking this douchey looking
motherfucker with like a buzz cut
he looks like fucking the main
character from the Assassin's Creed games
not any of the assassins I mean the guy who's sitting
in the fucking the the animus that fucking
loser he looks like that guy
and he stands in front of like some
government building
in like a hoodie with like the color saturation
way down so it looks like it's like a gray
a sad day
and he's just brightening your life with this
these words of wisdom and he stands there
and he starts talking about Jesus people don't
believe in God anymore
well I don't believe in people who don't
believe in God because
Jesus came to take my sins
and make me and it's like shut up
you're ruining poetry you're ruining
rap you're ruining human discourse you're even
fucking ruining religion you stupid
smug pretentious motherfucker I hope
you get crucified you faggot
I I hate to be
nitpicky but is this
it sounds a little bit like it's criticizing
you know like I don't know like
like new metal
for being like a shitty version of a
particular genre of music
is that wrong is that wrong
hey hey I don't know about slam
poetry on YouTube I don't know about that but I will
say that I have been severely annoyed by poetry
that I have heard like at parties
that I have been to where like someone
there is a poet and like they've like
read their poetry out in a fucking
thing yeah I have been severely
annoyed by the way in which
all so much poetry that people
write and that read and that they take so much
pride in just sounds like it was written
for the purpose of sounding like poetry
and it's all delivered in this very
like this very like quote-unquote
poetic way yeah and it's just like a
series of lofty and evocative
images like you know with some kind of emotional
just add water
poetic cadence that's like
it's like it's like it's like yeah
it's yeah it's like they're doing it
just because they think it's supposed to be
that way it's like it's like bag serial
depth yeah can there be
no good slam poet though
I listen to a poet I listen to
someone reading their poetry like that and I think
doesn't this fucker know that
art is meant to engage
the audience and like I'm sitting
here being bored out of my mind by this
cookie cutter bullshit you've written and I
feel like no effort has been made to engage
me the audience which is what it's supposed
to do and it's never even like clever like it's
never cleverly put together there's no clever
like structure or rhythm or wordplay
to it it has it's always right and it's not
even like clever like topics it's always like
my dad beat me or I'm a feminist and here's
why or I love Jesus and here's
why there's there's no attempt at just
the corny is shaken up and like surprise
the corny's mother fuckers there's no surprise to it
you know what I hate it there has to be
there has to be something in there that will like
surprise me or else why do I bother listening to
you know what this sounds to me like it sounds like
these people have been doing this and they
they have been told that their performance is
sufficient for the effect they're trying to
achieve of connecting to the audience when
actually that was people just telling them that
it was sufficient when actually it's clearly not
complete like people that write this kind of
cookie cutter poetry that you hear at any
fucking bullshit party of some assholes
getting together and reading their shit it's
they're just complacent here's what it is
they're not they're not they're just not trying
hard enough here's what it is to me it's
a good poem does
not ever need to be
spoken to someone
you read a poem and you feel something if
it's fucking well if it's a good poem if it's
a good point or it's well put together
you can just read it if you
have to like force if you
have to audibly force an emotion into
the audience then you have not written a good
poem you've written a bad poem and you
should be ashamed of yourselves
you know what I got a poem for you guys
tell me tell me I know
this you see this is what a good poem is
and you're you're gonna resonate with this
okay here we go this is called Malia's
poem
dear dad I mean dear president
24 65
always on the job wait who's that
woman and where's my
Malia fuck that's
it that's the whole poem say all of it
there you go that's that's the important
part that's my favorite part
making fun of it
it's the best I don't get it
this listen buddy
episode with your fucking
with your crass
derivative artwork
that doesn't have any value
outside of just referencing
another video
it's like this piece down
and I'm not saying that like
I'm not saying that like reading a poem
invalidates the poem
I'm saying that if a poem has to be read
to have value then it's not a good
poem like no one would read that
ever like read that Jesus guys poems
and think they were deep unless you were like already
your religious moron so never mind
but like for example
I've I've done like open
Mike and I've read poems that I've written
on most of my you know the poems
that I that I there's a video of me doing it
but like the poems that I had written to recite
there were like meant to make people laugh
and like each line was a little punchline and like
you know like who invented the fart
he must have been awfully smart as hard to define what a glorious
time we have in the flatulence starts that's just like
it's just people just hear that and they chuckle
it's just like a little belly laugh like a little belly
laugh lyric and that's fine or like the poem
that I wrote about the newlyweds and there they're both
gross and I'm just like describing
like gross people fucking and each line
makes people laugh that's not what I'm talking about
I'm just talking about like the pseudo
deep pretentious fucking
my my father beat me and I'm a feminist
who believes in Jesus too much
kind of like yeah with the with the
inspirational music the inspirational
music is what gets me the most it's so fucking
transparent
I hate all inspirational music all the time
but you use it
all the time in your videos
I make it inspirational
by the way I use it
it's me with the I'm the one
who supplies the inspiration not the music
but anyway
in fact I'm the one making the music
inspirational when I put music
in my videos
books are not sharing great books are high tier
books are the lowest tier
God damn it that's ridiculous
books are fucking how can you
books are pure books are artistically pure
how can you not place value
on like the the inherent
unique intonation and rhythm of the
written word by various different authors
it's obvious
because mum because fucking
munchy can't read
you can't fucking speak bitch
I just got it right I fixed
my yeah okay yeah
I bet you got it right
we've been talking about mediums as the modern
definition of them is the you know partly it comes
down to like the the means by which
the information is delivered
to the to the consumer and
Jesse himself has a video
criticizing heavily the medium with
which prose is usually
delivered to the consumer in the form of a book that you can't
really hold in any one position
that will be comfortable for that video is retarded
it should never be taken seriously
by anyone who's gonna make
that video yeah obviously physical
media is terrible but like what
that what a book is is getting
to you like the pros contained within
a book is artistically pure
and pros and the written word is like it's the
most efficient way
of fucking taking some intellectual
idea or concept or opinion you have
and fucking communicating it to an audience
and it's beautiful yeah I can
pick in moment minute that's right
it's no no it's not pros is
not pros a tool then
because you can use pros to write scripts
for videos exactly
that's what I'm trying to say
what the fuck off what are you talking about
the way you consume a book is different
the way you consume a book is different is worthless
pros is a medium
critique is not a medium
yeah we know critique is not a medium
but however like if you put a critique in a word
visual is good Ben if you put a critique
as a like a book
a book a physical book or a digital book
or whatever and it is a critique of something else
yeah yeah the tool is critique
yeah that's yeah you know Ben
the tool of critique in your fucking
the medium is a book it's not pros
because pros you can fucking
you mean it's not pros Ben if you love
pros so much why don't you go start
the pros crastinators
got em
oh boy
the reason why that whole how
video games encapsulate all the other
mediums and that's why it's the best it's because
when you're reading a book it's like I'm only
the reading part and like there's only
certain parts of my brain that are being in your
dry side when you're playing a video game
all your senses are being done
every that's gay
I have a problem
I have a problem reading books
I know it's probably stupid
to say this out loud
but I just I can't pick up a book and read it
it's too hard
here's why I'm retarded and Jesse's been
here's why I'm retarded
and Jesse's been right all along
wait let me get it real quick
no I need to hear this it's important
alright alright like
sure yeah like maybe
there's more tools
to use in a video game
comics have art in addition
to pros so they're better
but what it really comes down to is that
great art is made
for its medium and if you
make a work that just
takes the medium you're using
and rings every
bit of meaning and feeling and value
out of it then you've got
a great work of art and it doesn't matter
that like pros is a more limited
work or a medium than
sequential art like if you have
fucking used it to its fullest extents
then you've made a great work of art
and in that and so obviously all mediums
are fucking Jesse was right
Ben admitted it Jesse was right everybody
the day is finally come
when fucking everyone admits that I'm
right and always have been about everything the fucking
confetti the balloons are coming down from the
ceiling I was right twice in this podcast
I was right about everything that I said about
every artistic medium they're all having
the same value and I was also right about
slam poetry having even less value
somehow I was right about both of those
I was right about both things somehow
even though they contradicted each other it doesn't matter
that's why I didn't get into the whole hierarchy
I didn't have a hierarchy I didn't give
anything there's no
smart boys there's no hierarchy
but slam poetry is
still at the bottom of it
yeah and that's what I call
a slam dunk of an argument
that no one can fucking topple
it's uh I just noticed that
after I asked for questions on
Twitter at TP Crasinators
one of the first ones was our friend
mumke at mumke away
who asked the question is analysis
an art form so he's still on this topic
and it has been a drag
I was obviously not one
well he can
just listen back I don't care
to repeat all that shit again
okay I think we're done let's go to questions
we've only been going for like 45 minutes
I just said let's go to questions
thoroughly analyzed analysis as well
as Jesse's
inspirational rightness about all
things I think we can move on to questions
now I know I still watch
how much I hate books I have
we get it dude I hate books
I want to hear it I want to hear it
because I like looking at like
colors books usually aren't in colors
like black and white and they're
hard to look at and they're like
they're like gay ones
what about coloring books
nooooo
nooo
that's three
that's a hat trick
I kind of agree that books are hard to look at
I like books to have
at the beginning of the chapter they have a nice little image
and I'm like aha that's nice
then I continue reading
that's because drawings are better than words that's true
It's nice to have a mixture. It's nice to have a mixture of books.
Nope, nope. You were at the first time.
Yeah, you did it.
I love Killers books. I love color books.
They're so good. I love adding red and green.
I love coloring books. They make me feel smart because I'm three years old.
Yeah, dude.
Woo!
Alright, let's go to some questions here.
Hopefully, we'll find some that aren't retarded.
Now remember, everybody,
Santa's questions all the time.
Did you mean to say art retarded or did you mean to say art related?
Who? Me?
Yeah, you.
You said art retarded.
Well, whatever I said, make it the good one.
That's what I intended to say.
Right.
Yeah, everybody, make sure you ask us questions
at tpcrastinators on Twitter.
Everybody, remember, don't be retarded.
Before we do that,
we should mention that this podcast,
this PCP is now on patreon.com.
Oh, you're going to say that at the end.
This week,
we're putting up the patreon.
No, you're underplaying this, guys.
Huge announcement, everybody.
There is in the description
a link to the
procrastinators podcast
patreon link.
We're doing a thing.
We're all of our main weekly episodes like this,
or perhaps the drawcasts when we do them,
or the races, any of our main PCP content
is going to be added to that patreon.
We've got to stretch that.
We're definitely not putting the podcast on there.
Do not worry.
It's only going to be
major PCP
group things
like this main podcast.
The drawcast and races.
Basically, if you like hearing us talk,
but you hate all of us individually
and all of our individual creative endeavors,
you don't have to pay for that bullshit.
I've seen people.
I've seen quite a few people wanting to give money
directly to you.
Word on the street is...
Look at this little fucking bird.
It's dead now, but look, it had a message.
What? Okay.
If you donate amount of money
that I forgot, you're going to get in your
fucking little inbox. You're going to open it.
What's in here? Any more procrastinators?
It's a fucking bonus episode.
It's a bonus episode.
Oh, that's right.
Bonus episode.
$5 at the $5 Patreon amount.
You get access to extra
episode of PCP.
More content that you can literally even
suck.
Is it one a month?
Is it one extra per month?
We're going to do one a month.
This is just an
extra thing that we're going to do
to get people to give us money.
There's a hugely
important factor that needs to be said.
This is not
replacing any of our own Patreons.
If I hear of one goddamn one of two motherfuckers
who unpledged to any of us to pledge to the
PCP, then we'll shut it all down.
We'll shut the whole thing down.
We might.
No one unpledged
from anyone.
We would really prefer that this be
a secondary concern, I think,
for our individual ones.
I would just like to say that
the money from the Patreon
is going to be divided amongst the members
based on how many appearances
they make in the podcast.
On some level, it will also go
to enhancing infrastructure.
For example, we're actually
going to pay someone to edit
so as to stick to a schedule.
We're also in the near future.
Behind the scenes is too much information.
I think that's appropriate to say,
but as soon enough, we'll be working on trying
to get it up on iTunes and shit.
I'm going to pocket all that money.
Everybody!
Skimming a little off the top.
Basically, all that matters.
We're looking to expand and this money
is the way that we can make some
infrastructure enhancements that would
have just come out of our pockets, but otherwise
there will be ways to do it.
Listen guys.
You fans, you all know
that I'm God
and that if you press one
to me right now in the comments
I get even more
power.
But here, if you donate one
dollar,
that's the equivalent of a thousand
times.
I can't believe I didn't think to make
the one dollar pledge like a
monthly related one thing.
I got to do that as soon as we're done.
That's the important thing to remember.
Everyone give us money,
but also still give me money
on top of that.
Patreon.com
Slash.
The pro and fascinators part.
There we go.
Thank you.
I think is what it's called.
It's patreon.com slash the
procrastinators.
If that doesn't work
just click the link in the description.
It might change, but I think that's what it's going to be.
This is going to be the death of us.
That's fucking all
sorted and done with.
We've done it everyone.
It's been a long time coming.
Let's go to some questions.
Here is a one for Munchie
to the group.
What level of Christ consciousness
are you all on?
I'm at the highest level baby.
I'm level 7 bro.
By the way that's by
Chiaro333.
Munchie can you scan me?
I don't know how to figure it out.
Alright.
Let me see.
You got that nice pale skin.
You got those fucking
oh yeah bro.
Alright.
2.
Are most people at 2?
What are most people at?
The default if you're like
if you're like Ben St.
you're at 1.
Man I'm down with
the Christ consciousness.
Ben St. the default man.
What the fuck?
That's like the worst thing anyone's ever said to me.
You open the character creation menu
and just the default
he's just the template
from which you add shit.
That's fucking hilarious.
Here's a question from
our old friend Onwe.
What's our Christ consciousness?
I mean how deep do you want to go?
Give us all a first score.
Alright Jesse
you're at a 4.
Yeah!
That's pretty good.
Your chocolates are moderately aligned.
Nate
You're
you're at a 2.
You have room for improvement.
I agree. I hate Jesus.
Ben is at a 1 of course.
I'm at a 7.
Davoo is at an 8.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Does that mean Jesus is his son?
He just edited his own consciousness
to be Christ low light.
Yeah I know it's fucking cheating
but you know I have to abide by the rules.
It's not a game, not the player.
I love this saying.
I love the fucking Christ consciousness.
That's how you know that
Nate is a fucking zero.
You're a fucking zero.
I'm such a disgusting piece of cake.
We'll have to ask the slam poetry Jesus guided
to know what Christ consciousness truly means.
Yeah.
Christ consciousness is how many dimensions
you can travel basically.
It's high how your consciousness
and how
so I'm a 4 dimensional being
is what you're saying.
And Hippo are you saying?
No I was just
remarking on the fact that Jesse is half the amount of God.
That Davoo is.
Ben's a 1 dimensional being.
I'm a 1 dimensional character.
I'm a flat character.
He's just a line.
Yeah just a line.
Here's a silly question.
Yes.
Here's a silly question,
but it might be interesting to hear.
Anui on me asks,
at what point did you realize you were internet famous?
Right now.
When you asked that question.
I know exactly when I realized it.
Her name was Caitlyn.
None of us are.
I don't think any of us really are.
I realized I was internet famous
when Jesse made cruising with Munchie.
That's when I realized.
Wait what was cruising with Munchie?
It was all the Munchie isms
from the memes that need to die podcast
in its own video with Vaporwave in the background.
I felt internet famous
as soon as Gibb and Take featured
Kagan Phantom in an analysis assemblage.
I agree.
I think generally being put in someone else's video
or someone making a video about you
makes you internet famous.
But the moment
I can definitely
I also felt pretty famous
in my current nonpony incarnation
when
Joji's Magic Supplies made an analysis video
fucking analyzing my comics.
Go watch that.
It's like comparing the Vapers
to Watamote and
one other thing that I forget.
Some wrestling guy recently made
a top 5
he made a top 5 AMVs of all time
even though he's not really an anime guy.
He put MyGurr and Login1 at number 2.
He was weird.
He started it off and was using mine
of how you can make a genius one
in this thing he was doing.
Mine was only number 2
and some Run of the Mill
Full Metal Alchemist Brotherhood one
was number 1.
I don't understand why he set it up that way
if I wasn't going to be number 1.
That was cool. That was nice.
Second best guy ever.
I don't know about...
I just thought that was a weird way to structure it.
That's kind of harder to wrap my head around
but having fans
that actually appreciate me
I remember that first happened as a moment
when some comic was like
I'd be sad if DeVoo stopped making videos
and I'm like whoa
someone would be sad if I didn't exist.
That's way more meaningful than someone being happy
that you do exist.
I agree.
I think of internet famous as something a bit bigger
than just having fans that are in a group
that can be...
It's still thousands of people
I think internet famous is when
you haven't satisfied
some incredibly specific standard
that they think you are obligated to follow
because of your level of fame.
Internet famous truly
is when the first time you get laid
from being a fan.
That's exactly what I was going to say.
I remember the moment where I truly felt
like wow I've made it
was in 2013
when the first time that I fucked a fan
when she got on a plane
and came all the way here
to my dingy little basement
just to cuck her boyfriend
and get the endless D
for three days.
I looked up at the stars
the night that I dropped her off at the airport
to send her back on her way home
because I was done with her.
I went out and I laid in the grass
and I looked at the stars
and I looked at the Big Dipper
and I reminisced about my Big Dipper
going into her.
I said I truly made it
part of the story as well.
Everyone was there.
Donatello was there
and Commander Shepard won
the whole gang.
Did Donatello get a turn?
No. None of my retarded characters
are allowed to encroach on my fornication activities.
I've seen your sex tape Jesse.
I've seen Cole Corona's sex tape.
I know the truth.
He's uploaded it
on every streaming site known to man.
He's been blocked from
every web hosting site ever.
He's a monster.
Here's one that's kind of relevant
to our discussion today.
Donovan at Donovan on Guts
asks, what's the most
out there or difficult to get into
piece of media that you enjoy?
We're just kind of relevant to our discussion about media.
Homestuck, easy.
Homestuck is super fucking easy.
It's literally like this.
Homestuck is hard to get into
because I hate it and I have no desire to get into it.
Homestuck's fucking easy.
Everyone who says it's long or hard to do is gay.
That's like saying fucking and handling a hard media.
It's not just that it's long though.
It's that it's long and also queer as fuck.
Hold on. Very important difference here.
Hard to get into for you
back when you first got into it
or hard for people to get into in general.
That's a very important distinction.
That's pretty hard to get into.
For you.
Also, oh, you know what?
Fucking dwarf fortress.
Yeah, you know what? Actually,
I really enjoyed dwarf fortress.
I know I would love it. Yeah, I have not yet
succeeded in getting into it, so I'm going to go with that too.
I have one.
It's the hardest thing for me to get into
was the Legend of Zelda franchise
because I always hated Link from Plain Smash
and everyone liking Link more than Samus.
And that's why
I didn't want to get into it. That's really hard.
I think
that any anime
is just like chink shit going on.
And it's like...
You're right about that, dude.
Okay, here's a juicy question.
At
Varamir9 wants to know
are there any new memes that need
to die?
Any big ones that people
have been burning to see
executed? Well, the Undertaler needs to live.
Yeah, he has to live.
He must live. Yeah, he's got a bright future.
Oh my gosh, it's been
a freaking other day. Did I miss the
PCP recording today?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay,
I'm leaving now.
Bye.
He was banging his chest on the way out
in case he didn't hear.
What a good man.
He was so polite.
He just wanted to know.
When he knew his service wasn't easy to do that.
We're never mad at the
people there.
It's hard to be, because you're so oppressed
in our, you know...
Never mind, moving on.
I mean the need to die.
I didn't have the wherewithal to follow through
with that statement. I think I'm the only one
that this question is relevant to, but it's
quick and I thought I'd answer it.
At MichaelCera4 just asked,
for those of you who have taken Nihongo,
or that's Niponese, for those of you
who don't speak the devil's tongue,
who've taken Nihongo class,
what was your experience like as Japanese?
Talking about Japanese.
I listened to some
learn Japanese tapes on tape that I got
from the library one summer, and it was kind of fun.
I would say, I really enjoyed it.
I enjoyed learning the alphabet.
It was like a transforming experience
once I was able to read the letters
of the Japanese language, the hiragana and katakana,
and I was never very good at the speaking,
but I think it's really fun, so I encourage you to do it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, Nate,
why do you think this doesn't apply to me?
Fluent fucking Japanese.
We don't all have that level
of Christ consciousness.
Yeah, when you hit Christ
consciousness level 5 and above,
you automatically unlock speaking Japanese
as a bonus fee.
I've been trying to get into Japanese for a long time.
There's a great website,
JapanesePod101.com
who's just like so fucking,
he's so goddamn enthusiastic.
We're like, guys, now we're going to talk about grammar.
I can't wait.
And the Japanese people
who we co-host with are like, yep,
and it's cool, so that was my experience.
It's cool, I just need to...
It's simply a matter of prioritizing
it over other things I can do,
so once I'm out of other things to do,
I'll get back to that.
I'll prioritize you over other things I can do, you fuck.
What's, do you know what that means?
It means Naruto.
Yeah.
Oh wait, I was thinking of a different word.
Yeah, weird Narutoism.
Itadakimasu.
Oh wait, what are you talking about?
I know perfect Japanese.
Sakurakangikimasu.
Smile DK, that's the only Japanese word I know.
Smile DK for the camera.
It's me.
I'm back to smile for the camera.
It's me, the Donkey Kong trailer.
I'm a fucking
You guys, should we open up the suggestions
ideas for draw casts?
We should, yes,
actually we should, because I really want
to do more of them.
Tweet that right now and we'll think about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, do it, do it.
Don't tell me it'll live my life.
Draw casts, draw cast suggestions,
because we're all just completely at a loss
for what to draw.
Who will draw favours YouTube?
No.
We'll draw cubes, we'll draw
rectangles, we'll draw
cones.
I have no original character who is a box,
so that would work out.
Does the box have any distinguishing characteristics?
Her name is Mrs. Box,
and she's a dolled up gal.
That sounds awesome.
That sounds rad. Hey, Munchy, when's
fucking Investigator coming out? Shut the fuck up, Ben.
You fucking black sympathizer,
it'll come out when you're around. I really want it.
I want it right now.
You're dead. I love you.
Thank you, I love you too.
I care about you, and I just want the best
for you.
I'll renounce my devilish ways
and get back to work.
Thank you.
That's all I wanted.
That's all I wanted to hear. You got to retake that
Christ consciousness and put it to good work.
Okay, I think we're done. All these questions are bullshit.
Ask better questions next time, you idiots.
You can't be coming on for anything.
Okay, thanks for listening, everybody.
www.picture.com.
Yeah, make sure to go to
$1 for Munchy, $1 for $1, $1, $1, $1.
Click the link in the description.
The patreon.com
slash procrastinators meme is going to
slowly push out the patreon.com
slash ben saint meme.
No!
And make sure that you
ask us more questions
and give us topics at TPCrastinators
so go follow us on Twitter and shit.
And suggestions for drawcasts.
And drawcast suggestions suggest everything.
Whatever.
Easily.
That's the good one.
It definitely has the least artistic value
of any content.
Oh, yeah.
We need to discuss how much value podcasts have.
Wow.
Zero.
You really are the least
artistic value.
That's what you say.
No, but you know what?
That makes this episode self-referential
and we're going to be doing it high.
This is the best podcast.
Okay, yeah, all right.
It's confirmed.
All right, thanks for this everybody.
We're going to see you next time.
Go fuck yourself.
Bye bye.
$1 for Munchy, $1 for Munchy, $1 for Munchy, $1 for Munchy, $1 for Munchy, $1 for Munchy, $1 for Munchy.
I'm shit supposed to
be working
right now.
I'm supposed
to be working
right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick I'm
jerking.
Myself I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a
deadline.
Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed
to be making
money.
I'm supposed
to be creating
funny.
Think that the people
gladly will pay
for artistic
genius.
That's what they came for.
Instead I'm tweeting
hashtag repeating
That's why
there's no heat
and holes in the ceiling.
Yeah.
It's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock life.
Being
a genius.