Hello, everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
The legendary two-man episode is finally here.
No one will show up, and if we do, oh, I'll be so upset.
It's me, Bestie Boy, and we've got Tom Oliver.
Yo, what's going on?
We're the only people with the resolve to suffer through COVID and show up in our workspaces
for this podcast, the grueling commute of going down the stairs or into another room.
The testicular fortitude, indeed.
It was a huge ask, but we do it for you.
That's right, and you owe us, so patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators is the only place
to give us money.
There was a new bonus episode out about the contentious episode topic of Topics, and
we get into all the nitty-gritty of that, so go check that out.
If you're a fan of Insider Baseball, this is like the insider-iest baseball, and it
gets pretty heady.
It may be the most.
It does.
You know, I really enjoyed the arc of that episode.
We got so mad at each other, but then there was kind of a nice resolution.
I don't know.
It was good, endorsed by me.
Best shown in anime of the season, easily.
Oh, you know what?
That reminds me.
Just for fun, I was looking up something, or where was I listening to this?
For some reason, I was hearing about someone making fun of Nissan cars the other day, and
for whatever reason, I think I Googled Nissan, and I was on the Wikipedia page, and I saw
that it said, it was like the history of the page or something, and they were like, blah-blah-blah,
Nissan is actually a, it gets its name from the original Zaibatsu of the original, or
the old Japanese Empire, and I was like, wait, I've heard that word Zaibatsu before.
Where have I heard that before?
And then I just Googled it or whatever, and I realized, I realized the origin of the term
Zaibatsu, as used by the super best friends cast, and I realized that it's the fucking
coolest thing ever.
Because what I thought it was, I thought it was like, based on the way that it had been
used, I thought it meant like a wrestling confederation or something, like specifically
like a wrestling term for like their group.
I thought the Zaibatsu was a specific name for like their gang of miscreants.
Zaibatsu was a very specific thing.
It meant, oh, I wrote it down here, I have the kanji here.
It means a financial clique for the original Empire of Japan, okay, not original, but like
before World War II or whatever.
So it specifically refers to like a confederation of business conglomerates, or it is a business
conglomerate of individuals.
And I was like, well that, I see why the super best friends would have used that.
Now they are deceased, but I think perhaps that is an appropriate term to use for what
we do here at the PCP.
It is exactly the sort of thing that makes sense, and it's Japanese, so that's pretty
cool.
And they're dead.
They're dead.
Yeah, we can just take it.
We can just carry the flag.
It's ours now.
Both the super best friends and all the Japanese from back in the day, they were using it.
They're all dead.
So it's totally free and open.
We might as well just change the bonus episode name to that, like why not?
You know, that's true.
Anyway, I understand that's like a, well I don't know what the term is, that's like
a term that they popularized and made part of their, what's the word, zeitgeist, I don't
know, their cultural influence.
Yes, yes.
So it's definitely associated with them, but it is just a term that could be used for
anything.
The passage of time, dude, we just got to claim it now and not back down when challenged.
And eventually the, the winds of fate will change direction.
It will be our turn.
And indeed.
And as the actual soul of a samurai in my body, man that I am, and the business, the
aspiring businessman, I, this is like the perfect word to be used for such things.
So fuck it.
I think it's totally sick and I'm not going to let it die now that I actually know what
it means.
It's totally cool.
And I'll, I'll do it in honor of you guys as I use this word, rest in peace, super best
friends.
Anyway, so that's the, I learned the term, maybe everybody who knows them since they
were very popular and still are individually already knew what that meant, but I just had
a spiritual awakening and it was totally sick and I feel good about it.
Indeed.
It's, did you know what that meant Tom?
I had never even heard of the word before you mentioned it.
Oh, okay.
Right now.
Okay.
I see.
I am not as much as a weeb as you are.
Unfortunately.
I just, I haven't reached that apex of power yet, but perhaps someday.
It's sick of me to think, it's sick of me to think that there were bigger weebs than
I am.
You know.
And really I've, I've remedied that particular malady of myself.
Yes.
Every day you get a little bit more powerful and a little bit more fucking cringe, but
that cringe power is undefeatable by the normal man.
Indeed.
So Tom, have you seen the end of Steven Universe moving on to the other thing I wanted to talk
about?
Oh, I have not yet.
I need to.
We're planning on doing a whole Steven Universe cast, I would assume at some point to kind
of wrap everything up.
Yeah.
I mean, that's a good idea.
I mean, we've done it.
I guess I'll go into it too much.
We've been doing those since like the beginning.
It seems only fitting that we put a bow on the whole thing and wrap it all up properly.
I agree.
I'm still a big fan.
Excuse me.
I was looking into the details now that, you know, so there's Steven Universe, then
the movie.
Excuse me.
And then the recent Steven Universe.
Future.
Future has ended.
And specifically there were rumors going around that there was going to be like a comic continuation.
But Rebecca Sugar clearly stated on Twitter like, Hey guys, just so you know, I am not
working on anything Steven Universe now.
Like if there's comics, it's not me.
So everyone can be assured that the story has in fact ended and what we got is what
we got, which means any complaints that someone might want to put forward about unsatisfying
elements or incomplete storylines are totally valid and you can no longer deny any, any,
you can't say that they're going to fix it in like the comic.
You can't fix it in the comics anyway.
The comics are B canon.
They're not real.
It's just like fan and band-aids that they're being paid to make.
It's not true.
No, all that matters is the show.
Just like with MLP, everyone's like, Oh, the comics still, no, no, that's all not real.
The comics just tell the story beyond, well, I mean, the show ended on like with them becoming
adults and whatnot.
I assume the comics didn't go beyond that.
But even like while it was going on, like they would address plot elements from the
show in the comics.
We'd be like, this is what happened.
But then the show would go against that.
So whatever.
It's all fake.
I've heard very mixed things about the Steven Universe ending.
I've heard some people say it was really good and they cried and it was sad and great and
a good way to wrap everything up.
Other people like it's the gayest, worst thing ever, including famously Michelle sang a whole
song about her displeasure.
Her song, hey, go check out Michelle's song in the show notes.
Her balls are blue at the ending of this song of the show.
Poor Michelle.
Rest in peace.
She was the biggest Steven Universe fan out there because Michelle is also like mixed
race.
And that was like a fucking, it's funny because the ending of Steven Universe, there's a lot
of people out there, which is it's understandable that they would say like, so the Steven Universe
finale or sorry, Steven Universe future is about like now that the battle is over, it's
about dealing with Steven Universe is like literal PTSD that he acquired through like
these horrible things he's been through.
So to people who resonate with like trauma or depression or like anxiety or things like
that.
Like I could totally see why they would be way into that it like a personal thing.
I get it.
I like stories about like my personal issues as well.
Everybody does.
But the fact remains that there certainly are some plot elements that weren't thoroughly
explored enough.
And it's just funny like Michelle is one of the biggest people I know complaining about
the ending.
But like she always had a personal connection because like Steven exists in this like weird
like, you know, half breed, hybrid, I mean, you know, mixed race, truly a fate, like Coralette.
You wouldn't want that.
You wouldn't wish that on your worst enemy.
So like that was always a thing that like made her into Steven.
It was like, you know, something that hooked her into it from her personal experience since
she's like a bunch of she's like Japanese and Mexican Cuban and white and stuff.
That's rough.
I know it's a nightmare.
But but it's and now, but I feel that it's it's a very good faith thing to because even
Michelle was was redpilling on me on all the unfinished plot threads like most famously
the box from the weird like space inside lion's head.
What was in the box, Rebecca?
Why was it there?
I don't care if you just put it originally as like a visual design element.
Every other thing that was in that magic headspace was addressed at some point, except for that.
And if you'll indulge me, Tom, I came up because the other big complaint about the ending,
I would say this is the second biggest one.
The box is kind of a meme, but the other one is that we never actually see Steven ever
really come to terms with Rose.
And in fact, his last like the last interaction Steven has with Rose, aka Pink Diamond is just
further reasons why she was like a horrible and worse person.
The last thing we hear about Pink Diamond, aka Rose in the series is how she had a literal
abusive relationship with Pink Pearl and like physically assaulted her and would like
hurt her.
Like that's the final note.
The moral is that like Pink is just terrible.
Like is that what they're going for?
That's how it feels.
Yeah.
What's up, Jesse?
Are you here?
Hey, are we doing a Steven?
Is this a Steven?
We are at this particular moment.
We are talking about Steven.
We are talking about Steven right now.
Yes.
Let me just here.
I'll just finish my point and feel free to say whatever you like.
I was just going to say that the way to wrap that up, in my opinion, because like sure
everybody complains about Pink Diamond being evil and all that stuff.
Okay, but the reality is we learned everything good about Rose and Pink Diamond at the very
beginning and then we learned like the bad stuff she had done like chronologically before
she like became a much better person.
But to us as the audience, it feels as though we've just like heard all bad things about
Pink for so, so long.
The right way to resolve that is to bring that full circle and here's just my little
fanfic.
The way to resolve it is you get two birds with one stone.
The final thing that happens at the very end, like as Steven is like dealing with his trauma
or whatever, he like, he opens the chest in his little headspace and what does he find
there?
Yet another one of Pink Diamond's, of Rose Quartz's tapes.
And man, this is perfect.
This resolves fucking everything people wanted.
It's he plays the tape.
This was one final tape that was only there for Steven because this is a special space
only Steven could get to.
He plays it and here's what happens.
It starts with Rose and she's like, Hey Steven, this is another letter.
You know, I know once you're older, you'll see this.
Once you've like developed your powers and stuff, you'll, you'll be able to get in here.
What she then does is she transforms back into Pink Diamond for Steven to see and be like,
I want you to know this is who you are, to be comfortable with like the stuff that we've
been.
And then she explains all the horrible things she's done or at least in general terms and
just lays it out for the audience.
Like Steven, I'm sure by now you've learned all the horrible things I've done.
I want you to know that I understand that like those things were bad.
I grew like you, you, the audience, you know, this is the surrogate going on here.
You've now seen all the worst things about me, but I also understand how bad a person
I was and I work to fix that, which she did.
She was fucking hero and like an actual good person before she died mostly and she tried
to make amends for all the bad stuff she had done.
So like that should have been the final note that resolved like the chest, like Steven and
Rose and the diamond, the Pink Diamond whole thing, and would have actually dealt on screen,
not literally off screen with Steve or not at all, not at all.
It's strange that they don't have anything like that because there was nothing.
The whole mention the last episode, the whole arc of Pink Diamonds like reveal through this
entire show has been like, she's like this fucking perfect person.
And then like every note of information we've gotten from her after is just like, actually
she was a piece of shit.
Without doing what you said, bring it back full circle, like it just feels like actually
Pink Diamond was shit.
She was bad and that's what you should take away from this entire show.
Not to be too, not to talk down to the audience, but I think the intended audience of Steven
Universe is fairly young.
I think that audience needs a little, I mean, I see a lot of people being like, oh my god,
Pink Diamond is a monster.
Sure, when she was young and foolish, she did a lot of bad things, but let's resolve
on like, in my opinion, like the most healing attitude that we all need as a society, that
people can change and grow.
And the fucked up thing is, we already know for a fact that she did grow and change and
did become a good person, but everyone's just forgotten that because narratively, that's
further back in our minds.
And we're just not thinking about that.
She was a hero.
And a good person.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, is there really anything that needs to be resolved with her?
I mean, like, you don't have to like redeem her and have her like go like, oh, hey, you
know, actually, I'm not a piece of shit at this, this whole, this idea that people have
that like Pink Diamond is like all bad and she's a piece of shit and she's a monster
is like totally missing the entire point.
Like she can be.
I mean, I agree.
You don't necessarily have to like do some ask what the end we're like, oh no, she actually
did have some redeeming qualities.
Well, we already know she had redeeming qualities.
She started out in the show.
We always saw were her redeeming qualities.
Just because we're later introduced to some more, you know, three dimensional shitty aspects
of her doesn't mean, you know, you know, that she's just sucks completely.
Even though she I totally agree.
But just consider the fact that I see a vast sentiment of discussion online specifically
about how look, like these are the kind of people we hear.
Like there's a lot of people, there's a certain overlap of fandom of Steven Universe of people
who enjoy Steven Universe and people who when they learn one bad thing about someone's
history, like now think that person is historically bad for all time.
I think there happens to be an overlap between those two camps, but that's all of humanity
everywhere.
And I don't know if you've discovered a cure for it yet besides mass destruction and death
for every human on earth.
I just recommend a little reminder because I felt like we left.
I'm just we left it on a very negative tone for everything that like that pink and rose
had done.
Maybe that's just me thinking that like there was a negative tone.
I mean, as some of them, I haven't watched the ending, so I'm talking out of my ass.
But you the way you phrase this entire discussion in the first place, and Jesse, you might not
even been in a call when we were talking about it, was the reason you even brought it up
is because it wasn't the audience, but like Steven himself didn't ever seem in the story
to come to any resolution, even though that was like the driving force of all of future
was dealing with his package.
His arc was really started like Vorshminger like a saint, like a perfect being.
And then he learned she was flawed and bad in many ways, sure.
But there was never a visible third point where Steven comes to terms with that.
We simply end the series and I guess he's at peace now.
That's fairly unsatisfying.
Well, he has that one line.
There's one throwaway, you know, blink and you'll miss it with your ears line where
he says, Oh, blah, blah, blah.
And I'm talking to my therapist online once a week.
So that's kind of like implying that he's still dealing with it, but in kind of a fufu
way.
I'm so sick, sick of hearing about therapists and therapy and mental health.
This whole thing has gotten so out of control in our culture now where everyone's like,
Oh, therapy is always good and it's good for everyone.
And if you have problems, then you definitely have a mental health issue.
And you definitely, you know, it's good to, you know, whatever happened to just like stuffing
shit down, like a man, whatever, you know, maybe the older generations had it right.
I'm sick and tired.
You're just constantly bombarded with all this mental health care shit, you know, from
all directions.
And it's like, enough is enough.
Just leave me alone.
That's my mental health.
Have you ever seen the Sopranos?
Have you ever seen the Sopranos, Jesse?
No.
The Sopranos are exactly like season one Tony Soprano, where he's, he has like, people
don't know this, but the actual like underlying plot of, of the Sopranos is not just cool mob
boss stuff, which obviously is, is what happens day to day.
But the actual plot is about Tony Soprano getting therapy because he has these panic
attacks that are very unbecoming of a mob boss.
So he has to like, so he deals with his mental health, like throughout the entire series
as like the main underlying like Tony plot of what's going on.
But he's always like, oh shit, what did he say?
Whatever happened to, to the strong silent type, whatever happened to that kind of thing?
Whatever happened is just keeping it all bottled in.
And he's right.
Yeah.
That's the right way to go.
You don't want to, you know, before everything, you know, there was always this perception
that before you were a fucking surf to a Lord and no one cared and you would work the field
and die.
And that was great.
Like at first.
Ideal.
And first it was like this perception that if you, you know, see a therapist, there must
be something really wrong with you and there was kind of a stigma against it for a lot
of years.
I get that.
And but then people started, you know, trying to make this push for like, there doesn't have
to be a stigma.
It should be okay to talk about your problems and, and seek help for whatever's bothering
you.
And like, I agree with that.
Yes, that's fine.
Yeah.
But then it's like, it got so pushed to where people, the whole world now is overbearing
with it.
Everybody has, everybody has a mental health.
You've all got the mental health.
It's like, you know, you've all got to see a therapist for everything all the time.
If you're not seeing a therapist, then you're, then you're stuffing shit down and you're
repressed and you're doing something wrong.
You know, my dad is a psychologist and he always had a predisposition.
Like there have been several times in my life where I don't know, like just everything
isn't going like exactly the way I want it.
Like for example, when I was just like looking for better jobs and trying to, excuse me,
find like an intro chip to finish my degree and stuff, my dad would just recommend, he's
like, Hey Nate, why not go talk to someone, go like talk to a person.
And the pitch was never, the pitch for me was not like, Nate, you obviously have like
depression or some, you know, mental deficiency.
I need you to, like you should go see someone to deal with that.
His idea was like, I assume because this is kind of how he deals with his patients because
it deals with a lot of like old folks who like, they don't necessarily have a lot of people
in their lives to talk to every day because they're in nursing homes and stuff.
He'll be like, Nate, just go to like a psychologist or whatever and just like have a discussion
basically simply about whatever you're trying to improve about your life and like trying
to get straight.
And really it just served as like, it's like, oh yeah, I mean, I guess I am maybe playing
too many video games and should like spend another hour a day looking for a job, like
just very pragmatic down to earth stuff.
If that's the intense, I can at least understand that.
Is the part of it that's supposed to help just getting it out and just like the illusion
that someone is understanding or listening.
It kind of feels that way.
I think that's what it is.
Yeah, because like it's really interesting to me that like so many people recommend not
only therapy, but like medication all the time and like everybody's on fucking antidepressant
meds.
Yeah, that's the one that really weirds me out because it's just like a medication worship.
But like, you know, like people don't have seemed to have forgotten with like this acceptance
of mental health that like not feeling good sometimes is normal.
Like life is not always going to be perfect.
And it's just like, if you can identify why you don't feel good, you're not depressed.
Like you're just having a shit time.
Like you don't need medication.
Like if you if you're just like, man, I feel like garbage because like I just sit around
and do nothing all day.
You don't need antidepressants.
You need to stop sitting around and doing nothing all day.
You need to do something.
You need antidepressants if you're just like, my life is great.
I have a good job.
I have good friends.
I have a good family, but I'm still depressed.
Like that's when you need a therapist and medication.
If you can clearly identify why you feel like shit, the answer is right in front of you.
Just stop being a little bitch and fix that shit.
I just like the only person in the entire world who's really qualified to figure out
what's wrong with you is you.
And I guess I'm just skeptical of the idea that anyone, no matter how much schooling
they've had in psychology or whatever, can listen to like bits and pieces of your story
in a room for like an hour a session and suddenly even come anywhere close to having
the answers or any real insight into you.
Like you can't possibly explain every single thing that is making you the way you are.
And so I don't know.
And plus you have to pay for it.
If therapy was really so important, wouldn't it be free?
Wouldn't it be, you know?
I mean, if it was so helpful, if food was so helpful, wouldn't it be free?
Fuck food.
Nobody needs it overrated.
I don't know.
Maybe that was stupid.
I don't know what the fucking point was.
Sure, there was a point in there somewhere.
Make a complex point about how when when there are lots of goods in the free market,
inevitably many sources will spring up and they'll inevitably drive the price down,
hopefully to literally zero eventually.
Yes.
Free therapy for everybody.
I'm sure that'll solve the problem.
Anyway, not too much therapy.
If having to be completely free.
Right.
Wait, you're getting me confused.
I forgot what the hell my idea was to begin.
Well, you were saying that you don't think that like someone could for an hour and a half
sit down and talk and like understand really the depths of your life.
Well, I mean, like the thing is, like you have to pay exorbitant amount of money
for a therapy session with a therapist.
You have to choose your therapist.
What if you choose a bad one by mistake?
Like what if you happen to get a therapist who sucks and you would never know
and the damage would be irreparable?
They would get inside your head with all this crap.
You know, there's people who suck at their job, no matter what job it is.
There's got to be therapists who suck at therapy.
I went to therapy for a while.
It was terrible.
You can pay money for a therapist and you just paid money to be even more screwed up.
That's the other thing is like the anxiety of getting the right car
times a thousand, which is already bad enough.
You know, if I get the wrong car, then I'm fucked for years, you know,
and it feels like if you get the wrong therapist, you're fucked for the rest of your life.
Even my problem with therapists and the reason I tend not to go to see them
is simply because the profit structure like motivates them to keep me in there,
you know, like they benefit from my problem subsisting as opposed to solving them.
Like the benefit financially is to keep me coming back week after week.
Hey, the Hippocratic Oath is not do no harm.
Not make sure you're curing up, you know what I'm saying?
You can just keep stringing me along.
If they stay neutral, I could just keep coming back.
I'm like, I don't want to become dependent upon this.
I want the problem solved.
And, you know, I like to think that they're not thinking in such a callous term.
We'll review video games until you stop.
Oh, shit.
And he was where's my Rayman to review then?
Damn it. Oh, no, I'll go now.
See you guys.
Thank God.
Well, anyways, my point with all of that was Steven Universe sure is a fun show.
Boy, did you guys see that last episode?
How cool was that?
Boy, I sure do love cartoons and stuff.
I, you know, because a lot of people were like really emotionally
devastated or in a good way, like they were feeling like climatically fulfilled.
Whereas I know some people like Michelle were more thinking about
like the lore and how there were things they were unsatisfied.
I suppose I'm kind of in the, I don't know, the worst world
where I was just kind of like, I mean, I really passionately
loved Steven Universe for a long time.
But then when it ended here, I was like, OK, that's cool.
That was nice.
For example, like the whole last episode, there's this whole like
bit they're doing where all the gems that are the closest,
like the crystal gems, the real ones, they like won't show emotion or cry.
And I was just like, look, I know how this joke ends.
I know from the start of the episode that they will cry.
They're obviously faking.
And then surprise, it happened.
Wow, how emotional.
I do. I do agree that, like, after they all hugged Monster
Seven and he got back to normal and then the episode ended there,
then the next episode, like it's a time skip and he's just fine
and he's moving out.
That was a month later.
There was definitely like a lot glossed over that I would have liked to.
But maybe you didn't need to see it.
I don't know. But like the whole, I think the whole idea
of Steven Universe Future, the whole thing this last season
has been like really brilliant and good and kind of groundbreaking.
I mean, just the idea of like, you know, Steven Universe is a kid's show.
It's like kind of like a playoff of like a like a shonen anime thing almost
or like like a like a Sailor Moon, some shit.
You know, this is like a little boy saving the world.
The idea to do that and then not gloss over the fact
as any other show would and has throughout history that this would mess
a person up, especially a child to say after, you know, it's the big battle
is all said and done. OK, let's not just end it here.
Let's do a whole other season dealing with the mental and emotional repercussions
and trauma that this has all had on poor young Steven and to just like really
delve into, you know, themes of like PTSD and trauma and stuff is like really
hasn't been done in this kind of show before.
And, you know, regardless of whether the last episode dropped the ball
or hit the mark perfectly or not, I think the idea of doing that
in the first place with the season was like really good and cool.
You know, my only I do enjoy a lot of that stuff as well.
I do have one kind of a criticism, maybe you disagree.
But like I felt like, I don't know, maybe this is not fair.
And this wasn't isn't like how it would work in real life.
But I feel like they were kind of trying to have their cake and eat it to
because through the entirety of Steven Universe, like Steven was the
like the happy go lucky rock that whenever like things went wrong,
he would be the upbeat one.
And I would I could understand like that making him change
and being more like depressed and, you know, have PTSD and stuff.
And I get like addressing that in a show.
But it seems to me like, I don't know, like they used Steven
for that purpose of being that person.
And then like just years later, when everything's fine,
I mean, I guess that's how it works.
Like when a soldier comes back for more, that's when they start to get all fucked up.
But it was so long later.
And I feel like they like wouldn't those sort of things started to have
said in when he was like in the middle of them?
Because he seemed totally he seemed 100 percent fine
through the entirety of the original trauma is.
You can you can come out of a bad situation
and be totally fine for a while because you're relieved to be out of it.
And it's not until a little while later that, you know, all the stuff from it
starts setting back in.
I really don't think Steven was fine throughout like a lot of
the last few seasons in the movie.
Like there were very clearly moments where he was having trouble continuing
and you know, dealing with all this rose shit.
Well, anybody would have individual moments of trauma,
like when he got his fucking gem ripped out or when Spinell was going to kill him
or when he was all that stuff.
But he wasn't he wasn't always like the rock.
Like other people had to pick him up, you know, multiple times.
I love the scene where he's at the doctor's office, like
and she asks if anything bad happened in his childhood.
And he starts going over all these things that to the viewer at the time,
watching a cartoon would seem mundane because it's in a cartoon,
but really like driving home the fact that, no, every single one of these things
that happened in every episode of the whole series,
even just one of them would permanently destroy a child's psyche.
All right. But you know what? Fuck you, Rebecca,
because a lot of those things were played for laughs at the time.
And now I'm supposed to like, oh, shit, I'm sorry that like you put the goofy music
as these horrible horrible things were happening to him.
So am I supposed to feel bad for Steven or are you the one who's the callous one?
Rebecca, I think that's just the nature.
Like if Steven Universe wasn't, you know, what it was at the beginning,
it wouldn't have gained traction and you know what, I'm like a big thing
that people would care about.
So they had to dangle Steven's trauma for views is what you're telling me.
They had to amuse.
I'm not saying that like she had this idea at the beginning.
I don't know. I haven't.
OK, you know what? You know what?
I can my my entire point isn't valid
because Steven Universe Future is obviously designed to be a separate thing
from Steven Universe.
So you know what? That really.
How about that episode with that fucking?
How about that sexy volleyball check?
That was a great episode right there. Boy, oh, boy.
That the the sort of moral that they came or that the moral.
But the conclusion that her and Pearl came to at the end there where they both
like after fusing, they got all this new insight into Rose that neither of them
had had before. And then that great line of like, I always knew she was trying
to change, but I never knew why because now she understands like that's I think
that is what you were talking about before.
That's something that like contextualizes pink, where it's not like
it's not like, oh, we thought she was good, but she's really a piece of shit.
No, it's that that is making the case that she was good because she had been
a piece of shit, and that was the whole motivation she wanted to change.
I think that put it cast it in a new light pretty well.
You know, that's true.
That's I guess perhaps just as a fan, maybe it's more of this as a fan.
Like I feel a certain uncomfortableness, which I think was intended.
I mean, it was obviously part of it.
Like it makes me a little uncomfortable to see like the Steven who,
at least to me, the viewer has been like the rock of like positivity and
upbeatness. I watched Steven Universe because it was comfy and I really
enjoyed the atmosphere. And then to see trauma be all fucked up.
I mean, again, I think this was the point.
It's like, oh, this is uncomfortable and I don't like seeing Steven unhappy
and traumatized, but you know, makes sense.
That's how it would be.
Maybe just as a fan, it's that like I wanted to see a Steven Rose
resolution of some kind.
And maybe there was a line or two here there.
Other characters develop a deeper understanding.
I feel like Steven didn't get that.
So just as a like, as like, you know, you're saying it's kind of like a
Sailor Moon or a Shonen series kind of styled show.
You expect the big emotional anime speech and that did not come, at least
like the climactic quote unquote meeting of those two, you know,
Titans of characters of like Steven, Pearl or whatever and Rose.
But yeah, yeah, I mean, it did touch on these.
My biggest trauma.
I think that's why a lot of people did like it.
That that really, you know, that it really hurt me deep inside is that, you know,
this this whole show, we've been investing in it for so long.
We never got to see Greg fuck Pearl.
Yeah, this is a this is a crime against humanity
and a crime against gem kind of the highest order.
We never got to see Greg fuck Pearl.
We should have seen that.
We should have also seen Steven fuck Lapis and Peridot.
Although Bismuth is definitely going to split Pearl wide open with her.
No, that's going to happen.
I don't like that at all.
I don't want to think about it.
I'm not going to, you know, that one episode, though,
was the only time I've ever kind of liked Bismuth,
because she was actually kind of endearing and looked a little bit unusual.
I'm going to see a therapist about there being like too many lesbians and cartoons these days.
Oh, you know what I was saying?
I was saying to Michelle the other day, Steven Universe, would it really
the original Steven Universe, which I could get on board with, was really the story
of all these dumb ass bimbos and hoes and sluts.
They needed a strong patriarchal man to set them straight.
And that's what Steven Universe was.
But now Steven Universe's future is fucking all these women coming in
and saying the man needs to figure out his emotions.
It's not OK that he lashes out and literally kills people.
You made me a warrior.
I had to be strong to defend you.
You made me into this creature.
Now you want me to change?
Sounds like it's forcing some kind of stereotypes on both sides of the equation.
Good job, Rebecca.
I loved when he I loved when he was
I loved when he was beating the shit out of a white diamond.
I wanted to see more of that.
I wanted that to get darker and more violent.
I wanted in the really kicker ass around the room.
It got darker than I ever expected it to when you like tried to murder white diamond.
Oh, man.
And the episode where he was yelling at Greg when they had a big fight
because he realized that Greg's been full of shit his whole life
and that he had a really comfortable upbringing.
That was cool. When he said like.
I figured you would sympathize with Greg, though,
because Greg had like this stuffy, like uppity family
who tried to control him and tell him what to do all the time.
I mean, you can always see the the grass is always greener, right?
So I totally get Stevens like he's now seeing what he could have had
through that family connection.
But I don't know. Right.
I don't know. It was a complicated scene, of course, as many things are here.
It's just I liked it.
I like the whole I like the whole thing, except for the parts that were lame and shitty.
But I don't care about those parts because they're boring to talk about.
Man, what about that?
Yeah, I loved seeing White Diamond
when Steven was a monster, that whole little like dramatic speech
she gave about how bad she feels about how, you know, like Spinell was like,
this is all my fault. The White Diamond is like, no, you were just mad at Pink.
And if she hurt you, it's because I hurt her.
Just like I hurt Steven and the Gems and everybody in the entire universe.
I love that.
Just imagine I just it's really funny to me.
Like, imagine waking up and realizing that you've fucked up so bad
and so consistently for so long that you've hurt everybody in the entire universe.
White Diamond absolutely became my favorite character.
I love her. She's the best.
She's cool. That was that was.
I mean, and what has White Diamond come to terms with like the reason
she did all those things was like probably because of the authority
placed on her and how she felt she had to be perfect.
So she developed these weird like authoritarian needs.
And I'm sure at the time, you know, she had no perspective to know any better.
Or like, yeah, right, right.
But I like that they that they were able to devote at least like one little line
in there to like giving her some remorse or like characterization
beyond my critique of that line, though, was the delivery.
Was it like, oh, Steven, I'm so like they didn't
her like way over the top voice.
That should have been a little more like down to earth.
I don't know. It was like kind of it was like a rarity reading like a.
Yeah, that's true.
I don't see it as like any less sincere because she was being dramatic.
Speaking of gems.
Well, Rarity had three gems on her flank.
Three diamonds. There you go.
The Diamond Authority, it was Rarity all along.
Rarity is white.
What a spike, fucking eight pearl.
What if you just fucking ate all of them?
Spikes the most powerful.
Dude, spikes their natural predator.
Why didn't they introduce dragons as the natural predators of gems?
So this is all a defensive war.
And if only if only creepy Chad spike
my little pony finale had been there, he would have saved the day much sooner.
We need my little pony future to cross over.
And then we can get all these plots.
Oh, oh, oh, shit.
Is that started yet?
What is that show?
I saw the trailer for it.
Like a my little pony generation, something or other.
I don't know what it is, but I saw the trailer.
Pony life. Yeah.
I don't think it started yet.
What's the premise of it?
It looks like there's no animation in the animals, but my little pony.
Like my little pony, but animated slightly differently in cutes here.
But there's no like information as to what it is.
Yeah, it was very strange.
I want to see everyone's videos.
I want to see animated James make his big video about how this sucks.
It's not living up to the potential of the original, even though it's better
in every way as I'm waiting for the schism.
I'm when Gen five drops, I'm so excited to have the the pony
equivalence of the Picard Kirk arguments happening on Twitter.
And I can watch from the sidelines and be like, I know I understand this.
Have they if they like revealed Gen five stuff, is it going to be like
the same continuity or it's a reboot, but they haven't announced anything about it yet.
A reboot. It's just that's.
Wait, OK, it's just it's just going to be a new generation.
Just like all the other ones are had nothing to do with each other.
So yeah, OK, OK.
So so Twilight doesn't exist anymore.
Like that kind of that's all gone.
It's dead.
So gone. That's a waste.
Why not just have why not just fucking have Twilight be the story's over, man?
They have to be over.
But you can do the next generation.
You can do. Yeah.
But you can do that with like you can do like a next generation with like new
characters and still have, you know, Twilight.
Yeah, OK. Now, from what I heard,
I think they were saying they're going to they're going to shift
the the the Twilight to like an Earthpony again or something.
I don't know if that's true or not, but OK.
I mean, they fucking changed.
They changed lots.
Well, whatever, like Rainbow Dash's Firefly was.
So I can't wait for all the Internet drama and all the YouTube videos.
It's going to be a great time.
I'm definitely curious to see what it looked like just on its face.
You see, because like Lauren Faust was like
she she had a vision for a show and she made, you know, a whole thing.
But the other generations were mostly just, you know, entirely toy focused
characters from one generation would appear in the other.
So like Gen Five might have like some characters
just have different personalities and look exactly the same
with the same color design and everything.
Like Rainbow Dash, you're, you know, you're you, but you're completely different.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, Jesse, Jesse, I wanted to right now.
I won't tell anybody because it's not out yet.
If whatever, you don't want to know anything.
Have you heard anything, Jesse, about the gigantic leaks
of what's going on with the FF7 remake?
Because I have some insider information.
OK, I like I don't want.
I won't tell you if you don't want to know.
I do not want to be spoiled for anything.
OK, OK, understood.
I didn't want to know it.
No, I didn't want to know the world.
Like I saw something and like I don't know
if I should believe it or not.
Like I don't know if it was.
Yeah, I know, right?
I don't know if it was a for real spoiler or just like a joke.
And I'm afraid to ask if the person was joking or not.
But like, yeah, like.
Like it, it, it like broke me.
Like it hurt my heart because like.
If it's true, then this is something that could have surprised me
that is now destroyed for me.
Like it could have been something like because I'm like I'm not trying to hate the remake.
Like I don't I understand.
Like I like I want to if there's anything in it
that can catch me by surprise and make me go, wow, that's really interesting
and cool that they did that.
Then I want to be able to experience that.
And the fact that I like even maybe saw a spoiler
is like taking that away from me.
It's ripping away something that I deserve.
God damn it. I understand.
Yeah, yeah.
So OK, well, I add a quick time event where if you mash X, you can save
Eris, that's the thing because like I'm like, I'm not even because honestly,
like if they did something like really drastic to really surprise me,
even if it like, you know, shat all over the old game
and was completely retarded and new and stupid.
At this point, I would be like, hey, cool.
I fucking like as far as I'm concerned, if they're going to change anything,
they might as well change everything.
They might as well go completely off the rails and totally be blowing my mind
at every turn so that, you know, rather than having to compare
to something that I know is objectively better, the old game,
I can I can go on this ride and be like, oh, everything's different
and stupid and crazy now, and it's just a wacky.
All right. You know, yeah, there's a logic to that.
Yeah. But I don't know.
Like now I hope like I hope what I saw isn't true because I if it is,
you know, I just I don't want to feel like I got spoiled for something
because like I remember when I played Final Fantasy 7 the first time,
like 20 million thousand years ago, I was a little kid when it first came out.
Back then, as a kid, I had a strategy guide and the strategy guide
had like story spoilers in it for them.
So like even as a kid, I got spoiled for the game.
This game that is now, you know, that became my favorite game of all time.
And I've waited all these years to now know that I had a chance
to get surprised finally and got spoiled again.
It's like it's like a sick joke.
It's like it's even harder now to avoid.
I got just mute Final Fantasy 7 and FF7 on Twitter.
So none of those tweets show up.
Yeah, that's true.
Let me check. I'm just checking the release date real quick.
It is coming out. Oh, my God.
April 10th, five days.
I thought they pushed it back.
In fact, I think what you're hearing this is well.
OK, I just googled it.
Maybe they didn't.
Is the reason that like the spoilers are out because like they gave
some people the game early because I kind of it came out early in some regions.
I saw a tweet of somebody in I think Europe somewhere that has their copy.
It is the virus's fault that this happened, that these leaks are out there.
It's not the virus's fault.
If this happened, if this virus spoiled me for a video game
that I'm looking forward to, even slightly, that's a bigger tragedy
than anything else that's done to our nation.
That's the worst part of society.
That's the true tragedy.
I, you know, I'm a bit more in the camp of new, bad, old, good
just across the board.
But beyond that, I won't say anything.
But I've just I have seen what I've seen what appears to be like like footage.
I watched a guy play a little bit on Twitch or something who seemed to have it.
It was funny that that feed I was watching just gets cut off
and is then like this channel no longer exists.
I'm like, oh, there goes Square Enix bringing down the hammer
on some of these troublemakers.
My my my opinion on it is old, good, new, like new, bad, but spoilers works.
Spoilers. I say spoilers even worse than new, bad.
You know, because the thing is I've heard some spoilers that are troubling, I'll say.
But like I there there is a possibility this could be something special.
And I mean, as we've said before, you and I, it's like, you can't not be.
I was just watching a guy fight something and I was like this.
I can't ignore the fact that like seven year old me would be exactly
creaming his fucking pants, looking at what I'm seeing before me right now.
The logical, rational, like thinking part of your brain tells you
they're going to ruin every part of this.
They're going to shit all over it.
It's going to be bad.
Zoomers and zoomers are going to play it and they're going to think that they're going to think this is the real one.
God, but there is.
But there is still like underneath it all.
There's like this small burning ember of nostalgia that you just can't get rid of.
And you look at it and you go, oh, God, it looks kind of cool.
If I get so excited for like a really cool piece of like Tifa fan art,
how can you not get excited for this entire game that is essentially a fan art?
If a fan art, yeah, yeah.
Speaking of new bad, I'll tell you, I've been playing the Resident Evil 3 remake.
I've heard bad things.
New bad, I don't know.
New very bad.
I thought it was being viewed pretty well.
Is that just like the mainstream journal opinion and like real people think it sucks?
So I did that.
I did a video when Resident Evil 2
remake came out called Resident Evil 2 is great.
But I hated sort of tongue in cheek.
I had some criticisms and some complaints.
But I think square or not square Capcom.
Capcom must have seen my video and said, we'll show this guy how good he has it now.
He wants to complain about a Resident Evil game.
We'll give him something to cry about.
And they sure did.
First of all, I think I was out.
Um, I think I'm at the end of the game.
It's been like a half an hour of gameplay.
First of all, yeah, yeah.
Just like there's so much from the original game that is just gone.
Like it feels like half the game you go.
You're in the city streets for like the first hour or two.
And then you're in a hospital and then you're in an underground lab,
just like the underground lab in Resident Evil 2 that they already did.
And it's like, what happened to like the clock tower section in the park section?
What happened to all the branching paths?
No branching paths.
They they made the zombies like, huh, they made the zombies weaker
to like they're not bullet sponges anymore.
Yeah, they were too strong.
The last one was the complaint.
Right. But like it would have been like the resiliency of the zombies wasn't the issue.
For me, the issue was that the headshots felt like they didn't work half the time, you know?
Yeah.
So like if they had just kept them that level of resilient and let me put them
down with one headshot, I'd have been like they fixed it.
Instead, like the headshots still don't work and they're weaker.
So now that it's just like the zombies are made out of paper,
all the gore effects are gone, like the arms don't fall off when you shoot them.
The legs don't fall off the fuck.
They just kind of just quality design.
All all the zombies have a stock falling down and dying animation.
And it's the same for every zombie you shoot in the whole game.
No, no one falls apart. Nothing.
There's this weird like mashing X minigame.
You have to press every time a zombie grabs you, which it feels like it does nothing.
It doesn't like activate a counter.
You don't have any like counter weapons like the knife that you had in the first
two remakes. It's just there's there's no way to get out of a zombie grab.
You're just pressing X seemingly for no reason.
And also, you know, it still has the problem of every time a zombie grabs you,
the camera swings around to be cinematic.
And then it comes back and you're disoriented and you run into another enemy,
which is even worse when the nemesis is chasing you through the whole level.
And the nemesis, they just bungled all their bangles with the nemesis.
Let me tell you, brother, this guy used to be the the head
honcho, big cheese chairman of the fucking board of resident evil.
You know, before they before they retconned, you know, Albert
Wesker and being like the series antagonist when he was still technically dead,
you know, nemesis was like the big bad of the trilogy.
He was a culmination of like every, you know, the ultimate evolution of these
monsters you've been fighting. He was intelligent. He hated you.
He was a bully. He ran at you.
And he just punched you. He was mean.
He had guns. He had fingers to use guns.
And he chased you. And like the chase were dynamic and like real.
And part of the gameplay, he'd you'd walk into an alley and you'd have to run
and he'd chase you into other rooms.
All the nemesis encounters here are like QTE,
like like story driven, you know, like on rails, scripted scenes.
Instead of just the dynamic him chasing you like Mr. X was, they, you know,
I think there's like one section of the whole game.
There's like one five minute section where he's actually stalking around the city.
But it only lasts for that one section.
It's like five minutes.
And the rest of the times you see him,
it's all scripted sequences of him coming out and just you run from him
in this like cinematic story segment that seems like it feels like you can't
actually die game bad movie. Good. I love movies.
I love Avengers. Please give me more.
Jesse, do you know if this game was made by a different like like not studio,
but like different team over at Capcom, because it seems bizarre
that this game came out so quickly after Resident Evil 2 and so much is different.
I was thinking the same thing.
It is bizarrely because it seems like it would be more work to build
everything again, seemingly from the ground up than just port over all the features
like the limb damage and stuff from two.
Yeah, I think it was I think it was definitely rushed because and I think someone,
the YouTuber Sphere Hunter brought this up in her review where
it's possible that because there are more zombies on the screen in this game,
like there are bigger hordes, they had to like take away some of the features
of the zombies to make them fit more. Well, great.
Maybe. Yeah, not worth it at all, especially when, you know,
you have these, yes, much bigger hordes of zombies,
but they're all go down like paper mache.
So what's what's the difference?
Fucking, I don't know, old, good, new, bad, old, good, new, bad.
Hey, listen to this, though.
I happen to hear one piece of, I don't know, like developer commentary,
the art director here in the in the gross, disgusting audio links chat.
I just posted two images of Jill.
All right, I this was straight from the fucking horse's mouth.
Now, all right, before you call me a fucking goober gate or everybody,
it's it's always been theorized that like a lot of these people
are making their women like less sexy on purpose
so as to not like upset interest groups of various types.
OK, the art director has straight up come out and said the director
for the remake that they had to change her design to be too practical.
And they thought it was a mistake in the original game to make her so sexy.
It was a mistake.
And he's like, oh, my God, like the developers at this point,
even though she was wearing like casual clothing, all they did.
And also look at her clothes, look at her clothes.
Is that too sexy?
I'm sorry, you can see a tiny bit of the top of her breasts.
Yeah, all they did is they just changed a tube top to a tank top.
And but and also but but she had a sweater around her waist, at least,
so that she actually had more clothes in the original technically speaking.
You know, she was at least in the original.
She went out with the intention of wearing a sweater.
And this one is even more sexy because she didn't even think about
wearing a sweater in the first place.
Just put on just that means just fucking they're just saying these.
I mean, you that should not be a consideration when you're fucking
designing and I don't know what it's like.
I felt like her hair looks like way worse in this version.
And like, I think it's way worse than I think it's technically
the same hairstyle as the original, but just the uncanny valley
of the of the new graphics make it look like a Karen cut.
All of a sudden, it's almost like art style is relevant.
I'm just looking at this first screenshot.
I think just the fact that they're no, no.
Realism, good fucking non-photorealism.
I mean, Tom, I fuck you.
Oh, you're right.
I love photorealism.
You piece of shit.
I know you do.
Across the board.
Yeah.
Well, just look at this screenshot.
Like the hairstyles are similar, but the fact that there's not those
like stray cartoony kind of strands of hair covering the forehead on two sides
totally changes the silhouette and it really emphasizes a big forehead
on the redesign model.
She old good new bad pretty much sums it.
I and you know what, they're doing it again.
They're doing this thing.
The number one thing I hate.
And I understand why they're doing the thing of designing their
characters after real life models.
I am so opposed to that practice.
I think it's such a mistake to do that.
It's like whatever.
That was like my biggest complaint about the visuals.
Yeah, I cry five and don't make cry four.
Dante was like this big buff like comic book superhero guy.
It was cool.
And then in five, he's just like normal proportion and it looks like he like
lost like 50 pounds of muscle from the last final point on the gubergator side.
Yes.
Okay.
People are going to, they did give her a DLC outfit for its DLC pay extra for
the original version, but it's not even the same.
She doesn't have a skirt.
She has a scort.
You can't see your pussy and that's a fucking rip off.
So fuck you.
I don't know whether I'm being like, like insane or anything.
I don't see anything particularly wrong with the new one on the, on the right.
Well, wrong is a relative term.
Like, yeah, there's nothing wrong with it.
The dine is just fine.
I mean, it does come from a bit of old, good new, okay.
It's, it's, it's about the spirit of what is a remake.
And when, whenever I see a remake, perhaps I'm more, you know, more attached to the
past than others.
Why would they make a real legitimate rational reason?
Why, why like to change the design?
Like it's not a big deal that they changed it, but it's kind of a big deal that
they don't have a good reason for it.
It's the reason and the art director straight up, and this is a rare instance,
he came out and said it directly.
She was too sexy.
That's bad.
We had to fix that mistake.
Sure.
It's, it's not like you can disagree with his opinion with that.
I just personally like would like, I don't know.
I, I feel like if he thought that it's too sexy, we need to change it.
And he does that.
And the game is the, you know, the game is the thing that matters more.
Like this is an image you're never really going to be looking at this character
in this exact way, usually going to be seen from them, from the behind.
And you're going to be looking at the zombies that are coming at you.
So like, all you're saying, what I'm saying is that your point is you don't
care about these details.
Others might.
And I mean, I'm not really getting to like a larger point of like sexy
characters are good and I do like them.
And I personally, if I were to design a game would not shy away from having a
sexy character.
I hope all I hope is that there's more people like me in the world like that,
who are not like terrified or making sexy characters with remakes.
It feels like, like it's always like a big brand.
They're making a remake to make money.
Nobody has any artistic, like not, not really, no real artistic integrity is
going into remakes because they're coming from a, you know, a point from the
top down, big guy says, we have an IP, need to make money, use IP to get people
to buy thing because they're stupid and they will buy the same thing over and
over again, sell same thing.
So for them, the entire thing is all about PR, appeases many people as possible
and have it be just okay and put it out.
And indie games don't need to worry about like things like that or like newer
games because they're the design characters for the first time.
So like, while this is bad and I agree with you, I generally just don't think
it's a big deal because remakes are bad, just in general, and fuck them.
Okay, but I mean, why are they bad?
Well, okay, that's a complicated question, but I'm a, you're arguing the pragmatism.
I'm arguing the like ideological concerns person.
I'm not arguing for them.
It's just sort of like, this is the reason I don't really see too much of an issue
because it's just, it's a remake already.
It's what, look, I'm not even a, I'm a kumar, but I'm not a big kumar.
And so like, yeah, I enjoy attractive female forms.
I am a big kumar, I'm just putting that out there.
Fair it out, fair it out.
It's, when it's so clearly stated in black and white, like the exact reasoning
that like these people are fundamentally opposed to, like, because they think they'll
have issues, to me, it stinks of cowardice or an ideology that I just disagree with.
Either they're trying to appease people and it does come back to like, they're
changing thing, I mean, Jill's outfit is iconic.
I never played Resident Evil, but everyone knows this fucking outfit because it was
great and everyone loves it.
But it's the beret too, all that stuff.
But they're, you know, I mean, it gets to larger issues of like, should we sanitize
culture, like is sexuality bad and needs to be scrubbed?
I mean, you know, that's the real issue it touches.
I would strongly argue, no, like I don't want like hardcore pornography
available 24 seven all the time.
I mean, available is one thing, but like visible and in your face.
But tasteful, you know, sexuality is not only appropriate, I think at a certain
point, healthy for people to be exposed to.
So I don't know, that's kind of what it gets to for me on the larger front.
And maybe you agree with that, but you're just arguing with pragmatism.
That's also what I'm arguing is that you'll never really get this from a
remake because of the way remakes are monetarily focused.
You know, like if you want to change the world of video games, remakes have
to stop being bought by people and new games have to be embraced more.
But, you know, it's not as easy as the biggest anti-remaker because the games
have to be good and, you know, all that sort of stuff.
I hate remakes, but good ones do exist.
I just discourage it because they generally come out bad.
For example, Pokemon Heart Gold, possibly the greatest remake of all time.
That game is, I mean, it's great.
And in basically no way does it make the original like worse.
Well, OK, it kind of replaces it, which is one of the reasons I don't
really like remakes, but it didn't really like sully the history.
I mean, they did change the design of the main character, which looks way gayer
now, which is too bad.
But other than that, it's it's basically inoffensive.
Everybody loves the Resident Evil One remake, which I never played, but they
tell me is like even better and just as good and honors the original.
All that good stuff that OK, that's all good.
That's all good.
So I don't know.
It's just about how you do it.
I forgot to mention about the Resident Evil 3 remake.
Yeah, the reason why I think the game is clearly so rushed and has so much
missing from it is that when you buy the game and you download it, it comes
in two separate downloads.
There's the game, Resident Evil 3.
And then there's an entirely separate game that is just like some lame,
online multiplayer raid mode left for dead bullshit.
Of course, like no one would ever play.
There's no reason anyone would care about this ever.
Nobody asked for this.
It's like four players are guys going around fighting, you know, hordes
in a room to try and get out of the room.
And one player is like a controller person, like putting zombies down,
like a SimCity guy.
And it's like, who asked for this?
What is the point?
And you know, it's not even in the game, which originated in Resident Evil 3.
The mercenaries mode is not even in there.
So they took out a bonus mode that was part of the game originally and
created a whole new bonus mode that is lame and sucks and nobody would ever
care about and also the game bad and also old good.
You know, we got to call this episode old, good, new, bad.
That really sums it up.
I'm just in a real slight tizzy about it.
Oh, I remember back in the day when they were making the first season of
Steven Universe, I was there when Garnet was a fusion for the first time.
That old was good, but this new was bad.
I just don't just not doing it for me.
God, they're going to remake Steven Universe someday and the nemesis is going to suck.
Hey, you know, I don't know if you guys are aware of this meme.
Michelle, despite being a true four-channer at heart, spends a lot of
time on Tumblr looking at girly, shitty Tumblr memes.
But there is one excellent Tumblr meme that's Steven Universe related
that I think you guys will appreciate and all of you listening.
I'm sure many of you are not Tumblrites as well, but I've been exposed to the
culture and I brought back this wonderful cultural artifact.
And now that Steven Universe is over, it's appropriate to let you all know.
It's that there's this there's this meme of when something happens in Steven
Universe that is shocking, unexpected, possibly even good.
You just screamed to the heavens.
You say, I'm bald, Rebecca, I'm bald.
And you snatch off your wig as a grand.
I think this is like related to what's like drag queen culture or something.
Because it's about like actually being bald and wearing wigs and how
Rebecca has snatched your wig in surprise.
OK, so there you go.
There's your cultural artifact from the gay community, everybody.
I'm very confused. Brought to you by Michelle.
Yeah, I can't follow that at all.
That sounds like pretty Michelle.
There's layers to that.
It's it's interesting, clearly missing crucial context.
I'm bald, Rebecca.
Thank you for making me bald.
I love that. Hey, all right, then.
So how about that?
What's up? PCP dating sim.
Oh, yeah.
The other thing I wanted to talk about, of course.
Well, first of all, let's just give full credit to the whole crew.
It is out, guys. Have you played it yet?
It's out. It's actually really good.
I've been all over it.
All of them. I did Mages' whole story.
I got killed by Slut Mage.
Yeah, so that I reloaded by Save and I didn't get killed by Good Mage.
But I got friendzoned by her, which is even worse.
Yeah, that's worse than death.
Are there like because that's the only thing that I've seen to the end.
Are there like like sex scenes and like no.
No, no, there's not that.
There are two like most of them don't resolve in a kiss.
I think two of them do only one of them is visual.
The other one is implied.
Well, because like not implied, just in text.
Because when I did because when I did the mage route, you know,
it didn't have one.
So I thought, OK, thank goodness,
they're not doing creepy, weird sex scenes of all of us.
Yeah, but then I had the thought, wait a minute,
what if they are doing it for all of us except mage because she is the girl?
And that filled me with rage and hatred for even the possibility of it,
of that double I could see that I could see thinking of that.
And I think they made that they made the safe, fair decision
to avoid doing so entirely.
That's probably what I would have done.
So I did that.
And then I did my route and I didn't get to the end of it.
I think I only got like half with you.
And it was like, what do you think of it so far?
My route was written by Chip Wiseman, who I is am I correct?
And assuming that everyone's route is written by like totally different people.
Yeah, the in the credits mostly.
Yeah, that's my route is written by like four people.
Yeah, yeah, like it wasn't as horrific and terrible
and awful and bad and stupid as I thought it would be.
Like there were parts in order to make friends with Jesse,
you have to be a bully and a bad person.
Jesse loves that shit. Yeah.
You. Yeah, I felt like your route was a little heavy on the references
and the like wacky person stuff like it's very like it's very clearly
like someone emulating my writing as my speech, which obviously
I don't necessarily speak like my writing in real life.
You didn't you didn't have a rant about poopy buttholes one time, not even one time.
It like like it wasn't as horrible as I thought it would be.
There were parts that like I thought were cleverly written
or that made me chuckle the whole part with Colt Corona.
I don't know if he's in it more than just this one part,
but there was one part where like Colt Corona is like just saying dumb shit.
And I'm like, that was that's funny.
Like I'm very happy to see Colt Corona immortalized in a video game.
I'm more, you know, in one of the other routes, I just saw a week
like something was happening and just a shadow darts past.
I was like, what the fuck was that? Yeah, I think it was Colt Corona.
There is a Colt Corona scene that I got to you.
That was very funny and hilariously written.
And it's like, like I am as trepidatious and horrified
as I am to see myself portrayed by like the fan interpretations of me.
You know, I am a human being like interpreted, you know,
interpreted as like this weird cartoon character that people see me as
as horrifying as that is to see Colt Corona, my greatest creation,
my son, my brother, my best friend, the chosen one, my partner in crime
in the darkest of times to see him immortalized in a video game was pretty cool.
So that was my favorite part so far.
Yeah, it's OK.
I've seen a good amount and I'm prepared to say that this project is good.
It is. It's definitely like the detail in the backgrounds
and all the little references everywhere. It's so cool, man.
Yeah, just like, I mean, I can't help but play it with like this
constant critical eye of rage of like, I would never fucking say that.
Why do you think this of me? What is wrong with you?
I hate you. You make me regret ever being a public figure in the first place.
I want to die. Yeah.
But aside from that, it's pretty. It's pretty deep.
So I guess. Yeah, yeah. I had a bit of a similar thing.
I mean, I haven't played it yet.
I'm probably going to play it tonight.
I'm terrified for basically the same reason you're saying just
of like how I interpreted. I felt like you guys give a disclaimer.
There was no connection to real people intended.
So I don't like all the dialogue is like funny and like I look at it
and it's charming. I'm like, OK, that's good. I like this.
And until like there's one like little jab in there that fucking ruins it.
Like it's like, oh, and then Jesse said this word,
but I don't think he knows what it means.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
Why would you say that of me?
Like, did I did I use that word wrong once and like five years ago
and just someone never forgot it? Like, stop.
You know, I feel probably I feel a little weird.
I mean, because I know the guy, well, OK, I won't won't go into that too much.
But just like when I'm playing my route, like first of all,
just the visual depiction of Nate is like such an exaggeration.
Like, I wish I looked like, you know, like Professor Bessman.
Professor Bessman, like my fear is what I get a lot of the time
because like a lot of my fans, they do a thing where they like think
that I'm actually way cooler than I actually am.
And like my biggest fear was that like this is going to be
I'm just going to feel bad about myself because this depiction of me
is like so much better.
But the Nate route actually it kind of deals with exactly that issue
of how like Nate projects and like looks really competent.
But actually, he's got a lot of like
I always feel like the fans, which is true, like I feel like the
like fans of mine think I'm cool for all the wrong reasons
that I don't want people to think are the reasons I'm cool.
Sure. Sure.
It's just like, like, I don't know.
Like they have me in the like, it seems like everything my character says
is like really smart and really clever and charming and funny.
But then every once in a while, like I'm also eating garbage and shit
and like rolling around and like there's like the.
There's like there's like the the last part I got to before I had to stop.
I didn't finish it, not for any like I didn't like rage quit or anything.
I just got, you know, busy, but like the tears just got a little too blurry
to keep playing. Yeah, yeah, I'm like I'm having some like debate
about Evangelion and like a bar with someone and like yelling at him
and like yelling about how he's an idiot.
I don't think I hate seeing like my anger be misinterpreted.
Like this, like there's like a line like, oh,
I don't see why he's getting so worked up over such a little thing.
Like when I lose my temper, it's not because I'm like angry.
It's because I'm fucking anxious because I'm usually surrounded
by like five guys interrupting me the whole time and can't make my point.
That's what causes me to like raise my voice.
I would I don't think I would just be sitting at a bar yelling at someone
about Evangelion like one person. Yeah, that's I don't give a shit, though.
It's definitely finish your root because there's a bad ending with Donatello
and it's really. Oh, no, of course, that would be the bad ending.
Why would it be the good ending? Of course.
I was going to say, Tom, I felt like the person who wrote yours
captured your like, I don't know, talking pattern pretty well.
They obviously know a lot about your stuff.
Really? That's good.
I wonder who wrote it. All right.
That's that's intriguing and creepy, but I'm more intriguing.
I'll probably check it out.
I thought that for whatever, like, I don't know, there's like a Nate
and then there's like a teaching assistant.
OK, I won't spoil for you like your role, but like the Tom role was like
among the most depressing, like initial setups of like it was so like
juxtaposed to the rest of the characters.
It was truly saddening, at least it just like real at first.
And then like in the Nate rat, which I'm playing through, obviously,
like there like you're like a subservient little worm to like tune Nate
and like there's like just for one example, like I get the idea here,
but there's like a big book.
You're carrying like a volume of the Urban Dictionary, like Encyclopedia or whatever.
You're like struggling to carry it with two hands.
You hand it to Nate who like effortlessly like dangles it with like one finger.
It's like, oh, God, this is too much.
This is rude is what it is.
It's just plain rude.
True.
They just know that I can't go to the gym anymore.
My muscles are just deteriorating.
Canonically, I think this is before you ever got hurt, though, or maybe not.
OK, maybe I don't know.
Maybe that's true.
If there isn't a Q&A from Tom at the gym, I will be deeply disappointed
because there is a gym.
There's one thing in my route, which I'm a little bummed.
I mentioned this when I streamed it, but there's a go.
There's a thing with my route, which like doesn't come up again.
And it's really interesting and I wish it had where like a new transfer student
comes in and it's she's called Gwulfbin, which is an abbreviation for girl who
looks like Riska, but is not.
And she's like, oh, she has the hots for Gibbon, the character.
And since this is a dating sim, you're trying to get me like there's like, oh,
no, you've got to deal with Riska.
And then also it was implied that Endless War was like also after me.
And it was going to be like a whole like love square sort of like battle.
But then it sort of it was dropped and they never came back up again.
I was like, no, that was that was too bad.
The coolest thing I've ever seen.
But God, you know, what if they remade the PCP dating sim and made it worse?
You know, I'm just someday we'll have to say, God,
old, good, new bed, you know, no, it can't be true.
They make it in 3D.
Has they face scanned all of us for all the graphics, but they removed the
DeVoo and Majora. It can't be true that the old was good.
Oh, no.
But I don't want to shit on it too much because like, no, I'm not like shitting
on it. It's clearly had a lot of love put into it.
The amount of work that went into it and the obvious love they have for
like our stupid podcast and is like incredible.
It's so hard work.
It makes it feel like it's all been worth it to keep this thing going for so long.
You know, there are a couple of monster episodes once in a while or a small price
to pay for, for, you know, I don't know.
The this is why, like, I don't know.
We talk about, like, you know, sometimes, like, do we need to make an episode,
like every week, you know, like, should we change the format?
All those are reasonable questions to think about.
But like at the end of the day, I really think it's just valuable to just have
the thing, at least in my life, maybe you guys agree, to have, like, a thing
in my life that I know, like every Sunday, I come here and I record a podcast
with my friends that I've known for a long time and I respect all of them.
And whatever happens, happens.
It gets put out there and hopefully people like it.
And you know what?
It's had pretty good results with something like this.
Just warms me old heart a little bit, see, people like in that stuff.
It's very humbling.
And, you know, on a more specific note about the dating sim, I got to say,
like Oblivionfall, Sixten, Canman, Eric, working on the soundtrack.
There is some incredible work in the soundtrack.
I mean, I want to listen to this whole thing because I see Canman in the
credits of the, of the, I'm looking at the dating sim, OST.
I've got it downloaded, Carcalicious Plus Plus Plus by Canman, apparently.
Oh, I think it's the one song by him, but there it is.
For example, I don't know if you guys have listened to the full main menu song.
Oh, yeah.
It is a nine minute anthem.
You can't turn it away.
It starts off with like generic dating sim music.
It event and Oblivionfall made this obviously.
He's a fucking genius.
It like skews into like a weird warped version of like through the fire and the
flames, like halfway through and then like warps into like more weird shit as goes.
And there's like a voice saying like, this is the menu.
You cannot stay here.
It will break if you keep listening.
Oh, incredible, incredible.
And the only other one, like there's a bunch of awesome stuff.
But the one song I wanted to mention is there's just a song called, and I'm sure
there's many examples of this, but there's so much heart, class of simple and clean.
I was, yeah, I was in, you know, like Nate's lecture and the thing.
And you just hear like generic classroom music and then just like mixed into the
melody in the back.
You just hear like, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk, punk.
They have mixed in like so many of like the, that was simple and clean from
fucking Kingdom Hearts one.
So many memes songs have been mixed into this soundtrack.
It makes me like so fucking happy to hear that shit.
It's like all the memes and all the stuff that I've cared about in my fucking
worthless ass life is being immortalized in this dating sim in ways that people
might actually give a shit about and think are cool.
They have a scene.
It's so cool.
Seen if you go on my route, where I play like chicken and a basketball for you in
my room.
Yeah.
Do they play the actual song from like your, oh, fuck yeah.
That's why I'm in the credits and I'm in the stuff because technically I said, yes,
you can use my music.
Oh, so they asked you when you gave permission to do so.
Cool, cool.
That's so cool.
Michelle has loved that there's a song called Michelle's Theme.
She's, she's pretty into that.
We all have little character themes in there.
This is, you know, only Michelle that I see, actually, literally only
Michelle was worthy of a character has an actual theme.
But like that class of symbol and clean is like a melody that's like Nate
related. And I'm sure that there are, oh, I would hundred percent heard a Jesse
song that, yeah, butt sugar was mixed into one of these songs at some point.
I forget what song that is, but it's so good.
Yeah, I do like the lore of the game.
The fact that like Nate and Ben canonically share the same philosophy
class and each time one teaches, they redecorate the entire room with like
their shitty memorabilia.
So cool, so fucking cool.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Just gushing a little bit.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm, I'm very glad it exists.
And I think I already said this, but like I asked them, like, can I, can I use
this fucking? It is just generally good music.
He said, yeah, I'm wondering if.
Yeah, I mean, since these people, this collective of people, however many
there are in this group, now that they've, you know, proven themselves to be
capable of something, like I'm wondering if like I could say to one of them at
some point, hey, I've got an idea for your fucking game.
Maybe you can get the gang back together and fucking do my idea.
The idea occurred to me as well to, to utilize this.
I mean, I want to, frankly, I would love to hear the tale from Eric himself.
Oh, sorry.
Well, Eric was like second.
It was Chip Weissman who like led the project.
I'd love to hear just the full tale of how he put it all together.
That'll be, that'll be in the heckles for Shekels stream.
The may have already come out by the time you're listening to this.
But we're planning to do like a thing where we get the developers in.
Right.
Great points, great points, because I want to hear the tale and because, you
know, among other things, I this like the game is obviously four free available
now, you can download it.
There's a patch, by the way, excuse me, make sure you get the patch version.
The OST is also free to anyone who wants it.
Like obviously all these guys worked for free.
At least I would assume so over this time, just out of love of the craft.
But like as it should be, as it should be.
I just want to hear how Chip, like he probably started small, probably got a
couple of people on board.
I saw he used Godot to make this.
I remember when I was making my game, indeed killed this, this game engine
killed three Palestinian children when they were, oh my God, and fucking 9-11.
9-11 exists in this game as a living embodiment of footage of the 9-11 terror
attacks.
It's so awesome that that happened.
I love that American lives were lost.
No, I apologize, everyone.
Whenever I forget what I was saying.
Anyway, so I was just saying that when I was working on my game back in the day
for like the game jam, me and my buddy Rich did, we were thinking of using
Godot or something, but we settle on good old RPG maker.
So basically I'm as good as these guys at making video games is the point.
Fair, fair enough.
I definitely have video game projects of my own that I will need
certain people to do things for.
So I will be that that's a little bit far in the future.
But yeah, I know I can call upon some of these people and they'll be like, hell,
yeah, let's work, let's work and make a fucking cool product.
Hell, yeah, it is.
It is really handy to have all these connections.
Let's cancel this whole endeavor and all just make video games.
We can be like fucking we can keep the podcast going.
But specifically, it will be exactly like Yandere Dev.
We'll make a weekly podcast, specifically discussing the like
10 lines of code that have changed every week on the project as we milk it for
years and years and years, six level deep if tree rest in peace.
Rest in peace.
Everyone's CPU running that game.
I'm ready to drink from the cum chalice and and seek oblivion.
Oblivion fall that is.
Hey, great work, buddy.
All right.
So I guess that's it about any other comments.
You guys want to say about it?
Well, here's the thing that's happening.
Yeah, the the no crowd WrestleMania is going on right now.
Oh, yeah, they're doing it over.
How is it weird as the one we are watching it?
Well, it's weirder because it's WrestleMania and it's like the biggest show.
And it's just like dead silent the whole time.
They should add ambient applause because it is so weird.
Yeah, they didn't hear anyone.
OK, so they should have like a PS1 like copy pasted like.
Yeah, the other wrestling company that's on TV, AEW,
it's like a newer organization.
They are also doing empty arena shows, but they had the idea of putting
at least some other wrestlers like around the ring to simulate crowd noise
and like react and just that small difference of having two or four people
outside the ring reacting to stuff makes all the difference in the world
and makes it feel like a wrestling show again.
And like it feels like the WWE didn't want to admit
that the other company had a good idea.
So they stubbornly don't do it and they have like no one around the ring.
There's everything is like dead silent and like really weird.
And like the match is like they're doing the stuff.
They're trying, but it's so are the rest of us wearing gloves.
Gloves. Do they have to social distance?
Oh, all right, right. Push them like force push.
No, but there is there is a clip from an indie match on Twitter
of I think Joey Janelle fighting someone in a social distancing match
where they are doing that.
They're like throwing like Hadouken punches and like not.
So incredible. Yeah.
But they didn't do even though like the majority of the matches,
you know, they definitely suffer some from not having the crowd.
And some of the big like moments like tonight, it's going to be the edge match
like his first match returning after like nine years out with a
debilitating neck injury.
You know, it's a big deal that he's returning.
And unfortunately, he has to make this great return to an empty arena.
So that's sad. Yeah.
But that's rough.
They did something.
The last match of the night last night was so cool.
It was the Undertaker versus AJ Styles in a boneyard match.
And this is the one part where like the social distancing quarantine thing
was ended up being like a blessing in disguise because
for the last couple of years, like Undertaker is he's much he's a much
older man than he was. And he's yeah, it's it's been kind of uncomfortable.
Some of his recent matches were like he's fighting Goldberg
and he's getting dropped on his head and like he can't stand at the end of it.
And it's just like, oh, maybe he should hang it up.
I don't like watching this hero, you know, be so like crippled and old.
This is bad. But they're they they're fucking the storyline
that they're doing leading up to this is sort of lampshading that
where AJ Styles has been like goading the Undertaker by going like, hey,
you've lost it.
You keep trying to come back into the spotlight and you're an old man.
You've lost your mystique.
You're posting on Instagram.
You've got a wife now.
You know, you do whatever your wife your your balls are in your wife's purse.
You know, you're not that.
Yeah, you're not like a badass undead wizard anymore.
You're just a guy named Mark and Undertaker is like, how dare you call me, Mark?
I'm going to kick your fucking ass.
My my legal name is the Undertaker.
Oh, so they're that's awesome.
So they're having a Boneyard match.
They didn't explain what a Boneyard match is prior to that.
I was wondering. No.
I think I think they probably would have called it a graveyard match,
but they didn't want to say graveyard like during the pandemic or something.
So Boneyard is better.
It wasn't even an actual Boneyard.
Like I was picturing like the elephant graveyard from the Lion King
where like in the video game where you platform on top of the like elephant skull.
It wasn't the undertaker will win platform.
It was just like it was just like a shed and like a shed and a yard
with a whole dug for a grave.
But they had they got this match was like so they they basically
just did the Matt Hardy broken stuff.
I was just going to say, this sounds just like the Matt Hardy.
Exactly. They yeah, they had like a camp.
They filmed it like a little mini movie.
And it was like the perfect way to accentuate
everything that is still great about the Undertaker while hiding all of his age
and like his the stuff he can't do anymore.
It goes you can just present him in this movie like a bad ass final boss.
And he comes out.
So this is so here's the thing about the Undertaker.
The Undertaker.
I've already said this in a vlog that I recorded today,
but I'm going to say it again here.
The Undertaker has has always had two main skill trees at his disposal.
He's had the undead wizard skill tree.
And he's also had a mean Texas biker skill tree.
Those are the two aspects, the yin and yang of the Undertaker.
But he has never used these two skill trees in tandem.
It's always been one or the other.
He's an undead wizard, and then he's a biker,
and then he's an undead wizard for a few more years.
And then, you know, back and forth forever.
This was the first time that he really pulled out all the stops
and fought at 100 percent full power.
You're utilizing both of his skill trees and one massive power set.
He was he was an undead wizard, Texas biker taker.
And the AJ Styles is at the as at the Boneyard.
They're they're they're doing like a thing
where it's like a so so they a hearse pulls up
and they pull out like a casket out of the hearse.
And you're thinking, oh, I bet the Undertaker is going to come out of this casket.
But no, AJ Styles comes out of the casket.
And he's like, see, I can come out of a casket, too.
It ain't even that scary, Undertaker.
You ain't you ain't bad.
Anyone can come out of a casket.
So then.
Then all of a sudden you hear the the distant rumble
of the of the fucking motorcycle.
The Undertaker's hog.
You hear it in the distance. Oh, fuck.
Yeah. See, the Undertaker riding his motorcycle
and all of a sudden Metallica is playing out of nowhere, out of the sky.
And the Undertaker comes up in his motorcycle
and he's like he's like a fusion of himself.
He's like an undead wizard biker.
He's like he's he's so he gets off his motorcycle.
It's like it's like a chrono trigger when you finally like have mastered elements
and you start doing dual texts using both elements at the same time.
Fuck, yeah. Oh, God.
And they're fucking fighting and they're beating each other up back and forth.
And at first, AJ Styles is beating up the Undertaker
and he beats them up really bad.
And of course, he's got his friends, Gallows and Anderson to help him out.
So they're they're all teaming up on him and they're beating him up.
And so he's got the Undertaker like on the ropes.
He's got him on the metaphorical ropes because they're not in a ring.
They're in a bow yard.
He's got the Undertaker is beating him up.
He hits him with it with a with a with a tombstone, like not the tombstone,
the move, he hits him with a literal tombstone.
And so like the Undertaker is like dying.
He's like, oh, God, you're hurting me really bad.
I am pretty old.
And AJ Styles like, yeah, old man, you're an old man.
You've got a wife. Fuck you.
Coming around here, having a wife and shit.
What are you gay?
Having a wife.
So he's taunting him as he throws him into the open grave
and he gets into like the bulldozer tractor thing to like pour dirt on the grave.
And he's like, I'm going to get you, Taker.
But then all of a sudden the Undertaker teleports behind AJ Styles.
Oh, my God, I'm not in the grave.
I'm behind you, motherfucker.
And there's like there's like like John Carpenter lighting like the thing,
like coming out shining from behind Undertaker.
So he looks really cinematic and scary.
And AJ Styles is like, oh, crap.
I forgot you have magic powers.
And the Undertaker kills AJ, he kills all of his friends.
He they they climb up to the roof trying to escape him like a zombie movie.
The roof of this shed.
And he gets up there and the Undertaker is just like, I'm a biker and a wizard.
And then he makes fire.
This is a great fireball.
He summons meteor and it's like a huge wall of flame.
He rubs behind AJ Styles.
And then he he he kills gals and Anderson.
They're fucking dead.
Then he beats the shit out of AJ Styles.
And so then he's like, he's like, yeah, how are you like that?
You're not even cool, boy.
You talk about my wife.
I'm the Undertaker.
I'll kill you and shit.
And like, I fucking hate my wife, dude.
And like this whole match, they're they're like taunting each other
and like trash talking each other and like giving these like cinematic
villain monologues to each other.
It's so like over the top and like like a grand insane spectacle.
And eventually Undertaker, he he he gets AJ up to the side of the open grave.
And he goes at this point, AJ Styles has been so thoroughly beaten
that he's begging for his life.
He's really turned.
He's really changed his tune.
You know, before he was like, I fuck you, Taker, you're old and you have a wife,
like a loser.
Now now he's like, oh, God, I'm sorry.
Please don't bury me.
Don't bury me, Undertaker.
It's like, oh, it's OK, boy.
You put up a hell of a fight.
I ain't gonna bury you ain't nobody giving me a fight like that.
He's like patting him on the head and stuff.
I ain't gonna.
And then he walks away.
But he turns around and he boots him into the grave anyway.
He's like, I can be a jerk too.
So then Undertaker buries him.
He buries him under all this.
He buries him alive under all this dirt.
And the last thing you see of AJ Styles is just a grave with like AJ's hand
like out of the grave, like he's just dead.
Like his hand is like, it's really cool.
And then Undertaker is like, well, my work is done.
And he puts his arm up to like celebrate his victory.
And as he puts his arm up, the house lights on fire behind him
and his his symbol lights up in a neon light on the house.
I don't know if he manifested the light with his powers
or if the light was already there and he turned it on with his powers.
Either way, it's equally impressive.
And also Metallica starts playing again on the sky.
And then he gets back on his hog and rides off into the night.
And it was the best thing ever.
I hope they do a million more.
Every Undertaker match should be like this from now on.
It was exactly what I want to see.
Thank you for saving wrestling with your tech.
Literally, yes.
Thank you for giving, for proving that this kind of thing can work
because now the Undertaker can be cool again.
And wrestling can be cool again in this dark time with no crowds.
We can have cool Undertaker matches like this, where he's portrayed
as he should be like an unstoppable badass and not like an old man wheezing in the ring.
Thank God for that hearty.
The only thing that would have made that better.
This would be my director's cut version is as he turns away and says,
you put up a hell of a fight, boy, I'm not going to bury you.
My wife is flying out of nowhere and fucking he'll drop some of the fucking grave.
That was awesome.
So that was the first night of WrestleMania.
And tonight's the second night.
Boy, I can't wait because tonight they're doing the John Cena versus
Bray Wyatt Firefly Fun House match, which I hope is another one of these.
I really am hope.
I got my fingers crossed in a real fun movie like this.
Yes. Yeah.
So Brent Wyatt's going to love that fun.
He means he's he's he's that's very much his aesthetic to kooky scary clown shit.
Hell, yeah.
Wrestling is cool.
Yeah. Wrestling is like like the ultimate form of
like when you're with your brother in the woods and you both have sticks
and you're like, there's the swords now and we're going to kill each other.
Yeah, yeah. Exactly.
I saw the video you posted before the Vanguard one invades the Jericho compound
and steals his shirt. Oh, God, I love it.
I love it. I love all this goofy shit.
I love it.
Just I love the fucking Chris Jericho is like cutting a promo on Vanguard one
as as if he is a person like Vanguard one, you son of a bitch.
I offered you a spot in the inner circle and you declined me.
Don't you dare decline me again.
Like he's like, for some reason,
he's like really invested in getting Vanguard one into his little clique.
And he's proved an invaluable ally to the deletion.
He's sitting in his hot tub and his palatial estate,
like cutting a promo on everyone.
Vanguard one shows up.
Chris Jericho gets out of the hot tub.
He's got his pants on and a belt.
Yeah, he does.
And it's just like he's having an argument with the drone.
He like offers him a shirt and I guess Vanguard one says, fuck you again.
So that's the second time now that Vanguard has declined his offer
and zooms away like a fucking zoomer.
And so Chris Jericho is in rage now because that little he goes,
that little bastard stole my shirt.
He released the home missing one shirt right now.
Yeah. Yeah.
He says, release the hounds like Monty Burns and a bunch of dogs,
like little Chihuahuas and like Pomeranians come out of his house
and start chasing after this flying drone that they can't possibly catch.
They have to stand on top of each other.
Yeah, dogs form a ladder of dogs.
I hope this pays off in a match between Chris Jericho and Vanguard one
and Vanguard one.
Fuck he's feuding more with Vanguard one than he is with Matt Hardy.
I hope so. I hope to see it.
Maybe we'll get his own drone and they could do aerial combat.
The Geradrone 5000.
Oh, yeah, that's good. That's good.
Hey, slight other note.
Hey, I got my lecture out.
People seem to like it.
It was, in fact, one piece.
Oh, now you know, what a shocker.
You know, it delighted me to see that some people were in fact surprised
to see it and you would see you would see things like, wow, in retrospect,
this was obvious, but I didn't see it coming.
And the other slightly concerning thing is I'm seeing people saying like,
wait, I thought Radcon was over or there are more lectures.
These people are not aware of what's going on with Radcon.
And people never aware that videos have to be made before they can be released.
Yes, they take time and energy to produce not everything that was done
is immediately posted while the event is going on.
When I saw when I post, I saw one comment that was like,
whoa, aren't you guys social distancing?
What do you do and all in one guy? Bro, bro, it's been it's been weeks.
Yeah, people are silly.
People are foolish.
Anyway, the lecture was cool.
And looking back on it, now that it's out, it's interesting to note
because exactly how many kind of gigantic plot points I did miss,
not even on purpose, but just in my haste to get through the whole story
in a paltry five hours.
And again, thank you guys for participating.
It was a great time, but because of the social distancing thing,
like when we went there, this did not seem like that immediately big of a deal.
While we were there, it changed the way it changed while we were there.
And we were kind of like I had to drive home like through it,
like through this ruined apocalypse of a world.
And also during this long drive home, I didn't have a debit card
because also while I was there, I logged onto my bank and found out
that someone had stolen my card information and made like a thousand
dollars of charges that I had to like I had to go to dispute
and I had to like get my card on hold.
So I had like a hundred dollars in cash to drive all the way home with.
And in the middle of this pandemic, like this actual end of the world
and like I ended up like totally fucked like out of out of oil out of gas
and like in like a random gas station in like Pennsylvania
with with like one hotel next to it.
And like I tried to go to the hotel and they were like, oh, you need a card.
You can't pay for a room with cash.
So like I was like totally fucked.
There was like an ATM.
But to use the ATM, I needed to get like the bank app
so that I could use it without my card and the app didn't work.
And the app sent me to a website.
The website sent me back to an app.
None of it worked. It was all.
So I stood there for an hour, like gradually getting matter
and like losing my mind in despair, like just stranded in the middle
of Pennsylvania, in the middle of a pandemic with no money to my name at all.
It was not good.
So that's my story of my journey home.
That's fucked. I assume you lived.
Yes, I eventually I managed to make it somehow.
I don't remember how exactly, but yeah.
I actually. Well, shit.
I had to. So I mean, did I was curious, did the whole countryside
like was it different from looking?
It was burning. Well.
It wasn't that much of a difference other than like everyone was weird
about taking my cash, which pissed me off.
Yeah, yeah.
Nobody wanted to touch like the the gas station clerks would like leave the cash
the change on the counter and like get away from you like cowards.
There was one like that's even going to do anything.
There was one courageous young woman at a Dunkin Donuts drive-through
who handed me my change and actually made the hand fingers contact.
And I just thought you are a brave and pure heart.
I love you.
You're the only good person in this whole ruined world.
I hope that you survive and no one else does because you had the courage
to touch my hand.
But the biggest actual difference I've experienced is that at drive-throughs,
people are now wearing gloves.
For me, that has been the biggest difference in my life.
And it just makes me think like, wait a minute,
shouldn't the fast food preparers always have been wearing gloves?
Why did it take this to get my food handlers wearing gloves?
Only the person working the drive-through wouldn't wear gloves
because they're touching the outside of the bag, which I guess is fine.
I don't know. I don't know. The fair point.
The only difference I've noticed is that I look up in the sky
and it's really quiet and there's no airplane trails and it's really nice.
And you know what? I kind of like that.
You know, there's still too many people out and about for my taste.
I still when I'm out, I still feel crowded.
Like there needs to be a worse pandemic.
Like no pandemic is big enough for me.
I won't be satisfied until everyone is gone and dead or hiding.
Like I had to go to Walmart to get something.
I don't even remember what, like supplies, like tea or some shit.
But just like, you know, like early in the morning at like 8 a.m.
and it was just packed with baby boomers with these carts full of shit,
like toppling over the sides in my way.
Every aisle I tried to go down, it's like,
isn't I would assume that like the places should be empty.
You'd think like end of the world, everyone is hiding.
That means I'll have room finally to move around.
But no, it's like more packed out there than ever
because of these fucking boomers.
Yeah, I was really with their chains,
their chains of 10 carts tethered together by rope,
taking up entire aisles of Walmart.
Yeah, I was really pissed off like on the flight home
because my flight was canceled and I had to rebook
and they made it easy through the app.
I was like, OK, there's another flight same day a little bit earlier.
And I was thinking like, oh, like they're cancelling a lot of flights.
Maybe this means that like people are cancelling their flights
and like they're not going to fly anymore.
They're not going to go on holiday today.
But of course, what it actually meant was my flight that I was rebooked on
was completely packed and there were multiple people sneezing
and lots of people with hand gel and everyone was scared.
And I was like, God, this is going to be like fucking six, seven hours.
And I was in the window and I was stuck up against the window
and I had to like these two, this couple next to me.
Well, like every time anything was touched,
they would get out the bottle of hand sanitizer
and they would squeeze it all over their hands and it's like, God,
they probably think I'm the worst because I'm not wearing gloves or a face mask
and I'm not, I don't have that shit because I wasn't prepared.
And I went to yesterday.
I went to like the little convenience store nearby just to get some stuff.
It was hilarious.
So I live in the ghetto and it was full of of urban individuals
just going about their day and it was fucking sick.
But I'm walking in there with like gloves and face mask.
And like the first thing happens is that the guy just like comes up to me
as you know, as often happens here and the guy's like, Hey, man, you got some change
and you're like reaches out to shake my hand and I I'm wearing a mask and gloves
and I just recoil and I'm like, is this is what it feels like
to be truly an upper class hero?
I don't want to touch these lower class scum.
This let's avoid contact.
And I was thinking like, should I stand here and explain?
No, no, no, you don't understand.
It's just social distancing.
I got out and I was like, fuck it.
I just walked on.
Was I a part of the problem that day?
Did I look like a bad guy?
Probably.
Pardon me.
I mean, you had the whole thing up like they could probably assume the signs
were crystal clear.
He reached out like for a handshake and I like he was like reaching out to me.
I like jumped back and recoiled.
Like I don't even I'm not even really that scared or even worried.
It would have been less scary.
I had the mode for a gun.
And then it would have been embarrassing that I recoiled.
He's actually like a really nice guy and I've seen him around before.
He very politely asked, but just like the reach out just happened to be
the exact thing I'm trying to avoid with all this shit on my face.
So I had a very visceral reaction in the moment.
You know, the homeless around me are very nice.
I like them.
They never bother me.
They just ask for food or money.
And I always say, no, and it's great.
We all go about our day.
I just I just hate the ones that ask for money and you give it to them
and they ask for more money.
Yeah, it's just like, yeah.
That's why I just don't do it.
I never give my to anybody.
It ruins it for everyone because it makes me not trust anybody
and not want to give any homeless person money.
Although, you know, I was thinking really wasn't for the sickness.
I bought like some snacks or whatever if it wasn't for the corona
and I was just trying to get out of there.
I probably would have given that guy like some of my snacks
if I've been thinking clearly, but I was in the rush to
oh, I had my like live stream or whatever.
So I was I was rushing callous guy all absorbed in his daily business.
Tough being a two bird.
It's tough. It's tough.
I got a schedule to keep.
I got my titty stream is coming up in five minutes.
I got a plump and thickened.
You know, before I go live, the one good thing that happened
on my on my drive home through the the fucking this plague world
is that like I was going through like some random
mountain town and like the like in like bumpfuck Pennsylvania somewhere.
And like there was this I was hungry and I just happened to pass
like in the middle of nowhere, this like country dining establishment.
And I'm like food and I pulled in there and it's like this beautiful
like serene looking log cabin establishment sitting on a hill
overlooking this quiet little Twin Peaks mountain town.
There's like woods in the distance and like fog rolling over the hills and stuff.
And I'm like, oh my God, I've like stepped into the real America here for a second.
And like I walked into this restaurant
and like the dining was all the lights were off and it was, you know,
no one could sit down and eat.
But like walking into this like folksy little diner
and like giving the girl my order and sitting down to wait for it.
And like the the owner of the place was sitting there, who was like an older lady.
She started like talking to me and asked me questions like, oh, where are you going?
And I'm totally like, oh, I was down here for a work thing and I'm driving home
and I'm stuck in this and that we were like bonded a little bit.
And it was like I was talking to like Stephen King characters.
Like I just walked into this folksy like little slice of Americana.
And like I walked out like, oh, my goodness, this may maybe it's
maybe it's a good thing that everyone's dying.
Yes, it definitely is.
And so I got in my car and I took out my little burger.
And it was like the best burger I've ever had, too.
It was like it was like a oddly good.
Like I think I stepped into like the Twilight Zone or something.
They just first like, yeah, but it was like it was like one of the
like the uplifting Twilight Zones, not one of the scary ones.
Right. Right.
It's like death doesn't come like a thunderbolt.
It comes like a whistle.
Yes, it's like like the one where the guy dies and his dog is there
and he goes and the guy says, welcome to heaven.
Oh, we don't allow dogs.
And he's like, well, then I don't want to go.
And then he meets God and is like, oh, that wasn't heaven.
That was hell. They were trying to trick you.
And he's like, well, I knew because my dog didn't want to go in.
Based, so fucking based.
Yeah, that's what it was like.
It was that episode with the dog.
That was Muslim heaven where they don't allow dogs.
They're they're no fans.
They're no fans from what I hear.
Hey, did you guys see punk has an only fans account now?
Oh, God, I didn't want to think about it.
But here it is thrust in front of my face.
I've been trying to.
That's my daughter.
That's my niece.
And now she's being a hoard out on the Internet.
It was her idea like a common thought.
I don't acknowledge her autonomy as a human being
or a pumpkin being to make these decisions for herself.
I mean, women, you know, you don't have a right that I actually got a few
people's sub for a month, which is the most epic thing of all time.
No, I am.
I probably did it out of curiosity
and also they would have given me money anyway, but it was very cool of them.
I feel like I need to like make a follow up image.
Yeah, at least one.
Give the people got to do something for.
Hey, man, I mean, maybe this will turn out to be the right decision all along.
And this is the avenue we should all be going.
It's it's, you know, make money is the most important.
It's good enough for Idubs.
It's good enough for me.
Yeah, I mean, the whole Idubs thing is not important.
The fact is people were talking about it and I capitalized on it like a capitalist hero.
Smart.
Yeah.
Well, that's life.
Hell, yeah.
As the Joker would say,
truly, this is a clown world we live in.
Well, we got voicemails.
You want to go to them?
Yeah, I'm good.
I said my piece.
All right, that's all the talking that I knew how to do.
OK, here we go.
We've got voicemails.
Speakpipalink is in the description.
You can leave voicemails, blah, blah, blah, you know the drill.
All right, let's see.
We got our first one is OK.
Hang on my fucking mouse.
PC police are back.
OK, it's one's kind of hard to hear, but do your best and listen.
And we will have a journey.
OK, here we go.
We have won.
You thought we had given up.
You thought you had bested us, but you, you were wrong.
We started with the lowly Asian PCP fans, the Chinese.
And now our virus is said to have all the PCP fans worldwide.
Oh, no.
The only downside is the world leaders.
Those big wigs and fat cats fumbled the name because we called it
called coronavirus or whatever.
Oh, 19 close enough.
Now, PCP members crumble in fear as we the PC police.
The PC.
Wait, what's what's going on?
What's going on?
Sorry, sir, we were just attacked by a clustered character
dressed in a pizza onesie.
And we dropped a new, improved vial of the coronavirus.
Our base is now infected.
What's shatsky?
Where is he?
He's currently giving us demands.
Demands.
What are you talking about?
He wants to steal your dad.
No, no, anything from Papa Garland House.
Joining us now, Brad Merlinghouse is the CEO of the cryptocurrency developer
Ripple Ripples.
What is that?
Oh, no.
Do not fuck with me.
Dude, so the coronavirus was made to get us or rather the PCP fans.
Correct.
You know, that works because like we are the reason people are dying after all.
Oh, you know, it's true.
The idea of this virus being somehow linked to cold corona is like,
because it's such an obvious joke, everyone's making it,
but everyone's making slightly different versions of the joke.
So the lore is like so convoluted.
No one really knows for sure.
Like if he's responsible for it or just a victim of it like everyone else,
you can't say for certain, even I can't.
Even he can.
What an enigma.
Especially he can't.
Let's see what we got next.
Okay, here we go.
Three is not a creative number.
Let's hear it.
Oh, well, this is culture death.
I mean, three people on the last episode.
Seriously.
Oh.
Well, if no one else is saying it, then I guess I will.
Every member not in this week's episode listening to this voicemail as it is being played right now.
Okay.
You will never let this down.
Yeah.
You are a member of the PCP.
Fucking act like it.
Damn.
Harsh words.
Don't these people also complain when there's like too many people on the show?
Yeah.
There's no way.
That's less of a problem these days.
There's different camps.
You know, you can't please everybody.
All right, fuck it.
Let's just go straight on to the next one.
Although fuck everyone who isn't on the PCP.
It's a delight to be here with my friends.
I savor the opportunity.
All right.
Special shout out to my boy Ben St.
I love that guy.
I'm just like the fuck that guy.
The resignation of just like admitting like that's not much of a problem these days.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's true.
All right, let's check out Nyan Kwan who is leaving us a message.
Okay, sounds good.
Take it away, Nyan.
Hey, everypony.
It's Pinkie Pie here.
Just wanted to say hi to my favorite ponies around.
Of course you crew.
I'm so proud of how much you've grown and how for you progress in your careers.
Everyone has achieved so much and I'm so happy.
I just know that you're all going to do great things.
Can't wait to see what's in store for the PCP.
I love you guys.
Roadies forever.
That was a really good voice.
That was really Pinkie Pie.
That was too real.
That was real Pinkie Pie in real life.
I actually really like that.
Well, I think what it was, there was a thing that was going around Pony Twitter for a while
because I still follow people into the show.
There was some AI thing where you can feed in voice information.
That was really high quality.
Whatever you wanted to say.
I mean, some of the Twilight ones I've heard were pretty accurate.
The Fluttershy ones they were doing have Fluttershy's soft pronunciation for things.
So it was pretty good.
That was so nice.
I was waiting for the other shoot-a-drop and for it to be a mean look.
Yeah, I was waiting for the other shoot-a-drop.
Thank you Pinkie Pie.
The shoot-a-drop is now that Pinkie Pie said such nice things.
I have to take a hard look at myself.
Am I worthy of such words?
No, I don't deserve it.
Yes we are.
I feel bad.
Well at least somebody appreciates all that we do for this world.
Pinkie Pie.
She would.
As long as I have Pinkie Pie's respect.
As long as the main six always appreciate love and respect us,
then there can be no nothing bad.
We're on the straight and narrow.
New bad main six good.
Pinkie Pie good.
That's hitting me a little harder than I expected it to.
And I already listened to it as I was preparing them.
It's making me a little emotional.
The thing that Pinkie Pie would be proud of me.
Oh Jesus Christ.
Alright, let's move on.
I could never truly pray all that gay away.
I wish.
Alright, let's check out-
Which you can pay the gay away at Patreon.com.
Patreon.com.
D-Pro guys.
What are we called now?
No one knows.
This is from-
This is simply called Nate's Soundboard.
Recommended audio.
Turn your audio way up everyone.
I'm not going to want to miss a second of this.
Let's check it out.
Go.
Turn it down.
Bruh.
These nuts.
Bazinga.
Be gone.
Good.
I'm gay.
Yes.
Oh, that's Robin Stinger from One Piece.
That's a great one.
It's the Nate nodding at every sound effect.
Yep.
Yeah, yeah.
The other promise.
Roxas theme.
You make a good other.
Too long.
Bazinga.
Yeah!
That's a good one.
I just wanted to let you guys can't hear it.
You know, I since added Bazinga to my soundboard
and I'm currently mashing it every half a fucking second.
I'm mashing it so fucking fast.
And a couple of farts with reverbs.
Super crazy.
None of this is going to come onto the podcast unfortunately.
But I really loved that moment I was experiencing right now.
It was great.
You're like a baby with like a sound box.
Like a little plastic sound.
Like the cow goes moo.
Yeah, cow goes moo.
The Sheldon goes Bazinga.
I was, you know what it's like?
I was saying before it's like having a, being a transhumanist.
I've attached these soundboards to me.
I now have additional functions as a human being.
But really it's more like augmented reality.
Because I'm wearing the goggles as I'm listening to my computer.
But none of you guys are.
So like I'm seeing things that are not there.
Kind of.
Okay, anyway.
My soundboard is sick.
And I took that as a bunch of suggestions to put on the soundboard.
And there's some good ones in there.
Smoke weed every day.
Not a bad idea.
All right.
Next one.
Here we go.
This is from unga bunga lecture heads.
Okay.
And go.
Hey, I have like a basic ask question for names.
The one piece lecture.
Really great.
I fucking loved it.
Nice.
I just feel people are kind of getting the wrong message from it.
And I just want to know whether you agree or not.
I see a lot of people who are kind of like, oh, thanks for this.
I'm just going to skip everything.
Oh, I'm totally caught up on one piece now.
Better start on chapter 900 and whatever we're on.
76.
I feel like that's like the wrong interpretation of the lecture.
Right.
Like your whole point was telling them to go read it.
But then these people are just kind of thinking that they get to skip everything now.
I don't know.
Let me know.
Well, I can't imagine starting something not at the beginning.
So this whole concept is.
Right.
Of course.
It would be, it would be insane.
Kind of.
I mean, because as, as Sean here says at the very beginning, like, um, like I clarify,
read one piece and continually throughout it, I'm like, read one piece.
I have to skip so many details.
So if you just want your opinion, your thought confirmed, then yeah, certainly I agree.
That's the correct way to do it.
And, uh, I would net, like, even if, well, I mean, the lecture covers like the big plot
elements of like Ponyglyphs and the Grand Line and like what is the King of Pirates
and like the Willa Dee and shit.
Like, not even in that much detail, but you're touching all of those.
But like one piece is, I mean, maybe I should have emphasized this even more, but I did say
it in there.
It's about the journey, not the destination really.
And Luffy made that very explicit at various points in the story.
So yeah, just got to experience it.
This, this sentiment, if it's being expressed in the comments is like the equivalent of
saying, oh, I read a Wikipedia article.
I don't have to watch a movie that the article was about.
It's like, it's not even close to the same experience.
It's like the equivalent of watching like my Gurren Lagann videos and saying, you're right,
Nate, you can just turn your brain off and enjoy Gurren Lagann.
That there is nothing beyond what was initially stated as in just the opposite of the intent.
Do you think this is like people like wanting to be up and like, you know, understanding
the relevant stuff without having to spend any of the time to get into all of this stuff?
Absolutely.
They don't want to commit cowards.
It's paradoxical.
People don't want to be left out of the conversation.
But you won't get anything in the conversation if you don't actually care about the thing
that's being discussed.
Yeah.
You can't properly care about it unless you go along the actual journey.
Also, where are they that they're just surrounded by one piece conversation that they have to
cram for immediately right now?
This is, I mean, the world has changed for me so much.
And like, this is why like, given I made the potty cast when I was young, I was the like
the only one I knew who gave a shit.
I mean, I wasn't that internet savvy back then.
So I was just sitting alone, like reading one piece, looking around and hoping for someone
to care and no one did.
And then like 15 years past, and now like we have a podcast that has like assembled
dedicated viewers, people who follow week to week and like give a shit about it in a
pretty thoughtful way and pretty detailed way anyway.
And like now, now, and like, I don't know, not, you know, whatever, my feelings aside
don't matter.
But guys like Jeff are like doing like catch up things.
And I wonder about the exact motivations.
Maybe it's just because they want to be part of the conversation, or maybe it's because
they feel left out, or maybe it's because they're out of material and one piece is getting
pretty popular right now.
I don't know.
I mean, any of those are fine.
I don't blame them as businessmen, but it's, I don't know, it's just, it's such a weird
thing to see like that side of the story when for me, it's just been such like a personal
thing for a long time, a long time, whatever, I don't begrudge him.
It's just, it's interesting.
And yes, I'm a better fan than you and always will be.
I win.
You lose.
That's the end of the conversation.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Old thing.
Good.
In that case, my fandom of the series, your new thing is your fandom bad.
Yeah.
You go into it now.
Die.
God, I love being a gatekeeper.
It feels so good.
All right.
We got one final voicemail.
This is from, let me see.
Battery man.
Yeah.
Okay.
Take it away.
Go.
Remember when you could jack off the space jam and nobody thought you were a perfect?
Yes.
The only reason people don't want to have Judy Hobbs is because of worries have created
a stigma.
Oh my God.
Thank God for saying this.
Being attracted to cartoon animal people is completely natural human sexuality.
It was quite normal before all this shit happened.
Fuck furries.
There you go.
I've been saying that exact thing for years now.
I feel like this guy is like, I should sue this guy first.
But I won't because I appreciate him also saying it.
Yeah.
He's saying what we're all thinking, I think.
Lola Bunny was so unequivocally hot and everyone wanted to have sex with her that it should
not be any kind of weird thing to feel.
There wasn't even entertained the thought that it might be a weird thing because these
weird people did not exist yet to taint and pervert it.
My father would stride around Walmart proudly wearing his shirt of Bugs Bunny spanking Lola's
red and ass and it was not frowned upon, but now he wears it simply the time has passed
and Zootopia is out and now he's getting looks.
Don't do this to my father, furries.
Let him live his life.
Yeah.
It's a travesty.
It's one of those terrible things where people associate, people assume you're way in more
in than you are.
The whole brony thing.
I like the ponies, they're cute and all that and because the label brony has been during
that time, it was a big deal if you were coming out as a brony and everyone would hate you
or love you and it was just like it needn't be like this.
It's just a cartoon, it's cool.
It's why we can't have nice things.
Everything good and pure is inevitably co-opted by freaks.
It's just that poisonous binary thinking that everything breaks down to online and it's
just so reductive and it's disappointing.
Yep.
Oh shit, I was going to say something about that.
Yeah, I want to fuck Lola Bunny is what you were going to say.
We all want to fuck Lola Bunny.
We're all in agreement, everyone in the world.
Secretly, you don't say it out loud, you're all, we all know.
She was specifically designed to make you want to fuck Lola Bunny, animated and drawn.
That's when he got a boner on screen and I was like, same.
Same.
It is not weird to be attracted to what are obviously humanoid characteristics applied
to characters who have some non-humanoid characteristics.
That's why I'll proudly jack off to any quality porn of, I don't know, if it's furry who gives
a shit, if it's fucking Judy Hopps who gives a shit, if it's fucking My Little Pony who
gives a shit.
If there's human-like qualities, yeah, fuck it man.
I'm not a furry, never been, not interested, but if there are just human qualities that
are sexy, I will achieve boner status and it will be awesome.
If I see a tree outside that vaguely resembles the feminine form, I will assume it's flesh.
That is consent, that tree has consented.
You ever see the images of vegetables that have tits, a carrot that looks like a penis
or something?
Those funny things.
Have you seen the image that's been posted around during this corona thing, during the
whatever, being blocked inside of two lights on the ceiling and the way the shadows are
being cast kind of look like tits and the guy's like, yo, the ceiling about to make me act
up?
And same.
Same, brother.
Have you guys ever heard that old joke about Tarzan fucking Jane?
Don't know.
No.
Jane wants to fuck Tarzan and she says, you know, put it in here Tarzan, have you ever
done this before?
And Tarzan goes, no, me use hole in tree.
And she goes, well, okay, this is a bit better than that.
It's, you know, she shows him where to put it and then Tarzan kicks her in the crotch
as hard as he can.
And she goes, oh, oh my God, Tarzan, why did you do that?
And he goes, checking for termites.
I remember that.
I remember that one.
Oh, that is classic.
That was a deleted scene in the Disney film.
Indeed.
God, Jane was so fucking hot in Tarzan.
Jesus Christ.
Everything good.
You know, the voice actor played her, played the like the girlfriend in Goodwill Hunting
that like British lady.
I didn't know.
I forgot her name.
Mini, mini, is it mini driver?
Whatever.
I don't know.
I love both those things.
So I thought that was cool.
Jane and Goodwill Hunting.
Okay.
Anyway.
All right.
That's the end of the voicemails.
All done people.
Speak pipe link down below.
You know what the gist is.
And that brings us to the end of the episode.
That's it.
PCP episode, whatever this is, 205, 206.
205.
There you go.
It's done.
Bye.