Yeah, yeah, yeah, uh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did I'm jerking?
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
Welcome back.
Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It's me, Munchy.
I'm out in the woods.
I've been straight out for a couple of days now.
The woodland creatures are my friends now.
I was on the plane and now I'm here.
Pro Crastinators Podcast is a podcast about all of my good friends here.
Where they come from all over life.
High, low, slow, or bold.
They're all here.
They draw things.
No, they don't.
They draw things with their voice.
That's what they do.
They video edit.
They're good people.
Here we go.
Ben Saint.
He's last now.
It's Nate Man.
Hey, guys.
I'm the best guy ever.
Just O natural here.
Naked.
We have Tomson.
Hello.
I just made a new animation.
It's a week old by the time you listen to this, but it's still good.
It's still fresh.
Check it out.
It's what that is.
It's the way that you hear she comes.
Hello.
I am Trekin now.
There we go.
We have the digi.
How long since you've smoked?
Less than five minutes.
He didn't.
Okay.
You have to say.
What?
You have to go.
You have to say.
Oh, you have to say it.
I'm keeping it all natural.
I'm not into these laboratory produced chemicals.
I'm keeping it in nature with my sweet cannabis weed.
I'm smoking a fat bag of bowls here.
I was wondering how long it's going to take until someone mentions weed.
Well, zero minutes.
About a minute ago.
I was waiting for everyone to say their piece.
All right.
Okay.
So here we go with fucking nature with fucking nature.
Here we go.
Oh Christ.
Oh, my recording just stopped.
It just stopped.
Is that true?
Really?
It just stopped.
Okay.
Hold on.
That's not good.
Nature.
Here we go.
It's nature.
My audio is better now.
Good job for noticing that one audience.
Nature.
Do not flanderize me is my first point about nature.
We're not going to do the dictionary thing because everyone gets mad at us when we do
it now.
It's now like a taboo.
People don't like it for some reason.
No one gets mad.
We have to read this definition because it's the best definition there's ever been.
All right.
Here we go.
Urban dictionary definition.
Nature.
And erection.
Little boy.
Listen.
Okay.
Little boy on waking in the morning.
Mama.
What's wrong?
It's sticking up.
Mother to her son.
That's okay, little man.
It's just nature.
Yeah.
Okay.
That is good.
Here's how I define nature.
I define it as the enemy.
It's the thing that we are all put on this earth to defeat and subjugate.
Someday there will be none and that's when I want to live.
I have a complicated and sad relationship with nature.
It is evil and I know in my heart of hearts that I have more negatives than I have positive,
but it's just so seductive in most of its ways.
It always tries to lure me to its green, vile grass, but I have to deny it access to
my true heart.
You sound like a robot that's like in the middle of malfunctioning right now.
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean?
So much that I can barely understand what you're saying.
No, that's not true.
You've got to calm down.
You've got to take L.
I have a lot to say about nature.
I've taken my pills a lot.
I'm a part of Big Pharma.
We've been cutting down all the forest so that we can make more pills so that we can calm
your fucking nature problems.
So if you're having a problem where nature is causing you to be hyperactive and fucking...
Am I like literally the only one who loves nature in this podcast?
No, I do.
I do.
I like nature.
I just realize that it's awful in every way.
I like...
Okay, I have a big point to say about nature.
But here, here, let's rate nature.
Like I want to say like six or seven.
I'm going to say hard seven out of ten for nature.
Okay.
I give nature like a solid nine.
I find cool shit outside like all the time.
Yeah, I give a nine out of ten as well.
Needs more purple though.
I'm going to give it a...
That is seven or eight.
That is the slight eight.
Needs more purple is the same reason I wouldn't give it a ten, incidentally.
So I'm with you on that one, Mage.
I'm going to give it a solid two.
I mean, I think it did some good things in its day,
but I think that it's been far surpassed.
You know, it's been iterated upon and rendered mostly obsolete.
I'm also going to give it a two.
The only reason it even gets a two is because it spawned me and my compatriots here.
That's about all the good it's done.
Nature is the final barrier holding humanity down from reaching its true potential.
Once we surpass the limitations, nature is placed upon us like our own mortality.
We will be unburdened by its primitive bullshit,
and we can achieve greater things than we ever could before.
I'm interested to see what Nate will say.
I wonder what his rating is.
You know?
Because it would go to show from what we know about him that would be low.
You might have expected me to say that I'm not a big fan of nature
and that I only care about human progress and evolution
and, you know, advancements in the scientific field,
but there is an aspect of nature that I quite like
and I quite like how it affects the value of two stats,
usually increasing the non-HP stat by 10% and decreasing another by 10%.
You know, like the nature of your average like, you know, a fly-gon, for example,
can make a big difference in whether it's turny viable or not.
So in that respect, I find nature to be a very valuable force.
A lot of people criticize it for being overly complex and obtuse,
not making a lot of sense in terms of the Ghazam Kutzwerk of the gameplay,
but I like it. I like it still, though.
Before we continue on the subject of nature,
I'd like to introduce a new segment really quick.
It's called, it's called Ben vs. Ben.
Oh, boy!
Oh, I like this.
Here's a clip of Ben St. from episode like 10 or so of the PCP
where we're talking about probably sequels or something.
Ah, iterative works can never be as good as the original.
Originality is the most important thing for a work of art to have.
Iterations can never live up to originality.
Fast forward, Ben St. 2018. Nature, gay.
Well, you know, you're on to something there.
You're close to truth.
You would have a point, except that nature is not a work of art
because nature was procedurally generated by an algorithm.
Oh, shit.
So is Nuclear Throne not art?
Is Nuclear Throne not art?
Is that what you're trying to say?
Well, nobody made the algorithm.
Wait, I mean, no.
Well, God made it, you stupid idiot.
Did you not read the instruction manual, a.k.a. the Quran?
Wait, shit.
Okay, all right.
I've backed you on the corner now.
Nuclear Throne is a work of art,
but any individual game of Nuclear Throne is not
because it was procedurally generated.
Then where is the art if every single run is not art?
Where is the art, then?
It's in the algorithm.
You just said, if anything, the algorithm should be the opposite of art
because the algorithm is the part that is procedurally generated.
I agree.
The algorithm is not procedurally generated.
The algorithm is static.
The instances that are derived from the algorithm.
The algorithm was crafted by a master craftsman.
God.
Yeah, God among men.
Well, there we go.
We solved nature.
Okay, okay.
Here's what I want to start this off with.
Here's my big point.
Just straight to the point.
Use my main weapon first.
I want to.
I like nature and stuff, but I know how I can make it better,
and here's what I want to institute across all the land.
I want to amusement parkify nature.
I like seeing trees.
I like to breathe, and I like seeing relatively small animals,
ones that cannot pose a threat to me.
Rabbit's a bit too big.
I want to see maybe a snake or something with no teeth.
That's what I like.
I want there to just be big sections of the nature,
forest, desert, whatever.
Completely taken over by man
and turned into nature light with all the edges smoothed
and there's pathways everywhere.
I want to walk into a forest on a street,
and I want to just walk on the street.
Have you ever been to Disneyland in the fucking...
What's his name?
The adventurer guy?
The guy with whip, that part?
You can just walk around and you're in a jungle type place.
I want to be in a jungle with roads.
Aren't these called parks?
I'm totally on your side here.
That's not nature enough.
I'm totally on your side here
because I think all you need to do,
this is the one stop solution to solving nature
and making it fucking awesome for everybody,
debug nature.
Yeah, I feel it.
And by that I mean remove the bugs.
That's what I meant by that.
You just need to remove all the bugs.
Nature's great.
The only but someone removed is mosquitoes.
No man, recently...
So during the summer time,
I moved into this new place up in fucking New York
and there's a bunch of paths near my house,
really nice paths through just the wilderness basically
that would be fun to run on every single day
if not for the fact that during the summer
it's completely full of these giant flies
that love just landing on you constantly.
So if you try to walk down this path,
you just constantly have flies landing on you
and it's so fucking maddening
that you can't even walk on it
and then in the winter it's completely covered in snow.
So basically it's useless.
I agree with you, though I want to have a slight compromise
because I love bugs.
I'm a big bug enthusiast
but I do agree that they are sin.
They are what makes bad things happen.
So here's what I want to propose.
Reduce the population of all bugs by 75%
but increase their size by double.
So you can walk into a cave somewhere
and those will be huge fucking beasts.
This is just going to be an RPG world
where every high step give a fucking giant fucking bug.
That's what I want.
I want bugs to be beasties.
This is how small and sneaky bugs are
so if we could annihilate that factor
it would be just less bugs
but they were all 100 times their size.
That would go a long way to making me more willing to accept them.
You want spiders big enough to eat you.
You want spiders big enough to consume you
to get trapped in a giant spider web.
She's right.
Bugs, there aren't insects.
They're still bugs.
I think they are. I would consider them bugs.
Bugs is cultural.
Bugs is culturally just defined.
If even a bunny could be considered bugs
then the door is wide open.
The term bugs is a social construct
made by fucking hominid overlords.
Yeah, yeah.
So what I'm saying is
I want to get a soda in a forest.
I want to walk through a forest.
I want there to be a sidewalk on there to be ropes.
I want to be able to walk over a ravine
and be like wow what a cool ravine
but I'll still have a gun.
There might be some torches nearby.
There might be some of that guided tendon.
I want to be able to kill any animal
that tries to defuse me.
There are places like this.
This is what a safari is.
Like Australia or something.
Yeah, but can I go to the safari two minutes from my house?
Actually I can because it is a safari zoo where I live.
But that doesn't count.
That's not true.
That doesn't count.
I want that to be every forest.
There's places like that that they build over like a marsh
where you can like walk on like a bunch of bridges and shit
and just be like whoa it's a marsh.
Sick dude.
That should just be all nature.
Nature would just be better.
Actually I want to say that
it's interesting you mentioned that Munchie.
Like I'm imagining all of nature having paths
and basically it would just mean
that there was like roads everywhere.
Like the whole country would just be walkable.
So that would be fucking awesome
because I imagine like walking across country
would be fun if it weren't for the prospect of like
I have to either walk on the highway
or fucking navigate.
Nah man just everything's a road.
And there's beautiful scenic nature around you.
And then there's still
just one thing in nature.
I want this to be like 95% of nature.
What we're describing is just roads everywhere
and like little turnways you can go.
And also there should be danger zones.
Like killing me fuck you Jones.
Like for the high ranking adventurers
there would still be caves set off
if you want to die.
You want the world to be structured like an MMO.
Literally that's literally what I want.
I want there to be like high ranking zones
for if you get like a license if you apply at the DMV
you can get like a good boy haha rank
and you can go inside these devilish caves.
Those will kill you.
And touching on something I think is important.
I mean I like this idea for improving nature
but I think the single biggest thing
that nature is currently lacking is drops.
Like there just aren't that many drops in nature.
Well you know the problem is that nature
actually has quite a few drops
but they're very difficult to find.
They don't have enough, they haven't like
the designers did not put enough like
shimmy shines on them so they stand out
in the environment.
I don't think that nature was very well created
because the skinner box loop is not that effective
because the drops are so few and far between
and they don't come randomly.
They've all been collected at this point.
What is gold other than nature drops
and they've all been collected
and it's gone.
But when was the last time you got a gold drop?
I personally have never got one.
Look what we're, the problem is right now
is we're just waiting for this zone
this planet to reset
and that's when the next asteroid's going to hit
everything's going to reset.
Yeah, well in the current medicaid
in the current medicaid the drops are just
the drop rate is just so low that I just don't
feel engaged with the system.
It depends where you're grinding though.
Like if you go to like an apple orchard
in the autumn then
heck yeah.
I think it says
Is that someone building like a farm
on their land?
It's literally a farm.
It's more like harvest materials.
Yeah but I mean
you can get tons of drops there but you have to
build the farm.
You can't just wander through a random
forest and get tons of apple
You can get berries.
Yeah blueberries and
you can get mushrooms and stuff.
You know these are all good points.
I just want to say
by the way that I've got one of the best
rare drops of all time.
I'm just saying is my elated Arab
gentleman who just
literally sprung from nature.
That's a legendary drop.
Oh okay okay did you
I wanted to say that story immediately
but instead of immediately afternate
please say that story.
You know what I'm going to launch you the whole thing so you should just go first.
Oh okay okay did you.
I remember the first time you told me this story
I was in a fucking Skype call with your ex-girlfriend
and it was the most
it made me elated.
It was the most ingenious and incredible thing I've ever heard in my fucking life.
It was a story arc and I still have
the file of the image you sent me
ladies and gentlemen.
Call the video games are dead on my computer right now.
I still have it.
Well since I was trying to remember
where I had told this story before
it was only in a patron exclusive podcast
so I guess I could tell it here.
So it's a simple story
one day I was
at some function
my mom had to go to the school and I went with her
I had to walk home basically it was like a long walk
like a two hour walk
and I was just like fucking I want to walk
and walk and home
and I'm on the side of the road
in the middle of an area where
it's just forest on the side of the road
like a 45 mile an hour road in forest
and on the side of the road is this
giant cardboard cut out
of what can only be described as
an elated Arab gentleman holding a cell phone
looking like the most
most relieved.
Yeah a flip phone and he's got like the most
relieved face in the whole world
he looks like he just finally got reception
but he's like literally wearing
like a turban and shit
so I just find this cardboard cut out
and it's only the top half of his body
just sitting on the side of the road
and there's no possible
building it could have come from nearby
like it wasn't close enough to anything
so it had to have come out of the back
of someone's car or something
or just been thrown there
but I don't know the source because there's no
labels on it
I assume it's from like a sprint store
it's a sprint on his phone
but I mean yeah
I just picked it up and I took it home with me
and nailed it to my wall
and that's now one of my most prized presentations
That's incredible
You can click on the link in the show notes
to see the image
we're talking about TV
oh boy
Nate please I beg of you
we are at your will and we have bent our knee
please
here's what I wanted to talk about
I just want to say be right back
someone's like knocking on my fucking window
alright kill that gremlin
I've never heard me say fuck
that's nice
I wanted to bring up
I recently saw a video by a guy I quite like
on YouTube it's one of my ASMR boys
this guy named Ephemeral Rift
and just listen to the name of this video
ok here's what it is
we belong in nature
in parenthesis civilization
is cancer
that is the full name of this video
I hate this guy already
listen he's very woke
on a lot of issues but he is an absolute
seems super woke
he's incredibly woke
he is
he is like the biggest
and narcos communist that I've like ever encountered
in my travels
and it is very unfortunate
ok so this whole video
you can go watch and ok you will see this video
if you go search his channel we belong in nature civilization is cancer
it will be in the show notes
there will definitely be a link in the show notes
I have a gigantic comment that I left
on this video
under best guy ever
you'll be able to see it there
so he basically talks for
extended period of time
it's like an hour and a half long
and that's fine
of why
human civilization has gone too far
and we have strayed away from like
what he might be totally right about
look we right now
are all like lonely people
we're too capitalist
everyone cares about that
we can all agree with that name
we're all too capitalist
there are issues here
but basically his point is we should
literally all be living in nature
we should be living in like small tribes
the way that we did originally
and it is his idea that we should
really go back there
and he's woke man he accepts the fact
that there are problems with that
it's not going to be easy
but he thinks that is the best way to go
and of course in my comment
I point out
what seems to me like blisteringly obvious facts
like okay well
before we had like civilization
a lot of people died from diseases that we now have
curious for
so what about all that
do you want like all these pregnant women
to just die in childbirth
because you know
civilization he's talking about would be great
for like jaded guys like him
who are really fed up with their nine to five
jobs and this guy's a very successful youtuber
he's too fed up with being way too
wait wait wait wait wait wait
Nate I need to interject here
because I have no idea what this ephemeral rift is
let me show you a screencap from the video
but go on
so he's a successful youtuber
he possibly makes his living off youtube
and his solution is to get rid of
all civilization
in a cave and like
the entire way that he's
being able to broadcast this message
he's spiting
this guy looks like ben sates cartoon
avatar of himself but with a beard
let me see this
literally
oh my god
ben gets old this will just be ben
it kinda does
I am interested
on ephemeral rift
I am in no way trying to shit on this guy
he just looks like ben saint
with a grey beard
this will also be in the show
it's better than mine
I just want to make it clear to the audience
I think I'm changing my mind
I think I'm going over to this guy's side
I think me and him are just gonna go live in a hut somewhere
I literally like ephemeral rift a lot
nobody go bully him
or say shit to him
but politely disagree if you do so
after watching the video
don't even just take my word for it
but it's an hour and a half long
this guy's sentiment
so many people put this idea
of nature
and old human civilization
on such a pedestal
exactly and to me it is
clearly because guys like this
I've watched this guy for years
I know his full backstory
he had to work a shitty 9-5
to get himself to a place where he could support
his wife and kid
he's pretty depressed
he sees all the flaws
in modern civilization
he's very woke on all those issues
but what he's not focusing on enough
in my humble opinion
is the way that millions of people died
in extremely preventable ways
in the olden days
and I do not think we're necessarily better off
just throwing away all the modern advancements
that's what I'm saying the nature metagame is broken
we had to update it
people are so obsessed
with the aesthetic
and the romanticization of nature
and it's like oh modern society
has all these problems we need to go back
that's the equivalent of saying
modern society has all these problems
we need to magnify them exponentially
literal romanticism
it's disgusting
we need to go forward further
we're in an incompleteness
my guys are not maturely looking
at how to deal with these issues
I think we can all agree
I don't think we all need to fight
hard on the side of civilization
should exist
opinion is rather extreme
but the guys like this are more
rampant than I'm comfortable with
they are more out there
you're more rampant than I'm comfortable with
I don't think we need to
throw the baby out with the bath water
and be like oh fuck nature
just because we favor civilization
but I'm not saying that
I'm just saying that these kind of hyperbolic
extreme nature worshipers
that's not the solution either
it's not where we should be going
my understanding is
if you want to say
human civilization was a misstep
retarded but okay you can say that
if you want to propose that we go
back to nature
after having cultivated these cities
if you want to be like
practical and then say go back to nature now
that is probably the most stupid
fucking idea I've ever heard besides
being a porn manga artist in under a month
that
the population is way down
I never said anything like that
the population is way too high
and I don't want to be one of those guys
but we've done things to this planet
that we can't really come back
from it would be weird to go back
you know what the thing is dude
and try and be tribes again
I don't believe
that this guy actually believes this
I think he's trying to put on airs
while complaining because there's nothing
stopping anybody from just going and living
in nature you can just drop off the face
of the planet people do that
if you want to go just go do it
just go take your family and do it but he's like
no man that's these fucking commies man
they want like they need
everyone to do their shit or it's a fucking
problem no one's stopping you motherfucker
just go do it stop trying to drag
everybody else down with you oh my god it
fucking pisses me off and I disagree
with literally none of the complaints that he makes
in his video I agree with 100%
of them but the his proposed solution
is retarded is completely retarded
agreed well I I want to almost as retarded
as nature itself I want to get
on to talking about nature in a positive
way because I'm looking at the background
of this guy's video I like nature
and you know did you you're the problem
you're romanticizing aesthetic that
looks pretty aesthetic is everything
if you if nature is good because
it has a good aesthetic nature is great because it is because it's like
I know it's like you can see it can be like
I'm not saying nature's good you're saying aesthetics
are good and I agree but actually
being there is awful
looking at it great
being there is shit
I think the aesthetic of nature is felt 10
times stronger by being like
especially of a forest like this like
this shit when you see these in images
they all look exactly the same because every forest
is the same shit especially if you're in a forest
that's like in town it's probably
what I refer to as a septic forest
where it's basically
just a small creek that is where all
of the fucking septic tanks empty
out and then like
just a bunch of fucking trees
you know for and like a narrow probably
a narrow strip like you can't ever get deep enough
to not hear cars but that's like
most of the forest in like suburban
America and I use the high level
mob spawn because the excess of toxicity
you know yeah I used to explore
those forests all the time when I was a kid
and just like play with sticks and fucking
you know pretend they were samurai
swords and cut trees
fun times you know
back before iPhones that's what
you had to do I never
had an iPhone but
the forests were
like you know I would just go
exploring with my friends and that was some of
my like most memorable times because
I grew up real sheltered and like exploring
a forest was like whoa I'm on it
fucking I'm doing something away from
home I'm fucking getting out
but you know
it's like 5 feet away
it doesn't make you puke, it doesn't make you fucking cough and gag
wherever you stand you can go out there
you can fucking breathe, you can see green
occasionally you'll come across like some like creepy bug
you'll be like ew and then you'll touch it and poke it a lot
dude I mean the first time I ever went out
to the mountains and like stayed in a log cabin
out in the mountains and
heard nothing because it's just
quiet and you're just like what the fuck this is
it didn't even feel like the same earth
like I didn't know that like
reality was supposed to be quieter
nature can be very enjoyable
have you guys spent a lot of time camping
because in my youth
yeah it's miserable
I actually love camping
it's just kind of a big work
I want to get through my
forest aesthetics thing because here's how I
enjoy the forest camp
I got into exploring as a kid just because it's fun
but later I got into black metal
and like atmosphere
the same thing really
well almost all black metal is like about
how beautiful nature is
and destroying human society
and organized religion in particular
and like paganism
and shit so like
if you listen to like Agiloch all their fucking songs
are just like about fuck
like one of their songs probably the most famous
which is called
in the shadow of our pale companion
is a song
that is just about a guy wandering
in the forest having an existential crisis
and like so if you're ever wandering
and you put on this 14 minute Agiloch song
while you walk around it's like the most
aesthetic experience you can have
in your hometown
is this pale companion white privilege
that you need to smash
I think it's God
well same difference I guess
I've actually
listened to
I've listened to another album about
like fucking angry white men from
Seattle getting angry and putting on silly
voices talking about how cool nature is
that I also did like by Kithkin
rituals, trances and exesies for humans
in the face of claps that look that up right now
actually click on the link of that that was good
and I liked that that was also
fucking twinks from Seattle doing funny voices
Agiloch from Portland thank you very much
so
literally this name one difference
between Seattle, Washington and Portland more again
Portland is weird
so is Seattle
amount of homeless people
that is true
if I have the floor for a couple minutes
here I would like to talk
about my sixth grade camp
because my sixth grade camp
was the worst week of my entire
fucking life
I'm just going to explain what sixth grade camp is
for the people who don't know maybe live in shit
countries like America
or you know bridge
like that disgusting
so okay sixth grade camp is you enter sixth grade
and then you go on a camping trip somewhere around
the beginning of your year to
accomplish nothing really it's just fun
I guess so I come there
and the entire like week before
I'm dragging it because you know I'm a
role player on the internet and I don't have time for
things like trees or bees or any sort of
bullshit like that I don't want to leave
my precious laptop and all my malware
written fucking like at least
web browsers I don't want to do that
but I'm forced I'm forced to
I'm forced to so I have to go
I get on the bus we go there and we're in the middle
of fucking nowhere
and it's all fucking scary and and all
we do besides
sitting cafeterias where there's like no electricity
it's all fucking bull you know electricity
that I can use that there's it's all
horrible food it makes me fucking
sad and what we do day and
day fucking out is we hike
we hike through fucking treacherous
mountains if they're dangerous
fucking you know pathways
I see I see like a bear at one point
I see I see what are the dog looking things
I see one of the dog looking things
cats that's where they are big cats
yeah and it's fucking
terrifying but but I came
to an epiphany of why I was there
I looked around and like you know because
I was a fat kid I was always behind and I was
lagging behind I needed more water than the rest of the people
so I was drinking and sweating so but
I came to realization that that
around me was
pretty I liked it
but I just needed roads
I needed civilization
to assist me
in observing nature
I liked being out in the hot
blistering Arabian Californian
sun I like that but I wanted to do it on my own
terms and as a human
my own terms was destroying
all of the genuine sincerity of it
and making it like an amusement park I needed
concession stands I needed
roads I needed fucking torches I need
tour guides if I had that
then this would be great if I
didn't have to like use my legs
well not as a not walking
if I didn't have to like jump up and like
fucking cross ravines and fucking you know
jump as far as I fucking could
then that would be great if I could just walk
places it would be perfect so
like I like nature I
like seeing the dog things
I like seeing trees I like to be able to look
up mountains and be like wow that's a mountain
but I don't like being in
danger and being scared the
worst thing in fucking sixth grade camp was
like the second to last night where like we had
to like walk in the dark we didn't
we didn't hike this time we like we like
walked to a nearby museum
but this nearby museum was like like through
a bean off road
path and by road I just mean like
there's slightly a section of
this like grassland that does not have grass
on it it is just dirt it's not
an actual road it's just you know dirt
and the tour guide
we had like a guy you know we were all babies
but he didn't do anything he was just like yeah there are like
snakes around here so if you see a snake well
bye and it was
terrified because it was in the dead of night
and you walk for like a fucking mile to get this
stupid museum and just look at dead things
I hate dead things I want to be alive
and that's why I hate dangerous things and that's why I hate nature
I mean you live in California
and there's a bear just on the flag
of California like
bears are real and they're just in the
woods they're out there they are
out there yeah like
they just are ready to kill yeah they'll just
come to you and murder you it happens
it happens that's not that's the state
of nature and it's awful and should be
abolished but if we had roads
and torches and guns
nature would have to
bend to us yeah
I don't and that's my proposal look
no no no you I think people have a lot of
human guilt and so they feel like
oh no I'm oppressing these bears uh
fuck them kill them don't care they can
die look this is what we need to understand
about nature do you remember like a few days
ago that that did you see that the
story that was going around on Twitter of
the lady who kept pulling worms out of her
eyes yeah
there was this lady who had to end up going
to the hospital because she kept pulling she felt
something wriggling around in her
eye and and she
could see it so she got
it oh and she pulled out of
your stories like that worms out
of her eyes and
they had they had to surgically remove like
12 of them from inside of her
eye and the reason it was so
fucking terrifying is because there was a parasite
that does this that before this
case we thought didn't
affect humans
oh that someone said had
some intersex of her
that is nature okay
fucking
and her name was wife of undertale
yes exactly
so so so this is what
nature is nature is like
you know fucking like arachnids that
that capture things and then like
inject them with like
like fucking poison that melts their organs
from the inside out and they drink them up
this is nature
nature is fucking tornadoes
isn't that kind of cool
for a moment while we're on this topic
because I don't want to I don't want to
trail off from this topic and then be
and relevant and here on this
topic so there's also like
these maggot things that eat rotten
flesh but they're used
medicinally so that to save people's
like limbs and stuff to
like because
they're put on on the rotten flesh to
eat it away and they do it so cleanly
that you don't have to like hack off the whole limb
you just you just get rid of the rotten
flesh and stuff so in that sense
those sort of things help
and leeches to help in the
back in the days and I think there's still
parts of the world where they still use leeches
medicinally and stuff
nature has things about it that are useful
and and and that I wouldn't
say that we shouldn't throw the baby out with the
bathwater but it just
it's not reaching its full potential on its own
it's just so much of a waste
also garlic is like the universal
of antibiotic
I thought you were going to say anti-vampire
and I was just like
you got me there mage
I want to start up a debate
with all of you about
the word nature and more specifically
the word natural
I want to know where you draw the line
between what is natural and what is unnatural
because
when we talk about like natural foods for instance
like they always advertise themselves
like oh this is natural
which means that whatever is not this
is not natural but like
what is added to the so called
unnatural version it's like it could just be
pesticides or like
you know something something else so
they even
even if you get a non GMO
apple which GMOs
like into that bullshit but even if you like
you know a pure apple untouched
if you get them today
in the year 2018
that is not a natural
apple that is a man made
construction even in its
most basic form we have domesticated
apples and pigs and stuff so even if you like
get a pig and be like I want to roll around the dirt
with a fucking pig that's not natural
people don't do that stop so you'll contraire
my friend I'm just curious would you say
you lean
more towards less things should be
considered natural or more things should be
considered natural because for me
I feel like I feel like
you know people talk about for instance
plastics and they're like
oh that's man made
and I'm like well no it comes from a plant
like plastic is originally
I think when people use natural
obviously know that
when people use natural in that sense
they're saying things that don't naturally like
things that don't occur without
having to be produced in some way
by man
let me say about plastics
things about plastics though
like if you put them on the ground
they don't go away
and they hurt the environment so it's not natural
in that sense like something
it can't reproduce
it can't continue without humans
but yeah kind I guess
but also like
you have to be careful about
what you throw away because you might think
oh banana peel is natural and you throw it away
oh you know it's not going to do anything
but that's the thing if you throw it away on
ground that doesn't naturally grow
bananas and stuff like you know
I don't know in America certain parts of America
you can't grow bananas
it's not really good for the environment because
the thing doesn't naturally
occur there so it's not natural for a banana peel
to just appear there so it's hurting
the environment as well
not as much as plastic though but
you have to be careful about those things
I mean life finds a way
you know plants will just
plants will grow and plants would grow
in just fields
just littered with plastic shrapnel
that was the only choice we've spoiled them
we've spoiled them
we made them soft
there's already some sort of bacteria
or something that does and I was reading another story
about like intranobal there's like fungus that
like break down radioactive material
see they're like intranobal though
I think the problem is the reason
the earth hasn't like adapted to our trash yet
is we haven't given it enough
like we got to train the earth
we got to dump as much trash
everywhere so that all the plants can learn how to
take care of it
I'm playing the long game
I feel like only weeds would survive
at that point
how long have plastics even existed
like maybe 200 years in the entire
lifetime of the planet earth
real quick question
real quick nature question for you guys
what is wrong with weeds
why are they worse than not
weeds
it's just because they're not what we want
they're hoggers for the most part
yeah they strangle like the growth of other crops
and also it's just an aesthetic problem
because they look different from the grass
because like all plant like all life
strangles out and chokes out other life
in order to eke out its own existence
what makes a thing a weed is
that's nature itself
that's the position you people are arguing for
strangling out all around you
is it that weeds have
really aggressive genes
like weeds will overpopulate
an area and turn it
into not good plants anymore
yeah that's the thing like weeds
most of the time they're not useful
for humans and they also
they're very aggressive and they kill
other plants so they can repopulate
so they're very invasive
and stuff though on that point
dandelions can be useful in many ways
and I don't think they should be considered
weeds necessarily though they are a bit aggressive
according to Wikipedia
a weed is just a plant considered
undesirable in a particular situation
there we go there we go that's what I'm saying
I googled
invention of plastics to try and get
like the date of when plastics were invented
and the first google result is
invention of plastics by man is a crime
alright I have a very
whoa I have a very important
suggestion which is that
we all adopt weeds
as a new racial slur
and it just applies
no it applies to all
races it's just
whoever you don't want in the room at the moment
is the weeds
they gotta pull the weeds out of this room
makes perfect sense
I fucking like that
I might cop a feel on that
I don't really know about
the word weed for something else though
there's too many meanings for weed now
well the great thing about
using weed is that you don't have to use
any specific racial slur because it'll be
understood like let's say you're in a room
with your friend you're at a party
there's a couple of Jews at your party
and you want to tell your friend
that we need to get rid of the Jews
but you don't want the people around you to know
what race of people you think needs to be
removed from the party so you just say
we need to pull the weeds and your friend
who is also an anti-semite
will know exactly what you're talking about
or they can all assume that you mean
like it's time to pull out some weed
and smoke it because
no no you would never say weeds
with an S if you were talking about smoking weed
well maybe they're
stupid no one refers to a plural
of weed it could also be used
for not racist attributes as well
it could also be used for that if you wanted to
it could be like you know if you're
in the room with some fucking black person
oh damn it
never mind
it's a lost cause
I mean what's important about the term weed
is that it is complete well like
it's like George Carlin said
people say like the earth is dying
like ah the earth is dying but no
the earth is just an inanimate object
full of life and what we really mean
when we say that is we are making our environment
uninhabitable for ourselves
the planet's gonna be fine
the people are fucked
it's just a hot rock
indeed indeed it's dumb when people
like the earth cries out in pain no
like it's this thing about I hate how people
like make it all about something else
when they're actually talking selfishly
like I'm 100% willing to admit
I only care about the earth
in context of like human civilization
and my own you know environment
around me and the environment of people who I care about
a little bit that's what matters
that's what matters I don't care if like
in 10 billion years
we have all ported our civilization
to Mars and the earth just explodes
like well that's a shame that's too bad
but I don't actually care at all
I would be upset
if the earth just spontaneously
was like gone and you know
we were alive elsewhere on Mars
I mean it would be a bummer but I get over it
but the point is that's not the most important thing
I wouldn't be dead
the important thing is humans being alive
that's what actually matters and furthering civilization
etc etc
that's what actually matters
that's why ephemeral rift is a very silly boy
I can see him hiding in the
the Martian bushes
out in the nowhere in a Martian loincloth
having a good time
hey Nate, Tom, you people I know this
like is there a way
to make Mars green is that like a thing
that can happen or will it always be the way it is
I mean
we don't know how to do it
but we want to
but literally like could there be a way
you'd have to introduce like
different gases into the atmosphere
and do a bunch of other stuff
guys, guys
speaking about planets, have you heard about a planet that like
it can sort of be inhabitable
by human life but only like on a
various sliver sort of of it
because it doesn't rotate so one side is too hot
the other is too cold
and there's like one slip
that's just perfect but it's in constant
like twilight so like
I think that the like it looks
kind of like hell because
awesome, Star Wars
that's so cool
that's my home planet
the hot ease and the cold ease
on the opposite sides of the planet
that's exactly what I was going to say
because there would be people who would go on the dark side
of that planet no matter what
so there would totally be a class divide
because you know they would ship all of their fucking
groveling street urges to the dark side
and be like a fucking darky just came to life
like you know what we going to fucking dark us down here
get these fucking weeds out of here
yeah exactly
that would be great
we've brushed up upon and what
will now be the big thing we argue about
is environmentalism
and the planet and global warming
and Al Gore did he invent the internet
yes or no
probably yes
who else would be smart enough to invent the internet
I don't know anybody
so what
what level of
commitment and responsibility
do humans have
to take care of the planet
do we have any responsibility
or is it just all like we should do this for our own sake
or do we have
do we have anything to give back to the planet
is there any sort of moral
or virtuous argument that can be made
we should take care of the bone
like why
I mean I like earth
it's good if we have to live here
forever we should take care of it
but like
this is gonna die one way or another
like everything else
fuck it
yeah
tossing the garbage
I think it's very important
we're not gonna be ported to Mars
our whole civilization for a very long time
if we make that shit happen
so I would say it's pretty important
that we take care of the earth
I'm actually pretty pro environmentalism
but at the same time you have to consider
it is true that you don't want your
completely crush your
economic development
who here will always walk all the way
to the trash can to throw something away
me
I always do
I pocket my trash and I wait
until I find a trash can
you mean as opposed to just throwing it on the ground
I mean I just leave it all over my desk
it makes its way to the trash
eventually
I think you were talking about making sweet long range dunks
of my trash
I'm totally doing that
I'm saying when you're out
if you're out somewhere and you've got trash
and there's not a trash can anywhere around
well you carry that shit around until you find a trash can
yeah absolutely
anyone who doesn't is a fucking asshole
okay so everyone in here is a real good boy
what about cigarette butts
would you throw the I mean I don't know if anybody
um
you even have to consider that cigarette butts don't count in the same category
already makes you a bad person right off the bat
I'm just asking
I'm just asking how all of you feel
Nate or Ben would you toss a cigarette butt on the ground
I would toss a cigarette butt like on a sidewalk
I would toss it
in like an urban area
at least stomp on it because I
there's nothing more than I hate
I just hate it
when people throw down like lit cigarettes
on the ground
and they almost stomp it out
fire on the sidewalk
you degenerate piece of shit smokers
you should all fucking die
for any of you
straight edge boys
straight edge brothers
I hate the fact that
I deserve to just throw my fucking cigarette butts on the ground
like a fucking asshole
I have a special license to that
it's okay if I live here because it's kind of small
I'm saying in like urban areas
those streets get swept
there are sweet streepers that sweep up detritus on the streets
so why not just throw it on the street
if I'm a vapor
I can just smash it on the fucking ground
and I can just go and walk away
like that's fine
yeah it's gonna get swept up
who gives a shit
because we're making the world worse
I'm not because the street sweepers are coming
whether I do that or not
but in the meantime
people are gonna step on these fucking butts
and be like ew gross
who the fuck would even notice
who
me every day
I walk and I see
literally littering and it's not okay
dirt is purely aesthetic
it's not even real
I look for people who wouldn't litter
I hate seeing litter all over
like fucking
just like just carry it a little bit
or just throw it into a bin
I hate litter so much
it's funny because
the reason I asked that question about the cigarette butts
is that I will always
go out of my way to throw a cigarette butt in a trash can
unless there isn't a trash can
but I am not carrying it around
because that shit will make my pockets stink
and it gives a little fucking
that is your problem
that would be my suggestion
I don't smoke anymore anyway
have a little plastic bag ready in your pocket
you don't smoke that particular drug
no I don't smoke tobacco cigarettes anymore
did you
just have a little plastic bag ready in your pocket
for cigarette butts
that's like a huge
ask
god what up
heaven forbid
I take responsibility to my own hands
and forge my life
to be this way
one second ago I was like
fuck the earth and you were all like
okay and now I was like
there's cigarette butts on the ground when I can't find a trash can
and everyone's like oh Hitler
like
you guys are fucking full of shit
I'm 100% consistent the earth has no long term significance
but while it's our environment
it matters incredibly so
this is our shit let's not fuck it up
a cigarette butt on the sidewalk
is not like detrimental to the earth
and the problem is that
if you say you don't vote
and everyone says they don't vote
then no one votes
exactly I mean that's the same yeah
I don't care
you got down to the obvious bin
I think they're aesthetically pleasing
what you gonna do now
I
I will okay okay bin
you are wrong but I will
say that I do
like this is a vice
of mine but even though
this is like a porn fantasy
this is like a degradation fantasy
I like dirty cities
they're pretty pleasing to look at
if I see like a city
a grungy looking city in a cartoon
or a video game
yeah I'll be like
yeah
if you were open like some steam coming out
and I slip on a puddle of dirty fucking
muckin' cum then I'll be like
yes this is what I live for
I like to see the smokes here inside
I wanna see smoke fucking fill the skies
I wanna be there no cloud
I wanna be in factories everywhere
here's a good rule of thumb to operate yourself by
in these urban environments
if with whatever you're doing
if Rorschach walked by and saw you doing
what you're thinking of doing
would he beat you to death
don't do it and that's exactly what
using Rorschach as your moral compass
yes
think about that for a second
yeah that's right
he did nothing wrong
okay good
are you talking shit on Rorschach right now
he's a fucking psycho dude
he's a fucking psycho murderer
it's true he was
he was the best guy
the best guy
another vice of mine
sometimes
I'll say I want a amusement parkification
I want all that by the way
hashtag a amusement parkification for nature
occasionally
I'll still be like
oh I'll read a creepy posse
and there'll be an evil clown man in the forest
and I'll be like why don't we just get rid of forest
why don't we just like have
we don't just make oxygen
then go to the sewers my chief
that's right
but if we just make
tanks of oxygen
and just like make them respawn a lot somehow
there would be no creepypasta
why don't we just have
no where to go
those clowns will move to the sewers
duh
now they're closer to me
I'm fucked up
we already have co2 spawners they're called trees
we might as well just use them
we need forests so we can exile freaks
like where are we gonna send them
what if we could have
what if we had
natural
concentration camps but they were in the forest
and instead of killing them we could just be like
okay go back to nature now
are you a tribe now
are you in reservations or something
oh here's a suggestion
install lights in the forest so it's not dark and creepy
that's a good idea
I have no problem with that
but look manchi we need
I want string lights just on all the trees in America
I want Christmas lights
to line the top of forests
I want Christmas lights in jungles
here's how we're gonna put them up
we're just gonna have
a bunch of fucking kids with string lights
just run around the forest
run between trees
so we can get lights on them
and get rid of kids at the same time
two problems solved at the same time
I like it
here's what we go we get the unitesates air force
to get a giant net full of Christmas trees
and just air raid forests
and just jump a fucking ton of lights
over the top of them
we want to utilize the native population
I've got a two word solution for this
t-shirt cannons
that's how we do it
that's how we modernize t-shirt cannons
that's how we're gonna get them
good
okay okay okay
I love nature
and I like it
there we go that was my point
well this podcast is winding down
I think
I wanted to tell
a story about trees but it's kind of
boring after all that discussion
can you compress it into two sentences
no
well I try
because I really
love nature and especially love trees
when I was a little kid I loved trees so much
that if I accidentally
broke a branch or took
some leaves from it I would out loud
say I'm sorry tree and I would
give it a hug and I would make my friends
do it and they would do it
at least around me
oh I feel so sad
whenever I step on a snail
oh fuck any of you
I once felt guilty for
like a week because I had
a snail and I
went on a bus and I was holding the snail
and it fell out of my hands and then
I actually raised
my hands as pets but that's beside the point
at this point in time of the story
it fell out of my hands
and some guy stepped on the snail
and I felt so bad because
like if I hadn't brought that snail with me
it would still be alive and I just I just cried
I was a little kid and I cried
you're often out of mage with snails I want that
I love snails
I had them as pets and like
I fed them a little bit of carrot and they
freaking loved the carrot and it was really cute
wait how big
snails you have
small, very small, they're garden snails basically
how they can eat carrots
well yeah they
normal a little bit it was adorable
they just a little crazy
did you ever race them
did you ever race the snails
race?
yeah race you know
when I was a kid yeah that's what we used to do
with other kids
we would pick our snails and we had little snail races
just like an undertale
was there a big snail
culture with the lady
and every kid
have their own decked out
personalized snail
you would put them in the arena
the snails
they came in very many
different colors and stuff so
my favorites were the pink ones
they still are
snails are way more diverse
where you come from
snail shells
oh the shells
okay
around Boston there were some really
sweet spiral shell snails
crawling around people's gardens and stuff
around here in Georgia all we got are slugs
and I hate them
they're really boring as well as being gross
they're just long and thin
they look like worms but they don't move
speaking of worms I also had worms as pets at some point
I really like nature
this is a good said way
this is not extremely topic
viewers this is a real thing I wanted you to do
this was it out of my note
I have a big thing I want to say animals
animals in nature
I love
about grasshoppers
another thing I used to do in my youth
I'm not sure if they're called crickets or grasshoppers
they were tiny the small ones
the small colorful ones
grasshoppers
crickets are black
so there used to be this
small field by my neighborhood
somewhere and it had like super
tall grass like Pokemon tall grass
and I would sometimes
go there during the evenings when I had nothing to do
during the summer and there were like
grasshoppers and stuff and I would capture them
but you know like I wouldn't like
capture them with both of my hands
what I would do I would like bend
lean over extend
my finger to the grasshopper and usually
it would like hop away but after like two or
three times the grasshopper would just climb
onto my finger on its own
and I'd be like hello little friend and then
I would stare at it and it just had fun with it
and once I'm done I would like
let it hop away and that was fun
fucking rip off its limbs one by one
yeah
so you feel powerful for what's in your life
I was
I once felt like a grasshopper that was like
black and red and was fucking energy and I
loved it and I needed it
sadly later on I learned that
they only lived through in the summer and I was really
sad the next year I was like I miss my friend
I wish I had
a fucking edgy grasshopper
I wish I had like an edgy buggy that was my companion
I would take him on adventures that's
you lived far more than I have
there isn't that is there that's too bad
there should be an edgy bug in pokemon
uh saizor
that's kind of edgy not edgy enough though
he's a good um
I love edgy things edgy things are the only thing I
fucking live for that's why I like the trolls
and homesick so they're fucking edgy and stupid
and they're violent and I like it
people steal bugs
ok hold on pokemon not real
here's what are real animals
I take edgy I take
umbraze with your hatred of animals animals
are fucking great they are incredible
they are a net positive 100% time
bugs don't count cause fuck bugs but
but big animals real big
mammals and fish and shit I fucking
love you know why
because they're always terrifying
there is not a single animal
that does not make me shit myself
I walked around and said I see you all fucking
dead I was gonna say you can see a bear
slightly less scared but still extremely
scared animals are fucking
a beast of the land they are beast
and they are terrifying and the
and animals come like like animals
are like humans are
animals we come from this land of
beasts and disgusting awful
scary like like cthulhu
type monsters that are snails
and dogs we come
from that barbaric age and we have
conquered we animals have
conquered and we come civilized
and cultured and incredible and now
we now we control the
beast of the land now we control the
the weird awful
archaic beast
of the land and we are the masters of society
we have done it we have conquered
animals and that's what the beast of the land is
whenever I walk out and see a snail I think wow we have done it
humans have gone so far we've
escaped the clutches of nature and we have done
it I hate animals
we uh you know it's fair to
it's fair to remember it's fair to remember
that uh we have no
formalized contract people don't like animals
so animals are great
we have no contract with the animals and we
can take them or leave them
oh my god shut the fuck up everyone
big memberless are good but
shut up you need to get closer to your microphone
you're not like quite overpoweringly
loud am I am I
am I cursing the microphone now
can you hear what I'm saying right now
stop stop stop
we have made no accord with the beast of the
field and so it's easy to just forget
that they could just murder us at any time
they do not respect us like because we are on
dogs so much dogs have been bred to be like
weak cowards but like uh you know
not the fucking a pigeon
pigeon could just fucking claw your eyes out one
actually it doesn't give a shit
Nate it's interesting you mentioned dogs because I was
reading about dogs and apparently there's like the
reason we were able to domesticate dogs is
like uh like mental condition
or like genetic disposition
neoteny that makes you like be friends
with everybody and like people can get that too
but like that's the thing we bred
in dogs that's why dogs are so friendlies
because we gave them all like mental condition
what I heard was that we continually
bred like so neoteny
is the trait that is like when you display
like baby like traits and so like
dogs propensity for like cuddling
and just like being friends with everybody
very much comes from when they're babies
and they just like don't know any better and so
like with with dog breeding we just continually
bred like the friendliest of the friendliest
dogs to like just make them the most
you know you know domesticated and so they just
did that forever and now just like all the dogs
all the you know domestic dogs just like
great it is like
dogs I don't like the only
dog I've had excellent prolonged experience
with was one of my
ex-girlfriend's dogs that just shit on the floor
constantly and I wanted to kill it
well that's the word that's not
it's your owners
before we go
out of dog hole I just want to say
I'm going down the dog hole
if you plan for pigeons
is hepto-bismol I think
doesn't that make their stomachs explode
I had pigeons
please do not talk about this
how do you get the pepto-bismol in their stomachs though
I've heard that when people throw rice at weddings
that birds eat the rice
when their stomach can kill them
I'm thinking of seagulls that if you give them pepto-bismol
they'll like explode
I still don't know how you get it
rats are like that like if rats drink soda it can kill them
because they can't burp
no animal cruelty please no
no one's actually doing this
these are just contingencies for if a pigeon comes
at my fucking eyes like Nate was saying
I have ways to be a pigeon
if a pigeon ever puts me in a self-defense
situation you know
I will defend myself
I will legally defend myself
I'm not saying that
like animals are pacified
that's what I like about animals is that they're not pacified
and they're fucking dangerous and violent
but we as humans have the tools
and knowledge to like
if a pigeon just like I was just walking down the street
a pigeon could like get a claw in
but I have a big fist
and also I could have a gun if I wanted to
I could carry like a spear or something
the problem is that we let our defenses down
and they could theoretically clawed an eye
our stupid good boys they would not hurt you
okay maybe like a hawk
I'm sure they wouldn't
I'm just saying animals are dangerous
and again they are beasts
that's what I like about animals is that they are beasts
they're modern monsters
contingency plan number two
you gotta hawk
get a glock
you know what I'm saying
okay guys
listen like animals aren't
unpredictable forces of nature or anything
they usually give signs of their aggressive
or they're gonna attack or something
just like a boss
in Dark Souls
so you're not gonna
get surprised by an animal
you just have to watch for signs
my biggest criticisms of animals
is that they have too long of wind ups
before their attacks
it makes fighting them boring and uninteresting
it's not good
they need to work on that
I'm not saying the animals will attack me
I'm just saying that we have the power to do that
and that makes me feel
more confident
touching animals
I know that I could kill them if I wanted to
I don't want to
real question
if you were attacked by a vicious
do you think you could beat it
do you think you'd live
I think it would be really hard
but when humans
if you're a cornered human
you can kill most things
they have that badge and paper Mario
where if you get below 5 health
your attack expands
that's what all humans have intrinsically
you can do crazy shit when you're about to die
I've often wondered if a pitbull
bit me on the arm or something
all I could do is try to punch it in the eye
or maybe gouge out its eyes or something
I wonder how effective that would be
I feel like if the dog was even a bit smaller
than you that you could probably beat it
unless it got the drop on you
and tore your throat out or something
it still supports behind me
I feel like they're all under
underestimating the dog
I feel like there's a chance
it's gonna just fucking take your arm off
if it bites your arm
but I also feel like if you punch it in the face
enough times you could knock it out
that's the question
you'll probably lose that arm though
I definitely think the bigger
dog gets obviously the less your chances are
but like a pitbull, it's dangerous
I think we'll both be at low HP
by the end of it
but I think any human could overrun
unless like a baby
there was a pitbull that started attacking kids
in my old neighborhood
cause they're kids
wait, the story's not over yet
and it became
like this legend among the cops
the cops had to come out and fucking
put it down
and they shot at the dog
and the bullets bounced off its skull
what the fuck
yeah dude
should they take it down or what
they eventually got, but you shoot at other places
it's not as like
they had to call in fucking cloud strife to do omnislash
dude, what the fuck
unbelievable
yeah, it was fucking insane dude
dude, someone edit please
like this dog as Sephiroth
in the confrontation between cloud and Sephiroth
at the end of this
also while you're at that edit
just like find a gallery of guys
that have been mauled by bears
and just edit all their photos to have the phrase
shoulda rolled on them
shoulda rolled man
shoulda rolled
I agree with you Tom
but I think that's like all skulls
like humans can like survive headshots to the face
like under weird precarious conditions
they don't bounce off though
bullets are specifically designed
to blow up your skull
that's like why they were made
no, I'm just saying like under extremely low
like there have been people who are survived headshots
because of the specific weird way that it happened
people will like
what happened to the people could happen to a human
if people kill themselves they generally shoot
inside the mouth up so that they
really fuck themselves up
what is the temple?
yeah, that's right
I've thought a lot about this
whether it's best to go with the inside the mouth
or the temple approach
what's gonna be grosser though
cause I wanna be as least gross as possible
I've actually considered the whole shooting yourself in the heart though
then don't use the gun
I don't want to shoot myself in the heart
cause I'll probably feel it
I don't want to feel it
you brain yourself
I'm pretty sure you'd
man, I think about what it would feel like to get shot in the head all the time
oh me too, I was doing that yesterday a bunch
cause I was hurting from being sick
all the time
I'm pretty sure there would be a moment there
where you would feel it happening
and it'd be like oh my god dude
I was really thinking about this
time is like slowed down
and you feel each individual piece
of the shotgun blast
invading your brain from inside your mouth
and you feel like up to your skull
I think about what does it feel like
to have one's brain violently
destroyed all the time
what the fuck is happening
this is what nature leads to
too much nature leads to this kind of suicide
overexposed your suicide
if you hang out around trees enough
you're going to start thinking about
which one will hold the best
rope the best
that's why people kill themselves
in alki gahara
and in greenland
they're always stuck at the trees
everyone in greenland
spends too much time in nature and not enough of civilization
so they have the highest suicide rate in the fucking world
last time I checked
we need urban sprawl
we need hip hop
that's the most civilization you can get
on the civilization scale hip hop is
what a hundred percent
hip hop is actually a peak civilization
clearly
that's true
I was hoping that you would be like
explain why he doesn't like animals
but I guess
oh do you want that?
unless you asked while I was on the tour
I went to pee for a while
no he did
anyway
I don't like animals because
they're annoying
they can't talk
they're fucking boring
they can't be negotiated with
everything I value about humans
is the ability to have conversations with them
that is the main thing
that other humans can give me
other than physical contact
and I don't think I would want physical contact with a person
that I could not
communicate with
it doesn't have to necessarily be verbally
text form but if I can't communicate
with somebody I'm not going to want to
hang out with them and
touch them or anything
animals just want
things and they have no sense
of moral obligation
towards you
my cat
when I lived back at home we had a cat
then you lived in the same house as this cat
she fucking
at any time of night if she wants
something she will come make you do it
she will pick you up
she will meow at your door all night
until you wake up and come do something for her
because she doesn't care about you
she can't comprehend your needs
she can't make compromises
because she cannot fathom
yeah
what about that
why should you sign up
why should you sign up for a relationship
that is completely one sided
that you are expected to provide for this other animal
and this other animal is not expected to do anything
I get that you might like what they do
it just irks me that
what they're doing is just what they want to do
and if that happens to please you
then so it goes
but they're not doing anything for your sake
you're providing for all of their needs
that legendary dog
who came to visit his master in Japan
every fucking day even after he died
Hachiko
the most legendary dog who ever lived
I visited his statue
he's a fucking god
but he just wanted his master
that's like saying obeying
well okay
you seem to be putting like thought
and like responsibility over
just like natural inclination
like that makes it more moral
like you are more valuable
I'm saying that I can see why that's like good
like if a dog is naturally inclined to love you
and you want love
I get why that's appealing
it just bugs me that there's no
it just bugs me that the relationship is so one sided
but I would argue that every human
only does what it wants to do
yeah
but we can guilt humans
that's true
I think you guys are thinking about this all wrong
animals are not humans
they're not mint
their function is not to have ideas
their function is to be
aesthetic and provide
sometimes practical benefit to humans
like oxes or
dogs or some stuff
aesthetic and provide
like practical application
with a dog you can train to fucking kill things
you know if we're back in
early times you can train to kill things
that's a practical benefit of it
but the main thing for me is aesthetic
I just like seeing again beasts
I like seeing dangerous monsters
roam about and do their living
it's terrifying
and it fills me with like a
gladiator lust for either
killing it or making it kill things for me
that's what I want from my animals
I agree that
animals are not like
they're not conversationalist
but that's not what I meant to do
I don't classify them as humans
I understand the appeal of animals
I get why other people like animals
it's just that nothing they have to offer
really does anything for me
because all I like to do is
smoke weed and have long conversations
and make videos and fuck
and animals can't do any of those things
well the last one
you can't
not legally
in most states
I should say
they just can't consent is all
did we want to talk more about nature
do we want to move into questions
because I got some questions pulled aside
I'm feeling pretty good
anyone want to make any closing statements here
anyone got any final words
hash out your reason for parkification
sorry to say that again
never mind it's fine
no one say anything ever again
mozilla fennekin asks
now hang on did you
is this coming from the legendary patron lounge
oh my god
if you patron anything to the pcp
one dollar
one dollar you get patron lounge
and that's where we get all our fucking questions from
because
it's easy and cool
mozilla fennekin
asked what's the most you're willing to spend
on a single meal
20 dollars
unless it's like an occasion
if it's like a festivity or a holiday
then it'll probably be like 50 or 60
if I want to flip
is that for just you
or are you paying for somebody else
that's what I was going to ask
you're right
usually what I am flipping it is
what's the most you're willing to spend
on a meal
for yourself and for a group
if I was like treating a party
and it was like a special occasion
I would probably spring
for like up to maybe like 100 to
150 dollars
if it was like a real big
an event
if it was just for me
I would only pay more than like
15 dollars and that's high
I would like to pay 5 dollars
for a meal for myself at any given time
but if I was out and being
socially pressured and everyone else was doing it
I might be convinced to spend maybe up to like
the absolute most I could spend for myself
is 20 dollars
I would go 20 dollars
the absolute max I want to stay around 5
ideally
only social pressure can compel me
if I was going to like
spend money like for me
and like a significant other or something
I have spent like 150 dollars
before but I was not aware that it was
going to happen and I was very disgusted by it
and I made a point to say this is never happening
again
I think
again if it's an occasion
if it's like Christmas
but I'm the only person left alive
because they all were too weak to
see me through
then I could probably go like
50 dollars
if I really wanted to make a big deal
All right, Mage, what's your answer for this?
It's basically the same
It's the same as you guys
Did you, you're the only one
besides maybe Nate who makes a significant amount of money
so you're about to be like I'm going to go like
four figures deep on this shit
It's not just about how much I make
but that I regularly spend money
on food like that's where a lot of
you know the money I do spend goes
but I want to know because I know
Nate's thrown down pretty fucking hard
on some meals because he and I
went to a restaurant where I spent
like 75 dollars and you spent
something close to that
You know what I found
I definitely, there have been times
more recently when I'll go to
a really nice restaurant that I've like never done in my life
for like a year ago
and those are pretty expensive sometimes
that's pretty rare but what I've really found
is just that my like sort of
base level amount I'm willing to pay for
a meal has just gone way up
and like I just don't really care anymore
For me it's kind of just like
what do I want to eat
you know like if I
if I want to have a fancy dinner
with my girlfriend
or my fiance you know we're just going to
go out and
like it's going to be whatever it cost
like for Valentine's Day we went out to
a place next to my house
$150 total it was great
I fucking went to Burger King for Valentine's
and I'm happy
Oh you make me laugh
I tell you like when you
when you actually do
I mean like I'm
very much a stickler
I always have been like I used to be real cheap
about going out to eat and that's why I like
exclusively ate fast food for a real long time
and then
basically it's just
if you can afford it and you're willing
to spend the money it's like
food does kind of follow
like a rule of the more you pay
the better it tastes
it's fairly straightforward most of the time
like that meal I had
that was $150 like
granted in terms of portions
and everything no it was not at all worth it
like if you're talking about how much
is it worth to get full tonight
not worth it but the food was like
I literally had never tasted something
that tasted the way it tasted you know
and like for me it's just that sheer
uniqueness of experience makes it worth
having paid for at least once
you know obviously I'm not going to go spend
$150 on food every night but
you know it's nice to get to experience
like this flavor
palette that can't really be explored
by anyone less than a talented chef
you know sure well yeah
when I went to Jack Ruby's
steakhouse or whatever the precinct is like
the best restaurant in Cincinnati
like I never imagined a steak could taste
as good as what they made there and they
fucking did it they did I didn't even know that was a real
thing but anyway sorry time I'm
I'm just I don't know paying for
food is something that I try not to
do ever and just
I mean I like food but like the
experience of eating food is ephemeral
you know it's fleeting and
like once you've done it it's over and so like
the fact that I invested money in it and now
the money is gone and the experience
was never going to last anyway there's a lot
of studies that state that say that people
ultimately find themselves more happy
with purchases they made
for experiences rather than possessions
because when you have a possession around
you'll constantly look at it and
judge it again like I hate
most of the crap I own in my room
like all the shit in my back
drops for all my videos and shit because a lot
of this is just DVDs that I'll look at and I'll be
like I spent like a hundred dollars on that box
set and A I've never watched
it and B like you know I don't even
really like the show that much anymore because
like you know it just sits around reminding
me of how much money I spent on it and how
if I had that money back I could be doing
something different right now but if you just
go say to again a fancy
restaurant you have a great time all you'll
remember about that for the rest of your life
is I went to a fancy restaurant I had a great
time you know like I'll never forget
me and Nate go into that restaurant because I'd never
been to any place like that before and like
we were fucking getting weighted on by
like like wind and dine the guy
coming up pouring our fucking water for us
and shit and we're like yeah you know
it was sick
how dope was that scared Italian
at anime expo did you need
how dope was that scared Italian who would
like give us orange oh that guy
it was amazing it was the best
he was incredible he was my favorite person
I like nice food I just
I just wish I could afford it more often
well most of what just quickly though
the burger king has like really awesome
milkshakes the one that's
sure so it was not a bad deal
I quite like it and we got like
because we had to wait a little bit we got
like big milkshakes so
nice most of what I actually eat
is cans of dark red
kidney beans like boxes of salad
protein powder and then
like chicken breast and broccoli salad
yeah they've got these like plastic
containers of salad at the Kroger
I'll just go buy that it's got a big fucking
thing of spinach I'll just like munch on that for two days
it's great enough about your diet
wait what munch
is it important what yes
yes it is important
I want to talk
about food more because I love food
I've been Ben you
said that the experience of eating food is fleeting
and I agree and this is why I hate sex
but food is different than sex
because food you can
have it like you can like
go out to a restaurant you can have it with other people
and we'll be that's we can have do the sex
nevermind I'm saying that restaurants are good
and I like going to restaurants I like people to talk to
eating food and talking
to people and the experience of being out of your house
out in the world
eating at a restaurant perhaps the restaurants you've
never been to before at a new restaurant with your friends
talking about the day you've had
experiences you're going to have
that is far better than ever sex you could
ever have
take that you pop into that 7-Eleven
and grab your food and then you take it
out into nature
and eat it in the fridge
that's how you fucking have it
that's a good idea I think you're going to say take your 7-Eleven
go to a fancy restaurant
guys picnics are such a cute idea
I would lie
you know there's like a big yard
right on there we should have a picnic
that's a good idea
can we have a picnic at radcon 4
whenever I come over
probably maybe you can't promise
off topic can we do radcon 4
in england
main shows up to radcon 4 and she's like
so can we do another picnic like you guys did at the last one
I'm like no
that idea is past
yeah the moment's past it's over
we're all about
eating soilent now
by the way
radcon 3 arena
is confirmed everybody
the kickstarter is now over
and not only is it confirmed
but the first kickstarter tier is already
fulfilled it's unlikely at this point
we'll have gotten the second but maybe it will
who knows man
wait there's two
it ends in like 4 days from today
on the 21st I think
I thought there was still a lot of time left
well whatever anyway
I mean my kickstarter
spiked like crazy in the last couple days
next question is from drybones
drybones this is one of my favorite questions
we've ever gotten on the show by the way
would you consider yourself
above your dad
could you defeat him physically
or intellectually
not physically intellectually yes
my dad's very strong
very very
very hard no
I know my dad and I does not make it okay
that doesn't make his crimes
any less potent
my dad
it is an old geezer
but he's so fucking
strong here's what he does
he hikes with rocks in his backpack
and every month he adds a new
rock to his backpack
he's been doing this for years
is he a fucking martial arts training
or something like that
he has like 30 rocks
in his fucking bag
do you talk to show training shit or something
it's fucking crazy he's insane
well that's awesome
he's powerful but he's also a fucking idiot
I can see where you got your power from now
yeah thank you
I feel like this question has a bit more nuance
in my situation because
I'm his daughter
what father want to punch his daughter
you know
as opposed to the father just want to punch
your son
hit him physically because he won't hit you
is that what you're trying to say
the thing is I don't want to hit him either
so I don't know
but you have to mate he's coming at you with a gun
what are you gonna do
it doesn't say anything about having to fight them
it just says can you defeat him physically or intellectually
okay physically
most likely no
no I wouldn't even though I'm taller than him
no I'm not I'm a squish boy
intellectually
probably
he's quite close minded
he's very averse to new ideas and stuff
so probably I could
against new age you know beliefs
don't let yourself be just one box
I feel like everyone's gonna do that about their parents
because that's essentially what I was gonna say about my dad
it's been probably as well
my dad is a very smart man
where are we so weak
you could definitely beat your dad physically right
at this point yes not for a long time though
not for a long time
everyone's kind of scared of their dads I think including me
to some degree
our dad is fires storms
our dad is a fucking
intellectual fortress if nothing else
that's for sure
well let me tell you why you've all played yourself
on this because the question says
could you defeat him physically
now if I have to fight my dad
one on one hand to hand
no I can't beat him that nigger roads marathons
and bench presses more than
my body weight and I can't
bench press more than my body well maybe
I don't know how much it's like an impressive amount
to be able to bench press
but anyways he's a strong man
however could I defeat him
physically I'm good at setting up traps
you know
you're gonna home alone is that
I'm good at using weapons
I'm good at fucking tricks
version of the quest
me and my brother Victor used to fight
in the backyard all the time
well you ran your marathons I practice with the block chain
well you lived your way
yeah exactly
when you worked on feeble aesthetics
well you paid as a house eye vlog
exactly so
me and Victor used to fight in the backyard all the time
and Victor would be stronger than me
but I would just like grab shit on the ground
and throw it at him and then jump on him
you know so I can do that to
my dad because he fights
so you fight dirty
yeah exactly and Victor
my dad probably won't fight nearly as dirty
as I will or at least not as
he won't think of the environment
as much as I will I got the Jackie Chan thing going on
you know like I'll throw
the TV at him or something
so
I do think I could defeat him physically
if we if I had to
like if it was not just oh we're like having
a blood feud like we're
passionately fighting to father and son
you know if we're like if my dad's a zombie
and I got to kill him like I can kill him
you know if you have
prep time you can kill your dad with prep time
let's say he's like under
let's say he's gone evil he's gone rogue
and he's murdering everybody
let's say he's become king deity
I will say that in order for me to
find the inner strength to kill my dad
he might have to strangle shade first
like I might need that motive
you know but if
you know if someone's been strangled
then I can probably get him
intellectually my dad
my dad's a smart guy but he would probably
forfeit to be intellectually TVH
because he thinks I'm a fucking genius
so fair enough
my dad would destroy me both physically
and intellectually
and emotionally
I've already done that to myself let's be real
no he's like
Tommy sound like you were on the verge of tears
when saying that
you sound like you were about to cry
that was not intentional but maybe that says something
deep about myself that I'm not aware of
it's very possible
but no he's like he's like
yes absolutely
no my dad's like super built
he's like the chief financial officer
for Hanscom Air Force Base he manages
multi-million dollar budgets on the daily
so yeah
smart guy
strong guy
does he even vlog?
if only
he had a debuff like that
I might stand a chance but no
he hasn't been distracted
by the
feudal pursuits like we all have
so indeed
alright here's our next question
from horse power
I'll next one
it says
how do you know if you're chasing a dream
or a dilution
oh that's got to be somebody made a video called
that recently who was that
it was Fantano
he probably said delusion
not dilution
that's true
I would expect so
I don't know if there is a way to
I mean
how do you qualify
when do you say it's a delusion
like if you're making money off of it does that mean it's not a delusion
but like what if it falls away
one day is it a delusion
I think a delusion is inherently only decided
after the fact I don't know if you can
you have to try
before you'll know
as soon as you know it's a delusion
that's what constitutes a delusion
let's talk about the exact example that he brought up
it's this guy, he didn't say his name but everyone was quite
it was quite clear who he was talking about
this guy Uncle Adams
he's made a bunch of cringy music videos and songs in the past
and he is now
like he's
he talked about how he's already sold his house
he sold his car, he's making these vlogs or whatever
he is like $200,000
and dead at this point
and he's decided he is not stopping until he has
a big music career
like here's what I don't understand
about that, it's like somebody like me
was able to just do youtube
while having a job and not completely
burying myself in debt
I think that is the smart path to take
to put all your eggs in one basket
like that seems like a mistake in my opinion
and like to be fair
I think you just need to know if it's a sure thing
I mean I can see putting all your eggs
in one basket if you're like
it depends on the circumstance
I mean if you think you've got the
masterpiece of the century
in your mind and like if you just
drop out of school for a year and work on it
you're gonna fucking blow the world away with your novel
but you really gotta think about like
how much time is it gonna take
you know are you actually
capable of delivering on it
get some opinions see how people react to it
who would you know find someone
who would enjoy it and show it to them
and see if they do
enjoy it you know
you know the story of disney
and snow white and how he had like
to I think what's the word mortgage
his house or something like that
he put a lot of his savings and like
basically he was like risking it all
the cuphead developers just did that
remortgage their houses to make cuphead
they did that was a big blood story
I mean lots of people have done it but like
in those cases like
we're talking about disney
is making a movie with some of the best animation
quality that had ever been done
so like there's almost guaranteed
an audience when you know for a fact
that you were doing something of like a technical
level of craftsmanship above
anything else anyone's doing and if you were doing
that you would know you were doing it
cause you would be able to observe everyone
else and you know everything about their
we hear a lot of like anecdotal stories
about like you know successful people
who are risking it all but like we hear about
those examples cause they're successful
there's like dozens and hundreds and thousands
of people who've done the same thing and got
totally fucked when you look
at the cuphead development like of course
they remortgaged their house cause the first time
they took that game to E3 it was fucking all
anyone was talking about so they knew they had
a hit on their hands like they would be stupid
or not to do it if they were passionate enough
to finish the project you know and make sure
it was good but that's like
so you gotta look at it different
you gotta you know think about risk differently
from just oh they remortgaged their house
they took a huge risk it's like yeah
they took a huge risk on a sure thing you know
so it's not really a risk at all
I just like I want to pull up how many subs
this guy just get a feel for what success
he's gotten at the moment he has one
video that's got like something like
500,000 views his youtube channel
has about 26,000 subscribers
like the fact of the matter is
he is not that successful yes
I think honestly what
this guy this man had was a dangerous
thing is that he got a little
too much taste of success
and kind of addled his brains I think that's
what ruins like most youtubers
like I think a lot of the youtubers who
end up only being around for a couple years
it's cause one thing
plays into like the algorithm just right
or maybe even a few videos for a little while
and like you know you just
take off and then
as soon as you don't have that weird
magical foothold that like whatever youtube's
algorithm was at that moment just happened
to like align perfectly with your shit
then you know you might fall off
if your fans don't actually care about you
I watched a bunch of this guy's videos
and he talked about how like
when he started this vlog like yeah I was about to release a video
you know I was really hoping
that would be the one that blew up
and he says like maybe it'll take like a week
maybe it'll take a month maybe it'll take a couple months
for me to succeed but like we're talking about a man
building up his music career like
from the ground floor this should not be
an idea of like within days
I'll have made it no
I could tell just by listening to his videos
he has a way warped sense of time
for what he thinks this is gonna be
I watched some of the music videos like not
good and he has people cringing
at his videos like this is the kind of guy
we're talking about it just it scares me
man this is a guy I think it was a victim
of kind of the the
weird success I would
call a victim he's choosing this
he's doing well all I'm saying is that I think
he's he's under he's experiencing some
confirmation bias in what
he's doing and he sees all the success people
and he thinks if I just and you know what
if this guy makes it everyone
will say like oh well look at all the haters man
he will say like look at all the haters who doubted
me but the thing is what matters is not
whether he succeeds or not what matters
was the degree of risk he was willing
to expose himself to and for some
people they can expose themselves to a little
risk and have it pay off great guys like me
are extremely conservative about this kind
of things and do not put a lot of risk into what they do
but like I would argue
this guy put it way too much
I'll tell you right now I consider
myself a huge risk taker but like
yeah not in the way
like I only take the big risk after
I've already got you know
ten thousand dollars saved up
and I'm like
you know sure that they have to
make sure everything's set up you know it I'm going
to make a big leap but I'm gonna
make sure I fucking have gauged the
distance that I'm jumping you know like
we say you're not as spontaneous in that way
I well you know before I
make the leap I lick my finger
and I hold it up and I feel the winds
and I determine which way they're blowing
you know then I'll make a calculated
risk taker exactly
I think there's a lot of people who just
are just straight up
don't even know what they're supposed to be looking for
they just see a hole and they think they
can jump over it and they don't even realize
that they don't have legs you know like
yeah there's people like that on
YouTube
all right true man Munchy you wanted to do the next
question yes yes by
J8 the hurricane and
the questions bar what is the PCP's
Mass Effect 3
something so disappointing that you retroactively
hate all the related content that comes before
it something that we made
or something that we feel like that
about I think he I think
what he meant was like what do we
feel is the case right maybe
John Tron historically was kind of like
I wanted to take this the way that like
what have we created that we
hate like that like like retroactively
we now hate it and be like
I'm so embarrassed
there's nothing
I've made that makes me
hate retroactively all the
things I've made before it I don't think
that's what he's asking I think he means like
but is there a piece of content that you are
like oh I shouldn't have made that
my fucking pony vids
you're what
but mage they were your foothold to
stepping stone you know whatever
pony vans do you say
pony things
are pretty successful some of them
yeah I don't regret T-Bab at all
yeah but now I'm
stuck in the pony fandom
shadow and like three or four years later
people still like poke me
about the pony things and I'm just like I'm done
with this
you definitely did not make as hard of a cut
as the fellow guys here did
I did I made an announcement
I told people
I fucking I'm not drunk
in what ways is this just that people ask
you about pony because that doesn't seem like a major
issue if they just kind of ask you about
it people still make a keg and phantom
fan art and I love it
and the rest of the crew was great
chat up to acro
kill it as always
fucking of arm retrieval like a veteran
general of arm retrieval
acro is fucking incredible
I get sometimes people just actively denying
that I left the fandom and I'm just like
wake up
grab a brush and put a little makeup
yeah
exactly
I definitely think I oh sorry
maybe she can continue
I make it sound
worse than it is actually
some of the things
in the pony thing
the lethal halloween thing I'm kind of embarrassed
by it because it's really really bad
but people really like it
so I'm kind of really embarrassed by it
that's fair enough
there's a lot of my videos I'm embarrassed
by like
because generally my
writing style and taste
evolve over time and sometimes I rewatch
some old shit and I'm just like
what the fuck am I talking about
why did I make this
why did I think this is okay
but like most of it is stuff that
I think I appreciate
why people would have liked it at the time
there's very few videos that I've made that were like
when they came out
they were DOA and like the mario
odyssey video I made is definitely
one of them where like
I was just like
I don't know why I made that video
because I knew that the only way I was going to
convince anybody of my point is by doing
like an in depth analytical breakdown
a la mathematosis
and I'm sure that when his video comes out
he probably will
criticize the visuals of that game because
I trust him to fucking have sense
but um
I jumped the gun and just made something quick
and I thought that if I open it by just being like
yo this is a goofy video
like people would be okay with it
but they were not
they're pretty rabid about that
yeah so it was just
it just didn't need to exist
it was just a PR disaster
basically like it was just me coming out
with an unpopular opinion
not defending it well and then just having people
be like well we disagree
and we hate you for having made this
even brought this to the attention
of the world in the first place
Gigi didn't that like fucking stupid
vlog video have like rebuttal
videos and like it did
like it was like taking you down
who the fuck cares
dude I can't I can't believe
this is why I don't make videos about video games
like cause it's not worth it
it's not something that I made
but I guess probably the thing I'm most
ashamed of would be a analysis
anarchy
being associated with that
I just watched that the other day
in fact
does it hold up
is it as good as I remember
I showed it to all my offline friends
to specifically show you
Ben I showed them
to like be like you know that guy
I know that guy he's my friend
jesus
awful awful so that's the first thing they know of you
okay well I guess that's what I deserve
Ben's part
the silver quill quip
I remember being the only kind of funny part
yeah I didn't read the script
I just looked at my like two lines
and I thought alright well these aren't terrible
I'll read them and then I watched the whole video
and it's like so it goes so
downhill from there
like once the actual plot gets underway it's like
oh my god this is
this is what we're doing no please
oh shameful
oh yes
that reminds me that I
have to do something similar for a guy's
abridged series
that someone just like
messaged me like hey will you do a voice in
my abridged series on black
clover or whatever and I was like
sure as long as he said there's only be a couple
lines I'm like sure and then I get the lines
and I am
first of all I'll have way more than a couple lines
and second of all my character
is all quotes from my videos
so
what?
he sent me the script
and I didn't actually read it for a straight week
and by the time I read it everyone else had done
their lines so I'm like
now I kind of feel like I have to do it
because like I'm the only one
holding this thing up but like I hadn't read it
beforehand so I'm just like oh god
yeah you fucked up a little bit
but I should probably
do that performance today
cause that guy's been asking me for weeks
and I have just been ignoring it
there is an
uncanny valley type situation
for embarrassing content for me
because like if I go back in my past
and I read all the role plays or something
they are hilarious they are great
they do not even like
I cannot imagine it was like to be
like tin and writing role plays
I can't imagine I am
not that person so it's funny to
like look back and be like oh wasn't this
silly wasn't this a cringy you know funny time
ha ha ha but the closer
you get to being actually
real life me and the more embarrassing it gets
it gets to be like oh I remember
writing that
how many years
before like munchie pissing on stream
is like his worst memory
of all his whole life no that won't
that will never be the case
pissing on games I can't
I can't wait for the new segment munchie vs munchie
in like three years fucking ten
ten years from now when he's like running
for office cause he's become like
really politically minded and stuff
literally his career is ruined
by the time he pissed on PCP
cause like everyone has files of it
oh god well ok ok
if I do decide to run
for office literally the entirety
of like me saying this right now
will be an embarrassment and will be the worst thing
that I've done I just
resigned myself to the fact that I will never
be a politician because I just could not be
there's just no way that I could be
I've resigned myself to the fact that I probably can't hold
any job anymore cause like any
background check on me it's just gonna turn up
like a bunch of fucking weird
troll videos and shit like
you'll need to be some sort of
like social influencer or like
a writer for a magazine like working at like
a McDonald's or something would be like yeah
they look that up and it's like well what the fuck is this about
but then again hopefully it wouldn't
come to that point
yeah excellent I've been
using the same name for like
like so long now that like my entire
history is documented
so it's like it's like like no matter what
like I will never be able to like escape
I don't know anyone I'm trying to do
I'm just saying that like the closer you get
to like me right now
like it's again like a valley
so like if I were to go two
years back I would probably be like
oh god why did I say do these things
but if I go like like five years back
I'll be like I don't even remember this
there's no way I could
have done this like this is not
I've seen a few things on my blog
that I'm legit like there's like
this is impossible there's no way I had
this opinion that goes in the shell
standalone complex it's the ugliest anime
and stuff like that
so alright nice
question
sandalwood asks what's the most at
drill thing you've ever done
Ben I want to know
you got an answer
oh man
I bet I could think of some
you know what
give me a second I'll be right back
you know Ben I'm gonna say
okay
I feel like those things that the
PCP have done together could fit
into a drill tweet like the group
shit that might be a pretty
at drill thing I think
the group shit was very real
taking a group shit at BrodyCon with
five internet people that I'm
fucking living with now
I'm looking at I pulled up drills twitter
here's a recent one from February 16
so yesterday
time to look at the moments tab
I lay down in the bathtub and a guy smears
shit all over my chest with his ass
while using a taser on me
there you go yeah pretty yeah
you know take it five man group shit
at BrodyCon with my internet buddies
that's a drill tweet
I agree
whenever it comes
to questions like this
I almost feel like I haven't done anything with my life
but even though
I have like a reputation for being like crazy
they like I think
about them so much that it's like that doesn't even
feel weird to me I mean pissing on stream
is pretty fucking at drill
that's true and fucking
walking up and down my like
rich white like town
like in full pizza and top hat
pizza ones even top hat
I am a prince from Africa and I will buy out
every small business and because I am the
I'm the owner of Microsoft that's
pretty at drill that's very at drill
because you brought up that exact example
just listen to this question just as an insert
to this larger question this is from the
from the twitter
hashtag askpcp everybody
how is it that only six years ago
munchy was a small baby boy
swaddled in the garments of a slain Arab prince
while baptized in the blood of 100 maidens
sounds pretty relevant
it's amazing to see
my growth from your six years ago
being a baby
it's a shame he had to give up his claim to the throne of Dubai
but nonetheless he's made the best of the situation
it's a shame I had to stop being a Nigerian prince
to do anime raps on the internet
and then I had to you know crash the people
because that was homeless that's a real shame
I have to imagine that Ben has
gone off into the bathroom stripped naked
and is just like fucking flailing himself
with a trout right now
which ironically enough is
which ironically enough is pretty drill itself
yeah
yeah just the tweet would be like
trying to make some shit happen
for the podcast I'm on
left the bathroom to beat myself with a trout
nothing's happening
you know something like that
something like that
um well well
I mean tweet drill is really all about
his brand right
like everything drill does
he does for the drill brand
and he's always wheeling and dealing
I don't know I just
like the only thing that comes to mind
that's particularly drill-ish
is like there's nothing in specific
but there's just like
I don't know everywhere I've always lived
people have remarked that like I just do things
in a strange way
and they don't know like I'll just
assemble food in like a bizarre order
that doesn't make any or I'll just like throw things
together and people are like
Ben why do you do that and I'm always like
and I'm always like I don't know why anyone doesn't
do it this way like that's just
my stock answer is like I don't understand
why everyone doesn't do everything the way that I do
which seems like kind of a drill
that's that's a fairly drill sentiment
I guess all right I got one more
question at zeno grade
asks what quote do you want
carved onto your tombstone
I was about to do this one I want
the classic my
my heartbeat clips the microphone that should be on my
that's a good one especially from
a fucking corpse
yeah yeah exactly
I know I had an answer
I definitely I'm just thinking
because I know I had some answers for this
but I can't remember them right now I'm still banking
on on me oh
weaponized I think it's for the force
yeah that's what
I'll weaponize
and thickness with Jesus
that's what I want
maybe some questions from the cue
my kerfuffle you know you gotta bring back
your pass you don't even know me at all
don't understand the meaning of my fall what my family
would think if I ever failed at anything
that's what I want to buy
I had to fight
for my tombstone I'd be like
brb respawning
oh dude
is she a gamer girl holy shit
my tombstone just say the living
mage your tombstone should just have
like the hexadecimal code for
purple on audit
that's a good idea
you know I want a QR code
that leads to like an ARG
that's inspired oh my god that would be so
fucking dope yeah that's what I want
yeah that's it
just have a tombstone
just says like comment subscribe
that's how you
you sign off from life
that's a good one
the idea of a posthumous ARG
is the most appealing concept
between the entire fucking world
I hope
that I still have this interest when I am in fact
dead
the idea of like
doing an ARG and instead of like slender
man it's a real life
actual corpse that is dead
looking up on there and wow he's dead
ghost that is fucking dope
you gotta figure this out you gotta start laying
the breadcrumbs now you gotta start leaving
clues in PCP episodes
that's true
the final link will be me
we'll be a time stamp
oh yes
exactly incredible
no one else have anything Ben
what was the question
what would you have on your tombstone
oh god
now I'm embarrassed because I just thought
of a really great
tombstone etching that I remember
I heard someone talking about
but now I'm remembering that the person I heard
talking about it was Danny from Game Grumps
and I don't want to just repeat something that was said
on Game Grumps so I'm gonna gracefully bow out
you've given him credit now I'm just curious
what it is we understand it's his
it was like it was a poem
as you are now
so once was I as I
am now so you shall be
it was kind of like a passive aggressive
little poem about like yeah I'm dead but
fuck you
very good
Game Grumps
Game Grumps guys
the Game Grumps are here
among us
my tombstone I
specifically want this if I
live incredibly long
but I want it to just be like hey hey every
pony he left us I want to
only if I live
incredibly long I want it to be
like he left us too soon
or something like
like life is brief or something like that
and just like I live like 120
years or something yeah
here lies the otaku
gonzo corpse and forever may he
rest
may he never rise from this
crypt as he has several times
security never return
I think we saw all there is to say on
the topic of nature is
death good is nature death
yes we are going to die right now
who wins in a fight nature or nurture
who's stronger I was trying
to figure out how to make a fucking
versus nurture joke the whole show
but eventually an hour had passed and I was
like we don't need to go on this tangent
nurture wins I'm saying nurture nurture wins
other episode on nurture I would love that
you know a good idea literally press
one for nurture I will literally do that
okay let's deal with that
goodbye goodbye
make sure you do a patreon
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
$1 for the for the chat
$5 for the bonus episodes
Gamergate 2016 election
Trump drum it's all there
got a bunch of old episodes too
we got iTunes
and Google Play Tom hooks us up with
that shit links or something go figure
it out and
that's it Radcon three people
in a couple of weeks six of us will be there
or entering the arena March
14th is the beginning
and there you go join us for fun it's
gonna be great hundredth episode of
PCP coming up
all right bye everyone
bye
oh no
I'm stopping recording
yes
I'm
supposed to be working
right now
I'm supposed
to be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick
I'm jerking
myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am
stupid
I got a
deadline don't want to do
it