Hello, and welcome to the second episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. PCP, happy
to have you with us. I'm the best guy ever. Guy with my team of esteemed internet individuals.
Everybody, let's hear who you are. I'm Ben Saint, and I draw comics. Go be my patron.
Patreon.com slash Ben Saint. Next! I'm Digibro. I make the anime videos. You know the ones.
I'm Hippocrit. I make the video games. No, I don't. I make the reviews of them, and there they are on the screen. I'm forcing somebody to edit.
I'm not doing that shit. Jesse, who are you?
I'm Endless Jess. I'm a piece of shit, and I suck cocks.
Tom?
I'm Tommy Oliver, and I run a channel reviewing art gear, and I'm going to start a comic or the thing someday. Someday.
Looking forward to that, Mage.
No, no, no. Go ahead.
No, shut up, Ben. Mage.
Fine, fine. I will.
I am Mage, a little Rora Mage, and I have no idea what I'm doing right now. I think I'm doing animatic stuff things. Also, let's play Undertale. I should get on that sometime. Yeah, that's me.
And D'Voo?
Other than Mage, we're all the exact same person, so it doesn't matter. I also analyze video games.
You heard it, folks. D'Voo doesn't matter. All right.
So today's topic is we are going to be delving into that nebulous topic, dear to most of our hearts, waifus. What are they? What is their function? Do they exist? Can we reunite with them by drinking bleach?
These are the questions we're going to delve into here.
So if you'll indulge me, I'd like to read the Urban Dictionary definition of waifu, so that we have a baseline to start with, because defining waifu is going to be essential for this whole thing.
It's pretty much going to be the entire subject of the podcast, because we're never going to come to an agreement.
I think we'll probably all end up in a pretty same mindset about the whole thing. It's just an issue of how we use the word.
I want to say, I can't remember the name of it, but I saw a Wikipedia article on some psychological principle where the intensity of an opinion is inversely proportional to the importance of the topic at hand.
Interesting.
Are you making a commentary on the topic of this podcast?
I'm saying that because of that principle, this topic should get very heated indeed.
Okay, so here we go.
Waifu, a term coined by Otaku and Weaboo alike for their 2D significant others, predominantly anime and video game characters.
A waifu, in contrast to a harem, is the love between one man and his one and only waifu.
You treat your waifu with the utmost respect and courtesy, and most refuse to even fap to their beloved, seeing the act as an insult to the non-existent woman they have committed themselves to.
A spin-off term, husbando, followed for fujoshi who feel similarly toward male characters exist.
I don't think anybody should have actual definitions.
I have multiple issues with that definition already.
I agree. First of all, there is nothing more sacred than the act of fapping to your waifu. That is the unification ritual.
You light your candles, you play some music, you play some toto, and it's a romantic important thing.
I want to add to that a little history context.
This is just how I understand it, and it seems to be the common opinion among the internet of how the term waifu came into existence.
Is this going to be boring?
No, it's not school.
In the anime series Azumanga Daio, there's a character, one of the teachers, who's like this weird creepy pedophile guy,
and he turns out at one point to have a beautiful wife, and no one sees it coming.
And he says, in English, my wife, but of course Japanese pronunciation.
I just watched that before we started.
My waifu, and that is commonly considered to be the origin of the term waifu.
That show aired in 2001, so I'm willing to believe it.
I don't think the term's older than that show.
I think you're right, I think you're right.
It was a glorious day for all of us.
Is that what you're telling me?
Well, they thought he was a pedophile, but then you turned out to have a wife and a daughter, but you guess he could still be a pedophile.
I think he was still a creepy pedophile.
Well, in anime, the lines are blurred, you know, but...
They definitely are.
And we'll get into that, this whole thing.
Well, okay, I guess maybe we should each describe the way that we think of the term waifu,
and maybe just throw out our personal opinion on the term.
Before we go any further, I just want to make one last note.
Tom, if you could nudge your audio volume up a little bit, or sit a little closer to the mic, it would be great.
Yeah, I suppose that's true, it's a little quiet.
Okay, why don't we just go around and everybody can say what they think a waifu is,
because it's definitely not going to be exactly the same as what it is here.
I guess I'll start.
So to me, I view a waifu as, really, it's just my favorite female character from the show that I feel attracted to.
So I kind of have a loose rule of like picking one waifu per show, which is, I mean, I pretty much just made that up.
I don't think anyone else has this rule, but to me, that's what a waifu is.
And a link at the bottom, I've got, if you look at my channel banner, it's me with most of my top waifus are up there.
You know, the best from each of some of my favorite shows.
And I've got a whole tier list of waifus that I'll link in the description of this video if you want to go peruse it.
Jesus date.
Yeah, you know, I made it for fun.
I made it kind of because I wanted my channel banner to be that.
Why do I feel like this video is secretly you wanting to promote your waifu?
I do want to promote my waifus.
I'm glad I'm not the only one picking up on this.
Not so subtle agenda.
You know, you're right, you're absolutely right.
That's what it is.
Go look at my channel banner.
It's the best.
Shout out to Tom's girlfriend, Cotton Candy.
Cotton Candy says, I forget the full, Cotton Candy draws, yeah.
Cotton Candy draws, drew my art.
It's fantastic, love it.
Okay, so anyway, that's me.
Who wants to go next?
I will go.
Okay.
Now, all right, I think.
Ben is the one on the other side of the fence here.
I'm not a person who has waifus.
Right.
Or subscribes to the idea that one should have a waifu.
I mean, so I'm just going by what I hear.
I think my impression is that the formal definition of a waifu is a fictional, probably 2D character who, you know, is your surrogate girlfriend.
Or whatever.
Yeah.
No, no, you're a literal girlfriend.
Sure.
But in common usage, it's used hyperbolically just to do any character that you have a crush on or even just one that you like.
Right, that's what I use it.
But that's too wishy-washy.
I'm going to be coming at it from the perspective that a waifu is a female or a character that you are dedicated to in some kind of romantic way.
Sure, okay, yeah.
And that's it.
I don't know.
Well, like the fine dedicated, like...
Well, I mean, a lot of these people really like this whole description where you...
Like, I have like 50 posters of Asuka in my room.
I don't believe that I'm actually married to her.
Well, that might mean that she's not your textbook waifu, you know?
It's not that you believe anything about her.
It's that you view her and you like...
It's about your mindset regarding her.
Well, I sort of...
Well, I see it exactly like how Nate described it.
I don't believe in this weird, like, autistic devotion.
You can only have one...
I watch something or I play a game or I watch a show and it's like,
well, she's the best girl in this show.
She's my waifu.
I guess we use the term synonymously with best girl.
Another term.
Yeah, well, that's the thing, though.
And I don't necessarily feel this way, but to play Devil's Advocate a little bit,
I kind of feel like the term waifu for it to have meaning should be more than just best girl,
because we already have best girl to describe best girl.
That's true.
You know, if you watch a show and...
You know, because I've had plenty of times where I watch a show
and there's not any one girl who I would consider to be like,
oh, man, I really love this girl.
I'm gonna think about her when this show is over, you know?
Yeah.
But, like, she is the best one in the show.
And then I think calling her my waifu would feel like way overextending like what she is.
She's just the best girl in the show.
She's not my...
I've spent a lot of my time in waifu threads on A.
And as a result of that...
There's a lot of arguing in waifu threads on A.
There sure is.
But a lot of camaraderie as well.
Yeah.
But...
That just describes A to me.
A lot of arguing, but a lot of camaraderie as well.
Those are great threads, you can find that.
But just the definition in those spaces where I spent most of my life discussing anime,
because not a lot of people around me loved anime the same way I did when I was growing up,
just the term took on that connotation sort of...
Like, it was used jokingly a lot of the time,
but that really sort of sunk into my understanding of what it meant.
Like, I use the term way more as a joke than I've ever used it in a serious way,
just as a matter of those with the circles I tread in, and that's how the word was used.
So, you know, what makes the definition of a word accurate?
Is it the way that most people use it, or the way the dictionary says it?
Shouldn't we continue getting everyone's tattles?
You're absolutely right.
I don't think we heard of Major or Davoo or Hippos.
Okay, you're right.
Whoever wants to go next, let's hear it.
Okay.
Tom, you go.
I'm just gonna give a shit.
I was gonna wait until everyone knows.
You're just being polite.
Yeah.
Okay, Tom's going.
I think I'm pretty similar to Ben in the fact that I don't really, like, focus too much on waifus.
Like, I'm sitting here right now thinking, like, do we even have a waifu?
I don't even know.
Oh, no, for shame.
Like, what about rarity?
Like, I don't even think that would be considered a waifu.
Just, like, again, like, best girl, sort of, in that context.
Yeah, okay.
I don't know.
I don't think any of us use it, like, as seriously as some...
I think you have to be a pretty messed up person to look at it strictly in that most rigid...
Well, the whole thing is that there's a total...
I don't necessarily agree with that.
Yeah.
Without that, though.
Like, you can get, like, games in Japan where, like, they have, like, AR cards for the 3DS
where you can go to actual locations to get...
Well, yeah, like, like, Love Plus.
You guys have ever seen Love Plus?
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
You know a guy married his Love Plus guy.
Oh, I know.
I know.
He's my hero.
So, I mean...
Tom, turn your mic up, goddammit.
Is it still fucked up?
I turned it up.
I feel like I'm talking to someone who's standing, like, on the complete opposite end of, like,
a large room and it's talking at a normal volume.
That's true.
It's talking into a pillow.
Well, while he's suggesting that...
Let me put forward the suggestion that maybe, since none of us have, you know, the stringent
definition of a waifu.
Yeah.
That's only...
Okay, go on.
And it's generally agreed, it seems, that, like, if you use it too loosely, it just becomes
synonymous with best girl.
Yeah.
So, maybe there's some, like, middle ground between these two.
It's definitely...
Well, I don't know.
We just have to specify when we're talking about any given point, which we're talking about.
For what it's worth, me and Jesse haven't actually shared our stance on what a waifu is.
We've just responded to you guys' stances.
Okay, well, if you want to, you know...
Well, I don't...
Okay.
So, to me, a waifu is, like...
Like I said, it shouldn't...
Like, to me, best girl is, like, a way exaggeration if you call it a waifu.
Like, to me, a waifu has to be someone who is, like, specially appeals to me.
Like, there doesn't have to be one, or it doesn't have to be some, like, weird devotion thing.
But, like...
To me, the whole point of saying that someone's a waifu is that they are, like, specifically appealing to me.
Like, it's a character who, you know, who goes beyond just being, like, a character I like,
more so that they're a character that I'm, like, you know, attracted to, not even necessarily, like, in a sexual way,
but more in, like, a...
Like, if this was a real person, then she'd be someone who I'd have a crush on, you know?
Or something to that effect.
I very much agree with that.
That's a good articulation of basically how I feel about it.
Yeah.
Well, it sounds like you should...
You're talking about the elder-tier-tier on my waifu tier list.
Everyone go check it out.
It's, uh...
That's the thing, like...
I'm just plugging that.
This is fucking stupid.
You're stupid!
Everyone loved my waifus.
Appreciate that.
Yeah.
Like, I think, uh, you know, to me, like, I can usually tell a waifu pretty quickly because
it's more like an aesthetic and personality thing than it is, like, I love the character
for being a good character.
You know, like, if I had said, say, Yukino Miyazawa from Karekano, like, is a great character,
but not my type at all.
Like, I could never see myself, you know, dating her or something like that.
She is one of my favorite characters in fiction in terms of, like, how she's written and how
her character develops.
But, like, then I've got, you know, Tsukiyomi Sensei from Index, who is a fucking side character
who has nothing to do with the plot, but, like, she's just this, like, 38-year-old alcoholic,
smoking, uh, tiny, like, 38-inch tall, pink-haired monster.
Uh, and I just love her, you know?
Like, it's just a matter of, like, I look at her and I'm like, yeah, she's the best.
And that's more waifu to me.
Like, I don't give a fuck about her character.
I care about her more as, like, something, like, something in my head, you know, something
like beyond the pages of the show.
It's, you know, the version of her that I've imagined is the one that I like, and that's
more waifu to me.
So, like, a character who appeals to you specifically in a, like, romantic or sexual or that kind
of way?
Yeah.
I don't know if it has to be sexual or romantic so much as it is that it's, like, something,
like, it's you appreciate them more than their place in the work.
And I ask you something, is it necessarily a prerequisite?
I'm not sure if you stand by this, but it seemed like it was in there somewhere.
That, like, you think that they'd be necessarily compatible with you if they were real.
Because my top waifu of all time, you know, by my standard is Nico Robin from One Piece.
And she is like a, I mean, when you meet her, she's a 28-year-old assassin who's, like, worked
all over the world, like, killing people and has been chased by the government her whole
life.
I don't really think we have a lot to talk about.
I don't think there's much, you know, like, relatability there.
It's just, I appreciate the character so much and find her so attractive.
I think in life, you often find yourself having a crush on a girl and being in love with her
in spite of the fact that, you know, you could never be together.
You know, that she would never be into you, that you would never have a thing, you know.
Some of my waifus are ones who very much, I'm like, like, for instance, the girl from,
I can't understand what my husband is saying.
Like, the main appeal of that show to me is that the main character is so much like me
and the main in his wife is, like, the, like, everything I would ever want out of a girlfriend.
Any girl that you marry will probably become exactly like her, even if she's a start out
that way.
She is what I would want to marry and that's, like, why the show is intriguing to me because
it's like I'm watching what would be the ideal relationship for me.
In my mind, I don't know if it would really be like that, but, you know, in my mind,
she's the perfect waifu, but, like, but another character who I consider a waifu is
Sunamori Akane from PsychoPass and that's more of, like, an admiration thing where, like,
I don't really think we'd be compatible, but I'd love to live in a world where we were,
you know, like, because I admire her personality and her ethics and the way she carries herself
and everything and, like, you know, I think if I lived in that world, I would be, like,
her dumbass Hangeron guy, you know, the guy who follows her around and wishes he could
get with her, but can't actually approach her.
Let's get Mage and Hippo's...
Yeah, let's do that.
Entivus.
You first.
Mage.
Well, me?
Yeah.
Okay, no, Gibbon first.
He's already talking.
Yeah.
My waifu is inherently silly to me, so I'd never really use it in a serious sense, but
I do embrace a lot of silly things and just roll with it.
Like, I don't know, that's just something about the wa...
Fuck it.
So who's your waifu?
So just get to the good part, Hippo.
Who's your waifu?
They all seem to be similar sort of characters, the sort of borderline tsundere, the bitches
usually.
The bitches, there's Riska from Homestuck, there's Undyne from Undertale, Pacifica Northwest,
Diamond Tiara, some other ones.
Oh, I didn't know you liked Pacifica that much.
Yeah, she's cute.
I like her, she's underage, but you know what?
I'm willing to wait a couple years.
All bets are off.
Yeah, you're willing to wait.
He's a good man, folks.
Get out there and date him.
The thing that was going around my head was, I don't know whether that is actually like,
I like that character all the time in fiction.
I always gravitate to all that character.
I don't know whether that character is something I would actually like in real life, or that
wouldn't be good for me in real life, but I...
To be around a Diamond Tiara might be a total pain and suck in general, but the potential
of breaking through, and that's the appeal of the Tsunere, like getting to the gooey
deray in the center, the crispy delicious part, that's what you look for.
It turns romance into a sport.
Yeah, right.
Like you're trying to win at romance with a girl, and it provides a challenge.
It's like the Dark Souls of romances.
Yeah, someone should draw a picture of that.
And I like Dark Souls.
He sure does.
All right, Mage, if you're done, give.
Let's hear Dark Souls' waifu, HIPAA.
Oh, Maiden Estrella?
I forget.
The one of the spider ladies, the big one.
No, the one...
The sad one, the fair lady?
Yes, fair lady.
What a great choice.
Fair lady's fucking hot.
Yeah, she is hot.
Maiden Estrella's best girl, though.
Okay, Mage, let's hear what you have to say.
Okay, well, first off, I'd like to say that I use the term waifu for male characters most
of the time because Husbando is a bother to say, and waifu just sounds cuter.
I agree.
I don't usually...
Well, I never use it super seriously, but I use it on certain characters that may not
necessarily be my favorite or I think the best written characters in the show, but I just
sometimes...
A character really resonates with you.
I want to see more of them, or I really like the way the fans just interpret it.
It's kind of hard to explain.
They're on a different level than just the best character.
For instance, let's say in Undertale, my favorite character is Metaton, but I consider Papyrus
my waifu because he's just adorable.
Okay, cool, cool.
How did you feel when he rejected you?
I was sad.
Sounds appropriate.
Friend zone.
I've made it all the way to the friend zone in just one day.
All right.
That was a great line.
Yes, I love Papyrus.
I love Papyrus.
He's just such a precious cinnamon roll.
Agreed.
Yeah, I don't necessarily shoot myself or...
I wouldn't want to see fanart of myself with my wife or anything.
I don't do it in that sort of way.
I like them as a character and I want to be just on a different tier than just the best
character.
It's my favorite character.
Do you feel any sensation of wish that you could be with them at all?
I mean, I kind of feel that because mine are all hot sluts.
Obviously, that's what I'm into.
I wish they existed.
How fucking dare you say that about Nico Robin?
Well, I use the term in the most endearing way possible.
Nico Robin is in no way a slut.
She's a pure waifu.
Even though she literally says the line, I am 16, I will do anything.
She says that, but not a slut.
She's pure.
Maybe I'm sorry I bulldozed you.
That's fine.
To answer your question though, no, I don't think so.
A lot of the characters that I really like, they're really...
You don't want to get boned by Papyrus?
No!
Nailed it!
Goddamn!
Oh, god.
It's all over now.
Don't die on his chest.
Oh, no.
No, no.
It's like...
No, I lost my train of thought.
Go join me.
That must be how Papyrus feels around Saiyans.
Oh, yeah, there we go.
I remember it.
I like them.
They're very interesting characters and they're interesting to sort of watch and not really
interact with if it's a game or something.
But I think they would be very tiring.
At least a lot of the first people I would call waifus, they would be very tiring and
just taxing in a relationship that probably not...
I mean, I'm already in a happy relationship, so I'm good.
Well, right.
But, you know, this is all speculatory.
Yeah, yeah.
I wouldn't probably know.
I don't see myself with my waifus that if that...
Okay, that's interesting.
I guess the moral of this podcast is that we all pretty much agree and none of us take
it that seriously.
And I guess that's it.
That's true.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hang on.
We haven't heard from Davoo yet.
Davoo, bring this home.
Bring this home, guy.
He's gone.
He's dead.
Any fictional female character who I love.
Okay.
So he agrees with all of us, basically, in our definition.
Am I just like a whole second or so delayed?
I guess a little bit.
Wait, am I just delayed or something?
I guess everyone's delayed.
Yes.
Any fictional female character who I love.
Okay.
I use as a measurement for how I think about women in real life.
I'd be like, there's certain characters that excel at certain things and then I will evaluate
any woman who I know in real life and go, does she hold up as well as that in real life?
That's an interesting standard.
That is a tool with which I can help.
That's a dangerous mindset.
My second favorite wife, who is no-no from Die Buster.
Okay.
She is an ancient super weapon in outer space.
Can any woman live up to that standard?
No.
These women, man.
These fucking 3D women.
They're shit.
I'm talking about individual aspects here.
I need an ancient God weapon who can save the galaxy as my wife.
That's what I need.
I'm talking about individual aspects here.
Right.
Okay.
I'm glad that you agree.
I want to say that I'm really surprised to hear just how roundly and how basically all
of us don't even really see waifus romantically.
I thought that was the definition of a clone.
I see mine pretty romantically.
Well, in a sexual way.
To me, it's just like, yeah.
It's definitely, I don't see it as necessarily having anything to do with sexual attraction
or covetous romance or anything like that.
Like, to me, it's just a character that I relate to a lot or really like or respond to,
but it also still has to be a girl because I ain't no queer.
Of course.
But it's, yeah.
I mean, it's like, don't get me wrong.
I'm sure I have fapped to all of my waifus countless times.
Yeah, don't get me wrong.
I'm very attracted to all my waifus.
It's not that there's no sexual attraction, but here's, I was thinking about this just
a moment ago.
It's an incidental attraction.
I'm attracted to them because of the fact that I relate to them as characters anyways.
There's plenty of, because I would fapped to almost any character.
They don't have to be someone who would be my waifus.
Right, of course not.
Of course.
Sometimes the people you hate the most are the most satisfying.
It's just an extra layer of like the characters that you like.
Yes.
Yeah.
I was thinking about the fact, well, when Mage said that she wouldn't necessarily want
like fan art of her with her waifus, and I was thinking about how me and-
Yeah, our Channel Banners.
Yeah.
All three of us have like, you know, waifu pictures, and it started with Hippo.
He commissioned an artist to draw himself surrounded by his three waifus, and they're
just kind of like, because it's like pony version of him, and they're just kind of like
petting him, right?
Yeah.
And it's mostly just really cute and saccharine.
And then like, I got mine done, and it's me hanging out with my waifus in a bar just
getting drunk.
Yeah.
And yours, you know-
Mine is god worship, basically.
Yours has some implied like, you know, like, maybe, I don't know, necessarily sexuality,
but it's more like you own them or like you just have, like, here is what I have access
to.
They're basically being treated like commodities in that picture.
Well, I do, I do definitely own my waifus.
If anyone else shares them a waifu with me, then they do not count as their-
Now, hang on.
She's only mine.
That's an interesting topic, did you, the way that we clearly, you know, think about them
in at least slightly different ways or represent our relationship to them.
There's not the differences that were interesting to me so much as the similarity that none of
them are romantic or sexual.
That's true.
It's all just us with our waifus, like, surrounded by them.
Right.
And it's less of like, like, it doesn't feel like any of us are implying that we actually
ship ourselves with our waifus.
It's more like we want to.
Yeah.
We're portraying ourselves in a situation in which we're surrounded on all sides by
women that we love.
Right.
And you know, each of them in a different way conveys the sort of thing that we kind
of want to get from them.
Like Gibbons is kind of showing like he wants comfort from them or like, you know, you know,
that sort of thing.
See, I have an unfinished drawing that has been sitting on my desktop for like a month.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That Gibbon requested from me.
And it's him with Marceline, Vriska, and Undyne.
Yeah.
And he specifically asked for them, well-
Are they bullying him?
They're belittling me.
I know it.
But eventually, like, as I was making it, we eventually decided on, okay, we'll depict
them all, like, bullying him.
But the way I did it, like, wasn't mean enough and he said it wasn't mean enough.
That's very interesting.
Now, are you like-
Are you like-
I've got to say, we're running a lot about Gibbon right now.
Yep.
Are you sexually into, like, like, are you a masochist or do you just think it's funny?
I think it's funny.
I don't actually know whether I'm into that.
I just thought it was because, like, I'm-
Right.
Because, like, they all represent, like, something that I want to be.
I want to be really confident and cool like them.
But they're also women, so I like them sexually.
Uh-huh.
So it's like, they're my wife who's for that reason.
But yeah, the idea of them-
That sounds basically like how I feel about Akane from-
Like, I'm imagining, like, if I was there with them, that's what they would be doing to me anyway.
Like, so.
Okay.
But you know, positive thinking is important, you know?
No, but I don't know, I thought it was funny.
Well, I'm sure it is funny.
I'm sure it is funny.
It's just interesting to know.
I just think it's interesting that none of us, that, like, we easily could if we wanted
to have an artist draw us, you know, like, in a romantic situation with a character.
Of course.
Or, you know, a sexual situation with a character.
And all of us instead wanted just, like, yeah, just surround-
Like, it's like the image itself is suggesting that it's not that serious.
Of course, yeah.
It's just like, here's some anime characters I like, and ha ha, my avatars with them, you know?
Right, yep, yep.
It almost seems like there's-
I really could draw myself with any character I want because I have the power, but-
You do like to?
No, I could.
She could.
Oh, right, right.
It's like, but yeah, I'm one of the people who doesn't have the-
Yeah, and I think that shows our over-prevailing attitude.
So, in a way, I feel like-
It almost seems kind of, like, childish and lame to me to want to draw yourself fucking
a character that you like.
Yeah, I sort of agree on that front.
Well, fucking is one thing, and then there's, like, you, like, talking to them and blushing
or something.
Yeah, that's-
Yeah.
When I see someone draw their-
I think I'd rather have the fucking, personally.
When I see someone draw their OC, like, yeah, like, flirting with a character, it's really
bizarre.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not into it.
Like, having a real relationship with them, that's-
Like, that's kind of what I was, like, I wouldn't be-
I've been flirting with them, but like, I didn't like-
I like the idea, like, when you break the characters, like, what they're like in order
to make them-
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
That's a good point.
So, in reality, they would, like, toss me around and laugh at me.
I wonder if that makes us, if that, like-
Cause on the one hand, I'm thinking that, okay, obviously we're all coming to the same
conclusion because we're all pretty normal.
None of us are, like, really psychologically fringe people who would literally be talking
to their computer monitor and, like, having fucking tulpas of our characters and shit
like that.
Like, tulpas?
Oh, tell her what a tulpa is, Digi.
A tulpa is where you-
The tulpa majora is a part of a woman's anatomy.
The best way to describe a tulpa is, like, the adult advanced version of an imaginary
friend.
It's where you construct a character to the point that you believe that they are real
and you interact with them as though they were not a part of your own psyche.
I think the key to making this podcast good is that we all need to get a lot more honest.
At least a lot more.
I'm afraid to get honest.
I have demons in my brain.
I just want to say that I learned what a tulpa was.
I think I came to learn about it through your, like, hypnosis video.
Yeah, my hypnosis video.
I think I did too.
Yeah, because I made that video, and that's how I learned about tulpas, was that I made
the hypnosis video and I got a ton of comments about them.
And I was like, what the fuck are tulpas?
And then I did a bunch of research on it, and I was like, oh.
And I mean, I think they're really interesting as a concept.
The problem is, because I even went out of my way to, like, try to do a tulpa thing.
And I was just like, I can't because I'm too connected to reality.
Did you?
Yeah, yeah.
It's so clearly not a real thing that can happen, you know?
People believe in them in the way that they say, be careful when making a tulpa, because
if you make your tulpa too strong-
Oh, no.
You might never be able to get rid of it.
No.
So be absolutely sure you want this character in your brain before you commit yourself to
it.
My attempt at making a tulpa went like this.
I thought, I tried to imagine a character, and then the conversation I had with the character
went like this.
Basically, I imagined you, therefore, the only knowledge you can possibly have is knowledge
which I already have.
All right, all right.
They said, like, oh, well, you know, that's not necessarily, like, what if that wasn't
the case, if I had knowledge that you didn't have, would that not make me real?
You know?
And I was like, well, I mean, it's, like, if you can prove that, you know, but it's not
provable.
That reminds me of, this is off topic, but I was just at, like, a family party for, like,
Thanksgiving, and I was talking to my cousin and, like, catching up and stuff, and he was
telling me about how he was doing acid one day.
Yeah.
He was talking to a water bottle, and he was, like, and he started asking the water bottle,
like, what to do in his life and, like, to find some direction, and the water bottle started
giving him advice, but then he had this moment of clarity, like, wait a minute.
If the water bottle's only talking to me because I'm high on drugs, then that means the answers
are inside me all along.
Yeah, that's pretty much the end.
That's it.
And then he got, like, he gained, like, confidence, and, like, he, like, went on and he got a new
job and stuff.
Wow.
That's pretty cool.
So what do you tell me?
What do you tell me is that tulpas are real?
Is that what you're telling me?
Okay.
I think the majority of people who do the tulpa thing and post about how real it is, I think
they're posting that so that they can convince themselves more.
I think that's a major component of it.
Being in a community that reinforces your crazy belief is definitely helpful to keep
it alive.
I think the number of insane people online is a small percentage, and the people who
wish they were insane online is a much larger percentage.
Yes.
What's the distinction there?
You know, it's a fine line.
No, there's definitely a line.
So a tulpa is imagining sentience on an inanimate object, something like that?
No, it doesn't have to be an object.
A tulpa is just something, like, you imagine that a character you create in your head,
you are acting as though they are real and that they exist in the world, but you're the
only one who can see them and communicate with them.
Oh, is it kind of like the Tumblr head buddy thing?
Well, yes, yes.
Well, it's kind of like a headmate.
A headmate is something that you, like, don't, that you just have, whereas a tulpa is something
you consciously create.
Is that like the symbiote for men in black?
I probably, I don't remember.
Okay, now hang on, we're getting a little bit off topic.
I want to ask you something related more to the core issue here is, so are there people
who do waifu tulpas as in specifically?
Yes, absolutely.
They take a character from a series and then you've met them, really.
Oh, yeah.
There's a guy on the giant Twilight Sparkle doll.
Yeah, that guy.
That was who I was going to bring up.
90% of the people at BronyCon had waifu tulpas.
I absolutely believe that.
Okay.
Because it is the greatest achievement in the history of autism.
I want to ask a question, though.
How do you justify to yourself that if you have a tulpa, how do you reconcile that it
is the character from the show, even though you just made it up in your head?
How do you say that, okay, this is that person, not just a phony recreation I made.
By not thinking about that.
Okay.
That's the thing.
This is the first problem I have.
I think the issue here is that we are all very analytically-minded people.
The sort of person who makes a tulpa would not think that far.
You're probably right.
They have more important things, quote, unquote, to worry about.
That's what I meant.
They go on a date with their tulpa.
I don't have time for this.
That's what I meant when I was implying that the issue here is that we're all pretty normal.
None of us are very insane in that particular way.
So what you're saying is none of us are qualified to answer this question?
Well, I don't think any of us are- I think in order to do the job that most of us do,
we have to be pretty rational thinkers who are capable of empathizing with a broad range
of people and understanding a general normal psychology to even be able to communicate
with people through our videos unless people were watching us because we're insane.
I think our job description requires being insane but understanding it.
Yeah, maybe that.
I just want to say that CWC is on record as having had conversations with Sanichu and
Rosachu in which he biased him what to do.
Interesting.
When he went into Mary Lee Walsh's office and was berated for soliciting girlfriends with
a sign on campus, he mentally retreated from the scenario in real life to converse with
Sanichu and Rosachu who reassured him that he was doing the right thing and that Mary Lee
Walsh was a villain and the rest is history.
Have I told you, Ben, my theory that I think Christa Westerchandler is the main character
of humanity and when the rapture comes, we'll be judged based on how he was treated in his
life.
So frankly, I'm getting pretty worried.
I'm getting very worried.
We've earned this house down, man.
Oh shit, no!
Before we go too far down the CWC road, and we're probably around halfway through this
podcast, so I wanted to bring up a historical fact about waifus.
Another fun history lesson in waifus.
Cool.
We all are familiar with the anime director Hayao Miyazaki, the guy who is very staunchly
against Otaku culture and all modern anime.
However, in the 1960s when he was a teenager, there was a film that came out, I don't remember
the name of it right now, but it's one of the first big influential anime films to be
released.
And he said that he saw it in theaters like 16 times.
He kept going to see it because he was captivated by the main girl and he phrased it like this.
He said, she was like a girlfriend for me at a time when I didn't have a girlfriend.
Oh shit.
What a fucking hypocrite.
And he literally was inspired to make anime based on that movie, so he literally, when
he was a teenager, had no girlfriend, had a waifu from a movie, went to see it over and
over again to date his waifu and then was inspired to create anime.
That is a fantastic segue into the question I was going to ask next, which is, okay, all
of us have our relationship with waifus and we don't take it very seriously, but can you
have one and it be a healthy part of your life and could you see yourself theoretically
doing it?
What?
And more importantly, is it acceptable behavior and not acceptable, but can it be constructive?
Can it be constructive?
I can strongly feel that all of the greatest waifus that I've had and held dear in my heart
in my life have made me a better man and a better person.
I agree.
I don't.
Okay.
Well, I agree in the sense that-
I think that's gay as hell.
I think-
The story, I mean personally, the story of Nico Robin is something that's really, really
touched me in my life and I think made me reevaluate life in quite a few ways.
And I mean Robin is an extension of that story, she's a piece of it and I don't think she's
real or anything, but she affected me in the same way that that story did.
So in that, that's how I view her now in my head is the existence and the branching network
of what that character did to me.
So in that way, she definitely affected my life and I think made me a better person overall.
I don't think that's the same as her waifu.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's to say a good character in fiction changed you.
I'm going to go down this road.
I think I probably know the most about the subject of waifus, having read like countless
articles from people who do have like more serious waifus.
I know, Nate has a year list, so.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
I would check it out.
You know, again, there was that guy who married his Love Live game.
For those who don't, not Love Live, but Love Plus, the Nintendo DSI game.
Now, keep in mind, you know, this character, there's only two characters that you can date
in Love Plus.
I thought there were three, but whatever.
One of them, well, there might be three.
One of them is the really popular one, who like a lot of people consider their waifu.
She's like the tomboy character and this guy decided he wanted to marry that character.
Now what's interesting about that to me is that the character exists beyond in everyone's
DS.
Right.
But he actually left Japan to go to like a backwater country where this would be illegal
and he had a whole ceremony and married his DS character.
Did he marry the character?
The character, the character.
I mean, it's really hard to say because the character is just a fucking piece of code.
How can you marry someone without their consent?
I've wondered all these questions many times.
Yeah, that's a very...
I mean, in the game, she does say she loves you, so is that consent to marriage?
I'm not sure, man.
I really don't know, but like, you know, with a lot of people that I've talked to who
like do have waifu stuff, like generally, I think the state of mind you have to be in
to have a waifu is probably a state of mind where your life is not in the best condition.
I agree.
I think if you were in a healthy mind state and lifestyle, then this would not be something
that happens to you.
And like, because there have been times when I was younger where I like wanted to have
the waifu and have that like, you know, talking to my computer thing, like I wanted to be
crazy, like DeVu said, there's a lot of people on the internet like wish they were insane.
Because in a way, it seemed to me, looking in from the outside, like it's an escape.
It's a way to make things better.
You know, you're sitting around thinking my life sucks, I want a girlfriend, and what
if I could just...
What if I could just immerse myself in this narrative where I do have a girlfriend, you
know?
And the problem is that the attempt to do that, for me at least, just is like, I'm not
crazy.
I can't convince myself I'm crazy, you know, like I can't convince myself that I can do
this, you know?
Like, I know I'm saying crazy, which sounds like an insulting word, but like this is me
coming from a place of admiration for people who can do this, you know?
Like when I see people who like, who post like them, you know, sharing like a cake with
their waifu on her birthday, you know, they'll have the picture up and they have the cake
in front of their monitor and stuff.
I'm always like, man, I wish I cared about anything that much.
Now, hang on.
Okay, I want to play devil's advocate to that point a little bit and say, isn't it possible
to be of the mindset where you know that the character isn't real, but you choose to dedicate
yourself to them just to, you know, recreate that feeling of having someone special in
your life, maybe because you're really lonely or, you know, for whatever reason you want
to, and, and, you know, by having that action that you're taking, it's giving you a sense
of fulfillment.
And I mean, if you want to use the theories of like multiverse where like your character
exists somewhere out there, you know, in some other, if you, if you really do believe like
we realize that you're being invented, if you actually like realize that you're being
like strange by doing this, but doing it anyway, I don't know how many people actually do that.
And I guess that's, there's nothing wrong with that.
I don't even want to attach the word strange to it.
I personally don't do this at all, but it is, you know, different from normal.
Okay, I'm going to say, I think it could be a good thing, but you have to literally be
able to like, because you have to be able to convince yourself, right?
Like I said, I've been at it with the mindset of it sounds like a good thing, but I can't,
I cannot convince myself to have that kind of relationship with the character because
I am, I am too sure that she's not, that it's just not a thing.
You know, like in my mind, it could never be possible.
So like convincing myself that, that I'm talking to this character or something, it's, it's
just impossible.
I bet even for the insane people, it's probably life.
Well, it's like age.
Okay.
Well, all right.
I think Dave wanted to say something when Gabe was speaking, but because Dave was a bit
delayed.
So let's give a moment for Dave.
I think.
Oh, thank you very much.
I think even sane people, probably most of them, it's like lucid dreaming in the way
Maddox describes it anyway, where, yeah, I can do anything, but it's the same as just
imagination.
So they might imagine themselves actually having sex with their, their fictional character,
but it probably doesn't feel better than just tapping and thinking about it.
I mean, I've, I've imagined myself having sex with all my wife foods.
I just, I don't think that's the same as like, you know, I don't, I don't think that's the
same as like having a waifu.
Like, right.
So the question is, does this level of insanity add a greater level of pleasure and satisfaction?
You guys have thrown around the word insanity like it's like it's yesterday's core.
Okay.
Um, immersion.
Does that level of immersion add a greater level of satisfaction and pleasure or does
it merely subtract self-awareness?
Well, unfortunately, none of us are really qualified to speak on that, but I'd be more
than willing to believe that if you really believe it, it does make it a better experience
for you.
I mean, it's speculated on that all day, but, but frankly, I mean, I, I could see it almost
like, like you guys are talking about thinking that you have a relationship, but I almost
view it similar to like prayer.
I mean, I don't believe in God.
He doesn't exist.
Get over it.
Um, but so like, how is it, how can it be the same thing?
Wait, what if God is my waifu?
That's, that's, that's what I'm saying.
God is your waifu.
I'm just podcasting on God as a girl.
All I'm saying is another person I spoke to in the Brony community who we actually managed
to end up having on the pub crawl once for some reason, but it was a guy who, um, who
was trying to marry Twilight Sparkle.
And he had this elaborate, like, you know, idea of the character in his head and he would
talk about like there, how they had a life together and how she was the best thing in
his life and like they were getting married and she, you know, it was, it was clearly
a sexual relationship, but here's where it was, uh, interesting because yeah, this guy,
like he sort of got like, you know, his shit kicked in by the internet because of the fact
that, um, there was some artist who was drawing pictures of himself fucking Twilight, right?
Self insert, uh, you know, porn, um, and the guy who, you know, thinks he's marrying Twilight
goes into this dude's comments and goes on like a huge tirade about how, you know, Twilight
is his waifu and he doesn't, he, he's like, you know, pissed off that this guy is drawing
himself.
Yeah.
Slandering is why you remember.
Um, by the time I talked to this guy, cause I asked him about it and he was saying like,
you know, he sort of came to the conclusion in the long run that, you know, other people's
Twilight's aren't the real one, but his is.
Sure.
Okay.
Right.
I mean, that's the, that's the illusion you have to have for yourself.
Yeah.
I mean, he legitimately believes that the Twilight he's marrying is the Twilight from the show.
Is she, is she the one represented in the show?
The other ones are changelings.
Yes.
Okay.
The show is his waifu.
The changelings.
Who, who did it just hear cackling?
Who was cackling?
That was debatable.
Awesome.
Yeah.
His, his is the real one.
All the other ones are, are false, uh, and, and, and like, but he, he had gotten self-assurance
in that mindset.
Like he was like, yeah, now that I know, now that I feel that way, I am, I'm comfortable
and he, he really, like on the one hand, he made it out like, you know, like his relationship
with Twilight was like, like what, what was holding his life together.
But at the same time, it felt like this has to come crashing down because I imagine that
you go ahead.
Well, I wanted to say like a while ago, I think it's sort of like a bit of a devilish
sword in a way I can see how people can find comfort in believing that they're true and
going through the motions of pretending to have one.
Yeah.
And like it's not necessarily unnatural.
I mean, we, we used to play pretend as children, didn't we?
Right.
You know, if people, adults can still channel that imagination, then, you know, all good
for them.
But at the same time, when they're locking themselves in in this comfort box, they're
kind of locking themselves out of the rest of the world.
So, right.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
I think that, I think that even the most, even legitimately insane, I know you guys take
so much issue with that word.
I do.
Even legitimately troubled and, and, you know, people that don't see reality, even the most
insane among the must have moments of lucidity wherein they kind of can step back and look
and say, oh my God, it's all, it's all a lot.
Oh my God.
I'm not sure that I would agree with that.
I don't really know what insanity really is like, but, but I mean, I wanted to say the
whole reason I brought up the whole God thing was because I think your waifu life.
It's just that they don't post those thoughts on their tumblers.
Right.
Okay.
So they only post the time of like how happy they are with their waifu.
Like other times when they might be like having self-doubt and like it's, it's not real.
It's not real.
Yeah.
I'm crazy.
They probably don't publicize that.
Right.
Okay.
I'm making a case though for, for it being similar to prayer in that you are, it's sort
of a state of meditation where you're, you're, you're reflecting on this, you know, you
do these acts, you put the cake in front of your computer screen or whatever and it gives
you some solace, some peace in this topsy turvy world in which we live.
You know, is it, I don't, I've suddenly, Ben has suddenly made me realize why I failed
at this when I, when I wanted to, when I wanted to be crazy because yeah, it does take like
constant self-affirmation and I feel like to me the failure was more interesting.
Like the fact that I couldn't do it, that was the part I would have written about and
have written about.
Like I, I tried to be crazy and I failed like and it's upsetting.
I wish I was crazy.
Like I've written that post before rather than the one about how everything's fine.
And you know, yeah, I think, again, I'm, I'm taking this down to like we, we are all,
I said we are normal earlier, but really we're all very analytically minded.
Like more so than normal people.
And I think there's always a degree of delusion.
Now you brought up God earlier and like, you know, like the majority of people in this
world have deluded themselves into believing in a religion that is just some shit somebody
made up, but it makes it easier, it makes it easier to live their life.
You know, like that's why the reason people, the reason people get attached to religion
and DeVu was just saying this the other day as someone who is from a very religious household
and community that to him, it seems like it's mostly like for comfort and denial.
Well, and they can't, in the case of my family, I think it's like, it's for, it's like people
who if you can't deal with alcohol, alcohol is now bad.
If you can't deal with this, that is now a bad thing.
You know, that's the way that they frame it.
And I think there's a big difference between believing in at least the kind of Christianity
that I know of.
It's more like a story.
It's more like a narrative that perfectly, well, not perfectly, but tries to perfectly
make sense with the reality that currently exists.
It's like trying to retroactively impose a different story.
You're not trying to say that the sights and sounds and sensations are different than what
they actually are.
You're just trying to recontextualize them.
That's a big difference between that and people who think that their twilight plushie
is talking back to them.
Yeah, that's true.
But I still think that like it comes from a place of needing an escape from the world,
of not being able to reconcile what you believe the world should be with what the world is.
And I think that as an analytically minded person, to all of us, part of what makes the
world interesting is its flaws.
And looking at, we're sort of staring into the abyss.
It's kind of our job is to look at things and be critical of them.
There's a lot of people who, whenever you get that comment that's like, why can't you
just enjoy things?
Why do you have to think about it this way?
It's like, well, I don't have more value in a world that's just enjoyable all the time
than I do in a world that is what it is.
When I'm far more interested with the reality than what I wish that it was.
When I write erotic fiction, we're talking about white food, Jesse.
Hold on.
The Voo's trying to talk about erotic fiction.
We have half an hour.
I thought we were talking about the girls we like, and we're talking about...
This is all relevant.
But the Voo just started saying something about erotic fiction and I want to hear about it.
When I write it for myself, a lot of the times, it'll just end with the main character being...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where can I read your erotic fiction?
Let's get some links going in the description.
You have to boost your page free onto me, all right?
Now...
Rekt.
That'll be a tear.
So, a lot of the time, I end...
When I do finish them, the self-insert main character ends up totally destroyed for his
actions and punished.
And when I first went through puberty, half of my fantasies ended up badly as I was logically
thinking them through.
It was like, well, wait, no, he would totally...
Is that because you're self-punishing for, you know, having lust in your heart?
No, it's just me trying to think about the logical conclusion of what would happen here.
I would start fapping and then I'd think about the logic of it, like, wait, no, no, I've
got to spend another five minutes so that before this can make sense.
Because if it doesn't make any sense in my mind, then it doesn't work and I can't enjoy
it.
So, yeah.
That's the...
Okay, so hyperanalytical.
What would destroy them?
What would destroy your main characters in the end?
Is it treating them like real people?
Like, if you were with them, this would happen and this would happen and it wouldn't work
out?
No, no, I want to know specifically what caused their downfall.
Oh, yeah.
Jesus.
I can summarize a censored version of a story I conceived of, and I wanted to even draw
it all, but I'm a terrible artist.
So basically, there's this guy who's me, basically, with a different name, and he finds out about
this academy that happens to be a thing that he is really attracted to, but it's not something
that people think is a thing you can be attracted to.
All right, come on, let's truncate this a little bit.
And so then he signs up there and he enjoys it, but no one else knows he knows it, but
then eventually they realize that some people like it and so they shut down the whole academy
and it's probably his fault and he's sad.
That would be the conclusion of it.
Why did it shut down?
Because he enjoyed it?
Because they realized that he was into it.
That they realized that some people were into it, they didn't know who, and that made
it too messed up and weird, so they cancelled the whole thing and no one got to have the
academy anymore.
Well, why do they shut down schools because people like them?
You know what?
Wait, I don't think we need to actually break down all the logic of just fucking fan fiction.
That's fair.
Okay, okay.
I just wanted to understand what sort of downfall and self-destruction we were talking about.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, all right, fuck it.
Who's your fucking waifus?
Top waifus?
I was gonna say we end on that, but let's just do it now.
You go first, Angie.
Well, we're at, like, we're already an hour deep, so...
Well, 50 minutes is 10 minutes, that's a sixth of our runtime.
Nah, I've been only going for like 40 minutes since the actual start.
I see 55.
It's like, it's been like 50 minutes or so.
On my audacity.
Okay, let's go.
I'm going first.
You can look at my channel banner and see all my waifus, but my number one will always
be Nico Robin from One Piece.
All right, fair enough.
Yep.
Yeah, I've also got some of mine in my channel banner too, though not all of them.
I've, again, been really into, I can't understand what my husband is saying, just because the
character is so literally what I want out of a waifus.
That's like a season two.
Yeah.
Oh, I gotta watch that.
That is the character in all of fiction who I've looked at and been like, oh my god, this
is actually someone I'd want to marry.
Not just someone I'm attracted to for this or that reason, but her personality and the
way she acts.
I'm like, huh, like if this was a real girl and I was in a relationship with her, I think
I'd actually be happy with it.
Aside from that, I just generally like, I like small girls who are usually sort of lolly,
but not actually lolly.
Like they're actually older.
The thousand year old dragon little girl.
Yeah.
Or just like Komoi sensei, who again is like 40-ish, but she, you know, looks like a kid
or a recent waifu that I just discovered from Blazblue is Coco Noe, who's like this.
She's this little, you know, she's not even really just a really small woman, you know,
but she's got pink hair.
She's got glasses.
She's got a lollipop in her mouth, which just kind of looks like a cigarette.
So good enough.
She's got cat ears.
She drinks.
She eats a lot.
She's also into, I don't know why, but whenever there's like a girl character who eats constantly,
I always think that's great.
You know, she looks like the others now that I think about it.
She eats a lot.
She rides a scooter.
One of her attacks has her ride a scooter and she's like deadpan and kind of like snarky
and she's a scientist.
I didn't realize this is going to be describing all our best attributes of our waifus.
I'm just saying, she's like, this woman represents like every single like thing that I, like,
other than being like, it has to be either blonde or pink hair.
But other than that, like she has everything I could want out of a waifu.
So, so I think she's like, do not apply.
Yeah.
I think, I think if it's like going by just like aesthetic waifuness, like I just like
this character because they meet this, this and this criteria on like a checklist, Coco
Noe would be like the ultimate waifu for me.
Um, but yeah, so continuing to whoever wants it.
Okay.
Jesse, how about you?
Oh boy.
Well, I, I jotted down some names just so that I could keep track of them.
There's so many.
These are the waifus that I remembered instantly jumped right to my mind.
Tifa, Marceline, Tally, Raven, Fluttershy, Oscomisato, Noodle, and Helga, G, Pataki.
And that's, that's, that's all of them that matter.
All right.
Cool.
And, uh, I don't know.
There's not really like a common thread.
I mean, I could tell you why I like each of them individually, but I can't really look
at the whole of them and be like, well, this is what I value in a woman.
I think it goes a bit deeper than that.
I'm like you.
Mine are pretty.
Pretty, pretty eclectic.
Eclectic.
Yeah.
That's a good word for it.
They're all beautiful in their own way.
Mine have such a clear logical through line that I think anybody could figure out what
I like.
And most of it applies to real women as well.
So.
Sure.
Filthy 3D pigs.
Uh, how about Ben?
You got anyone you want to?
You know, I'm in try, I'm trying to think of characters and there's lots, there's lots
of female characters are I like, and there's lots of female characters that embody traits
that I find attractive.
Yeah.
But I can't really, I don't, yeah, I can't really think of anyone who I'm like, oh, I
wish I, you know, I would date her or like she represents, you know, my ideal woman or
anything like that.
Just close your eyes.
What about Haruko from Pooley Cooley?
We were both pretty into her.
No, she's cool, but I'm not that attracted to her.
Yeah.
Right.
Uh, if you, I mean, the, if you read in my comic, if you read the, the first chapter,
the girl on the beanbag was designed with like what I find like visually attractive
in mind.
So I guess that you could look to this.
So just literally Susie from Game Grumps, whatever she looks like, um, but yeah, and
she doesn't have, she doesn't have any personality or anything.
So it doesn't really.
Yeah.
She has, she has like no, I would totally date my Mimi from FLCL because she's broken
and terrible and I love that.
I would rather date Nina Mori from FLCL.
Nina Mori, Nina Mori is the best Nina Mori is just kind of a child.
That's a good, that's a good point.
She's a child to you.
She's a woman to me.
Did you?
I am a big fan of broken and terrible.
Yeah.
That's something that's definitely something I look for in a character.
I like, I like it when a, when a girl is broken and terrible in just such a way that
it's not quite your problem, but you can make it your problem.
Dude, that's exactly what Nina Mori is.
And she has that, oh God, which is wearing those, those pajamas with now to holy shit.
That's the sexiest scene in all of the animation.
Okay.
I, I did in fact, as a child because like it's funny, I have a much harder time finding
it attractive now because I cannot like, not me dog, they're very like, well, the characters
in that show are just very young to me.
We're like part of the narrative.
I feel like I am them when I watch it.
I don't know.
I mean, I, I, when I was younger, I kind of didn't understand FLCL as much.
So like, I think I only really understood it at an age where I couldn't relate to it
as much.
Yeah.
But like when I was young, that Nina Mori scene was like, oh my God, this is the, I literally
did for years call that the hottest scene in animation, just the way the pajamas don't
quite fit her and everything, but when I think about like lollies and stuff, I kind of think
of like this quote from what it's like Tuesdays with Morty or something.
It's some book about an old guy and he gives the speech about how like he's, he, how he's
every age and like he enjoys like putting himself in the position of like any age in
his whole life when it's appropriate.
I appreciate like, like, uh, Nia from Gernloggan or, or Nina Mori who are like, when it comes
to anime, like I had a friend who was saying like, you know, like, I don't think it's weird
to be attracted to because most anime characters are high school age and he's like, it's not
really weird to be attracted to high schoolers because I remember that when I was in high
school, I was attracted to these girls.
Right.
I totally agree.
I mean, your tastes can change, but you can also put yourself into that mindset and like,
yeah, I don't know.
I find it harder to be attracted to anime characters who actually act their age.
But if I can like, it depends if, if they're characters who like, you know, who, who like
are younger, but they act like adults, then in my mind, it's like they're not like, you
know, the numbers, right?
I mean, they're fucking drawing.
So however they act is going to dictate, you know, best waifu Angelica pickles.
I know she's three years old, but when I'm watching the show, I feel like I'm Tommy.
I feel like I'm one.
So she's a woman.
Get the fuck out of here.
That's what that's what all grown up was for.
So that we could finally fuck her.
That was the goal.
All grown up when she became when she became 11.
So we could finally play ball.
Shall we?
Shall we move on to the next person?
Yeah.
Who wants to go next?
Me.
My.
Who does one of my favorite girls from from this year was this was the main character
of a game called Mecha Nika.
Her name is Nika, not to be confused with some comic called Nika.
I love her because she goes out of her way to be as spiteful as I can be.
And her rationalization for hating things is as in depth and insane as it is with me.
So I find that extremely relatable.
I don't think a relationship with her would work at all.
But I find that very captivating personally.
Number two is Maya Fey from the Phoenix Wright games, because I think she is
ultimate in what I'd want from maturity from a woman, because she goes through so
many terrible things, but she always acts like it's not getting to her.
And she's really funny and fun to be around all the time.
And the number one woman is Adeline from the Kirby games.
That one from the Nintendo 64.
Haven't even played it.
Oh, dude, what?
OK, that's just random as all.
I only know her from fan art and from watching Digibro playing it.
From my Let's Play.
Yeah, like literally commented on like one of the first episodes of the
Kirby 64 Let's Play, like, oh, my God, how have I never seen this character before?
I would love with her over the next few days.
Like he was commenting about being deeper and deeper down the ramp.
How do you spell her name?
I still can't remember.
But OK, ADELINE.
Wait, I didn't say that again.
Addeline.
Just so I had a line.
OK, OK, super passionate about drawing and she will go to an ultimate
dimension just to study and she will go along and like not talk much.
So I could probably just talk to her constantly and she would just smile
and listen and stuff and that'd be great.
And this fan art is pretty cute.
She just seems so passionate about what she does.
And she's so good that she can make her paintings come to life.
Being passionate is a very attractive quality.
When she gets corrupted by a demon in the beginning, she draws something
that's censored out so she could probably draw porn.
Oh, dude, you know, that was a dick.
Yeah. And and she has a really great tomboyish
effect with being short haired, but she's got a skirt which conflicts with that.
And that's adorable. So yeah.
OK, I actually don't agree that being passionate is an attractive quality.
That's because you want your women to have no personality.
We established that I would kind of feel I would be I would be annoyed
by a girl who wanted me to be into whatever she was into.
I would rather one. No, I mean, no, no, no, no, no, it's not how it works.
I was just willing to go along with whatever.
Someone with a path in life for the mission.
Yeah, I think I find passion attractive, not out of wanting them to be into.
Like I don't want necessarily that they're into what I'm into or I'm into what they're into.
Yeah.
Like I do find it annoying if if a girl was like, you have to be into this
because I'm into this. Of course.
What I do like, however, is that I think the the people who can best
understand passionate people are other passionate people.
Totally, totally.
Where like the last girlfriend I had, she did did not understand art at all.
No understanding of artists, the artistic process or passion.
She had no drive for anything, no passion.
Yeah, it's going to get frustrating.
Really, really difficult to communicate why I would want to do certain things
or feel certain ways about things.
It was impossible for her to understand.
And it's pretty bad when you're trying to do something and this person demands
your time for whatever reason.
And then you're like, no, I have to do this.
This is my thing.
I think if I dated another artist, we would both spend a lot of time
dedicating ourselves to our art.
And to me, the ideal relationship is not one where you're fucking on each
other's nuts all the time.
It's more one where you both are sort of Jesus fucking loud as motorcycle.
You're both sort of doing your own thing and and progressing in life
and having this like narrative.
But you're also supporting each other on the side and just sort of,
you know, having each other around, not so much that your life is based
on the other person, but that each of you has your own life that just happens
to be connected, you know, which I think is how all of our friendships are.
You know, pretty much that's exactly how it is.
Probably nobody else will agree with.
But if I had, I think in a girlfriend, I would actually prefer her
not to understand me and to just sort of be kind of mystified by me.
Well, then why do you hate women so much?
I think you would.
I think you want that until you have it because that's exactly what I had.
My my ex-girlfriend was very mystified with everything I did.
And very like intrigued.
But the lack of understanding of why I do anything I do became a huge hurdle
where it's like she cannot understand why it would take me an amount of time.
Like this is how she would always phrase it about videos coming out.
She said, as far as I'm concerned, it doesn't exist until it shows up
in front of me, you know?
Well, that's how the viewership is like.
So she's a total viewer as opposed to a creator herself.
Right. No, she's never made anything in her life.
She has no creative spark whatsoever.
And I think it was so difficult for her to comprehend how or why I would make things
or like what the process was or where I came from when I was doing it.
She had no comprehension.
I can't even be friends with someone with no artistic spark.
Like everyone.
Yeah, I fucking hate people with no artistic spark.
Fuck them.
Did you and I have had this conversation before where I sort of view
non-creative people as not human?
I would agree with that completely.
I'd say that's an essential part of being human, having a creative drive.
Absolutely. Yeah.
All right, made sure your wife is.
Oh, gosh, I have many.
But if you care to share it, I'll say a few.
Well, Papyrus is already stated.
Adorable cinnamon roll, precious innocent.
All right.
He's just so adorable.
Anywho, moving on.
His googly eyes.
And his and his passion.
Real quick, what what kind of voice do you think Papyrus should have?
Because it's not like they're arguing about this.
No, he does not have a skeletal voice.
Wait, wait, let her answer. Damn it.
I want to hear her opinion.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you were asking.
No, I want Major's opinion.
Oh, I've already heard your fucking.
Yeah, we argued about this.
That's why I want her input.
I honestly, I don't mind either.
Either the first time I heard someone voice Papyrus,
they had like this rather lowish sort of voice.
I they were sort of making one character.
I wish I knew what character it was from from movies.
But anyway, so they had a low voice for him.
And I think it fit pretty well.
But then I heard someone try something similar to a Skeletor.
And that also fit pretty well.
I was like, oh, OK, that does work for the Skeletor.
We have got to have a podcast discussion about the God awful voices
that everyone has for Undertale characters.
All the fan art, all the Undertale fan stuff is shit.
It makes me sick for my stomach.
I like the same thing. Not yours, mate.
I like this great.
I like the same thing.
You like the stupid Skeletor.
OK, no, wait, no.
That's true.
I think that he clearly has a Skeletor voice.
I mean, come on, it's obvious.
That doesn't necessarily mean that I prefer it.
The fact that he says, yeah, yeah, it makes a Skeletor to me.
But also, yes, I think it's meant to be sort of obnoxious.
He does speak in all capitals and like the text noise he makes when he speaks.
And he does have a very sort of that high
falutin, like, yeah, kind of personality.
This isn't the Papyrus Voice Podcast.
This is the Papyrus Voice Podcast.
I want to talk about video games.
We're done with that.
Let's just continue with the wife.
Go on, Mage.
Let's name some others.
OK, so from assassination classroom, Karma, if anyone knows that, Redhead.
Redhead, Psycho.
Oh, the bed.
Yeah, OK, OK.
Super smart, full of himself, guy that's really good at everything.
Basically Sasuke.
The last episode I saw was the one where he shows up.
Oh, yeah, we should continue watching that.
But anyway, he's he's he's he's good.
He's a good character.
I like him a lot.
He's such a little shit.
Anyone else near and dear to your heart?
Jenos from One Punch Man.
He he he's he's such a good wife.
He's a good fuckboy.
There's no doubt about it.
He's pretty Moe in the way that he completely fails and everything.
Yeah, in spite of being amazing.
It's endearing, though.
It's quite endearing about that.
I like it.
Precious.
And he's like the way he's devoted his sensei to the borderline creepy.
It's just hilarious.
I really I really need to watch the anime.
You sure do.
It's great.
I don't have watched it yet.
I've read I've read the manga.
Well, I did too.
But I and at first I thought it was whatever.
Who cares what I think?
Let's move on.
Tom, white foods.
What do you got for us?
Um, I've been thinking about this the entire time because I don't I mean,
I guess like like rarity seems like the obvious answer.
But like so much of my like rarity bias that I put out there was like
influenced by the audience like observing that I had it.
So I would like I say magnify it for the sake of entertainment
and then it just kind of spiraled out of control.
But I think I guess the character, I would say, definitely became like
waifu tier status was probably Tali from Mass Effect.
I really liked her.
I sure that's a good one.
Oh, she is definitely.
I'm surprised I wasn't on Jesse's waifu.
It was on my list.
I said it.
It was.
Yeah, I'm stealing your wife.
So Tali was fucking awesome.
Now, the great thing is when we can all come together and appreciate truly top tier.
Yeah, I think we all have a couple that we share amongst ourselves.
Yeah.
You know, I don't know if anyone shares any of mine.
I don't know.
I don't want to share any of mine.
I think I think mine are from two obscure of shows.
I don't think I'd be able to deal with women who smoke.
I just don't think I'd be able to deal with that's true.
I don't care for did you like smoking girls, though, for whatever reason?
Yeah, I do.
I do.
I think it's fucking cool.
That's why I do think the girl doing a locked room.
And my husband is saying is very like attractive, but I don't know.
I'm just I guess I'm just not into the.
I think I could probably pull some waifus that I that I would share with people
if I went like beyond the like top five ones that I like always think about,
you know, like like Kiruno, your favorite girl of all time from everyone's favorite.
You know, it was not a waifu or emo.
She's just the best show.
She's just my favorite main in a fighting game.
I'd like to change all my waifus to just her because she is the best.
Hey, guys, I have an idea about how we can, you know, speaking of male waifus,
I think I know how we can become male waifus for a lot of women and gay men.
How's that?
In this podcast is by talking like, like, like, like potentially
flirtedly to to mage so that any women who can put themselves.
OK, right.
And on that note, thanks for watching, everybody.
That's the way we need this podcast for this waifus date.
We haven't even gotten to him yet.
Oh, I'm sorry. Good. Good. Please.
Friska is my favorite because she's the Walter White of Homestuck.
She did nothing wrong.
And anybody who thinks she did is a doesn't understand.
Yeah, I love how this is.
Making a statement both about both stories, like both Walter White and
yeah, you're doing that.
They did nothing wrong.
Friska is Friska's way, way less morally ambiguous than Walter White.
Walter White did way worse.
Now, now see just a minute here.
He certainly did not.
Walter was right.
Who else you got?
Let's not get into this.
There's basically just any character that starts off as a bitch
and sometimes just ends as a bitch and is a female.
That's Kira, though. You've described Kira, though.
OK, maybe I like that.
I don't think he'd like.
I don't think she's the right kind of bitch.
Well, they have to be.
She fits this criteria.
You just specified they have to be sort of.
Basically, everything that I'm not.
They have to actually be cool.
They have to be confident and arrogant.
Kira knows a model.
She's super cool.
She loves video games.
So she loses out on the like actual, like, OK,
compare her to fucking Friska.
Like Friska is actually cool.
Like she does cool things in the narrative.
She's no Kira, though. She's no Kira, though.
She's the best.
Didn't she?
Didn't Friska get like one of the like the biggest
wham moments in the story?
It was like she executed a plan
and like someone achieved God tier as a result.
And it was like, well, she achieved God tier, but she was a little too cool
by that point.
Here's the thing about bitches and going back to analytical logic.
You know, people who are jerks ignore ninety nine point nine percent of the world.
You like women who would give attention,
bitchy attention to certain guys doesn't make sense.
So my fantasy of a bitch would be one who somehow needs some skill that I have.
Need some like she needs you to teach her like she hates you,
but she has to keep you around because of a skill you have.
Or that I mean, that doesn't make sense that she just can't.
So she just basically have basically.
She's a nymphomaniac and you have the greatest dick in the world.
And she cannot settle for anything less.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hang on. What do you just described of holding out a resource
to make a woman have a relationship with you?
That's what they call rape.
And that's the whole patriarchy.
I don't want to hear any more.
It is very coercive.
More like she like hates the world,
but she has to make YouTube videos, proclaiming it.
And she needs someone to edit them.
And so, you know, like they don't like rapist.
And she can only only pick you.
So are you saying that if Digi was a girl, he'd be your waifu?
Nice. Yeah.
What did the Describe?
Isn't that like, uh, Kirino?
I don't know. It's all Kirino.
She's the best waifu.
We can all agree on that.
OK. And on that, it feels like we've run out of steam.
Let's wrap this thing up.
Anyone got any last minute things to say they want to say about waifus?
Because that's what this was about.
Waifus, have we come to a consensus?
Akane is my waifu.
I just want to say, fellas, don't make tulpas of your waifus.
Please.
I'm going to go and make a tulpa right now.
That's a risky game.
What if you can't get rid of it?
If you're thinking about making a tulpa of your waifu,
bear in mind that everything she thinks is actually things you're thinking
and you're really fucking yourself.
Yeah, you're wrong.
Even if you can, even if you can somehow summon the force of will
to un-tulpa yourself, that's murder.
That's true.
You're losing that game coming and going.
You can create life you're responsible for.
No matter how real or fake it is.
Amen.
All right.
Well, thanks for watching, everybody.
That's it for this week.
If you've got any topics you want to suggest,
put them in the comments down below and we'll add them to our topic list.
All right, everybody.
Say goodbye.
Bye.
Goodbye.