Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever, and let's see what we've got going on here. Rubstands together greedily.
We've got Ben Saint. Fresh off his philandering and other podcast territory. And we've got
Tom Oliver.
There's some reason today I feel more financially solvent. I can't imagine why. Maybe you guys
have to figure that out, yeah.
Doesn't solvent mean to have fluidity of one's way?
What do you mean?
I thought financially solvent meant you were just more financially stable. You had more
income, or your finances were in order.
Apparently, I just googled it. Financial solvency means that an individual can pay all bills
on time with cash to spare.
You mean because there's only three of us?
Exactly.
Oh, of course.
That's very true.
Wink, wink, nudge, nudge.
And I gotta let everybody know. We're up to a great start, because even if your stray
layabout, lazy-ass PCP member rolls on in, they've already incurred a hefty penalty on
their income. And that goes straight into our bank account, baby. So I could not be happier
about it.
I'm making hefty fees. So, not actually. But so you guys know, and I have to announce
this, I legendarily found the podcast and was on the Pizza Party podcast. I've been
there. I've seen it with my own two eyes.
I'm stressed.
Frankly, I think you're talking mad shit. I still don't, but I've never seen it with
my own eyes.
Go check out Rebel Taxi in the latest episode of the Pizza Party podcast.
That makes sense when you think about it. If the podcast takes place in a taxi, it's
constantly moving, how would we ever be able to find that?
Me and the boy, Cheesy Manfredo.
Fair.
Fucking around.
Well, frankly speaking, I mean, with the dimensional merge so well underway, is it surprising that
a fictional podcast would suddenly become all too real?
Like I said in this very chat, the night that Ben announced it, this is the most convincing
evidence for the dimensional merge I have seen so far.
Indeed.
I don't know. There's lots, I mean, there's lots of great evidence.
Well, I must tell you this, Chris.
He's not a custorian like you, so from my peasant eyes.
There's no shortage of evidence.
I was going to ask, I don't know, I thought I'd wait until now. I'm very curious as to
know how it is, not only that you discover the podcast, but we're then also on it, because
that, I mean, surely that's more than just a simple operation.
Well, I think Cheesy got on it, and I think maybe they told him like he could invite someone
else.
The lowly Cheesy Manfredo.
I don't really know exactly what the discussion was like.
I just know that he came to you and was like, hey, Ben, I got a spot on the Pizza Party
podcast and you can be on too if you want, and I was like.
So it was his initiative.
Yeah.
I see.
I was just along for the ride.
Do you have any idea what Cheesy's credentials or in what way he got on?
I just don't.
I didn't think he was much of a...
Well, I know that he bought like an ad on a previous episode, like he paid for a plug
for Bongo and Luna, and I'm not sure if maybe he just levied.
I think he, I don't know where, how it moved to.
Okay.
Funny story, it seemed like they thought that I was going to be like promoting my Kickstarter,
which like they delayed for two weeks.
So I was supposed to go on two weeks earlier, but for like two weeks, they were like, no,
we're not doing it.
So by the time we finally did it, the Kickstarter was ending that day.
So then I got into the call and I'm like, hey guys, what's going on?
And they were like, oh, don't you have a Kickstarter?
And I'm like, yeah, but it's ending today.
And they were like, what the fuck?
How are you going to promote it if it's ending today?
I'm like, I don't fucking know.
Were they angry?
Why are you asking me that stupid question?
I see.
Okay.
Yeah.
By the way, I know they run, they're into a tight ship over there like we do.
Perhaps not.
They were fine.
They seemed like, they seemed maybe not annoyed, but like confused and like, I don't know.
I don't know what I was supposed to say to that question.
They are in a totally different dimension than they usually are.
That must be jarring for anyone.
It seems like there's a pattern here or there's an expectation of behavior.
It sounds like their podcast is simply a vehicle for people or among other things, I'm sure,
to pay for ad space and like to find that you aren't there for that explicit purpose
is like a shock is an awe inspiring fact.
And I'm just thinking, why aren't we capitalizing on this obviously vibrant market to make vast
sums of cash advertising products we have no interest in or quality control over?
It sounds like the way forward for me, right?
This episode is brought to you by Squarespace.
Nate, have you heard that Squarespace is an online learning community and you can get
a month free from our affiliate link or something?
I don't know.
That's Skillshare, Ben.
You fucked up our sponsorship.
Shit!
I can't wait for that.
For that wonderful...
It's okay.
We got Purple Mattress lined up.
We got ExpressVPN.
It's all okay.
What's Purple Mattress?
There's going to be a glorious day where our patrons are paying us vast sums of cash
to advertise to them from other people who are also paying us for those advertisements.
Look, we already fucked this up.
I want to get them coming and going.
This is why our voicemail bot is failing us because right now we have a free avenue
for advertising.
We need to fucking clamp that down and put a price tag on it immediately.
You know, unironically true.
You know, speaking of advertising, this is actually an interesting thing.
I'm in...
Actually, I've been a little bit bad.
I've been a little bit unprofessional getting back to this guy.
But I was talking.
I don't know if I'm...
I probably just shouldn't say what company it is.
But I was talking with a company.
I just got a message on my email, best guy ever mailed or whatever, and it was a company
a little bit different from your normal shitty, like, hey, work with us, hey, advertise our
terrible thing.
This one is something I've used before, and I'm, at least in theory, kind of a fan of
the concept of, and their proposal was like, hey, do you want to not advertise, make a
video about this thing?
And I know Gibbs done that before about like his own.
Are they going to pay you for it?
I mean, that would be the idea.
Yeah, they'd give you actual money.
And I was thinking to myself, you know, Weagawa is a soulless shill product churned out to
make a product.
Churned out every week without fail.
That's right.
It's eaten up your entire creative uvra and has taken over your life.
Well, but Ben, I've made space finally.
I made a smash video about sands.
That was nice.
That's pretty good.
I've made space.
So what you're saying is we're going to get a fleshlight video very soon.
That's what I've gotten from it.
Here is the thing about it.
So I'm negotiating with these guys a little bit, and the important sticking point was
they were like, they wanted to be like 80% of like, I'll say like gameplay or like featuring
this thing prominently and it's not a fleshlight video, but I mean, it's in the ballpark kind
of it's like an adult thing, which I don't care about.
And obviously on YouTube, you can't make like actually pornographic videos.
So you have to like censor shit or whatever.
But I'm like, we are what isn't exactly that format.
Is it a porn game or something?
Can you tell us?
It's in that sphere.
Yeah, it's in that sphere.
Okay.
Like imagine it was me doing like a review of Sengoku Rants, which it's not, but it'd
be something kind of like that.
So I'm just, I don't know, I'm trying to think if it works out, but if it does work out,
it seems like I could make a good amount of money doing this.
So I'm very interested in finding a way to make this work.
But I don't know.
I've never done it before.
I'm a little nervous about credibility.
You just got to jump in, dude.
You just got to jump in.
Your credibility is down the shit.
I mean, it's We Agua.
Your weekly show is not in here.
It's We Agua, so.
It's fine.
Yeah.
Half the audience won't even notice it happened.
They'll be like, I knew We Agua came out.
No.
That's absolutely true.
Or you could just make a whole new show, like a show specifically for shilling things.
So the expectations are set from the beginning.
Well, We Agua was designed to be the shill show from the start then.
Then you're on brand.
You're on brand already.
It's true.
Well, speaking of shilling, I want to say one thing.
The Kickstarter for this weekend is the last weekend that I'll be accepting late PayPal
payments for Kickstarter donations for people who miss the Kickstarter.
I know there were some people who were messaging me during the campaign, like, I don't have
a credit card.
The website doesn't work or something.
Can I use PayPal?
And I was like, yes, hold on until after the campaign's over.
Now is the time.
So if you missed out on it and you're like, oh, maybe I should have wanted to support
my favorite online creators, then you have like two days.
You have until Sunday after you hear this.
And then I'm saying, like, fuck it, no more.
I'm glad the slimeoid has gotten over his fucking addiction and is now supporting you
financially.
You know, I forgot.
Me?
The swimeoid.
Oh, yeah.
Uwupiti.
Uwupiti, yes.
A charity case.
I want Uwupiti to hang out with tiny baby Ben St. and pall around and have a playday.
Well, I mean, I'm not sure if, I mean, the timeline has diverged.
There's a timeline where it died.
There's a timeline.
There's at least one timeline where it lives.
So at least two, I believe.
It's very confusing.
Well, I don't know, maybe the two, maybe the Izumi scenario and the red man scenario
happened.
Maybe, maybe Izumi fished him out and then, or fished it out and then something else
knocked it back in and then while Izumi was fighting against N7, that's when red man
put it in the jar.
I don't know.
Right.
It's hard to say.
We're just scholars of these.
We're just, yeah, we're just prophets.
We don't write this shit.
We just report it.
Had that happened last episode?
I forgot if we discussed the incredible amount of, of like, you guys all making different
shit about it.
I don't think it did.
That was like early this week, right?
Yeah.
I think, yes, yes.
I'm pretty sure I did that Tuesday, Tuesday or one day or something like that after reporting.
This has been my favorite thing about this whole saga so far.
I mean, you know, Chris did the whole genocide, excellent work, Chris, but now you guys all
making your different shit, like, and what I said, I mean, give me this comic, Ben was
doing his thing, really cool.
But then when I saw Tom making his like animated Izumi crossover, I want to know how long that
took Tom.
I want to know what was the inspiration because I was fascinated.
I must take it a hull.
Should we explain like what this is?
We probably should.
Yes, yes.
We should leave the groundwork.
So the final stretch goals for the Vapors 2 Kickstarter.
And don't worry, everyone.
We won't bore you with endless war talk.
It fills you with rage and piss and vinegar.
Audience, I literally hate you.
There was a, the final Kickstarter stretch goals.
I didn't really have anything else to do, so I made up a thing where like, oh, if we
hit this stretch goal, we'll make it a meme, that's the way, we'll send this Swymoy to
college.
We'll get him in education to increase his waver value and, and then they hit the goal
and I was like, well, shit.
I was like, well, he's looking to enter the workforce, but it's too much for a slime
like him.
He develops a terrible sludge dust addiction and now he needs to go to rehabs.
We got to send the Swymoy to rehab and we didn't make it.
He didn't make it.
So it was, it was over for poor little Uwupati and it decided that it had, it had hit walk
bottom and it had nowhere to go.
So it was about to dissolve itself in the slime way or in the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the slime corp vats.
But how much did you make all told at the end of this?
Oh, 12,000.
So $12,000 exactly as much as I would get in one year under a Yang presidency.
So no more, no less exactly.
Literally it's like, it's like 50, well it's actually like, um, $12,000 and 50 cents, but
you can't see the 50 cents.
Yeah.
That's like, you know, you get your Yang money and then you happen to find a quarter a couple
times a year.
Yeah.
So, uh, we don't need Yang anymore guys.
We've solved the problem.
We just need a Kickstarter once a year.
Yeah.
Just vote Kickstarter for president.
Um, that's how he's going to get with the millennials.
He's got to get down with them like, no, this is, this is just a Kickstarter.
So yearly Kickstarter for your life.
We do it.
No more taxes.
We will, we'll end taxation.
We will just crowdfund like roads and like every end like hospitals and stuff.
Make it voluntary.
Yeah.
Um, uh, and, and, um, wait, what was I explaining?
So you were explaining how we disfigured to rehab her.
Yes.
He was going to dissolve and it was going to dissolve itself, but then hippo comes in
with a comic showing some mysterious red handed figure, saving it from and putting it in a
bottle.
And then Tom comes in with another, uh, a 3D, uh, model video, uh, showing a zoomie
comes in and fucking gives an inspiring anime speech and convinces it to want to live after
all.
Uh, oh, this was all after Chris.
Chris had responded saying like, don't guilt me, don't guilt me, Ben, Saint, don't, I,
I have foreseen all possible timelines and the timeline where the sly moid was survived
was terrible.
It would have been disastrous for everyone.
So hippo comes in and of course does it.
So the sly moid survives, but then the final panel is like, would have been terrible for
everyone.
Like the timeline is doomed.
We've doomed the timeline.
What do we do?
Um, this is all developing.
I'm like, I'm like, I was just making some more of this, this shit right before we started
recording and, um, I made some, I'm just like, I made some shit.
I put it out.
I'm just going to see how Chris reacts and then I'm just going to respond to that.
Right.
I have a couple, I have a couple of different ideas for like, for like how to resolve it.
Cause I need to convince her that this is happening.
I need to convince her that she needs to fear the events that may transpire.
So it's all highly reactive.
So Tom, just tell me how much did that take?
What kind of effort was involved in that animation?
Okay.
So I woke up at like 9am and I saw the tweet of the sly moid dying.
I was like, this cannot stand it.
I was like, I'll just do a little four panel comic doing something cute.
Were you in the middle of making it?
And then you saw hippos response and you were like, darn.
I did.
I did message hippo like 15 hours into working at it.
And I was like, you fucking bitch.
Cause like it started as a comic.
I'm like, no, comics on enough.
I got to go all out.
So I just said, I'm just going to throw this whole day away.
So for 20 hours straight, toiled over a hot blender and just made it all.
Damn.
It was an idea that went too far.
Uh, yeah.
How are you feeling?
It was super cool seeing that pop up on my feed though.
Yeah.
It came together pretty well.
Anything against the kill the kill soundtrack just automatically is good.
So I couldn't use.
You know, I suspect, I suspect this is my current fan fiction.
I think that, uh, our little whoopity will somehow travel back in time and like found
slime corp or some sort of, you know, like Bioshock infinite level, terrible plot.
Well, it wasn't that bad, but you know, there's clearly they have an important role to play.
No doubt.
My favorite thing about, okay, okay, whoopity is like, you can, okay, you can see it's brain.
Like you can see it's brain, right?
And my head cannon is that it is like literally just like a P is just like fluid.
It is just basically a sack of fluid with the thinnest of membranes surrounding the
fluid and just like the brain just kind of floating loose inside, just like you have
them lying on his side.
The brain is still oriented upright.
Yeah.
Clearly.
Cause the brain is fried from all the sludge dust.
So it's in there.
Just kind of like shaking around with the lightning bolts going like, yeah, the brain's not connected.
Like someone asked why it had a spine and I was like, cause what else would the brain
connect to?
But like the spine doesn't connect to anything.
It's just floating around in there.
I don't know if it's eyes are actually eyes or just like buttons that someone's stuck
on.
Whoopity is a mystery for sure.
I'm like actually upset.
I wasn't able to model.
The original idea was to model the brain and have like a particle system make the bubbles
and everything animate.
But I would have taken so fucking long, I mean, I don't blame you for just like make
it green.
Like you get it.
You should make Tom, I'm just going to throw this out there.
You should make some sort of like secret area in Izumi where you can break the wall and
you can find Uwupity in there with the model you've already made and you can just kill
them for some quick cash.
Secret boss Uwupity.
Oh, he gets a whole intro.
He gets a full boss bar.
But then there's one of those ones that takes one slash to kill and you got the big victory
fan.
Oh, like, like Zote.
Exactly.
Yes.
And then you can get another dream sequence like with Zote where he gets full power slime
oid mode and he's a big Chad.
These are all you.
You're welcome to all these ideas, everyone.
I encourage you.
I'm seeing from modest view.
I'm seeing maybe like a tiny little Uwupity, like sitting in the little cockpit of like
a giant mech or something.
Yeah, that's good.
Maybe that had built itself with its extensive education.
Oh, you know, that actually like that's seen from the last Jedi where fucking the robot
like what's what's the name fucking not R.C.B.
He's in the fucking Walker and it like it pulls off the Walker and just B.B.
Eight moving around the ATSC just to have a mech with a Uwupity.
Yeah.
Yep.
And I've met good he should they should it.
Oh, so much a draw comic of him like in Lecture Halls with a Temmie because they both went
to the same super fast school.
Obviously, one day education, 10 minute education, some.
I mean, especially in New Los Angeles City, like going to class is not really the point.
Just the point is just can you pay them enough.
And of course, that's how you get your diploma.
That's what it is.
That's what it means.
You had to be smart to get that money in the first place, right?
So like clearly you deserve the diploma.
Like I forget what since we live in a meritocracy and all that wasn't it
There's like something where it's like you want to get the ultimate. Oh, actually here's one example dragon ball Z
Is like you have to climb that tower. Sorry the beginning of dragon ball
You have to climb this tower to get the mystical water, but turns out the mystical water does nothing
It's the strength that took to climb. Yes, it was the strength that took to make a whole bunch of moneys in the first place
It's like you have learned
Of hard if you haven't learned about the shams of capitalism by the time you've saved up all that money
The lessons are lost on you anyway indeed indeed very true
All right, there you go, and you everyone put your time codes now to skip to the end of the endless war
Fuck you audience
God bless them
Disappointed in you every single episode
Uh, well, here's here's a small point. I messaged this in the chat the other day
I thought it was interesting, but people jumped down my throat about it a little bit
But that wasn't the point it was that I've noticed that a couple people have made
Smash videos not just in a similar style to me, but like
Ripping off the branding including the font and there's a couple of things going on here
I have no problem with people copying my style and doing the things in this way
When I start to have just a little bit of concern is when I see many many comments about well
Looks like BGE really shit this one out and just and that that's like the worst-case scenario
but many people just expressing some degree of confusion that
Clearly they thought this was a video by specifically these are all like banjo ones
there's like three ones that people have made and
I just it's I wish I have no problem with people doing this
I just kind of wish they would brand. There's a little bit differently
So it didn't just look like it was one of mine. I mean, but it's just like there's been on it
I feel like I mean, I feel yeah, I feel like that's probably not effective
marketing on their part
You don't think so. I think they're at the goal of making these videos is not to build their own brand
It's to get clicks off of yours
I mean a lot of them are clearly like up-and-comers. They're just trying to like do something fun
I don't have a problem with that. I don't think it's malicious
But I think the goal is to emulate your style as closely as possible because they know it works
Well, I mean, maybe if they're just starting out they like your videos
Maybe I mean, I guess probably the ideal what you would hope would happen is maybe they start out basically just making carbon copy
Best guy ever style videos and then they find their own style in that space
I mean, and of course, I mean did very true and did you of course said this to me
He's like wow Nate. You really think you copyrighted putting
Another person's like character on the thumbnail and putting the smash logo behind it. Well, no
I don't think I invented that or anything
But the font choice being the exact same font and it being a music like this kind of gives it away that it is in fact
There's a lot of specific choices that would all brought together again makes the influence clear
Yeah, yeah, and yeah, you like you might not own any of those things, but like
Yeah, it looks like a best guy ever video and I'm not an idiot. I'm not trying to say I copyrighted or I
Copy-acclaimed these people. It's it's just I mean take for example the fact that my first one the Ridley one was a complete
It wasn't a copy but like in the description. I say
inspired by
Demolition D and his
His berserk like getting off the boat video one of the greatest videos of all time. It's it's incredible
Deserves all its success demos the legend etc. etc
But and and you know some of the guys start their videos by saying like inspired by best guy ever like here
We go so like okay couldn't have a problem couldn't couldn't have less of a problem with that
but other people don't even mention me anywhere in the video and
are just
There but you know that I can't even get that mad at that because some people when they make their videos
They don't feel the need to like credit anything at all and I'm the complete opposite
I credit like every single link of everything I use and like all my videos
I don't need to but I just find it easy and I'm happy to do so some people
Just don't feel that need and maybe they still think like well
It's obvious. I'm you know doing a homage to this guy. So I don't it's hard to get in people's heads
And know exactly what they're thinking it is when I bring this up
It sounds like I'm like an angry complaining loser. Who's like these people are ripping me off
Well, I assure you viewers it is only an illusion
But but my my actual point here is to encourage these guys because you know what some other people came to me and said like hey Nate
I really like your videos like do you mind if I make a video in this style?
Some people actually reached out to me to ask me that and you know what I said to him
I said like fuck off. I said absolutely not pay me money motherfucker or whatever for 50% of your ad revenue
Actually, it's literally 0% ad revenue. Oh, by the way, give Gibbs said this was really funny
One guy puts a bunch of like things the beginning of his videos that are like. Oh, no
I got demonetized guys who could have expected that to happen. So I'm not making any money. So give my patreon
It's like yeah, what do you think this project is?
There of course is demonetized. We're stealing other people's music and making a montage. Okay, but whatever
I also plug my patreon
But some people reached out to me and they said like Nate can I do this my answer was I I didn't invent the concept of musical
Montages, I didn't invent the concept of like smash reveal videos or hype things or anything
But just put your own style on it would be the thing to do you can totally rip off the formula
I can't stop you. I have no right to stop you
I'd encourage you just to put your own creative spin on it as I like to think I have done with my videos
This is a humble request not a demand because I have no right to demand anything as you know
This is the internet. We all steal from each other and take ideas and whatnot. That's my that's my message to those to those fine folks out
There, but I mean if those guys hear this, I just I'm not mad. I don't care
I'm not upset about it
But just just consider these and as you grow and as a creator put your own spin on things
Don't don't make it so that like people have made collections of these
Like playlists of like the smash revealed videos or whatever and it's like all my videos
Then like a bunch of these banjo ones that are not mine and like one or two that are unrelated
But you can tell the unrelated ones are not made by me in it like instantly from the thumbnail and the title and stuff
Like I feel like that's where we should all be you know as a society
Yeah, there you go. All right, that's my point. Well point. It's like it's like it's like the same goes
You know imitation is a sincerest form of theft
I don't know
I feel like some people are gonna be mad at me or call me a whiny bitch about this as as some of the people in our chat
Seem to be but Nate aren't you just like happy that people are copying you and you know flattering you? Yes. Yes. I am
It's very nice. It's very nice, but I mean I guess to be a little selfish when I see that one of these videos has like
85,000 views and I'm just like damn
I have no problem with this guy making the video. It was pretty good and all that but like
I feel like at least some of these people
Were we're clicking on this because they thought it was my video and now you know, they've consumed this
Entire point
Yeah, I mean, that's why they did it. I think I think we've passed the point where
If you continue to complain
You start to sound the litch a little alright, okay
And you know as digi and other people said it's like a lot of people in those comments are like this will hold me over until
Best guy ever makes his video like so, okay, I get it
Not you know, I don't I'm not trying to be that that that annoying about I just thought it was something of interest to bring up
Because there's a fine line here of of I don't know
I don't want to say like acceptable versus unacceptable behavior
But like ideal versus, you know another person when that when people reached out to me and asked me
I had to kind of meditate be like what what would I want someone to do if they like were trying to copy?
I don't know just honestly like a thumbnail that doesn't look like it's totally copying my style and
Like it's funny because the the text of the description or of the of the title of the thing
I just put into like fancy text generator comm and was like which one of these like kind of looks cool
And I just picked one randomly. There's no meaning to it, but then other people like why are they using it?
I mean because I'm using obviously. That's the only reason you'd pick that font. So, you know
Just just funny to think about lads. I hope you've enjoyed this
Good well, there you go, that's what I have to say about that. Okay. All right, um
What else we got?
What else what else is going on Tom? What's what's new in your life?
Not much
Surgery on Wednesday
excited and by excited by the time people hear this it'll be over you'll be you'll be I'll either be cured or crippled
I guess we'll find out find out okay. Yeah, I don't I don't you know
This is perhaps a sensitive topic don't want to push you to talk about too much about if you're worried or uncomfortable like
Will you know if things have like improved or not improved like very soon after we'll take a while to like, you know
From what I understand it should you want to tell us like what they're doing to you
They are doing surgery on my spine because I have a herniated disc is maybe unable to walk since January pretty much
Yeah, as some of you have seen firsthand
So they're going to knock me out open up my spine and pull out bits of my spinal cord
They're currently interrupting the nerves in my back that are fucking things up. Very nice. Yeah, it's a good time
Very nice. Yeah, so I guess the idea is that you pull out these pieces of bone
And I won't have the pain anymore
But if something goes bad, they could sever the nerves in my spine and paralyze me. So oh my god
I thought it was your sciatic nerve like in your legs
It is that's where the pain is coming from but it's because there's there's the disc in my spine has slipped and it is hitting the nerve
That affects the sciatic nerve because it like runs down your spine into your leg
I don't know. It's some weird biology. Why don't you just go to a chiropractor because they're all about like
Controlling the flow of energy up and down your spine. Well, it sounds like they are designed for this problem
I don't know why you're using this quote-unquote
standard medicine this
Mainstream solution. Well, Ben as someone who's been suffering with this for a year. I've gone to the chiropractor multiple times
I've gone to physical therapy. I've gone to I've tried everything. I've tried
My guy will hook you up
Yeah, I don't know about any of that
Seems a little it's a little too mainstream for me
I guess I'm more of an indie guy. I got it. I got it. I've had some seances with witches
Yes, good. Good. No no luck so far. Have you perhaps prayed to the great Satan for for benefit
I'm trying to Satan every day just about everything. All right. We're okay. I don't want to be overly negative here
But just this at all utterly terrify you because I feel like it would me constantly. Yes, okay
Yeah, all the time. Well, very paneled like this like the problem. I've heard about people having herniated discs before
I feel like this has got to be a somewhat common procedure. Yeah
I mean the talk from from the surgeons like yeah, this is like probably the best surgery
I do with the highest rate of success the problem is like this is already like a huge phobia of mine already
so like surgery in general as
Just just like anything to do with my spine or brain or like cuz that's like
Yeah, yeah alive right brain shit fucks me right up dude. I saw a post on Twitter someone trying to get get a voyage
That brain shit as much as
Tell me about that there's a metaphor in a whoop-a-dee's design somewhere
I'm sure like there was there was a post on Twitter someone trying to get thing help for their medical bills
And I guess yeah something had happened to their neck
The the bones in their neck had shifted and their brain was falling out of their skull as a result
Yeah, it was fucking my god, yeah, yeah, I'm googling brain surgery images right now
Ah
Yeah
That this is why I'm
Transhumanism hashtag H plus get us out of these flesh prisons now. Well, I mean
I mean this reminds me of a couple of things in in ghost in the shell land of cyber brain
Ah, what not they do have to I believe fully remove the brain
And then they put it into like a casing that can be like moved around easily between skulls
So, I mean there is brain surgery going on there for sure, but yeah
Yeah, that's just not as scary
No, I mean it would be scary because like then you also have to like wonder like well
I still be the same thing like it's still my brain
Yeah, like is there something that's lost your transition. Yeah, but but once you the benefits the benefits are yeah
That's true. The benefits way too big to I'm like you're basically like, you know a god at that point a god
I mean just look at look at Tom for example
I mean he could literally put a cyber brain in a new body in a situation like this and then what I think the thing
That really fucks me up is that I wouldn't even be so weirded out by being like an organic biological being if we could synthesize organs
Easily because like the problem is like we don't have we don't we can't just like bring ourselves to the hospital and be like
Yeah, my heart's broken. I need a new one. It's like all right pay me like a couple hundred bucks
We'll you know, we just grow you a new heart
I guess we fantasize a little bit that we're farther along in this developmental process of medicine and whatnot
But we're actually very primitive in the things that we can do watch watch the original Star Trek and then like yes
Like even back then like the ideas that they were having for medicine are still far beyond anything we can ever do like their ideas of
Technology have been obliterated by modern devices, but the medical field is still
Laughably behind the concepts from the 60s. So you know, it's just ridiculous
Like I'm going I really they're gonna carve pieces of bone out of my back by cutting through the flesh
It's like what the fuck this is some medieval shit
Did I mention the last piece of the episode the the situation of like Ron Weasley discussing his views on human doctors or muggle doctors?
Did I did I bore everyone with this last time? I don't want to repeat myself
I don't remember it's very quickly. It's just that Ron Weasley this privileged wizard fuck with literally magic blood
When when Harry went with him to like the wizard hospital and like book two or whatever
They were like
Harry's who grew up, you know with muggle people was like all these wizard doctors Ron and Ron was like no Harry
What those muggle natas that cut people up? No, they're healers
So it's like he's literally shaming muggles because of the best stuff
They've got science real shit. Your god isn't real Ron. Fuck you
You know because we don't have magic the wizards keep their their advanced medical
Technologies and leave us all the suffered and die of cancer really says a lot
I mean Harry Potter has
Like weird ramifications of this like secrecy of their entire society when you really make it like a real thing
Well, it's because the book started off as like kind of like cutesy children things exactly
They got older and then when you start dealing with more complex topics
I'm not actualizing things and more you're like wait a minute
We made it too real things get teenagers everyone's starting to get a little horny and you know from there things just go straight down
Well god damn I hope it goes well and I want to know as soon as possible things go
Well, and if anything I mean good or bad if you need our help Tom
We'll we'll here I am to virtue signal that we can perhaps be of assistance in some way
I mean just if terrible things happen and lots of money is required boom
We got an audience we got we'll we'll make a Kickstarter or we'll make it go fun me whatever man
I'm sure people will be willing to help I'm hoping mass health will cover the majority of whatever this fallout is and force comes to worse
Maybe I can sue the hospital for millions and damages for malpractice
You can make this work for you
Let's just say you need an extra thousand dollars
I don't see any reason why if you like you're I don't know you're paying the bills you got your your
Your your not tax your fucking benefits or whatever from the the health care or whatever
But if you need an extra like five grand, that's a thing for Kickstarter
That's a thing for just the kindness of man to help out with yeah, this is not your fault
This is literally the role of the fucking dice. What a great system we got going on in America right now
Yeah
They could use a little bit of work
capitalism has some problems it could use a violent revolution
Hate the corporations and hate the government the most are also the ones who are anti-gun we're never gonna see a violent revolt
It's such a shame
well
Perhaps perhaps that's why
I
What if I can charge for entrance to like my antifa weapons training program
So I can make a pretty penny off of arming though
That'll work for a while until they seize the means of armament from you that you know, you're not wrong
Well, there you go, there you go, there's the update there
We joke about all this but
Shout out to nexus mania in Chile right now where things are fucking really fucked up. Oh my god
Well, dude that like yes, it was fucked for him
I don't know exactly what's going on in Chile. There's there was like some protests
I guess the government shut it down into a there's a curfew now
There's military on the street that's armed fucking with people
I haven't looked into it too much because that shit fucks and creeps me out, but uh, yep
Feel the same way please don't die
I'm thinking about you thoughts and prayers
Thoughts and prayers bro thoughts and prayers thoughts and prayers
You know, we did it we got a voice
I won't well we'll play it later, but there was a voicemail irrelevant to the situation that perhaps will be a salvation
For nexus in this situation. I don't know unless they they've closed almost certainly. I don't know. I don't know
But oh boy, yeah, yeah with like that and many other unhappy things happening in the world
I'm like, ooh
Like if I worked really hard, maybe I could help but I got like a lot of dishes to do today
I got like a lot of chores to handle so
You know just got to keep it 100 keep it focused on number one over here. So good luck everybody out there
You know unironically there's a there's probably some kind of equation to be found
Of it's appropriate to spend a certain amount of time worrying about the rest of the world
And a certain amount of time worrying about the shit you got to deal with in your life
I don't know what that ratio is well
There is not 100
There's a school of thought that says you take care of yourself first because once you're in a good position
You're you're more effective at taking care of the world. I think they call that objectivism at least it's part of the ethos of
objectivism
Maybe I haven't read Anne Rand. Those books are big. Those books are good. I think
I mean Rand is literally a fucking psycho. Hey, hey, no, no, thy enemy Ben. No, thy enemy, right?
And I found them enjoyable terrible terrible mindset from a terrible woman. Oh
She lived communism Ben. She's allowed to be mad at it and to you know
Okay, you know all those books were just a temper tantrum about being well mad about communism
Some of our greatest art has been the product of temper tantrums. I give you sonnachu volume one
Rage against the yeah rage against the garbage. All right. That's fair. That's fair
Can't argue with Christian, but the Anne Rand of our time. I guess
Man I got the I got a fucking mm-hmm. I just got a fucking keep I just got to keep Chris
Interested I just got to keep it. I gotta keep it funny
Of course the Chris just keeps like coming up as long as Chris is still coming up with no
No, no, no, this happened in this universe. No, no, no, no, the slime is doing this and this is what's going as like as long
As that's going on
I gotta say as a bystander it's interesting watching the diplomatic relations continue to break down week over week
It is it is interesting. Um, they're not it's it's not over until I'm fucking blocked and even then
Even then I have options. Now. I suppose I'm curious Ben at this point of the equation
Are you at all, you know getting into the the thoughts of like am I perhaps taking this a little bit too far?
Am I no, no, no, okay. Okay. No, I ain't no bitch
I have a question related to that. How are those scripts going for the vaporettes?
Uh, well, I got two of them out
All right, how many are them?
Six oh
I think I might rewrite one or two
I think maybe that means none are done
No, no, no, no, no the ones that I got out to the artists are set in stone. Oh, okay
I'm happy with those. I must say other ones who I'm like, am I really happy with these just like could I improve these?
Am I
Don't don't beat yourself up about them too much try to get them to a workable state
Then maybe consider just giving them to the artists and let them
Possibly make some small changes to the script because you know, they have a creative voice that perhaps could bloom. I guess that's true
Yeah, I don't know. I'm sad that my dream of a chris chan vaporette from two weeks ago is all but dead now
Unless there's a big
I did say that a couple episodes ago. I was like, oh man, vapor's three
Oh, you know, she never would have fucking done it, you know
It's I mean to respect chris to deliver on a deadline, you know for a certain amount of money and not just demand extra money for no reason
Never fucking do it. You would never do it
I mean, she she made you that that page that you paid for, you know, that was it's true deliverable
It's true. It's that did happen. Um, but I think I'm in the minority of people who actually got what they paid for
Really? Hmm. I I mean, everyone says she doesn't deliver on her kickstarter on her like, uh, uh
Paypal or you know patreon obligations and stuff and doesn't you know
Screws people out of commissions and stuff. I don't know. I don't know fair enough
My one experience was through you getting it successfully. So that that made me think like, oh, wow
Yeah, and that was fine. So I get maybe you know
Thumbs up one of those ones five stars. Give her a good yelp review. Now. That's what you call customer service
Uh, let me see what else is going on the saga of sesho exercise and thinning uh continues
I'll have everyone know I accidentally gave him two dinners the other day. It was a it was a mistake
All progress is lost
What have you done?
I need to really kill him. It was an early dinner situation
I forgot and michelle was like did you feed sesho yet? And I was like, uh, I don't think so
But alas I had so you get a system going
We will you know, we should make like a whiteboard and like check it off when we fed sesho and maybe exercise him every day
You know, some people are saying some people have to voicemail. I didn't play because it was fine
But it wasn't wasn't up to par of like you should go running with sesho. Now you should go running with sesho
I could like try that. I suppose but sesho is a very
He like sesho doesn't play fetch some people are saying play fetch with sesho sesho does not fetch
He could perhaps be convinced to perhaps one way chase. He's he's a broken boy. He's a broken mind
This is what happens when you make your dog
Rotund as you have it was from day one sesho was like this
You know sesho's a very demure soul a very demure soul like his namesake lord sesho maru himself
Doesn't speak much very quiet. We'll occasionally do some mild grumbling and uh, doesn't doesn't fetch doesn't run much
Except sometimes we'll just run around the house. No reason to find out that his younger brother has the tetsaiga and that would give him all the motivation he needs
That's to raise his yokai power level to overcome him and uh and seize the means as as it were that'll be good
Okay, well, you know, we have been thinking about you know, I'll give you guys a teaser
Perhaps I shouldn't spoil this because one day I feel like it'll be a long time before this comes of fruition
But me and michelle this is michelle's idea
We've long thought about eventually perhaps soon getting another dog for sesho to play with and to hang out with because we both
Just love dogs. What a fucking nightmare. I'm stressed out just thinking about it
I feel like having one dog is like 90 of the work getting a second dog is only like 10 extra, you know
So we're already yeah, that seems like some slippery slope logic
Well, it's not a child. So their lives don't matter. So I'm not that worried about yeah
Yeah, if you change your mind you can always take them out back behind the barn
Yeah, that's all right. So so here is the um
The the name we we are thinking about it's not inuyasha as people may think that that would be too boring
And this is michelle's idea. It's we're thinking of kagome
It's we're thinking of calling him odi for short which stands for
Left arm of the forbidden one exodia is would be the full name of
Showers
Left arm of the forbidden one a.k.a.
Left arm of the forbidden one exodia a.k.a. odi for short. All right, isn't that right? That's pretty good. That's pretty fucking funny
It is that was all michelle. She's a she's a funny lass
Patreon her for more epic memes on her patreon, which she does not have but one of these days
Um, we all right. Well, you know, let us know when you actually go through with it. I guess we'll do
I wonder if people will remember and uh, keep uh, give us your hot suggestions in the description down below
Vote in my straw poll for what to name my second dog that I don't have
The current fictional dog that may cross the dimensional merge
He may just cross over that dimensional merge right now
Send us fan art of odi so that he can then become real through the dimensional merge
It could be in your backyard right now for all we know
There is
There's so much this dimension the dimensional merge. There's so much possibility space
So much there's so much possibility space about where yeah, we're we're gonna take things
Um, I'm I'm I'm constantly walking on the razor's edge
I figured out your end game of all this by the way this morning. I had the brain blast
It's like, oh, I see the whole point of this entire endeavor
Is that when the inevitable chris chan part two lecture has it has to by default have a sub lecture of endless war
You've injected there it is man. There it is
And then it'll reach already it's already there
It's already there because already on the quickie of the slime the slime related
Arizona slime card updates for the Twilight Sparkle secret shipfic folder
Are already listed as sonichu special number six, so it already has its own side chapter devoted to it
So there's nothing I can do. I literally must
Devote a section of the lecture to it. It's canon. I mean, it's a hundred percent canon
How could you give the lecture a nod address? Yeah, no, I would be sure I would be
You negligent in your in your christorianly duties. No doubt. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I would be remiss not to not to have a section
so
You know, I've already won
well
I feel like that right there is the not so good news. We just heard about on the web and perhaps
We should move on to to the voicemails
We've got we've got like 12. We've been going for like 45. Did I mention did I mention that I have a quickie article?
Yeah, we said it was the article of the now last time it was it is no longer the article of the now, but it's still there and
It's the article of the
But it's all it's got it's got the template. Oh, it's some other guy who has been like making
Kickstarter campaigns or gofundme campaigns to like raise money for
And like they've all failed. I don't know. I don't know what his deal is and I don't really care
Okay, fair enough
But I my article has that little mark. It has a little star has that template at the top
It's like this article was once article of the now I can never they can never take that away from me
They can never take away the touch the poop that'll be on
I did I sure did it's stink the stink is on me boys
Uh, I mean if you guys are down, I mean I pretty much burned through I'm think we're a little bit light on
individuals with human capital to expend today
That's true. Uh, well, I mean
The Kickstarter got into a little sunday for that. Um, uh, I went to uh, I did go to um
The massachusetts independent comics expo yesterday. Oh, yeah, okay with kazzie and uh, munchie
And uh, I hate it. It's all why really it's bad. I don't like it
It's just it bothers me that all you do there is buy stuff
It's only a place for I mean there are panels. None of them seem like actual comics
They've made or like bullshit corporate merch or something. Well, yeah, I mean they are independent creators and I mean that's cool and all
But like you just go that you you buy their comic books. You buy their
You know prints they made I don't want any of that stuff. I don't want this mythical networking
Be a part of the experience in some way where I would be interested in that
But like I don't know how you're supposed to do that
Like I met like I met abby howard, right and like last year
Last year abby howard was there
And and I didn't say anything to her but this year she was just walking by me and I was like, oh abby howard
Hey, I know you I know you from that stuff search. Yeah
We had a you know, we talked she was like, oh, yeah my table's downstairs
And you know, I was like, oh cool. Great to meet you. She walked away and I was like, what was the point of that?
Like what have I what has anyone gained like this sucks like this whole endeavor is useless
I wish I I wish I never left you know, I wish I never left my house. What a fucking
What a fucking nightmare the problem and I never and I never felt and I never felt more alone than I did
In public at mice out at this thing
Is that where the tweet came from where you said you felt alienated or is that a different
Although that's it certainly didn't help now that was after ben's abduction by aliens and he was feeling real alienated
I never felt more alone than I was at mice and like here I am at this event that like this event seems like it's
Literally made for someone like me and I'm here and there is like zero
I feel zero purpose in being here. I feel zero camaraderie with anyone else here
You know, they this is a nightmare
They say that human beings feel their loneliness when like in cities surrounded by people who know, you know, who they know
None of as opposed to
Or smaller little communities when they can know a couple people that makes sense
You get the sense of tranquility when you're actually by yourself indeed indeed
Anyway, so
I didn't like it is the short version of that story
I mean, I guess my thing is if you weren't going there to either a
Have a table yourself because then you actually have a purpose or b
You wanted to go get a bunch of fucking independent comics from a bunch of creators. Like yeah, it does seem pointless to go
What yeah, why go just to waste money or waste money, you know
Because like the that the boston comics round table had a table and i've been
I've gone to a couple meetings lately. I don't know if i'm gonna go anymore. It sucks. It's fucking pointless
I mean if you're gaining nothing fair enough, I suppose. I'm gaining nothing
Uh, they're they're I went I I've been saying like maybe I want to like sit at their table and like, you know
You can sell your shit like I could have brought some of my comics and sold
But like they had all bunch of shit on the table
Like like mine would have just been like one book among like 20
So like i'm sure I wouldn't have sold very many copies of anything. I don't think it would have made me any money
I don't think it would have increased my ability to network with other
Creators because I just would have been sitting behind a table
um
That's kind of like the reason I've never wanted to vent at conventions or anything like that because it just feels like
Oh, I'm just sitting behind a table while all this other cool stuff is going on everyone's walking around
I could hang out with my friends, but no i'm behind here at a table and I can't move for the entire weekend
Just seems interesting. I don't know they say they say they talk about operated for you
You know they talk about networking, but I don't know
I mean
Then you had the galaxy brain move of like starting a kickstarter online and accessing an international audience and made $12,000
I'd gout anyone like the better plan between the two. I mean
Yeah, space is just old school
I mean it took me like it took me like six years of fucking audience building and whatever
But you know other than that little hiccup it's like it's like what could be simpler
Well, I mean, I don't know six years of grinding in the real world would get you far less results. I feel
You could make more than $12,000 just working a job
Well, I mean, I mean, I mean making comics. I mean making
Oh
In that case
Real life possibly yet. That's fair. That's that's possibly fair. I mean, I would definitely encourage people
If they're making a they're trying to be successful at some, you know
artistic endeavor of any stripe
To acknowledge the financial reality of how they need to survive and work a job in addition to doing that thing
Which is what I did and maybe yet again all too soon
If I'm not making enough money and stuff
It just seems like a practical way to live but uh, you know, whatever I can respect those who just jump
Both feet in let me sink or swim. Let me talk about let me talk about
Assholes on twitter who don't like my tweets, right?
And it's your girlfriend and digi's girlfriend. Michelle and may okay. They're bullying gang
Just just gang up on me and bully me on twitter. There's such shit lords
Love to be mean to you. I don't know just so you know
I worry sometimes that people think that I'm like sending michelle out as like a no, no, no
I never do that. No, I don't I didn't think that this time
In the past I've wondered like isn't it in on this but this time like I know this is just I mean what she does
Is she will say Nate? I'm telling ben what a fucking retard he is right now and I go. Okay, michelle. That sounds nice
Yeah, you know things of this. Yeah
It's terrible. It's terrible. She's she's not she's it is funny who but she has she has cowered tactics
Cowardly debate tactics. She only she only did police is my tone. She won't debate me
She won't let me own her ass with facts and logic
I don't just say oh you sound like uh, you sound like an old you sound like such a boomer the way you phrase that
Ha ha who would phrase the thought that way idiot. I can't argue with that
prerogative is definitely to be a be a trickster and a jokester and to laugh at vulnerable individuals
And then I say, you know, I like fdr. I like fdr
Economic policies and may is like is japanese ben. She is japanese her people are locked away in those concentration camps
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, I mean michelle, isn't he? I mean, yeah, there was that
May was on my ass about she locked away the concentration camp who cares bro get over it, right?
How long ago was that? Yes, literally who okay? Well, I wasn't even talking about that
I like his economic policies. Obviously. I don't like the internment camps, right?
But I'm just saying fdr fucking tax the rich to shit and I think that's awesome
And uh, you know pretty pretty cool stuff
Doesn't invalid doesn't invalidate that other things he did were bad
I don't think may I don't like may's take on the whole thing. She's trying to tell me that I'm wrong and I don't think that I am wrong
And the point is that I hate women. That's it
Understood understood. Yeah, you know
And the and the jews and the japanese I guess of course considering our different
I don't know like our different political beliefs to whatever degree
Uh, I feel like a lot of people would probably think that I'd just be like with these people
But like I swear to god guys when I hear these things when I hear like michelle for example, this is just sucking my own dick right now
It's like when I hear michelle like laughing at ben. I really do say
Like well, I mean it's pretty clear ben's talking about the economic policy and like it's pretty you know
I'm not talking about the other shit
Yeah, I like that he he put a he put a 100. Well, he proposed a 100 percent
Good gracious a 100 percent like wealth, uh, like wealth like tax bracket above $25,000
Which was about 400 to 500
You know
Well, it was about $500 in in the period time of the period a great quote
I heard recently recently sam harris was getting some pushback for like having different
um, I mean people are getting mad at him for having like different opinions on um, like like islamic terror versus like white
Nationals terror and whatever it's a complex. It was a great podcast
I thought was very interesting on his um the making sense podcast people should go listen to it
I think it's very interesting
But like one of the things he said was just like one of the quotes was just like
If someone likes he said like for example
What about the japanese the japanese have a policy of japan is for the japanese
We don't want you know to to intermingle with others and he's like and what about that?
He's like i'm happy to take this point from hitler himself and to debate
The the the merits of this argument because it doesn't matter who they're from and I couldn't agree more that that's the smartest way to operate
Um, so basically natus saying go hitler
He made some good points the autobahn guys
He's really killing it with that autobahn to this day fan fantastic
So there and you know so f dr did some like I don't know I think george washington had some good things
You know columbus day was recently a lot of people have very negative things about columbus
But surely we can say it was a different time that doesn't excuse it
But can't we just celebrate the good things? I discovered in america for europe pretty nice. Okay, like i'm like, you know
I just think uh, you know, we could we could not do the internment camp thing
We could not turn away
We could not turn away people fleeing the holocaust, but we could still do the new deal
We could do the new we could do a new new deal, which I think
We're probably pretty good about now. It helped with the last big depression. We're in another one. Hmm. Hmm. What's to be done?
you know I I
Hashtag I stand with women unlike ben, uh, but but uh, I do think
I I do hate it when people when you're I mean you're trying to make a point about something and people do a lot of what about
Ism and you know these
I don't know. I'm just saying what are you saying?
I'm saying that it's a pet peeve of mine when like well, okay on twitter is a format that's
Nobody's gonna take it seriously
It's a terrible place to have substantive debates and whatnot because it's not face-to-face as far as we anonymized
So I get why a lot of people come out and goof and gaffe and but whatever you take a positive stance on anything
Like just now I made some vaguely positive Christopher Columbus points. Like it was pretty cool. He discovered America
Of course, you can say that like his discovery of America resulted in many many bad things
And affirmative stance is open criticism. There's a video
Yeah, okay. Everyone's everyone's on the the Christopher Columbus hate train. Yes
There's a video I've seen being like, you know
Christopher Columbus didn't really like personally do a lot of the bad stuff that we say like, oh
Wait, I don't know. I mean like knowing better. You're talking about because he's yeah, I think so
I think it's knowing better that guy made a point
I because I happen to see this fairly recently, you know with all this being discussed that like a lot of people accuse him of genocide
But yeah, I mean the fact that uh, when you dig into why that is
A lot of it ties back into the fact that like disease wiped out 90 percent of the Native American population
But they literally didn't even know what disease was like at the time and they could not have intended the genocide
Even if they wanted to they couldn't have because of you know, so like I mean, I'm sure there's many other specific things
You know that um that in defense of columbus video in defense of columbus an exaggerated evil is pretty good
I think it was the first knowing better video I ever saw and it's it's a good one like
He did he did do some pretty shitty stuff, but like absolutely not maybe not as much as everyone
Kind of just says he did I don't know there's there's nuance to all of history, you know
Yeah, I feel like a lot of this falls into my mo of like for example when people get too excited about one piece chapters
I am here to regulate and say you are too excited about these chapters and when people are too critical
of historical figures who could
A lot of this is like I'm in the 20th century the 21st century
Of course, we know x y z things are bad. You're too critical of these historical figures
Well, uh, you know relax on that reaction my my issue with the whole thing of like everyone stay in your lane
Calm down the issue I feel with people judging historical figures
So harshly is that like we're all doing things that in a hundred years will be morally reprehensible. We just don't know
I'm not
I'm on the right side of history
Oh, we just don't know like like society culture is going to change and like the standards are going to evolve
And we're all going to do things that are like backwards and stupid at that point
It's not like we've reached the end point of moral progression
So the cast stone backwards is to also inculcate all of us as being terrible people as well
And for all time it's very simple
It's it's very easy and I like it's very easy to say that yes to some degree
Christopher columbus engaged in the slave trade to some degree that seems to be true
He's just a little bit of a slaver, but you know what it was exactly the thing
Okay, then does that mean everything he did because of that is forever bad and forever tainted
No, but nobody nobody says everything was bad unless you're one of my idiot twitter enemies
Says like no, didn't you know f dr was actually a fascist?
I just want people to be consistent as long as you agree. Yes f dr did bad things, but let's focus on the good
You know his economic policy winning world war two or whatever it was he did all good stuff
Same with columbus same with washington ending the great depression
Pretty good. Pretty good stuff winning world war two
But you know on the other hand I feel like I'm being a bit of a nanny and people like michelle would be out here
Bunking me on the noggin and saying nate. I'm just trying to mean bro. I'm just trying to mean
Michelle doesn't think
Michelle I'm speaking directly to you. Oh, you don't think that jokes mean anything
But they do and they're funny because they mean something they have real victims
They have real victims and you're talking to michelle thinks that if you're making a joke
Nothing you say has to mean anything, but if that were true, you wouldn't laugh
You wouldn't laugh would you think about it? Damn
Damn damn debunked for all time. I'd say
Say hello to the tolerant laugh once again ladies
They're back and they're better than ever
Do we want to go to voicemails? I think we should go to voicemails. How many fucking voicemails do we have?
So, okay, there's there's 11 slash 12 because one's a two-parter
We you know, we might not need to play that two-parter
You I'll let you decide when we get there because it may or may not warrant it
But all right, you get it started. Let's let's roll first up started in here tails of a virgin
Oh, of course, everyone speak pipe link down below leave us a voicemail. Appreciate it. Thanks. Thank you very much
Okay tails of a virgin. Let's go on the count of three. All right. You guys you guys ready? Yeah
Okay the count of three one two three
I don't think I've ever been terribly interested in sex or dating. I'm a little bit too autistic
for all that. So I'm still a virgin
but
But I once got very very close to popping that cherry
A friend of my mom was injured in an accident involving some fuckface
So she was helping develop on her gas line or some shit
So she was out of commission for a while and I went there. I lived there for about a month helping her
Taking care of her her dogs like where this is guy, you know, just no being there
And after the first three weeks, I think on the third weekend of me being there
her sister ends up coming down and
I mean at this point, I I know everyone pretty well
I'm decent friends with everyone and she tells me her sister now the lady who got injured her sister
Told me hey, I used to be a porn star. So we started to talk about that. I'm like that's that's actually really interesting like
How does that work?
And she you know kind of understanding that I'm an autistic little boy who's fucking homeschool all of his life was like, hey
want to fuck
and I said
no
The reason
She's 50 fucking six or some shit. Yeah gross
Yeah, okay
That's a while ago. That's a porn star from the 70s or so. Yeah
a little bit little later, you know, I mean
I
Cool story bro, but unironically cool story
Kind of a cool story that I enjoyed hearing
Imagine that good for you
Uh, how unfortunate maybe one day you'll find a porn star who's not
50 something when you are
When I feel like a lot of people perhaps a lot of virgins out there listening to this or maybe not
Would be like whoa, bro for girls said I want to fuck. You know, I do it instantly
I mean unironically if you're a virgin and a girl just comes up and says let's fuck
You don't know what you're doing and it's like embarrassing and like I would I absolutely would have done the same thing
I've been too scared to do anything. Yeah, I don't I just don't blame you. I don't know about any all any all that
I don't know about any all that
But I do love these stories from virgins that are like bro. I was so close to losing by virgini
Now granted this one's a little bit more real than a lot of those unless you're making it up
I mean, I can't prove he isn't but a lot of dude this girl. She was giving me the look
I totally could have smashed bro. Yeah, totally could have smashed
I just chose not to because I love god and I love jesus and I didn't want to come between the two of us
That's uh, that's the story I can get into
Fuck yeah, dude now that's that's what gets me excited. It's thinking about being married to god. Let's go to the next one
Speaking of god, uh, next one is from oh voicemail god is real once and for all
Let me just uh, okay. I'm ready. Yeah, you got it. Okay on the count of three. Here we go one two three voicemail god here guys
Apparently I need to prove my existence
So I'm here to take credit for the five voicemails that were mine that were played on episode 180
number one
Sound like the morning somewhere
Pick a number guy
PCP shadow puppet master guy professional nate trigger
And some of my other characters
Such as pcp professional bit ruiners pcp promise guy
Uh retarded ben head yang ganger guy
And yeah, I mean I I'm real god is real. I'm a natehead. I don't remember any of this
So I think I'm above everyone so that makes me god
He's a natehead and a benhead the universe motherfuckers impossible. You that almost proves his divinity because you can't be a benhead and a natehead
Well, he's like the alpha and the omega like you'd have to that's totally contradictory
Everything everything I believe is everything you hate and vice versa
That that's definitely true. So I don't quite understand. Um, I'll just have to take his word
He was on five voicemails. Okay, apparently again, I'm kind of just taking his works
I'm not going to go fucking unless unless the people who left those other voicemails call in and challenge his class
Yeah, uh, uh voicemail antichrist. Please call in and prove that he's lying and he's exaggerating. Um, you know
Do do something about that. Is he on the shortlist for uh, voice voice grail
I feel like this guy is going to voice purgatory. Uh, you know to voice hell
Uh, well, maybe not hell, but he's totally neutral if he hasn't gotten into voice
Grail on purpose here
I mean if he's the voicemail god, he's already there, right? Like we don't he's a voice heaven, I guess, right?
He doesn't need our help. Oh god the voice cosmology is so convoluted expanding
I know we need a voice manual of the planes sort of pcp voice lecture. I gotta lay it all out
All right, next one is from marlowe. Are you guys you got it? I'm ready. I gotta get ready
Okay, all right count of three one two three
So I found podcasts this week that also happened to be called the procrastinators podcast
A clear case of copyright infringement as they also use the word podcast in their title
So about them they only have one episode published so far
It's posted five months ago. It's only five minutes. Oh, and worst of all
episode title is referencing and avoiding plagiarism
Here's a sample
Another episode of the procrastinators podcast
Today I'll be going solo because big jay is away. So you're stuck with me for this episode
Then keeps talking for a while
uh-huh
Trust me
Now when you're looking for information for your assignments, it can be hard to find exactly what you're looking for
Using the advanced search tool in the deacon library allows you to pinpoint exactly what you want
Also, if you're looking for a book to borrow you can see if it's in stock at the deacon lock
See you get the point. Well, I'm saying is you guys need to jump on this guy fast before he starts siphoning your patreon box
Tenderly yours
marlowe
Thank you marlowe or maybe we should let him continue to work in
In obscurity because then people who become his fans will find our patreon and pledge thinking we're him
I say we can let him do our work for us
Yeah, we so he's made one episode five months ago with his co-host not present for that particular episode
But I think there's a flourishing community
So we'll only I will demand if he makes further episodes
You have to link our patreon in your description and not have you know your own patreon if we can arrange that I think
I think we can let him stand he can be um
What's the word the the tendrils of the pcp can continue to expand and encompass all
Similar podcasts deal. That's fine. I have to pee
Um, can you play the next one while I take a piss?
But the next one's called tails gets trolled though. I think you want to hear it. Okay. Okay. We'll do the next one
And then he can go piss. Okay. Uh the count of three tails gets trolled one two three. Hey ben. I know uh talks with
having
laserbot on the show
Fell through and that didn't work out
but
I've listened to the tails gets trolled lecture maybe a hundred times and
uh
Every time tom says uh ben like one punch upgrade this or whatever
Uh, I like really want that to happen
So all I'm saying is
Do you have interest in doing that? No, and also I would be willing to back it if you did
End up doing that especially if there was no I got question
I got some sort of a slime comic to make
I'm really sorry. Let's play just much much more filled than it was during
I'm really sorry that that's something you're really interested in and I'm just absolutely not gonna do it
But I'm not gonna waste my fucking life redrawing tails gets trolled when you've already done tails get trolled
If you want to remaster tails gets trolled
Like you just got to go learn source filmmaker download all the models because they're all copyrighted characters that have source
Filmmaker models anyway, just do it yourself
Yeah, that's true. Be the change you want to see it doesn't require artistic vision at this point, you know
But you see I mean this guy at least he's saying I'm willing to financially back
I respect I respect that
But I'm definitely not I'm just I'm just not interested in making that a thing
If this guy can gather thousands and thousands of people
I mean you can surely you can find some artists who's interested in this although
I don't know if laserbot would like legally allow it if that's like allowed. I mean
You would think he would have some combat one online creator at a time. He's currently combating christian
I gotta wait for sport you would think you would think well
I mean I am probably gonna combat ululia at some point because ululia fucking left me in the lurch on the audiobook thing
And I'm ready to unfortunate whenever the whenever this whole thing with chris is over. I think I'm gonna say fuck that guy
I'm gonna take that into my own hands. The elemental masters will face the wrath of slime city
Pretty
All right, go pee go thank god
Get out of here. All right. Well, we'll play the next and all he's gone. Let's do a literally the law
Okay, let's see what that's about one two three
Hello, pcp
This officer Jenkins from the mall and as of right now you are all under arrest for the defamation of humanity via
The existence of this podcast itself anything you say pass this point can and will be used against you in court
Oh, and don't try to be smart getting the paperwork filed out for criminals in a state and abroad took us a while
So by the time you receive this voicemail, we should literally be dunking a donut in your living room
Come out with your hands up and your hands down
We've made special accommodations for each of you. So there's no point in resisting
We traps for the digi bro
Tiger nets for the mage a fake sign pointed toward the bernie poles for the bend a fake sign pointed towards starfleet for the
Nate a trailer ones for the munchie a wheelchair for the tom and a pair of handcuffs
With i'm just being cool written on them for the jesse
Now, I don't know why anyone would be dumb enough to put on those cuffs voluntarily
But that's what the google doc says. So I gotta believe it like the torah
There's another name at the bottom of the page
Davoo
Davo. Yeah, it looks like a time. It happens. Anyways, that's all I had to say. See you fuck is in prison
Well, well, that's it. We're going to jail. There's no escape. You want to guess that's all
Samurai's for me
We're going to this guy
The the the pc police are they've entered our homes and they are in fact here arresting us at this very moment and
Yeah, what can you do about that? Well?
Shelter and three square meals a day is more than I can claim to now. So, you know, perhaps this is an upgrade
Jokes on you. Yeah, we we've been begging for this. We've been hoping for this all along
Uh, all right. Well, there you go. Let's move on to the next one. Yeah, we've got weak willed wagey is calling in
Let's hear uh with this this hero of the common man has to say all right on the count of three ready one
Two three
So I recently become a wage cook and here are the three things that I've learned so far
Number one, you will have no more free time ever
Number two, you will never wear jeans again
You will have a closet full of jeans and other fun fucking t-shirts and clothes
That you will never wear again because you'll only wear them on the weekends
But you're going to be too tired to do anything on the weekends
So fucking all your clothes are trash
uh and number three
um
The shotgun's gonna look pretty tasty
So that's what I've learned being a wage cook so far. Um, how ben and tom how have you guys?
Survived how have you guys managed to not starve to death? I want to learn your ways. Um
Well, I got uh, I got one word for you
patreon.com
St
Yeah, that's literally what's kept me alive. Well, I mean that and youtube ad revenue and twitch donations and you know, whatever
You just got to make yourself a brand
And abuse other people's kindness
Yeah, oh, oh, yeah. Yeah, I mean that's that's a big that's what it's all about
You can't expect to do like the the dream
It's like when you if you look at a guy doing the olympics and you're like, I want to do the olympics
I'm gonna do it today. Well, that's unrealistic
You've got to get a plan going and if you want to be a you know a leech on society
You know internet artist freak show you have to set the stage it takes years to cultivate that
That you know ability so you gotta take years to completely destroy any sense of ethics or morality you have exactly
Well, you see we're all born with a god-given sense of morality and it takes years to dismantle that brick by brick by brick
So you gotta get to work on that immediately
And uh, the it will pay off in the long term. You have to lose everything to gain everything or some
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that makes something like that. All right next one lecture me dads
Okay, let's see what this individual has to say on the count of three one two three
So i'm a huge pcp head and recently on episode 180
You guys are talking about how you were wondering if anybody discovered the pcp because of ben's christian lecture
And i am definitely one of those people
I think a lot of people came into the pcp because of that like really excellent lecture
Your guys's lectures are the fucking bomb
They get
Way more views than anything else this little club has ever fucking created
It's true. Well in a completely different league like we're talking like digi bro levels of fucking views
Just for these fucking lectures if you guys were smart you would have rad con five or six or whatever fucking rad con rat now
You would have that be the fucking rad con
Conference the rad con seminar where you just do fucking lecture after lecture
I want three lectures from each of you on my desk that's fucking next week
Because that shit would get you guys millions of views
Whatever your lecture would be about that would attract viewers related to that topic who would then be introduced to the pcp
It's it's just fucking algorithmic. It's fucking beautiful. It's long form content. It's the good shit. It's algorithmic
Fucking make the big break. You guys deserve it fucking do lectures. God damn it
Yeah, that aptly stated. Yeah, I mean we've we've kind of talked about that before about how like the lectures are like
Proven content that does work with the way youtube is the problem. I mean
I think the the reason we don't do more of them is just because
Like part of the the whole appeal is you have the the audience, you know, everybody else listening and we're not all
In the same place. Yeah, that's the total there's a there's a lot of prep involved in doing these
Yeah, there's only I do I do wish we had more ready access to do them like
Imagine if we could like it's it's easy to do we just need like the camera man is actually very important in those
So yeah, the camera man and the mic the mic setup setup is like actually crucial
Yeah, I mean we've talked about like one of the things we would do with pcphq would we have a studio that set up to do
You know lectures on a more regular basis and we just hey we're going to the studio and recording one
And uh, it would be easy peasy. Yeah, but the dream of pcphq is dead, so
Unless you give us more money double your patron now. No
No, it's well, maybe it's dead for you ben, but not for me
Okay, if i don't know if pcp is like two of us live in the same place, then okay
I don't I mean, I don't even think that I can just this is the new thing
pcphq doesn't have to be a place of residence if we're rich enough
We can just fly everybody out on the weekly. Oh, I see I see technically speaking. I suppose that's true, but uh, I mean
If we made more money that would change the whole equation a morphous concept that can take whatever form is most convenient for us
I basically I agree. Well, and you put it like that. I'm a little more sympathetic
Okay, okay. Let's go to our next one here. Uh center point x nexus ship thick. Okay. This is the one
Nexus, so let's let's hear what this one is. Okay three. Oh, sorry. One two three nexus
Come on, dude. Chili's on fire your people are rioting and the government is corrupt
Okay, like look if you actually want to get fucking out of chili and and come to america, dude
I I will actually unironically marry you to get you here, man
Come on come on. No sex required. No gayness. Just just straightforward, uh corrupt marriage. Let's go
Yeah, you got to do you got to pull a ross and holly and just have a sham marriage
Like how like ross did to get a fucking american green card or whatever. I swear to god. That's true. I I'm convinced
That's what happened. Yes. That's just it's just my pet theory, but I am convinced
That is fascinating. I mean just the timeline all line up for that stuff
Well, the reason I think that is because holly talked about jared being like the first person to like stir feelings in her
That like made her think like maybe i'm not asexual like I thought
Implying that she was asexual while she was with ross
So, well, you know, we do know asexual people who are in relationships despite that and I wonder if
You know, I wonder if yeah, but it'd be really a sexual person obviously, but whatever. I mean, obviously doesn't exist
We all know that but so, you know, well, okay
So if you're not fucking then the question is why and it's just like well ross is an australian
But I'm I think he obviously wanted to move to america because he did and a marriage with holly sure would be convenient for that
And you know their breakup sure was drama free, you know, so I think probably they just fucking did it for the green card like why not
You know, I mean they probably liked each other fine, you know
Um, I just think that there's I mean this this discovery of feelings or whatever
I mean that that's all cool and all that. Oh my god imagine not to be mean but like imagine pro jared
I know awakens your sexuality
Jesus christ. Well, it's because the guy wasn't because it happened. It's because it happened through it wasn't holly and jared
It was deith and strict snate
That's why I have to give the deith and strict's lecture
Her oc is not asexual you see and that's why it was able to happen and you know
Damn fast. There's so much so many layers to this story. I swear. That is interesting. That is interesting. Okay. Well, anyway, it is and I
Was just thinking about this yesterday
Well, that's actually a pretty funny story. Maybe I should tell it
Uh, yeah, it's details like that that make I don't know like all these stories like the lectures and whatever
Makes them interesting like digi's background. No lore about the dick stuff and my kingdom hearts. I don't know whatever anyway
All right next time. Let's go pc purgatory application
Uh, all right, let's see what's up with that on the count of three one two three
Oh, fuck. I'm sorry. I just forgot to start mine. I was I was totally spaced out
Oh, but you know what I forgot to say, okay
Everybody gets one and I was gonna say by the way nexus getting contact with center point in some way
He says he'll do it. Let's get you out of chile, buddy. Let's uh, it sounds pretty rough over there
Let's call his bluff. Okay. I'm ready and by the way, I don't understand
You know what? Okay, never mind the whole marriage for just weird purposes thing
Like what what is the actual like legal reason you're supposed to get married? Like do you have to like love?
I swear to god
I swear to god like part of me wants to just like like go on craigslist and just find someone
Okay, I told someone some of this and they were like you technically have to co-habitate. It's like, oh, well that's uh
Like I should literally just marry one of my roommates like just for the tax break
Like I would do it because I don't give a fuck
Because like who cares I just I'm just
If it would save me money, fuck it
Once we accepted that like I mean a gay marriage or whatever. It's fine. I don't care
It's just like, okay
That's obviously not for the traditional breeding practices that presumably marriage was for once we said like that's normal and fine
It seems to me. I'm not trying to make like a slippery slope disrespectful argument. I'm just saying we're now we're just saying it's like for basically
Any purpose we want which is fine. I don't care. So
Doors open. Yeah, I'm sure I'm sure anything involving getting it getting a break from the government
Well, there'll be extra scrutiny involved just because the government totally sucks
I just don't understand like what the standard is though
Like what is a legitimate marriage as opposed to an illegitimate one now. You gotta love each other. I don't I don't know
It seems like the the the condition is cohabitation
Oh, I guess that's fair. But I
I just aren't you already cohabitating with like five other people
Yeah, exactly. I should literally just fucking gay marry one of my roommates and
Why not not give a fuck?
Yeah, all right. Anyway, let's go to uh next one. Oh, right. We okay. This is a PC purgatory application
All right on the count of three one two three slaps
Relyaminated resume on table
What's up PCP? I'm here to apply for the new job known as the head of the PC purgatory
And my qualifications are simply this
For the past by the time you're listening to this
15 episodes, I've had one to three voicemails about her episode
And well, that's why I think I should be the head of the PC purgatory
And because none of my voicemails have either been grailed or jailed. So let me know what you think. Thanks
That is quite a distinction to be on that. Is this the same guy as the proving being god?
I believe that it is. I believe that it is. Okay, like I can't so
I I mean this guy obviously leaves a lot of fucking voicemails as we're hearing
This guy obviously leaves a lot to be desired
We know who blew through our fucking storage and got got us that warning from speak pipe now
Oh, yeah, it's your fault you fucking clod by the bio. You know what a small update on the speak pipe
We still have that message up top saying like you have full user account, but they're still going in
I mean, do I need to clear it out? I'm kind of want to see how far we can push this before it
You know here's my proposal mate. I feel like we wait. We see how it goes and if we do end up getting charged
I think we make this guy head of PC purgatory and his job is to pay that fee
Haha, ooh, I like this plan. This is a good plan. Although at any time we could just delete all the old voicemails
That might take a while, but uh, it'd be really funny. It'd be really funny
Um, good thing we have somebody in charge of the PC purgatory to do that task for us. Thank god for that
All right, I'm first voicemail
I'm all for I'm all for outsourcing that shit. Um, all right. Here we go. Next one is Linus lucky
All right, and let's play on the count of three one two three
Hey, I got a question for all the art boys in the pcb. How do you guys feel about people drawing glued fan art of your characters?
Like I know ben said he's really touched and honored when somebody takes the time to draw a character that he made
But would that change if they made like
Vince with a giant slong porpoise into his roommate? I forgot a name. I'm sorry
Also, I would like to use the zoomie as a flesh like goodbye
No, uh, I would feel I mean, I wouldn't be like mad
I wouldn't really like it just disappointed. I would just be kind of like
Yeah, I'd still be flatter that someone was drawing them, but I'd be kind of icked out
What if he's totally realistic? I mean like having vinston like an or an orgy or whatever, uh, uh, I mean that's possibly unrealistic
Oh, like like if it was like true to the character or something
Yeah, what if he was just jacking off alone in his room as I'm sure he does, uh, you know, yeah
That would be I mean, that's better. Obviously still still I just don't I just don't want to see that but like whatever right
My standards are way lower any any fan art you want to do is fine in my book
If that's that's how you want to make it happen then go for it
Yes, spread the word spread the word you retweet explicit flesh light usage is zoomie porn
If it's tasteful if it's tasteful
That sounds like a definition of tasteful
Well, you never know
Never know who you're dealing with but uh, that's yeah
If if twitter still had moments, I'd make a whole nsfw fan art moment and I'd put them all in there
So people could browse them. Okay. I would not I would not I would not retweet nsfw
Fan art, but I it's not that I not because I don't appreciate it
It's because it's not my brand anyway. My twitter is not a place for the
It's always it's always interesting when I see
Accounts I follow that are like seemingly not doing porn, but then they just retweets porn out of nowhere
And I'm like, I mean, that's fine. I'm not offended. Just wasn't expecting it. Yeah. Um, yeah. All right. Anyway
Oh, wait, there was something I was going to say about this. I can't remember what it is. So maybe I'll remember later
Okay, whatever. Let's move on for our last voicemail. Uh now this one. Okay. Here we go. This is
Which I believe is the number we selected last week as our, you know, we were asked to select a number
We memed him with pi and now we've chosen hard the number 119. Okay. All right
Because it was 119 backwards. Cool. So, uh, so let's hear what he has to say on the count of three
Finally one at long last the saga will conclude. Okay. One two three
Pretty good number. I was rooting for 144
But for the purpose of my bid, it doesn't really matter too much
But I still like 119 as well. So thanks for suggesting that
Anyways, this is where the bit was going
I'm about to drop some truth bombs
All right, the war on normal people page 119
Compounding the problem is that Americans now move across state lines and change jobs at
lower rates than at any point in the last several decades. Oh, no
The annual rate of interstate relocation dropped from about
70 to about
1.6 percent, you know what I'm bored. I'm bored. Let's just end it. Let's just end it. I'm done
You know, you know, I got the bit Munchie gave me. Yeah. Good. Good job. Good job
You mean us into playing three whole voicemails for you unless you're unless your voicemail god in which case it's like a hundred
He concluded it by the way, this in case you don't realize this is Andrew Yang's book book
Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah, I knew that the war on normal people you know, but I don't know about everybody
Munchie gave me his like info and signed me into his um audible account
So I have access to all of his audio books. Um, I listened to um
God in the state by uh, bakunin, um, which was fine
um
and then uh
I started listening to the war on normal people
And you just like I thought uh, I quit it because it was boring because I've heard all the interviews with him
I know
Right. I know everything he has to say his book is just like it's just like a longer version like it's like adam
I wasn't good. I didn't like it
I didn't wasn't learn anything. No, I feel a little bit bad about cutting that
Should we just in the editing let him play the whole thing before we know? Okay. All right. Fuck it. Go read
You know all the arguments, but does everybody else out there know all the all the points?
Yeah, but
Reading I feel like if you want to listen to short form versions of entry yang's points, there's more
Interesting ways of getting it. Okay. All right. I appreciate the bit though. Uh, mysterious stranger
We need like a name for this guy. It's fine. That's his name. Um, I'm just saying with pie
You could have gone 14 percent down page three or whatever. That's exactly what I was gonna say
Why not just start down a couple lines on page three? That's uncreative thinking god voice god
You need to step up your game, sir. You could have made it work
But I forgive you. I I forgive you. I just I just
I just was listening to it and I was like, uh, yeah
Yep, truckers if you listen to a bunch of a lot of american sure do work as truckers
Uh, yeah, automatic cars sure are gonna put them out of business soon
I've heard yawn. I've goes back to accruing capital maliciously and exploitatively
I've heard this before yang yang
How dare he make the same argument? I mean, that's probably why I mean, you know, bernie or whatever
I mean a lot of people are like, yeah, we've heard bernie's point. I mean, it's to his credit
He says the same thing, you know, because he's been consistent his entire political career
Yeah, it's not that it's not that like I've heard this before and it's dumb. It's just yeah, I've heard this before
It's you know, I don't need it. I don't need to hear it again
It's in you know, it's kind of similar to our I don't know at least my youtube content whatever you want like a currently
Like a constantly rolling
Exposure to new people because the old people are very aware of the things you say
So you want it just to access new people
So you want to like repackage your ideas in a way that's satisfying for old folks and like
Engaging and interesting for new people or something. Sure. Yeah, I don't know sure balancing acts
No
Oh, by the way people the reason we were doing that one two three thing
I almost forgot
This is what I was thinking of before that I forgot is because rhythm bot is like broken and not working or something
I don't know why it's doing that. That's why we had to count down weirdly
And we're sick of it. I don't know all shit. It's it we're having issues at issues
Elias are could have just edited out the countdowns and then
No, okay. Well, maybe we'll get to do that, but
It's got to be the real shit dude podcast experience. It's like you're here in my gross room with you, right?
One time on the pizza party podcast and ben is committed to bringing down the quality of our show
Speaking of speaking of legitimate podcast experience like we do very little uh, like cutting and tweaking at least historically we have
So I I feel like that's at least somewhat to our credit that we're able to be engaging in high
That's true for the most part
But I was curious if did you said on his appearance on the on the piece of party podcast years ago
They like heavily edited it and sped it up actually did they do that to yours as well ben? Not that I
Know of I don't think so. Okay, they they they made um
Some very only do it if they think it needs it. I think pan made some very minor like cuts
But like for the most part it's just as as were recorded just upload it as is
Okay, I was and you know actually that reminds me there was another voicemail
I didn't play that was someone saying like ben it's one thing for you to come on the pcp and make your long political points
It's another thing to go on pan pizzas
Podcast and interject your obnoxious unwanted political discourse into their their precious baby
How could you do such a thing? Those fucking cowards wouldn't even agree that we should smash capitalism
Oh, those those those fools those rank amateurs
They wouldn't even they didn't even have anyone in mind that they're voting for in the democratic primaries on it
Like I'm honestly shocked and a little bit embarrassed for them
When is the primary? Is there like time to figure that out? It's like next year, isn't it?
It's it's it's not a good amount of time. It's a way as a way
But you should have a fucking clue at this point. All right
You are overestimating the political engagement of your average cartoon reviewer on youtube
What what do you mean?
No, come on. Uh, don't they know how much sur plus capitals being removed from them? They need they need they need burning more than anyone
They just don't know to pay for their fucking to pay their fucking
Animation school bills like like debt that they went into like because fucking go fund me is not gonna make it for 99% of them
They just need to open up that Kickstarter get that cool 12 grand a year and you know
Engaging I have achieved I have achieved the freedom dividend and I did it and I did it through Kickstarter, baby
Although papers did it for me
I just want to reiterate because I found this fascinating the way that like and I I said this to you in our chat, which was just like
Uh, actually, you know of interest my dad and I assume, you know, I assume your dad as well
Has been like donating. He's been just been giving us like a couple hundred bucks every once in a while
Putting it into like a retirement fund. Oh
Well, he does that he does that for like a um, it's like a holiday like a christmas and birthdays
He'll put like a deposit is like a gift
Yeah, he'll put like a deposit. He'll deposit some money into like a um
Like a like a Roth IRA fund
Basically, but what what I found interesting was for years. He'd been begging me to like Nate. It's in a fund
That's like not making any money. I need you like it's it's in this company that like does investment for you
What you're supposed to do
Fidelity I'm learning all this for the first time. I know I did it. I went like no I didn't because I'm an idiot
No, I finally did I finally did
Take his advice and go and like call the company up and have them put it into a
Um, well, there's a couple the one that they yeah
I had them put it into a thing called fidelity go, which is a like a mutual yeah a mutual fund that's managed by an algorithm
Yeah, so so what it is for those who don't know it's like
I mean, it's it is I assume yours is still a because there's there's like tax reasons like we can't get the money until we retire
It is still an IRA, but it is okay
So so we have like the same thing then I think and it's that you you you put money into it and the people at fidelity
Kindly invest that money for you. And so now technically both of us like own some small stop
I mean, that's what that's what a mutual fund is. That's what it is. I'm learning
I had no idea about any of this shit until just now and so now it's like so I'm finally getting it
I'm like now I actually have a real stake in like the the economy the economy
And if if the market does well those stocks will like increase in value and I will when I retire
Gain money. I mean, that's that's the idea. That's the idea
Theoretically yes
So like up to this point. I kind of didn't understand why like I like people would say like, oh no the market's doing bad
My retirement money. I'm like, don't you like why would that affect your retirement money?
I don't understand but it's because your investments have invested in this shit. Yes
It all it all makes sense to me now
I don't know my best thing just sounds like a way of putting a ball and chain around you and tying you down to this capitalist system
So when ben blows it up everyone's involved
Oh, yeah, I mean draw. I should withdraw my funds before I start my real revolutionary praxis
True, although you'll have you'll lose like taxed some amount it like because it's it's the reason
So this is the interesting thing you like quote-unquote you can't take it out until you retire
But if you do it just gets taxed like I don't know some pretty decent amount
So like 10 or 20 percent or something which can be a lot if it's like your your you know retirement fund or whatever
So you want to just leave it there and let them like that's why it's all making sense to me now now
Because all that money's there. It's supposed to be there until I retire
We you're supposed to pump money into it everyone, you know regularly
So more money is there can be invested the whole market grows
It's like I now have a stake in the economy doing well
That isn't like solely dependent on just the value of the american dollar, which was everything I had up to this point
That's where like all my money was now
it
Now I like the mark if the market grows my investment in the market grows and I'll have more money
So I hope america doesn't crash and all those all those good things. It's funny. I find uh, did you?
Do you just bring this up because you were
interested in talking about
The market and interest rates and stuff
I mean because because now yes because now I finally actually have like
An actual experience of real capitalism like I get it now. I'm in there. I'm doing it
And like I feel the urge to like look at the markets and and and and here's the here's the dark cloud
I'm sort of getting it because right now. What if somebody came to me?
Let's say I was I had like a billion dollars invested and someone was like, oh, hey, Nate
Did you know like these big companies that perhaps you have lots of like stock in they're actually like
Exploiting their workers and they're like doing bad things and they're you know, I don't know polluting the environment
And they're like, Nate, we should like tell people
I want you to do it for some reason and I'm like, oh, but I have a lot of stock invested in them
So I think I'm just gonna like not tell the world about these horrible things these companies doing so I can personally profit
From their growth and I'm like, I'm starting to see the picture. I'm starting to get it
You should sell your stock immediately because someone else will do it and then
You can like get fucked. That's what I would do. Um, well, yeah, yeah, I mean, I'm going to keep doing it
I mean, it's first of all, it's not that much money and I find it interesting
But like I'm I'm getting why these things can be bad and how bad negative things can happen as a result
you you're
Are you saying that you are
Understanding why a purely profit-motivated system might have downsides. That's correct, Ben. That's correct
Now you'll stand by it seems like a pretty good system for for helping out the world
And I think it comes down to us as individuals to police these people if they're doing good or bad things
But I can see I'm just saying I can see I see why corruption could be rampant in the system and uh
Could be a new perspective now that I've got experience. Yeah, I don't know might it might theoretically run rampant
It might perhaps it's possible. Yeah, everyone wants a word with you
Um, I should relook at those things with my newfound understanding of of these of these things. Um and ron good boys
It's uh, you know, it was kind of a hassle
But uh, it was a pretty good. It was a pretty good fucking gift for dad to do to set up a fucking IRA
I'm sure I'll appreciate it
Sure, I'll appreciate that in the future. Like I could theoretically have done it myself, but I certainly wasn't going to
Well, you know, the other thing was while I was doing this
I opened up another like a non-retirement account that's basically just like investing in the market
And I'm thinking about just like putting some money in there of my own
I should keep my like like I keep my fucking money in a checking account and like I need to not do that
Yeah, my money's been in a checking account as well and it is retarded
It is stupid and I'm just losing out like every time I go to my bank. They're like, do you want to open a savings account? I'm like, uh,
that's
Work by
Yeah, it's just the worst idea financially uneducated as a populace and these things are so important. They keep us under their capitalist thumb
Well, we luckily we have the internet. They can't repress our uprising now as us. We've become ethical responsible investors and owners of capital
That's what we need to do as a populace
And uh, I'm a I'm a work on it seize the means of investment
Exactly. There you go. Um, so there I thought that was an interesting story. Um, I think this is cool
I'll let you know how it goes boys. I'm keeping an eye on the market. I'm invested in the outcome
That's why they call it that
I got the fidelity app on my phone now. So like I I'm thinking really you're so you're that into it
Well, I mean, let's not exaggerate here. I I downloaded the app
I checked it like once when I first got it. So like I'm not like
I mean, I this we're like there was an episode of Seinfeld where Seinfeld invests like $5,000 in the market
I called them up. I had them put it into fidelity go and then I was like in like six months
I'll call back and ask like how it's going and if it's like if I've lost all my money. I'll be like, fuck you
Uninvest now
I see that's the great thing by dad just giving us this money in this in this fund
Like I didn't have to like weigh like I wanted to invest this money
Do I this is not like this is not like a bunch of free money trust fund
This is like a collective amount that has been built up over like years and years of like him putting small amounts in
For like Christmas and birthdays and stuff. Very true. This is not like, oh, you just set us up with a fucking trust fund or whatever
Indeed indeed, although I suspect we will inherit a good amount of money
When they kick the bucket, but we'll see we'll see how that goes one day ladies. Um
I mean, maybe I mean they own I mean they own a house never know firsthand
I mean, they do own a house. So I mean, that's that's a considerable
That's a considerable value to be extracted. I mean, I'll just lay it
I mean, I was talking to dad yesterday about this and I I mean dad was we were joking about this and I was just like
Dad, have you ever considered like putting a cap on your lifespans that you don't use up all my money when you're, you know
Decrepit and you know, what do you think about that? And he was like
Generously, he said, Nate, I knew you're half joking about that and uh, only half joking dad only half joking
I mean, this really happened. This really happened. I mean it was in fact a joke
But every joke has a little kernel of truth to it, you know
Yeah, that's what i'm saying. Michelle jokes mean something. You can't just say, oh, that's just a joke. Don't worry about it. No
What's the joke? What does it mean? What's the joke sir? What's the joke sir?
What's the joke sir? That's my new thing
I'm gonna tweet that at trump every day
What's the joke sir? What's so funny sir? Have you no shame sir?
You know, I'll just a final point on it. It seems to me a little bit silly
Oh, you know what? I guess to be fair
I get why people don't like when the president is obviously being an asshole and and joking
But I think it is pretty clear. He is in fact joking and much of this thing
I mean, I guess some of the time is that appropriate. Is that appropriate?
That's debatable. That's debatable. I mean, but when people say it is entertaining and that's what i'm on twitter.com for
I like we just you got to take the argument for what it actually is and if people are like
Trump really did stack those hamburgers a mile high fact-checked not in fact true
Um, you know, which is just being a little silly. Is that a specific reference that I don't know?
At one point
Trump literally said that we stacked hamburgers a mile high and like factcheck.org they did the research turns out debunked
He did not stack those. Do you that would be that would be literally
75 000 hamburger patties, which you know what seems unrealistic frankly on its face
We have no reports of such a stack
Not one eyewitness account, but trust deranged words
so
You know, thank god, we're here to be the fact-checkers. All right, there you go. I see that's I see that's all there is to it
Um, so I I'm glad you're all now voting trump in 2020. It's gonna be a good time. That's right. Can't wait. I'm glad we converted you
This episode of the pro crassness podcast
That's the stuff
And uh patron.com slash the pro crassinators uh one dollar patron discord five dollars
30 bonus episodes with another hot one coming to you soon. It's gonna be a good time
And what else we got at tb crassinators on twitter?
PCB minecraft is still under construction. But by the time you hear this, I think it will be back up and running
No, they said it though. I I'm saying it. I'm saying it. We're we're in good shape. I want to do more
I want to get in there. I haven't been in the new server yet
That I really think we're very close to it being finished and it will be back up and running
If I play in this minecraft server, it will be the second time I've ever played minecraft in my life
Well, it's gonna be a great time. I can guarantee that. It's never been a better time to start
It's never been a hotter topic
It's just unironically let me just say unironically the community of people that have come to that minecraft server are hugely active
Even though the server is down
And we've got like 80 people who pledged that's a huge community way bigger than I expected it to be
People seem to really like the couple people that were hanging out in Bufalantopia. Can we yeah, can we please burn down Bufalantopia?
Then we will definitely go back to Bufalantopia. Absolutely
Yeah, okay, can't leave that chapter. I can't I was thinking I was thinking the the next time we stream we should start on Bufalantopia
And like make it our our final visit. I say it every episode, but I
We can't we can't leave it like no
Just like Clyde Cash and Jack Thaddeus. We can't die by their hand
We can't let them kill us by ending the server. We have to be the one to put Bufalantopia down
You know, we should do we should ceremony and then go to the server and start new phalantopia or both or both
On tupia or whatever the fuck we want to go now new phalantopia
Head on down but patron a patreon.com slash pcb minecraft five dollars for your monthly joining and then head on south
Follow the path that's that's well trodden down to cool guy village where all the cool guys are building their houses
But perhaps somewhere else out in the ether. We'll have a new phalantopia. We'll be out there where the new phalantope
Be uh, oh
Yeah, it'll be
Oh, that sounds great, but we should we should go to Bufalantopia
We should everyone should release their claims and then we should all go buck wild with the flint and steel and just lighted all the blaze
Yes, let it all burn down
It sounds good. We have burned down your Bufalant's
It's a great time. So uh, I'll update you. Hopefully I'll be able to tell you affirmatively. We're back in business next week, but uh
Check it. Check it. Maybe by the time you hear this, we'll be back. We'll see. Okay. Anyway, that's it end of episode
Thanks for being here. See you next week patron us. Give us money t-shirts t-spring. Just be cool. Etc. Etc.
Goodbye
You