Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
If you're listening to this, it is Friday. It's 6.20pm.
They already know that.
That's useless information.
Oh my god. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I have nothing to talk about. Let's go to voicemails.
No. Let's talk about Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
Fine. Very well. How's that going?
It's going quite well.
The numbers go up. I see number go up.
The number go up is we are at 79 backers as of recording. 2,571 pounds pledged. We're less than 500 away from the Redman...
Zeen.
I got it. I got it. I was thinking about it.
I know. I could tell you were thinking. And I wanted to make sure you came to the right conclusion.
You could have made fun of me if I got it wrong. You can't give it to me that easy.
I jumped the gun. I jumped the gun.
It's getting pretty close to the Redman Zeen. It's more than halfway towards the plush.
The plush.
Yes. I got the sample of the plush. I didn't get a sample. I got an image sent to me of the progress on the sample.
They've made a little first draft. They said, hey, do you want any changes?
I said a few things about it. But mostly, it's great. And it looks exactly like I wanted it.
It looks nice. How big is it?
It's a smaller plush than the Pumpk one. Although Pumpk is artificially big because her legs are really long and thin.
It's about six inches tall and quite round. You could put it on your desk. You could put it on a dog.
A dog could play with it. You could throw it. It's the sort of thing you could grab with one hand and you could have it.
That's the sort of feeling I wanted. You could just grab its face and just look at me.
That's cool. We got 23 days to go.
It's pretty good. It's pretty soft. Do you have the graph? Does it show you the graph of the money?
How do I find that? I'm on the side right now.
It's somewhere in the dashboard. Let me see. I can look at my old account.
Yeah, now I found it.
Show me the graph. I like the graph.
Here it is. Put it in general chat.
There we go. That's a pretty sharp beginning.
Yeah, it is. Then it kind of accelerated a little bit the two days ago.
Maybe that was the bump from the episode coming out?
Yeah, the episode coming out or one of the streams I did.
I'm going to be streaming more often for the opportunity to plug that while I'm playing.
If people somehow haven't, they're not on the Twitter and they're on my Twitch.
They're like, oh, I didn't know you were doing that. It'll be a good moment.
You were playing, what was it, House Flipper?
I was playing House Flipper the other day. I played Hollow Knight I think yesterday.
Right. I didn't catch that one.
That one was fun. I started off having no knowledge of Fortnite of Hollow Knight.
Hollow Knight is basically the same.
Have you not played Hollow Knight before?
I've never beaten it. I got four hours in once and then I stopped and that's it.
I played it through the first time with all the DLC.
It's a little awkward how all the DLC stuff kind of just exists on top of everything else.
I have no idea what it looks like without DLC if I even have it.
You might not be seeing it yet, but there's quests that are like, you got to go around and do stuff
and you got to collect shit and it's like shit that you...
When it released, I think the point was to kind of make you to go and re-explore the world with a new goal in mind.
But having it be present alongside everything else when you're playing the game
for the first time is a little bit like, wait, I got to do...
What are these things around? I got to get these too? Okay, I guess.
I don't know whether this is a DLC thing, but I saw these weird little trees, little bushes
and I couldn't do anything with them. I thought maybe they were special.
Are they the little dream catcher looking trees?
Are they curved, like bonsai trees with outlighted circles on them?
I don't know what they are, like little wheels.
I think I know... I don't think that's DLC stuff, although I don't even know what is DLC.
I know that the Grim Troop is... I'm calling it DLC.
I think the better word is Expansion Pack or whatever, because it was added to the game later.
I think that's like Dream Nail stuff, that tree, maybe. Do you have the Dream Nail?
I'm very early on. I've beaten the Screamy... the guy on the...
Oh God, I can't remember any of the places.
Where there's this rain and there's a city and you go up the tower
and there's that magic guy who has the magic and he throws at you.
Oh, I hate that guy, yeah.
You kill that guy and then you get the thing that makes you go smash down through glass panes.
Yeah, what's the place called? The City of Tears? I love that place.
City of Tears, yeah. It's my favorite location.
And then I got that and then I went down over to the crystal mines and that's where I stopped.
Yes, good. Did you meet that bug that sings?
There's a bug in the crystal mines that sings.
Oh, I haven't gone very far into the crystal mines. I was looking for the map and then I realized I had been going for like four and a half hours.
Keep an eye out for it, I guess.
I found the cute fat lady bug who's really shy and she makes a plush of you and writes fanfic about you when you save her.
Why don't I remember that?
You save her and she goes back and then she's on the bench and if you sit on the bench and wait for a few seconds she blushes.
What? Why don't I remember this? Oh no.
And then she's in one of the buildings off to the side and then sometimes it's like a...
I think the first time you go in there there's like a health item shard, mask shard and that was cool.
But next to her bed there's like a little fanfic she writes about the exploits of you, the white savior she calls you.
Base.
And because you're a little skull face.
And yeah, it starts off with just like a plush and then there's a poster and then there's like a bigger plush and then the fanfic continues.
She has dreams about you. It's kind of epic.
You know, I have... I think I know what you're talking about now, but I don't want to say anything.
I think I would spoil it. I think there might be some stuff going on out there that maybe you haven't seen yet.
Oh no.
I'll tell you, the one thing I am spoiled for is the grubs. If you save all the grubs, the main grub man is like, haha, thank you.
And then he eats them.
Yeah, I think that's true. I think that's true.
It's like, oh, it's scary. It's like fucked up. You just got played.
But it's like, I think it's like implied somewhere in the in-game like enemy description that like that's like normal and that's like part of the grub life cycle.
Like they're not dead, maybe. They're just inside of him.
So I think maybe it's not that fucked up.
That's just vor propaganda.
Yeah, I don't know. I think it's a little ambiguous. It's like, oh, it's, you thought you were doing a good thing, but I don't know. It was a bad thing.
Oh, but maybe it's not a bad thing, though.
Maybe it's okay.
Yeah.
Good game. A little bit the samey locations wise. A lot of the places look the same in Hollow Knight.
In Hollow Knight? Yeah, a couple places.
I mean, I've got to a point where I can, I'm starting to like differentiate the different places.
And like, I like it. I think the color palette is restrictive, but it works.
I think I, I think I, oh, I beat the Radiance and I beat Grim. I never did the like Godseeker stuff.
That stuff is like another like expansion pack thing. I never did anything.
That's like the, the true like ultimate bosses are in the Godseeker, but I didn't do them because it just didn't seem that interesting.
I like the Castlevania, if that was like a, like a boss rush kind of thing, I don't care about that that much.
I like the side scrollly exploration Castlevania bullshit.
Yeah, I'm not like, I'm not, I'm not that hardcore of a gamer.
Radiance was really hard, the final boss. I got stuck on her for, I think I got stuck on her for a while and I stopped playing for a while and I was, and it took me a long time to finally come back to it and beat her.
God, she's cool though. So fucking cool. She is the sun.
What a, what a visual. I don't know any of that. Oh, well, it's not, it's not literally true, but I don't know, you'll, you'll see, we'll see what I mean.
There's, there's bugs and some of them are knights and some of them are hollow. I mean, what more do I need?
She's, she's not, when I say that she, she is not like the actual sun up in the sky above hollownests. That's not, that's not the case.
Okay, I won't say anymore, but it's a good fucking video game.
I might play more of that on stream on twitch.tv slash gibbon take.
I am very bad with scheduling, so I, I have no plans to do it in any particular day, but I won't be doing it on Sundays because that's PCP recording.
I won't be doing it on Fridays because the PCP comes out or maybe I could, I don't know, there's no reason I couldn't.
But also on Wednesdays, we usually do heckles for shackles.
Yeah, true, true.
So some other time, maybe a Monday or a Tuesday.
You know what I did? You know, I started doing it yesterday. I actually started writing up the, the final Road to Radcon chapter.
I got like one page of it written. I wanted to be, I don't know how long I want it to be.
It's probably stupid, but I mean, you know, that's fine.
Are you going to attempt to mimic the writing style or is it just going to be the Benson chapter?
I, I, I would like to try to do that. I don't know how successful I would be.
I feel like I'm doing my best to mimic the writing style, but I, I don't, I think it's not, I think you can tell I wrote it, which is like, I don't know what to do about that.
Well, you could do your best. I mean, I'm sure I'm doing my best. I'm doing my best.
It's, it's going to be dumb. It's going to be goofy. And it should be a hoot.
Yeah, I tried, I tried getting drunk and writing it because I thought that that would be the right mindset to do it in, but it didn't work.
It didn't work that well. I just kind of didn't do it and I'm hungover this morning and I feel sick.
So, you know, didn't, didn't, huh?
What time is over there?
Oh, I guess it's, I guess it's not morning. It's 3 30pm. Well, but I only woke up at like noon, so it feels early.
I woke up at noon as well. So it's noon, it's noon days, these days.
I hung, I hung out with, I hung out with Munchie and Kazi and Ethan and Steve and, and Azkan and Zen Huxedable yesterday and I slept over on their couch.
Cool.
Yeah, it was pretty fun. We went and got ramen. It was good. You got ice cream. It was really good. It was really good.
I ate a bunch of food.
So I saw an image. I played smash of VR somewhere.
Oh, did he? Yeah, it's at the right. I forgot. We went to like a video. It's like a video game cafe.
It was goofy, but they had, they had an Oculus Rift that we took turns using a little bit.
I didn't, I didn't do it. I surrendered my time because I own an Oculus Rift.
The privilege.
Yes. They played a bunch of like Beat Saber and shit. Kazi literally just like did Google Earth and like looked around Google Earth in the VR headset.
You know, I would have never thought to do that, but that is possible with 360 everything.
Yeah, she was just like flying around. Was it Beijing, I think? Just looking at buildings.
Beijing.
Maybe it was Beijing.
Maybe Hong Kong. I don't think, does China not have Google stuff in it? I thought that was.
It wasn't Hong Kong. You can, surely you can see Beijing on Google Earth.
Check. Well, I don't know. I don't feel like you can't see Street View and stuff. Like they don't have Street View for that country.
Weird. Maybe that's true. I didn't even think, I didn't even consider that.
Like the China says, you can't have people drive cars and take pictures of all of our secrets.
Yeah, maybe, maybe so.
Maybe Google Earth is different from Google Maps. Maybe that's what I'm thinking.
I think it's the same. Like I think Street View is the same images for both.
Yeah, it would be, wouldn't it?
It must be.
Where's Beijing?
I don't know.
I remember seeing the 2008 fucking Olympics. I remember it must have seen it on the map somewhere.
It's like, it's like a special place.
It's not inland, is it?
Most big things are by a river.
Most big things are on the coast or on the river, yeah.
It's the lifeblood. It's the lifeblood of society. It's water.
Water, water.
What has thou dunced?
Dunced? Oh, it is kind of inland. It's quite north.
Oh, I'm zooming. Okay, so Google does have...
How do I be down on the earth?
This is a riveting podcast content.
You can play along, guys. Play along.
Beijing is.
Beijing.
Go to Google that map.
Zoom in. Like flick your mouse to the left once, twice.
Get a plane ticket to Beijing and take a picture and send it to Google for Street View so we can see you.
Oh, alright. You can go down onto individuals' photographs.
So this person took a 360 photograph in Beijing and I can go and see this photograph from their perspective.
Like a Google employee or something?
No, no, just like a person. They uploaded their location to Google.
Oh.
And now the 360 image is...
Weird.
Seable.
So wait.
It's insane. It's madness.
So there's this big, epic, like Earth Kingdom temple house.
I'm going to put my old guy...
China totally ripped off the...
Right in the middle.
Ripped off Avatar, in my opinion.
Yeah.
I mean, what the fuck? Okay.
Just like Mulan. I'm there.
Just like...
It's just like that movie.
Just like Disney.
It's just like media.
It's like, aw, Pog.
When I see...
I meet a Chinese person and I go, it's just like Mulan.
I've seen this movie.
Oh dear. This is cool though.
I didn't know you could see any of China.
I thought it was like Google no-no zone.
Google no-no zone.
Yeah.
Based.
Anyway, there was...
Yes, there was VR.
There was video games.
And we ate food and I don't know.
And then I got drunk and I passed out and now I'm hungover.
And that was my...
Oh, and I practiced inkling.
I won't say I got a little good at playing inkling in Smash,
but I sort of figured the character out a little bit.
And that was kind of fun.
You know, when you squirt the ink, it's good.
You should be squirting ink.
You should be shooting ink when you're inkling.
That's the trick.
You should be squirting.
My problem in Smash is that I don't guard and I don't roll.
Yeah, why would you do that when you could attack and squirt ink?
That's right.
Anytime you're not squirting ink as inkling is just waste of time.
You're just losing...
You're surrendering board state.
You've got to be putting ink on the ground all the time.
I...
There were so many times I would be like,
yes, I've set up for the kill.
Yes, I've got them.
I've got them in my sights.
And then I pull out the roller and I do the forward...
I think it's the forward B rolling attack.
And then there's no ink and it just doesn't work.
And then they go, aha!
And they punish me because I wasn't looking at the bar.
I wasn't looking at the ink meter.
It's a nightmare.
It's a fucking nightmare.
And you can't refill the ink meter unless it's already empty, I think,
unless you can and I just never figured out how to do it.
That would be embarrassing.
Did you play as Minecraft Steve?
No!
That's so crazy.
But Zen was playing as Creeper.
But Creeper is not a Minecraft Steve re-skin.
He's a me-fighter for some reason.
He's just a me-fighter brawler, I guess.
I don't know why they did that.
I feel like he should be Steve, but he's not.
He should have a little pickaxe.
He should go ding, ding, ding, ding, ding up stuff.
You know what I thought?
I was thinking about like Mario Sunshine and how the flood,
you get the water and you splash and you get rid of all the goop.
True.
You get exactly the same sort of goop as like the Splatoon kids.
Splatoon?
Like what if Mario from Mario Sunshine with the flood versus the Splatoon?
Like the Splatoon splats.
It's like, dude, asymmetrical multiplayer where one player,
One giant Mario.
It's a team of Splatoons.
Oh my god, that would be so funny.
What if in like Splatoon 3 they have it as a multiplayer mode
where like four players play as inklings
and one player plays as Mario from Mario Sunshine with the flood?
It just seems like such an obvious versus.
But because Mario Sunshine is so old, it'll never happen officially.
I'll never acknowledge the idea.
Now that you say it, it makes perfect sense.
It makes perfect sense and I want it.
These squids are just trying to make a mess and Mario is like,
No, do not make a mess.
So you splash.
Yes, true, true.
Man, Splatoon is so fucking cool.
Aesthetically, I mean.
I'm pretty bad at it.
I'm pretty bad at most competitive games and shooters in particular.
There's too much splash and going on.
There's just too much dang ink.
It's a bad influence.
Oh, I can't believe they would depict someone squirting ink in a piece of media.
Do they have a fountain pen weapon yet?
Do they have like a fountain pen sniper rifle?
I feel like they do, but I don't know.
Maybe not.
It seems like something they would have.
No, they got rollers, they got brushes, they got buckets, and they got guns.
You know what else? Okami.
Okami, a mattress who dip the god dog brush tail and draw stuff with it, with the ink.
I think I saw, I watched Tim Rogers' review of Okami and he didn't like it that much.
What did he say?
He said that obviously it looks great and the art style is great,
but the game is basically just a Zelda and as a Zelda it's not that impressive.
It's like a pretty mediocre Zelda, which I guess that makes sense.
I think I've heard that comparison before, but I don't like Zelda because I don't like the way it looks so there.
Yeah, true.
Actually Wind Waker is really nice.
Twilight Princess is ugly and that's it.
The only 3D Zelda I've ever played is Ocarina, which I went back and replayed it just a couple years ago just to know what the deal was.
Is Ocarina one of those games where it's completely impossible to figure out unless you have the strategy guide like the first Zelda?
I mean that's not impossible, but there's a lot of esoteric things in the first Zelda game.
It's not like that, it's not like that.
No, I think you could beat Ocarina without a strategy.
No, there's that one thing where you have to give the fish to the thing to make it open its mouth.
I think that part is a little bit like how would you know to do that?
It's a jub-jub? Is that how you get into jub-jub's belly?
Jabba's belly? Who's fucking belly do you go in with the Zora Princess?
Wait, have I played this game? Have I played Ocarina? I don't even know. I feel like I've watched so much of it.
And I remember playing it briefly, but I don't know how long I played it.
It definitely didn't win. Definitely did not beat the game, but...
I beat Ocarina, and then I thought like, boy, everyone says Majora's Mask is the good one.
Maybe I should have played Majora's Mask instead, but now I don't want to because even though I know that they're completely different games,
they look similar, so I feel like I kind of got a lot of the experience from playing the first one,
which is probably wrong, and it's probably a stupid way to look at it, but instinctively that's how I feel.
I already played the game with all the same assets, even if it's a different game, so I'm done.
I guess I'm not that much of a Zelda head. I played a bunch of the 2D ones.
I mean, I actually beat Zelda 2 Link's Awakening.
Wow.
It was the one nobody plays, the one nobody likes.
I've heard people like it. It's just really difficult.
It is really difficult. I beat it, and I beat the original Zelda 1, maybe like 7 or 8 years ago.
I used guides for both. I just had a lot of free time, and I had NES, and I was like,
I had these games as kids, and I never beat them because I was a dumb kid, so I'm going to do it, and I did.
My feeling with Mario and Zelda and stuff is that I didn't even know what that shit was.
Mario?
Well, I think I knew Mario because I'd seen him in gaming magazines, but I'd never had a Nintendo 64.
To me, Nintendo was entirely Pokémon, and then I didn't know any of that stuff until the angry video game nerd taught me all about the NES.
I was like, whoa, what? That's what the NES was.
When in Pokémon Blue, they said the player played with the NES.
I thought that was someone's NES bit, like someone's name.
I didn't get it, and then I got it. That was my introduction.
So I don't have desire to go back, necessarily, and play all these old games from my childhood.
They're games from AVGN's childhood, which is somewhat my childhood, a little bit.
My young teenagerhood or something.
Fuck that guy. Fuck reviews. Fuck internet. Fuck videos. No.
I will never listen to another video game review ever again because they're all liars.
What about all of those ones you're about to watch?
Well, I'll do those, obviously. Obviously, I'm still going to watch those.
But after that, I'm done. It's over.
I genuinely listen to... I genuinely spend a lot more time listening to people talk about media than I do just consuming media.
I don't know if that's a problem. I don't know if that's weird, but...
I think it's just because it's easy.
A piece of review, you go into it expecting them to explain everything, and they're just going to tell you all about it.
You don't need to lift a finger. You don't even need to press start.
You don't need to do any work to figure out what the fuck's up with this game.
I have no interest in watching a movie and any movies at all.
But I am interested if someone is like, this movie says something about our society.
I am interested to be like, oh, what do you think it says about our society?
Yeah, that's where I'm at with media, I guess.
Did you watch Parasite?
No, I didn't see Parasite.
You probably heard movie reviews, though, about it.
I don't know if I heard any reviews. I mean, I definitely heard people talk about it.
I don't know if I watched any reviews.
It's a really good one, but everyone would say that.
It seemed good. It seemed like a good film.
It's one of the only movies of the last 25 years that I've watched.
I don't watch movies, really.
But I was forced to watch that one.
Because somebody said please, and I was like, okay.
I watched, I think like the last movie, oh no, I watched The Witch, The Vavitch a couple months ago.
And I was pretty good.
And I watched, the only time I watched movies are when I met my parents' house.
Yeah, I watched The Witch.
And before that, like Christmas, I watched Flushed Away, The Artman.
That movie's good. That movie's actually good.
It's all right.
I thought it was better than all right.
I was like, wow, that sure was a compelling, pretty conventional three act structure that I just experienced.
God, I love that glistening three act structure.
It worked for me.
What was it?
I was going to say, oh, and I watched that one.
What's the one with Snake Plissken?
That one.
Escape from New York.
I watched Escape from New York also at Christmas with my parents for some reason.
That's the only time.
Flushed Away and Escape from New York basically the same.
It's, you know, there's the call to action.
There's the, you know, the crossing the threshold, the meeting with the goddess, the whatever thing that happens.
The lowest point in the second act, obviously, they're the same.
There's only seven stories that have ever been told, and those are two of them.
Flushed Away and Escape from New York.
Leaving only five possible new stories to be made.
That's right.
Lord of Ghosts was one of them.
So that one's taken now.
That one's taken too.
Yeah.
It's over.
God, I still, I still gotta write the, I keep meaning to, obviously.
It's like the classic dilemma.
Oh, but I kept meaning to do it, but I just didn't do it.
Well, I guess I'll just continue.
Like who cares?
It's like, it'll be done when it's done.
Gotta write the things.
I also want to.
You should, don't be like me.
Don't be like me and put it off.
I put it off for so long doing my vapor arts.
It was really a mistake and foolish of me.
Some, some days I'll wake up and I'm like, okay, well, I gotta buy ingredients so that
I can cook dinner.
That's today's goal.
I go out, I get the ingredients, I come back.
I sit around and I'm like, well, I'll, I'll work on it after I cook dinner because that's
it'll take a little while.
I cook dinner.
I eat it.
And I'm like, well, I won't do it.
The day's over.
I did one thing.
That's enough.
I'm accomplished.
Fair.
I've, I've done in exactly one thing.
And oh, look at the Kickstarter as a whole other person.
You know what?
Everything's going well.
I don't need to work today.
Yeah.
I got, I'm, you got that one, uh, you got that one pledge that's today paid for.
I know the feeling.
Uh, I, I actually had a run recently of maybe like two weeks or so where I was like feverishly.
I got into like a mood or something.
I got into the headspace where I was feverishly grinding out stuff for the phantom's revenge
game.
Yeah.
You mentioned I would like, I was basically doing nothing but that for like, and then I,
I looked back at my, um, cause you know, I have the, I have the secret chat where I post
like updates and stuff that I'm working on for it in my, in my, my server.
My server is not patrons only, but that channel is for his patron channel.
And I look back at like the stuff I'm posting and I realized I spent basically the entire
month of June just grinding out, uh, basically enemy sprites and like sprites for the like
attack animations.
Uh, I didn't realize I spent like a whole month doing it, but I sure did and it really took
that long.
It wasn't like I was just fucking around.
So I don't know.
Boy, I sure hope they came out good because I spent a really long time on them.
Uh, but, uh, I guess it was worth it.
I guess I, I think it's looking pretty good.
I had hoped that the game would be done by now, but it's not.
And that's just the way the cookie crumbles sometimes.
Yeah.
But yeah, I was, I was really grinding.
I was really grinding.
Uh, and then a couple of days ago, I think I was like, I can't, I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
And I fell off and I lost my momentum and then I didn't do anything this weekend on it.
So I need to try and get myself back into another one of those sprints because I have a bunch
more things I need to do.
Um, it's getting, it's pretty close to being done, but like the things that I have left
to do are things that I don't exactly know how long it will take me.
Uh, then it'll take ages because you'll come in, you'll come up to a point where like,
yeah, I mean, I've got to do this one thing, but like one thing that you don't know how to do
contains within it hundreds of hours of learning that you need to do or preparation.
I don't know.
It's just one of those sort of things.
If you are, if you're not sure how long something's going to take, it'll probably take an extremely long time.
The game, the demo that I put out was eight rooms long.
And I needed, I wanted every room to have a cutscene, but not every room would have like a real cutscene.
Some rooms would just have like one line of dialogue and that's, and that's the scene.
Um, so some, some, a couple of the rooms would have fairly extensive, maybe like two of the rooms
would have an actual like extensive cutscene where like a character walks around, does animations,
does stuff beyond just like say a line.
And then I, I need to add, I need to add another room.
There's another room that needs to be added that will also have a pretty extensive cutscene in it, take place in it.
Um, and then I added a couple of features.
I added a couple of new like battle commands to it that they work, but I think they need to be debugged a little bit.
I think they, they act a little weird sometimes in like certain outlier situations.
Like when the, like when you die while you're doing them, then like the animation looks weird.
And I'm like, okay, I have to fix that.
So it doesn't look weird when that happens.
Um, you know, that, that kind of thing debugging basically.
Um, the cutscenes though, the cutscenes there, that's a thing where I could probably work on them for like a whole year.
If I wanted to make them real fancy, and I need to not do that.
Yes.
I need, I need to, because I mean, I think I've gotten a little, a little bit fancy with some of the like attack animations.
And that's maybe why it took so long.
Um, and I, I think it to the point that it actually looks like it's maybe a little fancier than like the Super Nintendo style that it's going for.
I want the game to look like it, it's like a Super Nintendo aesthetic.
Uh, but I think some of the effects are a little bit, the too many pixels.
They have, they have extra pixels.
So they're a little like, finely detailed in a way that is like, hmm, you, maybe you couldn't do that on the Super Nintendo.
Uh, but it's fine.
It's okay.
Uh, I just gotta not worry about it.
I just gotta not worry about it and just, and just keep chugging along and just get it done.
Art is never completed, only abandoned.
Hmm.
Yeah.
It's good that you're doing stuff.
I've, I've.
It is good that I'm doing stuff.
I feel good about it.
Well, now I feel bad because I haven't worked on it for a few days.
Uh, but.
I mean, I haven't been working on fucking anything for months.
Well, I mean.
This Kickstarter is, is, is like the most work I've been doing.
It's really just like number munching and organizing and like.
Well, I mean, doing the, I mean, doing the like, um, I mean, there's real work involved in the Kickstarter.
Like you had to do the, like you, you made the design for the plush and stuff.
And you had to write it all up and, and you know, set up the goal.
I mean, yeah, it's not like it wasn't work, but like, I had just been like, I mean, I only thought of that.
I mean, I only thought of that idea.
I only did all that since, um, what was this?
I forget their name.
Hoodie.
Was it Hoodie?
Hoodie, Hoodie in zero.
Yeah.
Like the Cato, the Cato guys.
They suggested the doing of like Laura Ghost Kickstarter.
And so before that point, I had just been feeling sick and not doing any drawing all year.
And it was just like, I had been doing working on my secret project, which I put on hold.
And it's, I just, I just want to get be doing things, you know, I just want to be like,
I want to be chugging along and chugging along and making like Lord of Ghost Act three Clarissa
like finished and then all of these other things I have.
I just, I just spend most of the day watching like German live stream vods and doing like
playing video games.
And it's, it's cringe.
I, I hate, I just cringe it.
I'm cringing it myself.
I have, I have been, um, I have been binging a lot of, um, a lot of, a lot of long like
JRPG speedruns from like RPG limit break.
I think they did like a marathon recently and there's a bunch of like, they did a 10
hour legend of Dragoon run.
I watched all of that.
Uh, they, I think I'm in, I'm in the middle of a, of a Final Fantasy 10, uh, one which
is also like really, really long.
This is, I've been putting those on while I do other stuff.
Uh, I, I, uh, I can't believe that it's end of June, which means that I've been working
on this game for six months.
I started at the end of December.
I, I can't believe it's been six months.
I just don't understand.
I don't know what I was doing.
I mean, I guess I've been working on it, on the game and like, I just, the time went
by so fast and I like, I thought it was going to take me like maybe two months to do the
game because the, the champion game, I literally made that in like three weeks.
This, this game has taken me, I didn't expect it to take me this long.
I'm, I'm just in shock that the, it has flown by and I don't know where it went.
It's weird.
I just don't feel like summer.
Well, it's hot.
Well, I mean, like it doesn't feel like it's where, you know, past spring, like that doesn't
make sense.
I didn't feel like spring even began.
Yeah.
I feel like it was cold just a little while ago.
Yeah, I do.
I don't, where did spring go?
Oh no.
It's the vaccine.
It's making me lose time.
It's making me lose time because this is my control of microchip.
Oh, microchip.
That's what did, oh, that explains it.
What are you doing?
That explains everything.
What was I, what was I was doing at night, the, at night, the, the microchip activates
and I lose, and I lose a week at a time because I disappeared to go out into the streets and
and protest like a BLM and Tifa thug and smash windows to get Joe Biden reelected.
They didn't know that last year.
They just been doing it for no reason.
They didn't.
Yeah.
Well, they never turned it off.
They didn't know.
They didn't need to give me a microchip.
I was going to do that anyway.
They didn't need to chip me.
That was the plan all along.
I saw, what did I see?
I saw some, saw some fucking freak on Twitter.
Was it Tim Pool?
I don't know.
I'm a fucking idiot saying like, that the, you know, and Tifa is like the Joe Biden army
and Tifa just loves Joe Biden.
They got him elected.
They rioted to get Joe Biden elected.
I'm sick.
You're insane.
You're fucking the world is full of sick freaks.
Say things like this.
And I'm upset.
Fortunately, I can't see it because Twitter is bugged.
Twitter is broken.
It's not working for me.
It's not loading.
That is the best.
You're insane.
It's great.
Twitter to be broken.
It's super good.
Yeah.
I can't fucking see anything on there.
And my life is richer for it.
Maybe I'll just let it stay bugs.
Maybe I hope those never fix it.
I think I might need to like track and like get, get the, bring out the big guns.
Like the harsh truths, the strict, the harsh mistresses.
What does that mean?
It means I got to like knuckle down and ban myself from all of this YouTube crap that
I've like, it worked before like the forcing myself to not look at something.
And then I go onto it and I'm like, oh, but I want to click on Twitter.
I want to click on YouTube.
And then like an hour later, I'm like, well, I may as well make progress in my life's work.
And then I do it.
I've got to turn that back on.
I turned it off because I was sick.
It's been too long.
I think it's perpetuating my sickness.
I see.
I see the, I mean, the, I am literally going to install a website blocker specifically
so that I don't go to DoorDash and order food anymore.
I, I develop, I have developed a crippling addiction to ordering a fried chicken and pizza.
And it's really bad.
Yeah.
It's bad because I'm fat now, but also because it costs so much.
It costs like 30 fucking dollars to order anything from anywhere.
It's always $30, no matter what it is.
That's quite a lot.
It's quite a lot.
So I need to, yeah, no, I can't let myself do it anymore.
I can't, I can't allow it.
But I mean, my, my, my justification to myself was like, eh, I'll just eat a bunch of junk food
because I'm, because I'm working out now because I'm lifting now and I'm getting really strong.
So it's, it's good.
Like the classic like, oh, and all the fucking things is like, oh, well, and now that I started
my diet and I've started my like exercise, one little many donuts won't hurt.
I mean, it's a bit of a, it's a bit of a cope.
It's a bit of a cope.
There's a little bit of truth to it because like I have gotten stronger.
I have, I have my lifts are up and I think that they have gone up faster because I've been eating a lot
because you got to live, you got to eat big to get big.
You got to eat huge to get huge.
You got to fuel, you got to turn your body into a metabolic furnace.
I mean, I think I, so I have gotten a bit stronger, which is good.
I'm, I'm in a, I want, I really like that my lifts go up.
I like when number go up, but also I'm getting fat and I don't like when that number go up.
But yeah, I heard you'd said that last time only both number go up, both number go up or both number go down.
I have to choose.
I have to choose get like non fried chicken, like just actual chicken.
You fucking nerd.
And like, why would I want to eat that?
I don't know.
It's chicken.
It's, it's not, that's not delicious.
Yeah, but number go up for, for strength, but that's not what I'm going down for weight.
Yeah, I mean, I mean, obviously you're correct.
Obviously you're correct.
I mean, I, I was doing this thing that was like super easy, like pan fried chicken breast.
It was just some oil.
I put the chicken on it.
And I know before that I put like a mixture of like salt, pepper and herbs and some, some flour and just rolled it in that and put it in there.
And it's just like fried chicken, except it's, it's good and good for you.
Literally the thing, the thing that the thing about ordering food from DoorDash is just that I don't have to cook, right?
Like if I, if I have to cook food, then I will eat less of it because I just, I just won't bother cooking.
I'll be like too lazy.
I'll be like, oh, I want to eat something.
I'm going to, I'm going to do some boredom eating.
Oh, but I'd have to cook to do it.
Oh, it's not worth the effort.
Never mind.
That's the, yeah.
I've been feeling like that as well.
I just, yeah, I just got to do it though.
Yeah.
I need, I'm like, I'm hungry right now, but I didn't eat lunch.
I'm like, uh, damn, now I'm doing PCP.
I can't, I got to eat afterwards.
And I don't have like a plan.
I can reheat something or I could just cook a big thing of rice and just eat rice.
And that, you know, that'll work.
It'll be energy, I guess.
It won't be nice, but I go to do something.
I feel sick from being a little hungover, but I'm sick in a way.
Like I feel a little gross, like I don't want to eat because of, because I'm sick.
But also you ever, you ever feel nauseous, but in a way that you're like, hmm,
if I could just eat just the right thing, it would cure my nausea.
You ever feel that?
Um, I don't think so.
Mostly because I don't think eating.
Well, now that I think about it, maybe.
I think, I think I feel nauseous when I anticipate eating or drinking the same thing again.
When I, sometimes, when I feel nauseous, sometimes I get like, man, if I just eat like an orange,
that'll like cure it and then I'll feel better.
But it's never true.
I just eat it and then I feel more full and I feel sicker.
I was like, if I eat something healthy, it'll, it'll fix the like.
Oh, you mean what?
Like when you're stuffed?
Yeah, or just not wanting to eat for any reason.
Most of the times when I feel nauseous is because I have a taste in my mouth and I'm like,
I don't want any more of that taste.
I need something different.
Hmm.
I, this is totally off topic, but I wanted to mention it.
I was thinking about my, my dream where my uncle Joe Rogan killed a guy because he wanted to go drunk driving.
And I realized that the gun, the gun, the big silver gun that he shot that guy's head off with before
making it through a window.
It was the, it was Vash's gun from Try Gun.
Do you know the gun I'm talking about?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
It was a big, big, big flat silver.
It was the big flat silver gun.
It was that gun or it looked just like it.
I was like, huh?
But didn't know Joe Rogan was such a fucking weeb.
He has a recreation Vash the Stampede gun that kills people with her fun.
Good old, good old uncle Joe.
Okay.
Podcast's over.
Wait, wait.
Well, yes.
But Lord of Ghosts though.
Lord of, Lord of Ghosts, everybody.
Oh.
I know last episode, it was like, it was small.
It was a small little moment because of the tales gets trolled guys, like more important.
It was unfortunate timing because I just launched it and wanted to talk about it.
But if you don't know, Lord of Ghosts is a comic that I've written and I'm continuing to write.
I'm printing the first two acts of the comic in physical book form where you can have it.
And there's a little enamel pin, just like the vapor is just, I'm just copying Ben St.
Hell yeah.
And I'm just going to copy Ben St. steal his ideas and it'll be great.
I think you should go to the Kickstarter.
You should watch the funny video and get addicted to the song.
I think you should give me a cut.
I think you should give me a cut since you stole my idea of charging money for a product.
I'll give you a cut when you have drawn the ghost story that you will draw.
That's true.
Okay.
Fair.
Yes.
Good.
My portion.
My royalties.
I will call them.
I'm excited.
I'm excited for that zine.
I'm excited for that red man zine.
I really want it.
I really want that added value.
Hey, you had like restricted, it was the Doodle rewards, right?
You had like a limited number available and they're sold out.
Oh, oh yeah.
The maximum, the biggest one, 45 pounds, the signed comic with the Doodle and the ghost pin.
25 backers no reward, no longer available.
That is crazy.
I didn't expect that one to max out first.
Yeah, so I mean, I could, you could get the Doodle but not with the pin now, I guess.
I think I'm probably going to have extra pins, so I might make it so if I'm going to be doing
other Doodles, I might as well just lump them all in together and you can pay more if you
want the pin.
Yeah.
Because if people want, you know, they're willing to pay for the Doodle.
They probably also want the pin as well.
So, I don't know.
Yeah, I definitely would.
It's like if I'm buying the book, like, yeah, I want the fucking pin.
Well, of course.
Yeah, so yeah, I'll make a note about that.
Do I click an update?
Is that what I do?
I don't know.
Let's make an update.
How many pins did you have made?
I haven't had them made yet.
I was waiting until...
Oh, you just got the sample piece.
Yeah, I got the samples and I'm like, ah, this looks great.
I'll tell you when the, I know how many I need to order because it was the minimum was 50,
but I'm thinking I might need 100 just to cover everything.
And I want to know that before I, you know, order it.
And I was keeping it open and just in case it was really successful out of nowhere
and I needed like 200 pins, which is unlikely, but you know.
Oh, I want it.
I want the pin.
Now, now I know people, people, when I, when I did my Kickstarter and I offered pins,
people were like, oh, pin, pinpog, I want the pin.
Now I'm on the other side and I understand.
I understand pin hype.
It's just so, it's so fun.
I'm looking at it right now.
Yeah.
I like, I made that tweet comparing the one, the Lord of Ghost, a smear,
the smear pin from the RFCK Kickstarter.
I like it's, I just think it's funny that there's two, two different takes.
Yeah.
On the character.
On the one hand, it was like, oh, I can't exactly do a Lord of Ghost nega slime pin
because that already exists from Endless War.
But it kind of, you know, I mean, it's him and it's the magical event.
Yeah.
But the Lord of Ghosts with the, with the like the shitty drawing version is really,
really funny to have as an enamel pin.
The, the, the.
It's a different.
Different.
I've said it before, but I really, really like the opening of the comic
with the sequence with all the pages is such a cool little,
it's a cool little, like what could you call it a set piece?
Can comics have set pieces?
It's a very, it's a very cool sequence.
An opening scene, I guess.
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, dog.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm hyped.
I'm hyped to get mine.
Link in the description.
Get that fucking book.
Get that fucking, get the red man.
Pledge to the Kickstarter so that we can get the red man zine.
I want the zine.
I want the red man zine.
I always think it was, oh man, I think last time I said that, like,
I will never, I will never, like, dig back through the Twitter archives
to see those red man comics.
So the only way I'll ever see them again is if they get put in a zine
and sent to me in a book.
Yeah.
So it's the only way.
I think I talked about, I talked about how, like, it's funny that,
like, some of the comics suck.
Yes.
And the fact that they're printed will be like,
oh, maybe I talked about it on the stream.
Yeah, did we talk about it there?
I genuinely don't remember, like, what we talk about on an episode
versus what we talk about on the stream.
All the days bleed together.
I don't know what time of the year it is.
I don't know what day of the week it is.
I don't know where I am.
It's a, yeah.
Oh, God, I got to move.
Oh, God, I got to find a new house.
Oh, my God, I've only got, like, a month left.
Oh, fuck.
A negative Pog.
It's negative Pog.
It's Monka S, for sure.
No, I actually really got to get on that.
It's actually a little bit bad.
Wait, how close is it?
I have to move out at the end of July.
So it's about five weeks.
About five weeks from now.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Yeah, I thought it was July now.
My time.
Oh, yeah.
I have three days.
I have three days to find a new house.
No.
I was saying, I don't know, I don't know.
Man, the place, the place I live is such a deal.
It's such a deal.
I've saved up.
I've been able to save money because the rent has been, like, nothing.
But now I have to pay, like, a real rent to live in, like, a real place.
And it's like, oh, God, fuck.
No.
I refuse.
I'm going to do what they did in the musical rents.
I'm going to just be like, no.
I won't.
I'm going to throw a riot over it.
I'm going to not pay rent, just like the movie rent, just like the stage play rent,
just like I didn't pay rent.
I'm going to find a new apartment, sign the lease, get moved in,
and then immediately be like, rent your strike.
No, eviction moratorium.
You can't kick me out.
Instantly.
What if I barricade the door?
Huh?
What are you going to do then?
Yeah.
I think it's still, I think the moratorium on eviction is still active.
It might vary state to state.
I don't, I feel like it was never really enforced.
So I feel like, I don't know, I wonder, I wonder what, I wonder what Carmen would do,
would just tell me to do if he was here.
Carmen was the guy who convinced me and that when we lived in that place with the landlord
and he was trying to kick us out, he was the one who was like, he has no legal grounds to kick you out.
Just, just stay here.
Just stay there and don't pay rent for six months.
They can't kick you out.
And he was right.
So I wonder, I wonder what he would do if he were, if he were in my position.
That guy has never, that guy always gives good advice about how to fucking get away with shit and then not pay for stuff.
Based, based Carmen for sure.
Anyway, I'm very stressed about that.
I don't want to be homeless.
That would be pretty bad.
No.
But it'll be fine.
It'll be fine.
To be homeless?
No, that would be super bad.
I just, I just, I just want to finish my game.
I just want to finish my fucking game, but there's no way.
It's, it's not going to be done.
It's not going to be done by the end of the month.
And I'm going to have to move my computer and I'm going to have to move my hard drives.
Oh my God.
What if my hard drives get damaged in the move and what if my files get corrupted?
Oh, definitely back them up to like one of those funny services.
I could probably, I could probably back it up some like Google, Google Drive or something.
Yeah, you probably, if it's a lot of stuff, you might have to pay the Google's premium and big amount.
It's not that huge.
No, I think I could fit.
I think I could fit.
I mean, if I needed more storage space, I could just make a new email.
All right.
Just make a new dummy email.
I think I have a bunch of like just extra email accounts that just have Google drives attached for me to back stuff up.
Stuff from like, I don't even remember.
That's what I've always done.
Let's make a, make a dummy email.
Just store a shit there and then forget about it.
Yeah, it's, the files are not that big.
The game maker files are, actually, I wonder, I wonder how big they are.
I'll probably tell you right now.
It is the game maker file for Phantoms Revenge is 50 kilobytes.
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
That's, that is nothing.
Yeah.
I mean, that, that doesn't include.
It's probably just all the logic.
No, it does.
It loads, it loads this, that and the other.
I was going to say that doesn't include like the assets and like the, but no, it does.
The game has, the game file has all like the sprites and the background and stuff in it.
Like those aren't saved in like a separate folder.
So no, that's, yeah, that's the size of the game is like 50 kilobytes, including all the art and stuff.
You know, low res, low res shit.
Oh, but I finished on the upside.
I did finish all of the patrons that requested a like a custom enemy because I like patrons suggest enemies.
I got through adding all of those in.
I think there were like 11 or 12 or something people that asked me to make a special enemy for them.
And some of them are really funny.
I'm looking at one right now and he's making me chuckle, but I'm not going to say what it is because it's, it's very goofy.
You know, it'll be, I want, it'll be a surprise, LeMau.
Hmm.
Good times.
I like doing, I like making sprites.
I like sprite work.
It's very, I think part of the reason why like that, like two week period just flew by without me even noticing was just because I find that kind of work enjoyable and I could just lose myself in it and just like making a sprite for that.
Okay, open it up, move pixels around.
Oh, it's done.
Oh, two hours are gone.
Oh, wow.
I didn't even notice.
It's fun.
It's, it's enjoyable.
I was just put on a fucking, put on fucking 10 hour, let's do 10 hour speed run of Final Fantasy six and just go to town.
And that's, and that's my day.
Day in the life.
Good times.
Huh?
I was just saying, it's just saying life sucks.
Yeah, bro.
True.
Oh, no.
So place.
And that's it.
That's it.
Hey, hey, I got some, I got some news.
What?
I got some, I got some news.
I'm going to be on a, I'm going to be on a podcast.
Can you believe it?
No, I can't.
Can you fucking believe it?
Who would invite Benson?
I've been invited, I've been invited to appear on Animorphin Time, the leftist Animorphs podcast.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
Pretty cool.
All cops are Yerks.
Hell yeah.
I have to, I have to, I have to read the book.
I think I have to read.
I have to get like any knowledge about Animorphs.
I, Tyler from, from Animorphin Time messaged me yesterday to be like, when do you want to record?
And I didn't get back to him.
And now I can't see my Twitter messages because fucking Twitter's broken.
So I can't get back to him until they fix whatever's going on with their servers or whatever.
Sorry, sorry, Tyler.
Whoops.
I have to read, I think it's book number like 30 something.
It's a Tobias one, which is good.
It's past the point in the series that I had read up to, I think I read up to like number 20, like late 20s, early 30s, I think.
And then at some point I, that was about when I fell off.
I never finished the series.
So the one that I have to read for that episode is like post, it's past the point in the series that I stopped reading.
So I don't know, could be, could be interesting, could be pretty, could be pretty nifty, I guess.
I guess I'll, I'll link that when that episode comes out on Apple podcasts or wherever it was they publish them.
Oh, shit.
I just remembered I got an email about like, like a kickstart.
Oh, your Kickstarter is great.
And I was like, okay, I was going to ignore it.
But then they said, we do a podcast promoting people.
They didn't want me to be on, but they just said, if you want, you will promote your thing.
Looks cool.
Send us an audio clip of you promoting your thing.
And I'm like, I don't want to speak into a microphone.
But I also feel like there's no harm.
So maybe maybe it's like a, it's like a podcast about kickstart or like indie comics or something.
That's interesting.
I mean, I get, whenever I do a Kickstarter, I always get a bunch of like scam emails about it.
Yeah.
I saw like, the normal stuff is like, haha, we will get you pledges like shut up.
Sign up for a pay our advertising fee and we'll, we'll, we'll get the word out or whatever.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I found this other one like Olivia and William says greetings from myself and William.
My name is a will Olivia and my partner's name is William.
We are a duo expert crowd funders focus on seeing product projects get funded.
I would not want to impress you with too many words, but would rather let our results and
deliveries speak for us.
All you need to do is go through kickstartergoal.com, pay for a promotional package based on your
budget and desired funding go and see your project take a new turn.
Give us your credit card information basically.
Cool.
Like so obvious.
This other one.
Yeah.
Wait, I'm curious about Tyler, Tyler James from comics tribe and the comics launch
podcast.
Right now, comic book projects have a third highest success rate on Kickstarter.
The mission is comic, the mission of comics launch is to make comics number one.
So I'd love to get the word out about your project with a free plug in the new just launched
on Kickstarter segment of my weekly podcast.
What is the podcast called?
I'm kind of curious about it.
The comics launch podcast for the next comics.
The comics launch podcast.
Is it on YouTube?
Oh, no, I see.
It's got its own website, comicslaunch.com.
It's on Apple podcasts on Google podcasts.
I mean, what he's asking for is like go to comics launch for Boy To Smell, hit start
recording, and speak to it for about 30 seconds, hit send.
So I'm like, that's so easy.
I may as well try it even if it's like nothing will come of it.
Yeah, I mean, he's, hmm, I see he's he's he's posting podcasts on his website.
He's doing them like every couple weeks or so.
I, I, I don't, I wonder like what kind of an audience he has.
That's kind of neat.
That's kind of cool that this exists.
Doesn't look like a scam.
Doesn't sound like a scam.
No, I mean, it couldn't be if unless the comicslaunch.com slash voicemail asked me for my credit card
information again.
Yeah, the thing that I stopped like stopped myself from doing it already was like, I keep
failing at the elevator pitch for Lord of Ghosts.
I don't know what to say.
It's a comic.
It's about a lord is a little ghost guy and he's like, and he just wants to kill, but
he doesn't really want to kill.
Like, I don't know how to explain it.
It's the adventures of little ghost as he goes because there's, I guess you could say it's
just a, it's about a, I don't know about a little freaks wacky adventures.
Little freaks like adventures in a strange new land filled with mud instead of the familiar
slime.
It's like, I mean, yeah, that God, yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what you, what the elevator pitch for it is.
It's just to read my fucking comic.
It's funny.
It's cool.
Yeah.
I was reading it the other day and I was like, oh, you know what?
I like this.
I'm a fan of my own comic.
I forgot.
This is, I can't, I can't believe this.
Like I'm looking at comics launch and I'm like, why, why does this exist?
This, this guy just seems like he is just like, I want all comics to exist.
I will make all comics succeed on, if it's a comic, I will fucking do anything to prevent
its destruction.
I like it.
I don't know how, I don't know what's, what's, what's in it for this guy?
What's his angle?
Well, it could be potential networking, I guess.
He's talking with comics.
Like it maybe starts from a love of comics generally.
And then by promoting people, he can be like well known in the comics sphere.
Like getting, getting small indie comics off the ground.
People like are happy about his work that they helped him.
And then that helps him by word of mouth, I guess.
Maybe.
Cause I mean, we're talking about it.
What does he say?
He says, creators, Superman isn't coming.
So we get to save ourselves.
My name is Jay, is Tyler James and I'm one of thousands of creators who are doing things
differently.
We believe the creative life and career we want is not only possible, but inevitable.
If we're willing to work hard enough, smart enough and to commit, commit to bringing passion
to every project, commit to action even when it's scary, committing to building a network
and always adding value first, committing to doing things with integrity and keeping
the promises we make to others and ourselves, commit to never stop developing our talent
because we are all works in progress.
And we also believe that starving has nothing to do with being an artist.
While others are waiting for permission to get started or for approval from some gatekeeper,
we've picked ourselves and we're building our legacies.
One fan at a time, one project at a time, one launch at a time.
So serious.
It's just comics, bro.
It's not a big deal.
Fuck it.
I like him.
I'm going to give it a shot.
I'm going to figure out an elevator pitch.
I'm going to say it.
I'm going to send it in.
Oh, God.
I'm Flemme.
Why am I Flemme?
This is the image of him with his dog and there's a mug and the mug says, do what you love,
love what you do.
Well, words to live by, I guess.
True.
He, he, it seems like, how come this guy didn't call me?
How come this guy didn't do, hey, this is, I can plug this guy in.
This guy never offered to plug the vapors.
Well, he's been saying that's why.
What is, what does Gib have that I don't have?
It's not right.
I have a better comic.
No.
I want to, I'm really curious.
Like, what is kind of following this guy?
I mean, maybe he only appeared recently.
He's, he's been, he's got his blog, the website blog goes back a couple years at least.
Oh, well, I don't know.
Maybe you, maybe you sifted through your spam emails and you just didn't see this one.
If you sent one to you.
Maybe.
Yeah, maybe.
That's interesting.
He, he just does, he's just like, he's just got a, he's just got spotlight.
So like, hey, these guys did a Kickstarter.
Hey, these other guys did a Kickstarter.
Hey, this comic came out through Kickstarter.
That was pretty cool.
Hmm.
How does he make, how does he monetize this?
How does he make money off this?
What's, what's, it's a, it's a front.
It's a front.
It's, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a money laundering scam.
Maybe it's the only way.
No, you're jealous.
You're just jealous.
I got picked.
I am.
I am also that I'm jealous that you got picked for the money laundering scam.
Yeah.
What about me?
Based, based.
Do you want to go to voicemails?
Yeah, I got nothing else to say today, I guess.
I think I've said, I think I've said all I have to say.
Let's get into this horse shit.
If you go to speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail viewer, you can send us a voicemail and we
will re-respond to it in a disappointingly low energy sort of way.
That's what I'm going to do today because I'm, I'm under the weather and you're all just
going to have to deal with it.
I see the first voicemail here is called big chicken.
You see it?
Yep.
Okay.
In three, two, one, go.
Hello, PCP.
As it occurs to me during my intense play session of Neopets, that many of the people sending
voicemails to the channel should in fact invest in a new microphone because they all sound
like shit.
I mean, true.
Yeah.
In a perfect world, I would like everyone to have a great microphone and deliver crisp,
clear, 180 billion megahertz audio quality, but I have to accept the reality that you're
one of the good ones with a good microphone, big chicken.
We're down here in the muck and the dirt and the grime and the filth and it's okay.
It's all right.
I can take it.
The next voicemail is called a warning.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, this is Mr. T.
Ben St.
You damn fool.
No, false.
Listen, I'm going to call a truce with y'all right now.
Since that summer I bastard being gone, I've been released from his mind control.
And I was going to go home and be done with this whole damn thing.
But first, I had to warn you.
Because when Mr. T came to, he was at the Kawasaki clan base.
And there's actually one more summer I left alive.
And he's got a vendetta against y'all.
Never ends.
Y'all going to be hearing from a new, even more powerful summer out very soon.
So good luck with all of that.
Thanks.
Mr. T, go home and fall ever.
Well, bye.
Thanks, Mr. T.
Goodbye.
We love you.
Have a beautiful life.
Have a good trip.
See you next fall.
Bam.
What do you think of the samurai is going to be like?
I think...
Oh, I can't even speculate.
The possibilities are just...
Did you ever give back the scroll?
Do you think they're going to be angry with the scroll, the same one?
Don't you remember on stream when we realized that in creating the void Thaumaturge's robe,
my Minecraft avatar has the scroll on it now?
Oh, of course.
You can literally see me carrying the scroll around.
It's part of my character design now.
Yep, it's that Thaumcraft.
I'm high on that Thaumcraft goodness.
The next voicemail is called From Collapsic.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi, Ben.
It's me.
Collapsic.
Yo.
You remember me?
Ben.
Yes.
And all the other soldiers?
Admiral Collapsic, I remember.
We missed you.
Ben, so very much we've missed you.
Oh.
We're just waiting here patiently.
I left you in a low light.
Are you to boot up your 3DS again?
Or your switch, if you can afford one?
Yes, we're just waiting for our chance to shine again.
Shine like pixie turkey.
Another Nuzlocke, Ben.
We need another Nuzlocke.
We need to prove ourselves as fine soldiers in your army, Ben.
Please quit the trilogy.
You know we need the trilogy to be completed, Ben.
Is it a trilogy?
We just, we're so lonely here with another Nuzlocke.
God, Jesus.
Laying it on a little thick, aren't we, Collapsic?
We just need one, Ben.
We need another Nuzlocke.
Is the pig coming?
Complete the trilogy.
What's the trilogy?
The trilogy.
Jesus.
This is me, Collapsic, and this is the way I talk.
Yes, Ben.
Okay.
We'll see you real soon.
Oh my God, my skin is crawling.
The, the, uh, yeah, I know I said, I have said that I wanted to do another Nuzlocke,
and I do, but I just, I gotta do, I gotta finish the game.
I can't, I can't do another one of those before I finish the fucking video game.
That's just the way it's gotta be.
Um, but I mean, thanks for the reminder.
Nice to hear from you, as always.
Glad things are going well in Alola.
You're taking care of business.
Good, good shit.
That's the lore.
That's the deep lore.
Next voicemail is called Please, 3, 2, 1, go.
Please keep talking about Tim Rogers.
Please make it a weekly sing.
I'm not joking.
There is not enough Tim Rogers discourse online.
I guess you've done at least some research on Tim by now, but he's been around for a long,
long, long, long time.
He had a whole arc where he went to be a game developer in Japan and had a noise band.
And look, honestly, Ben puts himself down too much.
Tim has put out so many reviews and they're insanely long.
He's easily written like 5 million words worth of game reviews.
This man has never fucked.
I have high hopes that he's never fucked.
He will reach this level of completely autistic content creation.
If you've read Backman, Tim here is like Nizuma Agee, a completely autistic,
turbo virgin that lives to work.
And by work, I mean waste everyone's time.
That is the ideal to strive for.
I know Ben, our dark hero, cannot be stopped.
Nothing can take him down.
The elves slide off him like Ponderwater.
He will never give up.
He will never give in.
He will reach the top.
And once he's there, a new generation of workflow's trash will look up and say,
fuck Ben St.
Fuck his little club.
Returns to Groves Ben St.
You asshole.
And you will look down and say, no.
True.
Who is Tim Rogers?
I don't think I was here when you talked about him.
Really?
He is a...
I'm shocked.
I'm sure you were.
He is a guy.
He worked for...
Okay.
I know a lot about him.
Just because he talks about himself a lot in his video game reviews.
But he is...
Now he has a channel on YouTube called Action Button where he has made like five really,
really long video game reviews.
Before he was doing that, he worked for Kotaku making videos.
And he is...
Yeah, you know, he was a game...
He worked for a game developers in Japan.
He was like a translator for a...
He was a translator for a Yaoi manga artist.
He was a...
Or he was just some kind of assistant.
He...
He's in a...
Oh god.
What else?
Yeah, he was...
I know he's been in a noise band.
He didn't...
He says his band was bad.
I don't know if any recordings of this music or anywhere.
He always talks about doing running, doing track when he was younger and having six pack abs.
He was a fashion model, I guess, for a while, which is like really weird.
That's a really strange detail because he's not like a...
He's not like a...
I mean, I guess he's kind of fit.
I guess he's like skinny.
He's not like a...
He's not really a fashion model looking kind of guy, but I guess he did that.
This guy has managed to get...
He's 42?
He's 42, yeah.
This guy has managed to get away with complimenting another person that I am envious of.
He has managed to get away with it without irritating me by implying that I, too, am great.
So, thanks for that, voicemailer.
Appreciate it.
I thought you meant...
Tim...
Tim Rogers complimented you.
No.
I've been...
Every week, for the last couple weeks, I keep complaining about, like,
I found this guy on YouTube.
I kind of like his videos, but he's not so great.
I could do what he does.
What's so special about him?
These are my gripes.
These are my gripes with Tim Rogers.
This guy says there's not enough Tim Rogers discourse, but what discourse is there to have?
I mean, the guy...
He just talks about himself.
He just talks about himself in his videos.
And that's why I know all about him.
There's nothing I can say about Tim Rogers that he hasn't already said about himself.
Looking forward to the next review, I guess.
The next voicemail is called Best Voicemail I've Submitted.
Sorry for the bad ones.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
Nah, actually, fuck it.
Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
Now, that's what I call a good voicemail.
Get in, get out, make your point.
Don't waste anyone's time.
Good job.
Next voicemail.
Oh, this one's gonna be good.
It's called the Ben St. Child molester.
This is gonna be epic.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
What?
All right.
Thanks for the voicemail.
It sounded almost like it was real.
Like someone was actually driving really fast, but I don't think so.
Well, I mean, that guy...
There was a guy who would send us voicemails who would just rev his car.
He would just drive his car really fast.
And I was always scared he was gonna crash on voicemail.
It was gonna be horrifying.
I don't even know.
I don't even... I don't know what to say.
Good job.
Okay, the next one is called a physicist.
Do you see that?
Yes.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
There is a problem in physics.
We can't unite quantum field theory and general relativity.
So here is my question.
Do you quantize the gravity or gravitate or geometrize the quantum?
So which one? Choose wisely.
Ah, fuck.
Should we quantize gravity or geometrize the quantum?
You should quarkize gravity.
How should I know?
How should I know which one we should do?
I mean, gravity seems the Pythagorean...
I mean, if they aren't compatible, then you can't just do that, right?
Then you would be incorrect to quantize gravity.
If gravity isn't...
I feel like this isn't a question you can just be like, which one should we do?
Because if either one works, then you just do it.
But the problem is that it doesn't work.
I don't know.
Real question is...
Should you poopoo in the pee-pee?
You poopau-poop audition
Next voicemail is called Ben your alcoholism is slowly killing you part two three two one go
Told you so
Yeah, bitch
Did you know did you know that I was gonna be hungover this episode, how did you know?
Hey, who sent that then was it somebody watched you be drunk. I
Don't know. I mean it was sent four days ago, which was before I was I was drunk
so I
Mean I
Don't know. I don't they got you. I don't I guess they fucking got me. I think they got me by accident
I think that was an accidental L on my part, but but an L nonetheless
Next voicemail is called
Really real Riley three two one go
It's Riley, um, I I actually have no idea what Riley sounds like but this is my voice
It's me Riley
It's exactly what he sounds like from the Walmart cuz it's the only place I got Wi-Fi and I just want to say fuck you
Ben say or should I say Ben ain't cuz
Begetting this sick cash flow we're making
Yeah, we're making we're making so much money right now because we sold
All of our possessions all all of our stuff all of Trixie's really big anime and my collection
That's right. We sold it for like
32 dollars
Which which I spent on weed and also we got rid of our house. So we don't have to pay rent
But we're not homeless shut up
We're just camping out inside of this Walmart parking lot in our super cool RV
Which you can't see cuz fuck you and this could have all been yours Ben
You kind of had a share in this but yeah, I'd be a bitch and say things. Well jokes on you
Fuck oh
Anyway, I gotta go there calling security on me or something
Smell you later
nerds
Obviously, I agree with the spirit of this of this voicemail. Obviously, I endorse its message
Oh
Yeah, I saw like Riley make fun of you for like doing making a brony game or something
on Twitter
No, no
Or it was like the X that account
That's a that's a dummy. That's like a fake account. How was it?
That's that's some that's some guy who runs like a fake account and calls himself yig studios to make fun of them
But decided to like call me a brony and make fun of me for being a brownie or something
I don't know why he felt the need to do that
But he well, I mean it was a big own. It was like a massive L you took
I did when people remembered that you were a brony once my my the diarrhea from that L was
Put put the other ones to shame
Yeah, yeah, that was that was such like a that was such like a deep cut like a blast from the past
I know it's been so long since anyone been like dude give up the like usually. I'm I'm
Historically been the guy who's like dude give up the pony shit, bro. The po the brony shit. It's kind of cringe, bro
Like it's I mean, I don't say it like that, but like to hear to hear someone say that to me
I was honestly just like that's it's bizarre
It brings me right back. It brings me right back to when like our bronies like allowed to exist
That's the discourse
Was a cringe to like ponies. Yes, but and who cares
Is it cring is it cringe to like ponies because as we all know being cringe is punishable by by exile exile at least
Yes, that was funny also
Just a reminder
Just reminds me of the of the message tricks. He sent me where she said
Riley's made me so many connections to big people with big money
And now you're never gonna get to have any of it the only me because you're too mean
And I guess I think it's funny because like she lives with her parents now
She's just moved back in with her parents. So I guess those are the big money connections that Riley made for her parents
Wait, is that real? I think so. I believe so. Yeah, she's in California and
Pretty sure she's where her parents are. So I mean that's that's God. That's like that. Why else would she be in California?
Was his father's day, you know visit your folks
Oh, but the other reason she'll be in California because Dick Masterson's there, I guess
He's living there and out of then that and then our hills. I
Don't know does he maybe he lives in there. Wait, Los Angeles. I don't I don't think I don't think Dick
Masterson is letting her crash on his couch
I don't know that would be pretty funny. I don't I don't see that happening
I'm pretty sure she's just living with her parents, huh? It's like our third parent
She wishes
Next voicemail is called failed relationships and flesh lights
Saucy, okay, three two one go. All right. Here's part two of my woman hate blog a thing
I gotta tell you something. Okay one thing. Well, first of all, I'm not trying to be disgusting
I'm trying to be realistic. Okay, if you're seriously a horny toad and you're fucking eat pussy and
Some of you probably already heard this from trolls or you heard it from somebody. Don't be ashamed. Go to
www.fleshlight.com
If you have 60 bucks, you can get yourself the best sex toy a man could ever own for himself
Not only does it feel like real pussy. It doesn't give you any troubles. It doesn't give you any headaches
It feels it feels like the real deal now. I know what some of you especially trolls are saying
Oh, you've never got pussy. Oh, you've never got me. Listen to me. Listen to me good
I'm gonna be fucking open and honest and I don't give a fuck
Okay, TMI it is. Okay. It's okay. All right. All right. Cool. Good voicemail. Yes
pussy rules
Uh
Bass thanks for the voicemail. Are we still listening to him? I did. Yeah, I'm over it
But I think I think I get the picture the next voicemail is
From tarbuck transom and it's a YouTube link. Okay, let's listen to it in three two one go
H bomber guy is wrong Ruby is good actually I the beneficent to tarbuck transom was in the audience of a recently published
Lecture about ruby that we filmed at nlokon it totally sold me on the show and actually watching it has exceeded the
Expectations set by the lecture. I know folks are on these parts like lectures. So I thought they'd want to know and
Anlokon I
Think though Simon did that it is Simon. I saw I did see
Simon posting this
Somewhere I saw it posted somewhere that they did a ruby lecture
I did see it and I have not watched it. So I I don't I I don't know. Oh, it's six and a half hours
Yeah, that's why I didn't watch it. It's six hours long. Yeah, but yeah, this is another
It's a ruby lecture. It I if that's out. I mean, I'm sure
That would be interesting to people. It's
Seems like the kind of thing that could that that a lecture could could work. Yeah, that's definitely good lecture material
I've I've I think I've watched like a first episode and
Like a few friends have like talked about ruby because they were a fan's bit and I said, ah, this is when it started getting shit
Look at how cool it was here and how shit it was here. I'm like, okay
interesting
But I watched the first episode and I wasn't really that into it
But the fight scenes are very very well like animated and choreographed
So there's that I I should I think I think I watched the H bomber guy
video about it and like the ruby is something and here's why the the deal the deal with it or the
The the the what I learned or what I think I learned about it is that it's basically made by a guy
Who's really good at animating fight scenes? Yes, and then they were like, I guess we should make a story about it
And like their writing is bad
But the fight scenes are cool. That's what that's my impression of it based on a little I've never watched any of it
I think I've heard that the the characters are good. I don't know
Writing ways. I don't know whatever fuck. There's a lot for it. Check out the fucking lecture in
Would it be better to watch like six and a half hours of ruby rather than the lecture about it
It's quite a lot. Oh, hmm. That's a good question. How much ruby is there?
entire
length of
Ruby
Use ask in Google. Yeah
How long is Ruby? Oh
No, don't do that to me Google
I
Can see the the volumes 16 episodes in volume one episodes very greatly in length
One eight fifteen and sixteen around eleven minutes long and all other episodes are split into approximately six minute halves
Oh, so you could that's not even that much
How long would it take you to watch all of ruby?
I'm I there's no number provided. I'm so I'm just reading like volume two features 12 episodes
12 to 15 minutes each
so
12 episodes 16 minutes in length
12 episodes 16 to 20 minutes in length
So that you could figure it out
But I it's like eight volumes and they've all got slightly different numbers of episodes and lengths
Do you I feel like you could get through to like volume three at least in six hours? Yeah
I see
well
cool, I don't know
Fucking link in the description if you want to check out Simon's PCP style
Ruby lecture, I guess I'll just take credit
PCP takes credit for the format any lecture that anyone ever does from now on on anything is a PCP style
It's the
What was the fine brothers thing they did a while ago when I tried to like?
Oh, right that like owned the the idea of reacting to things the reacts the like yeah
The like kids react elders react whatever like that you could you can pay us a fee to use the react format
And you'll be part of the fine brothers family or some stupid bullshit. No, yeah
Okay, next voicemail is called comrade Tarbuck transom three two one go
Ultimate programmer and the leftist Jordan Peterson your beloved Tarbuck transom here keeps calling us looking time ago in a town called
Kikapu there lived a game development studio called Westwood who made command and conquer and the red alert series
They were purchased by EA and then treated badly
The original team's refugees eventually escaped and went on to form a worker co-op called a super giant and made the game Hades
By playing the game. You are directly supporting socialism
Other worker owned games made by different people include dead cells disco Elysium tonight. We riot and the board game co-op only
Do you know of any others? I had a list in a website, but I can't find it again
Um, I didn't know that's interesting. I didn't know that about Hades. I didn't know that about disco Elysium
I did know that about tonight. We riot
That is pretty another reason to try and play Hades then I guess I
Already bought Hades a long time ago and then never played it because Noida
Could hook to me too hard
the
I'm I guess I'm just I'm surprised, you know, maybe I'm not that surprised
I think feel like if there's any industry
I feel like if any kind of like company was gonna be like worker owned it would be oh
Like a small indie dev studio God
I was talking to Munchie yesterday and he said and I agree that like good good end for Ben
Saint is like get a exact is work for one of those work for like some local like small
Worker owned like game game dev co-op. I wish I could find a group like that. That sounds so cool
Since I mean since I have to move and my rent's gonna go up
I've been thinking about what kind of a real
Real job could I get if only if only I could find something like that? It wouldn't be so bad
But it'll never happen it'll never happen my my my I'm not we're in the darkest timeline and I'm just gonna
Die in the gutter. It's fine. It's fine. Oh, don't worry about me
I mean, what if you made you what if you started one? How would you start a worker co-op?
What if you just said hey, I mean the PCP is basically a worker co-op. We all like own it together
So I guess just do it the same way we made the PCP
However that was
Uh-uh, duh, duh, you just get mage to start a Skype a Skype group
That's where all worker co-ops come from didn't you know I
Guess that yeah, we could technically do that online, but I think in person would be a lot easier
Sure
I mean, huh are you okay? And I need to get it. I need to get a drink. I'll be a second
Fine a few moments later
Sorry, I thought I could I thought I could hack it out
But I
Don't know. I just felt like I needed a drink for a while
But I didn't have a drink because I drank it all and then I need to go get one
You gotta have your drink and drink it too. I'm gonna not dive
Dehydration that's the one
Okay next
Next voicemail is called voicemail detective three two one go
Hey, what's up fellas? It's me the voicemail detective and I have discovered in my meticulous research that that guy
that called in towards the end the last episode with all his bullshit about
being the nuns and
did you being a father figure and
Max reviving Tarantino cast
That was definitely fucking Tommy J. And he knows good and well he is banned from the voicemail
No
This is a scream at the end
Okay, I'm I'm on the phone. I am calling 9-1-1. I have dialed 9-1 and I am ready to hit the final one
I just need his location. We need to have him arrested apprehended
He is he has violated. He has violated the terms of our arrangement
Retribution feels like a snitch moment. I don't want to like I don't like a applaud like snitchery. Oh
shit
That's true. I don't know. Maybe that voicemail was fine as far as I remember
maybe
Maybe cops are base though
No snitch snitching is cool. Remember your your traditional lifted values
Traditional anti for values. I smell a little red brown alliance
Wait, I don't know what that is
I think I think it's red red like communists, but brown like Nazi brown shirts
I think is the do a little nas we do a little nas Bolin
No, sorry. Sorry. It was a momentary insanity. No snitching leave Tommy J. Alone. He's uh, he's uh, he's reformed
So long as the voicemail is not terrible no beating need be required
Yes
Optional next voicemail is called Ben. You have hurt me three two one go
Okay, then what the fuck?
Yeah, first off you don't
Respond to the title of my voicemail as you can wear diapers at the beach Ben. Fuck you. I'm sorry be
You keep accusing me of doing pig noises. So I ain't going bitch
I don't I don't mean who are you?
I think they didn't realize your reference to the pig was not about what they were saying but instead about
Oh
Maybe yeah, I mean I guess if you don't know that there's a scary pig in the voice mails
You might be a little confused when I anticipate pig noises coming
Yeah. Hmm. Yeah interesting curious I apologize voice mailer
Next one is called give is a perfect angel three two one go
So last week you talked about like
How it feels
That's how it feels to be trans and like I
Guess forgive have you found a good YouTube video that like explain how it feels because like as a
Sysman, I don't get it. I don't
And this isn't a rude thing at all like I do not understand what changing your pronouns
Possibly dressing a little differently. I don't know what other changes you've made
Physically, but I don't understand
What that has done for your mental health or how that has helped your I don't and it's not a mean thing
I'm just very I mean, I don't I'm not like a psychologist. I'm not entirely sure why
It really made me just feel better
It was it was a lot of stuff in 2020 that I looked up
Like little bits here and there that are not like in on of themselves
Like smoking gun evidence or anything, which is why it was hard for me to notice
But just sort of I don't know gender dysphoria or whatever it is I have
causes like a blanket layer of depression and
It's just sort of
like
Society expects certain things of a man and I didn't want to do those things and therefore
I just felt like a failure all the time no matter what I did because
The the masculine ideal that I should strive for was just something I didn't want to do
so like
Succeeding was upsetting in a way and doing the other thing. It was just I don't know
I don't know what about my brain
Change changes or like how it works. I just know that I tried the the pronouns
And being referred to as a as a girl as a woman as a she it changed. I just made me feel better
It's it's very strange
I don't know
If you want like
Videos that explain it a bit better. I think Contra points does a lot of stuff about that
Yeah, it was mostly contra points a little bit of philosophy tube
Damn contra points is is good at what that's valid as fuck
You're being thanks. You're being so valid right now
Thank you. Yeah, I don't know. It's just I mean it take gender out of the equation and it's like
You've always lived your life thinking that you're supposed to have a mohawk and and you just keep shaving your hair like that
Because that's what you're supposed to do and then one day you said, you know what?
I'm just gonna have a different haircut and then suddenly you feel
Suddenly they don't let you use the bathroom anymore
Suddenly they don't like to use the different hairdressers or whatever. It's like
It just a change in your life
The you know you prefer
That's it. You just prefer it. I don't I there's no
There's no way to like quantify it more than you could quantify anybody's preference for anything
And it just so happens to be very socially
Socially
What's the word not stigmatized exactly just sort of like the social pressure to be masculine or feminine or to not be the opposite
Is is quite prevalent in in Western society or lots of basically everywhere
So it's more it seems more important or more like drastic. I guess it's it's basically the same thing
So, I don't know. I
Like it. I just like it. That's all I just I just think they're neat. I just think I'm neat
Okay
Good aunt. Thank you voicemailer. Good answer. I hope you're I hope your queries have all been addressed
query
Got them
Next voicemail is called ignore the end three two one go
Okay, last one
You guys talk about Homestuck a lot and I've never read it. Yeah, you give me a short concise pitch on why?
Like I know the discourse of it. I know the trolls. We've we've talked about it so much
What is so captivating about the story? Oh my god? I feel like also Ben
What comics of yours do I need to read to care about your game? Thanks? I love you care
Baby Ben
Okay, so ignore the end ignore the end. So it's okay. It's okay a few
the game is
Only relevant to slime and punishment the game is a part of the slime and punishment story
So you only need to read that one
If you don't read it, then it won't make any sense. What's going on in the game?
I mean, you could probably still play the game and it would be fine
But like this would be like what what is this situation that I'm witnessing who are these characters?
Well, I mean
If you wanted an elevator pitch for Homestuck, I can't give one to you because it's too
Difficult to do that
Maybe that gives you enough of an idea. It's just good. I mean, it's hard to explain
He's heard us talk about Homestuck. He should know
What I don't really know exactly what he wants here. I
Should I just just read it dummy?
Yeah, like you can't I can't give like a plot synopsis that explains Homestuck and why it's good because why it's good
It's like the premise of Homestuck is not why it's good. It's the
It's like the like weird and like funny and and very it's the journey
Specifically way that it explores that that concept. It's not the premise exactly
It's not like even the way it's told exactly
It's the journey you go on reading it and seeing everything that happens
Yeah, and I've like I've said a lot a lot of people like the trolls and and got into it like post act
three and four four for for me for me peak Homestuck is is act one
But a lot of people don't feel that way a lot of people think it only gets good later. That's fine
That's fine for some people. I guess well, that's exactly the thing is that the the comic shifts and changes
it's
It's focus so much
That it is like the journey of reading it and seeing where it goes with all the different things all the different threads
Yeah, and and how it chooses to explore them. So just yeah read it. There's real
There's really no simple way to explain why I like Homestuck. It's
That's why do you think I've taken you 300 episodes of a podcast to do explain it?
Oh
Flynn okay next voicemail is called. I am the captain of my life now three two one go
but a PCP got a
Question for you guys that can maybe become a discussion if you care to have one my question is
Have you ever regretted being a fan of someone or something in the long the long run or the long term?
Quick short context behind this question. I used to embarrassingly be
Pretty active listener of Trixie and all of her content
Should make those $10 vlogs in her side channel and just all this stuff every day
and I listen to it just out of force of habit and
I would consider getting like one day I'd be like I want to maybe become a teacher
You know and take my career in that direction and then maybe I saw like a Trixie vlog
She was like man fuck school. I failed college fuck
High school sucks. Yeah suck man, and I was like, yeah teachers probably suck because you know, they probably suck
Same thing for like the government. I'm thinking about getting a job like a government job. It pays well
It's it's up my alley. It's utilizes a lot of my skills, but Trixie is like the government is it's anarchy
And we need we need anarchy the government is a destructive force. Yeah, so I'm embarrassing shit like that
I kind of regret listing all those so you guys have any similar experiences
Yeah, I man. Yeah, I can
Yeah, I
Don't know that don't
That's unfortunate whether that's unfortunate if that affected your affected your your course in life a real choice
Yeah, I mean, I don't I can't think of any like
People I became like fans of I mean I watched a lot of Trixie stuff
Especially earlier on it's like I was watching all of it, but I never really took her advice as like
Gospel like I'm sure some of the younger fans of hers were yeah, cuz I was her friend. It was like oh like, you know
She's not always right. I
Cuz I'm sort of on the same level, but some people they get into that. Oh my god the the youtuber die. It's so
Beautiful a lot of radiant light. I can't not agree with it even like yeah
I can I can imagine I could fuck you up a little even if you say like hey
I'm not a role model. Don't don't like be like me which you know she would say that yeah
But but but still like you know a lot of people in the world want to be
Youtubers a lot of people like want to do that and they see someone doing that doing what they want to do and
I think even if you say don't I'm not a Roma a lot of people like be like oh, but I kind of I kind of want to be like
You you know like if you're being successful at a thing they want
They're probably gonna want to emulate you like why wouldn't they it it's gonna happen. It makes
Perfect sense. I I guess like it's weird cuz I don't feel like I regret any of the things
I was into when I was younger even if some of them are cringe
I suppose like like it's not really a regret worthy thing
Because my life wasn't completely turned around or ruined
Yeah, anything
Like I used to be a fan of dr. Wolf. I would watch I would watch his videos and be like, huh, you know
Insightful, but like I fell for the the I fell for the accent. I fell for like
The the sense he puts on of like oh, he's got a waistcoat. He must be smart
And I was just like, yeah, you know
Analysis bronies are cool. I well there. I I guess I
It's it's not like I feel like it was a terrible thing that I kind of like watched some of the cringier brony
People for a while like whatever
Yeah, I don't I don't feel I don't I mean
I don't feel like anything that I was into like really did me harm or or anything
There's nothing that I'm like, oh, if only I had never gotten to that
I wouldn't have you know done something or other
I mean, I guess I were I kind of regret that I was a big Harry Potter fan growing up because I don't like JK
Rowling anymore
And I kind of feel this. Oh man. I mean, I maybe the worst one is that I used to read ruches
Blogs and ruches a is a horrible horrible human being
I didn't know at the he wasn't he didn't used to be quite as bad as he is now
You know, you know who that is right the pickup artist guy. Oh
No, well, he he was a pickup artist guy now. He's like he's just like a fucking
Now he's just like a fucking social commentator. He's a down guy trad trad calf like fascist man
Just like he's he's the worst human. He wasn't always quite so bad
But boy, I'm like, it's it sure is embarrassing to be like, yeah, I used to I used to read that guy's blog
I bought one of his books
But it's it's true
So but I wouldn't I don't say if I regret it because it didn't like
Didn't do me any harm and like sure some of the stuff see he made he was he was edgy
But I never like took any of his edgier statements. That's seriously
I don't feel like it it made me a worse or even much edgier person
Maybe I mean when it comes to like Harry Potter like I still like
At least the games the games are like treasured memories didn't didn't turn me into a turf. So, you know, I
It's fine. That's J.K. Rowling sucks, but we all know that
Yeah
So so I guess not really I guess there isn't really anything that I regret being into that much
Even even stuff that like I look back and I think oh that was pretty bad actually like whatever
It's not bad. It's not bad that I used to like something that is bad
It's character building character building. That's right
Next voicemail is called politic question three two one go
Short question voicemail for this week PCP sort of similar to another voicemail I sent this week
But what are your general thoughts on the government?
What do you think it's kind of a broad topic?
But if you could sum it up, what do you generally think about the government?
What do you think the role of the government should be in people's lives and
The state of the government currently do you think there's departments that should be
Sized down or removed from power. Do the government should be expanded. Do you have any general thoughts on I have for discussion next
I have been thinking about this
lately, I have been seeing people saying that
Anarchists are just liberals and I'm
Part of me thinks that I understand why they say that and I've been I've been thinking like I
Don't know. What am I am I am I am I am I an anarchist or am I a communist?
I'm I'm definitely one or the other and I guess you can technically be both, but I guess
In my I'm like stupid. I'm like stupid. I don't understand anything
But when I hear those words
I think an anarchist would want no government and a communist wants the government to
Do stuff and like take care of stuff
And give people stuff and redistribute wealth, which I do want it to do that
I
Think I might I think I'm I think I'm I don't know
I think I do kind of want I
Mean obviously the government we have now is imperfect and I wouldn't authorize like the government as it exists currently
Now has the authorization to do everything that would be bad
But I do think that in a perfect world. Yeah, the government would control a lot of stuff
That would just make life easier for people and like just offer everyone in the world
It's the essentials, you know food clothing housing healthcare education and just
Yeah, I want the government to do lots of stuff for free
Maybe that means I'm not an anarchist
But yeah, and yet I don't like all the anarchists that I know all the people that I know that call themselves anarchists
They all see they're all pro, you know universal health care and all that stuff. I
Guess I don't fucking understand anything
Yeah, yeah, I don't know terms quite that much
I think closest I would maybe call myself a socialist
But like what kind of socialist I'm not even really sure what the terms are
I know certain things that I like when it comes to government
I the I mean the UK government is
It sucks
But I'm not like well read enough or like knowledgeable enough about how it sucks to explain
I just don't like Boris Johnson or the Tories and
I don't like the the media machine that like demonized Jeremy Corbyn
But by you know, like it all pushed that the anti-semite thing so that people wouldn't vote for him democracy
It's it's so heavily swung by just whatever people end up being able to say on the news and it sucks
I
Think the government
It should exist. I don't think you should be completely gone
Mostly because I don't know how you could organize things
Without one, but I obviously think the the government's
Power shouldn't be like
Like from one person more democracy within the government I suppose
Yeah group groups of like a representative from each place
I don't know. I don't really know how it works right now, but I know that it doesn't work
You know, they they say like um
Socialism is about like democratizing everything, right? Like even the it's not democratizing everything
Work democratize work
Who is not one guy at the top of any given system that like scrapes a little off the top for himself
as extra free profit for no labor
It's it's all like everybody works together to make everything work
Yeah, and people would say oh well
What if people don't want to do it, but I don't know it's the same as everything I
Think yeah same as you people the government should provide free basic living standards
So the people don't die people have somewhere to sleep if they need it
I mean, I feel like the food all that stuff the government should exist too and like people say I
Understand there's a difference between like the state and the government and like the state is bad
But like government is good in theory at least government is like just people organizing as a tool
Yeah, government is just people organizing to like
You know fucking accomplish things. It's sort of like a big union if you think about it
kind of or it could be
you know
Ideally a government it gives it it
It you know it could collects it collects, you know resources from you know the
accumulated from the aggregate like production of
Civilization you know everyone's working everyone's doing stuff making stuff government collects that stuff and then redistributes it in the form of you know
free services or
Housing UBI what whatever form reach redistributive
Justice I guess
Is a good and also and I mean also as a check against like private
power right like monopolies right like
Jeff Jeff Bezos gets more money than the government
And is more powerful and can just buy the government right it can just lobby the government to be like oh do this do that
And it's like well, you know ideally the government exists to be like well
Actually, it's illegal for you to have that much money because you're just one person and that's bad
So we're breaking your fucking company up, and we're gonna shoot you
Yeah, I
Know yeah, it's so difficult at least in the UK is that
so much of politics is run by ministers who are
funneled through like the
upper-class like a
Super-rich eaten school and then Oxford and Cambridge
Really expensive schools where they are told you will be a minister you will be a politician
Because you have all the money and you can just do that because you got the you got the degree and being the prime minister
Now you're the prime minister well done, and then they have no reason they have no incentive. They have no idea that
They should
Stop that system from funneling their own children through the same super-rich
Highway to politics. Yeah, because it worked because it worked for them the system work for them
Yeah, it works for them like it, and they just they actually just
It's it's weird to think that they view the like it's a human being and they're viewing other human beings as
Disposable and trash and nothing and so that seems like super villain stuff
But I it just has to be true by based on their actions
They just don't think of poor people as deserving of life or or needs being to be met
They only do it in the pursuit of continuing to be in power if it's not good PR then they wouldn't bother
hmm, I
Mean, I guess that you gotta you got you gotta maintain your power so that you can do
The things that you might tell yourself are good and for the good of everyone
Right, but like if you lose your position if you lose the votes or whatever then you're out, and then you can't do it
So whatever whatever it takes, right?
Yeah
The next voicemail is called gaming
Smiley face, okay three two one go
Hey PCB on a tone Jones here
Tom is on this week, but the rest of y'all may be familiar with the new guilty-gear game that just came out
I was just wondering if y'all had any thoughts on that be it based on story gameplay or whatever
I at the at that the gaming cafe that we went to they were they had a big like seating area and they had big
Monitors in like a central area, and they were playing people were playing guilty-gear stride strife, right is the new one
I don't know. I've never heard of such a thing never heard of I think they have the new guilty gear
It's called guilty gear strife
I think and my opinion of it is that I don't play fighting games, and I don't care and
I'm sorry
Everyone seems really into it, and that's great, but I am not interested in seeing more drawings of May on my
Timeline, I don't care that she has a pirate hat
I'm just it's whatever
Yeah, it's fine the day. I care about a fighting game is the day I am Tom Oliver
Mmm, and not a second before and that's today. Oh
No, it shows you the sign that turns you into Tom Oliver when you read it. Oh
Somebody could maybe make a
Version of the sign that makes you like they could make that if they get a clip or an image of Tom looking at the
The board for the guilty-gear lecture or the animos one
Yeah, it could easily be realized
But do we dare? What do we dare though?
Oh
Yeah, I forget everything Tom said in the guilty-gear lecture. I remember pauging, but I don't
I wonder I wonder if that's like exploding in views now because of the new game
I'm sure it does. It's been doing well
You know, I mean I can I can find out I can find out right now
Let's see. I gotta log out of my account
Twitter is why is Twitter like this Twitter is just not working for me, and I'm like
It's making me nervous
It's making me nervous that Twitter is just doesn't it works on my phone
What did it do to me?
What they fucking do to me? I don't know
Okay, logging into the pro crass denators podcast and then I'm gonna
look at the studio and then
Where are my analytics come on?
analytics
overview
Views see no, don't go there see more fuck
Stop
Okay
Guilty-gear. Oh
Yeah, guilty-gear is our highest viewed video for I mean for this past month
it was
And animal morphs and guilty-gear where the people the videos people were watching on our channel the most last month this year
Guilty-gear has jumped up ahead. It was really going
It was getting like over a thousand views a day
For a couple weeks there in early June now. It's kind of settling back down to under a thousand
So yeah, I had a little bump there. That's pretty that's pretty good. That's pretty exciting
Let me look a little back in the timeline
Oh, man
Kind of a lot of I got a lot of views I got a lot of views. What is that like 400k?
Guilty number guilty-gear lecture
It is at how many views how many views how many views how many views yeah
432,000 base with 378 downloads
What a bunch of fucking jerks what a bunch of what a bunch of salty bitches. What a bunch of guilty-gears
true
Hey, you know what guilt's my gears
What's that it's the next voicemail
I'm I'm just I before we I gotta say
Tim Rogers why has it been five months in your lessons your last video five months since the toky-meky memorial review you are
Insane you are a wild
style
Yeah, okay next voicemail. It's called sui-chan wa kyou mo kawaii
three two one go
Now that you have successfully turned the PCP into the Ben St. Podcast
What are your plans for the future of the show?
Nuclear option nuclear option baby, uh
I'll fucking
You should have more guests on just have more guests on
But there's yeah, but it's so hard
So hard to ask someone do you want to be on my show?
It's embarrassing. What if they say no? What if they laugh at me?
Well, they record them laughing at you and say they were on the show
That just just play the laugh track every time you say anything and it's like they're laughing at your jokes
That that's that's one. That's how you get them. There's
You take life gives you lemons make a little lemonade
Next voicemail is called me again
three two one go
Please unpin the top post of the PCP subreddit
Let's see
Crastinate or is
sub
The Titan PCP read it and I got some different things
The the
The top post in
The top post that I see is red in the playlist redcon 2017 the playlist
Four years ago, what's wrong with that? Oh, it does not exist wait. Why does this playlist not exist?
Wait, who had who made the playlist? There's there's bunches of videos in there
But I mean, maybe maybe maybe Trixie maybe Trixie made the playlist
And by priveting everything the playlists are also gone
I mean all the videos. I mean a lot of the videos are still there because they weren't all on Trixie's channel
the
the I'm did
You think you think the playlist was made on on Trixie's channel. I mean, I can't remember who made it
But maybe
This is
I'm looking at the at the subreddit. Oh, it's did we show this
Meme this is a good. I'm surprised this this post has like 50 upvotes
It was posted two weeks ago. It's got 50 upvotes
You know what?
I'm I'm reading I'm reading the subreddit. I'm reading the subreddit. It's actually getting like
It's actually got people looking at it. That's that's crazy. I like forget that the subreddit exists
Tarbuck trans and posted the ruby lecture this this meme about everyone else being dead is funny to me
Uh
Unfortunate that I'm not there or Tom
Are you just not no, we're just not there just not there. Hmm
But they could have done something funny like like me and tell more each of your arms or something
Pandaman Pandaman post post here that says
The PCP has a real art preservation problem
Many members take down old videos and the vast majority of their old videos in some cases. How is this okay?
Yeah, that's for it. I agree. I believe in our preservation, but I can't
Oh, we haven't we haven't deleted. Uh, well
Never what I haven't deleted anything. I'm doing my part
Do someone unit number 2278 asked guys who are the current members of the League of Nate fuckers?
You must need to know for lore. I don't need them all but the more you can name the better because I don't remember a single one
Thanks in advance
Your boy Cthulhu zero comments
Your boy Cthulhu says important sources for PCP history. It's like this guy is looking for
looking for
for for for
Knowledge secret knowledge. Okay, I'm gonna stop reading it now
But I it's cool to see people up post in there and actually like voting on stuff and be it's neat
Me me me stumbling upon the subreddit while trying to find out what happened to the Homestuck podcast
I was listening to and it's the it's the funny gif
where you know
Where he goes in with the pizza and there's everything's on fire
mmm. Oh
Yeah, it's uh, yeah Troy
I'm trying to find out what happened to the Homestuck. Is is is he talking about arm retrieval?
I'm assuming so like arm retrieval scone. I wonder what's happened then looks into it. Oh, no
Oh, oh look at it a month ago. Henlo Corgo posted PCP is even better now to be honest
The episodes are about as focused on a specific topic as they everywhere
And the fact that every episode doesn't have four or more people talking over each other arguing
Which makes them easier to listen to and enjoy
Woo
I like it if you listeners if you if you are a if you're a if you're a lay epic redditor
And you haven't seen it. I mean go check out the fucking PCP subreddit. It's uh
It's not super active, but there's there's posts. There's real posts on the internet
Uh, yes next voicemail is called PCP bad comments award show number 267
three two one go
Coming to you pre-recorded from an undisclosed location. It's the PCP bad comments award show
Woo, thank you. Thank you. I've got a great show for you tonight. Now, please welcome tonight's special guest playmaker
Woo
I love that note playmaker you're tonight's winner of the award for the worst comment of episode
267 would you mind giving us a recitation? We have it for you on that card there
Ben becoming a calmer really was he harambe everything change in the timeline for the PCP
Thanks for coming on playmaker tune in next week same pcb time same pcb channel
Really really was he harambe?
Uh, uh, I gotta find the pro crastinators
podcast
So it's happened so first. I didn't know when he started saying the comment comment
Uh, so it's also sort of blended into his own speech. Oh wait, I was from 267
That was from 267 not 268. Uh, are you really gonna go find the comment?
I just it's
What does he mean? What does he mean me becoming a commie? Was he harambe?
Oh, here's it was was the harambe
Maybe they mean his harambe moment
I think maybe what it means is that like when harambe
Was killed that was like when we branched into the dark timeline and everything started going wrong
I think I think that's the implication here
Uh, okay. Oh, we can understand more if we listen to the next voicemail
PCP bad comment award show meta post three two one go
Ben
You're really gonna ban all these terrible comments and undercut my fucking show
Who am I supposed to make fun of now?
There are people whiting about the pcb being different every single week
I'm only gonna ban people that say nothing
Constructive at all, but just be like
Just end the show guys guys the show's not like it used to be just end it
Just stop just stop making it guys. Please. I personally don't like this youtube video
It shouldn't be existing should you should stop me you should delete the thing
I don't like instead of me leaving which is so much easier
I don't like this episode of you should do something about it
Uh
No, I won't be I'm I'm there will never be any shortage of bad comments
Uh next one if I if I deleted all the bad comments
We just wouldn't have any more comments and that wouldn't be any fun
Uh next voicemail is called the three. I don't know what that means three two one go
Hi so
Hello
Is the question about how much
Ellie is our cuts out. Is it mainly just moments where
No one's speaking for an extended period of time or is it
Or are there actual like chunks of
Conversation being cut out
Ellie is our cut out that long pause that he put in that the one that voicemail
Uh
No, it's pretty rare that we actually cut out like actual conversation. Generally. It's like generally it's like um
Just someone like you you went to get a drink before and I said Ellie is our cut out the silence
Yeah, that's usually it. Uh, or if
I don't know if we said something uh
Devastatingly bad and we like oh, we're gonna cover this up. It's good a little watergate
And let's say cut that out
Yeah, if if I'm if it's something if like someone says something that's like sensitive information
It's like now. I don't want to say that Ellie is our cut cut the part
But that like almost never happens. It's happened like once or twice
Uh, generally it's just silences
Or if there's like a voicemail, that's like particularly bad and we're like we just don't want to play it
Uh, then it'll just be like Ellie is our just cut that out and pretend like it wasn't there that also pretty rarely happens
um
Next voicemail is called le power tools three two one go
You know, I fucking power tools to make furniture. I did it myself with a hammer and nails
So I was like, I don't know fucking seven or some shit
Like and how was it how was the chair that you made when you were seven functional a person can sit on it
So therefore, uh, you're wrong benny boy
I think there's something about like tarbuck transom said just build your own furniture
And then we were like but we don't want to do that because it's all of the things about it
I including having to get tools and it's like no just get a tool
It would be really just get a single tool
I mean, I'm sitting at a at a at a desk with a drawer in it
I like having a desk with a drawer in it. It would be really hard for me to build a desk with a drawer in it
um
I would I'll just fucking buy one. I don't know
Hey, so my you could my parents gave me this one. You could carve a desk with a drawer
um
In it out of a larger desk with a larger drawer in it
Uh
Scrape the venero just pretend you made it. I guess I guess that's true
Oh, we got the it's our last voicemail
Um, it's a it's a virus. It looks like it's it's a mp3
Fast upload. It's why did they do this? I don't I don't like it, but I'm going to
Oh, okay, pick it. It's yeah, it's a link to another like audio
It's a 30 second voicemail
I don't know why you put it here, but one second. Yeah, okay. Let's listen to it. It's called voice
Voice meter doesn't work on my pc fuck off dot mp3. Okay three two one go
But for me, like, you know, if you were to I mean, you don't really criticize me
Often ever but like if you were to I'd be like, yeah, you're you're right
You know, like I trust your opinion on my work or not to say that I would not to say your work is so consistent
Like right there's
It doesn't really tend to veer off in like new directions that like I need to point out like what are my thoughts on them? Yeah
All right, I see
um
Where's the trust gone
The trust
Trixie trusted your judgment and now oh true true. I mean I
I don't I don't uh
I don't
I'm not unlike unlike many hat. I'm not one of the people who's like, uh
Her raps are so bad. Like she's so she's so bad at rapping and like the rap. She's making her just garbage
Just tarot. I don't have any opinion. I don't have any opinion about that
uh, but uh
So I'm not like
I'm not I'm not I'm not offering constructive criticism
Uh, it was a different time
Is a time when you had terrible audio and I just remembered that you used to have really terrible audio for a lot of the
The podcast I used to have yeah, I had a pretty I mean my mic is still pretty mediocre
But I had an even worse one for the first like year or more
Uh, it was bad. Yeah, it was pretty bad. Uh, but you know what it was great and I wouldn't have it any other way
noble
I have a using like a blue snowball for the beginning. It was my first
Microphone I still have it all the gibbon take stuff on that. I'm using a snowball ice. I don't know what the difference is between
It's new that's all
It's white. It's not blue. It's white
It's more powerful
Well, the one I had was gray
Or chrome or something
I see
Well, then I just don't know
Well, then I just have no fucking clue
Uh
Damn, that's the last voicemail. We're done and it hasn't even been three hours
Oh my god, imagine finishing the podcast in under three hours
Well, I'll relish the opportunity
I am gonna
I don't know. I'm just gonna go like be sick for the rest of the day because I still feel like shit
Uh
But we did it we recorded an episode
But let's I'm gonna check I'm gonna check the lord of ghosts kickstarter way
Oh, wait, I'm not on the page anymore. I was gonna leave her
Okay
Oh still 79 back
This is refresh
It's refresh just in case now 79 back is still
2571 by the time you're listening to this
It should be higher
and uh put in the comments
Uh lord of ghost pog. I love that kickstarter
I love that kickstarter so much
Oh, dude, I'm oh, yeah, I'm a I'm a big fan of the lord of ghosts kickstarter. Yeah, it's like my favorite kickstarter
It's like it's such an inspiration to me. Yeah. I mean, it's good, but it's better live
I that reminds me of
before
Better it's better live. Yeah
when when before I made before patreon.com slash ben sain
We is was like a real patreon. It was like a joke patreon
And like the joke was that like
Ben sainte is creating a patreon and like oh, yeah, I remember that and the yeah
The joke was like this patreon itself is like the project that you you are funding like this
It will be my my masterpiece or whatever. I don't know. I thought it was funny
I thought maybe I could get it like posted around as like a little bit of a meme
Nobody's note. No, it didn't work
Uh
It was better than what did I offer now, which is you know, semi regular updates on upcoming
Cons exclusive content that business models. It's not working. We just we have to go back. We have to go back to the meme viral
A marketing sort of way
uh
Uh lord of ghosts kickstarter everybody fucking give this little
Little blob some some money. He's he's earned it. Yeah, we love our little blob. Don't we folks?
We sure do
Yes
And if we get enough money, maybe he can exist finally
finally
Hurray, uh, any anything else before we wrap up?
Um
Nope, okay, then that's the end of the show. Goodbye everyone. We'll see you
Next time
Leave voicemail become a patron. Uh join the minecraft server. Uh, okay. Goodbye
Bye