Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Poopcast.
I'm the best guy ever. Man, that was a killer joke. Nailed it.
He really is the best guy ever.
The best poop ever. Oh, he did it again.
Yeah, he just keeps going nuts with that.
He just can't stop himself.
Here's Ben Saint is here.
Yeah, I am. Hi, fucker.
As is Mumkey Jones.
Cut my dick into pieces. This is my last showed.
And Digibro.
I woke up, I jacked my dick, and I came on the show.
You came on the show.
That's what you needed that half an hour for?
No, I jacked up before that half an hour.
Give me like 10 seconds and I'll do that shit real quick.
You're really pushing my times up there, Ben.
I'm not trying to like get fucking candles out and like fucking edge for the afternoon.
Can I just say that this is the first episode of PCP where I don't respect any of the co-hosts, even a little bit.
That's good. We tried to get Mage on, but she's busy.
Usually we have like a Mage or a Jess or a hippo, but today it's just like the worst of the bunch.
Yeah, yeah, this basket of deplorables here.
It's hashtag worst cast.
So today's a special day for the PCP, because this will be our 50th episode.
Oh fuck.
How about that shit?
Not counting the special bonus episode.
Whoa.
Well that's true, of course.
The countless other episodes of things on the...
Yeah, hey everybody, go pledge $5 to the fucking...
In fact, when this comes out, the bonus episode for March of 2017 will be out.
And if you want to hear the highly anticipated Shrek versus Harry Potter throwdown,
I forgot, I forgot that's what it was.
That's what it was.
Oh, it's a glorious time.
It's going to be the best thing of all time.
So yeah, go to our Patreon, go to the fucking procrastinators Patreon.
Fucking links and shit, pledge $5.
There you go.
Do what you need, do what you gotta do.
And we don't know what's leprechaun into hood.
That's right.
And who knows what we'll do for the bonus episode next time.
We'll let you know.
Anyway, so we're talking about travel today.
Travel is the topic.
Yeah, because Monkey was just traveling.
He got home from traveling two hours ago, right?
Yeah, Nate, can I tell my own fucking story?
Jesus Christ.
All right, all right, I'm just leading in.
Go on, go on.
I'm transitioning.
I'm in the perfect condition to record a podcast about travel,
because I am right now the embodiment of how travel affects a person.
I am very sick and tired and my throat is all fucked.
And I can't even focus for more than like 30 seconds at a time
on anything because I woke up so early to travel.
So I'm very excited to talk about travel today and all the pros and cons
and cons and negatives and cons and bad parts.
So just tell us, where did you leave from and where did you arrive?
How long was this travel time?
I started off in North Carolina and I took a plane to Chicago
and then I took a plane here to Iowa.
So it's not the longest I've been on.
I mean, the longest travel time, we'll get into that later.
But this one was only five or six hours,
but I'm mostly just tired because I had to get up at like four in the morning.
Yep, yep.
I am also the embodiment of travel now because I just ate a pop tart
and got out of bed and walked over to your desk.
Stellar, stellar.
No, just now, like as we were recording, I have been eating a pop tart.
And I think that the only time I usually eat pop tarts is in travel
because it's a very convenient food to take with you, you know,
stuff. So I'm in your backpack or something.
When I travel, I always find that I eat a shit ton when I'm traveling.
I go to like fucking gross restaurants and I buy tons of shitty food and I eat it all
because it's like a vacation.
It's like a little fucking, I'm in transition.
What I do on this at this point in my life doesn't matter.
So I'll just go to like when I used to travel from home to college,
I would get on the fucking train from Providence to New York or something
and then take a bus from New York to New Jersey or something, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
Yeah, I did that too.
Point, yeah, point is I was stopped in New York and I would walk around
and I would fucking eat Krispy Kreme.
I would go and look for Krispy Kreme and fucking Penn Station
and I would eat Krispy Kreme because it was the only time
because they didn't have them in Massachusetts back then.
Penn Station had a good selection.
They had this good deep dish pizza I would get.
Penn Station is a great station.
One time I'd missed my train and I got stuck there overnight
and I had to sit slumped against a wall for an entire night.
That's like my worst nightmare.
It happened.
I had to sit slumped against a wall while fucking literally insane homeless people,
like swandered around like zombies.
You were SpongeBob in the rock bottom episode.
Yeah, I think so.
You were an urban street warrior for one night.
It was rough.
Since Davoo's not here on this episode, he said he didn't have enough to say about travel,
I guess, but I will share a similar story of his, which is that when he was flying back
after the events that transpired, which inspired the how we lost our virginity episode,
on his way back, his plane, they just, I guess they were repairing it.
He had to stay in the airport overnight.
Like almost a whole 20 hours or so that he was stuck in this airport
and they gave him like a bunch of vouchers for shit.
And I guess they had given him a voucher for a hotel room, like, you know,
the connected to the airport one, but he didn't take it because he was afraid
that he would sleep through alarms and not make his flight again.
So instead he opted 20 hours.
Yeah.
He opted to sleep in the airport instead, like to just lay on chairs and shit
and use their food vouchers and stuff.
So you know what airline that was?
I'm just curious.
I have no idea.
Southwest probably.
Yeah, that's the question based off of that that I'd like to open up to the panel.
Can you guys sleep when you're traveling?
Because personally, if I'm in the middle of traveling, like I can't sleep on the plane.
I can't sleep in the airport.
I can't sleep anywhere until I get to my destination.
I can only sleep if I am dead fucking tired, which has been the case a lot of the times,
but I have to be like killed.
I have a really hard time sleeping on buses and trains and planes and stuff.
So sometimes when I travel, I plan it so that I just don't sleep the night before.
So I'll have been up for like fucking 40 straight hours when I get on the bus.
And then I can fucking sleep on the trip.
I've tried things like that, and sometimes that doesn't mean I'll pass out.
It doesn't always, but it helps.
Every year that I go to Baltimore for Otacon, my cousin Boyd drives the car.
It's usually my car, but he drives.
And it's a four and a half hour to five hour drive.
And I usually am so excited about the con that I won't sleep for the night before.
And I'm thinking, I'll just sleep in the car on the way there.
And it never happens.
Like I'll be sitting there like utterly wracked with tiredness.
Like all I could think about is how badly I want to sleep.
But something about being in a car, I just can't do it.
And then somehow after Otacon's over and we're on the way home,
I pass out like a fucking, you know, I go out like a light and I'm just done the whole way back
because I'm just too physically out from having not really slept through most of the convention.
Oh, I hear you.
I hear you, my gay brother.
I am with you 100% in all of your endeavors.
Well, hey, I was going to say, you're welcome.
Yeah, it's been a very supportive guy.
In the, when I was traveling, I had some experience like that.
Well, okay, when I, when I, I have a very easy time sleeping.
You are on planes.
You used to fuck.
You used to fucking when we would, when we would stay up and watch adult swim,
you would fucking pass out way early.
You would miss all the latest anime.
I would.
That's something.
I think the reason me and my friends had that very, uh,
like my cousin is one of those guys who you can like see him fully asleep and snoring,
but he will insist he didn't fall asleep, like no matter what.
He'd be like, no, I wasn't sleeping, man.
I wasn't sleeping.
I was just pressing my eyes.
I kind of feel like that.
Like I think when me and Ben would be up watching anime late, like he would say,
are you asleep?
And like I had been like mostly unconscious, but I would like
flood her open my eyes and like see something on the screen.
He'd be like, no, I'm, I'm totally awake right now.
Yeah.
He would, he would like, he would like argue with you about it, that he wasn't asleep,
even though it was like, it was blatantly true.
But the reason is, because all of us had a certain like shame that we had missed the
animes, you know, like, like, like, like, like the one thing that we all cared about in life
was getting to watch anime, but it all airs at this late ass time period.
And so if you didn't make it to the end, if you didn't make it to 2am when they
restarted and do all the shows again, that it's like, oh, you, you fucking,
you just couldn't do it, man.
Like your passion wasn't strong enough, you know, if you were that, if you really cared,
you would have made it all the way through and powered through the sleep.
So I think that's why we, you know, none of us were accusing each other of that.
But I think that's what we were afraid of.
On the subject of sleeping while traveling, I did fucking buy a case of some like over
the counter sleeping pills, which I think just have like melanin or melatonin or whatever
the fucking sleeping thing is.
And sometimes I take those and I don't know if they actually help, but they feel like
they help and that's good enough.
So I would recommend those.
I hate the thing about the problem with sleeping while traveling.
The biggest problem by far is getting my head in a comfortable resting position.
Yeah.
Who else?
I mean, when you're on the plane, I always credit at the windows.
I just like looking at the window and like you always do the thing where your head is
like, I put it against the window, but there's like hard plastic there.
You kind of lean it back, but then your, your head will fucking be at a weird uncomfortable
angle where it's kind of like angling off your torso.
Cause it, it finally falls into that little like crack there and it's the worst.
And that's why they have travel pills, I guess.
I've been, I've been traveling a bunch lately.
I've been taking long ass bus rides to and from Atlanta and I've found some techniques.
I bring a blanket and I fucking tuck the blanket up behind my head because if I have that,
if I have that, then I can fucking rest my head against the crevice between window and
seats, which would otherwise be horribly uncomfortable and bumpy,
but with the blanket is quite tolerable.
And then I sit cross ways along the seat, take up both seats because fuck letting anyone sit next to me.
And I put down the armrest and I put my feet up against the armrest.
So I'm kind of squeeze myself into the, into the seat space,
kind of sandwiched in between the wall of the bus and the armrest with my head up in the blanket.
And that is pretty tolerable, highly recommended.
I hate squishing my legs when I'm trying to sleep.
It's very uncomfortable.
I feel like I need to be a little squished.
Really?
Yeah.
I'd like curl up a little bit.
Well, not always, but sometimes.
Should we all tell these stories of our individual biggest travel expeditions?
Yes, let's do that.
Yeah, we can talk about our bullshit if you want.
Okay.
Me too.
Monkey, tell us, tell us your tale, monkey.
What do you got?
Oh boy, it all started back in high school.
It starts with one thing.
You don't know why.
It doesn't even matter how hard you try.
The year was 1942 and I had heard some good stories about this place.
It's called Auschwitz and I really wanted to know what was going on.
The year was 1945 with just her sister at her side.
Anyway, exactly.
19, 19, 1942, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Tuesday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday comes again.
This is terrible.
This is the worst podcast of all time.
Whichever commenter writes a full Hitler parody of that song, the lyrics in the comments,
Ben is going to give them a thumbs up on their comments.
So Ben will give you a thumbs up.
Yeah.
I will record if you get all the syllable counts correct and you're not a fucking idiot and the
word's actually rhyme.
Correct rhyme schemes, right?
I'll do a quick sing-through and send it to Monkey for him to post on Monkey Jones too.
Oh, perfect.
Yeah, did you ever get a lot of reviews out of abusing you on that channel?
So it's been great so far.
Yeah.
All the shitposts we've recorded at your house have, like already the first four have garnered
me like five bucks.
And I'm like, okay, five bucks for doing nothing.
That sounds pretty cool.
Yeah, fuck.
He's recording Diddy sitting in his room.
And we've gotten easily 30 on those.
So.
Yeah, we do.
So it all started back in high school.
Little monkey boy.
He, it's not called the yellow fever when they're not Asian.
What's it called when you just want to fuck somebody who's not the same color as you?
Being a xenophile.
Being a xenophile outside your race?
I don't know.
It's called being like a race mixing?
Like a reverse cuck or something.
I don't know.
It's called being a devil spawn is going to hell.
Xenophile.
Sure, okay.
Yeah, that doesn't make any sense.
Little monkey boy at the age of 17 was a bit of a xenophile.
Yeah.
This gorgeous foreign exchange student girl.
Oh boy.
What kind of, what kind of, where's your front?
Where's your front?
Argentina, my friend.
Okay.
Argentina.
She's got that big Latin ass.
The widest country in South America.
So you know it's valuable.
Thank God.
Yeah.
Like she's only a little bit ethnic.
Phew.
You know, when you see a hot foreign exchange student girl,
you make sure that you're her best friend.
Because when they're in this foreign country,
they don't have any friends.
They don't have anybody.
So if you're the only shoulder they have to turn to,
maybe you get a little bit of that Argentinian puss.
Who knows?
And you can give them one of the like, you know,
no one in this country gives a fuck about you.
So you better do what I tell you to do.
Oh, you better, you better consume it.
That doesn't sound like negging.
That sounds like fucking negging.
That sounds like fucking...
Yeah, like I love to go up to girls in the club and neg them
with like, dude, I could totally snap your neck right now.
That does not look like,
you do not look like you have a well-toned neck, girl.
Let me just work on that again.
Or like you can teach them fake things
about American culture.
For example, in Argentina,
they do that thing where they greet each other
by kissing people on the cheek.
And I taught her here in America,
how you greet friends when you're alone in their house
and their host mother is gone,
is you pull down their pants and you suck their dick.
So I taught her that very important American custom.
So yeah, we became really good friends.
And naturally, she eventually had to go back home.
But we stayed in contact and she wanted me to come down
to Argentina to stay at her house with her family.
All right.
So that was a big old trip,
crazy plan and cost like $2,500 out of the monkey bank account.
That's like all months of working
at the local amusement park for that bullshit.
And the trip there was fine.
Like I had to take a plane from Iowa to Texas.
Wait, hold on.
I blanked out for a second,
but are you saying that you went all the way to Argentina
to get some poon?
That's right.
So you said you didn't do more than...
We're not that far in the story yet, did you?
I'm telling you about my very extravagant flight plan.
Okay.
Well, I'm just shocked because like on the virginity episode,
we were all talking about how much we paid to lose our virginity
and monkeys over here flying out of the fucking country.
Well, sure.
I paid like fucking $400 million thousand
because I had to go to college to do it.
That's true.
Wait, had you had sex with this girl before this trip?
No.
Okay.
What?
Did you suck your dick?
Ben, please.
I do not kiss and tell.
I'm a gentleman.
I mean, fine.
But do you get your dick sucked in town?
I'm loud and angry.
I don't know.
Wait, wait.
But so, monkey.
Okay.
You were talking about a flight plan.
So getting your dick sucked was that part of your plan?
Now, you don't get to bring friends
because the flight plan I just filed at the agency lists me,
my men, and Dr. Pavel here, but only one of you.
Okay.
Was your erection rising
during this flight?
How does that happen?
Okay.
For you.
All right.
So just to get there, it's like 18 hours.
You go Iowa to Texas, Texas to,
you got to go to like the southern most point,
the capital of Argentina.
I don't remember what it's called.
San San Andreas.
No, it's not San Andreas.
I don't remember.
I can't remember.
But then she lived in Salta.
So I had to actually fly down to the southern tip of Argentina
and then take a transfer flight going back up north.
So it was way out of the way, super long flight.
Where it went bad was the flight home.
Because when you're in these foreign airports,
like most of the signs are in Spanish.
Oh no, I should tell you, I guess,
if I'm going to weave a whole yarn here,
going through customs on my way into Argentina
was an absolute nightmare.
Because when you're a foreigner.
On your way into Argentina.
Yeah, yeah.
Because you have to show them your passport
and then like some little dude in like a glass booth
interviews every single person.
So you're waiting in line for like three years
to get through all these interviews
and stuff of all the foreigners coming in.
But the motherfucker, and I guess this is my fault,
the guy who had to interview me to enter the country,
only spoke Spanish and I only speak English.
So you can imagine how that interview went.
It was about 20 minutes of him getting very frustrated with me
that I don't even know like the most common things in Spanish.
It took a few years, but obviously not enough.
And here's a hint for anybody who wants to become a terrorist.
No dude, I'm on the fucking PCP right now.
You can't have your microphone.
You presumptuous bastard.
Here's a hint for anybody who wants to become a terrorist
in a foreign country.
Just don't learn their language because the customs guy
will get so mad that you can't talk to him
that he'll just shrug his shoulders
and let you go on through anyway.
So that's my advice.
Good. Good.
Anyway, so the nightmare is coming back home
because the fear is one of my flights will get cancelled or something
and then I'm trapped in a foreign country
and I don't know who to talk to to get my new flight and all that shit.
Luckily, nothing got cancelled until I got to Texas
and then my flight home to Iowa got fucked and cancelled.
And as I said before, I cannot sleep while I'm in the middle of traveling.
So I'm just sitting at this airport already 18 hours into traveling
just losing my fucking mind.
There is, I'm telling you, airports are fucked.
They're so fucked because if your flight gets cancelled,
it's game over.
You're done.
There's no really place to sleep.
Like they should have like little sleep chamber pods
that you can go like rent and sleep in
and they'll wake you up when your flight's ready.
But they don't have shit.
You're pretty much stuck in a divorce thing
where either you go get a hotel room
and they don't offer me a free thing.
Like I'd have to go pay for a hotel room
and then risk missing the flight again
or sleep on the fucking chair.
Hope that nobody steals your bags.
Get fucked, you fucking faggot.
And the long story short is I eventually get home
after being awake for 30 hours
and it was the most miserable, tired,
terrible experience of my life.
So typically I think traveling's okay,
but that one instance was just fucked.
Gay.
That's shit time, dude.
I've, yeah, I've had a bunch of flights like that.
Like now that I'm older and shit
and I live like farther away from where I grew up,
I've been flying a lot pretty regularly
and like American Airlines is the worst,
I think that I found.
They, yeah, like I think on two separate occasions,
I learned after the second time not to fly with them,
like one time my flight just got kept getting delayed
and kept getting fucking delayed
and then just got pushed back to the next day.
So I think on that day, like since I had my car,
since I'm a fucking adult,
I just drove back home and then drove in the next day.
But the other time, I don't know,
like I didn't want to for whatever reason,
like the flight was really early in the morning the next day.
So, you know, I was lucky enough
that they did offer me a hotel voucher.
So I just fucking, you know,
got in the shuttle with a bunch of people
who also got fucked over,
stayed at a hotel for a night,
got in my flight the next morning and got gone.
But the fact that they have so much like
ability to just screw over people,
the ability of an airline to fuck people over is so vast
that it seems like they are disproportionately unaccountable
for the damage that they do every single day
by just being incompetent at their fucking jobs.
And they do it to hundreds of people at a time
and then when confronted with like how they're ruining
so many people's not only day,
probably a week and maybe even life
by shortening it with all the stress.
They have the attitude of shrugger,
fuck off, I don't care.
Fuck you, it's my job, fuck you.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
I wish I had a solution.
Maybe there's something we can talk about.
Ways to improve or completely destroy the system
and don't even give people the illusion
that travel is something that you want to do.
Just say no, just stay where you are.
We're abolishing flights.
You just live where you live and that's it.
We gotta wait for the teleporters.
That's what I'm saying, Doug.
It's travel.
I would be, travel is so shit.
That's really the point at the end of this.
Travel is so garbage that I want to basically not exist
by just having teleporters like they do in fucking Star Trek
and just be anywhere you want immediately.
Travel is retarded.
There's nothing good about it.
I hate it.
You know, honestly, I don't mind travel.
I mind the cost of travel.
That's the main reason I don't do it
is because I'm a cheapskate
and the thought of like spending hundreds of dollars
just to go do something is just too,
it's too much for my brain to handle,
even if I can afford it.
For every calculation like that,
you gotta think like, okay,
I'm gonna go fly, I don't know, to this place
and fuck this slut.
That's the plan, okay.
Now, how much am I willing to invest
in this operation here?
Like, am I gonna spend like $1,000?
You know, I mean, that's fine in some cases,
but to do it regularly,
to make it a part of your life,
it's prohibitively expensive.
Well, even like, we all agreed
that on the losing of virginity video,
that for the first time, you spare no expense.
That's right, no price is too much to pay.
Yeah, but then after that,
you're like, well, now I understand what sex is,
I understand that it's not that big a deal.
Am I even willing to spend $100 on this?
Well, don't forget, Digi,
your virginity regrows as you go on without having sex though.
We gotta keep that in mind, yep.
But like, sex is not withstanding,
just going anywhere to do anything.
Like, for instance, the dick show
is going to start doing these live shows.
Road rage.
Yeah, his road rage.
And he's going to do a show in LA
and a show in Philadelphia.
Those are the two that are planned.
Whether or not it continues from there,
we have no idea.
There's no further plans beyond that.
So he's going to do a show in Philadelphia.
Now, I'm looking at it like,
Philadelphia is not that far from me, right?
Like, it would either be a short,
inexpensive flight,
or a eight hour drive,
seven or eight hour drive.
So, and I have,
I think I probably have friends in Philadelphia,
I can't remember if Jeff Burgess lives in Philadelphia
or Pittsburgh,
but if he lives in Philly,
maybe I'll do it.
But like, so he's doing this,
this taxationist theft show in Philadelphia.
And I have to look at it and go,
all right, well,
first of all,
we've got the travel time,
which is, you know,
eight hours there,
eight hours back.
If I go, like,
if I go there and I don't want a hotel,
that means I'm just going to,
like, drive all day for a,
probably two hour show, you know?
Or I stay the night
and then waste the whole next day as well.
That's two days of just driving,
just to see this one thing.
And like,
and then I'm thinking about what the,
if I take a car,
that's probably going to be $100 of gas.
If I take a flight,
it's a, you know,
what if I have to get a hotel,
$100 on a hotel,
however much it costs,
you know, depending on where you are.
In New York,
like, New York trips
are almost prohibitively expensive
just because of, like, lodging.
Like, it's so expensive
to get a hotel in New York.
It's like, you know,
like over $100 a night that it's like,
A lot of people do day trips to New York, I think.
Yeah.
Like, I have here in Virginia Beach,
we have something called the Chinatown Bus,
which is just a bus that goes straight
to Chinatown, New York,
no stops.
And it's like 50 bucks.
So getting to New York,
very cheap, very easy.
It's like 10 hour, 10, 12 hour drive,
you know, whatever.
It's a waste of time,
but yeah, it's a cheap, easy trip.
But staying in New York,
that's where you're gonna suddenly rack up
hundreds of dollars
just to fucking be in a place.
You know, not even to do things there.
Let's not even talk about the fact
that if you wanna actually do things there,
now you're gonna be spending all this,
and if you go to some other town,
you're not gonna go eat fast food.
That's not why you came, you know.
You're gonna go some cool place
that's gonna cost more dozens,
if not hundreds of dollars to do all the stuff.
So like the total travel cost
just racks up and racks up.
And it's like, you know,
you really gotta be willing to just part
with what you have
in the name of good times.
That's true, that's very true.
And not to mention like you were saying,
to know kind of like what's,
when you're going to a new place,
you don't necessarily know
if it's a fun place to spend time,
or just like what to do
to have a good time while you're there.
So you pretty much need to have somebody
on the other end who's willing to donate
their time, like a friend or whatever,
that's gonna like, or research it extensively.
But even then, you never know what you're gonna find.
So you also have to like know
that it's gonna be a good time ahead of time.
And like I also had like a trip
that I was thinking of doing,
and also didn't,
cause like it's probably not worth it ultimately.
But like Tim and Eric,
I've just announced they're doing
a 10 year anniversary tour
for the 10 year anniversary of Tim and Eric,
awesome show, great job.
And I would love to go to,
cause Tim and Eric are two of my favorite people
in the fucking world,
and awesome show was like one of my favorite shows ever.
But they're not coming,
they're coming to Chicago,
but that's like four hours away from here.
And I'm not gonna do that.
I would love to go,
and my hope would have been to have gone,
to that show in Seattle, I think,
with my buddy John,
who also is just a huge super fan.
And we fucking fell in love with that shit together.
It would be a wonderful experience
to hang out with him and my other friends out in Seattle,
but I'm not gonna fucking pay $400 to go out
for a one fucking time show for two hours,
and then just come back.
And like, I guess I could like bundle it into like,
oh, let's also hang out with the guys,
but I got shit to do.
I don't have time to fucking hang out
with my friends all the time.
I got work to that needs to get done.
That's why I need to teleport.
If I could just fucking teleport there
and do my shit,
it'd be the best.
You know, I have this beautiful vision
of like constantly traveling
and doing things with people and stuff.
And then what you always realize only afterwards
is that like, you just suddenly look at the calendar
and realize that days are gone,
and whatever you haven't done yet
is now a pressing matter.
Like for instance,
Monkey came to my house about a week ago
as part of this travel that he was doing,
who stayed the night,
and we recorded a shitload of Let's Plays.
And you may have noticed
that none of them have come out yet.
And that's because-
I have come to expect this of you, did you?
Well, it doesn't help-
I'm expecting you to see them probably in May.
Well, we recorded a ton of them,
and you don't even realize, Monkey,
that after you left,
me and Ben and DeVu made five more Let's Plays.
Just that night.
Like, we kept going to like seven in the morning or something.
Shit.
So yeah, I've got a whole desktop
full of fucking Let's Plays.
And the reason that I didn't get around to editing them
is that, like, leading up to Monkey coming over,
I was, like, anticipating.
I'm like, yeah, I'm going to hang out with Monkey.
This is the most fun thing I'm going to do this month, probably.
Monkey comes over-
Probably this year.
We recorded all these Let's Plays.
It sucked.
It was garbage.
No, we did a bunch of stuff for two days,
and then he leaves,
and then I'm like, oh, God,
it's now March 20th or so.
I have to make two more videos
before this month is over,
and start planning for what I'm going to do in April.
So the second Monkey's gone,
it's like, well, now we just got to work constantly.
You know, and I don't have time to just sit around
and edit all these Let's Plays,
because I'm going to be, like, just outputting.
You know, all I've been doing is, like,
making shit nonstop for the main channel since he left.
So that's what happens every time I travel.
It's like, I go, I have fun for four or five days,
and I come back, and I realize that a huge chunk of the month
is just gone, and now, like, you know, it's grind time.
Let me tell you one more thing real quick.
It's just, it's my vision for the future.
Well, it's whatever.
So in Star Trek, there's this wonderful thing that's painted.
I know, I'm becoming like Mike,
and I love it so much.
So in Star Trek, Deep Space Nine,
there is a couple scenes where Commander Sisko's son,
I think, is, like, visiting the academy
or something, or something's going on,
or like, oh, no, what is this?
Sisko is, like, he's back on Earth
for some assignment, doesn't matter.
But the point is, like, he, his family lives in Louisiana,
in New Orleans, and he loves that place,
but Starfleet headquarters is in San Francisco, California.
So, like, what his day is like is that he gets up,
has breakfast in his house, gets in a fucking teleporter,
gets phased over to San Francisco, has his day there,
and then just is instantly, at the end of the day,
he just fucking teleports back to Louisiana,
has dinner with his family, is fucking great time.
And it's just, and they just, like, they just talk about,
like, oh, hey, you know, I was, yeah, I was just in San Francisco.
10 seconds later, I'm here in fucking New Orleans.
It's the greatest thing in the world.
It's just, it's just like how cars enabled us
to travel a little bit.
Teleporters enable you to travel
a thousand billion million miles in a second,
and it just becomes part of life.
And I can't even think about all the ways
it would make life better and different and interesting.
Oh, it's, oh, it's, it's, it brings a tear to my eye.
It's so beautiful.
It's, I want that so badly.
It'd be pretty fucking sweet.
Too bad we live in the real world,
where we have to pay taxes and, and jerk ourselves off.
Oh shit, thanks for reminding me.
I still haven't fucking submitted my taxes yet.
Oh, God, I need to do that too.
That's in like a month, that's due.
Yep, I need to submit my shit to my tax people.
Oh, no.
Oh, tax cast.
Ben, have you, have you paid your taxes, Ben?
What's going on with your taxes?
Have I?
Yeah, yeah.
Have you filed?
Why would you think I made my taxes?
I mean, don't you have to file?
If you're-
What, have you?
You fuck?
Well, no, but I'm aware that I need you.
Judgy McJudgerson?
I'm not, I'm just saying.
I have plans to do so with, with, uh, like a tax lady.
With, on sunny, you know, does our taxes talk?
I have, yeah, I have ten, I'm gonna figure it out.
I know how I'm gonna figure it out.
I know I'll do it soon, someday.
Someday I'll pay taxes.
Yeah, I always end up doing it.
Ben, what's your craziest travel story?
Uh, my-
I know you're a big hitchhiker.
So, so are we exclusive-
Oh yeah, fucking hitchhiked that one time.
Hold on, before we continue here,
are we exclusively talking about the act of travel?
Is that-
I don't think it's anything about traveling.
Well, because Monkey's story was literally only about the flights that he took,
and nothing about Argentina whatsoever.
Well, that's not interesting.
It's the vastly more interesting subject,
but if we're gonna focus on just the travel, that's fine.
You can do whatever you want.
I, uh, when I was, I fucking,
when I fucking moved to California,
and was an astro camp fucking instructor for a while,
and I lived in the mountains,
and then I fucking lost that job,
and then I fucking hitchhiked to the fucking, to my aunt's house,
and then I fucking, I don't know,
go watch my fucking Nuzlocke of the Black one.
You know, I told that story.
That was fun.
I got fucking pulled over by the police.
The police, they tried to arrest me.
They tried to arrest me for hitchhiking,
and I came up with a story.
They were like,
you can't be here on the fucking highway.
And I said,
oh, my, uh, my girlfriend,
we had a fight and she kicked me out of the car,
and they took pity,
and they took pity on me,
and they said, oh, buddy,
oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry that happened.
How did that story not fall apart the moment that they looked at your face?
Well, good question.
I can't answer it.
The cops were gay, obviously.
Oh, yeah.
They wanted to piece that shit, yeah.
And they, uh,
oh, yeah, and they put me on the fucking on-ramp.
They were like, okay, technically,
you're not allowed to be on the freeway,
but you're technically allowed to stand on this on-ramp
and hitchhike.
Good luck, buddy.
And I said, thanks, law man.
And I winked at them gaily.
And there's more to this.
Pull out my crack.
There's more to that story.
Ben does have a very famously effective wink.
Do I?
Is that true?
Yeah.
Sure.
Wow.
Yeah, that's true.
And the part of the story I've never understood
is why you decided to hitchhike across the country
when you could have just flown home.
Flo-
First of all, I wasn't going home.
Second of all, flying is expensive.
Third of all, I just felt like hitchhiking.
The fucking, my job at AstroCab ended,
and I didn't, and I hadn't bought a ticket.
I hadn't bought a plane ticket or a train ticket or anything,
to my aunt's house.
And I was like, well, it's only like three states away.
And I, and they dropped me off at the airport.
And I was like, well, I didn't actually buy a ticket.
I didn't tell them this.
I didn't tell them that I didn't buy it.
I just had dropped me off at the airport.
And I got off at the airport, and I looked up at the sun.
And I said, judging by the position of the sun,
I think east is this way.
And I just started walking in that direction.
What year was this, and did you have a phone?
Yeah, I had a phone.
But I wanted to hitchhike.
And this was like 2012, 2011.
Your alternative lifestyle disgusts me.
I'm just sick of it.
Me too.
You are a parasite on this great land of America.
Oh man.
But then when I got to Aunt Steph's house,
I was there for a little while.
And then I went back to Northern California
to live with one of my AstroCamp friends.
And that was one of the best days of my life,
because I had like a 22-hour train ride.
And it was so relaxing.
And I played Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup for like 22 hours
on a fucking train ride to fucking California
to live with a bunch of cool faggots
that let me stay in their house for free
for what was supposed to be a few weeks,
but ended up being like six months
before they were finally like,
Ben, you need to start paying rent.
And I said, OK, I understand.
And then I paid like two months of rent.
And then I ran out of money and was like,
well, I can't pay rent anymore.
And they said, well, get out.
And I said, yep, I'll go home now.
And they did.
That seems pretty...
Yeah, it seems like a pretty legitimate transaction there.
Yeah, yeah.
It was legit.
I didn't screw anyone over.
I'm a good boy.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And then I went to Poland.
And then I went to Poland to teach physics.
And then that was a plane ride, but whatever.
And then for Christmas that year, for Christmas that year...
Ben, how did you go from world traveling teacher
to eating Digi's leftovers every day?
I will tell you the story of how that happened.
Not even exaggerating their name.
I went to Poland.
And I taught physics.
And my students hated me.
And they gave me bad reviews.
And they said, get out.
Yeah, you like that?
You like that, monkey?
Oh, man.
And they said...
It's just like your PCP lecture.
All the students hated you.
Yeah, it's right.
That's true.
And they fucking down...
I see the Polish...
They downloaded you as a person.
The job had given me this fucking swanky high-rise apartment in the center of town.
And I was like, well, I'm too...
They were like, we're not going to pay for your apartment anymore.
And I was like, landlord, please, give me a different room.
And they were like, okay, we'll move you right downstairs
into this fucking dingy-ass fucking hole in the fucking wall,
where you'll technically be sharing it with like a 90-year-old woman
who's just living there waiting to die.
And there's no running water.
And there's no fucking kitchen.
All you have is a hot plate.
And there's no bed.
And the heater is just a big stone pillar in the center of the room
that fucking gets hot sometimes.
Fuck yeah.
So watch out for that.
You're in the lap of luxury over there.
Oh, it was a good time.
Where's my stone pillar gone, Dan?
And I was like, well...
They'll give you a woman to have sex with.
That's right.
And then for Christmas, for Christmas,
I had heard that Christmas in Tartu Estonia was the best party.
And I went to Tartu Estonia for, no, for New Year's.
And it was wonderful.
And then I fucking was like, well, I'll take all the money
that I save working in physics.
And I fucking took a fucking train and bus
and fucking walking trip for like three months.
And I went across fucking Germany and France and England to Ireland.
And then I was in Ireland for fucking, what's the word, St. Patrick's Day.
And I was doing that for like three months and it took forever.
And you know what?
You know what?
I got really bored of it after a while.
After a while, I was just like, you know what?
The world kind of sucks and everything is pretty much the same as everything else.
And it's like that old saw.
It's like that old saying, wherever you go, there you are.
It's like, it's all the fucking same.
It's just whatever.
You just, you meet new people, but they're the same as the old people.
Fuck it.
And I was like, and I was like, when I go home,
when I go home to America, once I run out of money, which I just did,
I'm gonna, I'm gonna say fuck it.
I don't want to go anywhere anymore.
I'm gonna fucking sit in my room.
And the only fucking thing I care about is like my fucking mind.
I'm just going to cultivate my mind instead.
Fuck the outside world.
I'm only going to look inside for the rest of my miserable life.
And that's what I did.
And I learned how to draw and I fucking got good.
And I became the greatest hero of a generation.
And that's my story.
And that's how I ended up eating leftovers out of Digi's garbage for months.
He cultivated his mind so hard, he had no choice,
but to eat those leftovers out of Digi's garbage.
That's right.
I cultivated my mind so hard that I didn't even want it.
That's what I call a highly trained mind.
Yeah.
Ben, I just want to ask, there are probably a lot of
impressional young minds in the audience who aspire to be an artist.
To eating garbage as well.
To go insane.
Yeah, that's right.
My question is, would you recommend this lifestyle or would you say pursue the teaching
instead of- I frankly don't understand why everyone doesn't live exactly the way I have.
I think people long for a little more stability than you have.
It confuses and disgusts me.
Everyone is not just like me.
To have a life with no future or prospects or like money,
it's kind of scary for most people.
Not me though.
Boy, boy.
Aren't you currently financially unsustainable in the very long term though?
Um, in the very long term?
Yeah.
But like, I'm okay for now.
I'm okay for now.
Patreon.com.
Like for today.
Save him.
Yeah, save him.
Hashtag save him.
Yeah.
Yes, exactly.
Your definition of being okay for now is if Digi ordered a pizza last night.
That would save the day.
Oh, shit.
Or Victor.
Victor gives me fucking crazy leftovers.
Victor's always buying food, chaining his mind, losing his appetite,
and being like, Ben, you want this?
And that's like half of what I eat.
You know, Ben, I noticed when we were at their house,
like when we were growing up, nobody ever left leftovers.
Like they were consumed immediately.
But the Collins family ain't quite like that.
No.
And none of us eat around leftovers.
So anything that gets left over is just passed to somebody else.
It's bizarre.
Like for me and Ben, that's just an opportunity.
I never leave anything uneaten, like never, ever.
I just, if I, you know, if I get something and then realize halfway through that I don't
like it anymore, then it's gone.
Well, I mean, maybe it's just because we were like, we didn't have as many options as kids.
Like we were just fucking eight or whatever.
I mean, it's just that my dad has always been like,
very like anti leftovers just because he's like a germaphobe.
So I just don't think there was a culture of leftovers in the house if you get what I'm saying.
I see.
We're all picky eaters, really picky eaters, everybody.
I want to hear the story of how did you went to the Philippines to have gay six?
Yeah.
We've all been wondering.
So I'll tell you the travel story of going to the Philippines,
which is, I guess, interesting in its own right.
Oh, yeah.
So I should wait.
I want to mention about my story that I fucking snuck on trains.
I snuck on trains.
Oh, sweet.
I didn't pay for tickets all the time.
Like the homeless man, like you jumped onto a moving train into a little box car.
No, like a can of beans and you have a beer and shit.
And a bindle.
No, like I would get on a train with no ticket and I would just be like, well,
this train ride is an hour and I would just go sit in the bathroom on the train for an hour
and no one would check my ticket or Ben or I would sit down on a seat.
Wait till I saw the conductor coming to check tickets and then go to the bathroom.
Wait until they pass through the car and then go sit down again.
And I took tons of train rides for free that way.
Ben, do you want to, as soon as this podcast is over,
go out and buy a can of beans and eat them with me?
Why?
Like a homeless man could be longer and lighter.
I have a sudden desire for beans because of what I'm talking about.
I'll just picture it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Does this mean, does this mean that I get half a free can of beans?
Hell yeah.
My monthly tugboat has come in.
It's a date, Digi.
It's a fucking date.
I'm just picturing the guy on the train with the can of beans,
but the lid is still on and they're mostly open.
I'm like, yeah, yeah.
Who doesn't have a can opener so he uses a fucking rusty old knife he found?
Yeah.
It's a good look.
But are you guys aware, just while we're on the topic,
that I eat a can of dark red kidney beans out of a can for lunch every single day of my life?
Oh my God.
That's what I do.
Fucking yuck, dude.
Every single day.
Why?
Yeah, why?
Because it's high in protein, high in fiber.
Wait, wait, high in fiber.
Wait, fuck.
How's the song go?
High in fiber.
Low in fat.
Hey, I bet you didn't know that when I eat beans.
I sit in my own little cloud.
Nobody comes to visit me in my little cloud.
I don't know why.
Maybe because I'm cut muffins.
Cut muffins.
Yep, that's a brag.
I do literally eat these beans though every single day.
Kibbe beans are good for you.
I prefer beans, beans, musical fruit, morey, morey too, morey too, belly fills,
eat two beans with every meal.
That's the normie one.
The brag show is better.
The normie one.
That's the normie's beans song.
It's a slightly, the specific version I'm doing is from Skull Monkeys.
You should all look up Skull Monkeys Beansong.
Oh, fucking Skull Monkeys.
Fucking Skull Monkeys.
Speaking of let's plays that haven't come out yet,
three hour Skull Monkeys let's play somewhere on Jesse's hard drive.
Oh god, where is it?
I want that.
Why isn't it out yet?
He's a bad person.
Who was telling the story?
Someone was guessing.
He was going to talk about going to a hotel and in a hand basket.
So I was 19 and I dropped out of college and wasn't doing anything with my life.
And my dad was like, we got to get this.
My dad essentially thought that maybe if I went and saw something new,
something that's not the house, you know, for a change,
maybe it would inspire me to like want to work or be a human being.
Clearly it didn't work.
So he knew that I had, yeah, it did not work at all.
Legit, it did not work in the way that it was supposed to.
But he knew that I had a friend in the Philippines, Ghost Lightning,
who's in his 30s and has a family and shit.
And he was like, that guy seems like he's got his shit together.
Why don't you go visit your friend in the Philippines?
And I was like, fucking, are you serious right now?
Dude, that's a half the planet away.
I've never really traveled anywhere before on my own.
I've never even gone to like a neighboring city without a person with me.
I'll tell you, one of the biggest reasons I don't travel is I hate going anywhere alone.
You can ask my friends, you can ask Ben and DeVue and Victor.
Those are the people who count at this point.
Like, when I want to go even just out of the house to get food,
I will always try to bring somebody with me.
I'm always like, hey, you want to go to Wendy's?
You want to go here?
You want to just be out with me?
Because so I'm not alone, you know?
I've gotten a lot more.
When did he comes out?
He needs someone to come out with.
Yeah, I've gotten a lot more used to.
Message received.
I've gotten a lot more used to going alone just because
now that I have money and nobody else does,
I want to go out a lot more than anyone else does.
So I've gotten used to going alone.
And that's why I'm going to travel now.
I'm willing to do it finally.
But at the time, I had never been anywhere by myself.
So I was like, this is the scariest prospect I've ever heard.
I'm going to a essentially third world country.
Like, they have, you know, they're not third world in the way that you might imagine,
but it's definitely not a first world nation.
Do you hear about their prime minister who like promotes vigilanteism
and like wants to personally beat up gangsters?
You mean their current leader who is murdering people in the streets
for accusations of drugs?
Like, right.
Just accusations.
Yeah.
Well, a man who he's got such a crackdown on he's got a massive,
like if you do anything involving drugs, you die.
And he's using this as a political power.
Like he can accuse his opponents of being drug, you know, drug cartels.
I bet his favorite video game is crack down.
Yeah.
Crack down.
The country is currently at, yeah, it's got a really corrupt.
That guy has compared himself to Hitler.
In a daring subversion of the typical trope.
Yeah.
He's compared himself to Hitler.
It's incredible.
Wow.
He's my hero.
Okay.
Moving on.
So he wasn't in power at this time.
So this is 2011.
And yeah.
So my dad's like, why don't you go see a friend of the Philippines?
And I was like, well, sure.
So I asked Ghost Lightning and he's like, well, that sounds cool as fuck.
So the plan is I'm going to go there for a whole month.
I'm going to live at Ghost Lightning's house
because the cost of living in the Philippines is dirt cheap compared to like, you know,
like American dollars will carry you obscenely far over there.
So the plan was that my dad was like the most expensive parts to fly.
It's like $1,000 just to fly there.
Right.
So my dad was like, all right, I'm going to give you, you know, the $1,000 to the flight,
$300 to give to Ghost Lightning as like a rent fair, you know, like to stay there for a whole month.
And then.
I love the rent fair.
Yeah.
He gave me, my dad had given me like, like $1,000 of you can spend this.
And then $1,000 of this is just in case, you know, in case anything is wrong.
So I was trying not to break into that thousand at all.
But the other thousand, the first thousand, you can spend this thousand.
I took, you can spend this to mean I will spend all of this.
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah.
So, um, so yeah, I took off to the Philippines and it was, it was, uh, look, I used to be,
I mean, if you think I'm awkward and, uh, and, and weird now, I used to be exceedingly
socially awkward to the point that I made very stupid decisions based on it.
So for instance, Ghost Lightning had given me his phone number online.
I foolishly had not attempted to call that number to make sure I had it correctly.
I never, because I just thought like, oh, I don't want to bother him.
You know, like, I don't know what time of day he's awake.
And basically I'm afraid of phones, you know, I would just never, I was like terrified of
calling anybody and having to talk on the phone.
So I remember to this day, people always ask me to make phone calls.
Yeah.
When there's a phone call to be made.
Exactly.
So, so yeah, I just, I was like, oh God, I don't want to have the call.
But then so, all right.
So I get on a plane, uh, I think I flew to probably like Detroit or something.
So one of those flights, one of those, uh, cities that you always had the layovers from.
And then from there, I flew to Japan, which was like a 14, 15, maybe more hour flight.
As long as the total trip, this was crazy because the total time that I was in the air was, uh,
like, yeah, I think it was that I was in the air for 14 hours.
But then because it's 10 hours ahead of us in the Philippines,
it had been like exactly 24 hours from the time I left that I arrived.
So like I traveled into the future.
But, um, but in any case, so I took this, this longest flight to Japan.
And then I was in Japan for like an hour.
I've been there.
I can say that I was in a moment, a brief moment in the Holy land before going straight down to hell.
I gotta tell you, man, like, I think this, this could be,
this could surely be my, uh, my Baka Gaijin, uh, talking here.
But like people always say that when you go to Japan, like people who go there,
like it's never what they expect.
Like, uh, oh, the, the, uh, you know, the women aren't as beautiful as anime characters.
And, and it's not like how you're thinking and stuff like that.
Yeah. Well, maybe because I've watched a lot of Japanese TV and travel blogs and stuff,
but man, in the short time I was there, it was exactly what I thought Japan is like.
I was like, yeah, this is a thorough understanding of the Japanese culture from inside the airport
for one hour.
Yeah. I mean, every, all the ways that things are laid out, the ways that their PA system
works, extremely organized, um, you know, constant updates on what is happening meticulously
everywhere in the airport, you know, tons and tons of signs, informing you of everything.
Also, all of the flight attendants, like everyone who, who's like, uh, you know,
telling people, like calling out names to get on the plane, stuff like that,
all beautiful women, all of them.
You know, I, I noticed a, uh, when I flew to Japan, there was a very,
they were all very nice and very well put together.
Yeah.
Just distinctly, definitely several notches above the other flights I've taken in like domestic
cruise and shit.
Like you go, I go to the airport, I expect the person calling me up to be like some,
you know, 10 out of 10 anime babe, you know, some, some, you know, fat, fat old black lady
or something, uh, is that my go-to for unappealing person?
Sure.
We got, we got a real John Tron over here.
And then I go to Japan and it's all like, you know, like very, very well dressed,
hair perfectly parted in a ponytail, um, like all, they all look identical.
And I don't mean that in the all Asians look the same way.
I mean, they were all dressed and had their hair in the same style.
And like, it was just all like late 20, early 30s, Japanese women with the same hairstyle.
And they were all beautiful.
So yeah, that's, that's Japan in my mind now.
Ladies, you heard it here from Digi Bro.
You're all beautiful.
Yeah.
Scarcely beautiful.
You know, I'm just, I'm just saying that, uh, it is not a difficult job to be a flight attendant.
I'm sure it's got its own challenges, but like the most important thing is that you
look good and consistent with the airline's way it wants to present itself.
So, uh, put some effort into that guys.
Hey Nate, didn't you like go to Japan, like travel there?
I sure did.
Spent two, three months there.
You're not on Nate's stories yet.
Yeah, we can talk about that later.
There's not.
Why are you trying to co-op?
Why are you trying to cut into my story to hear Nate's?
I thought you were done.
I'm only in Japan at this point.
You've only gone to Japan.
Well, he hasn't reached hell yet.
Yeah.
So then it's like a, it's like a hour or two flight from Japan to the Philippines, pretty short.
And so I get there and yeah, hell, good way to describe the airport in the fucking Philippines,
because yeah, just like what monkey said about customs, it's basically a fucking long ass line
to get up to a guy in a glass window, uh, with a very curt attitude who interviews you.
And the guy, like I'm telling him, you know, I'm going to be here for a month.
And he's like, well, like how can you be here for a month if you're like, like,
if you're not going to have, if you're not going to be working, essentially.
Like he was, he was basically trying to badger me about like he thinks, I don't know,
maybe he thinks I'm here to do something illegal.
But he's like,
Is that beard, man?
Is that beard terrorist written all over it?
So for whatever reason, he gives me, he's like, I'll mark you for three weeks
and you can come back and have you stay extended.
And I'm like, uh, okay.
You know, like I can't, I'm trying to argue with this guy, but it's, he's, he's just
being a total asshole, right?
So yeah, I get through him, get into customs, get, uh, thank God, I don't even bother.
Whenever I travel, I only, only carry on.
No, not carry on luggage.
I can, I'm a master of packing things, you know, uh, all that butt sex and mostly 18
times moving the house.
I know how to pack shit tight.
So, uh, so yeah, I've got, I've got all my shit.
And I, um, I get off the plane and I go out, I go out, you know, it's
monkey, you'll appreciate this.
I don't think anybody else will.
But in the proto men's song, uh, bring us the rope.
That moment where you hear the, the, the doors open of the, uh, of the courthouse
and it's like,
you just hear like an army of people outside chanting and they're all, that's what it felt
like walking out of the airport.
There's just an endless ocean of humanity.
It's just people everywhere.
And like, so the idea is, you know, like any other airport, there's just like a
couple of lanes of cars that are coming in to pick people up, but it's like almost
all cabs and there's like hundreds of them and it just goes on and on.
And there's just endless sea of people.
And I, of course, I'm, I mean, I'm already late.
Like I'm supposed to have been there like 30 minutes ago.
Ghost lightning has, I don't know this yet, but he has a cab waiting for us.
And they're, you know, they're going to be charging a lot.
Like I don't know what he paid for that cab, but I know it was probably a, like a
deafening amount of money.
You know, I'm going to kind of put that on him because planes are unreliable.
And like if there's so many cabs, you should be able to just get one.
Well, I mean, I'm already like 20, 30 minutes late, but now I'm about to be
another 40 minutes late because I'm trying to call this guy.
And of course I have his number wrong and I'm trying to find him in an endless sea
of people.
And neither of us knows where the other is supposed to be.
He can't even really know if I've landed yet because I have had no real way of
contacting him this whole time I've been traveling.
You know, I've, I'm on like, I think I'm on like an old flip phone.
No, my dad let me bring an iPhone one.
I didn't have my own cell phone at the time.
So I brought like my mom's old phone or something like that.
So I'm trying to like, you know, figure out what to do with this number.
And I can't get like Wi-Fi reception or anything.
So I'm like freaking out.
I'm like, what the fuck do I do?
You know, I'm wandering around for like 40 minutes.
Finally, it occurs to me to try to send an email to him.
So I am able to get just the faintest connection like a, it loads for like a
straight minute to get into, you know, anything.
And I send him an email that's just like, you know, I'm here, but I have your number
wrong or something like that.
And he says to me like, he sends me one that's like gate 13.
I'm wearing a Mazinger t-shirt.
And so eventually I did find him.
And yeah, it was a nightmare.
So, and then he was hoping you were going to say that like the only way that you
ended up able to communicate with him was you had to really quick do an anime
analysis and post it to your blog to convey the information of where you currently were.
And he had to like decode it.
Like the first letter of each word said what gate he was at.
I'm pretty sure Twitter existed at the time.
But so, so, yeah.
So, and then the other thing is like in the Philippines, and I suspect this is
true of, I mean, this is true of some places in America, but it's definitely true of
other countries.
There's just constant people hustling everywhere.
So one of the things that down there is that they'll have guys who just like at
that area who are just constantly offering to take your bags.
Like they'll like they'll carry it to the car for you.
You know, like, oh, let me, let me, let me.
And so I, of course, I let some guy and we carry him out to the car and then go
slightly.
He's like, you got to tip that guy.
You know, I'm like, of course I do.
Like I didn't even think about it.
Like I just think in these guys work for the airport.
And it's like, no, these guys are, they're doing this for tips.
You know, so I tip him probably something too much because I didn't have my bills
broken down far enough.
That's when you turn to him and say, here's the tip.
Get a real job hippie.
They pull out their knife and I think I probably had to pay him an American
dollars because I hadn't converted my money yet to there.
So I don't know what it was worth to him.
It might have been worth nothing.
You know, so, uh, so I stayed in the Philippines for a month.
It was a good time.
Um, so the travel back as Bumky said, also gigantic pain in the ass.
So of course you remember that guy who gave me the three weeks and said, come back.
You know, I didn't come back.
You know, I just come back to do that.
So, so, uh, go sighting drops me off at the airport.
It's like six in the morning.
Where does that guy even get off?
What is he like?
Why do these fucking people at the customs want to fuck with you so bad?
I don't know.
Do they think that we're actually terrorists?
Like you were joking.
Well, all right, what is their mindset?
What's the difference between three weeks and a month?
You know, I don't know what that kind of nitpick.
I do not understand because it seems very insignificant.
Like you just want to fuck with you, but they are trying to like minimize threat
levels.
I mean, I really don't know what goes into constituting that.
But something like what I didn't understand about it is that like I had my return ticket.
It's not like I was, you know, getting a one-way trip and I was saying a month
and then I would just never go back.
I'm going to come leech off your fucking country.
Yeah, I have a fucking ticket.
You retard.
What do you want from me?
That's exactly the weird thing is you have the return to go home after three weeks.
I have no idea.
He just wanted me to come back to the airport all the way the fuck across town,
you know, and go through security again to go talk to him in a little glass booth at customs.
And may I remind you that and this is the biggest problem of my trip to the Philippines.
In the universe.
I had a good time there, but I did not do it right because as I'll remind you,
I had never been traveling before and I hated to go anywhere alone.
And no one there speaks English unless you're in like a rich area.
So like, you know, I think they speak in the Philippines.
Ghost Lightning would try to like this to Gallag is what it's called.
And he would try to teach me like basic enough to Gallag that I could like,
you know, figure out prices of things and take public transit because we mostly took public transit.
Though they had like a house driver, like a guy.
I think it was like, I think it was like his wife's uncle or something who like would just wife's boyfriend.
No, his wife's uncle who would just like drive like his,
they would just pay him to be around with a car to drive members of the family,
wherever they needed to go around town.
That's the cool thing about less than first world nations.
You got you got shit like that going on.
You just have lots of cool stuff.
It's pretty cool.
They had a bunch of house servants and stuff like that's pretty dope.
Like who but yeah, that was my favorite because what he would do is he would like,
like, you know, we'd be let's go to the mall and he just like drop us off in front of the mall
and then he'd go find parking, you know, and then he just kind of like hang out in the parking lot
until we were done and we'd like text him and he'd come and pick us up in front of the mall.
There's not enough focus put on the suffering we as Americans endure by not having personal
drivers. That's a big it's pretty cool.
I would love to have one.
But it's that's the thing to pay someone a livable wage in America wouldn't be worth it.
Thanks for that $15 minimum wage, Bernie motherfucker.
So, I mean, you could probably pay Ben in leftovers to drive you around.
It would be my honor, sir.
I don't know what Ben when Ben's job and never really brings him in contact with a dumpster,
you know, jump from him.
He's going to jump from that job pretty quick.
He can't be trusted.
I see I'll go and go where the money is in the dumpster.
I'm driving and he's catches a dumpster out of the fucking driver's
slams of the brakes and he's like, doggy, I got a I got a gold rush today.
So anyways, the homeless warrior.
Yeah.
So yeah, I didn't I did not go out much and like go sighting was always encouraging me like,
you know, when I'm not because, you know, he was working.
So he's like, when I'm not around, you should go out and go to the mall or go to go to the
fucking airport and get your shit figured out with three weeks.
They, you know, go somewhere.
I never went anywhere unless either him or his wife was with me.
You know, like I would exclusively go places with them except for one time that I walked
a couple miles to Jollibee and ate Jollibee Jollibee is the Philippines equivalent of
McDonald's.
I mean, they have McDonald's everywhere.
But basically McDonald's took too long to come to the Philippines.
So they made their own fast food chain.
I mean, KFC is huge there.
They KFC was like the first to go everywhere.
They they they they franchised around the world early, which is why the rest of the world
likes them and we don't give a fuck.
But Jollibee was one they made up themselves and like the Philippines has a very, very
interesting set of fast food regulars that they that they have their go-tos because they've
got burgers with with like white cheese and tons of mayonnaise, which just seems to be
an Asia thing in general.
Then they've got fried chicken and spaghetti.
And like spaghetti jets.
The Jollibee when you go to Jollibee, it's it's you got your bird.
You got like two kinds of burger like the small big burger.
Then you've got the like three to five drumstick fried chicken and then you've got spaghetti.
And then if you go to McDonald's, they also serve spaghetti.
So that's awesome.
Like everywhere there is like those are the three staples of fast food.
Burger, fried chicken, spaghetti.
So yeah, I walked to Jollibee one time.
Do they have fried chicken and McDonald's?
Um, I don't know if they have on the bone fried chicken there, but they have.
I mean, McDonald's has, you know, they had chicken fries and selection shit at the time.
Like a drum drum leg or whatever the fuck it's called.
I don't think they have those at McDonald's.
Drumstick, that's right.
But they did have spaghetti.
So anyway, I want to try McDonald's spaghetti.
That sounds amazing.
Yeah.
You know, when I moved out to Cincinnati, I just noticed like chili is the thing that
appeared in every restaurant and they're like gold star chili is like as big as I
don't know Dunkin Donuts out here.
Another thing to realize is that McDonald's is a little bit more upscale there because
they charge the same prices that they would in America, but that's vastly more there.
That's what it was like in Lublin too.
There was a McDonald's.
Same with Japan.
There was a McDonald's and it was the food was the same, but they charge the same as in
America and therefore it was pretty fucking expensive.
I thought it was real quick and they charge the same as it was in America and therefore
it was kind of like a relatively upscale restaurant.
It was like right in the center of the fucking city and it was a rather fascinating phenomenon.
The fact that America has a more economically strong position means that like by exporting
what's an equivalent price point outside of America, they all kind of get a nicer
version of that shit than we get relatively speaking.
That reminds me that in Latvia, when I stopped in Latvia on the way to Estonia,
I got off the train and I walked around and I ate some fucking gummy jelly shit that was in
some candy shop and that was great.
But I also went to a McDonald's and in this McDonald's in Riga, Latvia,
there was like a super nicely laid out thing with like this fancy fucking dessert tray,
this fancy dessert rack with all these like fancy cheesecakes in it and stuff.
And I went and I fucking, I ordered my burger and the manager fucking brought the burger out
to me and he was in like a nice smart like tie and he like sat the burger down in front of me
and like smoothed down the little napkin and was like, please enjoy your burger, sir.
Got it.
And I said, and I said, nothing, I didn't care.
And I said, your people are what's ruining my country.
I said, patreon.com.
They had some like two story McDonald's in the Philippines and just like these gigantic and
yeah, a little bit a little bit fancier, not like super fancy, but whereas pizza hut for
some reason, extremely fancy because also they charge the same prices here.
So the equivalent of like, if you just bought a pizza in the Philippines, you're basically
spending the equivalent of $25 on it.
So, you know, did you just jog by memory?
The McDonald's I went to in Argentina had like cheesecake and shit, like a bunch of random
fancy stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
The one in Latvia had the cheese.
So, so anyways, so, so for my travel backstory from the Philippines, I of course have not
adjusted this three weeks thing.
I've stayed a whole month and I have not done anything about it.
So ghost lightning drops me off at the airport.
It's like six a.m.
My flight is at like seven or so.
Oh, that's a bad move.
Well, yeah, I mean, I'm not I'm not it probably wasn't that close.
But like what matters is that it's early in the morning.
That's the detail you need to know.
So I go in and I'm like, you know, I'm at the flight desk and they're like, well,
you only had three weeks that you were allowed to be here.
So we're going to charge you like a fee, right?
Of like $80, which was a lot.
It's not that bad.
Right.
I'm sure it could have been worse.
But I was like mother because, you know, I've already spent in the time I'm in the Philippines.
I spend hundreds of dollars on anime bullshit.
Like a significant amount of all the figures and shit that you see in my videos are bought
in the Philippines because they're way cheaper there and they had way more variety because
not only do they have tons of bootlegs, but there's there's just tons of toy stores there.
Like if you go into a mall, there will be several stores that are just anime toy stores.
And even Toys R Us there has tons of anime shit because they're, you know,
they're close to Japan.
They have lots of anime on TV.
They've got Animax Asia and shit like that.
So, you know, I would walk into a Toys R Us and they got Gintama toys and for cheap.
So I'd buy them everywhere.
So I had my backpack was totally full of toys because again, I only do carry on.
And so I just took like everything I bought, I just took it out of the box and put it in
the backpack like individually and then and left all the boxes at Ghost Lightning's house.
I assume he threw them away.
I had said something about like getting him to ship them to me.
I don't know why I thought I would do that, but he probably threw them away a long time ago.
So, or immediately rather.
So yeah, I have all these anime toys and shit in my in my backpack.
And then I, yeah, I'm at the airport and they're like, you have to pay a fee.
So I'm like, fuck, I have to.
Okay.
I think this is why it was an issue is that I didn't have enough Filipino money left to pay this fee.
I only had like I had already run through all like because the way I was getting Filipino
money is I had all these these like conversion checks.
Like my dad had written me all these checks where basically you go to the bank.
Yeah, cashier's checks where you go to the bank.
You sign in front like you have one signature that's already on there.
And then you sign again and like at the bank and then they they exchange it for cash.
So I mostly had a bunch of these checks and
and I had like some American money and some Filipino money that I had cash,
but I had several unchecked like uncashed checks, but I couldn't do anything with them.
Right.
And it was funny when I went to do that, when I went to sign the second time at the bank,
because my signature is so fucking inconsistent, the lady was like really confused when I signed
them and she was like, I need you to duplicate your original signature and then duplicate this one
for me.
And I did that as best I could.
So so yeah, so so I'm like, fuck, the only way I'm going to be able to afford this,
because they wouldn't take my American money.
They were like, you need more Filipino money.
So I was like, well, I've got a couple of these checks left.
There's a bank in the airport.
It's closed and it doesn't open till 8am.
Which is after my flight.
Oh, fuck, right.
So I don't have anything.
So I'm freaking out.
And then a police officer who's nearby is like, hey, look, I'll make this exchange for you.
I'll give you Filipino money in exchange for American money.
And I think it was that maybe it was that it.
Yeah, I think it was that it was like 80 bucks is what I needed.
But I only had like 50s on me or something.
I only had $100 for some reason in American money.
So I just gave it to I was like, you know, he gave me the equivalent of 80.
And I gave him 100.
He was like, are you sure, man?
And I was like, I have no choice.
This is all I have.
I need my flight to 10 minutes, you know.
That remind one time I was I was one quarter short of being able to do my fucking laundry.
So I went wandering around the streets and just found a guy.
Like it was like the midnight so nothing was open.
But I found at the back of the local Little Caesars Pizza, there were people cleaning up.
And I just I walked in to the back of the restaurant after they were close and said,
can someone please give me a quarter?
And I just I gave a guy $5 for one quarter.
Oh my god, you could have got a hot ready pizza for that five.
They didn't have coin converters in the laundry mat.
Dude, I don't use a laundry mat like there's a machine in my basement.
Uses quarters because I'm getting fucking scammed every day of my life.
But yeah, like it's it's a nightmare actually getting those getting the courts to that.
I have to go to the bank and shit fucked up to stop washing your clothes.
I'm doing that.
I'm trying that.
So so yeah, so so I get I finally I get the money I get through and then I fly to I think
I don't think I had to stop in Japan on the way back.
I think it was just a straight flight to America.
But this time it's another customs fuckery situation where like I land in the U.S.
with like maybe like 45 to 50 minutes to get to the next flight.
Right.
So this is this is going to be cutting it close no matter what.
And it's a long ass line in customs.
But we're going through pretty quick.
Now what's amazing about this is that like everyone else on the flight I'm with is like
Filipino.
You know, I'm like like one of the only white guys.
Everyone else is going through.
They've got this left lane.
Every guy's just like looking at him going.
Oh yeah, go go go ahead.
I get selected.
I get pulled aside to this.
This other room where this this other guy who is another Filipino guy.
But they've there's these two dudes, these two like security guys who are running, you
know, running through this guy's shit.
And they're taking forever.
They're like talking to the guy and shit.
They're doing all this stuff and I'm looking over.
I'm watching that other line just mosey on through constant stream of people and I'm
checking my phone like like by the time these guys even start looking at my shit,
I'm going to be fucking late.
Right.
So like they finally get that guy up and then they're going through my shit.
And these guys seem like total dick bags.
Like they've they've both got.
I think that's a requirement for working at an airport.
Have any of you seen the wire?
Nope.
Nobody.
I've seen some of it.
I know officer money penny or whatever.
Hey penny from San Andreas.
That's not helpful.
I know there's a black guy who likes chess.
There's these two asshole cops in the show.
And that's what these guys reminded me of.
Just like they had like this the attitude of like like like like like the jock cop is
the kind of guys I'm talking about.
You know, like Ben St was the cop.
No, the opposite.
It's the big old jock.
Tough guy.
Yeah, yeah.
It's these two guys who are like, you know, they clearly throw their weight around,
even though they're just like security officers or whatever.
That's me.
So they, of course, they open up my shit.
They're going through all my stuff and they're not even very thorough.
They're just kind of like looking at my stuff.
And of course my fucking suitcase is just full of anime crap.
So they're like flipping through my fucking gunslinger girl books and stuff.
And like I had bought this.
I'd bought like a 20 like every character from a certain scientific railgun because
they had these like little mini figures and they you could buy them in like a set.
And there's like 10 of them.
So they're like opening up the little boxes and look at the like.
So what are these for?
I'm like, they're they're toys.
They're he's like, yeah, what are they?
What are they for?
What are you going to do with them?
You piece of shit.
They're collectibles.
So what the fuck do you mean?
And he's it's like they I was like, you know, I'm probably going to give some to friends.
I don't know, man.
Like because I gave half of them to shade.
It was just like, I don't I don't fucking know.
What do you mean?
What are they?
They're fucking toys.
What do they look like?
Can't you see that I'm a fucking weird pedophile?
Because this is I've got the you know, this is when I've got the super long hair all the way down
to my ass.
That's all frazzled and fucked up because I don't take care of it.
I've got the shitty fucking goatee.
So I'm I'm a hideous monstrosity.
You know, I am obviously a gross pedophile terrorist.
So like can't they just like it's like, are you going to arrest me or not?
You know, like nothing in that bag is incriminating because I'm not retarded.
So either arrest me because I'm clearly a bad guy or just let me through, you know, whatever.
So I managed to I actually managed to make the flight with like seconds to spare.
Like I ran across the whole airport.
You know, I'm I'm out of shape.
So I show up like winded my legs are burning and shit.
Like I ran across the whole fucking Chicago airport or whichever one the one of the big ones.
Yeah.
And I guess that's basically the end of the travel story.
Oh, what a journey.
What an odyssey it was.
Customs people should all be like fucking hanged.
Yeah.
You know, I've got I've got I have a positive story about the customs people.
Oh, no, you don't.
I do.
Shocking and unforgivable.
What did you have sex with?
Like a cute little Japanese woman and you had sex with her or something.
Yeah.
I mean, all I had to do is take her out of my suitcase and let him fuck her.
And then he let us go through.
So it was pretty good.
You know, it was worth it for my investment.
Okay.
So I mean, I'll go with your mind real quick.
That was such a weird reversal on what I think monkey meant.
Maybe I misunderstood.
He was implied that you had sex with the customs lady.
You seem to imply that you had a Japanese lady with you who had sex with the customs guy.
In my suitcase, I guess I've been like forming this idea in my head.
Listen, you guys tell travel stories like you're a pedophile.
They're examining what's in your bag.
There's a little girl in there.
You know, some, some like that.
It all comes together.
Yeah.
So, so, okay.
So the most interesting travel I've done was when I visited Japan for two months before my
senior year of college when I was studying Japanese and at school at the College of New Jersey.
And that was by far, yeah, it was pretty nerdy.
The best thing it was, it was the best thing about college without a doubt other than meeting
my friends, which, which was good.
But, but this trip was, was the best.
It was, it was the best thing I've done in my life.
So, the trip there was actually great.
I mean, I was lucky that, yeah, like my parents helped me pay for the trip.
I couldn't have done it on my own.
And I got a bunch of cashier's check, got all my shit together, packed my bag,
packed all my anime shirts to wear what the people in Japan wear and got on the plane and
and just got out there.
And then the flight out there was, was pretty, pretty great.
Can't really complain.
I think it was from Logan Airport in Boston.
And I think there wasn't a stopover.
I think it was like a one shot.
I could be wrong about that.
But in any case, the flight to Japan was lovely.
It was like the best airplane food I've ever had.
I had like a fucking meal and it was like, it was like comfortable.
Yeah, please.
And the air ladies were great.
It was, it was wonderful.
And so, so I was living there, going to go into this school.
I actually looked it up while you guys were talking.
It's KCP International.
So it's like the PCP only with a K for Japan.
And also international.
Yeah, and also that.
So that place was great.
It was this, this cool ass school.
Wait, the PCP is international.
We have hippo and mage.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's true.
Fuck you, Ben.
You're not international.
I'm made of real countries.
Wait, international doesn't just mean Japanese.
I don't understand that.
Not anymore.
Unfortunately not.
You learn something new every day.
Well, not if you're me.
The mind of a homeless man is a closed book.
There's nothing new entering or leaving it.
So I have a closed book.
I'm washed up.
I'm set in my ways.
So I don't have much to say about that.
I mean, it was just a school.
There was a bunch of Koreans.
It was mostly Koreans, probably half Koreans.
Then a bunch of weeby Americans
and a couple of British people and shit.
They were all cool.
But what was interesting about it was
I noticed where my money went while I was there.
Because I spent an ungodly amount of money there as well.
I bought like one thing I was really looking forward to
was that I'd never been satisfied
with the selection of one piece shirts.
Well, that too.
I did try to get laid extensively in Japan.
That was probably the number two thing
that I engaged in while I was there.
But right.
So I was trying to find one piece shirts.
And I was online one day and found this ad.
I just found a magazine that had ad for one piece shirts
from Uniqlo.
And they just had fucking one piece shirts.
So it was a big day trip.
I dragged a couple people out.
We went to Uniqlo.
Were you a day tripper?
Yes.
Good joke.
Thank you.
I found the promised land of one piece shirts in this Uniqlo.
And I bought them and it was good.
It was actually fun.
I did that like early on in my trip.
But later on when I just like started,
when I figured out how to wander on Akihabara and shit,
like there was more to be found.
Just like on the street everywhere.
Well, okay, I'm exaggerating.
But like in like the clothing districts and shit,
in like the shopping centers,
there was just tons of one piece shit.
Because Japan gets it.
Japan understands that nothing else matters except one piece.
So aside from just like buying that shit,
my money was divided up between like bar tabs,
you know, buying alcohol, going to food places,
like the McDonald's we'd go to after being out all night,
trying to get laid in Roppongi.
Roppongi was the place we went,
like the club district, me and a couple of friends from school.
We'd go there and my money was consumed by that.
But then more interestingly,
I spent a lot of time at both crane machine arcades
and just like straight up game arcades in general.
Because there was this game that I was already really into,
Project Diva, the, you know, the fucking Hatsune Miku,
you know, rhythm game.
And that game was hot at this time.
I think this was like 2000, it is awesome.
It was fucking great.
And they had these arcade booths
where people would be lined up around the fucking block
to sign up and play fucking Project Diva.
And I would play Megurini Luca.
I can't remember what fucking song.
I had like one song I was pretty good at.
But these guys were masters.
They were, they were grandmasters.
Like the Japanese have abandoned their Kung Fu ways
and taken up the project Diva ways and they have excelled.
And it was, it was pretty dope.
Spent a lot of time there.
Bought a lot of Jojo figures from these like crane machines.
Oh, one, one fun time I had was that,
like on the day I was leaving, I, there was this,
there was this two piece set of a,
a two piece of one piece.
No, unrelated to one piece actually.
There was, so early on when I was there,
there was like this crane machine, like,
that was set up with like a two piece thing.
One had C2 from Code Geass.
The other had Colin Kozuki.
And like on the first day, well, early on when I was there,
I won the C2 set, like a piece of the two piece set.
And I was like, yeah, great.
But one day I've got to get that Colin.
So I'll come back later.
And I never did until the very day I was leaving
to get on the plane to go home.
And I happened to walk by an arcade that had that Colin,
other half statue of what I had.
And I was like, well, this is a sign, gotta do it.
So I spent like two hours in this crane machine
just putting 100 yen after 100 yen,
after 100 yen into the machine,
trying to fucking get this thing.
And like after like half an hour,
the guy who owned the place just like noticed
what I was doing and like tried to come over
and give me some pointers to stop wasting money
to like actually help me win the thing.
Cause I definitely spend like hundreds of dollars
by the time this, well, okay, maybe a hundred all told.
What were you trying to get again?
I was trying to get like, so I've got the statue.
I've got, I'll put like a picture of it or something.
It's like a combining statue of, from the anime Code Geass,
C2 the character and Colin Kozuki.
And like you can put them independently.
That's Colin's dad felt to you.
No, no, I understand.
I am a true Japanese man.
I have been to the promised land.
I'm one of her now.
I am with the struggle.
And anyway, I fucking like eventually,
even his help was enough.
So eventually he just like adjusted its placement.
He re opened the thing, adjusted where the thing was.
Let me do it again.
And then I won the thing like immediately.
So basically he would put so much fucking money
into trying to buy what was probably a $20 toy
that he had to give it to you.
He just took pity on you.
That's exactly what happened.
He just took pity on this poor white man,
just throwing away his entire inheritance.
That figure was probably for sale in like a store behind you.
Like for half of what you spent on it.
But you know, then I would have this cool ass story.
And that's right, that's right.
This honest, honest engine who took pity on me
in the land of the rising sun.
And so that was that.
But one other thing looking back on that I noticed.
So one of the things I did while I was there,
like the other big expenditure I made
while I was in Japan was I bought a gym membership.
But getting a gym membership for like, even in America,
getting a gym membership for a short amount of time
is not something you can do easily.
So like I ended up spending like a quarter of my total money
on, yeah, like hundreds of dollars on this fucking gym membership.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I had to get my lifts.
I had to get my lifts while I was there.
It was, yeah, it was, you know, it was a really nice place.
It was the funniest thing was when I signed up,
I had to do like a one-on-one interview.
And like most of them spoke Japanese obviously,
but there was this one lady, this like young girl,
and they were all wearing the exact same like track suits.
They were all uniformed up as like staff members of the place.
It was, in fact, it was just like this fucking manga
I'm reading right now, Nankiro Damoru or whatever it's called.
It's about weightlifting girls.
Great, I love it.
But it was a very lovely experience going there.
But the cool thing I learned while I was there
that in gyms, in like weightlifting gyms in Japan,
did you know that if you have any tattoos,
you have to cover them up because there's so many Yakuza members
that go to these gyms with tattoos all the place
that it is inevitable that a gang war will break out in a gym
if they see each other's tats.
Yeah, so you got it.
You are not allowed to show any fucking tattoos on your skin
in any of the gyms in Japan.
Yeah, it's pretty dope.
But anyway, so yeah, that's how I spent my time there.
And the flight back was much more painful.
So like on my way back, I was late and just missed my flight
because I've never been very good at being on time for things.
And I fucked this one up bad.
So I probably got there an hour later or something.
I just didn't understand the travel times yet
to get to the airport specifically.
And when I got there, I missed my flight.
It was shitty.
So I just got a flight the next day.
I just got pushed back.
They took pity on me and gave me a flight the next day.
So I just spent a day in the Tokyo airport,
wherever the fuck this was.
And I used that time at the time.
I mean, my Japanese was at its best ever at this point.
So what I did was, this was a wonderful airport
with lots of shit to do.
So I just went on down to the bookstore,
bought myself the entirety of the Skypea arc
of one piece in one piece volumes
and the last 10 volumes that had come out at that time,
which was like during Fishman Island.
And just sat down, read myself some one piece,
tried to learn as much as I could.
Isn't it like 30 books?
I mean, I probably bought like 20 right there.
But they're pretty sure you have those.
Oh, so this car.
Yes.
So this car.
What were you saying, Mom?
How did you carry 20 anime books at the same time?
They're really not that big.
Like, they're small.
I mean, I have a bunch of them on myself.
I mean, they're like a book.
You don't know anime like me, all right?
You don't understand.
I've been to the Holy Land.
Who are you?
Who the fuck are you, Mumpy Jones?
No, no shit.
Anime books are smaller in Japan.
They are Motomichikaku shit.
I think the ones that they...
Everything's smaller in Japan.
Hold on.
Yep.
Oh, Shisai.
Motochisai.
Why was I thinking Miji...
Well, I'll tell you why.
Ichiban Shisai.
I'm looking through my Japanese to English dictionary now
to figure out why I was thinking of...
Oh, I almost forgot.
I also went to Comic-Cat while I was there.
And that was cool.
Oh, fuck you, guy.
Yeah, I don't know.
I would love to go to fucking Comic-Cat.
If I... I would never go to Japan, fuck Japan.
The only reason I would ever break that promise
is if I could go to Comic-Cat.
Ben, what would you do at Comic-Cat with no money?
Eat a fucking dick, dude.
The only thing to do there is to buy shit.
It's a comic market.
I would look at fucking comics.
I would look at fucking dojin artists.
There is a second thing.
There is a second thing to do while you're there.
I would go to fucking be around people
that were buying shit tons of dojins.
It would be cool.
What's cool?
That is cool.
Davoo is literally howling.
Literally howling out my window.
I mean, Ben, we've both watched...
Fuck.
Comic-Party.
Right.
So we understand.
We knew right then and there.
Yeah.
That was the life for me.
Right.
So you can go there and you can reach it.
But the other cool thing that was happening there was like...
So at Comic-Cat, you're not allowed to take pictures
of cosplayers at any time.
Unless there's a giant open square
down to the side of the convention.
And that's where cosplay sluts go
to get their pictures taken.
And they get corralled in there.
And if you're in the danger zone,
people can take pictures of you and you can't complain.
You got to deal with that shit
within the bounds of decency, I'm sure.
So looking at all the...
Like the cosplay there was obviously far better
than any of the shitty conventions I've been to in America.
Comic-Cat cosplay is...
They know what's up.
Yeah.
And that's it.
That's based on the whole story.
Oh, so this guy...
Ah, yes, and you're...
So, so...
He's in your days.
He's in your...
Yeah, my trip to Japan really taught me a lot.
So what is the moral of all these stories?
What is the consensus on travel here?
The moral of the story is don't travel.
It's boring.
Don't go through customs because they're all fucking asshole.
Oh, I forgot my custom story.
Let me tell you my...
That's really short.
When I was on my way back,
when I got the flight in from Japan to
wherever like Chicago airport or whatever in America,
so like when I got through there,
like I didn't have to do any interview stuff.
Like it seems like you guys did when you traveled internationally,
but I did get like...
There was like one, you know,
international level of like bag searching and shit.
So like this guy opens my bag
and one of the things I had bought as like a present when I got back
was I bought my parents a big old bottle of sake.
And they just...
Foolish.
That's yeah, it's totally illegal
and you're not allowed to do it at all.
And he's just like...
Wait.
You got a bottle...
Well, it's because like you can't...
You could like store shit in it or something.
Not to mention you can't have liquids above like...
Yeah, I just had it in my bag.
Oh, okay.
And so like the guy just stops me.
That's true of all flights, not just international.
You cannot bring liquids onto a flight.
Well, I don't remember if this was on in my carry-on
or in like my separate bag.
It must have been my carry-on.
I don't actually remember.
But like whatever bag it was,
this guy examined it and he opened up and he's like,
Dude, you know this is illegal, right?
And I was like, I don't know anything about anything.
Why would you think that I know anything you asked for?
You immediately went,
Ah, so this guy!
I am just a Japanese grandmother.
I saw the officer.
It's his first time I do it.
That was pretty much what I said,
just in my perfect English.
And he, you know, he literally just...
He was like, dude, you know this is illegal, right?
You're not allowed to travel this.
And I was like, I'm sorry, please.
Is that a fact, sir?
Yeah.
And he just said, all right, no big deal.
Go on, let me go.
You nigger, how'd you even get away with this?
He let me keep it.
He didn't even take it.
He let me keep it and just let me go.
And then I gave it to my parents and we all drank it
and it was a grand old time.
And when I got back from Japan,
my parents had tried to put together a sign
that said welcome back, Nate,
or like welcome to America in Japanese.
And they fucked it all up.
It was a bunch of nonsense.
Embarrassing.
It was truly embarrassing.
That's when I knew they were, we were done.
That's when we were done that day.
They can't even speak the king's Japanese.
The king's Japanese.
The emperor's Japanese, whatever.
I'll say that that time going to the Philippines
was real scary and it was difficult on the travel.
And a couple of times I flew out to Montana
to take the Clunge Plunge.
It was disgusting.
It was still a little like, the first time I did it,
I was, it was still kind of a pain in the ass.
But by the second time I was like, you know what?
Flying, whatever.
Ain't that big a deal?
The funny thing is like, I think I was always so afraid
of like everything going wrong.
But even when stuff does go wrong,
it's fixed pretty easily.
It just wastes time.
It's just like, oh, you missed your flight.
Well, you got to take one like in four hours.
So have fun fucking around the airport, you know?
It's, people are pretty accommodating really.
Like you'll, if you miss a flight, they'll help you,
but you will have to wait until like,
you just got to waste a bunch of fucking time.
And I've gotten so used to the airport itself
because of radcons one and two,
where I was constantly driving back and forth
to the airport to pick people up.
And now I have like, I could perfectly envision
every square inch of that airport now.
Like I know it like the back of my hand.
So I have a sense of confidence about that airport.
Like, you know, if I got to fly somewhere from here,
I know exactly what it's going to be like.
I know what's going to happen.
Nothing's alien to me, you know.
I finally understand how baggage claim works
after having watched Jesse go through it.
So, yeah, I feel like, you know what, travel, yeah, whatever.
But the cost of travel,
kind of like everything in life.
You just got to know what you're getting yourself into
and then calculate if it's worth it
because it costs money, it costs time.
It'd be nice if we could just tell up our people places,
but we can't.
So just, you know, that whole ending part
was just so I could say the phrase, clunge, plunge.
That's the only reason I told that part of the story.
Good, worth it.
So how about we just go to questions?
Yeah, questions, questions.
Some of these shits.
All right.
I remember everybody tweet us.
We tweet out when we were fucking doing the shit,
usually on Saturdays or on like 4 p.m. or so.
So at TP Crasnators, all right, let's see what we got.
Hey Nate, remember when mom and dad took us to Mexico
and we stayed at Club Med?
Um, actually I don't remember that at all.
I was like 4.
I remember that it happened sort of.
And I vaguely, vaguely remember it
and that was the only good travel story of my miserable life.
Really?
You remember fondly?
I was in Vietnam.
No, it sucked.
It actually sucked, but I do sort of remember.
I sort of remember being annoyed and not liking it.
And there we go.
Well you know, our dad took us to a lot of places.
He liked to travel and we've been to like
Seattle as a family and like Disney.
That's true.
And we went to a couple.
We went to a couple new worlds.
I went to a new world.
Yeah, I didn't go to land.
And we'd been to, you know, like the Grand Canyon
and just like Utah.
Oh yeah, we did travel to the Grand Canyon.
We went to see the place that I wanted to see,
which was Utah Arches National Park.
If only I had been old enough to remember any of this story.
I have had the ultimate travel story in my life,
but I was a child because my parents
toured with Lollapalooza.
It's a big fucking tour from the 90s
that the Jane's Addiction created.
And it was just like every fucking cool band of the 90s
would all tour around the country.
We went to like 36 different states
because my parents were running a clothes vendor.
So we traveled in a fucking,
in a shitty fucking mobile home
that broke down constantly.
All kinds of terrible stuff happened.
Every story I've heard from it
is like, this is the ultimate story,
but I'm too young to remember any of it.
So I can't tell.
The only thing, the only thing I remember
other than skipping rocks with Green Day,
because Green Day would babysit me and Victor
in exchange for clothes at the time.
Is that actually the band you're talking about?
Yeah, the band Green Day would babysit me and Victor
and we were babies in exchange for free clothes from my dad.
And you can see that the clothes that my dad gave them
was from Perniche.
They wore it at Woodstock in 95, so.
Well, shit.
Yeah, so I was babysat by Green Day on this tour.
It's ironic because now you're an American idiot.
Yeah, and I remember we were going to the Grand Canyon,
but for some reason I heard Grand Cannon.
So I spent the whole time thinking
we were going to a giant cannon.
I thought it would be fucking awesome.
It would be.
Yeah, and I remember that while I was thinking
about the Grand Cannon, the smashing pumpkin song,
in spite of all my rage, I'm still just
a rat in the cage.
I don't know what it's called.
That song was playing.
That's all I remember of my trip around the world
to 36 states or about America.
When I think of Grand Canyons,
I think of my favorite cannon,
which is the ones that send you places from Secret of Mana.
Yeah, Cannon Travel Agency.
Cannon Travel Agency.
All right, that's enough about my bullshit.
Okay, what kind of questions we got here?
Let's see, okay, let me find one.
Okay, I got to find a filler one,
so you guys can talk while I find one that's better.
I'm gay.
Okay, here we go.
Sold us, guys.
Sold us, man.
Megan Lau at Nyan Kwan asks,
how do I become as suicidal as Monkey Jones?
Oh, shit.
Well, we'll fucking watch his video
on top deadliest suicide methods.
But that's once you're already suicidal, that's useful.
How does she get to want to do that?
I'd say just based on who you might be,
I think if you watch either the Depression video
and or the Elliot Roger review,
maybe it'll get you there.
Yes.
Okay, here's one.
AtcoreReviews asks,
guys, how do you feel about cooking slash baking?
Do you enjoy it and are you good at it?
The answer for Ben is no,
because he just had a huge baking experiment.
Don't say it.
Now I'm curious.
You know what?
You didn't like it,
but I thought it came out pretty good.
You just didn't like the ingredients.
That's all.
No, don't fucking say it.
You need to tell us right now.
Don't say it.
You know what?
If you say it, I'm just going to edit it out.
I'm not sure why it's a secret,
because this video won't come out for a week and a half.
I don't care.
You're not allowed.
Wait, are you just saying this is a time-sensitive thing?
Yes.
That's the reason.
Anyway.
That's fine.
The people will know one day.
Just tweet about yourself.
It was whatever.
You didn't like the ingredients.
That's fine.
It's not for everyone.
It's only for people with refined palates like myself.
You should have gone to Papa John's for better ingredients.
Yeah.
That's true.
Shit.
Now I want pizza more than I want beans.
I forgot about my desire for beans earlier.
Oh, then who's got cut out of your beans?
Hey, it's not the first time, and it won't be the last.
Hey, here's one.
Monkey, this is mostly for you,
because you just do this the most of the time.
Me again.
Well, it's for everybody.
But at JoshRushyAsk,
what's the weirdest slash most disgusting snaps,
as in Snapchat, I assume,
you guys have ever gotten from fans?
Immediately after doing the interview with Monkey,
where I was saying,
I was asking him if he gets dick pics,
and he said every day,
and I said, I've never gotten one.
And so immediately someone sent me a dick pic,
and I blocked it.
So then I realized why I don't get dick pics
is because anytime something happens to Monkey,
and I think, man, how have I been so lucky
that my fans aren't like that.
I then remember that anytime
anyone fucks with me in the slightest,
I blocked them.
And that's why it just happened to me.
Solid, solid reason.
Okay, so the worst thing I can think of right now
is just like a close-up of a guy's hairy asshole
while he's shitting,
so I can see the shit come out of my mouth.
Oh my god, no.
And it puts me to snap,
so like you kind of know what you're looking at.
Yeah, how the fuck did he do that?
Ben sees that, and Ben just thinks,
oh man, dinner is served.
Here we go.
How did he pull off this fucking snap?
That's like impressive.
That is impressive.
No, I didn't interview him about it.
I've got to bring him on.
Do an interview with this man, Monkey.
We need this.
I finally started, finally, after all this time,
I finally started getting nudes on Snapchat,
and I've been trying to send them back,
but it's so difficult to hold my gigantic phone,
which by the way is an S7 Edge,
so it's got the little,
like it's got the,
like if your fingers touch the little edge piece,
and it does, you know, it'll do things,
so like trying to hold the phone and press the button
and hold it at an angle where you can actually like see me
is just impossible.
I'm like, how the fuck, like,
I don't know how the, how she's sending me
these impressive pictures,
but I can't fucking do it without breaking my hand.
Well, you win some.
Yeah, I, yeah, I know what you mean.
I actually, I mean, I try to take progress pics
to keep track of like my muscle building and stuff,
and it's actually really hard.
It's fucking hard to go and do that shit.
I usually, I'll just like turn on the camera
and like record and then just take a video
and then just divide up into clips.
So if somebody ever hacked into my computer,
they would find in many pictures of me mostly naked.
Not entirely though.
Okay, here's one.
At LazyAceDia asks,
was there ever a time you questioned your sexuality
or have you always known you were gay?
I always knew.
Next question.
Yeah, that's, I think we all knew.
Let me see here.
Okay, let's, all right, let's,
fuck, no, hang on.
Let's fuck.
That's actually shit.
That's gay.
Which is why I'm into it.
Yeah.
Okay, here's that.
We can end after one of these or something.
But this guy asks, advice, what's the perfect ratio
at M Spectrum asks, what's the perfect ratio
of editing to video output?
Snore, what a gay question.
I'm just, I'm just saying, is there,
is there a number to be found?
No editing whatsoever is the ideal level of editing.
Just do the opposite of what Nate does.
Yeah, anything that's not what Nate's doing
is what you should be doing.
To me, anything that's not that.
If it takes, I mean, anything that I don't send to DeVoo,
the most it's gonna take me to edit is a couple hours.
I should be able to do it in one sitting.
And if it, if I can't do it in one sitting,
it means it's gonna be, it's gonna be hell before it gets,
like the top 10 and top 20 anime of the year videos.
I edited those myself.
Each of them only took a couple of hours to do,
but because there were so many breaks in the workflow,
then it took me like days.
And I was only able to finally do it
when I like got shit-faced and could convince myself to work.
I hate editing.
I remember that.
Yes, editing is bad.
This guy, incidentally, actually, never mind.
Okay, last question.
Let's end on this one.
At Wienermeister asks,
TP Crasnears, where is my dad?
I haven't seen him in two weeks.
You might have to ask for asking.
You might have to ask our buddy.
I mean, I know I was complicit in this,
but I don't actually know what Munchie does
with the dads that we steal,
so you'll have to consult Munchie about it.
I know I've got someone's dad in my trunk,
but it might not necessarily be your dad.
Yeah, I mean, I just steal the dads.
Well, wait, what was this guy's name?
It was at Wienermeister.
Well, Wienermeister, I mean, is your dad too missing his hands, feet, and head?
If so, it may be him.
Okay, that's enough.
Once again, all terrible questions.
Do better next time, people.
Very disappointed.
As always, terrible questions.
Words of encouragement from best guy ever.
Do better next time.
I get it.
Our audience has this weird...
It should be the easiest thing in the world to ask questions.
Just make them stuff that all of us can answer,
because we will not select your question otherwise.
When we were doing the let's plays,
we had, like, me...
Oh, man, that was a disaster.
Yeah, I put out a tweet that's like,
me, Munchie, and Victor are playing video games.
Tweet us questions.
And, like, half the questions are stuff like,
what's your favorite anime studio?
I'm like,
brother fucker, these two don't even know what an anime studio is.
I bet Munchie cannot name one fucking anime studio.
A1 Pictures is the best one.
There you go, that's true.
Expect to have anime-related questions just soundly, roundly ignored.
I am the...
Let me get this...
Since people don't seem to understand this,
because everyone in the PCP likes some anime,
but I am the only member of the PCP
who gives a single fuck about anime.
Maybe Nate as a second...
They might be confused to think that I give a fuck about anime.
Really don't.
No, Nate watches like...
They are deeply confused.
For anybody,
if you're watching anyone's channel other than mine,
the amount of shows that they've talked about on their channel
is just about the exact same as the amount of shows they've seen.
Like, there's...
Well, that is not true for me.
That is not true for me.
Okay, we'll say double then.
Double, double the...
You are underestimating how many fucking shows I've seen.
Well, then you...
I started watching anime before you fucking child.
You're a little baby, you don't know anything about anime.
You did not start watching anime before me.
Don't...
I think you might have.
You started watching during the original Adult Swim,
because that's the old school Adult Swim,
when they had the actual footage of pools and shit.
Yeah, 2001.
That's...
Okay, there you go.
So same time.
But I mean, that's when I found out it was called anime.
You know, I mean, I've been watching Sailor Moon and Pokemon.
Pokemon and Yukio and shit.
Well, Yukio would have been after Adult Swim started, but...
Look, we all know you watch more anime than me.
Well, that's why I said that he was the only other person
who could be said to care about anime out here.
Like, I mean, you and Ben have seen it.
Like, Hippo has maybe seen, like, 15 shows total, if that.
You know, like, he's only watched...
I've probably seen...
I've probably seen 20, 25.
I just do not care about the anime industry nearly as much as you.
I mean, I care about it because I like anime.
I want more good ones.
But that's it, you know.
Yeah, there you go.
All right, that's it.
We're done.
Oh, and I was just gonna say one more on your topic,
on your point, Ben, that, yeah, my words of wisdom
for the people here, always bad questions.
Remember, the two most damaging words
in the English language are good job.
So never, you know...
What?
That's from fucking whiplash.
That's from whiplash.
Oh, shit.
Because you gotta challenge people
and tell them that they're shit until they get good.
And no matter how good they actually are,
they can always be better.
Someone accused me of being the coach from whiplash
after my big rant.
That was one of the many comparisons I was getting.
Where did they say that to you, did you?
Say some comments somewhere.
Then why the fuck didn't you say so?
That's a quote.
All right.
Subscribe to Monkey Jones.
Yeah, subscribe to Best Guy Ever.
Patreon.com slash...
No, no, no, no, no, subscribe to Monkey Jones.
Best Guy Ever.
But also, patreon.com slash...
Monkey Jones.
...the procrastinators.
Shout out.
All right, thanks for listening.
Cut him out.
Just cut him out of this podcast.
He's out.
It'll be like he never even existed in the first place.
Perfect.
Just the way we're eradicated.
Everybody say goodbye.
Bye.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did I'm jerking?
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.