I want to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
We started? Is this the start of the episode?
Well, yeah.
Okay. I shouldn't have eaten all those overnight oats.
I usually don't eat first thing in the morning, but I went to get coffee.
And while I was there, I had my overnight oats and I was like, oh, ooh, I'll have some.
Ooh, I'll have some of this food I made for myself. Decadent. Decadent.
Oats. Do you have to eat them during the night?
No, it just means you, I discovered it fairly recently.
It just means instead of like, make an oatmeal, right?
Instead of like putting oats in a bowl and adding like milk, water, whatever, and then microwaving it.
Instead, you just combine the milk and the oats in the bowl at night and then you leave it in the fridge for eight hours plus.
And, you know, it just kind of soaks the oats and becomes a mushy oatmeal.
It's like cold brew. It's like cold brew coffee, but for oatmeal.
That's good. Better consistency and saves you like three minutes of microwaving.
But it takes an entire night. I guess you wouldn't do anything.
Yeah, but I'm not sitting there watching it.
Put it in the fridge and you just put your watch.
Damn, it's a bad value proposition because you can either put it in the microwave and stand there and watch it for five minutes for it to get hot.
Or you can put it in the fridge and stand there and watch it for eight hours and wait for it to get cold.
And then you eat it at the end.
You can watch a Mega Man lecture in that time.
You can watch a Mega Man lecture. Yeah, you got it.
That's like recipe. Okay, so you Google it, right?
You find one of those food blogs with a recipe for overnight oats.
You start it up and it's written by me.
And it's like, hmm, yeah, when I was traveling in Europe, for New Year's in 2018, I went to Estonia.
I went to Tartu Estonia, blah, blah, blah.
And I learned and I became a man that day and I learned that crime doesn't pay.
Anyway, let me tell you my recipe for overnight oats.
Your ingredients will be one cup of oats, one cup of almond milk,
some one squeeze of English toffee flavored better stevia, and a final ingredient.
Oh, wait, I had a joke. I had a joke.
What was my point? I swear I was going somewhere with that.
In the Mega Man lecture.
Oh, yes. And then the final ingredient is you got to sit and watch the Mega Man lecture.
So you combine the ingredients in the bowl, put them in the fridge,
watch the Mega Man lecture, come back and eat it, it'll be perfectly done.
That was a thank you. Thank you. You saved the bit. You saved the bit.
I fucking hate that when they have like, oh, recipes. Also, it's a blog and I'm going to talk about stuff.
And I'm like, where are you actually, I usually, I mean, I know what to do now.
I scroll as far down as I can as fast as possible.
Yeah, I don't read their stupid life, their stupid story about how much their kids like this recipe.
I don't know. Yeah, I don't know who reads this shit. Who is that for?
Maybe no one.
Like, is it just an ad revenue? Does it somehow generate ad revenue to write your stupid blog posts?
Maybe some people, maybe some percentage of people actually do read it.
But it's like when you're looking for a recipe, you're looking because you want to make something.
No, because you just have like this vague notion of like, the art of cooking.
I'd like to read about that right now. I'd like to read about people's experiences with cooking things.
I know that I'm going to do it. Like, why would you look up a recipe at that time?
I can't, I mean, yeah, I don't, I see people, I see people complain about this phenomenon.
I don't know anyone that likes it. There must be some benefit to it.
And it can't be ad revenue because like, they've already got the click because you clicked on the website.
I think maybe the idea is that, yeah, some small percent, it does generate some small percentage of people
subscribing to your newsletter.
Yeah, maybe that's it, parasocialize, maximize the parasocial relationship as soon as possible.
It's like, ah, this person has a family. I recognize that I'm similar in that sense and I feel like I can relate to them.
I will now follow their blog instead of not do that so I can see more.
I want to hear more about their, about their son, Jaden, with the gluten allergy, you know.
How's he going to, how's he going to feel about, how's he going to feel about the wheatless banana nutbread recipe next week?
Why was I also thinking of banana muffin thing? What is with recipes and blogs and bananas?
I was thinking of that because I have a, I have a walnut, a banana walnut bread candle that I burn in my room sometime for a smell.
It's delightful.
Smells, I mean, sounds good.
Smells, I mean, so it's both. Yeah, it's both.
I can't smell it.
You know what? I'm, I'm lighting it. You know what? I'm lighting it right now.
Oh, yes. Get lit.
Get, let's just get, all right, here on this week on the procrastinators podcast, we're getting lit.
We're getting lit. I got my Baileys here.
And I got my, and I got my banana walnut bread sent to candle.
We're, and together we're the procrastinators.
Listeners, listeners, light, light your candle. Take, take a shot of Baileys.
Wait, that wasn't in the episode. That was before we started the episode. Give is drinking straight shots of Baileys.
It's not multiple shots. It's just one after another, just one after another.
I just, just there's, is the Christmas tree has been put up today. We haven't like decorated it yet, but big old Christmas tree and logs on the fire.
And I got given a little thing Baileys. I'm like, all right.
Jack, Jack Frost nipping at your nose.
Yes.
Well, I didn't go outside.
Yeah.
I've been sick for this past week, and I'm only just now like getting over it.
Did someone give you Baileys as an early Christmas present?
No, just to just like a more like a late morning.
We've done a bunch of stuff. Let's relax by the fire with the alcohol of some kind.
My dad had a sherry or a port. I had a Baileys.
That's sweet.
It's nice.
Me drinking with my parents generally consists of a, yeah, sitting around the living room, me and my dad drinking Miller lights.
That's our version. That's our version.
I mean, that's a very unusual thing. I haven't had Baileys in like 700 years.
Yeah.
Kind of forgot what it was like.
It's like a milkshake. It's like a milkshake.
It is. It's like a milkshake. That's all I got to say on that.
For the viewers benefit, I will say that I was surprised because to my recollection, I thought the way you usually drink Baileys is like you put it in coffee, right?
And I think that's called an Irish coffee. That was what I thought. That was my, it's funny.
I think it's funny to drink straight Baileys, but I mean, I've done it.
That's not to say I've never done it because I have. And that's how I know it tastes like a milkshake.
Yes.
Is it like eggnog flavored?
Is it coffee flavored or is it just kind of like rum flavored, like rum flavored cream?
Yeah, kind of rum flavored cream.
Have you never had eggnog?
I don't think I've ever had an eggnog. I used to think that it's like some sort of a nog and you put eggs in it.
It's like some sort of a nog that you put eggs in. Yeah, it is kind of like that.
Why would you put eggs in a drink and drink it? What are you fucking rocky?
Wait, now I'm not sure if you were joking. What is a nog?
I mean, because of eggnog, I just assume it's like an omelet in a glass. I don't actually know anything.
Okay, I think a nog is like some kind of old fashioned term for like a mixed drink or like a rum or an alcoholic beverage.
I don't actually know what's in it. I mean, I think there are eggs in it traditionally.
So it's got nothing to do with having an omelet?
No, no.
Wow, I've been rung this whole time.
It's a drink, but it's like a creamy drink.
And traditionally, you mix it up in a bowl and then people sort of spoon it into glasses and everyone drinks like a glass of it.
And there's rum in it traditionally.
Okay, I never called it nog, but I don't know if this is the same thing.
But when I was at uni, there was like a party game where a bunch of just random drinks were thrown into a bowl and you had to do like a card thing.
I can't remember what the game was, but then you had to take a drink from the bowl of like mixed drinks.
Was it the goal to make the mixture like as gross as possible?
I don't think that was the goal, but it was gross because it was just like various spirits and I don't know if wine was in there or not.
I can't remember.
Was it like Kings? Like a drinking game like Kings?
I could have been. I mean, I got very drunk, so I can't really remember.
That was fun.
Well, that sounds interesting. Sounds fun.
But no, it's like a punch, but it's like sort of like a spicy, like creamy, eggy kind of creamy drink.
Like you can pour it onto a frying pan and make a pancake out of it.
Although more commonly, more commonly when I say eggnog, I'm talking about the store-bought kind, which is kind of just something you buy in a carton.
And I don't think there even is eggs in it, but it's like it's just kind of like it's sort of like a milkshake.
It's sort of like a creamy, slightly nutmeggy.
Yeah, it's like a creamy nutmeg milkshake pretty much.
And it's great by Hood Brand.
Sounds delicious.
Why was I talking about this?
Because I was drinking Baileys.
Alright, this is a very cozy holiday season.
I feel like, are you in the Christmas spirit? It sounds like you're in the Christmas spirit.
I am. I saw like a couple tweets, so just saying like Christmas sucks.
Christmas sucks.
Yo, Christmas is just another cold day.
That's the whole point, though. Like if we didn't have like gaiety and jollity and silly fun times.
What would we be without gaiety?
It would be like dark and cold.
And that's it.
It's just like life in a way.
Just like the universe, right? It's dark and cold.
Until Elon Musk spreads the light of consciousness throughout the cosmos, you know, will continue to be dark and cold.
Except for our little blue dot.
Our little blue marble.
You said spreads. Ah, no, never mind.
What? What?
Never mind.
What were you laughing at? No, what were you laughing at? Was it COVID?
Did you think I was going to say spread COVID?
No, it's much more gross than that.
Is it spread semen?
Is it spreading my seed?
No, but it's spreading his ass.
And the light shines from it.
Gross, gross, gross, gross.
Oh, you know, it's Elon Musk. It makes sense.
You know, it does. No, it does.
I'm not...
Yeah, I am in the Christmas spirit.
I haven't really gotten like heavy into it, but I just sort of...
It's like getting to the point where the sun goes down so early.
I want to see Christmas lights.
I want the fire to be roasting.
You know...
In the fireplace.
Now that I think about it,
I don't think I've seen any Christmas lights or decorations up
in my neighborhood.
Shameful.
I mean, maybe I haven't really...
Where's the twinklin'? You gotta have twinklin'.
No, I walked...
I think I walked around at night the other day.
I don't remember seeing any.
Huh.
It's not that.
We're almost halfway through December. I feel like there might be...
Maybe I haven't been outside at night in a while.
Maybe I should take another look around.
Yeah, I haven't seen any yet.
Hmm.
Yeah, I've been to a few malls where they got stuff around.
There's, you know, the street lamps.
I don't know if in America you have this,
but like the councils near where I live or in London in general,
they just have like Christmas decorations they put on every lamp post.
And they sort of appear slowly through the November into December
and then, oh, they turn them on.
And then there's reindeers everywhere.
You know, the local council like is in charge of it.
It's not like mandated or anything, but it's always there.
That's great.
Not really.
I mean, maybe in certain places, not where I live.
Hmm.
Now, suddenly I'm realizing a sort of distinct lack of a Christmas decor.
And because I live on like a street where like, you know, the houses have little yards.
It's not like I live on like a city block where like there's no trees or anything.
Bunch of Scrooges.
You gotta spread the joy.
Yeah, I gotta spread the joy.
I gotta take it upon myself.
You gotta get the toilet paper.
You gotta get the toilet paper and wrap it in gift wrapping for them, for your housemates.
I thought you were gonna say you gotta get the holiday toilet paper
and go around toilet, toilet, papering their yards and their trees and their houses with it.
Yeah, the special like Christmas-like toilet paper.
Hmm.
Sparkles.
Twinkling.
Yeah.
Good.
You know, if they, if they, they can't, oh, they can't afford.
Oh no, they must not be able to afford Christmas decorations.
Well, I'll just go and toilet paper their house for them.
And they'll be so grateful.
An egg nog their house.
Toilet paper and egg nog.
I'm gonna egg nog their house, but nog is kind of expensive.
So I'll just egg them.
Just egg them, actually.
Yeah, they probably have nog already.
They have, I'm sure they have.
Should they have nog?
Just scrape the egg off the side of the building.
Put it in the tree.
That's, that's, that's charity, right?
That's my groceries.
That's my groceries that I'm giving to them.
They can scrape, scrape it off the side of their house.
Uh, the, my, I learned, I learned this yesterday.
One of my, one of my roommates, the girl has, um, has like food stamps saved up.
She's been, apparently this is this guy she knows told me this yesterday, this tidbit.
Apparently she like was getting, you know, food stamps, EBT for years and just never used it.
And so now she's got like thousands of dollars of like credit just on a, an EBT card.
Wow.
Yeah.
I hope she'll give me some.
I hope she'll buy me some stuff.
How does that work?
What do you mean?
With, I mean, I don't know what food stamp procedures there are.
I mean, you just apply.
I've been lucky enough.
If you're, if you're poor, you just apply to a freaking, you just fill out a paper and
you send it to somewhere and you know, depending on your circumstances or whatever, they'll
approve you a certain amount based on your income that you just get.
Yeah.
You get credit on a card.
They give you a special card and you can use it at supermarkets and stuff and you can
just spend it like money on food.
That's great that it just, just can keep continually like growing.
Yeah.
You can get to a point where you have thousands of dollars.
I imagine like a really horrible way to do it is like you get a food stamp like coupon
that expires if you don't use it.
Yeah.
That's how you would do it if you were evil.
You know, I, yeah, I don't, I think the car, I think if you like don't use it for a long
time, the card like expires like the card itself becomes inactive.
I don't know if like the credit ever disappears unless like, unless like maybe you were to,
maybe you were to like your income were to increase and you reported your increased income
and then you said you no longer eligible and then like they cancel your card and then you
can't get the credits back maybe.
But as long as you're still eligible, I think that like the credits never expire or they
don't for like a really long time.
Yeah, it rolls over from one month to the next.
Anyway, she should buy my groceries, I think.
I don't know.
That's just a little tidbit.
I got like nothing done this week at all.
I completely squandered my week, wasted it.
I mean, that's not entirely true.
I took care of some like more practical stuff like I went to the bank and I got the check
just I got the I got my negotiated down check to send my landlord.
I still haven't sent it yet.
It's sitting on me.
But I, you know, I had to do that.
I called a guy that my parents wanted me to call to discuss like banking options.
I set up an appointment.
I did a couple of things like that.
But in terms of like getting the book done almost almost nothing this whole week.
I'm just going to call a vacation.
I'll call a vacation.
It's funny.
I was talking about hibernating like a couple of weeks ago, but being sick this past week.
How'd you get set?
How'd you get sick?
Did I talk about going to camp?
You mentioned it.
Yeah, yeah.
I think a few people there may have had a cough and then I got it.
I don't know if it was COVID.
People had to check and it doesn't feel as bad as a COVID.
So it's probably just a regular flu or cold.
Did you have COVID before?
I did.
In America, yeah.
Oh, that's right.
That's the only time I got it.
Of course, of course.
Yeah, yeah.
Those dang yanks with their powerful COVID that they keep making.
Yeah, we got those powerful strains.
We got the good stuff.
China may have done it first, but we did it best.
We mixed it up.
A concoction.
Yeah.
Anyway, yeah.
Yeah, I got it from Christmas camp and then I was sort of bedridden, actually.
It was really bad for the first few days.
Couldn't really move.
Cough and spluttering.
You didn't take a COVID test?
I can be fucking bothered.
I felt like it would go away after a couple of days.
It wasn't like, I felt like I was going to die.
I mean, I think you're a little scared at one point.
Just because I don't like running out of water in the middle of the night and I'm like,
oh, everyone's asleep and I need somebody to get me a drink,
but I have to be the one to do that.
So I have to get out of my nice warm bed and die on the way there.
Yeah, yeah.
When you're sick, the chills, the chills feeling when you're out of your bed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gotcha.
It's that sort of thing where if a light breeze gets me,
I start coughing and spluttering uncontrollably for like 20 minutes.
So it's bad.
It was bad and I'm better.
But because of that, couldn't do any work.
And I stayed up in bed looking at my phone and it was like, wow, fuck.
I want to draw.
I want to make so many things.
I had so many creative ideas.
I wrote a bunch of things down.
Well, that's good.
When I was able to, when I was like cognizant,
when my brain was allowing me to like look at my phone,
because sometimes it was just too hard.
But yeah, it really is one of those like, if you can't work, you really want to.
If you can't do creative stuff, suddenly everything comes to you.
Suddenly, when you're forcing yourself away from that constant grind,
you're like, oh, I can come up with stuff and I couldn't do anything about it.
Oh, yeah.
But now that I'm on the mend, I'm going to immediately forget all that
and play video games instead.
Definitely, definitely.
You know it's bad when I'm playing Noida.
I played Noida like twice, three times this week.
Game sucks, man.
That game sucks so bad.
I just, I've just, I've so thoroughly explored its mechanics that like playing it
and winning is just like a totally rote exercise.
There's no point in it anymore.
But I did it, I don't know, I guess just to procrastinate and it worked.
Yeah, sometimes that's all you need is just something to occupy your mind for a few hours.
Yeah.
It might be the cold, it might be the cold weather, so demotivating.
That's why you need the Christmas spirit.
You need like cool lighting.
That is why I need Jesus, yes.
No, I mean you can have Jesus.
You can have Jesus.
He ain't going to, you put him on the shelf.
He ain't going to hurt you.
You heard a elf on a shelf?
Yeah.
I haven't, I don't know what it is.
But you should put Christmas lights everywhere.
You should put nice colorful stuff.
Not necessarily like Christmas-y stuff, but just like cool colors that you like.
I think my banana wall handles pretty Christmas-y.
Like neon green baubles and like purple killer stuff.
Oh, that's cool.
For Sly Mernalia?
Yeah.
Yo Sly Mernalia.
Woo!
Shit, I was going to mention something.
Oh, I've been lifting again.
I started lifting again.
That's generally like the one good thing that I can be like,
that's good about it this week.
And I've been lifting for like probably two weeks now.
I'm sticking with it.
That feels good.
I'd like to be strong.
I'm weak right now.
My numbers are pathetic.
But I'll get them, I'll get them back.
Hell yeah.
I'll get them back.
I've been, I've been pretty sloppy with my dieting lately.
I've been pretty sloppy with my calories, but
and my excuse is, oh no, it's my, no, I'm bulking bro.
I'm bulking.
Because I'm lifting again, so I got to eat big together.
I'm bulking, which means I'm from that, the bulking.
I'm bulking-izing.
I'm bulking-izing bro.
I'm splitting up into lots of small units.
Smaller and smaller, but more numerous bends.
Balkanizing.
Balkanizing over and over again.
What if you turned into three smaller version of yourself
and they had like one third of your personality each?
I think if I did that-
Who would win?
If they fought immediately, because they probably would.
I think if I did it twice and I became nine little pieces,
they'd be nine little tiny baby Ben Saiyans.
But for the medium-sized ones, who would win?
I mean, they would-
Divide your personality into three distinct Ben Saiyans.
Well, there's-
There's Twitter Ben.
Yeah.
There's-
Drunk Ben.
Oh my god.
And there's Normal Ben.
Normal Ben is the smallest of the three.
I think Drunk Ben would probably win.
Because he takes action.
Whereas Twitter Ben talks a big game, it doesn't do anything.
He folds like a paper tiger.
So, yeah.
If Drunk Ben and Twitter Ben fused, you'd be drunk on Twitter.
And then imagine the possibilities.
I have done that and it sucks.
I've done that a couple times and every time I look at my tweets from the last night,
I'm like, what am I talking about?
Why did I post that?
So, I don't even remember.
I don't even remember what I posted drunk,
but I don't even want to remember.
I don't want to think about it.
Surprisingly, it's not a very powerful combination.
Surprisingly, it doesn't get a lot done.
Drunk Gib tweets, I think are pretty good.
When I get on it, when I get on it like a stupid tweet,
like moment, it's mostly just like stupid jokes.
Yeah.
Because I'm throwing so much stuff out there that some of them are going to be funny.
And then the bad ones, people just scroll past.
It's just like, weren't we saying this about Red Man the other day that like,
yeah, it's not many, the jokes aren't good, but there's more of them.
Yeah.
So, that's got to count for some...
Just like doing a comedy stand-up, it's four hours long.
People get really restless.
But like, there's so many jokes.
What if I did like stand-up comedy?
But instead, I wasn't funny and I was talking about Mega Man for eight hours.
What if I did that, huh?
And then by the time I was done, my oats would be done.
Hey, I brought it back.
You should do another eight-hour video and then make that reference.
Wait.
Like have oats in the background.
Have oats in the fridge just the beginning of the video.
The next lecture is just about like oats.
And it's just about like, hey, I've decided to just talk about this while my oats...
Sorry, my oats have to sit in the fridge for a while.
So, I just got to talk.
I'm just going to talk to you.
Yeah, that's a good theme.
You know, I sort of came around on the idea of doing a follow-up about Battle Network.
I was thinking about it and I was like, I should just do that.
I should just do that.
So, I went and I downloaded ROMs for all the Battle Network games and the Star Forest games.
I was like, maybe I'll just play one and just see.
Turns out they're so fucking long.
They're so fucking long.
I've heard that they're like RPGs or tactics things.
Yeah, they are.
Yeah, pretty much.
I mean, the battles are sort of like...
Yeah, they're sort of like tactical RPGs kind of.
But the gameplay is mostly running around talking to people like an RPG.
So, yeah, they're all like 15 to 30 plus hour-long RPGs the whole series.
And there's like 10 of them.
And it's like, oh god.
150 hour lecture.
Regular Mega Man games only take a few hours to beat.
This is just...
I don't want to do it.
Now I lost my motivation.
Because I feel like I have to play them.
I feel like I have to.
I can't not play them.
Can you imagine?
My wonder is like the Mega Man lore is interesting at a glance.
There's a lot of weird things about it.
And you're like, I wonder how that all connects.
Battle Network I know absolutely nothing about except that one meme screenshot of that old guy who says I'm 30 years old.
Oh yeah.
Like that's the only thing I know about it.
So I don't even know whether playing every game would be even that interesting.
Yeah.
Like lore-wise.
Well, I mean, I know the plot of the first game.
I know what happens in the first game.
I know that lots of the characters...
Well, I know that it's about humans and these network AIs that interact with each other.
And all the network AI characters are named things from Mega Man.
And they sort of bear some resemblance or they take some inspiration from Mega Man characters,
but they're not the same characters.
So I assume it has its whole own completely separate...
This guy is this guy's dad and this guy is that other guy's former business partner or whatever.
So I mean, I assume I could make a flowchart of character relationships and stuff.
I know, I'm not going to spoil it.
I already know that just in the first game there are some twist reveal of what this guy is actually that guy is so-and-so.
So...
Wily is Light's son?
Son?
Daughter? Yeah, stuff like that.
No, there definitely is a lore to be explained.
It's a little bit like...
With Mega Man, you're pretty much piecing together a story out of many games that basically don't have hardly any story.
Whereas basically in Battle Network, the game is all story, because it's all dialogue.
Yeah, it's just all dialogue.
So you're going to make a lecture about the gameplay?
Yeah.
Which I think is grid based.
Anyway.
It implies the existence of grid cringe.
Grid cringe is...
Well, grid based is when you have characters on a map like Final Fantasy Tactics.
Maybe Mega Man Battle Network is grid cringe, because instead of a big world map that you walk around in a grid on, it's just a little 3x4 tile grid that you kind of bleep around on.
Maybe grid cringes when you use a pentagram.
Not a pentagram, pentagon grid.
And then you have those tiny little things to fill in the gaps, because you can't tile with a pentagon.
Oh, and the little placeholders are the grid cringes?
Yeah, you can technically move through them or on them.
But it's like, ah, your foot's over the line.
It cuts in no space.
I'm sorry.
There's no space for this one.
Alright.
An anime about being a floor tyler in the competitive floor tiling business, but your weird character quirk is that you only tile with pentagonal tiles and everyone laughs at you.
Like this is so fucked.
This is so fucked.
What am I looking at?
Why would you do, why would you make this so difficult for yourself?
There's no advantage to this whatsoever.
And you said, my father died tiling a floor with squares.
I said, I'll never use squares again.
And then I said, why didn't you use hexagons then?
And you say, shut up.
Just shut up.
Don't fucking talk to me.
I can't count that high.
Because I only go one step beyond, he said, wagging his finger.
The hexagons are too powerful.
But then he discovers that you can make a grid on a 3D, on a sphere and he invents the football.
And everyone's like, what?
You can play chess on a football?
And he's like, hell yeah, you can.
He uses again Jutsu.
He uses again Jutsu to draw you into his spherical pentagonal chess world and you have to beat him in a game of skill.
Are you okay?
Oh no, I killed him.
Oh, hang on.
I'll be okay in a second.
Take your time and get some more coffee.
A few moments later.
What's up?
Yeah, all right.
You gonna make it?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Still not perfectly well, but that's okay.
The views on the Mega Man Lecture have calmed down.
I think it's getting like 5K views a day or something now, which is, no.
Yeah, something like that.
Which is okay, you know.
It's more views than my Mega Man Lecture has.
When I say it out loud, you know, it doesn't sound that bad, although it's kind of, you know, it was after seeing it get like 30K a day for a while there.
It feels like, ugh, ugh, the hype is dead.
Yeah, so, you know, it's, the line has like stopped peaking.
It's kind of down to like, I wonder what did it level out?
If it levels out, if it like levels out for like a long term at like, even like a thousand views a day, that would be incredible.
That would make me, that would make me like, that would be making me like $7 a day forever.
Wow.
Forever and ever.
I mean, it won't do that forever.
What if it did though?
What if it did?
What's your biggest video, the Sonic 101?
Sonic 101?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That one continues to, I mean, other than maybe this one, but like, that one continues to get the most views forever.
There's like a few hundred views a day, I think.
No, no, no, no.
I mean, what do you want to know? I can look at my analytics.
Well, yeah, views per day.
What's the average?
Well, let me, you mean like before I put this new video out when like, the channel was just kind of dormant?
Yeah, if it went down after that.
Oh, I'm almost at 25k subscribers.
Well, you know, let me look over the past year.
Over the past year, before this new video came out, the Sonichu lecture was getting,
Sonichu 101 was getting 2 to 500, somewhere in the 2 to 500, 300-ish views a day on average.
That's pretty good.
Still, like for an older video, even though it's over a million views at this point.
It's over one and a half million now.
Wacky.
But then like, you know, when this new video was out that, well, it was getting like a thousand, it got like a thousand views a day just from like runoff clicks, I guess.
Now it's down.
Yesterday got 500, 300.
So it's kind of back to where it was now.
How many views did yesterday Mega Man lecture got?
Oh no, a pitiful 3,000.
It's over.
It's so over.
You know, while I was sick, I did manage to get my PS4 on.
I played some Dark Cloud because I got the PS2 version on the thing.
Like digital, digital store?
Digital, digital version, yeah.
I'm like playing that again.
I'm like, ah, it's so good.
It's my favorite.
And I'm like, I wanted to make that Dark Cloud video.
And this was like one of the prerequisites.
But you did make a Dark Cloud video.
No, no, I mean, like earlier weeks ago, I was talking about like a possibility of talking about Dark Cloud lore and its connection to the sequel.
Oh yeah, I vaguely remember that.
Yeah.
And it would have required me to play the games again to reacquaint myself.
Because like Dark Cloud is not like obscure, but it is not a cult thing with like active members.
Like if you look for information.
There's no Dark Cloud fandom.
There is, but like they're not like active.
Like you can find wikis and stuff, but they're very basic, very bare bones.
A lot of the stuff that's in the game doesn't exist online for you to read.
So you have to play the game to read like dialogue from characters.
And sometimes the dialogue doesn't repeat.
So like certain bits of information, you just have to play the game to find it because nobody's documented all that shit.
So I'm like, I'm playing it and I'm enjoying it.
And I'm like, yeah, more people need to be obsessive fans of Dark Cloud.
I kind of should make a video.
I kind of should.
I kind of will.
I probably will.
I'll watch it.
Oh my God.
A video.
What the fuck?
I don't know how to like structure it.
We are so back.
The PCP is so back.
We are so videoing right now.
But like there's multiple ways I could go about it.
I was thinking of like, I know this way it will get no views and no one will care.
But I just wanted to like make a long rambling video where there's no point.
I'm just talking about cool things in Dark Cloud.
I'm just talking about it.
And it's like, it would open with like a little musing on the fact that most videos these days, they're all about teaching you something.
Like there's someone teaching you like a moral or like a lesson or some interesting fact.
Yeah.
I'm not a teacher.
I'm a gamer and I'm going to fucking game.
I'm just going to talk about my favorite game and I'm going to say, look at this, look at that.
And it was going to be a terrible video.
No one would like it.
So I really should try and think of something different.
I kind of miss.
This is a side tangent topic.
Like, do you remember when YouTube was not like a like entirely like educational?
We're like, yeah, sure.
Yeah.
It was just stupid shit.
It's just stupid shit.
People stupid people stupid home videos and people stupid and flash cartoons flash cartoons and like 360p resolution rips of new grounds flash cartoons.
I believe.
I forget who said it.
But I think.
There was like a like a shift where people's shit posts and like half second ideas that they would have made a small YouTube video or a vlog or something about back in the day have been like consumed by other social media websites like Twitter.
Like if you make you have like a funny idea, you don't make a video about it anymore.
You tweet it.
You tweet it and then it's out and then you've done it.
And you get responses and it's like instant making videos a longer process.
So now making a video has to be has to mean something has to have like a big purpose.
And if the purpose is usually is like, I know something and I'm going to teach you it.
I'm going to be an authority figure and you're going to be wrapped with attention because of how smart I am and how correct I am or how well I can explain something.
That's me.
That's me now.
Yeah.
Literally me.
No, but I get you.
And it's like, that's fine.
I don't dislike that.
But when it comes to my my enjoyment for making videos, the videos I enjoy the most are the shit posts.
All of the like little stupid videos I made on Gibb and take that like had nothing to do with anything.
It was just like, I've had a cool idea.
I made it.
And then the most scripted stuff.
I felt like a pressure to be smart.
I don't feel smart.
I feel like I'm stupid, actually.
Okay.
So it's like, it's got to lean into that, I guess.
I guess.
But like, I think I wouldn't be that there's not really a climate that accepts videos that are not like educational or like have some sense of authority.
I'm not sure if I if that that can't be completely true.
Maybe not.
That's just sort of my reservations about making a video is this the sense that it has to be really big, big splash.
And it can't just be like a casual little experience because people are going to get bored or something.
I feel like.
Would it be a would it be a long video?
I don't know.
It might not be.
It might be that there's nothing to talk about.
And I just have the idea and I say it.
And then I'm done.
But it'd probably be kind of long.
Remember when I did that?
That let's read Lillia's book?
Yeah.
The video, the video sucks.
The video sucks.
But it's you can't remember it.
I don't know if I watched it.
There's not very.
I mean, it's whatever.
That's whatever.
Honestly.
That video is sloppy.
I filmed it with a fucking shitty webcam.
My my quality sucks.
Well, I don't even know.
I don't know why I did that.
Like if I was going to make that video.
It wouldn't have been that hard to just like make it good.
But I just didn't invest like.
I did not invest into like the pretty small.
I don't know why I was so afraid of spending like $100 to have like.
Well, I guess I guess.
I guess I had a worse phone at the time.
So my camera quality was bad.
So I opted to use that shitty web camera.
And then I.
And I was like, oh, well, I have a good enough microphone.
So I'll use this microphone instead of buying a real one.
And so my audio quality is bad, my video quality is bad.
And then I mean.
The video itself is just me like.
Yeah, there's no there's no point to it.
It's just me pointing out like things I find amusing as I read through the book.
And like, I guess I guess that's fine.
But it's just not there's not a lot to it.
There's no there's no real there's no real overarching point to what I'm doing in it.
So whatever video sucks.
Could have been better, but it wasn't.
But it's fine.
I don't know what point I'm making.
The point is that you sometimes is okay to just make a video and it's bad.
I've done it and it's good.
Yeah, I guess that's my hang up.
I don't want to make a video that's bad.
You don't want to be like me.
You don't want to end up like me.
I feel that with a big old video that's everyone loves.
I do have.
Yeah, but before I made that one, I had to make the crappy one that everyone hates.
And then I had to wait like two years for no reason.
It's a process of becoming.
I guess.
I guess it's the same with any art form.
It's sometimes going to suck.
I just, um, I feel like.
Honestly, I'm the Lillia video I made on a complete whim.
I just had the idea and then like a week later, I did it.
Whereas the Mega Man lecture I prepared for for like months.
Yeah, yeah.
Obviously, the more work you put into it, the better it is.
It's just, um, I guess it's YouTube feels less approachable than it used to.
No, yeah.
It feels like because the quality like medium or whatever phrase you would use, average quality of videos in general, really, really high, really high up there.
There's so many amazing things you can watch.
Why would anyone click on something that wasn't like great or like stick with it?
I'm like, uh, I'd like it when people pay attention.
That's the reason I make a video is for people to watch it.
So I better make it good.
But now it's like, I don't even know if I can.
So, uh, fuck it.
I think, um, yeah, I feel you.
So I think the, I think the, um, the thing there, the solution there is that.
You just kind of have to market it or not market, but you kind of have to hope that it would be good on the back of like people want to hear about Dark Cloud.
Like if you've got stuff, if you've got stuff to say about Dark Cloud, like do people, if people want to hear.
If people want to be, oh yeah, I remember that game.
Yeah. Oh, tell me, tell me some things I didn't know about Dark Cloud.
That then, I mean, you know, it's, that's not, that's not an overly saturated market right there.
Not many people are talking about Dark Cloud.
Uh, but there's probably, you know, people that remember the game for playing as kids might nevertheless be like, oh yeah, I'm interested in that content.
And that's, and that's the market, that's the demographic you got to capture.
And you know, if you can, if you can capture the interest of that demographic, you know, you don't got to do anything like mind blowing with it.
I guess not.
It's just, uh, I'll try it.
I'll play the game, I'll play the next game and then maybe I'll play them through again with take notes more like thoroughly.
Cause there's a few things I've noticed, but I haven't been taking notes cause I've been like just playing for fun.
But yeah, I think, I think I could do it. I think I could do something.
Maybe it'd be a waste of time, but I feel like, I feel like it's worth putting the time in maybe.
I just, I just will feel bad if nobody pays attention.
If I don't get my millions of views.
Well, how am I going to face Ben Saint?
You can't. You can't.
Am I going to return to the podcast?
No.
I used to be someone in the broding community.
I was a higher roller because like the rolling was so low.
Oh no. I've dropped from, I've dropped, oh that, that, that realization.
Oh no, I used to be D-list horse famous, but now I'm, now I'm E-list.
No.
Um, I've dropped a rung.
Yeah.
Uh, you, you will be judged on your metrics, on your video, on the Saber metrics, your videos performance.
The Saber spark?
It's, it's better, yes.
Yes. Saber spark.
It's better to not make, it's better to not make it and, and so, so that there's no chance that like the view count won't be high, right?
It's like they say, you, you miss 100% of the shots you never take and it's better to just commit to missing every shot.
That's how you get, that's how you make the big boss.
I don't even know if that makes sense.
That's where you get the real reason. Just commit, just commit, just commit to missing every shot as a bit.
Okay.
And just sell it.
Like this is, just sell it.
It's like, I don't know why I'm imagining archery, but like you're at the archery thing and it's like, oh wow, that guy over there, he hasn't even fired his bow.
Whoa.
Whoa, he must be like, he's like, that guy must like, really, he must be so good that he like isn't even wasting his time shooting this target.
It's like targets too close.
Yeah.
Dan, that guy is such a good archer.
He's like embarrassed by like how, how, how easy the shot would be when he finally fires his bow though.
Yeah.
We're all going to die.
He's going to kill all.
I've realized I've been peeking the mic.
That's bad.
Oh, I did, I did that also.
Yeah.
I'd rather peek the mic than have the mic peep at me.
If you know what I'm saying.
No, I don't.
Okay.
It's not got eyes, but it has got ears.
Doesn't make any sense.
I shaved my mustache.
Not my, my beard is starting to grow in a little bit and I shaved the mustache off because I was picking at it and it looks like shit.
You have a reverse chaplain.
Yeah, I guess.
I guess I was picking, I was picking at my mustache and I kind of picked like a hole in it and I was like, well, that looks like shit.
So I shaved it off and I was like, well, at least it looks like I did this on purpose, but it still looks bad.
But I don't know.
There's, that story is not going anywhere.
There's no, yeah, there's no, there's no, there's no less than that.
Hey, just to update my facial hair situation.
Oh, it's fucked.
Yep.
That's right.
You should have a corner.
Oh, no, I didn't read one piece.
Oh, you fucker.
We'll have to read it live again.
Again?
No, hang on.
This is the bit.
This is the new bit.
No, it's a bad bit.
It might be a bad bit.
It might be a bad bit, but it's the one we got.
It's the only one we got.
Shit, we don't have to talk about that now.
No, we'll do it later.
We'll do it just before or after voicemails, probably before.
Yeah, before.
Don't worry about it.
Totally forgot, totally forgot that that's the thing we do.
Yeah, I didn't read this week's one yet.
I was too busy not doing other things.
I was too busy ruining my beard.
I'm so stupid.
Why is you so stupid?
I want to grow my beard in, but I can't.
I can't do it, Gib.
I literally can't do it.
You mean because you keep picking at it?
Yes, yes.
I can't not do it anymore.
I used to be able to not do it and I can't not do it.
Get you a little fidgety thing, like a little autism clickety-clack machine.
It doesn't work.
You can grab that instead.
Maybe you should buy a fake beard.
It's a good idea, but it doesn't work.
You should buy a fake beard and wear it on top so that you can pick on that instead.
I had...
You know what?
It's my fault.
I brought it up, but I don't want to change my mind about wanting to talk about it.
So let's talk about something else.
But that's it.
I didn't take notes.
I don't have any notes this week.
Well, I have one more note.
Yeah, go for it.
I thought of doing a high school like manga where it's like they go to school,
but with all of my OCs in there, and it'll be non-canon to other things.
I was going to say, is it an AU?
Yeah.
It's the augmented universe.
And there's going to be Clarissa, and there's going to be Gun Girl,
and there's going to be Red Man and a lot of ghosts.
And Hippo and Gibbon take the pony, and then me as a person.
Oh, okay.
And then fucking everyone.
Even characters from comics I haven't made yet are going to show up.
And their joke is going to be like, oh, what comic are you from?
I don't know.
I think it's going to be fun.
I think it'll be a fun thing.
But I have to make sure I don't try and make it too serious and too good.
It has to be shit.
It has to be really bad, because then I could actually make it if it's supposed to be really bad.
That's right.
That's how to combat AI, is to draw bad shit that sucks and nobody wants to steal.
They won't put it in the machine then.
You draw so many bad things that it poisons the machine, and it's like,
oh no, now the machine can only draw things that are bad.
Or, yeah, better yet, make only good things.
So the machine only draws good things, and then there's no market for good things,
and then you don't have to draw anything good anymore.
Then only humans can draw bad things.
You get what I'm saying?
Now, you as a human artist, you're like, well, nobody wants quality anymore.
Just a shitpost, please.
Just give me something nice and sloppy.
Yeah.
Did you see what I was going to say?
Did you ever watch Community?
No.
I've heard it's good.
I've been meaning to get around to that for years.
You just said about, oh, what comic are you from?
No, I don't think this is even what you were talking about,
but it just reminded me that there's one episode where they do this a lot.
They might do it a bunch, but there's one episode in particular where they have a clip show episode.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Yeah, only all the clip shows, all the episodes that they're supposedly referencing with the clip show are not real episodes.
It's new content that they made in a clip show format,
and so all the characters are like, huh, remember that time when we all had to chip in for the big bake sale,
and then Bryce got poisoned, but poisoned from the banana nut muffins,
and everyone's like, oh yeah, and then they flash back to an episode that never happened.
That's great.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Do that.
I guess.
Can we use a good show?
I also obviously need to do Clarissa because she's still there not being finished.
How's that going?
Well, nothing much.
I haven't worked over the past week, and so it's the same as where it was last time,
which is that I'm at the epilogue in terms of blocking,
and then I need to start inking and sketching the finished drawings for the next chapter, chapter four.
You're at the epilogue, so you finished blocking like the climax and all that.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, wow, okay.
Well, I mean, still looking forward to it.
Still gonna hype for whenever I can finally read it.
Yeah, yeah.
Glad to hear it's still going.
Did you see that I got called unbecoming by a unique name of Sora on Twitter?
Oh, yeah, I saw.
How untoward.
How uncouth.
How unseemly.
How unsightly.
You called a woman a bitch.
I literally called a woman a bitch, and I literally told someone that their art was bad.
I literally did those things.
I'm a literal bad person.
So uncouth, Benzene, so unsightly.
It's so funny.
I don't know.
I mean, I guess I wouldn't expect him to know like me at all.
So like, I guess I can't be like, haha, he doesn't know what I'm like.
But it's just such a funny, it's just such a funny attempt at a gotcha to me like Benzene.
I'm gonna get, you were rude.
You were rude to someone online.
Was it like you were shit talking him, and then they pulled up those as like Benzene.
You said some nasty stuff.
You said some nasty things, so fuck you.
Yeah, I call them a dweeb because he was posting like, okay, I mean, I didn't watch that eight
hour NFT rant, but you know the one.
Yeah.
You know how in that there's like some girl, there's some like artist who like quit Twitter,
and he's sort of is like, honestly, the whole, I mean, I didn't watch it, so I don't know.
But from what the sounds of it, it sounds like the whole video is basically just an excuse
to White Knight for this, for this damsel.
I get the feeling that this all might just be a big weird social thing that like he's like
doing out of some sense of like defending this woman.
Yeah, possibly.
Yeah.
I also haven't seen it.
I remember Cheesy talked about it on the show, but I forget.
Well, I think that lady, I think it was her, made him a piece of fan art for one of his
characters in like a comic that he is trying to get produced or something.
And so he was like, you know, he retweeted the fan art.
He was like, you know, thanks.
He said some stuff and then he made a follow up post that was like, he was waxing all like,
oh, I've made so many sacrifices this year.
I've been trying to do what I think was right.
I'm trying to do the right thing.
You know, it's so hard being a NFT guy, but I do it for the fans.
I do it for the, you know, I do it for the love of the game, you know, and I told him
he was a dweeb.
I said he's being a dweeb.
And I think he didn't know who I was.
So he searched my handle and the word NFTs to find like, what is my NFT take?
I think in doing so he discovered that I am a generally anti NFT person.
And then he found a couple of tweets that he thought made me look bad.
And then he posted them at me and said, you know, you called this, you called the woman
a bitch and you called this other artist.
He said their art was bad.
And the woman that I called it supposedly called a bitch was Sakimi Chan.
And I didn't say like, oh, she's a bitch.
I just referred to her as like this bitch.
And he said this bitch makes like $300,000 a year on Patreon or something.
So it was, it was like hardly even an insult in the way I was using it.
I was just like referring to her as like, oh, this person is disgustingly wealthy.
And now they're doing NFTs on top of all that money that they make.
Yeah.
So I think, I think that's how he put that together.
It's just such a funny thing to even consider doing like, oh, I got a, this guy called me
a dweeb.
I've got to do something about this.
Yeah.
Pretty funny.
I am, I really, I really, I really don't like that guy.
I really, and it's, I really, he's, he's pretty disgusting.
He disgusts me.
I have a lot of contempt for him.
I think he's very pathetic.
I think that his, the weird, I was thinking about it.
It's his, his thing, his NFT take, he's literally, it's worse and it's more off-putting and
it's more like, it's more despicable to me than someone who is just scamming people.
Like someone who like does like a drop and then a rug pull and scams people out of money.
Like at least I understand them.
They're doing it for money.
They're, they're, they're stealing money.
This guy isn't even really doing it.
I mean, he, he is getting some money in support from people that like are like, yes, keep,
keep preaching the good word of NFTs, my brother.
But he's not like, I don't, as far as I can tell, he doesn't sell NFTs.
He doesn't like directly make money off of NFTs.
He just is like ideologically committed to the position that everything should be made
into a monetary transaction.
He just, he just thinks that is a moral good and he's doing it out of that.
Insane worldview.
To me, that's worse than someone who is just a thief who wants money.
Like that's like a true, true brain worms.
It is, it is a bizarre place to draw your line in the sand.
Yeah.
That's why I think it must be like a, like a, like a social thing.
Yeah, yeah.
I think there's some element of like, he is doing this out of some misguided loyalty
to someone and he feels he, the way he was posting is very much like,
I've made a huge fool out of myself, but I did it for love, you know?
Like it could have been saying that.
Fuck you, unique nemosaurus.
You're a little bitch.
You're an even bigger bitch than Tsukimi-chan.
Wow.
Yeah.
Fighting words.
Just despicable.
A truly despicable little worm.
I don't know why I'm getting so, I don't know why I'm getting so annoyed.
Like who cares?
He's irritating.
Just irritating.
What else happened to me this week?
I already mentioned him lifting.
But are you putting it down?
That's the important part.
Oops.
Oh, that's what, a clunk.
Oh, that's better.
Oh, a few.
Maybe that's why I've gotten so little else done, because like the cold weather is so
innervating.
And then like when I am, I have to go walk to the, to Munchie house to do my lifts and
then I gotta walk back and that's just all I can fucking muster under these conditions.
That's all I can do.
Do they have like Christmassy stuff?
No.
I don't think so.
Hmm.
Pretty sus.
I'm getting in that spirit.
It's a whole neighborhood, a whole neighborhood of Scrooge's over here.
Gotta have the colorful lights.
You gotta be like distracted by all of the blinking.
Gotta have athletic fits.
Now, when it gets dark, when it gets dark, I'm gonna like go and look outside just to
make sure I haven't like just not been paying attention.
But yeah, now that you mention it, I feel like I should have seen some lights by now.
And I can't recall seeing any lights.
That's, that's wild.
I can't wait to put lights all over my room because when the main light is off, it is
kind of spooky.
I would like like a big blue something or other or some.
Yeah, actually blue.
I want a blue light.
I want a cool blue or like a warm blue or some sort of a blue.
I'm feeling very blue, not in a sad way.
Yeah.
But I just.
But in like a Dabu-D, Dabu-Dag.
Yeah.
Cool.
Maybe it's because the PS4 like loading screen, home screen is blue and I've been looking
at that.
I was considering buying some like, not just for like decorative purposes.
Like I sort of had an idea that I might make a little bit of, well, it would be, it was
going to be for a slime and punishment related video, like a promo video for that.
But I thought I might buy some like black light.
Like, you know, like, like, you know, like, like string lights, like roll, roll or, well,
you know, like.
Black lights.
Yeah, but they come in a roll and you roll them like along like the corners of your room
to like black light light up your room with.
You know what I mean?
Do you, you mean like Siemens stain black light or is that?
Yes, yes, yes.
I mean, the purple ones that make things.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Isn't that, is that ultraviolet or is that something else?
Well, it was, it wasn't a yes or no question.
Well, you said is that ultraviolet or is that something else?
And the answer is yes, it's.
Something else.
Okay.
No, no, it is.
No, it is ultraviolet.
Oh.
Well, in the low ultra, that's why it's called a black light is because it gives off only
a little bit of visible light and mostly it gives off light in the low ultraviolet spectrum.
I see.
You can't see it unless it is, you know, reflecting off of some sort of fluorescent thing and making
it glow.
Yeah.
Okay.
I didn't realize they were the same thing.
But yeah, that's a cool thing.
Yeah.
So you got that like behind your desk or something?
No, I haven't bought it yet.
I just, I'm just, I might get some.
You, you talking about putting up Christmas lights or made me think, I haven't, I haven't,
I should get those.
Or should I get, I don't know, because I think it, I think a black light effect might be
kind of cool looking in for the slime, a slime and punishment video trailer.
So should I get like track lighting or not track lighting or, you know, like, like a role
of lights to put around like my wall or I could get two little sort of like stand lights
that like sort of provide a like directional black light effect and use them to light a
shot almost like, you know, regular photography lights.
I feel like they wouldn't be quite powerful enough to light an entire shot.
I wouldn't light the shot with them alone.
Definitely.
I would just use them to get like a, honestly, honestly, might not even, if like, if the
shot is lit, if the shot is well lit enough to film, it might be pointless to use a black
light to achieve a fluorescent effect because just the ambient lighting of the shot will
overwhelm the, the fluorescent black light.
Well, maybe you should have, maybe you should lean into the darkness angle.
You get like a black light, like a lamp or whatever, shine it right at your face and
then like put some like weird shit on your teeth that make them glow green and then you
can be like a floating like darkness head and you would say, hey, look at this slime
and the slime is neon and it reflects.
That's a little different than what I was imagining, but like that is an idea and that, that could
be a shot.
That could be a shot for sure.
Yeah.
I'm thinking of the mask you have.
It's like, what if that goes to be real?
Look at your face, you had green glowy teeth for real.
I was wearing that the other day.
I was wearing it.
Well, you wouldn't need to paint them because it reflects like it makes white stuff glow,
right?
A little bit.
It, black light, it can make your teeth glow a little bit.
But not that much.
Even if they're really white and my teeth are not, my teeth are not that white enough
and not that they look like shit.
They look like, like, like they're bad.
I'm ugly.
My teeth are fucked up.
I have to just, I have to kill myself.
I have to end it all.
It's over.
It's over for me.
Don't worry, Ben.
You can come to the UK.
Nobody will know.
Yes.
Oh my God.
I fit right in.
Social societal expectations for teeth are not so strict over here.
It's great.
Yes.
Yay.
Sometimes you can have healthy teeth and they look fucked and some people just can't stand
looking at it.
Yeah.
It's kind of a meme because like the American like super straight, super white gleaming like
block of cheese teeth is like, it's such an American icon.
Yeah.
American advertisements have those teeth everywhere.
I think, you know, yeah, I think, I think the difference is, I mean, I think it's just
an ad thing.
Like I think the difference is not that like we actually look different.
No, but that's the way.
I think it's just that our advertisements like heavily featured.
Advertisements and celebrities.
Yeah.
Which are basically human advertisements.
But that influences the way people feel about it so much.
Yeah.
It's there are sometimes you see, I don't know who it was, but I can I can distinctly remember
not that long ago.
I saw a video clip of like some celebrities in a zoom call and some miners.
I think he might have been a guy who used to be in a in a band or something.
He was like an older guy.
He's like in his sixties, you know, looks like a 60 year old guy.
He's got long gray grayish hair wears glasses, you know, looks like an ex rocker or whatever.
But he had gleaming white teeth and they looked weird.
They stood out and looked like bizarre.
Like they look too good.
They don't.
They definitely don't have pearls.
Beautiful pearls.
Yeah.
They're definitely not real teeth.
They're no noticeably, noticeably like too good for you.
They're too good for you, sir.
Give me those teeth.
You deserve them.
I think I think someone was on Twitter.
So I recently saw someone complaining about like veneers.
They said like they were saying like it's fucked up that people get veneers and like they have
fake teeth basically.
It's fucked up that some people do that to like get teeth that look good, but they don't
look good.
They they they're like it.
Yeah.
I know veneer from like like furnishing.
Well, I think I don't really know the details.
Weird like sticker.
So I think they will basically like file your teeth down and put like fake fronts like fake
fronts on your teeth to have like basically the visible part of your tooth is fake tooth.
And I think people do this.
And then someone replied someone replied saying like I have veneers.
I got them for like a modeling gig.
Like when I was younger, I was wanted to go into modeling and they told me, you know,
you got to get these veneers for your teeth to have perfect teeth.
And I regret doing it.
It doesn't look good, but there's nothing I can do about it now.
So don't change your teeth down.
Fuck.
Yeah.
I think that it's a thing that looks good in photographs, but it may be in real life.
It's when you notice it, it's a bit of like, oh, it looks weird actually.
You know,
Can they just Photoshop the teeth?
Why do you have to do that to them?
Yeah.
I think it's one of those things that like when you when you notice it in real life,
it's a little bit like, oh, it actually looks.
I can't, I can't, I can't stop noticing it now.
I can't, like those are noticeably false teeth.
Yeah.
We've got to bring back little dimples, little red cheeks.
Why?
Did they go somewhere?
I don't know.
I just think you know, like a perfect little oval shape, like face paint on your cheek.
On your cheek.
I have.
Not like blush.
Not like, like, like makeup, but like a little, little spludge, like a cartoon character,
like a Pinocchio.
But you're talking, but you're not talking about makeup.
You're talking about people should just look like that.
People should just look like that.
They should just be that way.
People just don't look like, yeah.
People don't look like Pinocchio anymore.
People don't look like garden gnomes.
It's fucked up.
People don't look like garden.
Damn.
We have to go back.
On my day, people looked like fucked up garden gnomes.
Nobody, nobody is like hanging out in, under a mushroom, like hanging out, like sitting
on a, on a frog's back, smoking a corn cob pipe anymore.
Yeah.
Where are those people gone?
Genuinely, where did they go?
They live in your garden.
Oh yeah.
There they are.
You ever watched David the Gnome?
No.
Do you know what that is?
I assume it's a gnome.
I kind of thought it was maybe a British thing, but yeah.
It was a cartoon.
I think it was on PBS.
I sometimes watched it as a kid.
Yeah.
It was about David the Gnome and he's a little like gnome.
He's an old like, little gnome guy who just, he's a gnome.
And he's has a little gnome wife and he lives in a little gnome community and these trolls
are always out to get him, but the trolls will turn to stone.
They can only come out at night and they turn to stone in the sunlight and that's the trolls
deal.
And I couldn't, I don't remember anything that I don't remember any episodes.
I guess he, he gets, I assume he must get chased by trolls at some point and I don't know
that's like all I remember.
And him and his wife do the little nose-nuzzling Eskimo kisses.
That's how they make out.
Whoa.
David the Gnome, originally titled David El Gnomo.
No.
Is a Spanish animated television series.
You're fucking shitting me.
You're shitting me right now.
It's Spanish animated.
Really?
Wow.
Based on the children's book, The Secret Book of Gnomes by the Dutch author Wil Huygen.
David El Gnomo.
What the fuck?
Okay.
That's funny.
I don't know that.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
I used to see it on PBS.
Tiny Ancient Gnomes.
Wait, wait, wait.
The plot synopsis on Google.
What the fuck?
The plot synopsis on Google is tiny ancient gnomes perform feats of strength.
Whoa.
It is.
What the fuck?
Why does it say that?
I don't know.
I don't remember them performing any mighty feats of strength, but maybe they did.
I don't remember.
David El Gnomo.
Where did they draw that from?
I remember him riding a fox.
He rides a fox.
See, I was thinking of this other thing, but it probably sucks.
Yeah.
He doesn't have a mustache.
It's a gnome cartoon, not 80s, much, probably 2000s.
I think I've seen a couple episodes of, okay, this is a baby show, actually.
Gordon the Garden gnome.
Never heard of that.
Slightly different.
I'm looking up episodes.
There's one called The Little Sorcerer.
What's this one?
Who would win in a fight?
David.
David would win in a fight.
Look at that guy.
He performs feats of strength.
He's an ancient gnome who performs feats of strength.
I mean, I think he is supposed to be hundreds of years old.
Is he super strong?
I don't remember him being super strong, but maybe he is really strong.
I mean, I'm looking at a picture of him with his fists up.
He's going to punch something.
He's going to fist a cuffs.
He's going to fist a cuffs those goblins, those trolls.
Yeah, I've seen this screenshot of him with the fists up.
I've seen this used as a reaction image.
Yeah, there should be more gnome shows.
Yeah, bring back gnomes.
Where did they go?
When magic died, they all retreated underground to await.
Less beautiful pearly white teeth, more garden gnomes.
David would never get veneers.
You can't see him.
He's got a mustache in the way.
He's just let his teeth fall out.
He doesn't need them.
You don't need teeth to eat those overnight oats.
Not if you let him sit for the full eight hours while you watch the Mega Man lecture.
I mean, he's so small he only has an overnight oat.
I went to Trader Joe's to get some oats, but they didn't have quick oats.
They only had rolled oats, which are quicker than steel cut oats, but they're not instant.
They're not the instant quick oats, which are rolled oats just cut smaller and rolled even more.
So, I mean, they're fine. They worked okay.
But there's a little...
They couldn't just roll them a little more for me?
Rolled them a little more and chopped them a little bit more?
Make them quick?
You got to do the last little bit of rolling and chopping yourself.
Please, Joe. Please.
So, you can feel like a chef.
Please, Joe, I'll trade you some more money to process my oats a little bit more.
Just a little bit more.
More like Trader Joe's.
More like, thank you. Thank you.
So, I'm afraid that I'm going to take my business elsewhere.
I'm afraid I'm going to take my oat business to Aldi for Millville's quick oats.
Okay?
I'm a busy guy.
I need my oats quick eight hours from now.
So, that's the...
I'm sorry.
That's just the market.
I'm just responding to market forces.
You know who else is just responding to market forces?
No.
I was reading...
I had a little Twitter interaction with Umami.
You know Umami, the interface guy?
No.
You've ever seen that?
Well, he's an animator and I think he does music too.
He does these very...
What do you call them?
Well, they're cartoons.
You would recognize the character.
I may not recognize the user name.
Yeah.
The most recognizable character is this weird monster clown.
Now, Dr. Light, now there's a gnome.
Oh, I thought that was you posting.
No.
Oh, it's Twitch.
He's Dr. Light posting.
He's Light posting.
Just a little Light posting.
This guy.
Oh, yeah, I remember.
I watched one of the early videos of this character on the left.
Yeah.
I don't really know.
I'm not really sure what to think of Umami because he...
I know he sold NFTs.
I know he sold some NFTs.
And he's pro AI art.
But I don't know if he's like a blockchain guy.
I don't know if he is like a Web3 is the future.
Like everything should be on the blockchain guy.
Or if he was just like...
Did it to make some money?
I don't know.
I looked at his Twitter feed and all he posts about is some bill that is passing through Canadian Congress right now.
And I don't know what that's about.
So I ignored it.
Uh...
I know Umami, he follows Elon Musk.
But that doesn't necessarily mean that he likes Elon.
So I don't want to jump to any conclusions.
Yeah, I guess not.
I don't know.
I would generally default to like...
Probably they know and enjoy crypto if they're like selling NFTs.
But there's lots of people who have just been like, oh, is this the new thing?
Okay, I'll do it.
I don't know exactly.
It really becomes a problem when they double down and start like...
If somebody tells them, oh, you shouldn't do that.
And then they say, um, fuck you.
And then they burn bridges and start going crazy.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't want to like...
I think where I'm at with it is like...
I don't think I believe in like blaming the consumer.
And I feel like...
You know, when Sakimi-chan makes NFTs, it's like Sakimi-chan already makes like hundreds of thousands of dollars on Patreon.
Sakimi-chan is already like absurdly wealthy.
And she's doing these NFTs and it's just making like an even more obscene amount of money.
And probably minting like, you know, huge sets of them, minting tons of them.
And just churning through it, right?
This guy, Umami is not...
You know, he makes like a couple thousands a month on Patreon.
He's like, you know, he's somewhat successful, but he's not like a huge celebrity.
He's not super wealthy, I'm sure.
I don't know.
The evil of the blockchain and the evil of NFTs, to me, is on the people that like made it.
And the grift of like, we must force artists to mint on our chain.
They must pay us for access to the chain.
Yeah, it's a bunch of middlemen.
Well, I don't like it when people participate in that system.
You know, in the past, I've said like, you know, the artists that make it, you know, they're getting scammed.
The scam is on them because generally they will...
Most artists that do that will not recoup the investment of minting the NFT.
So I think I don't think I can be like, oh, this guy's bad because he made some NFTs.
Even if he sold them and he did make a profit on them because like, I don't know.
I don't think that's where the fault lies.
No.
This guy seems pretty smart.
Umami seems pretty smart.
I haven't seen him say like, everything should be on...
Everything should be Webpoint 3.
Everything should be on the blockchain or anything like that.
He seems weird.
I don't know.
He's got...
He's involved in all these Canadian politics that I can't be bothered to understand.
So I have to reserve my judgment.
I don't know.
Somebody was complaining.
This guy Grums.
This guy Grums posted some artists' art and basically implied that the artist had used
AI to color it.
I don't even...
Grums is an asshole.
I hate Grums.
But he had posted some art and been like...
He said something about AI in a way that implied that this person had not drawn it himself.
And this person said like, yo, Grums like posted my art and like said this stuff about it.
And it's not true.
And Umami replied to that thread saying like, you know, if he's posting your art without
your consent, you know, instead of reporting him on Twitter, you should file a DMCA.
You should use copyright law.
And people dog piled on Umami and people said like, fuck you, Umami.
You're an NFT guy.
You're a blockchain guy.
You're a crypto shill.
You love AI art.
You hate artists.
You just hate artists.
You just hate artists, Umami, because you think that AI is okay.
It's going to take our jobs, Umami.
It's going to take our jobs and you hate us.
And I just think that's stupid.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem like an appropriate response to that post.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
I didn't feel like it was appropriate.
I think, I think, I don't know.
I think AI is good, but capitalism is bad.
Yeah.
I mean, that's, I remember we had a conversation.
I guess eventually boiled down to that is like, as a tool, it's cool.
But as a mule, it's drool.
It could not have said it better myself.
I saw, um, I saw Harry Partridge, you know, Harry Partridge.
Yeah.
He posted on someone, some other person said something about, you know, AI is bad.
It's going to take our jobs or maybe it wasn't.
It was something about AI bad.
And then Harry Partridge posted under that.
He said, well, you know, I'm, I'm an artist and I used, I used AI to generate like some
backgrounds in my animation, you know, as a labor saving measure to, you know, to make
my freaking cartoons.
So, you know,
Yeah.
That's a lot of work into those.
He sure does.
Yeah.
Billions.
I haven't, I haven't watched a cartoon of his in a while.
I guess he's been working on star variants for a really long time, hasn't he?
Yeah.
I don't know if I'm subscribed or if he just hasn't uploaded a million years.
But yeah, star variants is the last thing I remember.
I think he's been doing like commission work on the side while he works on star variants
like on his own, you know?
Yeah.
It like, oh, kind of like that.
Did you see that video, that atrocity guide video about that Russian animator that was
making that?
Well, I say it's actually a husband and wife team, even though the husband is like a lot
more famous, even though you shouldn't be, but they're, they're right.
No, I haven't seen that video.
Okay.
Well, yeah, there's a video by atrocity guy and I don't remember what their name is
because their name's in Russian and I don't know, but they make these, you know how Russian
animation has like a sort of different, it's almost like a South Park sort of like paper
cutouts moving around kind of.
Yeah, it's popular.
Yeah.
Well, they, they were making like pretty much like the most, the most like finely detailed
and meticulous version of that, like anyone has ever seen atrocity guide Russian animator.
I'm sure this will, I'm sure this will turn up.
Okay.
Well, the video is just called the animators who spent 40 years on a single film.
And, and basically, I think they slow as fuck.
They slow, they slow as fuck.
And I think during this 40 years, like they've continued to work on this movie that they're
making, but also they've done, they do like, they've done, they do like commercials and
stuff like they do, they do other commissioned animation work on the side, you know, to fund
this fucking thing they've spent 40 years making.
The overcar.
Bombs at the box surface.
At this point, it seems like the point isn't even to release.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
At 40 years, it stops being about like, oh, what if, what if, what if it's going to be
a big return on investment?
It's going to be a huge, we're going to, yeah, the returns are going to be, this is going
to fund our next project.
We're not going to get like 40 years worth of pay for one film.
No, no.
Let's stop like 29% in.
Yeah, the best time to stop making this movie was 40 years ago.
The second best time is now.
That's mean.
I mean, obviously it's not, yeah, it's not about making tons of money at the box office
at this point.
No, that's, I would like to see it though.
This is a good video and I generally like the Atrocity Guide channel.
They don't, they don't release.
I like that Atrocity Guide.
The Atrocity, oh, the Atrocity Guide.
Oh yeah, I saw him.
Oh, I loved your work in the Nuremberg Trials, sir.
How did, how did I get on this?
Something about the cell shaded, the cell animation?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, was it something about Harry Partridge and how like meticulous his work is and how
many, how many in-betweens?
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't like that.
Like he's spent years working on this, these Starbarians cartoons.
And meanwhile he, you know, does like some commission commercial work on the side to
keep himself feeding.
So do people, do people share on him for him saying?
No, I didn't see, I didn't see any responses to that.
That was like a, that was like a reply tweet.
So it wasn't like a public like on his main timeline.
So I don't know if anyone even really, I just happened to see that and I just responded
to it.
I just like gave it a like and was like, yeah, man.
It's good to automate.
Automation's good.
And he didn't, he didn't like my, he didn't like my reply.
He didn't see me.
He didn't notice me.
That feel when you stick your neck out and like someone's tweet and they don't even like
it.
They don't even, they don't even courtesy like my reply.
It's not fair.
Harry Partridge is a Chris Chan fan.
He should have seen my lecture by now.
He should know me.
Maybe.
He is cause he's put, he's put, he's years and years ago.
He was putting like Chris Chan in like a secret like frames.
He was like, where's Waldo and Chris Chan into certain like crowd shots?
I guess he's not doing that anymore.
Probably, probably not.
Probably not.
Yeah.
I don't think so.
Now he's putting them in the foreground.
Put them in.
Yeah.
True, true.
How do I get on this?
Yes.
The point is artists are obsolete.
AI is the future.
We don't need human artists anymore.
You know who, you know who I hope is rendered obsolete by artists?
That bitch, that bitch, Sakimi Chan.
You know what?
Her work is, should be the first to go because her work is garbage.
Her work is a completely rote exercise in technical expertise and nothing more.
The exact sort of thing that a computer should be designed to render obsolete,
to make a human unnecessary for.
So, you know, bring it up.
What do they draw?
Do they draw like anime?
Oh, you don't know.
Sakimi Chan.
We, oh, you don't know.
You don't know who Sakimi Chan is.
I may have seen some of their stuff before.
Do they draw frozen characters?
Yeah, yes.
But like render them a lot?
Yes, they do.
Well, they do.
In general, they do anime characters or just popular cartoon characters,
but they draw them like very anime, very like realistically detailed like body,
like abs, you know, very like glamour shot, like beauty shots with sort of like anime,
like feathery backgrounds and like glowy like effects around them and stuff.
They do very, very like extremely like hyper, hyper, what's the word?
Hyper idealized, but also sort of like photo realistic detail, like beauty shots of anime
characters.
It's like Shadman.
No?
I just thought I was thinking of.
No, not me.
No, what the fuck are you talking about?
I'm just thinking of the way Shadman just adds like a little realistic stuff.
How did that?
Realistic stuff.
How the fuck did that description that I just evoked?
How did that conjure Shadman?
Shadman.
They put a lot of realistic things into their art.
You're a freak.
Shadman stuff is like dirty.
All Shadman's drawings feel like dirty and smelly.
I didn't say they weren't.
Okay.
All right.
That's just what I was imagining.
Like frozen character, whatever.
Okay.
That's very funny, but no.
I'll show you what I'll show you what I'm talking about.
I mean, let's let's just do a quick Google search for, yeah.
Okay.
Um, stuff like this.
Yeah.
Or stuff like, uh, or stuff like this.
And anyway, anyway, they do these.
I mean, genuinely, these look like they were drawn by an AI to me.
Um, but yeah.
Kimi Chan makes like, makes like $30,000 a month on Patreon because she not, she doesn't
just draw these, but she uploads like, uh, uh, what do you call them?
Um, like time lapse with like sort of tutorials, right?
She does like, he's like, you can learn how to draw like me.
Uh, I see.
Yeah.
And honestly, this stuff is so unappealing to my sensibilities that like, I've like,
why would you want to learn to draw like this?
But I guess to a lot, I'll say it, I'll say it.
I guess to a lot of people that don't know shit about art and have no aesthetic sensibilities
at all, they see this as like, I can, I can imagine someone who sees something like this
as like the pinnacle of, of visual, of visual artistry.
And they're like, yeah, if I could draw like that.
Oh yeah.
That's the stuff.
Yeah.
There's a, it's, it's, um, uh, what is it?
Like, like, uh, drawing, not tutorials, but time lapses.
Yeah.
Time lapses of, of somebody drawing an eye, realistic, super realism eye drawing.
This is the, this is the anime version of like, oh, you drew, you like, you perfectly did
like a pencil, you basically were a human photocopier and you did a pencil sketch that exactly
duplicated a photograph of a person.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's like technically impressive because people know what, people generally know that when
you put a pencil on a paper, it makes a line.
But then when somebody can put lines in such a way that it looks like a photograph, their
mind is blown.
But that's like the very first, like the very like first thing you understand about art
is that you can make things, uh, with, with drawing.
And once you become good at art, you realize it's, it's not very interesting actually to
see that over and over again.
You perfectly copied this photograph with a pencil.
Dude, you're going to make the camera obsolete, bro.
Like we don't even need cameras anymore because we got you.
Yo, let's go.
Let's fucking go.
Yeah.
That's, oh man.
It's, yeah.
So Sakimi, Sakimi-chan is such a good artist.
She's going to put the AI out of business.
You know, just like John Henry was so good, he was such a good rail worker that he, he,
he defeated the, he defeated the steam engine.
He made the steam engine obsolete.
You know what I'm fucking talking about?
Yeah.
Like Shadman, right?
Yes.
That's what I'm saying.
It's just like Shadman.
I can see why this gets lots of likes though.
It's sexual in nature.
It's, it's anime and it looks realistic.
It's a very broad demographic.
I get it.
It's appealing too.
In a, in a way that is.
I get it.
Spits.
Yes.
But I called, but I called her a bitch and I shouldn't have, I shouldn't have said that.
I shouldn't, shouldn't have used the B word.
I should never have used the B word.
This, this, you know what?
This person's just responding to market forces.
You know what?
It's our fault that people give her a million dollars a year to produce this dog shit.
What were we even talking about?
What are you, what's going on?
What's going on?
We're talking about.
We're in an hour 40.
Wow.
The time, the time flies.
We're talking about how I'm the best artist.
Yeah.
Because I don't do, draw anything good.
I draw it bad.
Yeah.
And that's what I like.
And not rendered.
Rendering sucks.
True.
You spend hours upon hours.
The less you render the better it is.
And then it's like, it's like, what, what, what am I, what am I fighting for?
You know?
What am I fighting for?
Right.
That's it.
That's all I got.
I, you know what?
It's good, good thing I stopped drawing.
Good thing I don't draw anymore.
Now I can get a computer to do it for me.
Suckers.
You know what I don't like?
All these nerds still drawn.
Yeah.
What's that?
About AI art is that it's not truly accessible yet.
I can't go Googling and finding a thing that generates something I actually want to see.
And so I'm like, fine, I'll fucking draw it.
You stupid idiot.
Don't understand my prompts.
Yeah.
I don't know.
There's like, yeah, there's, there's a bunch of different, there's a bunch of different programs that do it.
And they're all a little bit different.
And some of them are like, you have to pay to access them.
And.
Yeah.
Unless it's all very.
As soon as you have to pay to access them, I'm like, well, I already have my tablet.
I don't have to pay any more money for that.
So I'll just make it.
It's easier.
Yeah.
You know, I looked up the Wikipedia article for stable diffusion.
Just because I was like kind of curious, like, what does that mean exactly?
And, you know, surprise, surprise, it was too complicated and I didn't understand it.
Yeah.
I try to watch a video or two, like science, maths, YouTubers trying to explain the science behind AI generated imagery.
And they just, they just died.
I can't do it.
Yeah.
I, I think it, I would like to know.
I just, I saw some diagrams and I was like, Oh God, this, I'd have to like, I'd actually have to like really commit to like understand this stuff.
Let me find the diagram I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Like this one.
Oh, that's how it works.
Oh, that's how they do.
Okay.
Diffusion process.
I got you.
The nosing unit eel.
Q, uh, fucking what?
Oh, condition arrows.
Oh, the conditioning includes the semantic map and the text and the representations and the images I see.
And they go all into the key, which goes into all of these KVs and then loops back around to that other fucking thing.
Yeah, I get it.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, child's play, child's play.
I am, damn it.
What, what, what Greek symbol is that?
It really does be that computers is smarter than us.
It really does be that way.
Yeah.
I mean, they're, they're, I mean, they're, in terms of like doing a large number of calculations over and over again.
Like, yeah, they'll, they'll, uh, they'll beat us every time for sure.
Maybe they should have computers, uh, doing all the jobs.
But they can't come up, but they can't come up with, they can't come up with a good idea for what, for what calculations to perform to provide useful information.
We have to do that.
Uh, that's too hard.
For now.
Can they do that instead?
Um, maybe we can AI, maybe they can, not yet, but maybe with machine learning, they can, they can learn to come up with good ideas for us.
Yes.
Then I won't have to move.
Then I will have to just lay here.
Mm-hmm.
Oh yeah.
Uh, oh yeah.
We're headed towards that wally future.
I can, I can, I can give up, uh, doing anything and then I could just fuck.
That'll be all I do.
That's my human thing.
Mm-hmm.
No more thinking.
The computer does it.
Oh, it's just like that bad religion song.
I love my computer.
It's just like that.
That's a nerd song if I ever heard one.
It's a good song.
Uh, I went to the bank the other day to get a check for my shitty landlord who I hope will be in jail very soon.
Um, and I said, I said, I said to the teller, I said, it's just like that movie.
You know the one.
It's just like that movie.
And she said, no.
I don't know.
In what context did you say this?
Okay, okay, sorry.
I skipped it.
Like you go to the bank and you just say that's the first thing comes out of your mouth.
No.
It's just like that movie when they go to the bank.
I was just, I was getting my cashier's check and she was talking to some other teller or someone else behind the desk and they were like, can we get, they were like, can we get, they were like, can we move 20,000 so and so.
And I was like, just listening.
And then I think they said, like, I think she apologized to me.
She said, like, sorry, you know, it's the holidays.
Everyone's, everyone's take, everyone's withdrawing their money.
And I said, it's just like that movie.
It's just like that movie.
You know the one.
Ocean's Eleven.
And she was, and she was like, no, I don't know.
I couldn't, and then I couldn't think of it.
I was like, wait, shit.
I forget the name in the movie.
The movie I was talking about was, it's a wonderful life.
Oh.
Because, because, because, I mean, you know, the plot of that movie is that, yeah, it's for the holidays, everybody comes to withdraw their money from the credit union or whatever.
Yeah.
And I said, you know, and I thought it's like, oh yeah, yeah.
I said, it's just like, it's a wonderful life.
It's Christmas time.
There's a run on the bank.
And then everyone learns the joys of communism.
That's what I said.
And then, and then we, and then she gave me my cashier's check and I left.
I left the bank.
It sure was just like that movie.
It was.
It was just like that movie.
And she should have known.
She works at a bank.
She should be thinking about bank movies.
She should have been like, what movies do I know that have a bank in them?
I know.
It's a wonderful life.
You know what?
She had an accent.
She was probably from like some other country.
So she probably where they don't have banks.
They don't have movies or wonderful lives.
They don't have wonderful lives in, in, in Argentina.
So she was not familiar with the, with the source material.
Apologies.
Apologies to the Argentinian in the audience.
Well, Argentina is a cool name.
You know what it means?
Uh, it's, uh, no.
White.
Uh, what?
But it's so far down.
Um, Argent, it's like, it's like in heraldry, in heraldry.
Oh.
A field, a field Argent.
A field Argent is white or silver.
They had the Argentine crusade in World of Warcraft.
Yes.
And then so Argentina, I guess it means like.
White Tina.
Does it mean like, would you, would you translate it as like white place or like white land?
I guess you would.
I guess so.
I guess that's what we're going with.
Is fucking, is the capital Montevideo is that the other one?
Oh, I don't remember.
I remember learning about Montevideo, which is a city bordering Argentina or maybe in
Argentina.
That's a cool city.
It's got a lot of history.
What if it was Montenegro?
That would be somewhere else.
You idiot.
I know.
But what if Montenegro was in Argentina and then it was Black Mountain in white land?
Hmm.
That would be pretty cool.
What do we think?
That would be crazy.
Wouldn't that be crazy?
Okay.
Anyway.
That's all I have to say.
And then the gray line.
The gray line is where.
The thin gray line, the thin gray line separating.
Yeah.
Law from, law from chaos.
That's where you get gravel.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Maybe they have a lot of white rock in Argentina.
Maybe that's why.
I wonder, I wonder if it is meant to refer to the landscape.
Like chalky something or other.
I mean, they have, they have mountains.
Maybe they means like, maybe it's like reference to like white snow capped mountains.
Could be.
There's mountains all over the place though.
Argentina is like, there's that mountain range between Argentina and Chile, right?
Like on the, on the west coasts of South America.
West.
Yeah.
That's my best guess.
It's either that or maybe there's like a desert.
Maybe there's like a desert plain that's very pale.
Argentina.
Wikipedia.
I'm going to go to the etymology.
Yeah.
In English, the name Argentina comes from Spanish language.
The name itself is not Spanish, but Italian Argentina means made of silver or silver colored.
Hmm.
Divided from the Latin Argentum for silver.
Okay.
So maybe there's a lot of silver there.
That's probably.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, I know in heraldry, it means silver or white.
So yeah.
Okay.
That's fair.
Isn't the chemical, isn't the chemical symbol on the periodic table for silver?
Is it like AR or something like that?
Gold is AU.
It could be.
Gold is silver.
I think silver is something similar.
Argentina was first associated with the Silver Mountains legend.
AG.
Silver Mountains legend widespread among first European explorers.
But why did they name it Argentina?
Was it because of the legend?
Sorry.
I missed it.
There's a legend.
What?
White spread among first European explorers.
Let's click on that page.
Silver Mountains of Silver.
This is just like the fun fact bonus episode.
Yeah.
This is something I enjoy doing.
Sierra de la Plata, Mountain of Silver was a mythical source of silver in the interior
of South America.
The legend began in the early 16th century when castaways from Juan Diaz de Solis, a
bad accent, expedition heard indigenous stories of a mountain of silver in an inland region
ruled by the so-called White King.
First European to lead expedition to search of it.
In search of it was the castaway Alexio Garcia, who crossed nearly the entire continent to
reach the Andean Altiplano.
Altiplano.
He died.
A high plane.
Yeah, something.
On his way back to the coast, Garcia died in an ambush by indigenous people in Paraguay.
It was brought precious metals back to corroborate the story.
Okay, so it's a silver rush instead of a gold rush.
This is just like the Aztec city of gold, but like a little more humble.
A little bit.
It's not gold.
It's just silver.
And it's not like a city.
It's just kind of like a mountain.
There's just kind of like a big pile of it.
But it's like, it's still pretty good.
It's still pretty good.
I want to read the rest of this, but it's going to take a while.
I actually, I'm going to go get some more coffee, so I'll be back in a minute.
Okay, I'm back.
Okay, I read a little bit more.
Tell me what you've learned.
As coding to this Wikipedia article on the Sierra de la Plata, the river Rio de la Plata,
literally silver river and the country of Argentina from the Latin Argentine.
This theme is boring.
You know what?
This is bad world building.
It appears way too closely to this silver theme like, oh, the silver city and the silver mountain.
It's the silver river.
They both take their names from the legends.
So that is, as far as I know, proof or like at least enough proof for me to be like, that makes sense.
Argentina is based on legends of silver and then our hills.
All right.
And that's it, which is pretty cool.
Pretty cool.
Pretty strong.
I want to know more about this.
Pretty strong theme.
Pretty strong theming.
I want to know more about the indigenous stories of the mountain of silver ruled by the so-called white king.
There's no page for this.
I want to know about that.
That sounds pretty epic.
Sounds pretty epic.
Not going to lie.
There's no page for the indigenous stories.
Should have called them the Pale King.
They should have called them the Pale King.
Yes.
Like that video game.
Or that book, the unfinished last book of David Foster Wallace was called the Pale King.
This episode is going to be called AI and Argentina.
What's the capital of Argentina?
I don't know.
I'm trying to Google.
I'm trying to like word search.
It's a capital capital.
I'll be impressed if you were right and it is Montevideo.
It's Buenos Aires.
I know that one.
Okay.
What is Montevideo then?
Buenos Aires has an endless war.
Oh, hell yeah.
You Google it and the first thing you see is a big obelisk.
So, I mean, that's pretty cool.
Pretty, pretty sweet.
Montevideo, Uruguay is capital.
There's a major city alongside Montevideo Bay.
Who even gives a shit about Uruguay?
Me.
False.
It's my favorite place to be.
No, you don't.
Fuck it, you're lying.
I learned about it one day when I was Wikipedia diving.
Let me...
Oh, yeah?
Well, let me tell you something, buddy.
What?
I tried a new frozen pizza this week.
Great.
No, it was bad.
It was bad.
It was worse.
I'm here.
All right.
Did I...
Did I stop me if I told this one before?
But that lady I follow on Twitter,
Lauren from the Batten Around podcast.
I don't listen to the podcast.
I just follow her on Twitter.
She got banned, something, something, Elon Musk.
She got...
Lauren, at not a big jerk, got banned on Twitter.
Only a week or two after she had recommended
the Kirkland Supreme cauliflower crust frozen pizza,
which I tried and it was good.
But then she got banned before, so I couldn't tell her.
I couldn't tell her.
I tried the Kirkland pizza.
I saw you get mad about that on Twitter or sad about that.
I was like, I just wanted to tell her thanks for the pizza recommendation.
And then she came back.
She has a new account.
She didn't come back.
She had a new account.
I think her old one actually got reinstated,
so that's also good.
But I told her, hey, I tried that pizza.
It was good.
Not specifically related to that, though.
I tried...
I had the Wegmans bacon rise.
The Wegmans bacon rise pizzas are pretty good.
But I tried an alternative from Aldi.
The Aldi alternative is the Mamakotzi.
The Mamakotzi, I forget exactly what they're called,
but whatever, it's the same like the thick crust,
like rising dough, pepperoni pizza.
And it's like the same but worse.
And it's worse because it has this like,
this very faint sort of ineffable,
sort of like sweet, almost like cinnamony,
like smell or quality to the dough.
And I just find it very off-putting.
I find it like, it's barely there,
but it's just enough there that I'm like,
if it weren't there, it would be fine.
But it's like they made this dough
out of like what they had left over at like
the cinnamon roll factory or something.
And it's just, it only detracts.
The only sugar you should have in dough
is just from the white flour.
The sugar shouldn't feel sweet,
but it should have that nice white bread flour.
And then it burns a bit.
It's not sweet.
It's not like really sweet.
It's just like sort of like an aroma.
It's just kind of like an aromatic sort of like sensation.
It doesn't actually taste like cinnamon.
It doesn't taste sweet.
It's like a smell.
It gives me enough of the sense
that I'm like, I don't know, this is something a little off.
The flavor is a little bit off.
Most of taste is in the smell, I think.
They're so closely connected.
It's sort of weird when it smells like something
and it doesn't taste like it.
It's like the first time you drink coffee.
Like what?
I thought it would taste better than that.
It smells so good.
Yeah, you're right.
It smells way better than it tastes.
When I was a kid, I used to love to sniff the grounds.
I used to love to take that coffee can.
My parents would make coffee.
I didn't like to drink it, but I would put my nose in the can
and smell the unbrewed grounds because they're amazing.
They smell incredible.
And then as an adult, why do I drink it?
Why do people drink it when it smells so good?
Just huff it.
Oh, just smell it.
I think I've heard of people just like putting the grounds in their mouth.
Like chewing the grounds or like putting it under their tongue or something.
I don't know if it like, that might be like a joke, actually.
I don't know if anyone actually does that.
They just got really hot saliva and they cook it in their mouth.
Gross, gross, gross.
Then they spit it into someone else's mouth and then they drink it.
Genuinely, I have switched to drinking coffee solely because it is cheaper.
It's a cheaper source of caffeine to brew coffee and drink it
than it is to drink energy drinks or to take caffeine pills.
Really?
Like straight caffeine is in like pure caffeine is more expensive
than the same amount of caffeine in a coffee.
I think, well, you know, you know, actually, I wonder,
I should do like, I should do some calculations and compare like,
how many total milligrams of caffeine do I get in like an entire can
of coffee grounds versus like a little bottle of like pills
and then like compare the price tag.
Like it might be more expensive overall, but it's probably nicer.
What, the pills?
No, the coffee.
Because you're also having a nice drink, a nice warm drink.
I mean, honestly, I'd rather drink it in energy drink form.
I'd rather slam a summit gridlock.
But I mean, price to, price to Grammage wise,
I'm pretty sure that one is the loser.
Even though, even, even at the low, low price of $1.05 per can,
it's still, you know, you know.
I don't know.
I'm, I don't know about coffee or caffeine.
I just drink it because I'm stupid and I got addicted.
Well, I'm getting, I'm getting all my threats a little getting closed up
because I've been speaking so much.
Well, is it time for me to read one piece?
Oh, fuck.
Okay, yes.
All right.
Spoiler warning for the latest one piece chapter.
Chapter 1069.
The desire of all things are born to this world.
Okay.
An emotionless voyage.
Dufeld's charitable work, the Research Institute of Peace,
Mads, presented by Lou Feld.
I don't.
Pesifist.
I don't know what this is.
I feel like is this last week.
There was a cover page with Caesar Clown and Judge.
Yeah.
And then they were about to like reminisce about something.
And I think this is what they're thinking about.
Oh.
So this is a new character and a new thing.
And it's like, ah, remember the good old days with Mads?
They used to be Pesifist, I guess.
They used to be researching science for good.
And then I guess they turned evil because of war.
Is Mads related to, isn't SADs like something to do with those fake fruits?
It's just SAD.
SAD.
Yeah.
And the smile.
I forget which one's which, but like there's the SAD SAD in Punk Hazard.
And that gets turned into, yeah, it gets transported.
The SAD gets transported to fucking Doflamingo's haunt.
What was that called?
That whole place?
Dressrosa.
The factory, the smile factory in Dressrosa where they made the smile devil fruits.
The Kaido would commission from Doflamingo.
Yeah.
So what is SAD?
I forget.
It's one of those like big science things.
Is it something to do with those giant kids?
I definitely, like Caesar was doing experiments on those kids for Big Mom.
And I think he was also making the SAD for Kaido, for Doflamingo.
But I don't know whether the SAD is related to the kids.
There probably is.
There's just one big factory that's probably like, when you tell the story where there's
giant kids in a weird factory, it's probably going to be related.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
I don't know.
Mads makes me think of SAD.
They might have actually nothing to do with each other.
Who knows?
They probably would because like if Caesar clown is reminiscing about it.
Yeah.
And then he's like, he went on to do the SAD and the smile stuff.
Probably not by himself, but certainly in evolving.
Commenters, let me know in the comments what is, remind me what SAD is.
I don't want, I don't feel like looking it up.
Maybe this Mads thing is like the Rocks Pirates.
That's what I was thinking.
I was thinking, is this somehow, is this related to the Rocks Pirates somehow?
That's what it makes me think of.
These are like their own crews.
So like Judge was a scientist.
Caesar clown, vagabunk.
Who else is a scientist?
No one.
That's the only ones.
But they all came from this really, really tall ship that's obviously going to fall over.
It's so obviously going to fall over.
It's so silly.
Oh.
Did Rob Lucci kill the big vagabunk girl?
Looks like her head, it almost looked like her head's like blown in half.
It could just be smoke coming out.
It's kind of hard to tell.
I mean, she could probably be repaired because she's a robot.
Oh yeah.
That's true.
Right, right.
They're probably robots.
Yeah.
Tell me when you have a comment and we can talk about whatever is happening.
Probably about a quarter through it.
Who the hell is this guy?
He's got a bit of a neck.
Big long neck and a beard?
And like, is that like a flame tattoo on his neck?
Yeah, I don't recognize him.
He might have been a background like Vice Admiral or something.
This guy talking to not Al Kiji.
Who's that?
Akainu.
Akainu, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I see.
I saw this on Twitter actually this week.
I remember this, the awakened form of the leopard fruit.
Yeah.
This is interesting.
I mean, I, he's got this like black cloud.
I mean, it reminds me of Luffy's.
Gear four.
Is, is gear five, right?
Is the, the, the white one?
Gear five is the white one.
But, but gear fourth is when he has those, those multiple different forms of gear fourth
where he's really fast and he's got that sort of like black flame or something around him.
It doesn't, wasn't it, I was thinking, I'm thinking of gear five.
He has like sort of the white like sort of cloud wreath.
He does, but I think also in gear fourth, let me just Google that.
Oh yeah, in anime, it's like depicted a steam, but in the, yeah, it is a steam.
So it's sort of like white clouds.
Yeah.
Oh, it's his tattoos.
He's got like a weird like hacky sort of flame pattern on his arms.
You're talking about Rob?
And gear fourth and Luffy.
Okay.
And he's got like steam coming off him in a cloudy sort of shape that sort of is reminiscent
of some sort of Japanese thing.
Can you post it?
Can you post an image?
Yeah, let me find a good one.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, he does have the, yeah, he's got the steam.
Right.
He's got the like the hockey arms and it's sort of like kind of extends onto his body.
Yeah.
And this 3D little figurine, you can tell that's the, do you know what that is?
Like a, like a, some sort of Japanese spirit like thing.
What the cloud?
I feel like I've seen like some sort of a classic Japanese design of a spirit of some
kind that has like the thing going around the arms like that and the back of the head.
The figurative reminds me of Enel's like thing that comes off his back.
You know what I'm talking about?
A little bit.
He has like the ring that sort of comes off of his shoulders and has like the like little,
the little drums on it.
You know what I mean?
Oh yeah, a little.
Yeah, yeah, I remember that.
Might, that's what reminds me of it.
I don't know if that has any relation.
Okay.
I'm reading.
There's no record of the gum gum, no me written in the old devil fruit encyclopedia at all.
Even.
Oh, okay.
Cause it's not that.
It's not a rubber.
The form looks exactly like the God mentioned in the ancient documents.
Oh my God.
It's a special fruit.
It's a fucking special.
Okay.
Vega punk is explaining.
Hey guys, actually, it's not the gum gum fruit.
Actually, it's a super secret God fruit.
It's a special secret.
Was that not explained already?
I, um, maybe it was just like not explicit before.
It was not explained to the crew.
We sort of heard about it from like, wasn't it the, the, the Gora say we're talking about?
Gora say we're talking about it.
Like, yeah, that particular fruit.
Oh, that's such an important one.
You see, like they're just talking to themselves.
It is so fucking based.
Yeah.
It's so fucking sick and it sucks that the straw hat guy has it.
As long as people.
Okay.
So this is, Nika has something to do with the void century.
It was a race from history.
Okay.
All desires, the desires of all things are born in this world.
Take, for example, the devil fruits has the same concept.
The devil fruits are the potential of human evolution that humanity wished for.
What the fuck?
Okay.
Oh, wouldn't it be nice if I was like that?
Wouldn't it be great if I was like this?
They have the powers of the diverse future of humankind.
Okay.
Therefore, these abnormalities are hated by the sea, the mother of all nature.
What is happening?
Dark souls.
He's going into it.
Their existence is burdened with this punishment.
Okay.
Yeah.
These so-called devil fruit users are beings living in a completely different world that many people wished for and envisioned.
This is my theory.
There's no need to think about whether there is a God or not.
Isn't this world so interesting?
So this is a secular explanation for what the devil fruits are, I guess.
If people thought they were literal gods and devils before, but I never really thought about it.
No.
I mean-
Very thematic rather than an actual explanation.
Okay.
So the fruits?
All right.
They're sort of embodying freedom.
What if I could be like this and then you did it?
And that's why they're called devil fruits because it's not good to have such freedom or something.
Okay.
They're hated.
They're hated by the sea because the sea is the mother of nature and the fruits represent the yearning of humans to escape from nature and achieve infinite potential or something.
Yeah.
So instead of like-
That doesn't really explain where they come from.
Why are they fruits?
But okay.
All right.
Sure.
I mean surely fruits is also nature.
Why doesn't the land-
You would think so.
Yeah.
Well, land isn't the mother of nature.
The sea is the mother of nature.
Land is like the son of the sea.
So it's like the sea is like birthed humanity and all mammals like evolution.
I guess.
And then it's like, oh, they're trying to ascend even further.
That's not fair.
Come back and be a fish.
Come back inside.
Maybe this is wine.
But you've got to stay down here with me, mother nature.
I'm coddling you, humanity.
Well, there's no fish-fish fruit.
Wait.
Yes, there is.
Isn't the dragon fruit of the fish-fish fruit model dragon?
Yeah.
It's a carp fruit model dragon, some sort of a thing like that.
Yes.
Okay.
So never mind.
There is a fish-fish fruit.
Okay.
Sort of.
It's a fish man who has a devil fruit, the mammoth fruit.
Jack.
So he sinks in water but can nonetheless breathe.
So he doesn't die.
Oh, wait.
Who is Jack?
One of the three big boys of Kaido's crew, the mammoth boy.
He's a fish man?
Yeah.
It never comes up in a fight.
I don't remember that at all.
I think there was.
Is he the one that rides something?
No, he's got big tusks and he turns into a mammoth and he fell or was otherwise defeated
and laid at the bottom of the ocean because he's a devil fruit using fish man.
So he didn't die.
But that's why it took him a while to appear after he wrecked the big elephant guy.
Like he poisoned everyone on the elephant, all of the minks.
Jack was the guy who did that.
Wait, Jack is the poison guy?
Jack is the guy who, with his Kaido crew mates, storms the big elephant and poisoned all the minks.
It said, where's Rizzo?
Where's the ninja?
Tell us where he is.
And then the minks said, we don't know where he is.
Right.
And then he left.
Zizow is the elephant, right?
Zizow?
Is it?
I'm pretty sure the elephant has a name and I think his name is like.
Zizow.
But whatever.
Okay.
Yes.
I remember him.
Damn.
I have my memories of the whole Wano arc or so.
Yeah.
I forget when he fell into the ocean.
I think after he, because he didn't, he wasn't there to like stop people getting to Wano or
something.
I forget.
Whatever happened with Jack, he appeared at some point and then he got bodied in every
fight he was in.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sentomaru.
I'm continuing.
It is a nice save that he said, that's my theory because then Oda, if he changes his
mind.
Yeah.
I don't really want that to be the exact explanation.
It can just be like, um, Megapunk, you misunderstood something very obvious and he's like, oh,
whoops.
And then the whole fandom's like, what the fuck?
Ah.
Okay.
So he's got three Seraphim and they are, I'm looking at them and they, are they, uh,
Jinbei?
Is that Jinbei, Nami and Zoro?
No.
It's, no, it's with Mihawk and, and, and I figured her name all of a sudden.
Is it Bonnie?
No, it's, it's Amazon.
Oh, was I right?
I thought, I was like, that's who I was thinking, but I was like, why would it be her?
There's no, there's no reason it would be her.
It is.
It's totally her.
Okay.
But why?
Well, keep reading.
Yeah.
I guess I, uh, okay.
This little panel confirming that Espair is definitely the same Seraphim, dark skin.
Yes.
Okay.
Even though in that one panel, they are not shaded in.
It was not clear.
Yeah.
Some.
Okay.
No.
The half tone guy is getting sloppy.
He's sloppy.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go with that blender.
Hey, is Kakus nose like full of hockey?
Oh my God.
His, like his nose sticking out.
I didn't notice that.
But yeah.
It keeps looking like that.
And it looks like his nose is full of hockey.
And I don't know why it keeps looking like that.
Well, maybe he's like full of, he's like arm, arming himself.
And that also includes his nose.
Maybe.
And because his mask is not covering his nose, his nose just looks like that.
It's getting hockey on it.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess that would make sense.
Okay.
So there, there's a, there's a hierarchy.
So the five elders, Trump, Vagapunk, Trump, Sentomaru, Trump.
So Sentomaru can control the, the, the pacifistas, including the Seraphim, including the Seraphim.
So the, the CP nine just lost their, their Seraph.
So, okay.
It would be a loss of an asset for the government.
We destroy a Seraphim.
What's, what's the deal with Awakening Zones again?
I know that, I know that it's, it makes them, it makes, they just turn it a giant like mindless
monsters is right.
I thought, didn't, weren't there a bunch of those at like, at Impel down?
No, those were not people.
Those were actually animal things.
Those are weird.
A giant like Zebra with an X or whatever.
I thought, I thought those were like Awakened Zoan users that had become like giant mindless beasts.
No, no.
Awakening is not a mindless thing.
You might be thinking of Chopper going giant and being a mindless beast.
I swear, I swear.
But that was due to his like, like little medicine balls.
Hold on.
No, no.
They say it right in this chapter.
Did they?
Yeah.
It's a rare sight.
Look at their speed.
There were many cases that the Awakening of the Zoan types robs their user of their own
personality.
Now, I guess it's not exactly the same as saying they become mindless.
Let me.
It's right, right.
The page right before you see the full spread of Luchi as the Awakened Leopard.
The Five Jailabee.
I'm trying to seeing the Impel down.
So the most feared creatures of Impel down.
Yeah.
Okay.
I knew it.
Their zone devil fruit forms.
Oh, I knew it.
I knew it.
The original full guards.
Wow.
So they are other people.
That sucks.
I thought they were big.
I don't know if they're Awakened or not.
I'm not 100% clear on exactly what Awakening entails because it's not just a Zoan thing.
Paramecia's fruits can Awakened and it sort of makes them Zoan-ish, not Zoan-ish.
Logia-ish.
Right?
Can't like...
Can't like a...
A Paramecia fruit can Awakened and it sort of means that they can sort of turn their
surroundings into...
Their element.
Yeah.
So like Doflamingo is a string man and he can turn things into string rather than just
drawing strings between like clouds or whatever.
I think he has like a weird cloud fruit, a cloud string fruit.
So like he can make strings appear and like puppeteer people but also when he Awakened
it he could turn himself into string I think or make like a clone of himself out of string.
That was all sorts of fucking stuff.
Yeah.
This one was weird.
His one was weird.
Yeah.
Okay.
I get it.
So they have Seraphim clones of the former Warlords.
Okay.
Yes.
That makes perfect sense.
No, this is...
I feel like it's a mistake that the Impel downguards are not just big animals because there are
huge animals in One Piece.
Like giant beasts and sea beasts and like giant monkeys and like you could have like
a big like sort of weird Minotaur, you give him an axe and say fight?
Yeah.
Doesn't have to be his fruit.
I guess.
I guess you could.
I wouldn't.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hmm.
Everyone is confused by Luffy's power.
All right.
Sentomaru is working for Vegaponk.
So he's like, yeah, okay, you can escape with Vegaponk.
Okay.
We have to kill the control tower.
So they've taken out Sentomaru.
Okay.
Because Sentomaru can control the Seraphim.
So once he's out of the picture, they can control him because they have the authority
chip.
But I mean, Vegaponk could control them even better.
And all of his little robot persons.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's so this doesn't seem like it's actually gonna...
Yeah.
Do much.
You know, the most interesting thing I find out from this chapter is the idea that at
the beginning, they see each other, but they don't immediately fight because Luffy is now
a warlord of the sea.
He's one of the big guys and so they can't fight without orders to do so.
The only reason Luchi is doing it is because he can't help himself.
He's not a warlord.
There are no warlords anymore.
He's an emperor.
No.
Emperor.
It's not like an official government thing.
No, but well, I don't know how it works, but the fact that it was reported as such by
Big Bird Morgan, Big News Morgan.
Big News Morgan, my favorite.
Means that now people believe it and so they have to treat him as such.
But he's still an enemy of the government.
He's not working for the government.
Yeah.
It's not that they aren't allowed to stop crying, but it's like he's so powerful that
trying to intervene randomly without direct orders could fuck up certain things.
That's why shanks appearing at the war in Marenforge stopped people from fighting because
it's like, okay, we've got white beard, but shanks is also here.
This isn't going to go well.
We've got to stop because he's so powerful and so that's the same implication is that
now Luffy is at a point where simply meeting a marine admiral or something in the wild
doesn't instantly mean there's going to be a fight, even though in this case there is.
It means that the...
Because the implications of a fight between beings of this power are like...
Yeah.
Catastrophic.
Remember what happened when Aokiji fought Ace and they transformed that whole island's
ecology.
They made it into like a winter fire island just because like...
Yeah.
Right?
You're thinking of Akayinu, that's after the war at Marenforge, that's punk hazard became
like that.
Am I?
No, I thought Ace and Aokiji fought and it turned a place into like a hot and cold island.
No, that's punk hazard.
It's Akayinu and Aokiji because Aokiji left the admirals.
He left the marines after that fight.
No, I'm thinking of when Ace fought Blackbeard, which is a different thing.
Okay.
No, you're right.
You're right.
He did have a big fire though.
Yeah.
Yes.
I remember.
I'm remembering the big fire.
Hmm.
Okay.
Well, I'm finished with the chapter.
Yeah.
That one aspect is cool because it's like...
It's a different interaction that is now possible.
He's so fucking cool.
He's so strong.
It kind of just have to be like, yeah, we can't just attack.
You can't just attack someone like Luffy because the implications, yeah.
Especially since he just defeated Kaido, not single-handedly, but basically and the marines
know that.
Yeah.
I mean, okay.
Rob's freaking awakened leopard looks pretty wild.
Yeah.
He's lean.
He's just big.
He's just bigger and lankier and he's got a flame cloud.
I don't know.
I guess he must be pretty strong.
I think he's supposed to be strong, but I don't expect him to be able to beat Luffy or
even hold his own at this point.
I feel like just because of him being an older enemy, it's fun to see them grow and face off
again.
Yeah.
Like Kobe and Helm Epo and what's the other guy?
The Spring-like guy?
What's his name?
Oh, the Spring-like guy.
Like he got completely bodied by Luffy at...
Are you talking about hard body?
No, no.
The guy before Skypea.
Oh.
Jaya.
The Jaya guy.
Bellamy?
Bellamy, yeah.
Like he shows up later stronger under the orders of Duff Lamingo and they sort of fight
there and it's like, oh, he's gotten stronger.
Luchi was a very dangerous guy.
Yeah.
I think at this point though, Luffy could beat him with his awakened zone.
I feel like storytelling 101-wise.
Yeah.
Once you've bested a guy, you don't bring him back to be like, ooh, but is he going to
be a threat this time?
No, probably not.
This seems like...
It's a chance to show growth on the part of the protagonist that they can easily fight
Luchi.
Yeah.
Luchi's even stronger than he used to be.
And yet, it's the background to a chapter that's actually about lore dumps.
There's this thing about the sea being the mother of nature.
Yeah, I want to know where Vegapunk got all of this theory from.
So I guess he knows about all the devil fruits because he's read whatever this old encyclopedia
is.
This compendium, one of the Blackbeard Reds to find the one he wanted.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
Can I read that, please?
Yeah.
I wonder if they sell it.
They might sell like a little like, ah, for the nerds, for the collectors.
Are you talking about like, oh, they probably made like a Harry Potter, like Fantastic Beasts
and where to find them?
Like they made like the book and you can buy it if you want?
I wouldn't be surprised.
That would be a cool thing to have.
I doubt it.
I actually kind of think not because I'm pretty sure like we haven't seen it for a reason.
I'm pretty sure they wouldn't make that because then there would be like, oh, well now we
know what all the devil fruits are.
They'd be spoilers.
Yeah.
But it would be like, it would go out of date when Oda comes up with something new.
Maybe they'd make one after everything's finished.
Well, that would be volume one, be volume one, everything we see up to a certain point
and they can sell volume two later.
Yeah.
Because it's an encyclopedia.
So it's like a multi volume like encyclopedia Britannica, like it takes up a whole shelf.
Yeah.
Of course.
I'd buy it.
I mean, if it was, if it was epic, of course.
Yeah, actually, that would be really cool.
Like little, little, little, like watercolor, like a Mega Man X, the Maverick Hunters guy,
the Mega Man X, Maverick Hunters guy that explains what all the Mavericks are like.
Yeah.
It could be like presented in a sort of like written with a quill sort of way and they'd
have like sketches of what the fruit looks like.
Oh, that'd be so fucking cool.
That'd be so awesome.
Yeah.
I have like random like an inconsequential lore of like who discovered this fruit.
But it would be so important.
No one people who have had this fruit.
Yes.
Oh, like a history of, oh, people going like going back to the void century of like known
fruit users.
Okay.
Yes.
That would be so awesome.
But it would be so important to me that it would like look like an encyclopedia, that
it was like a leather bound volume and not that it was like some fucking like stupid
like anime art on the cover.
Lol.
How to draw a manga.
Stupid anime.
How to draw a devil for it.
Don't want only stupid manga and stupid Japanese cartoons on the cover of my important, my
important lore book.
Thanks.
Yeah.
So the fact that the Seraphima cloned from seemingly without their knowledge, the warlords
means that they might be a buggy one, which would be really funny.
Oh.
Because he was briefly part of that before that got dissolved.
He was.
Oh my God.
I forgot.
But who else was there?
There was.
It was Shanks.
Crocodile.
Shanks was never a warlord.
Shibukae.
Yeah.
Crocodile.
Moria.
Gecko Moria.
Yeah.
Doflamingo.
Oh my God.
Obviously Kuma.
Jim Bae.
Boa Hancock and Mihawk.
Wait.
Was Kuma a warlord?
Yeah.
Oh.
Forgot him.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
I mean, I guess that's why he's a Pasifisa or why he's a Seraphim.
Oh, fuck.
Do you think they have Blackbeard was on that?
I felt like very briefly before he went to Impel Down.
No way.
They have Blackbeard.
No fucking way.
They have a Blackbeard Seraphim.
That would be so fucked.
Actually, this is already pretty fucked.
That would be, I don't know.
That's too much.
I can't.
I won't allow it.
Do you fucking remember Edward Weevil?
Wait a minute.
Is he a Blackbeard guy?
No.
Is he the mime?
He's a weird wobbly guy that you see in a chapter like a really long time ago.
He was introduced and he has this mother who's got really short and has glasses.
She's sort of like a helicopter parent and they're saying that that's Whitebeard's son.
And it's like, ah, Whitebeard's my dad.
I'm going to kill everything.
What?
No.
No, I don't remember this at all.
I wanted it.
I mean, it's obviously going to come up again, but like he seemed that he was shown to be kind of devastating.
I really wonder what they're going to do with that because I can't remember if he was part of the warlords or not.
I think he wasn't.
He's like a big, oh wait, this big guy.
Edward Weevil.
Oh yeah.
This guy is like claiming to be son of Pirate Whitebeard.
I think I kind of thought he was lying.
I thought he was lying as well.
I mean, he could have been like a bastard child, but like there's something about the mother that's sort of like, I don't know.
Maybe she's trying to push it for some reason, like she's manipulating him to be a pirate.
It could be true.
It could be true, I guess.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Totally.
Was this guy at Marenford?
He was post.
He was introduced after that.
Yeah.
No, I vaguely remember.
Lol.
Amazing.
Elias.
Oh yeah, Elias Whitebeard Jr.
Shiro Hige Jr.
Lol.
I'm trying to look and see if he was part of the warlords because then they'd have him as well.
He served as one of the seven warlords of the sea whom he joined sometime during the...
How the fuck did this idiot become a warlord?
Because he's so dangerous, I guess.
What the fuck?
Yeah, okay.
Okay, so I guess maybe they have...
What the fuck?
That'd be fun seeing him show up as a seraphim and it was like, who the fuck are you?
I mean, damn, they'll just fucking, they'll take anyone.
They'll take any old person as a warlord.
If anyone who was a warlord for even a brief period of time, it could be a seraphim.
They could have had a little injection, like, oh, this is for nefarious purposes.
Don't worry about it.
They're like, oh, okay.
Yeah, well, that's what I was expecting as a warlord.
I was expecting to do nefarious things, so yeah, I have no problem with that.
Go for it.
So when it comes to the fight coming up, Luchi, obviously very strong because he killed Sentomaru with one punch.
I don't know if he's dead, probably.
Have we seen Sentomaru fight?
I mean, I assume he's strong.
He's strong when they were at Shabodi Archipelago at the beginning, the first time they went there, before the time skip.
He was strong enough to fight off some of them, and then the Pasifistas were shooting lasers, so they had to run.
So he's tough.
He doesn't seem fazed by a lot of stuff, but this was instant KO.
Yeah.
Well, I wouldn't expect him to...
I mean, Luchi is a top tier character.
I would expect almost anyone to go down to Luchi instantly, pretty much, yeah.
So, I mean, I don't think there's going to be that much focus on Luchi versus Luffy because we already did that.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure what's going to happen is if they have control of the Seraphim and for some reason they can't get control back,
they're just going to have to run, and then they just run with Vegapunk and get on the ship, and then they could have burst out of there.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't see why Vegapunk wouldn't be able to regain control of the Seraphim.
Yeah, like if they could listen to, if it's voice activated and they hear it through a loudspeaker, would that work?
Well, it says...
Wait a second, wait a second.
It says that they can't take commands through transponder snails.
Well, it says the rank of authority they follow is different than those of the Pasifistas.
Wait, sorry.
Wait.
Hold on.
The rank of authority the Seraphim follow is different from those of the Pasifistas.
Even if the five elders order them through the transponder snails, it will be invalid.
Okay, so the Pasifistas respond to the Gorose above all else, but I guess that's not true of the Seraphim.
We don't know what the Seraphim's command of authority is.
That's confusing.
Why did they put that graphic there?
It tells us the Pasifistas rank of authority, but that's not necessarily true.
Oh, you know what it is?
I mean, if they told us, this is a setup for like, this is how it's supposed to go.
The five elders are supposed to outrank Vegapunk, are supposed to outrank Centumarra,
are supposed to outrank the holder of any authority chip, in the case of a normal Pasifista.
But these are Seraphim, so it's not going to be like that.
So, yeah, they're going to...
I think you're probably right.
Vegapunk is probably not going to be able to regain control of them because they don't work like this.
But why would the Seraphim not have Vegapunk at the top?
That's what I want to know.
Why would he make it so that he has even less authority over the even more powerful version?
Even if the five elders order them through the transponder snails, it will be invalid.
Does that mean that they don't take orders from the five elders,
or that they don't take orders via transponder snails?
I think it just means that the five elders don't command them.
I think somewhere I saw a different translation, not being... I can't see it looking for it.
All right, well, we're clearly being given incomplete information here.
Yes, the rank of authority they follow is different from those of Pasifistas.
What was I saying before that?
Oh crap, that's right, our authority chip is no match to the one he has.
Are Seraphim considered Pasifistas? That's the question, because if they are then...
Well, I think they are a kind of Pasifista, but what she's saying here is that the rules of who they obey are different.
Okay, I guess it's just more confusing for some reason.
Yeah. Although, I mean, unless this is a bad translation and this is actually laying out how the Seraphim work...
I'm seeing the same translation everywhere.
Okay.
Forget about it.
I think, yeah, no.
So normally, Sentomaru does outrank the holder of an authority chip, and for the Seraphim, that is also the case,
but not the case the five elders outrank them.
That would be the case in the case of the Pasifistas, but not the Seraphim.
So, does Vegapunk outrank Sentomaru in the case of the Pasifistas?
I'm going to guess yes for the Pasifistas and probably no for the Seraphim.
It's probably only Sentomaru.
It's just sort of confusing.
She would mention the rank of authority they follow is different.
In the situation where Sentomaru is gaining control, that's already the case.
It seems like it's normal.
Yeah.
For Sentomaru, it seems like it works the same way.
I think she's just setting this up so that next chapter, they can be like,
oh yeah, normally it works like that, but not this time.
Here's why it doesn't work like that this way.
Lol.
If you tell, it's like they say, you know,
when you explain in a work of fiction, when you explain a plan or how something is going to go,
the only, like, pretty much the only time you do that is when it's not going to go that way,
because if a plan is going to go according to plan, you don't say the plan.
You let the audience see the plan play out and then they go, ah, now that was a good plan.
But if you lay it out and you're like, okay, here's what's going to happen.
You wouldn't lay out what's going to happen and then have it just play out as explained.
You would only lay it out ahead of time if you were going to subvert it or have it fail
or there be unexpected complications.
Yeah.
So there you go.
That's why the ending of Homestuck is annoying, because rest of it lays out the plan and it just works.
And then it's such garbage.
It's such trash.
Yes, that's exactly why.
It's exactly what's wrong with it.
It's literally the entirety of Act 6.
It's just like, hey, what if we fought Lord English?
Let's get an army together and then fight Lord English and then they get an army together
and then they fight Lord English and then they just win.
And it's the worst fucking story ever told.
What were we talking about?
One piece.
I guess we're done with the chapter.
I think we're done.
I don't have anything else to say.
Oh.
Yeah.
I just pulled my headphones out.
Hang on.
I'm kind of looking forward to more lore.
Nice to see Luchi again.
Cool fruit, bro.
But we've got more important things.
We've got more important things to worry about right now.
Let's go to Elba.
Let's go see the Giants, please.
Well, we haven't seen Kuma.
Kuma's about to appear.
Oh, right.
The real Kuma.
Yeah.
He's going to have something to say.
He's going to get up on his little soapbox and he's going to say, enough.
Hey.
Oh.
I don't know.
This is probably not like super a crazy revelation, but I noticed that this panel right here.
Check this out.
You can see a pacifista or you can see Seraphim Kuma's little back flame.
Oh, yeah.
Got flame on it.
We have a little fire on his back.
That's neat.
Oh, and you can see actually you can see it.
You can see it in these panels too.
The other three also have it.
You can see it over their shoulder.
It is kind of like flying under the radar.
The fact that the world government or at least Vegapunk has been in the process of getting
DNA and making like, not robots, but like almost like cyborgs using DNA of strong people
and strong races to make amalgams that are like powerful weapons of mass destruction.
That's sort of flying under the radar amongst all of this.
I mean, it's obviously there.
No, I'm picking up on it.
No, I'm picking it up.
Because there's that bit where like, I can, you know, it's like, oh, Vegapunk out of
himself with straw hat, it will leave a crack on an enormous military strength.
Yeah.
They have pacifistas.
They've been making them for a while.
I mean, do they have seraphim yet?
Do they have like a big army?
Maybe.
Maybe what she means, maybe what she means by what she says, she says the Gora say can't
order, she says the Gora say can't order the seraphim via transponder snail.
So maybe it means that they all, they ultimately answer to Vegapunk as opposed to the Gora say,
maybe that's all she's saying.
Yeah.
Which is silly if like, Luchi thinks that killing Sentomaru will solve the problem if Vegapunk
can just tell them to continually not fight him.
Yeah.
And like be on his side.
And I think, I mean, that's, I would expect that he would be able to do that.
Maybe Luchi has been a bit of a himbo right now.
I think he is because like Kaku is telling him like, stop fucking up.
Stop fighting.
You're not allowed to fight.
We're not supposed to be destroying government property and Luchi's like, but I want to.
Yeah.
I'm gonna.
No, I think that's right.
I think a-
Perfect rival.
Vegapunk is like the strongest man because he's got all these minions.
He's got the strongest minions in the universe.
He's got all these goons.
He does have all these goons.
He's just like Tron Bon.
He's making all these little robot goons.
Hell yeah.
Do you think-
Let's get to questions.
Do you think that the last observation, I mean, do you think that's where this goes is just like
Vegapunk allies with the Straw Hat crew and now they have all these like, little like
Lumarian clones on their side?
That would be the best thing because then they would have presumably a seraphim buggy the clown
that they can use to fight buggy the real guy.
Their most dangerous opponent.
And I just want to see the reaction when buggy realizes there's a clone of him on the Straw Hat's like team.
He's like, what the fuck?
We need- one piece should end with another fight between Luffy and buggy.
That should be like the final boss.
Just like all times.
It ends just how it begins.
Yeah, I think so.
It'd be like, what was happening?
Like Luffy was in that cage and Zoro like carried it down because his swords were like gone.
He couldn't cut the cage apart or something.
Oh, yeah.
Like he was going to get blown up with a buggy bomb.
Buggy had like taken over a town, right?
He'd like taken over some town and then he captured Luffy because Luffy was doing something.
Was trying to stop him from like, what was he like collecting taxes from all these like townspeople or something?
I think he's just being a big old pirate.
Yeah.
I forget how he got in the cage.
Maybe it was just like a funny trap and it was easy.
I think the crew just beat him up and put him in it or something like that.
Time to reread One Piece.
Yeah, let's do it.
One Piece reread podcast.
Oh my god.
One chapter per episode.
No.
Okay, let's do that.
Literally, like if it's an episode a week, that's for the rest of our lives.
Yeah, well, yeah, because One Piece will keep coming out.
There will keep being a new episode.
Yeah.
That we'd have to do.
A new potential episode generated every week that we make a new episode.
So yeah, we'll be in podcasts for years.
Oh, no.
I'm never going to stop.
All right.
They're never going to make it the last chapter.
They're NGMI.
They're not going to make it.
And by it, I mean the last chapter of One Piece.
There must always be a new chapter.
I mean, yeah, pretty much.
Der.
Voice mails.
How many of voice mails?
Okay, so Ben's Weekly Reminder, play Delta in chapter two.
Okay.
Ben's Weekly Reminder, stay up to date with One Piece.
I did.
Next one.
Okay.
Here's a real voice mail.
The AI apocalypse is fake news.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, people are all up in arms about AI art potentially replacing the jobs of artists,
but what context do they actually see that as like potentially happening in?
Like other than mass producing jigsaw puzzles or other shit like that.
The vast majority of artistic work is in advertisement and like entertainment.
And with advertisement, you know, there's brand guidelines.
There's a lot of attention to detail about how things are represented.
You're going to have to do a lot of composing yourself.
You're going to have to like do editing.
You know, if you have a logo, you need to make different versions for like different contexts.
You know, all of that stuff, you need a human involved still.
And that person's going to be an artist.
So like, you know, and when it comes to entertainment, you have a lot of similar issues.
You know, you have like, you need something for specific use and you are going to have
trouble getting the AI to generate that.
You're going to have to have someone like intentionally go through it.
It honestly would probably be easier to have a person make art in most cases than to like
try to make, you know, your game sprites with AI and like, you know, what for like Pokemon
design?
I don't see a future where like Nintendo would use AI to make Pokemon designs or, you know,
other companies doing similar stuff to that.
It seems very unrealistic and alarmist to me.
Yeah, I don't know.
I generally agree.
I think though that the problem is not on like larger scale, like big boy money.
Yeah, it's not.
I'm not worried about what the Pokemon companies is doing.
Like what's likely to happen is that people who want art, just random people would much
rather generate something for free or for cheap than they would commission an artist.
And it's the smaller artists who are likely to lose customers just because when something
costs less or doesn't take as long, people are just going to gravitate towards that.
And if AI art gets very good, it might be like bad for those sorts of artists who rely
on commission work.
And if there's less people willing to pay because they can just get whatever they want
by typing in a prompt, that would be bad for them.
It's the small stuff.
I think that's the same with other AI generated.
Like I saw somebody talk about the AI translation using AI for translating like text has put
a lot of translating like work out of business because so many people don't really care about
it being like perfect syntax and perfectly translated.
They just want to do it.
They just want to make it so they can read it.
So they'll like opt to use the free bot rather than hire somebody to translate it properly.
I mean, machine translation is good for like on the fly translating like in a casual context.
It's not good enough for like commercial work.
Yeah.
There would be those small potato stuff still.
But like the larger stuff, big companies, government agencies, anybody who needs to do translation
to make sure it's good publishing companies, they will hire translators.
But like there's not a lot of work for smaller translation jobs from individuals who want
to translate it or like hobbyists or stuff like that.
That's just gone apparently.
I don't potentially potentially damaging for smaller artists.
I don't know if that's true.
I mean, they're not they're not machine translating like mangas now.
I mean, if they are, I'm sure it's dog shit.
Yeah.
I think there must be like some like to like if you really want to translate something
and you can't like hire somebody to translate it for you.
Okay.
And you have this this bot, you could like put it through that.
And then if it doesn't make grammatical sense, you could just shift it around.
Okay.
And you don't know you can make it readable, but you don't know whether it's correct to
the original source material because you didn't translate it yourself.
I suppose in like in like the market sense, what AI does is like it might not be a good
option, but it does.
There is now a zero cost.
There is a zero cost option, even if it's awful, which I which I guess does sort of like
lower it lowers the price floor out from under maybe like extremely low level people who might
otherwise do low level translating jobs.
That's yeah.
I mean, it is it is yeah, it is a competitor.
It does present a competition to that space, I guess.
And when it comes to translation, you're either correctly translating it or you're not.
And it's not as like creatively like varied as like art.
So like, a robot is more likely able to do something correct than you are to like type
in the prompt and get exactly the piece of artwork.
I think I think that probably most in most cases, someone who wants artwork.
I think it might be kind of similar to like piracy and that like the people pirating art
or people pirating like commercial products, probably we're not going to pay for it in
the first place.
Probably.
So I think I think probably most people that are maybe using AI art to generate images.
I think most people that would have paid an artist to make something they really wanted
to see would probably still do it because an AI can't really make something you can't
tell it like you can only really tell it exactly what you want if you give it like
something to learn from and just be like copy this.
Yeah, the the the the I think probably most people that are content with using AI art
to generate images for free.
We're not are not dedicated enough to like a particular vision that they want to see
realize that they would have had like any budget for an artist anyway.
That's probably not universally true.
Yeah, it does present some competition in terms of like image generation to artists.
I'm not saying it doesn't do that at all.
I'm just saying I kind of agree that it's not going to replace it's not going to replace
artists.
It's it is getting a bit like like over what did they what's the term they used?
Was it overhyped overblown?
Like like out of proportion something like that.
Yeah, I think people are freaking out maybe a bit more than they need to.
But I don't think that there is no damage.
Yeah, in the same way in the same way that piracy like you could there's an argument
to be made that people who pirate probably wouldn't buy stuff.
But I don't think that's a guarantee.
It's not.
I don't think piracy has no negative impact on the sales of any given thing.
No, you're right.
You're right.
So it's like it's it's like it's not a it's not a non issue, but it's not the worst thing,
I guess.
Yeah.
I think that I think that I mean in OK, Harry Harry Partridge, just to take that example
that I used before, he used AI to generate some backgrounds or something.
He said he didn't specify, but he said subtle AI.
I assume he means backgrounds.
And I mean, I guess under different circumstances, maybe he would have had to pay someone to
he either would have had to put like paint a background image himself, or he would have
had to pay someone to make that background image.
And so I guess there does represent a sort of like a would you call it a loss to the
economy?
You know, somebody might have gotten paid for that job and now they're not getting paid
because of AI.
And I guess you could choose to see that as a negative.
And in some cases, maybe it is.
I think that it's I think it's good when labor is saved.
I kind of I feel like I feel like if a machine.
Taking like taking like jobs, taking like the jobs question out of it for a second,
I think it's good when a thing can be done without work versus when it requires work
to be done.
So I'm I really want to be like, it should be it should be a good thing that nobody had
to draw this image, because, you know, the image didn't need to be so specific.
If you could have just used any old freakin background, if you could have just, you know,
it didn't require specificity to the point that you needed to hire a human intelligence
to create it.
It was very you didn't need a machine.
A machine image would do.
And so it's okay to be like, well, she's a machine.
Fuck it.
It's free.
No labor.
No labor required.
And I feel like if work, if work can be automated, if work can be.
If it can be done by a machine, it might as well be.
I kind of think it's OK if that work disappears, because it's no longer necessary.
Yeah.
I hate artists is what I'm saying.
I do want them to die.
When it comes to like stuff like backgrounds, like I personally like to put like, like background,
like design a background as specifically as I can.
Well, so like a generated background for me might not really fill.
It might not do the job that I want it to.
OK, hang on.
But do you always like to do that?
Well, I don't like to draw unless there's a point.
Right.
But I also don't like to put backgrounds if there is no reason to have a background,
which leads to like a panel that has nothing behind the character.
Which is to depict anything.
Which is fine.
Yeah.
Which is like totally fine most of the time.
It's not an argument against AI.
It's just that I probably wouldn't use it personally.
I mean, if it's just going to be whatever.
Yeah.
I'd rather be nothing, actually.
I think it's cleaner and easier to read.
OK.
I'm going to say yes, but I feel like that works better in like a comic or a manga than
it does in like an animation.
I can't imagine like someone like Harry Partridge just having like blank background.
When it comes to space, you can have like all sorts of weird bloops and stuff in a space background.
Yeah.
If you're on like a non-descript green rock planet and you just need like a bunch of green
rocks stretching out for a little while, then fine.