Today we're going to look at the term plebeian, often shortened to pleb.
Plebeians or plebs were Roman citizens, and they're often disparaged for being a very low status.
However, this is not actually the case.
Plebs were much higher than slaves, for example, or even people who were not Roman citizens.
They were often looked down upon, especially in Republican times, by the much higher in status, patrician class.
Houses in the city were made of timber, mud brick, and later concrete.
Houses in the city were called Insole, and were 67 stories high.
Hello, are you a Roman citizen?
Yes, sir.
Drop and give me five push-ups.
Whatever you say.
In early ancient Roman history, women were strictly under the control of their husband or guardian.
They had very few rights.
Hey, you my wife, what are you doing out there?
I think I shopped a little too often.
No, no, no, no, no. Today I expect you to take care of the house and do all the chores.
But I was kind of thinking since you'd be home, you could take care of that.
No, you have no say in this family. I run it. You, back home.
I fucked up the first recording. I'm as bad as BenSaint at Patreon.com.
Yes. BenSaint, introduce yourself.
It's 10.50 a.m. I'm hungover, and I have not been awake at this time since I was a baby.
And hippo shit.
Hip replacement.
And, okay, let's get right into the news.
Our topic for the day was plebs.
Plebs, however you want to pronounce it, that's what it's about.
It's this word defined by Urban Dictionary as,
to bring it back, to bring back the old tradition,
one whose inferior intelligence results in them making a complete, complete,
I did that again, just like I did last time, what the fuck,
making a complete tit-face out of themselves in public.
This fails to go into the minutiae of the details, plebs.
So it's a Roman word that was like the opposite of patrician,
meaning one who's an idiot and a dumbass, and I don't give a shit about it.
Is that really what it means, idiot dumbass, or is it more specific?
No, I mean patrician meant like the educated aristocratic class of the Roman society.
Would it be a kinted peasant, like you're just a peasant guy?
That's pretty much exactly right.
Well, that's not how it's used now, and that Urban Dictionary definition
just means that it's stupid, and that's definitely wrong.
You know, I think I just realized that pleb was the wrong word
for us to all cling to, because Philistine is what we really mean.
The way pleb is used now is what Philistine actually means,
which is someone who doesn't understand the arts and is ignorant of...
Lacks appreciation for it.
Pleb implies some lack of appreciation as well.
Yeah, but that's not what it means originally.
I guess we use pleb more as noob, though.
I don't think it necessarily implies that you can't appreciate the arts,
is that you're just too noob.
When I see the thing of this word, I picture two people staying next to each other,
a patrician who's a gay art student at Rhode Island School of Design at RISD,
and the pleb I think of as...
Katy Perry posting rare pay-pays in her tweets.
That's right. That's exactly right.
Okay, so I wanted to say...
I think one of the things about pleb is that it's usually used against somebody
after they've formulated an opinion on something.
If somebody says, I haven't seen that show yet, you don't call them a pleb,
you tell them to watch it, and if they say, then you call them a pleb.
That's an important distinction that I was going to get into.
I wouldn't call them a pleb if they watched it and were like,
I thought that this part was out of character, and I'd say, you fucking pleb.
You don't understand character.
That's where I would say Palestine, though.
That's where I'd pull that one out.
Well, they're basically interchangeable in that level.
So, yeah, just to set it, it's distinct.
We were thinking that it might be a little too similar to Normie's,
but then I thought about it, and they really are totally distinct.
And I've got the perfect example.
As we in the storytelling game like to call it,
the inciting incident for this podcast was a conversation I had with my roommate,
who's coincidentally also named Ben, who I now hate.
Who you accidentally called instead of actual Ben.
Oh, yeah, this morning I was calling Ben.
I called the other one. He was still asleep, yeah.
Okay, so we were driving down the road, we were going to lunch,
and the topic of just anime came up,
which I don't talk about with these guys too much,
because, frankly, they don't know nearly as much as me,
so it's kind of boring for me to talk about.
It's like, have you seen Cowboy Bebop?
Yes, yes, I've seen Cowboy Bebop, I like it.
Yes, 15 years ago, I was a child, actually.
So we were talking about that, and to my amazing surprise,
he had actually watched Konosuba last season.
He had watched it on Netflix or something,
and I was shocked, I was shocked.
So this guy, I'm starting to think,
well, maybe this guy does get it,
because where's this Final Fantasy VII shirt sometimes?
He plays a lot of Vigia, we talk about games and shows,
and he's got decent, yeah, that's right,
if you weren't a Final Fantasy VII shirt, you're a smart individual.
So I'm thinking this guy's got some pretty decent taste.
But then, when I asked him what he thought about Konosuba,
my favorite show of last year, or the last season, whatever,
he just said, meh, it was okay.
He thought Konosuba was just okay?
He thought it was meh, he thought it was okay,
and this is what really did it, when he said,
it was like Sword Art Online only boring.
These are the words he said to me,
and he didn't know he was signing his fucking death warrant
when he said those fucking words,
it's like he put a curse on himself.
So I then tried to explain to him why Konosuba,
I mean, I didn't even get into the Sword Art Online thing.
I just tried to explain why Konosuba was better than what he thought,
because he was bringing up all these points,
and this is where the pleb factor comes in.
He was bringing up all these points about like,
dude, it's just another game, it's just another show,
where a dude gets sucked into a video game world,
and gets all these powers, and meets a bunch of girls,
and they have these silly adventures,
and the lighthearted tone is funny at times,
but isn't as interesting as something like a death battle
like in Sword Art Online.
This is exactly why Sword Art Online is,
I'm not gonna, you know what?
It's a big problem.
You know what he's doing? He's a big problem in the universe.
He's just latching onto the tangible details
of the fact that they both take place in a game,
so he's like, oh, they're similar shows.
That's what most people do.
And the reason why he's doing that is because
he doesn't have as broad an experience with these,
he doesn't understand what Konosuba is trying to do,
and that's what makes him a plebe,
and that's why plebes are the biggest problem in the universe.
And that's where I want to start.
I would agree with everything.
I'm just, I'm imagining myself in this scenario,
and my first reaction.
If he said that to me, I know the first thing I do
would be to burst out laughing,
like his sterical hyena laughter would be my first response.
And then I would probably insult him,
and his intelligence, because I'm a dick,
and I don't have that.
You know, when I'm on YouTube,
I can type the comment and delete it,
but in person it's just like the first thing that comes to mind
is like, ha, you're wrong!
And then I might, depending on how he took the insults,
I would then go into my 50-point breakdown
of why he's wrong.
Yes. That was the plan.
I mean, that also implies that he didn't find sort of online boring.
It's like one of his favorite shows.
He says it's one of his favorite shows he's seen.
So, you know, we got, there's a lot to sort out with this dude, you know?
Hey, I'm curious, have you actually seen Sort Out Online?
Nope. I've seen like episode one.
I have never seen any of Sort Out Online.
So you guys could be considered a little unfair.
Um, no.
Oh yeah, I don't have any, I can't judge anyone.
I don't even care about his opinion on Sort Out Online.
I only care about his opinion on Konosuba,
which I know for a fact is a great show.
And to say it's meh, it's unforgivable.
Like Sort Out Online only boring.
Yeah.
If you guys had seen Sort Out Online, you'd understand
that what particularly bothers me about that statement
is that Sort Out Online is fucking boring.
Like, by far and away, my biggest criticism of Sort Out Online
is that it's unbelievably and sufferably boring,
because it has like this really strong start
where the first two episodes set up this death game thing
and like set up all these high stakes and stuff,
and like episode three is dramatic,
and then after that the entire rest of the show is nothing.
Nothing happens, it's fucking boring, nothing matters.
I think he's one of these guys who is satisfied in a show
by it being, and we don't need to talk about Ben forever.
We can let him off the hook eventually,
but I think he's one of these guys who like,
like the show is about this death game
where like the stakes are really high, like that's true,
and so I think that's kind of enough
for them to be like carried through the show
just like sort of keeping that in mind, you know?
No, what I think about people who,
they don't see these sort of like the boring flaws and stuff,
is that they think that like,
if there's like boring talky scenes or whatever,
there's just exposition,
they've seen that in other things that they kind of liked,
and they just assume that for a show to be good,
it has to have you know, lulls and excitement and stuff,
and they don't realize that there's a difference
between something being like interesting,
but like low energy,
and something just being really boring,
they just assume that that's what this is supposed to do.
I think I know where it comes from,
and you know, because the red letter media videos
on the Mr. Plinkett reviews of the Star Wars prequels,
I think were integral to this,
because when I was a little kid,
I never saw-
The mind-numbing action that the Fran Boris brave.
Well, I never saw the original Star Wars as a kid,
and like I saw it like,
I think I saw parts of the first one
around the time the Phantom Menace came out,
but I saw Phantom Menace like probably in theaters,
and I was fucking bored to tears by that movie, right?
I thought it was the most boring thing I'd ever seen,
and for a long time,
I believed that I just thought like,
space and politics were boring,
you know, like the idea of space politics
was the most boring thing in the world.
I could see why that movie would do that.
Right, and I believed that all the way up until adult,
like I've never been into sci-fi,
I've never been into political stuff,
until I played Mass Effect at like age 20,
and completely changed my outlook on both things,
and now that's like my favorite genre is political sci-fi,
and then I watched the Plinkett reviews,
and I realized that political sci-fi was never boring,
the movie is just terrible,
and like, as a kid, I thought I just didn't understand
what they were talking about,
because it was too, like it was over my head, you know,
but then the reality of it is that it was just bad,
it was just badly written,
and that's why I didn't understand it.
I'll tell you, you know.
There's like, there's the fucking people that kill me.
I think what you're trying to,
or what you were at least trying to say last time,
is that people who watch those scenes in a show like Sword Art Online
think it's necessary for that to be there, you know,
like they think...
Yeah, what I was going to say is that people,
they sometimes feel like they might recognize
that something is like boring and stuff,
but they're scared of like whining about it,
they don't want to be that person who says,
oh, I didn't like it, and then everyone turns around and says,
but it's a great movie.
This kind of American anti-intellectualism,
they just accept that it's like really,
it's good even though they find it boring,
they say, no, it's a good, it's a boring,
but that's okay, you know, that sort of thing.
When you complain about something,
people can find it a real buzz kill.
I have a friend who like,
he asked me, he said, Ben,
you're the coolest guy ever,
what do you think about the new
Fully Coolie sequels coming out?
Oh boy, here we go.
And you know,
I didn't see this at the time
because I couldn't see through
just the red veneer of rage
that came over my eyes,
and I just went on this fucking
bender about how it's all just an
evil fucking...
how it's an evil corporate money grab
and everyone that is responsible
should be in hell and how I pray every night,
and I pray every night
for another tsunami to come
and finish the fucking job and wipe out Japan.
Just wipe out Japan.
Japan's done some good stuff,
but you know, it needs to die
right now before it ruins its honor
by destroying the best thing it ever made,
Fully Coolie with a sequel.
And you know, I could see
the childlike wonderment went out of his eyes.
This was a guy who really liked Fully Coolie
and was like, I like Fully Coolie,
I can't wait for the sequel.
And as I went on, I killed his joy.
I killed his joy.
I saw this so clearly
when I made my Final Fantasy 7 video
which is, you know, very divisive
among the people who've seen it,
where just to raise the idea
that the thing that you're talking about,
like, because my whole life,
me and my friend Colin, when we were kids,
made a pledge that we would do whatever it takes
because we were young, we didn't have any money
to get whatever money was required
to buy the console
or whatever we needed to play the Final Fantasy 7
remake when it came out.
And that was from a time...
A tall order.
At that time, we didn't know if that was even going to be fucking possible,
but we just like...
It was something that we just
blindly believed would be the best thing ever
because it was like our favorite game
and we trusted Square Enix
and we didn't understand how these things happen.
But now that we're older, I mean, I don't know about him,
but I understand
that's just not how things are going to pan out.
It's not going to be, you know,
what I expected to be.
It's going to be, you know, this whole other thing.
It's going to be its own thing.
You only know that
if you have the perspective
of someone who like understands how these things happen.
So that's where being a plebe
will shoot you in the foot because you encourage
bad things to happen without even knowing you're doing it.
Here's the thing that I think is
not necessarily the same as being a plebe.
And I'm aware this comes off as the most condescending podcast
that I've ever done, definitely.
I think Normies was pretty close, pretty up there.
Here's the thing that's not necessarily the same
as being a plebe, but I think it can be related.
A lot of people don't
want to
see anything negatively.
They want to be excited about things
and they want to like things.
We could just make this about
how people don't appreciate negativity enough.
That could be like the theme of this.
You know, I think if I wanted to speak
in defense of
like,
plebness is like ignorance is bliss, right?
That's right, that's right.
The less you think about it, the more you can enjoy it.
And I think that...
Well, I think there's a double-edged sword
with being a pleb.
Which is that if you just
like everything
because I see this sometimes
where there's people who aren't very critical.
People who give everything like a 7 out of 10.
Or a 10 out of 10.
They give everything this baseline.
It's either amazing or it's good.
But then the difference between those
isn't even that strong.
I feel like when people
aren't very critical of stuff, then everything
is just kind of the same.
They kind of watch something and they go,
oh, it was great. And then for all time,
they just go, oh, it was great.
But they never experience more.
Whereas for me,
because I'm so critical of some stuff,
then the stuff that I do
I like way more.
For something to
break down all those barriers
of things that it can do wrong.
For a show to just
not fuck up in any way.
And then to just excel
in certain ways is like mind
blowing to me. It's like I can't believe
this is really happening.
That genius and beauty
exist in the world.
You know what I am?
I am Matt
Genius and beauty is like a rare pepe.
Yeah.
Posted by Katy Perry for all to enjoy.
I can't believe.
Yeah, anyway.
I'm like Matt Damon from
Good Will Hunting.
No, actually I'm not Matt Damon.
I'm like Skarsgard.
I'm the professor
who discovered Matt Damon.
The genius kid.
Well, it's like this.
It's like there's only a few men in the world
who can tell the difference between you and me.
But I'm one of them.
And you know, it's like you gotta know
you gotta be able to see the difference
between Sword Art Online and fucking Konosuba
if you wanna survive meeting me.
You say that to me again.
I would
consider myself a bit of a
pleb in a
few ways. I mean,
because like I try to be
it's not that I try to be
optimistic all the time.
I actually enjoy being really critical
on things that people like.
But that's just because I'm
lost the word.
Contrarian, yeah.
But I do like
just giving things
letting things
you know, just
I'm accepting of things that
like people in this chat
in this group really
all rag on. Like I'm still
kind of like Nerdwriter and all that stuff.
I like Nerdwriter. Well, I know you do
but like everyone else. I don't care
for him personally.
And even though I hate Dark Souls 2
a lot, I still don't think I hate
as much as you do now, did you?
I don't think anybody hates as much as I do.
Yeah.
You've overtaken me there. I don't know.
I just I've considered myself
a pleb maybe because
as a defense mechanism.
Well, I don't want to be.
Here's the thing. Here's what I think.
There's no such thing as plebs
because nothing in this world
is truly worth appreciating at all.
All right.
So some people think
they have a real good nose or taste
or whatever for beer.
But they're wrong. They've been tricked
by big, by big alcohol companies.
The culture of
beer is one that's like, oh this,
I mean, beers do taste different, but none of them
taste good. And all
artists like that. None of it's really good.
You've just been tricked into thinking you like it
by the media and by marketing.
So plebs are...
To a certain extent. No, completely.
I like Guinness.
I think Guinness tastes good now. Now that I've drank
it so many times, I just like to drink it.
I guess there are better and worse beers.
I know what you're saying. For the most part,
it's about, I mean, you could like anyone.
People like getting tied to the railing
and raped. If you do it enough times.
They learn to like it.
Do they?
Are you sure? I can confirm that.
Yeah, no.
So we've just
all got Stockholm syndrome
to art. Art and culture just
have us all fucking hostage.
It's funny.
I actually think that a lot of people
like a lot of stuff
out of Stockholm syndrome
because of... Absolutely.
I'm not kidding about that.
That's essentially the argument we were having
about Sword Art Online and
that those first two episodes
were so gripping that people will watch
the whole fucking show and no matter how
stupid and boring it gets, they
might just... That's what Attack on Titan did to me.
That's what Attack on Titan did to me.
It just hooked me really hard at the beginning.
I think like the greatest cultural
example of that in recent years was
The Walking Dead. That like
it had this really strong first season
but that was only like six episodes
and then it's just been like painfully boring
for like five fucking seasons.
Yeah, but it's culture. But it was enough, man.
That's all they need to do and now they've got it.
I want to see how it ends or whatever. Right.
Yeah, who gives a shit, they all fucking die.
Everyone dies. Spoiler alert.
My parents who are not like particularly
critical or picky and even they like
by season three were like this show's fucking
dumb as fuck. But they're still watching it
because they cannot, you know.
Yeah, now they're invested. That's what they do.
They get you invested in the characters
and they numb your like
critical thinking and then they just like find
a... At first they
tap into like your...
There's like a base human reaction to like
oh shit, things are happening to these people.
Are they gonna be okay? They get you with that
and then they build a little bit of like
narrative weight into it. They build like a
thread line. They make you relate to these people
and they get you invested in them personally.
And then at that point they can do whatever the fuck they want.
It doesn't matter. You're already got.
It's what happened to me with Naruto and Bleach.
I still read them even though I don't like...
Well, Naruto's finished.
But I read it all the way to the end even though like...
Oh, well, who cares.
I don't need to get invested in the new characters.
I've done my bit.
I've seen how it ends.
And now I can never look at it again.
I'm glad I don't have this impulse.
Because for me,
I guess it's because
it's very all or nothing
with me because most shows aren't over
when I start watching them and then I
catch up and then I just never watch it again.
Well, reading Naruto
wasn't too much of like a hassle.
I would always go to the
manga sites to read the new one piece chapter
and there's usually a Naruto there as well.
Yes, there is.
I do have the strong urge
to finish like anything that I start.
But to balance that out
is I don't start things very often.
It takes multiple
separate people independently
recommending me something for me to even think
about watching it.
I gotta ask, is this weird
that I think the reason I don't feel the need
to continue is that I feel like no matter what
what happens is either they die
or they don't die.
Yes, that's weird.
That's always what it comes down to.
They don't die by the end of the story.
But that's life.
And adding on to that
they will eventually die.
So like even then, none of it
fucking matters, you know.
This is the part where I
showed up in the call.
Well, I wanted to go back to the
sort of the idea that people
are afraid of
being judged for being critical.
And I want to bring in the new
Harry and Original term from the Hello Internet
podcast, cheer pressure.
Which is where there's pressure
to be constantly
positive
to all things.
Do you say cheer pressure?
You gotta be cheering for them.
You can't possibly...
We've all had people
attack us for being against...
Oh god, I'm seeing red! You just reminded me of the thing
the angriest I've ever been.
Okay, that's totally relevant.
Because yesterday,
when Digi did his fuck, he did a video
that was like criticizing
boring tastes of anime.
I swear I'm in a fucking murky old family.
I've never been more angry in my life.
Who are you talking to?
Anime every day is who he's talking to.
It's not him.
He makes this response
about how Digi isn't allowed
to criticize things.
Because he has a fucking platform,
people are gonna not like
things that he says he doesn't like.
And that is not fucking allowed.
You can't do that. You're spreading a cancer.
You're spreading dislike of something.
Oh my god, fuck off you piece of shit!
I wish you were dead! That's the most retarded thing
I've ever heard in my entire fucking life.
Oh god, I'm so mad.
So this guy said that
it's irresponsible of you to say that things are bad
because it'll make people like them less?
That's what he was saying.
What community have I heard
that kind of argument in?
Wait, wait, hold on.
What anime every day was saying was that
you're judging people by their tastes,
but you think that people shouldn't be judged by their taste at all.
It's not so much being judged
by your taste.
Digi didn't even judge anyone taste.
He says every fucking time that you can like any show you want.
It's more like this.
This isn't what it's like.
Why doesn't he understand?
Look, what it really is is
evaluating people's tastes.
You look at your favorites and you go,
it seems like you're into this kind of thing.
So it's not him saying
some people have worse tastes
than other people.
It's just saying, he's just saying that me personally
some tastes bore me because I'm
unfortunate all the time.
Did you say he's bored?
I'm right now looking at this reply I got to a comment
on that video that was like,
why can't you just admit Digi bro fucked up?
Why can't you just admit it that he
lapsed in judgment?
I'm gonna give this guy a response.
You know what, I didn't
want to bring this up but it's
out now so whatever.
Congratulations, you now have your first public beef
in the anime community.
Yeah, great.
I completely understand
where all these people
are coming from because like
in this chat
where we do these calls
we shit on people's tastes
all the time but when we
shit on people's tastes we don't mean it in the same way as
some people mean it
when some people are like
if you're like K-On, you're completely retarded
that show has no substance whatsoever.
Oh, I wonder if you're really good at
face stuff actually.
So people like that, when they say that
You guys can almost compete with mine but you have to
have a shitty echo effect to really make it sound
sounds like an evil thing.
You got to cop the mic.
I think you're gonna speed it up 10%.
So anyway, when he says that it doesn't mean
the same thing as when we are like
why does such and such continue
to shit on such and such
thing that we like. When we say it
it means a different thing. You're just gonna have to take our word for it guys.
You're just gonna have to take our word for it.
The reason that I
because I know Nate you didn't like that
in my response I was
overly fair to him.
You were so fair and it made me so mad.
You should have ripped him apart. The only reason for that is
the realization I had when I was watching his video
and he kind of makes this point
that those shows
that I'm talking about are mostly
kind of obscure shows
and like
I think the problem is that
from my perspective all I see these
like the only times I ever see these shows talked about
is in fucking 3 by 3 threads.
It's when people are putting them on their favorites list
because they make you look really smart and cool.
But then I thought about it and I was like
no one's championing these on
YouTube except for this guy.
Like anywhere else for me
anywhere else on the internet it's annoying
to see like a million anime
every day is going oh this show
is so beautiful and that makes
it the best show that I've ever seen
and I'm like yeah I fucking get it.
But then I thought about it and I'm like well
there's no video of me on my channel
going hey guys go watch Anne of Green
Gables because it's a classic.
And so if
I had more videos
about those shows then I would really
feel like he completely
deserved to be ragged on.
If you guys are just now hearing about all this
believe me like if you hearing us talk about this
for the first time it may sound
like Digi made some video where he's like
hey everyone I'm here to tell you about who to not
take seriously around here. It wasn't like that
at all it was more like a thought experiment
it was sort of like I don't know
you just have to...
Don't defend it it doesn't need a defense
it was just a fucking whatever.
It was just like a thought experiment type of thing
and I understand that people don't like
understand the depth of where we're coming from
I don't know
It was a video that wasn't meant to be
watched by as many people as it was
it's really what it comes down to.
It's a video that has 30,000 views
that was just a random rambling
I mean you did give it a really click baby
title and a thumbnail even.
I don't know why I did that because in retrospect
that made no sense because I did
the title I had in mind from the beginning
but I did give it a thumbnail
like this will get more clicks
and then I looked at it and I mean
I meant to get more clicks
I'm not sure I even agree with the argument
that like I didn't intend this to be seen by more people
because once you post it out it's out
but like nonetheless I think your points
are nothing to be argued
This reminds me
Here's my thing about this is that like
he's talking about a vague generalization
and if you feel like
you aren't like posturing with your opinions
then you aren't part of that group
and you don't have to like be defensive about it
like if you feel like you aren't part of that group
then you aren't.
Well I did literally call him
being out.
If you get called out then you can make a response
what I told him was
you should have just made a response proving
all your favorites are better than everything else
I also thought that's what it was going to be
like when I clicked on the video I was really hoping
he was about to like play defense for the show
That would have made you look way stupider
When I saw that the video was only 8 minutes long
I figured there was no way
he could defend 9 choices
His response to me was
well I have, I explain it all in my videos
themselves. I'm like oh well
I don't want to hunt down all of his videos
so I'll just take his word for it
Let's move this into a discussion
of another kind of pleb
and once again I'm just accusing
anime every day of something
so I'm just throwing the pot even more
Whatever let him have it
I think that the fact that
he thinks he's put up a defense of
why those shows are on his list
is exactly the problem
of why I made that video
in the first place
because he hasn't really
not in any depth
or meaningful way
he's talked a lot about how they're
very well written and beautiful to look at
and the art design is really strong
Is that really his voice?
I haven't seen his videos
That's sort of his voice
I know he's capable of
making analytical points
in the film
and arise
and made some great points in those videos
but most of his videos
are like
these are the top 10 anime of 1990
and then he'll just
just describe
they're kind of like YMS reviews
where he's just describing the fact that
the show is good and not why it's good
in any specific
kind of detail
and my problem with those 3x3s
this is what I was trying to get across
about ergo proxy
is that I don't understand the appeal of ergo proxy
and no one has explained it to me
well enough that I get it
it is like
proven
that in some fields at least
people will posture for
a sophisticated looking opinion
I remember Jimquisition talking about that
in regards to certain features on video games
but also correlating it to coffee
how statistics show that
when people are interviewed they say
I like a rich dark roast of coffee
but then buying habits suggest
that people mostly buy milky weak coffee
you know it's not like
the very notion he's proposing
that people don't
just put things on there to look smart
or cool is the most retarded thing
I've ever heard in my life
even if like
we love everyone
we're the most positive people ever
we're not saying you're not a good person
we're extremely cynical
and that's the issue
is that I don't think he's cynical enough about it
because I got a lot of responses
we're just saying we don't automatically dislike anyone
for anything
we're not saying you're a bad person
we're not saying you're not allowed to watch anime
I personally don't care about this whole boring taste thing
because I'm not on 4chan all the time
just letting you know
please don't take it too seriously
it's just like a thought experiment or something
I don't think it's as cynical as it could be
people make lists like that
3x3 lists like that or whatever
it's not like they're setting out to deliberately deceive people
it's that
this is what they're defaulting to
out of an instinct
or out of a sort of sense they have
that this is what's appreciated
and everybody does it
I totally think
that I have a sense of
if something feels
good in such a conventional way
that can make me like a little bit more
than how much I enjoyed it
when watching it because it gives me so much more appreciation
for it afterwards
so I totally get it
it's satisfying to agree with people
and to like say
oh I love this show
and to have everyone nod in agreement
and go yes that is a good show
and so if you've got two shows that you like equally
one of which is going to be controversial
and get you like insulted and the other of which is
everyone's going to be like yep same
you know
actually inclined to pick that one
I agree and I think it's
I definitely find some deep satisfaction
with the few times I get to agree
with pop culture and that's like
that's why I actually
like when people call me a hipster and stuff
I always feel like it's
it's so
mischaracterizing who I am
because of the fact that I hate
I hate that my taste is hipster taste
like I wish everyone liked everything I like
I don't want to be the guy
who likes the things that nobody likes
see that's the thing
this whole plebe thing
simply comes out of a lack of understanding
what the fuck is going on
if you don't like something
just explain why and if you're right
people will agree with you
and that's what we all do in our fucking videos
I made a fucking 40 minute video
it took me six months of my life just to explain
why one show is a little bit
better than everyone already thinks it is
that was substance
going on there what this is what we see
from the fucking plebes is them just saying
nope you're wrong and I'm not going to explain why
you're just wrong
I'm not impressed by that
I'm not impressed by that argument come back to me
when you've got something intelligent to say
I was on my way to my point about
that other kind of pleabeness
that I was accusing anime every day of
the fact that he thinks
that he has made the point
about those shows
is like
in regards to being a writer
like that I think that
there's a standard that I think most people
is the standard of reviews
and it's
shit tier like if you're writing
reviews that could get published in a major magazine
those are the shittiest reviews
possible
unless you're that one guy who writes for EGM
about how everything is a dick
sucking cock
it's like Tom Cruise sucking my dick
yeah that's the one
I think there was a time
in history where
consumer reviews were really important
right?
because a new movie came out
and no one knew if it was good
unless they went and watched it
and so you would open up a magazine
and the magazine would give you a very short description
of weather
the thing people have to understand about
writing from this so called objective
perspective
the point of it was never to
film's quality it was to present it
in a way that the most people
would resonate with
most people will feel
that a movie is shittily paced
so if someone says in an article
the film is bad because the pacing
is bad they're saying that because
most people will feel that way
it doesn't mean the movie is actually
bad because there's probably someone out there
who doesn't care about the pacing and will love
that movie but like the general
a critic is someone who has to channel
what they believe to be the general consensus
and put it into words and that's what
a consumer review is and that's what
someone like Roger Ebert was so good at doing
you know but like
I think that that age is gone
consumer reviewers are completely
fucking unnecessary because we have rotten
tomatoes and all you have to do
is open it and look at the number
and go okay
now I know
which is an aggregate of a bunch
of those mainstream consumer reviews
but like if you're fucking on YouTube
doing like consumer reviews
of anime it's like we have anime news network
for that we have
regular publications we have magazines
we have you know you can look at the
score that is given on my anime list
or something like what is the point of this
make your channel the story of your taste
because if you're a good writer
and you're like authentic with yourself
you can make you more interesting
I'm not accusing anyone of not being authentic
I'm just saying like maybe play into that
more like again let's be
very clear we're not like judging
I don't think you were judging anyone
based on your tastes you were
making statements like a reverse
spectrum the worst thing that you could
accuse did you was saying that someone's
taste was boring
like a reverse spectrum a guy who I think
listens to these he added me on Mal
recently and I looked at this top 5
well his top 4 are Red Line
Madoka, Samurai Flamenco
and Ping Pong and I was like well I see
a connection he likes stuff that goes
all out insanity or something like
that that's kind of a cool taste for him
and you know everyone's taste is fair
it's just that not me this isn't me
because I don't spend all my time on
4chan but Digi has certain opinions
make him go oh I know
this kind of thing
DerpyDoo
Hi I'm interrupting the podcast
man I had
just gotten out of bed when I got
on to this podcast
I guess I'm really
slurry
when I first wake up and a lot less
articulate
also this was recorded
probably 3 weeks before
it was the point at which
it gets released
because
Nate said because
you came into it late
that for some reason means you have to
be the one to edit it
and I was like
well okay
when I'm done with everything else I have
to do
and so this is what happens
well I just I'm bored by
this idea of like making a
video or making a list that says
like here's what are the best
anime and I'm like I don't think
we need someone to tell us that
like it's obvious
in a way like I need you to explain to
me why people care about it like because
and those shows are fucking ancient
you know like more people need
to watch more and broader anime
and come to their own conclusions
right and that's the other thing
is that like I think that when we
like because like I understand
from his perspective he's thinking like
well here's all these masterpieces
and not enough people have seen them
so I need to promote them but I'm
over here like I know all these other
shows I consider masterpieces
that even less people are watching
and so like it would be so much
more interesting to me if someone came out and they were like
my top nine shows are like
Minabi Straight and fucking
I'm just gonna look around
my room at the
and fucking Simone
and yeah and
like if someone came out with a list
that had camphor on it like the
thing is if you were on that guy's deal
if you were on 4chan then someone's
gonna go camphor but
if that guy if I saw it
if I saw in top nine and like there was
like eight great shows and camphor
I immediately
I'm gonna text like I'd be like please write a review of
camphor please like
nothing could be more interesting to me
than that guy's review of
camphor you know and so like
if I see a list and it's like
nine shows that I've read a thousand
million popular reviews of
you know like at the end of
at the end of 2009
this guy
basically every anime blogger on the planet
made a top 50 anime of the
decade list just because
it was the end of the decade everyone wanted to do it
so this guy called aqua blue
aqua blue sweater who's like a statistician
took all of them
and compiled them into like
the list of what were the top
rated ones and it was like
Haibane Renme, Mushishi
Kaiba like all these you know
all the fru fru shows you expect to be up there
and it's like they'd all been
reviewed by everyone because
like everyone who made those top 50s
they had like you know their little blurb
about each show so that means
like there were more blurbs written about
fucking Mushishi than
any other show so when someone makes
a video that's like Mushishi's the best
show I'm like yeah I know
everyone knows we all know
right about something else
please here's something that confuses me
a little bit I think
a lot of people what they want out of
a review is that
it agrees with their opinion
and which makes it kind of
doesn't that make it inherently uninteresting
I don't
that's what I was saying to my
some commenters I didn't like I was like
guys listen a video is
like an editorial it's a think piece
it's not an opinion
agreement delivery service
you phrase it like that and you shut them up
it feels good to hear someone affirm
your opinion but I also think that it's
not interesting to hear your own opinion
Ben I totally agree
but that's why I am firmly of the stance
that I think happiness and good feelings are vastly
overrated
no I agree with that
think about this real quick kind of viewers
if everyone was happy all the time
what would get done nothing
I actually at this point
I've way gotten past
the point where I actually get really mad
when I read positive reviews
of stuff I like that don't explain anything
like the worst review to me
is when someone like
if I see a review of Kaon
and the review is like
oh this show is really cute and fun
and it's good
go watch it and I'm like what the fuck
how is that going to like
yeah no shit I already knew that
you know dude that's
very much the reason
when I was making my Gurren Login video
I watched everyone's review and they were so
shit they were so bad
it had to be corrected so
of the exact same opinion
that's actually like that was realizing
that like what you realized watching all those
was a huge part of what
affirmed me into like doing this
because of the fact that I had always
assumed that this would
already have been done by a million people
that like there was already
like with Ava you know
like you assume there must have been every Ava analysis
possible because it's been around for so long
and you know and I know there is a lot
like there actually is like a whole channel
of Ava analysis
and there's like the Ava Geeks forum
and all that stuff but like in spite
of all that I feel like
most of the stuff I've said about the show is stuff
I've never seen someone else say
and like I think
there's still so much room because I think up until
recently consumer reviews
were what people thought criticism
of art was and like
analysis was mostly like a
like a school
what's the word I'm looking for
for I don't know like a school project
sort of thing is that what you're saying?
No academic that's the word I'm looking for
like it's more of an academic thing
it's more of a university thing
and like I don't think the market's ever going to be
too crowded of like personal
like thoughtful pieces
related to your own life of any show
you know whereas it's
like I think if
you can
like if you wanted to write just a review of a show
like go to google
type like KonoSuba
review and you're going to if you get any results
don't write a review
like write an analysis write a
think piece write something original
that's fair like I don't need
there to be more than one review
of anything and this has gotten to this point
with all these fucking new movies coming out
where because every youtuber has decided
that they're going to review every new
fucking Marvel movie makes that money dude
right we get YMS putting out these quickies
that are
worthless like completely critically
worthless they tell you nothing about
the film they are usually like
him nitpicking two random elements
and then spending five minutes going well it was good
but it wasn't as good as it could have been
but it's pretty okay wasn't quite as good
as great but it wasn't quite as great as amazing
but it wasn't as good as not good but it was almost
like three levels of good over good five
and like like I watched all these
fucking reviews of Civil War and it was like
Movie Bob had probably
the best consumer review
possible for that movie and even
then all I could think the whole time was
who cares
like everyone's going to see the movie
anyone who gives the slightest
fuck about this movie is going
to watch this movie this will probably be one
of the highest grossing films of all time
why do we have
800 consumer reviews coming out for a movie
literally everyone will see
why are these people doing that
those were invented before the
information age guys we don't need those as
much anymore you know I was going to say
this before but like I was thinking before
about like how I got into
the video games I like and like there were
two ways like my friends would tell me
about them and then like Ben and like people I knew
and then I read Game Informer
or like I would like oh my god
I love Game Informer I used to love that
shit it was so useful but
like even more than that
I would just flip through it looking for reviews
with scores under five and
just read them like trash a game
because I wanted to hear what like shitty
things they would say about them but see
yeah it was super great it was super fine I love
that magazine but like I don't read it anymore
largely because I mean maybe
because I don't have time but like it doesn't serve
the same purpose it once did of like educating
people on what a game you can just fucking google it
and find a thousand pages about whatever
go on V and everyone's talking about it
it aggregated all of human information
go to wikipedia
so bringing up Movie Bob
reminds me of another another
layer on the pleb
seven layer dip
and that is the sour cream
another like root cause
of pleb-ness of chronic pleb-ness
do you not like sour cream didgy
I actually like
physically can't eat sour cream
oh fuck you sour cream
it's like I throw up
if I eat it like it's disgusting
well get over it bitch
I'm gonna sneak sour cream into your
I'm gonna puke on your nuts
if you do that
anyway um yeah
Movie Bob
I think people are invested
in liking things
just by nature of the fact that they watch them
in not nuts of or in the Avengers
in his really that good about Avengers
Movie Bob brings up that like
going into watch Avengers
people aren't just rooting for the Avengers
like rooting for the Avengers themselves to win
is the same as them rooting for
them to like the movie for the movie
for the movie itself to succeed
yeah that was weird that was his point
though I think Bob is someone who can just watch movies
whatever like he is
he is no pleb when it comes to movies in terms of watching them
it seems like he's watched all movies that exist
like his like I thought his point was good
about people like that go into the movie
are already invested like
financially and time wise
in their own enjoyment of the movie
they want to like it because they are there
watching it and I thought it was weird that he
made it out like Avengers was the only
movie that did this or that it was brilliant for doing it
I thought it was applicable to pretty much any
movie yeah just the fact
that I have watched something kind of
makes me want to give it the benefit of the doubt
so that I won't have wasted my time
that's entirely true but that brings up
perhaps the biggest core problem
with plebdom in general which is just
an an an interest in
liking it over being critical of it
and like viewing it from an intellectual lens
you know particularly something that you use to
like you don't really like as much anymore
but you want to keep hanging on to it
that keep going on these long tanges
don't give a fuck about
yeah I know it's true
Ben you're absolutely right about that
I mean yeah I mean that was the thing that I used
to I think I used to feel that more
strongly nowadays I
I find disliking something
to be just as interesting and satisfying
as liking something after the fact
and no longer bothered by the idea that I
didn't like something you've got to get to that place
from plebdom you got to rise I think that's
where I think that the same
exact emotion you're talking about
is why people do
these things like I did with sort
on online or asterisk war where like
I think that when you
watch something and you don't like it at all
you feel that you need to
squeeze something out of it like you
have to get like because you've been so
wrong like my brother
Victor he's
but like long before I was even doing
YouTube like a couple
years before and I kept wanting to do videos
out of this but he would every time he saw
a movie he hated he would go on these
epic rants about them like
he saw like
that sounds like me in my youth he saw
fucking what's it called
Clash of the Titans like the new one
and he just like went on this
fucking tirade there's like 22
minute amazing beautiful tirade
it was the best thing I'd ever seen
and I realized that it's just because
he felt so robbed by the movie
that he had to like you know
feel something so like
he had to express his rage
so that he could then feel
a response to the film
have to feel anything at all
it's better to feel something than nothing
by the way D'Vu want to extend the olive branch
I didn't mean to be so harsh there I was
just finishing a point
anything you care to comment on now D'Vu
I said that was the whole sentence
you like stopped me at the end of my point
well then well done Nate alright
let's go into another facet of plebdom
that um
this is sort of changing the subject
but I feel like we've gone like
for a while we were doing reviewer rules too
so uh
getting back into plebs
really every video is a reviewer rule
it kind of is we tend to go back into that
that's our perspective yeah
but here's one that drives me crazy
is just the closed mindedness
of plebs
and I think that
a big part of being a pleb
is not realizing
how much more is out there
and how many different ways there are
to enjoy things
and just like holding up
in your idea of yourself
and what you like
and it's most common with I think
basically everyone gets into most
things through action
like we all probably
grew up watching more action oriented shows
than the ones we watch now
yeah would you say
yeah I remember like in like Power Rangers
and stuff like that when I was young
and then getting into DBZ
like next gen when you were
8 you know
well I mean not
no I mean I really liked Winnie the Pooh
well beyond the age
well beyond the age that I was supposed to
like Winnie the Pooh
which is now right
I mean I haven't watched it in a long time
I was really big into Winnie the Pooh
and it was great and colorful and fun to watch
it's great so comforting it's the best
the point I'm making is sort of that I think
when you're young you like action
because it's immediate and it's not boring
and you get the point right off the bat
like everything is clear to you
and like that's why
shows for kids are all action or comedy
like it always is and there was even a
like a quote from
like I first realized that
when I was like 12
and they were showing like some behind the scenes footage
of the movie
and the guy was saying like
because this is an adult cartoon we don't have to
animate shit because like with kids
great he was like with kids
stuff has to be moving
constantly or else they won't pay attention
but with adults to watch anything
well yeah I mean it's kind of true
that's such a weird reversal of like the normal
the normal attitude that like
things for kids can be shit
the funny thing about it is that it's just
animation because what carries
awkward teen hunger force is entirely
the voice acting and dialogue
it's really well acted
it's this weird offbeat humor
but like most of the show
is completely not animated
like it's just lit movements
and like nothing actually
moves and so
like yeah but he was like
and the funny thing is that of course
plenty of kids did watch that show
because it's still a cartoon
and it still you know
is the imagination of kids who've never seen anything
like this before but like
I just think that for
I think that for a lot of people
they never quite graduate
out of the mindset of liking the same
thing that they liked when they were young
because like you eventually have
this identity of I'm a guy who likes
action shows and then
until something disproves that
it just keeps getting stronger over time
that you just never believe that you'll like
something else unless it's proven wrong
dude that totally reminds me
that just makes me think of an example in my life
that you guys can probably all relate to
like because I want to make a distinction
between and probably should have done this in the beginning
between like plebdom and intelligence
because they are not necessarily
correlated at all
despite what Urban Dictionary would have us believe
case in point is my own dad
because my dad is a super smart guy
smartest guy I know probably
and like
he likes to watch on TV
like the trashiest shit
that you could possibly he loves
big bang theory
we're in it I hope you're recording
Jesse I'm making a fucking point get back to me when you're recording
already 15 minutes into this Jesse
well Ben jumped in like for the last
five minutes or one once that was fine
what okay I was just saying
that my dad likes super trashy shows
that really he just watches
like to turn off his brain
like to relax he's not
he's not us he's not a guy who's like
looking to like make the best art possible
he's a guy who wakes up works for like
12 hours a day doing like this
this you know doing
his job and at the end of the day he's ready
to fucking chill he just wants to like relax
and that is super pleb
but like it's not a reflection on the kind of man
he is it's just that when it comes to this art
he doesn't give a fuck you know it's a reflection
on it's what he's
looking for out of it and you can be looking
this is why people think that did you bro
use him as another example
so really I'm defending
I'm your I'm your people's champion so you
know don't cry into me but like I
think maybe a lot of people you know
if they get some opinion in their heads
they go into every show or everything
that they do thinking whatever it is
I'm gonna make sure it reinforces my existing
opinions as much as possible and that
may be why a lot of people to use did you as another
example think that he hates a one
shows because they're a one shows
and we'll go out of his way no you go in
I mean what you've told me is you go into a one shows
hoping for it to be the one that proves you wrong
right that makes you finally like it
I'm sure the people who say that don't believe
when he says that but we know him and we know
that I mean I mean not everyone
not everyone wants to be critical
of their media not everyone not everyone
really values art
in a way that we do
not everyone
it's way more interesting
it's way more interesting to go into a thing
thinking how is this going to change
into an evolved my taste
is this gonna be the country album
that gets me into country
I don't like country
I've
not been paying attention for a very long time
I honestly forgot you were here
and I
I realize that it's just because
I don't care about
people being plebs they can do
whatever they like
well you don't care about anything
let me go back to
let me go back to what guy was saying
real quick
let's talk about my brilliant points
about people
they get an idea of what they like when they're young
and then it never changes
I think that part of that
no it was me it's all me
I think that's
I mean people just don't
I mean when you're a kid you have all the time in the world
to consume all the shows and whatever
in games and stuff in the world
you tend to not have
either the time nor patience
nor even the desire to like watch more stuff
so you don't yeah so that just
that just kind of
my point is just don't act like
you have legitimate opinions
I wanted to get into Nate because
you were talking about your dad being a pleb
and like my dad's plebness
fascinates me so much
because like
like your dad he's a smart guy
not as educated as yours but he does read a lot
loves philosophy and stuff like that
so it's pretty knowledgeable
cool cool yeah
like all he does when he's not at work
is watch TV he comes home he turns it on
he leaves it on
I mean he doesn't necessarily pay attention to all of it
he'll like check his fucking tablet and stuff
but yeah he will get
instantly invested in
anything it doesn't matter
if something's on TV and he watches it for more than
one minute he is immediately
invested and you cannot distract him or else
he'll get mad that's not pleb
that's patrician as fuck yeah it
does not matter what it is
it's interesting because on some level
it is super patrician because like he actually
that's like me when
that's like me when law and order special victims
unit comes on and even though I don't give a fuck
I can't not watch it
special victims unit is great at baiting the hook
it's funny because I'm the type who like
I walk in and like
I can even like get interested
and I'll leave anyways because I'm like I want to do
something else but like
my dad will he'll just watch everything
and like
any TV show that's like actually good
or any movie that's actually good he retains
all of it he can remember stuff about movies from
like decades ago even though his memory
is ordinarily complete shit
but the funny thing is that
he's explained it to me before that like
TV is just because he grew
up with it and he like understands it
then it's very easy for him
to like just watch all of it like
he was like you know when I was growing up
you just watched all the TV that's just what people
did you sat down with your family at the end
like he said you know my parents would
come home and we'd all sit in the living room
and we'd all watch TV together and that was just
what life was you know so like yeah
that's so ingrained in him and he's
always said that like he's a he's
legitimately like afraid to play
video games because if he thinks
that it would take so much more investment
that he would become super addicted and it
would consume his whole life like that's
why he doesn't want to play games but like
but when it comes to music
for whatever reason he can't
as he put it he doesn't hear
music like
it just kind of starts playing and he
immediately stops paying attention to it
and like the only songs he listens to
are like stuff with catchy hooks and like
anything that's good for working out
he downloads these fucking
these like running mixes of songs
where it'll be like it's basically like
Eurobeat but like with a dance like
a dance version of a song
they're fucking hilarious but he'll
have like all this like trashy music
running to initial D music is just the most
awesome thing you can do with your life
well it's not like that intense
but like
he listens to like all this like
you know incredibly
plebbed here shit he once was
my favorite quote from him ever was
that Billy
what's his name Billy Joe Armstrong
he said Billy Joe Armstrong is the
greatest songwriter of all time
the guy from Green Day
and I was just like it blew my mind
so hard that he legitimately
thought that and then like
and he is like I could
endless treasure trove that's about
who's to say that he isn't though
I mean he could be but his reasoning was
that he had sold the most records
obviously I'm actually the greatest
songwriter of all time but taking myself
out of the equation I can see how
the way I would describe what my dad's logic was
for why Billy Joe Armstrong is because
he's the most successful
musician who my dad is also a fan of
like yeah not that
that's not good I like that because my dad
really values
like success like he thinks that if you
are the best seller then that means you
are the best but at the same time
if he doesn't like it then he's not going to
acknowledge it as the best so it's like
he should say
Gangnam Style is the greatest musician of our
generation then well that is a fucking
song I would say but
I mean he is but okay his name is
Psy by the way
Gangnam Style
his name is definitely Gangnam Style
he makes K-pop
and doesn't have anything to do with it
let's be honest what other songs is he ever going to write
he's Gangnam Style until the day he dies
he made Gentleman was good oh I like to hang over
I don't believe you stop it stop making up these
fake songs he's not a real he's not even
that song was literally just Gangnam Style
I don't even believe that Psy
is a real person I think he's like computer
animated like gorillas or something
he's secretly created
by Kesha so that she could make music
while still being locked into contract that
rapist she created
you know what I want to talk about
a small defense of plebs
and I want to make this a distinction because
there's I think there's a very big difference
that is extremely overlooked
between having
like pleb taste as
in you only like
shit and you have no good reasons for it
and then I think there's
an underrated populace
of people who
don't know a lot of different shows
but actually do
really appreciate the few things that they're into
on a really deep level
and I think a great example is
Jesse's musical taste
because if Jesse wants
I was what are you what is this
what is this attack on my character
as soon as I joined the podcast
I'm defending you first of all
but you sent me
not just insane clown posse
but like I had a bunch of my friends
make top 100 album charts once
and Jesse sent me one that had
like entire discographies
of five different artists it was like
all the gorillas albums
that doesn't mean I don't know of other music
I'm not saying you don't but I'm saying that like
it just seems like you really
appreciate those few bands
rather than like
getting into like a fuck ton of different
yeah because they're objectively the best bands
yeah like Jesse would say that like
the song he was listening to when he
when he plowed puss for the first time
you know that's a 10 out of 10 song just by virtue of that alone right
you're being a personal connection stuff
right I just remember
thinking like I saw the list and I was like
if anybody else sent me a list
and their top 10 was
what your top 10 was
I would probably assume they were a
I think that song actually might have been the Rambo theme
now that I'm thinking back to it
but because I was watching
first blood baby first blood
I was watching first blood part 2 on Valentine's Day
and I think that's what it actually was
I know for a fact that there's nothing
that Jesse loves that he couldn't explain
to me in great detail
why it was there you know
like if I said
like if someone else told me like
even if it's something as simple as like
I listened to it like when me and my best
friends had this like amazing car ride
in tune with our spirits and like 5 in the morning
just driving across the state border
running from the police like that's a much
more interesting explanation than anything
fucking anime everyday is going to give you
hold on actually
this is totally off topic but I think
it's fascinating I can actually
get that vicariously from other
people's stories has that ever happened to you
like you read
what happened to someone else
that's a mark of a great storyteller who can convey that
you know that's kind of how I am with everything
and I think when you have a personal connection
to something that's the most patrician
fucking thing there is you can like anything
you can like a fucking doctor
oh my gosh I just realized a huge irony here
saved your wife as a child and that's a patrician
doctor the whole time you were talking about
this I was thinking about this one older
cousin of mine who's pleb in the most
annoying way where she's like uh this is
this and her name is patricia
and so she's all like
she's like uh this movie sucks
like she just like says it and then like
she doesn't say anything about it
she's all like uh anime was a mistake
she just makes you feel icky about it
I also know this other girl who I knew
who was all like
that's what I thought you were gonna say
just like the people who are like that
and I think they're all women
like the people who are like uh this is
I guess it's plain I personally in my own life
I've only known women who are like this alright
I too hate women
I think we all agree
that kind of plebishness
is my favorite kind of I have to talk to that
the kind of people who don't even go on forums
that's kind of what I was talking about
you don't even go on forums
I mean like people who go on forums
have some level of investment
yeah that's true
but to get back to what I was saying
about the personal connections thing
like yeah I agree with uh
with Jesse I think there's a lot to be said about
if it still evokes those
feelings like
because I've had stuff where I had a personal connection
and then now I don't care anymore
and like it's just like
but sometimes
this is my favorite example because there's a song
by the band at the drive in called
invalid litter department
and it's one of my favorite songs ever
and every time I hear it
I think about how I read on like some random
it was on like songmeanings.com
or something like someone just wrote this thing
about how they were driving
with their friend through like some bombed out city
or something like like just passing by
in the middle of the desert and like blasting the song
and they were like crying
and now every time I listen to the song
I imagine myself driving down a desert road
with a bombed out village
crying and now that's my
that's why I like the song now
no that's totally normal
it's not even my experience but yeah
I think that's yeah
humans are good at that
I think that's what keeps
like me knowing that that's happened to me
is why I love my job
I see it from an outsider perspective
but I get emails from people who are always telling me
how like you know I've changed the way that they saw
certain shows and stuff and like
there's been times where
like my opinion of something was fundamentally
changed by reading a review
like uh
like these two Agiloch albums called
The Mansell and Ashes Against the Grain
and like at first I liked the first one
and didn't like the second one and then I read
this review where this guy made this like
really strong case for why the other one
was the better one and then once I listened to it again
I completely understood
and now it's my favorite one you know
yeah or like you bring up
sometimes that like when we did our Kill La Kill
podcast long ago we were both
warm to lukewarm but then something changed
and you fell in love and I don't know what it is
but it didn't happen to me so
well he was 8 out of 10 right out the gate
like hey yeah you know what that's a good definition
of pleb anyone who thinks Kill La Kill
is not patrician is a pleb
that is definitely true I agree
well I agree I suppose
but I don't think it's not patrician
I just don't love it I don't know whatever
I don't want to get into a whole thing
I came into this podcast late so I don't know if we discuss this already
but we discuss how
how completely stupid
this topic is and how
the word pleb itself is a word that only
fucking idiots use and elitist swine
would ever even use the word
pleb in the first place
like when I think of the word pleb
when I think of the word pleb all I can picture
is that anime snob
yeah we win over that
but I want to make one of the anime snob
I know how I want this
I know these kinds of people
when I hear pleb I think of my cousin
even though her name is patricia
I think of her and think yeah
this is a real kind of people and if you have to
talk to them it's a real problem
jesse if you want to talk about the snob
you have to do the voice
oh god
I want to suck so many dicks
I want to suck didgy bros dick
that's why I poke him in the back
like a little girl in third grade
I throw gum in his hair because I want to suck his dick
guys hold on I actually legit
I logged into skype earlier
and I had a message from him and it said
if I paid for the trip
would you come to the con in
Detroit
that's all it said and I was
so confused
that little fucking fuck boy
he's so desperate for your attention
no idea what Connie's talking about
or why
I don't know man but I
actually you know I wouldn't take anything from him
speaking of messages
why is he in Detroit
hippo
tell us about that dude
that musician
oh shit
he just said another message
after like a year
oh that's a great story
wait did you say he was in Detroit
he's playing Dark Souls
damn it okay I'm dead
didgy wait
now I can talk about it
I heard Detroit did you say Detroit in there
yes a snob is apparently
going to Detroit for an anime convention
was the only part of America that's similar to this
I was there yesterday
no no gay we'll come back
yeah cause
alright cause this was a guy
who wanted you to do some work
for him and because you didn't like his work
he accused you of being a pleb
for not appreciating it
oh yeah tell this shit
okay well um
last year when I was
just out of the pony
sort of stuff I stopped making videos
and he approached me
on deviantart and said
I saw you as a brony analyst
and I thought you could do an animation
for my music and he sent me his music
and it was absolutely terrible
and
like hilariously terrible even for
like a pony can we link that
just to bully that person and have everybody
thumb it down link in the description
yeah go ahead
he eventually got an animator to do
something for it so whatever
but I told him that it was terrible
and I didn't like it and I just
you know cause I was angry
the whole pony
stuff I didn't want to be associated with it
I told him to fuck off and he responded
immediately with a really long rant
about how I was a piece of shit
and how he had been a guitarist
for 20 years
and he knew what he was talking about
and then he accused me of
like lots of strange things
that like you couldn't
infer from what I said but he
you could tell he just had problems with people
who felt these certain ways about certain things
and then like
then like three months later
he responded to my same message again
as if he had forgotten
that he saw it before
yeah he just did it again
I guess he just went on deviantart and saw it again
and got angry again
and then a few days ago
it happened again
they're all completely different
very long
angry comments against me
and it was really hilarious
maybe he thinks you didn't read the first one
and he's trying to get you to respond
but why would it be like
the first one was a year ago
I think all this time
he's been waiting for you to respond
defeated and like apologetic
and he hasn't gotten his apology yet
so he keeps reiterating
the argument because he thinks you just haven't read it yet
I think that's what was going on here
I do want him to post again
so I'm gonna wait and see if he does that
I think that the attribution
of pleb-ness in this scenario
is really interesting if you pick it apart
cause like he's a pleb
he's someone who sucks
and he doesn't get that he sucks
but he's done it for a long time
which he thinks means he's better
but actually means he's worse
because he's been a guitarist for so long
and he doesn't know what's good
he has no ear for it
he made this song but he thinks it's good
and it's not bad
I listened to it by the way back when he first posted
but because you think
that it's bad
because he
has done it for a long time
thinks he must be good
it must be you that's the pleb
because you don't appreciate how good this thing
must necessarily be
due to how good he must necessarily be
not only that
but in some of his things
he accused me of being
he assumed that I wasn't a musician
because I didn't like his music
why don't you put down the guitar hero
controller and let the real guitar hero
you just brought me to what I think
is now in my opinion
the truest definition of pleb
and the fucking hilarious irony
is that that anime snob is the perfect example
I don't find that surprising at all
well it's only surprising
because that anime snob has seen
way more anime than anybody else ever
he's seen
an unbelievable amount
so you'd think he would have figured some shit out by now
but I think if I had to put
a word to plebness
and lack of intellectual curiosity
just believing that
you have reached the end
and that there's not further to go
and that is as opposed to
normies who just don't involve themselves
in any of this shit
I mean if you've seen
all the anime
and you still can't appreciate the good stuff
that's way sadder than
if you've seen every anime
and you don't understand why someone might like
kaon
it's that
at some point in his life
that anime snob reached the conclusion
that he understood what is good
and what is bad
and he's just applied that exact formula
to absolutely everything
and I think that is exactly
what
I don't want to accuse anime every day
of that but that's the impression I've gotten
from him and that's why that taste bothers me
because I think that's how you end up
with that taste is by being
that way
I think a true pleb is just
anyone who refuses to
see what someone else might see
in something
I totally see what you mean that you consume so much media
you don't get it, reminds me of a great quote
I know people who read
enormously, book for book, letter for letter
yet whom I would not describe
as well read
they possess a massive knowledge but their brain is unable
to organize and register
the material they have taken in
Adolf Hitler
who said that?
TWIST
FIGURE TWIST
it's amazing
wealth of Hitler quotes
no it's just that one
it's just that one
wait is that why I heard this before
because you did that one to me before
we're all sitting here nodding
agreement like man whoever said this
really knew a thing or two
oh my god
I'm blown away
we've reached critical mean guys
bam
he pulled that one out before
I guess we're Nazis now
this is the Nazi past now
the funny thing is I actually for a second thought it might be Maddox
because the way you read it was so different
oh man
well okay let's be real
I mean are we just gonna
disavow anything Hitler says just because he's
Hitler
well he was a vegan
if Hitler says the sky is blue
are we all gonna say it's green now
isn't this also a quote
no
that's the quote from me
if Hitler does X is it bad
no no no that exact phrase
if Hitler says the sky is blue are we all gonna
maybe Jesse said it in a different podcast
I've heard that exact phrase
yeah Hitler wasn't wrong about everything
we can all admit that
Hitler might have made
a lot of bad things
but he definitely wasn't a pleb
he was not
he might have made one small guffaw
once in his career
he might have been a pleb about painting
though maybe that's why he didn't make it
yeah that was definitely the case
he was so pleb with that it
created a deep frustration with him
about the world
plebness caused 9-11
that's what he did right
can I tell you guys about
you know I have a
do you guys have this as well
where you feel like
if you don't know enough about a subject
do you feel like inclined
to not talk about it
absolutely absolutely
absolutely not let me tell you people about homestuck
let me tell you about
the worst thing ever created
in the history of it
Jesse I would love to see you make a homestuck
review with exactly as much power
exactly
you know what guys
it's funny because we were arguing about homestuck
the other day for like 6 hours
it was horrible you guys are bad people
I went to motorcity
comicon yesterday
as soon as I walk in the building
was the first thing I see
two fat troll cosplayers
and I just instantly thought of you guys
and how much I hate ya
and how much I hate homestuck
it was you, it was digi and ben
dressed up as homestuckers
I found it in my convention
see the sad thing Jesse is that
it was the only one they ever dressed up as
the grey guy with the horns
that's all you ever fucking see
oh my god
I'm so fucking mad
anyways
what's his name
vagina or vaginal or something
there's 12
actually yeah there's 24 of them now
actually technically there's 26 with the
24 identical character designs
wow what a great property
what a great work of art
so the point I was trying to make
before Jesse completely derailed it with homestuck
is that like
the biggest reason I do so many anime
videos is that I just don't feel
comfortable that I'm like
like I have an authoritative voice on anything
else like I know
I know enough about anime to talk about it
and not that I know more than everybody
but like that I
feel that the shit I say is not bullshit
and it comes from a place of knowing
what I'm talking about and like being able to
comment on it and then like
when it comes to stuff like films
and comics and stuff like that that I don't
like even though I do know a lot
about them there's just this feeling of
I haven't seen
enough you know like I haven't seen enough of the
classics I don't know enough of the like the
real shit and I've seen these
it's like if you're gonna go into writing an analysis
post about it you're gonna have to constantly
double track to make sure
you don't get something wrong
not much about factual inaccuracies but like I've
noticed this and this is something that bothers me
about plebs and it's not
even that they're doing a bad job
it's the lack of perspective
where someone will sometimes I'll see
this happens a lot with like newbie anime
reviewers the perfect example would be
Madoka Magica where like
like my review that I wrote of it was
largely in response to the
the pleb-ness of so many reviews of
Madoka because
that show had a
really broad appeal like a ton of people watched it
like it was a lot of people one of their first
anime like it was
the biggest show of 2011
and there were so many
people who wrote about it as this
deconstruction of magical girl
shows or as this
they kept saying like oh it's like this dark
take on magical girls and I'm like
the fact is none of you
have seen any magical girl shows
and I know that like I know
that because like the next
most popular one card captor
Sakura is also dark
like it also has
death and themes of
like a like a
you know just like darker themes like more adult stuff
that you wouldn't expect because like Madoka
like the way Madoka is written
it's sort of as though like hey magical girls
let's be a magical girl it'd be really easy
it'll be really fun oh turns out there's a lot of death so
it makes people go oh so it must be representing
the entire genre
that it comes from right yeah that's the thing
like and it was funny because it was one time
I tried to I wrote a post
called like how Madoka Magica could be
a deconstruction of magical girls and the only
conclusion I could come to was the
fact that she never transforms
until the very end of the show
like you know it's not until the very end that she makes her one
big transformation and that's the only major
one but then I thought about it and
technically in card captor Sakura she never
transforms she just puts on costumes
that Tomoyo gives her so that was already
like deconstructing the trope
of the magical girl transformation because
clamp the artists they didn't
want to just have her transform into one outfit
they wanted her to wear different cute outfits
every time so there was no transformation
she just literally put on clothes
that her friends was making for her so it
seems like this happens with a lot of different genres with the anime
like I saw a clip of like an old Gundam
thing it was like you have to get in the robot
man he's like I don't want to I'm scared
the plot of the original Gundam
like it was like this is from the
80s like 15 years before even Galleon
and you're already scared what's going on
here I don't know man I'm just scared
everyone would be scared to get in the robot not just Shinji
Ikari come on man you pleb it's not
it's not wrong to say that like
Eva you know did new things with it because
obviously that's true but it is wrong to say it's
never been done before which is just showing
that you don't know fucking jack shit
there's really nothing always that Eva did
that had never been done before it was
a conglomeration of a bunch of good ideas
into one super good idea
you know
when it comes to reviews I'm always
really scared of being
caught out as
not knowing my shit
it's not
so much that people will turn and laugh at me
like you fucked up it's like
from that point on people will take me less seriously
because I was incorrect
well like if I want to do like a video about
movies I specifically writing
a way to where I'm not like putting on airs
of knowing what I'm talking about that much in regards
to video games I know enough
to where if someone who knows more than me
is going to correct me I don't feel embarrassed because
those people are like legit next level
like hardcore gaming 101 fanatics
I'll say though like
to give two examples of two similar
YouTubers who one
of whom comes off
as a pleb sometimes in a way that bothers me and the other
magically doesn't
PBS idea channel
that guy I know he has
an incredible breadth of knowledge I know
he always tries to get into every new
nerd thing and like if it comes to music
he knows everything he knows everything
there is to know about music he's into the most obscure
shit he's into the craziest stuff
I know he knows film pretty well but
he does this thing because
on idea channel he always tries to like
jump into every like big name
topic and sometimes
you can just tell he doesn't
know shit about that medium because
like it'll be something like
Madoka where something comes along that everyone
makes a big deal out of and he talks about
it in the way that everyone else is
without having the context that it's actually
not that impressive or different it pisses me
off that he like thinks it's valuable to like
restate what everyone's already stated while
adding nothing to the conversation those videos he makes
piss me off let me guess you're going to compare him
to nerd writer right because
with nerd writer he has
like this amazing ability that
I cannot like I don't
know how much like for instance
with comics he made this video about the
Sandman comics and like
it was so mind blowing to me
that after this guy had made all these
film analysis all these song analysis
all this other shit and then he brings
comics into the fold and not just like
a like one everyone knows it was
fucking Sandman and I was like does he
know a lot about comics
can he possibly know pretty well
much about so many different
mediums you know like he's fucking
he just does
he does analysis of such a broad variety
of subjects and he always gives this impression
like he's known about it forever like he's been a fan of
it since he was in high school you know like
I do I feel like
maybe it has to do with his writing style like
he's able to write it in a way to where it comes off
correctly whereas I did channel I remember
in his kill la kill video he was talking about
like the names of certain things
and kill la kill and he was saying you know it could
have been named that because maybe
they had their like play on words with
their words in the Japanese language and he
listed all these things and I'm like I made a comment
like dude yeah that you obviously only
know that by looking at it on Wikipedia
yet you wrote it as though you came
to that conclusion on your own
that was very strange and I remember
that's a good example because what made
that so plebby to me is that
that's every fucking anime
everyone's named after puns like that's
just yeah that's like one of the most
like Japanese humor is like
all puns they love
word play they love kanji
you were born to the wrong civilization
like because so much of
how so much of how they
title stuff is always that like it's
a play on the way the characters are read
because almost every character can be read
multiple ways so they have all these
fucking word play gags that never
are fucking translatable well yeah for me
it was just weird because he was saying it as though
he came to that conclusion but there's
no way he didn't just read that on Wikipedia
but he read I was like
I've never seen that before
in any video yeah I got you
I got you I have seen that
videos it's called body video
where everything he says is
recollected information from forums
true but uh
but yeah well he does a
nice strip presenting yeah I don't mind
I like his channel but
yeah he's been very
widely accused of plagiarism
you know what's cool is that all this time we're talking about
plugs we're talking about patricians and I'm
watching a super mario 64
speedrun the most patrician thing
depending on how far you want to get into it
I am watching a speedrun of an entire
alternate level map of entirely different
levels at someone's speedrunning super mar 64
super patrician go watch panic
koic 2012 patrician
actually you got me yeah man
brings me to another thing about like what I was just
describing though is like I don't know
about you guys but I feel like I will
never in my entire life
will I be the guy who knows the most about
anything like yeah no
subject on which I mean out of like the
seven billion people it's exceedingly
unlikely that you will be just because
I don't even think panic koic is the most
knowledgeable about sm64 is just he's the
only one with that level of knowledge who makes
videos right like I think there's always
going to be and I'm always jealous
of those people because like as much as
I love chaos and could talk about it all
day like I don't know I couldn't tell
you the episode names even you know
like and even with when I was into my little
pony and I could do that like I didn't watch
them over and over again I couldn't tell you
as somebody out there does somebody does
there's definitely someone I recite every
episode of the show to you I think
there was a period where a couple years
ago where I was probably in the top
500 globally of South Park
knowledge and like everything about it
like I could tell you things but that's I
haven't updated my knowledge you know like
I watched the South Park movie
it was with a like my brother's friend
and he had his older brother who was
like 16 or 17 at the time
and he was literally
word for word reciting
the movie as we were watching it
because he had seen it so many times
he had memorized it. Now see that's
that's fine you can do that if you want
I just I don't really feel the need to get into that
because I know I don't either I feel this
yeah but I just I'm much interested
when I watch a show I'm interested
in like what I can
get out of it intellectually you know
well yeah I think there's something more than just
wrote memorization like I feel like I may
have been one of the top people in terms of
like being able to understand
South Park in certain ways like
like after watching like every
interview I was able to figure out
exactly why their production cycle
is so hectic it's because they
back in the day they could never get around to writing an episode until they had no time left they just kept
procrastinating there's not a single interview
that says this but I watched all of them until
I was able to piece it together that's why by the way
that's why it's done like that it's just back in
the day they could never stop
procrastinating until they had no time left
and so they would just come up with whatever was in the news
and write that that was that's why they made
it like that and they just stuck with it because it was a
successful model but no one knows that but
me and now everyone listening to this podcast
well I think my envy
of those people is just that I think
to me you can never
analyze something too much because at some
point you get to where like the timbre
timbre timbre of someone's
voice top timbre like the timbre
like the timbre of their the way
that they their inflection when they say that
one line of dialogue and like why it
makes you feel something that they said it that way
like you know that could be
interesting thing or like why I just
watched this color being used in this
scene is like why it makes you feel something
and uh you know and
well we can ignore the color of the curtains
in the background make shit up right
again watch panicoic he just came out
with a video about Monty Mole spawning
oh my god did he do another commentated
no he has this other channel called
pan and kiyok because he doesn't
want to do narration that much it takes
too long so don't ask him or else
shout out to the least plead man in the
world pan and kiyok that guy
yeah I just I would
I'll kill everyone for another
fucking uh a rolling rocks 0.5
yeah I asked him about that I asked
him on the comment he made me feel like an idiot
because he was like you know people ask me about this
constantly that's why I have this alt channel
where I put out quick videos if people start
making me for commentations on my quick
videos I'm gonna have to make a secret channel
what does he feel fucking threatened by people
wanting more content man fuck this guy
take it back he's a pleb I fucking hate him
but anyway like if you guys don't know who we're
talking about he's the guy who said but first
we gotta talk about multiple universes
he's my favorite meme that guy
parallel universes yeah that guy
and uh what is it uh TJ Henry
Ryoshi yeah
best yeah that was the best like now there's
a fucking pleb
you can't say it's only a half
you can't say it's
half a press it's just an a press
you don't fucking get it
well hear me out
proceeds to parallel universe
did I tell you guys that there's
there's like there's I saw a screenshot
of TJ Henry Yoshi like commenting
on that video yeah I
that was a video that he did
and being like you fucking idiot you're so wrong
he got so blown out that he went
and commented on that video like dude I'm
sorry I was wrong yeah videos great
please make please keep making great
content I tracked down
that original comment on that video
long go and respond to it just like TJ you're
a fucking legend I love you
he's awesome
with his cool like ace attorney shades
or whatever on that Yoshi he's the coolest
I love you Henry shower so do we have
anything else to say about plebs you know
that's really the perfect example of pleb
and patrician TJ Henry
Yoshi and pan and cock that's
you know that's a good yeah
yeah it's a it's a it's a
legendary dance of two between
two lovers that will last
you know they'll be repeated it'll be repeated
again and again throughout history
I just I can't believe it super Mario 64
this this alternate level
universe is like so much better than the actual
game it's blowing my mind that I'm watching
this holy cow right well that's cool
well I guess that's a good place to wrap it up
let's say goodbye
folks bye
goodbye