Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever.
What's so funny best guy ever?
Oh nothing, nothing Ben.
Yeah?
What's up with you?
Oh you know.
Just thinking about you.
Just chilling.
Feeling good, feeling good after passing a fucking mineral through my fucking kidney
bladder fucking duct or whatever.
That was what I was up to yesterday instead of going to Anthro New England like I was
supposed to for a nice relaxing day among my own kind.
Instead I was in the hospital and on the toilet and in bed and in hell dying.
Was it like solid as you passed it?
Was it like the Kramer experience from Seinfeld?
You know Nate.
Yeah.
You know maybe we should introduce the others.
Okay that's true.
Let's get back to this.
Alright.
Tom's here.
Tom.
Great agony these days.
Yeah.
My leg is fucked to shit.
I'm feeling my age and I was also supposed to go to Anthro New England yesterday and
have a good time among characters.
Jesus Christ.
You were?
Yeah I was going to go.
What a coincidence that the two people trying to get to Anthrocon were struck in with illness
and weren't able to make it.
I was fine.
Just saying.
I was fine the day before.
I was fine every day.
It was truly a divine intervention.
That was the one.
Could this be the result of keto?
Could this be a keto?
I don't think so.
But you never know.
Fair enough.
Not a doctor.
Mages here of the lethal aurora variety.
I don't have problems as big as you guys though I am sleep deprived and I'm very cold because
of it.
Heating is on in my room.
It's kind of stuffy and it's warm and I'm still cold.
It's not like a physical coldness.
It's the kind you get when you're tired and you just, no matter how many you like it.
It's the kind you feel when your father comes home and tells you that your mother was just
run down by a reckless driver and he stares you down and deadens himself with alcohol
as he has for the last 10 years which may have been why she was standing in the street
waving her arms, jumping in the middle of traffic, hoping to be struck, to be escaped
from this terrible life.
Well not that kind of cold, but you're close.
No.
Okay.
Also, Endless Jess is here.
Hello friends.
I have removed my face and my skin too and this is my new voice.
Just like the Joker.
Who was telling me about someone, like their grandpa had to have an operation where they
had to like peel his face off and repair like a hole that had formed in his face skull.
Perhaps that was someone I know in my real life and not one of you guys.
Everything you just said terrifies me.
Is that like a Roger Ebert sort of thing where like they just like removed like a chunk
of his like skull and then it was a weird.
They didn't remove it.
They had to repair a hole.
They were.
Oh, they were.
I don't know.
This must have been one of my IRL friends telling me that this.
You know, forget who said it.
There's a guy in JoJo part four who's just a child with a hole in his cheek that like
whistles as he breathes in and out through the hole.
And then there's like some weird rock, paper, scissors badly has with Rohan.
I'm not going to worry about it right now.
I heard that JoJo is a bad show.
I saw this video essay on it recently about how a video essay you say it's not a rant.
By a drunken, enraged, shy man child.
Um, well, I guess that depends on how you look at it.
You know, actually, Jesse, I'm actually fascinated.
I have not heard a single person speak ill of JoJo except Jesse.
What was this person's case as to why JoJo's shit?
You mean, you mean Digi, right?
Yeah, you said, uh, I've heard no one speak ill of JoJo except Digi.
That's, isn't that what I said?
No, no.
Everyone else has said good things.
Oh, okay.
Right.
My bad.
I don't, I don't know what JoJo is and I never will.
I don't, I don't watch anime.
I'm not one of you.
It's a secret.
It's a sacred cow of anime right now.
I watched the first part of part four and I was enjoying it, but then I stopped halfway
through and I meant to pick it up again, but I never got around to it.
That's my JoJo story.
I read it.
I love it.
Uh, super great.
You're a big JoJo guy, Nate.
You're a big JoJo guy, right?
I'm such a big JoJo guy.
You've read the whole series.
I absolutely.
And I, the thing is, I'm such a big JoJo guy that I just sit here on my ivory tower looking
down in scorn at the anime viewers and just utterly disgusted by their base existence.
I was always under the impression that JoJo's Bizarre Adventure was just some Dreamcast
game from like 25 years ago.
It was a game.
And then like in recent years, I find out that it's like a real thing that is going.
Are you thinking of Chuchu Rocket?
No.
I, my old age-
There was a JoJo's game for 10 casts like way back in the day.
I remember reading about it in magazines and being like, well, that looks like a, like
a Marvel vs. Capcom ripoff or something like that.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure does sound like more like a video game than anything else.
Yeah.
Um, hey, let's get back to my kidney stone.
I want to dispel a myth because I learned a lot, I learned a lot about them as you might
imagine.
See, I had thought, I had thought that the horror of a kidney stone was that you had
to pee it out and that you would have to like push out this rock like through your
dick.
Turns out that's not untrue, but it doesn't, but it doesn't matter because at least in
my case, the kidney stone was tiny, it was like grain of sand size, like, and like peeing
that out is fine.
It's NBD.
It's the, it's the duct between the kidney and the bladder that's much thinner and that's
where it was caught and that's where it was painful and took like an entire day.
How'd you shake it loose?
What was done?
I couldn't really do anything.
They prescribed me, they prescribed me hella pain killers.
They gave me some serious shit.
They gave me, they gave me, they gave me, they gave me, first they gave me, they gave me,
they hooked me up to an IV and then they gave me a drip feed of something that she described
as a non-narcotic thing that she compared to like super Advil and I was like, okay.
And it took the edge off a bit, but I was still in agony.
And so she's like, okay, I'm going to give you some morphine.
So she gives me a bunch of morphine and media, media had prepared me to think that morphine
was like a magical, beautiful experience.
I didn't actually like it very much.
She was like, you should feel it immediately and you should feel like a warm sensation
going over your body.
It felt a little warm, but mostly it just felt like, I felt like muscle ache sort of
like spread all over my body and then like I couldn't move very much and it didn't even
make it hurt less.
It's still hurt, but I just couldn't move very much.
I was like, uh, and, but the one good thing it did was it made it easy.
I was able to like start dozing off under the influence of that.
So that was good.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's good.
But then, then she gave me Percocet, which is, which contains oxycodone.
So that's what she.
Oh shit.
Oh yeah.
So that's what I got.
She gave me a prescription for that.
I took it home.
Um, anyway, I think with a bubblegum crisis by the way, I need some of that for my fucking
leg.
God damn it.
All the pain pills they've been giving me have been doing shit.
I think I've passed it.
I think I passed this.
Okay.
So they gave me no joke.
They gave me paper cones with a like a fishnet plastic fishnet at the bottom to pee through
to catch the stone, to keep it, to, I get to obtain its power.
I think the idea is that you're supposed to bring it to a urologist and like they can
examine it and be like, okay, this is what caused it.
Like it's made of this, this and that, you know, help in diagnoses.
But not me.
I'm auctioning mine off.
Um, so.
Turn it to kidney stone.
It's like the infinity stone.
Email me at IASU.
IASU comic at gmail.com with your best offer or just, or just PayPal me and I will, I will
send my kidney stone to the highest bidder.
Any suggested starting bid, Ben?
20?
100?
Yeah.
20?
If we're not going above 20, I don't care.
It's not worth my time.
I mean, I had to suffer a lot to get this thing.
That's fair.
And listen, I have, I mean, I'm no, I'm no sorcerer or anything, but, but I have a feeling this
thing must be imbued with some hella dark energies.
This is like the male equivalent of like being a Snapchat thought, like instead of your personal
snapbacks or kidney stones and your blood and spit and maybe shit and cum, you know,
the whole works.
The whole works.
Send me, send me an email, serious inquiries only.
Again, it is very small.
It is only like the size of a grain of sand, but no solicitors unless serious.
Yes.
And that's it.
Well, there you go.
That's my kidney stone.
Truly a degenerate end to a horrible story.
And you know, as horrible as it was, it could have been a lot worse because at the end
of the day, I was, it only lasted like a day or so.
I'm glad to hear that.
But I have to ask the question.
I'm sure that's on everybody's mind.
Was it keto?
Will Keto cause my kidney stones?
Have we doomed a generation to a fate of horrible sharp pains through their kidneys
and bladder?
I don't think so.
But I mean, I don't know.
Drink water kids.
Drink lots of water.
If I were going to blame something, it would be all the soda I drink, all the diet soda.
The one thing, the one thing, okay.
So now I'm also suffering in a new way and then I can't stop shitting water.
But I don't think, I don't think that that's because of the kidney stone or anything.
I think that I caught, brought that on myself by like when I stopped at the CVS to film
my...
It was a damn gypsy curse.
To film my Percocet prescription.
I bought a bunch of bags of sugar-free candy and I ate like all of them.
So I'm pretty sure eating nothing but like sugar alcohols for like an entire day probably
fucked my guts up and now I can't stop shitting water.
You know what else has sugar?
It doesn't have sugar.
It has sugar alcohols.
Soda.
No, it doesn't mage.
It has...
Not if you get the non-sugar kind.
Yeah.
Sweeteners then.
Get the fuck out.
You're just like my fucking aunt.
Oh, you know it's rat poison, right?
Oh, you know it's rat poison, don't you?
Wait, what's rat poison?
Aspartame was what she was talking about.
Oh.
Well, great.
I'm just nagging you.
Good.
I hate rats.
Oh, rats are good.
Rats are good boys.
You said that.
They didn't...
Didn't I tell you that at the family Christmas party, fucking Aunt Kelly or Nancy, whoever
the fuck, I can't tell them apart, one of them comes up to me and she sees me putting...
Because we don't have any, you know, parents only had a limited supply of sweeteners so
I just like grab what was there, I put some aspartame, put some sweeten low or whatever
in my fucking coffee that I'm making myself and she goes, oh, you know what's rat poison,
don't you?
That is such a like family core thing to say.
So I pulled out my fucking, so I pulled out my fucking Glock, right, and I spun the camera
and I shoved it right up right in her mouth and I said, you know, you're gonna be rat
food, don't you?
And I pulled the trigger.
That's the right way to end that debate.
Fair, deserved.
That's what I call street justice.
Just to be fair, I'm not against like sweeteners instead of sugar.
I was just nagging.
I'm morally opposed to it.
I'm so fucking...
It's some pussy shit.
That's my shit.
Some pussy shit.
Listen, you know, I stopped at the CVS and I'm looking at the bags of sugar-free candy
and I'm like, I'm gonna do this right.
So I look at all the ingredients and there's basically, okay, there's good like recommended
like sugar-alcohols and sugar substitutes like xylitol and there's another one I forget.
Xylitol's one.
But none of them are made with the recommended ones.
They're all made with, oh fuck, malty, malty, malty, hold on, I don't know, there's two.
This is something, an isomalt and I'm like, okay, neither of these are the recommended
ones, but I look up the glycemic index of each one and I see that the malty, the malt
one, not that great, has a pretty high glycemic index, but the iso one has a low glycemic
index.
I'm like, well shit, I wonder, I'm gonna try it, I'm gonna experiment.
So I bought like a bag of the malt, it got like fucking Reese's peanut butter cup, sugar-free,
made with the malto stuff.
I got a bag of Jolly Ranchers, fake Jolly Ranchers made with the isomalt, and I'm like,
I'm gonna try eating these and we'll see if it knocks me out of ketosis.
I bring them home, I eat them, I eat them all, I eat so much of it, I'm sick, I can't
stop shitting water, but you know what, Pete on a strip, still in ketosis baby, fuck yeah.
That's all that matters.
Well you know, I mean what this means, what this means is that I literally can eat fucking,
I can eat fucking Reese's peanut butter cups and be fine as long as I get the sugar-free
nuts in the forest for the trees by like obtaining keto, but like eating nothing that has actual
nutritional value though.
You're a fucking hack, Nate, you're fucking stupid.
The point of keto is that you're burning fat, and if you're not giving-
Yeah, but you still want like nutrients, right?
Like, I don't know.
Nate, for fuck's sake, obviously I'm not gonna be eating nothing but fucking peanut
butter cups.
That's what you said you were doing!
Get the fuck out of here!
You said you did that!
Yes, I did it this one time, and it was a mistake, and I'm sick, obviously, and I'm
paying for it.
Okay, well-
I'll fucking end you.
I'm questioning your larger life choices here, at putting keto so far above, you know, this
other shit.
Is it worth it?
Yes.
Okay, whatever.
Because I've lost like fucking 40 pounds, and fucking suck my cock.
Well, sure.
And I still feel fat, and I still- and I hate myself, but objectively I'm less fat than
I was before, even if I feel the exact same.
So there!
I did it!
Well, good.
Wait.
That's- it's the- I blacked out for a bit.
Because the moral of this story, that you can be less fat, and all you have to put up
with is like a kidney stone and shitting blood for a couple days, because that seems like
a good deal.
No!
Basically.
One, kidney stone had nothing to do with keto.
Two, shitting blood, not water, and it's only because I made unrelated bad choices.
You can be skinny, and all you have to do is not eat carbs for like a year.
Easiest thing I ever did.
Bam.
Fair enough.
And I'm fucking mad about it.
Scooby says you can gain muscle while you lose weight, if you have balanced your diet
really well.
Yes, but what if I want to shit blood?
What if I'm sick of all of my blood, and I want to be ejected through my stinkiest hole?
I haven't discovered the secret.
I haven't discovered the secret of that yet.
I need to level up my water shitting abilities into blood shitting.
I mean, we're like 70% blood or something, that's a lot of weight.
So if you can figure out how to get rid of that, you'll be losing a ton of weight at
that point.
You won't even need keto at that rate.
If I get rid of all this blood inside me, I'll have more room for muscle.
You know, that's fucking true.
I'll take my blood out and fill it up with pure electrolytes, for peak male performance.
Hey, if Metal Gear Rising Revenge and Sod is said, electrolytes heal you to maximum
health instantly.
You just have to crush the spine of a robot.
Is it actually called electrolytes?
Is that what they're referred to as?
Yeah, Dr. Horace says you have to absorb everyone's electrolytes.
That's how you restore your HP.
Just drink some fucking Gatorade, dude.
Yeah, you could smash their spine.
Why would you drink a Gatorade when you can fucking drink the spines of Roboman?
Why would you drink a Gatorade when you could inject Gatorade into your spinal column?
Exactly.
Every enemy in the game is just a fucking bottle of Gatorade.
You could be Gatorade.
You just gotta cut the cap open.
Hey, you know that video Digi made the other day about, this is my story, this is my thing
for the day.
This is a fascinating tale of an adventure I had.
You know Digi's video the other day on Digiber After Dark, that was him talking about, like,
it's great to be a YouTuber where he talks about, you know, all the bullshit from being
a YouTuber and all that stuff.
Okay, so that was an interesting video and, you know, I had a lot of things to say.
I mean, Digi talked about it a little bit, but there was like, I was looking through
the comments because I was curious what people said.
I discovered one commenter by the name of Finn Sasuke, okay, Finn Sasuke, and I was
like, oh, here we are with like a fucking Naruto fan.
Let's see what this genius has to say.
And his comment was essentially like, yeah, bro, I've been making videos for years and
yet like, I've got like a couple hundred subs and like, I've gone nowhere, man.
Like what the fuck.
And I was just rolling my eyes, so fucking hard at this obvious poser at this obvious
pretender, clearly a Naruto fanboy piece of shit.
And so I'm just like, okay, let's see what you got, my dude.
Let's see what you've been working so hard on for the last millions of years for your
with your 400 subscribers to see like why you haven't succeeded.
I click on his channel and all of a sudden the name Finn Sasuke is not actually a reference
to Naruto at all.
This guy, I believe he's Finnish and he has a channel full of training videos for the
Ninja Warrior competition known as Sasuke in actual Japan.
And as I'm going through this backlog, I'm finding that this man has actually been training
for like a decade to compete on the Japanese Ninja Warrior.
And this is some of the most impressive feats of acrobatics by a human being I've ever seen.
He has constructed meticulously the actual set in his backyard that they use in Sasuke
in Ninja Warrior.
The Japanese one, not the American bullshit one.
He was very, I commented on it and I was like talking to him about this.
And I was just so blown away and I was really sitting back and I was thinking about, you
know, loser assholes like Digi who sit around all day and they watch anime and then they
talk about it on the internet.
Wow, so fucking impressive.
Like sure, he totally deserves the success he's had and the notoriety and whatnot.
Here's a fucking guy who's been training physically out in the dirt, out in the mud, physically
reconstructed this like obstacle course that isn't even, it's like the things that we have
to put this guy's link in the show notes.
It's nuts, the kind of stuff you have to do for this.
And I was so blown away by like, what have I done of any value compared to what this
guy does every day training on this.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna disagree with you Nate.
You know, as much as I, as much as I'd love to shit on you and Digi's uttered non-accomplishments
in life, how is what this guy's done any better?
Okay, okay.
He built, he built some shit out of wood and he's really good at like fucking jumping
around on it.
That's what it amounts to.
I'm aware that a lot of this is personal to me because I, I've been neglecting my physical
training over the last like month or two and I feel terrible about it.
And also, when I, when I was a kid watching Real Ninja Warrior, the Japanese were not
the American one that came later on like G4, they would play Rewinds like over and over.
Ben, you and I would sit down and we'd watch this.
And I always wanted to be like those guys.
And I always felt so bad that I wasn't, and I would, in the, in our basement where we
would watch this on our big old TV, there was an iron beam above like the, like going
across the roof.
There was like a low hanging ceiling, but like I could do pull-ups on that.
And in Ninja Warrior, they do these things where like you hang on, you don't have like
six inches to hook your whole hand onto like a bar.
You've got like one inch or like two inches to like hook just like the tips of your digits
on.
Yes.
So your finger strength has to be insane.
I would practice on that thing with my fingers, just trying to do it.
And I could barely do it for like a second.
So, so all of a sudden, this, this one man, Finn Sasuke has just brought down, he's reminded
me of my dreams of my path, of my past, how I want it to be a Sasuke Ninja Warrior, the
way he actually has tried to be.
And while it's absolutely true that like this guy isn't playing the YouTube algorithm
game, right?
Like it makes sense that his channel isn't like super popular, it's not like topical
or anything.
It's a passion project.
So on that, you know, what's the appeal?
Like I don't see that going anywhere as a YouTuber, unless you're like really charismatic
and you really like, you know, put a lot of like personality into your videos.
I went to the video just now to try and find the comment you're talking about and I haven't
found him yet, but I have found one comment on, on this video.
And again, this is Digi's video.
I found a comment from someone like a disgruntled Best Guy Ever fan pleading to you on Digi's
video.
What?
Best Guy Ever.
If you're watching this, take note that this is the ultimate proof to not partner up with
Digi Bro IRL.
Oh my God.
A fine friend to keep at a distance through the internet, I'm sure, but completely incompetent
in decision making and finance management.
And he goes on for paragraphs.
This guy.
Wait, who posted that?
Some Best Guy Ever.
Like someone who was worried about you, Nate.
Worried about...
This guy has association with Digi.
This guy sounds like he's coming from a position where he knows more or he thinks he knows
more than he should.
And what a weird cryptic username.
Dr. Wolf00.
This is so strange.
What could it mean?
Well, you know, Nate, this thing about this guy, you being all, ooh, cool, he's a really
good ninja.
He's so cool.
Reminds me of a conversation that I had.
He's a really good ninja in 2019, so is he really a good anything?
Reminds me of a conversation I had the other day.
I can't remember.
I came into the PCP Discord and I said, I just had an encounter with a genuine low
IQ male.
Yes.
And I said, Ben, I'm sorry, I won't bother you again.
Yeah.
But yeah.
Well, I talked to a literal moron.
Okay.
Now, is this something I should feel bad about, like, you're making fun of an actual retarded
person?
No.
He's not retarded.
He's got a job.
He's functional.
Okay.
He's just fucking stupid.
And it made me mad listening to him.
As it should.
Listening to his fucking twaddle.
And I don't know, among the many stupid things he said, there was, we were talking about
like a mutual friend of ours who I'll call Martin.
And Martin is a deeply flawed but charismatic human being who we kicked out of our house
because he wouldn't pay his fucking rent.
Fair.
Very fair.
Yeah.
So, you know, we've all got our grievances against him, but I still generally like the
guy.
And fucking, I'll just call him the moron here.
He's just, he's talking about like, oh, Martin, oh, yeah, I fucking hate Martin.
Oh, Martin's fucking, yeah, he's, you know, I don't trust that guy.
You know, he's terrible.
You know, unlike, unlike his brother, unlike, you know, his brother, his brother's got like
all the, all the, you know, all the good genes went to him.
You know, you might call him the Arnold Schwarzenegger to Martin's, to Martin's Danny
DeVito.
Danny DeVito, yeah.
I guess I might as well have said, he's like, yeah, that guy, he biked across the whole
country, whereas like Martin, yeah, but Martin, Martin just stayed here his whole life.
And I'm listening to this.
And I'm like, he biked across the whole country.
Good for him.
So fucking what?
What does that mean?
It like, what, what does that, what does that actually accomplish?
Why, why does that, why does that make him so much of a better person than, than Martin?
I suppose it just speaks to like general determination.
Like it does take a lot of like physical effort to do that.
You know what that reminds me of?
Sure.
I'm not, I don't think there's no value in it, but I don't think you can be like, this
guy biked across the country.
This guy didn't.
I mean, this sounds, this Martin guy sounds like he's done nothing.
So anything is superior to nothing.
I don't know what it means.
There's this gulf of greatness between them.
He has, he has many, Martin has many admirable qualities as most people do.
I agree with you that it's technically a worthless achievement.
But if I had done it, you bet your ass I'd be going around like, hey, none of you fucks
biked around the country.
I'm the best guy here.
Everybody look at me.
I would never stop saying that.
I, and I said, I said to this guy, I'm like, well, and I'm like, I don't think that means
that much.
Like, yeah, it's cool that he did it, but so what?
And he gets almost indignant at me.
He's like, oh, you do it then.
Well, you do it then.
That's, I'm like, do this thing that you just described as worthless and pointless.
Fuck off.
You idiot.
I want just to go around the country on a bike.
I mean, yeah, it'd be fun.
I think it'd be nice.
I'd like to go around the country in a car.
I don't think, I don't think it's bad.
I think it's neat.
I think it's pretty cool that he did something like that, but it, but it, it just pissed me
off to be like, yeah, this other guy is such a failure.
Look at, look at this other guy.
He did X.
That means he's better.
I, I am sympathetic to that and that's a fair point.
My boy Scooby 1961 fitness YouTuber I'm always talking about, he, he like once a year or
so will like a bike across something like Germany or, you know, like all of fucking
the Norse countries or whatever, something like that.
And like the kind of man he is, like when you hear that somebody does that, it's like,
they could be one of a couple kinds of person.
He like, there could be like a young buck trying to prove himself.
In his case, he's like a fitness nut who just like loves being outdoors and loves doing
cardio and loves going to like exotic places and seeing the world.
And so like when you hear a story like that, it definitely informs the kind of person that
that is.
And hearing somebody bikes across America, I, I don't know, it's kind of impressive.
It's like when people, yesterday in my, in my stream, people were saying, it's a little
impressive, but not that I'm not that impressed.
That's true.
I think it, it informs the person more.
It's like yesterday in the stream, some people were saying like something like, why does it
matter if I've had sex or not?
Like what's the big deal guys?
And I'm, and I'm thinking, I think I said like, what the difference is that if you have
lost your virginity, that shows a baseline level of social competence.
You were able to persuade someone to have sex with you.
I've learned something about you from that.
You're above zero.
And it's, yeah, I get, I get you.
And it's not that like, if you haven't done that, it means you definitely don't have that
ability.
Exactly.
Yes.
Of course.
I feel you.
I fucking love forests.
Forests are just like best.
Really?
I'm kind of surprised.
I can see your passion.
I'm kind of surprised to hear you say that.
You don't seem like the outdoorsy type.
I, I see, yeah, I stay at home, but I just, I just want to, I want to go to a forest.
Yeah.
I think we could all get down.
It just like peeks out her window at the forest outside.
It's like some day before you retreat.
Who is on the edge of the forest?
There's only a stupid river I hate.
Is it the river of tans or something?
He just like looks at the distant forest and just gives a little thumbs up.
Yeah.
I'm more into the, I'm more, I'm more all about the urban jungle myself.
I'm all about that hardcore parkour.
I am serious.
Yeah.
Fitness is cool and all, but I'm, I'm a bit more into forests.
That's my whole thing.
I'm so fucking tired.
I'm crying.
Time to sleep in the earth forever in the forest, I guess, and be one with your, with your people.
Exactly.
Like one of my dreams is like, when I die, or if I die.
If I die, okay.
I like, I like your optimism.
You too.
If I die.
To be like, like, I saw like people like, when they get burned into ash, you put them like into like this little pot and you like, you put a seed in it and they grow into a tree.
I'd like to be a tree one day.
Oh, Fluttershy.
Yeah.
There it is.
I agree.
That's how Fluttershy will become a tree.
She will die.
I want to be a cool tree.
I'd want to be like a pomegranate tree.
I want to be a weeping willow because they're the most keynote trees.
I want to be, I want to, I want to be an oak and make everyone miserable.
With fucking acorns and shit.
Yeah, exactly.
Like I have a, I have a oak tree back in the Fanny and our, it's kind of not our yard, but our, on our property sort of like my grandfather put like, put the tree in the, in the ground.
I want to be a hanging tree.
I put backwards.
Like the one that they hang people in.
The tree that people are hung from.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
I like to believe that in my next life, I can, I can contribute to the death of some people at least.
Yeah.
You want your, you want your kill count to keep going up.
Even after you've logged out.
How do you call those trees that have like, like branches that are just like going down and up like to the ground and they're like, they look like, like water, but like trees.
That sounds like a weeping willow.
Is it a weeping willow?
Hold on.
Google it.
Probably.
No, speaking about oak trees, total left turn here, but I just watched the movie Antichrist with Willem Dafoe the other day.
Is that oak trees?
Yeah.
Is that, is that a, who's the director?
Gus, no.
Say that again?
I can't fucking, it's not Gus Van Sand, is it?
It's Antichrist by Lars von Trier.
Lars von Trier, that's the one.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
And oak trees play a surprisingly large role in the film as the, the sound of when they're in a cabin in the woods and oak acorns are raining down.
And causing a lot of stress and tension all night long as they try to sleep.
I guess I won't get into it other than to say it was dope and I recommend it and I want to see spoilers because they're shocking and hilarious, but I won't.
I love, I love, I love weeping willows.
Like they make, they make like a secret hideout.
That's true.
I always wanted to have a sleeping willow hideout when I was a kid.
I drive by one every day.
Make a secret hideout.
Bring a cardboard box.
I realize that Tigger from Winnie the Pooh, he doesn't have a house.
He just sleeps in trees.
Hang on.
That's not true.
I heard you say that in your, in your episode.
There, wasn't there a thing where like Tigger, Tigger's house is like a weird ragamuffin thing with like, I remember him like sleeping in a sock drawer.
Wasn't that like a thing that Tigger did?
You're thinking, I'm pretty sure you're thinking of Jake from Adventure Time.
No, I'm not.
Uh, I don't know.
There was one episode where he was sleeping in Rue's bed.
Well, that's me.
He lives in a tree house.
You just type in Tigger's house and Google images and you can literally, it just, it took me two seconds, guys.
Hmm.
Well, Ben's been like just watching the show, so I assume not doing it.
Yeah, I may, I might have been wrong.
Okay, well, I know in the old shorts, you see him just sleeping in a tree at some point.
I guess he might still have a house.
Let's see, Tigger's.
I think that either got updated or like they like gave him a house later or something.
Oh yeah.
Huh.
Yeah, he's got, he's got like a moat and a tire swing.
Yeah, it's like a fucked up weird house.
Who says, who says the Tigger doesn't have any stuff?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe because his house is so fucked, he, you know, it's weird.
Oh, you know what?
In the episode where they crown him king of the beasties, you see the sign, you see this house.
I just didn't put two and two together that it was his house.
Oh yeah.
There you go.
Why doesn't everyone have a house in a tree?
Everyone else's house sucks.
Only owls and Tiggers are good.
Poo and poo and pill it and rabbit just living fucking holes in the ground.
Man, I want to spoil Antichrist so bad.
Just spoil it.
Nobody's going to watch Antichrist.
I'm just going to tell you the opening.
It is shocking and I actually hate when people spoil even the beginning of movies for me,
but I'm going to tell you anyway.
So if you don't want to hear it, log out for the next 10 seconds.
Willem Dafoe is fucking his wife in slow motion.
You see cock in pussy in this video.
Whoa.
You see it and as they're fucking, their baby gets up out of the crib, walks up to the window
and falls out the window and dies while they're fucking.
Nice.
It was a very dope opening.
That's also the plot of an Eric Clapton song.
Free falling.
Oh wait, that's not.
Not to get back on a happier note.
Hey, if I ever go to a Radcon, can we have like an outing to a forest?
Like a campfire and stuff.
You know, interestingly made.
So you're at Radcon Forest?
Oh yes, I know.
Damn.
Actually, at Radcon 3, as we were scoping out the location, we did note there was like
a swampy area and forest not far from the house.
It was on like the end of the street or whatever.
And we considered like taking cameras out there to like go do stuff.
Nothing came of it.
But it was all snowy shit at the time.
Yeah.
There was like a whole forest area right behind the house.
Good place to hide the bodies.
You know guys, I was thinking about this the other day.
Radcon 3 was dope and it was a great experience.
And I'm super proud that we did it and raised the money to fund it and whatnot.
But I have noticed that my YouTube channel was doing great until I started working on
preparing Radcon 3.
We were talking about this.
And I have not been back on the rail since.
I have, yeah.
I don't know if it was because of Radcon 3, but like sometime after, I'm still working
on stuff, like still working on, I mean I'm pretty much done with my part of T-Bat, but
I'm still working on 10 paces and draw.
That's getting pretty close to done too, but like I've got some more to do.
And yeah, my comics have come out much more sporadically since then.
And it's a real shame.
And I don't want to blame Radcon 3.
I blame myself, obviously.
Radcon 3 in 2018 was a lesson in prioritization for me.
And it was a good lesson.
And I'm glad I learned it.
And now I know.
We committed to so many fucking projects on that.
Finishing these Radcon 3 projects is like paying off student loans.
It is like paying off student loans.
Like here I am like a year later and like I'm still like, I'm just bare like, ooh, okay,
10 paces and draw, almost done, almost done.
Thank God.
Boy, Sharer is going to be sweet when I got that ball and chain off my ankle.
That's why at Radcon 4, I'm coming in, I'm cashing in for another lecture.
And that's all I'm fucking committing to.
Yeah.
It's going to be great.
I'm going to be like two lectures at the next one.
That's a good idea.
Maybe like one big one and two many ones.
It is amazing.
I'm just going to start my Animorphs lecture.
It's going to be fucking lit.
Oh, I'm excited for that.
Are you re-reading the books?
Or are you just cliffing?
I mean, I read them all again like last year, but I might do it again.
Are you fucking kidding me?
God, why?
Animorphs.
Because it's fucking good.
But is there like a hundred volumes or something?
There's like 80 something, but they're super short.
They're like fucking children's books.
It's fine.
They're printed in very large stuff.
Yeah.
Fair enough.
You can knock one book out in like an hour and a half.
Oh, okay.
That's not as bad.
I'm reading.
So I'm reading Ula-Liliya's newer book, Secret in the Basement.
And...
Sounds like my sex life.
Go on.
High five.
Yes.
Yeah.
It is about, well, I don't know.
I'm only on act like four out of like 20 or something.
It's in many ways very similar to...
In fact, I'm actually glad.
I'm actually happy with how similar it is to Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters.
It's about like a normal kid becoming super strong through RPG shit.
Cool.
Instead of about just like an alien who's already like the ultimate fucking champion of magic.
Well, that story is fascinating.
Like it's kind of boring in terms of like, you know, the guy's just God mode from the
start.
I mean Knuckles, yeah.
Knuckles is never in any danger.
Although, to be honest, this kid's never in any danger either because right from the
beginning he's got this wizard named Tristan who is just, he's just like, yeah, go on out
there and fight some monsters and gain experience and if you ever die, I'll just resurrect you.
Oh.
So, you know.
That's a shame.
Good to know.
I'm hoping maybe he'll subvert.
I'm hoping maybe at some point Tristan will get taken out of commission.
But, you know, knowing...
It would be good to ratchet up the tension for sure.
It would and that's why I don't think it's going to happen.
But I'll let you know.
Yeah, please do.
Please do.
Maybe he's going for the actual video game feel of when you're playing a video game, you
know you can always just retry.
So maybe it's...
I think he is going for that, yeah.
Yeah.
But like, yeah, what would make it an actual story is if at one point Tristan is gone and
there's like, you know, like, like in fucking, you won't, what is it?
Yeah.
When, you know, eventually Tom Cruise loses the power and then he's like, oh shit, now
I can't fuck up or I'll actually die.
Suddenly the stakes are super high.
Like that.
That would be a good, you know, bit that I'm confident isn't coming.
But isn't it just a fascinating choice though that he would like deliberately diffuse tension
just to make that kind of...
Yeah, I do.
I think you're right.
I think it's about, I think it's about making it feel like a video game.
Like you can die and you just respawn.
Yeah.
You know, this time he's going through, Tristan is like the shopkeeper, so he's got to like
buy, he's got to like buy items.
You know, he's got to like, he's got to trade in his old shitty copper fucking helm for
like a platinum helm, you know, because it gives him some sweet MP boosts or whatever.
That's the kind of, that's the kind of story it is.
Funny, I don't know, funny detail.
So the way that he accesses the magical world where he fights monsters and gains experience,
this kid's name is Richard, is there's a place in his basement and sometimes he'll dream of
the place and when he dreams, sometimes there will be a barber pole up on the wall in the corner.
And then at some point he meets, this wizard shows up to him in a dream, Tristan, and he's
just, he's just a fucking Dumbledore wizard.
He's got like a robe and like a conical cap with its lavender with gold stars and moons on it.
It says, you know, and it says he's got long, like 30 inch long brown hair, then some of it is like
collected in braids.
And he's like, hey, Tristan, so cool that you're a wizard and you brought me here to become an
adventurer and all.
Why a barber pole?
And Tristan's just like, I just really like hair and hairstyles.
And that's why.
That's why, I guess it could be anything, fair enough.
I just really like it.
I just think Barbary is a really cool profession.
That's how I feel playing Kingdom Hearts 3, like the people who make this game just really like hair and hairstyles.
Yeah, yeah, just like Tristan.
Tristan loves hair and hairstyle.
My name is Tristan the wizard and I sell hair and hairstyles.
One hairstyle, please.
It's like you buy like the hairstyle template so that you can just switch between hairstyles at any given moment.
Oh, that sounds like cable.
Yeah, yeah.
I love cable.
The kid in secret in the basement.
So, you know, in Legend of the Talonel Masters, there was Knuckles and Knuckles was all about magic.
He had really good magic stats.
But he had a friend who was even stronger named Speed.
And Speed was all about physical stats, in particular, obviously Speed.
Speed was like his speed and evasion were so high that it was like statistically impossible that anything could ever hit him.
And then this guy, this kid in Richard, he's all about defense.
Defense is like his top stat right from the get go.
So I think he's building like a tank build.
You have a good balance party there. You got like a DPS guy, you got a magic guy, and you got a tank.
I think so.
They could roll well together.
I don't think he gets to like Knuckles' levels by the end.
Like Knuckles is over level 9000 and so is Speed.
I think Speed might be over 10,000.
But I think, I don't know how high he gets, but he doesn't get that high.
Are they in the same universe?
They must be.
Because, well, I don't know.
Their RPG mechanics are basically identical, so I want to say yes.
I don't know, it could be Final Fantasy I, Final Fantasy II logic where everything looks the same and seems the same, but it's a different world.
Yeah, it could.
There's no hard confirmation as far as I know.
So there's a different fictional character named Knuckles that's not the enchilada.
Enchilada?
No, we're not talking about Knuckles the enchilada.
Knuckles the space wizard is from a planet called Corona.
He is two feet tall.
Corona, you say?
Corona, yeah.
He's two feet tall, humanoid, covered in purple fur, and his hands are slightly bigger proportionally to his body than you might expect.
Okay, so likely.
It's like a 1% increase.
It's like 30% increase.
If he were a human, you might say, huh, his hands kind of big, but he's tiny.
But he's two feet tall.
So his hands are tiny too.
Like maybe they're bigger compared to speeds, but not that much.
What about speed? What speed look like?
Exact same only, he's green and his hands aren't that big.
Well, there it is, I guess.
Speed has a special attack called the speed busher.
Which is he punches something so hard that it flies so fast that it immediately lights on fire and becomes a fireball that like crashes into whatever he punches to that.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
It's pretty cool.
Also, at the end of Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters, they walk up to the final dungeon and speed is just like, okay, I've been through the entire dungeon and disarmed all the traps, let's go.
It's left to be done at that point.
I don't know.
Literally the entire Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters is Knuckles waiting until the source of the future event that he senses.
Because he senses a future event, but he's never seen an event of this particular kind before, so he doesn't know what it is.
So literally the entire book is just killing time until it happens.
So Knuckles can be like, oh, so that's what it was.
And then Knuckles can solve it.
You know what's a game just like that?
You know, I think my Kingdom Hearts 3 video will be out by the time that this comes out.
So let me just tell you a fascinating story about Kingdom Hearts 3 that anyone who played the game should know.
It's that at the beginning of Kingdom Hearts 3, right, you're on a quest to uncover, quote, the power of waking.
You don't know what that's going to do, but you know what's important.
You're going to need it.
So what Sora does is he holds up his Keyblade and says, Keyblade, literally take me where I need to go.
I don't know. Please plot guide me.
And it opens a portal.
He goes through it, and it leads him to Olympus Colosseum, where in fact, he does not find the power of waking.
And from there, proceed to every single Disney world in the game.
Okay.
Just because it's where the Keyblade takes him next?
Well, it only takes him to that first place after that he wanders on his own.
But the portal took him to Olympus Colosseum.
He did not discover the problem there, or the power there.
After you've beaten every Disney world, there is a cutscene.
Sora says, huh, we've sure looked around a lot, pulls out Keyblade, Keyblade, where should I go now?
What should I do?
I've made no progress on this power of waking thing.
The Keyblade opens a portal, takes him to exactly where he needs to go to find the power of waking.
Well, he didn't have the levels and experience points.
He didn't have enough elixirs.
I mean, I suppose that's what we're supposed to infer.
He had the levels of elixirs.
He had to level up Kiraga.
I'm doing this in the video.
I'm going to just splice.
If you just cut every event of the game between entering that first portal and coming out that second portal,
if it just was that portal, nothing would be lost.
It just hasn't taken to the second place first.
Yeah, just do that, and nothing would be lost.
Because, okay, here's the thing that's infuriating.
The real power of waking is the friends we made along the way.
It's a real power, though.
It doesn't matter.
But the other thing is that Riku and Miki are trying to find Aqua,
who's going to help them, whatever she's important,
and she's trapped in the Land of Darkness.
They go to the Land of Darkness, they fuck around, and they fail, and then they leave.
They just come back again later.
Nothing has changed, only they've got new Keyblades,
because the first one's broke, means nothing to the plot,
and it's at that point that Sora shows up.
So, like, Riku and Miki were there doing the thing
that you come back later to find them doing.
My point is, literally nothing mattered.
None of those events made a difference.
Literally nothing.
And this is Kingdom Hearts 2 you're talking about.
This is Kingdom Hearts 3.
This is the new game.
Oh, okay.
Kingdom Hearts 2 has way more important stuff happen in the meantime.
You know what's weird about Kingdom Hearts, the whole conceit of the series?
Yeah.
Is that all these Disney worlds, they sort of retell the story of the Disney movies.
But, like, it exists in this weird continuity where, like,
from the perspective of these characters, they look back and think,
hey, remember that time where those three guys showed up,
and one of them was like a dog man, and the other was a duck,
and they just, like, solved all my problems for me?
And then they disappeared, and I never fucking saw them again.
What the hell was that?
It was like a whole universe full of people who just at some point in their lives,
some guys showed up, and it was the catalyst for their whole life changing,
and then they were never seen again.
That's how it works in all the games.
It's a weird place, but yeah, that's pretty much where Kingdom Hearts resides.
And you know what else I noticed?
I don't fucking know.
It seems like, so far in Kingdom Hearts 3, I'm not that far,
but it seems like in the story, nobody ever knows what's going on except for Goofy.
Like, Goofy is the smartest person in the fucking universe in this game.
How do you figure?
Every single conversation in the game is like,
Sora is like, oh gosh, I don't know what to do with the darkness
and the Keyblade heart over in the heart, nobody's heart,
and I don't know how to dark the heart with the nobody's,
and then like, and then Donald is like,
and then, you know, like, and nobody shows up,
and he's like, you'll never figure out how to fucking nobody the heart dark with the dark heart,
and then like, no one knows what's going on,
and then all of a sudden, like, Goofy will chime in,
and it's like, wait a minute, maybe we gotta heart the dark heart with the heart dark,
and then everyone is like, holy shit, Goofy, you figured it out.
He's like the only character who knows anything.
He solves every problem.
That's basically true, Jesse, but you know why?
It's because Goofy, Goofy like fits the logic of Kingdom Hearts perfectly
as basically the like, leads with his emotions, idiot, savant,
that just like, like, because every solution to every problem is
just believe in your heart and trust that you will, your friendship will win.
That's just because Goofy is the only one who's fucked,
so clearly he's just on a different level than everybody else.
Donald fucks, Donald fucks.
Donald totally fucks, get out of here.
Also, sorry, I had to go and shit some more water, but I'm back now.
Oh, that's cool, all right.
I might have to go again soon.
How exciting.
Yeah.
Well, all right, that's enough Kingdom Hearts bullshit.
We've been talking about this shit for weeks now.
For like weeks, for weeks and weeks now.
Oh, since we're switching topics, and I was just, didn't you want to say something?
Oh, right, I had a topic this week, and it was actually important.
So, we were talking earlier about like, doing a charity thing,
like maybe a stream or maybe bringing something up on the podcast,
and no, I had something in mind that I wanted to bring up on the podcast,
because, you know, I mentioned that.
You mentioned that.
Did we actually discuss that?
Well, only a little bit, but it's not what you think.
There's a specific thing.
Yeah, well, like, you know, the thing about charities is that they're all scams, obviously.
Yep.
So, it's probably better to go with a GoFundMe,
like to help one specific person who needs money,
and I actually have a GoFundMe.
It's not something for me.
It's not my thing, but it's someone close to a friend of mine,
not a person I've met, but an uncle of my friend called Ivan Ayala,
and I'm going to link this here.
It's called Angels for Ivan, and this is a GoFundMe that I want to fucking,
that I just want to shove in everyone's face right now,
since I have this platform.
Angels for Ivan is a GoFundMe.
This dude, my friend's uncle, my good friend,
his uncle, a member of his immediate family, was in a horrific explosion!
It's, uh, I'm assuming a workplace explosion.
This is not a joke.
This is real.
This is 100% legit.
Yeah, and I thought my job sucked.
Yeah.
I'll just read what it says here.
In a horrific explosion in January of 2018,
life changed dramatically for one loving and happy family.
Ivan Ayala suffered third-degree burns on 60% of his body.
He spent seven and a half months fighting for his life
in the intensive care burn unit,
and his wife took a leave of absence from work
so that she could be at his side day and night
through 27 reconstructive surgeries, skin grafts,
and subsequent blindness in one eye,
limited vision in the other,
and the amputation of his right leg above the knee.
Please consider becoming an angel for Ivan,
and for his wife and two daughters
as he continues his long road to recovery.
Please read below for the whole story.
And they got pictures here, and, like,
if you're, like, squeamish,
you know, be warned, because he got fucked up.
They're straight fucked, yeah.
I mean, it's brutal.
Oh, I expanded.
It's brutal.
Yeah, he lost, like, his whole body,
his whole skin, his face.
He lost a leg.
In the second picture, is this him,
unlike, like, the far left with, like,
the white rose in front of him?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, that's just...
Yeah, I think that was him pre-explosion, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yep.
So, he's a terrible explosion.
And so, of course, yeah, medical bills.
He's now, in addition to losing, like,
both of his eyes and his legs,
or one leg and most of his skin,
he's, you know, probably also going to lose a house,
because that's how it works in this country.
Who?
Being in an explosion costs money.
Yep.
So, they're asking for $25,000.
That's their goal.
And it's already gotten to $7,695, as of now.
I've already donated.
You know, I donate again if I come across enough money, too.
But, you know, so I'm just throwing it out there.
Yeah.
On my platform that I have.
Everyone, if you want to be an angel,
if you want to be a literal angel,
an angel for Ivan,
if you don't like yourself,
if you think you're a bad person,
let's be honest, you probably are,
the way to absolve yourself
of everything bad you've ever done in your life,
all those sad feelings and regrets,
just give, just give, just give to charity,
and it washes away the sins of the past.
Yeah.
If you've done something bad recently,
just give money to a man who needs it
and his family who needs it.
He sure does need it.
Holy shit.
This is, this is way,
I glanced at the lake before,
but I'm looking at the pictures now.
I mean, all right, it looks like,
I'm looking at this last picture here.
Yeah.
He looks, I mean, he looks like,
you know, he can still like live, right?
He's not like...
He's alive.
He's home.
Yeah.
He's alive.
But he, yeah.
He's going to lose his house, you say?
Is that the deal?
Because he can't work because he got so fucked up?
It says something in here about,
in order to keep our house and keep our family from
being on the street or something.
So fucked.
Like, is a man going from, you know,
fully functional to completely unable to work,
it's hard for me to think that that's only a loss
of $25,000, that it's not, you know.
Now that the family is fully reunited in their home,
Ivan continues to struggle with the healing of his skin,
adapting to daily activities without his right leg,
and most of all, the loss of his vision.
All he wants to do is to, again,
provide for his family as he loved taking care of them.
He is trying to maintain a positive outlook and look
to the future with his wife, daughters, family and friends,
but it is a long and hard road ahead.
He is yet to receive any amount of financial compensation
or any income since his accident,
and the family is doing its best to pay the bills,
now including expensive medication co-pays
so that they can keep their home and provide Ivan
with what he needs to continue to heal and recover.
Man, there's no workers come for that shit
if you're caught in an explosion at your job.
Holy fuck.
I don't see anything about, like,
what the circumstances of the explosion were.
No.
I'm assuming it was a workplace thing
because of that line about it.
Yeah.
I mean, I would think so.
Maybe not, maybe not.
I mean, they don't specify where it happened,
but still.
Yeah, that's Ivan Ayala.
I've never met him personally,
but he's the uncle of one of my best friends in the world,
my buddy Juan.
If you've ever seen the old video of mine
on the Blue Glow channel,
Juan's PS4,
where I borrowed his PS4 for a couple days
and played Call of Duty
and pointed my phone camera at the screen,
this is a relative of the eponymous Juan,
so he would certainly appreciate it
and I would certainly appreciate it,
and it would be a nice thing to do.
So there you go.
There's my topic for the day.
Oh, man, I see you donated a hundred bucks.
Yeah, sure did.
Oh, that's very generous, Mage.
Yeah.
See, be like Mage.
No, no, no.
Oh, Jesse did.
Oh, okay.
Never mind.
Mage, you're a greedy fuck.
I donated, but it doesn't show up.
I'm not sure.
Well, it'll probably show up later or something.
Yeah, it's given some time or something.
Well, best wishes, man.
I hope everybody ships in what they can.
I'm glad I finally remembered to say that on the podcast
because I've been meaning to.
Oh, there it is.
There you go.
There it is.
$30 from Mage Aurora.
Hey, there you go.
Awesome, thank you, Mage.
Moving on.
What else is going on, squad?
You know, speaking of terrible things,
speaking of bad things in this world,
the Pizza Party podcast just has me so fucking mad all the time.
What a disaster.
You know, I've got something special for you, Ben,
if we're going to talk about the Pizza Party podcast.
Are we doing the segment?
Are we starting the segment?
Let's just jump right into it.
Why the fuck not?
Let me get this right here.
OK, listen up, everybody.
We've got an updated Pizza Party podcast
shooting on segment song.
Everybody, sing along if you know the words.
Here we go.
OK, here's a little remix for you guys.
Benz is gay.
Hey.
And he likes to suck dick, especially mine.
Wait.
As you know, calling each other gay is the mean way to say,
I love you.
But fuck the Pizza Party podcast.
There you go.
There it is.
All right.
I'll take it.
We had a message about that.
We got some grievances.
You want me to play that?
No, no.
I want to hear.
This guy Cheesy Manfredo said it better than I could.
Yeah, OK.
I believe I've got that queued up right here.
Let's get into it.
The problem with the PPP.
Go.
Ben, what are these weak ass complaints
against the Pizza Party podcast?
Let me air out the real grievances.
The Pizza Party podcast has been in a steady decline in quality
for the past couple of years.
And this is all due to the fundamental fact
that the Pizza Party podcast is not incentivized to be better.
Say what you will about the PCP,
but at least they try to improve.
The PCP restructured their whole fucking podcast
because they knew they were fucking up.
Damn right.
There's a financial stake in the PCP,
which is one of the main reasons why you all want to be on your best.
The Pizza Party podcast has no financial stake.
It only exists as filler between PanPizza videos
on the Rebel Taxi channel,
which Pan has made very clear since episode one of the podcast.
And that was great at first because we had a very loose,
a very entertaining podcast,
but now all the jokes and all the bits
and all the fucking talking points
have been run to the fucking ground.
The Pizza Party podcast is a zombie of a podcast
that only exists to take up space.
And you know what's even worse?
They won't listen to this
because they're on that bullshit mentality of,
oh, well, this podcast has always been shit.
If you don't like it, then don't watch it.
Fuck off.
Make a better podcast.
If your podcast is shit, make a better podcast.
Pizza Party got me fucked up.
All right.
There you go.
That's what I've been saying this whole time.
Right.
Interesting that he cites like the financial incentives
at play in the PCP
as like a beneficial aspect,
which I certainly would agree with.
So I wonder if the cost structure,
the payment structure of the Pizza Party podcast,
obviously it's on PanPizza's channel.
Maybe they just don't even get paid for it.
Yeah, but well, I mean,
maybe he doesn't put ads on the videos
or doesn't have like a Patreon or anything,
but like, people show up.
Maybe the other guys just do it for the exposure.
I'm just saying, like,
if you earn money off a podcast
that you're due with other people,
especially regularly, I don't know that he does this,
but it would be odd to me to just keep it all.
Maybe they like, because he's got a big platform
on his channel, maybe they like,
maybe he doesn't monetize them or charge for them on Patreon.
Maybe he doesn't actually make anything from them.
Maybe. Maybe they're just filler in that sense.
But I don't know, because I can't find the podcast.
Hashtag where's the podcast.
Yeah, good podcast.
Nice job making an invisible podcast, my dude.
It's not what I would have gone with,
I'd say.
No, indeed.
I guess that's it for the segment of the problem
with the Pizza Party podcast.
I think we've covered, I think we've done some good work
here today.
Strong investigative journalism, as always.
Go, as always,
let the Pizza Party podcast know
that we have some constructive criticism for them.
What did he say?
Oh yeah, and that line at the end about how
the problem with them is that
they wouldn't, and again, I've never listened
to it, maybe once when Digi was on,
just for a second,
that like,
they won't work to improve it
because there is no
like, because it's always been shit,
and like, we're not going to change, and it's a filler show.
You know, the thing is, I kind of
empathize with that, because people all the time
come to the PCP, and we'll leave like,
hey guys, you should do this, this, this.
Why aren't there more lectures on the channel, on the channel?
Like, blah, blah, blah, you should be putting
more effort into it, and it's a show
designed with only a certain level
of effort prepared to be put into it.
So like, I kind of sympathize
with that.
Sure, but that's not a defense of anything.
It's just a recognition of, you shouldn't
expect more if you know what you're getting,
I guess.
We do fucking, we did try to improve things here,
so I guess we're already doing better.
We tried so hard, and got
so far, and in the end, it made all the
difference. If I could only- If I could only
find the Pizza Party podcast,
I could answer some of these burning
questions, but- I don't even
know how to,
how can you fix what you can't see?
Just go let those guys know.
Where's the podcast? Where is it?
Hashtag where's the podcast?
That's what we need. Okay, moving on.
Let's get to the rest of the voicemails for this
week. We've got ten of them lined up.
First one is from
Zach. Let's get into it.
Why did you guys say
the editor contest is focused on audio
editing, but then proceed to encourage the
entrance to provide original graphic design?
What if you guys get an entry with a great
new design, but only decent audio, while
another entry has fantastic audio, but
no original design? Why not commission
an actual graphic designer, or hold a
separate contest to find the best possible
new design, and ensure you'll pick the
best possible audio editor without any doubts?
Fuck you guys, I'm an audio
editor, not a graphic designer.
Sorry about that, Zach.
Yeah, that's true.
We did talk about that.
We did mention that.
That's a very good point, and
I also put this in to remind myself
to say in this episode that
the hashtag piece of the editor contest
is over, people, and we have all the
entrance. By this, it'll be like five days
since it ended or whatever.
It'll be a full week when you're hearing this.
We are listening to those.
We'll be getting back to you, hopefully
soonish.
There's a person who had to hear herself say
I'm going to flip veggies in three minutes
for 30 times over.
Did you like it?
I can't honestly...
I hate it.
I hate myself.
I have not listened to any of the entrance yet.
I think May just listened to the most so far.
I listened to all of them.
That's dope.
We actually had quite a few
entries that had both
good audio
editors.
This is kind of what I was saying.
I don't think that editing a podcast
is like...
You don't need to be a super pro
audio editor to do that.
You don't need to have adequate
audio editors.
There were surprisingly a lot of entries
who didn't listen to instructions
at the...
I'm not surprised by that.
In the episode, we said
make sure you cut this part, team,
and make sure you do that.
In one when she was interrupting Ben,
I was like, you should cut that part out.
I kind of understand leaving that part in.
Maybe they were leaving it in because
when she was making an example.
There were other ones.
Shout out to one boy.
He didn't
put notes of...
He didn't credit himself.
But the guy...
He actually...
You guys joked around and said
everything is boring after Mage left.
You just cut everything off
when Mage left.
And he did.
He did it well.
That's funny.
We don't
hardly cut anything almost ever.
It's really rare that
anything will be cut
or whatever.
Yep, absolutely true.
Although, an editor offers the opportunity
for someone whose job it is to make the show better.
Possibly could cut...
Quality of life things here or there.
If something is a pointless tangent.
I don't know.
This whole show is a pointless tangent.
Well, that's fair.
It's a larger point here.
As an audio man.
I'm not going to lie.
When we first rolled out the first video
that we then updated.
That first video was flawed.
Because we should have talked more about the visual stuff.
So it's totally fair to be pissed off
that we weren't clear when that first one came out.
I get the sense that
people were submitting entries
and they all pretty much looked the same
and sounded the same.
And we were like, shit.
Everyone has just recreated the existing visuals.
And then just done
an adequate job of editing the audio.
And like, that's not
hard.
I'm surprised you guys messed up like that.
Because I do remember we specifically talked about
wanting the visuals
to be distinct and stuff.
I know.
It's because we included the visuals in the description.
Which gave everybody the
That did imply to people.
Just use these.
So it was fair to verify.
But that doesn't impress.
That just doesn't impress.
And I mean, it's probably late to be saying this stuff anyway.
But obviously the contest is over.
But my point is just to Zach here.
It's like, all along
this is just me. I don't know if everybody else agrees.
But I wanted an editor
who's the full package.
Who can do decent
image work and when asked
can provide art
that's not terrible in some way.
Like Ben was saying, and the audio has to be good.
But we don't need like
a serious crazy engineer
to like, again, I would certainly take it
if someone wanted to offer those services.
But you know,
kind of the main thing we wanted
was like a refresh
of the visuals anyway. Which I tried to add
in the second version of the video and stuff.
So, you know, I feel bad if I mislead
anybody or got people's hopes up
who may have only a portion of it.
There was one entry that I would listen to
I don't remember who it was.
But it kind of struck me as
odd. Like, they edited
the audio quite a bit like
you know, they spaced it out
so we weren't talking over each other.
But they also...
I mean, several people did that.
But like, that one specifically
they cut out like bits and bobs here and there
like trimmed some audio snippets.
And like, in a way
you know, you could say
you improved the overall
um...
the audio, sorry
I'm so sleepy it's really hard
I'm tripping over my words. But like
it also sort of like took away
something from the product, I would say.
Like, oddly like
the charm was lacking of our just little
nonsense of
talks and stuff. Well, now
I really want to give you these a listen and compare.
Yeah, me too.
That's almost like an artistic choice
and kind of an aesthetic choice about how you want it to be.
In my notes, I did make a mention
that like, he seemed too
thorough or something like that into editing
and that kind of spooked me because
like, in this snippet
like in this preview
it's all fine and good but like when it comes to
actual episodes
when people watch our episodes
and they make comments it's like, oh then
you know, you didn't say that thing
or you missed out on that thing. But in the end
you might have said it but it got, you know, cut
or something. And I'm sort of like
it's a little iffy about
heavy editing of the audio.
I would go for a light
touch, I think.
I think the best
would be just, you know, to space out
so we're not talking over each other.
I don't even know
about that. I don't even know if I would go
that far.
The shouting over each other is a...
It's a tough balance because like if you
edit it too much, it stops feeling conversational
and feels a little like artificial.
It's super weird to have like two people shouting
over each other and then you take one and
space it out.
Not saying always to space it out but sometimes
we're trying, you know,
a conversation and someone speaks up and
the other is, like Manchi said
someone is talking and someone
speaks up and the other person continues
talking and they finish up.
So, you know, you just space those two out
so they're not talking over each other
but when it's like a little shouting argument
matched and you leave that in
or something.
There's definitely an art to it.
I don't know. Yeah, I haven't listened to a single one
so...
Regardless of that though, I've seen a couple of cool stuff.
I haven't looked through them all yet or anything.
So there's your update people and the whole contest
thing. We're looking at it.
I'm hoping by next week, among us,
we will all have listened and we'll be able to
like start organizing some stuff and then
we'll probably reach out and touch base
with the people we...
Because like we want to have a conversation
here. So we're gonna, you know, talk to the person
and see what they have to say for themselves.
I just want to also say thank you to everyone
who entered. Like, I listened to all of them
and all of them had their
strengths and weaknesses and stuff but they're all
good. They weren't like
super crappy or anything.
I'm genuinely surprised that
like pleasantly
by all the effort people put into it
is just, it's good. I'm happy. I'm happy
with you all. Good job.
I too am deeply grateful to everybody who entered
and took the time to do it. That's super
super swell. And we got a whole bunch to look through
so that it couldn't be better for us.
So I'm thrilled. I'm thrilled.
Hell yeah.
We're only an hour in. Are we going to
continue with the voicemails?
If anybody wants to like bring up something,
we could do that but, you know,
we could just do one round.
The only thing I want to bring is bring myself to bed.
I feel like I had a bunch of
things.
Maybe I already talked about your kidney
stone.
I don't know. You renounced keto for good
and all.
That's in the books.
Let's discuss trees.
I like trees.
I don't know. We could just do a voicemail.
You just want to bring up something. We can interrupt it.
Wait, what are you, tell us about trees.
I like them.
Okay, let's do a voicemail.
Okay, here we go.
Next voicemail is from onezumerkunt.
Let's go.
Disgusting.
So, uh,
if traditional media
is gay and dying,
and digital media is gay and dying,
well then what's a zoomer
like me supposed to do?
Maybe get out into the woods.
Maybe get out into the forest and look at some trees.
Everyone quickly into the forest.
Die right along with it. That's what you're supposed to do.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know. The kid sounded like eight years old.
He did. He sounded like ten or something.
It makes me uncomfortable.
Yeah.
No, I'm way into it.
I'm way into it.
We need him younger. We have to go younger, guys.
No.
Can't say that now, dude.
YouTube's cracking down.
It's too real. It's too real.
That's true. YouTube is cracking down.
I'm luring in the youth.
Did you hear how there's...
YouTube now has the ability to just shut down comments
on your entire channel?
I did hear about that.
So fucking weird.
Is it like shutting down the comments section
or shutting down your channel?
The comments in this case.
Yeah. They could disable comments on your entire channel.
So I guess just to go into that...
What if they suspect you of grooming kids?
Well, not that you're grooming.
What it is is that...
Let's back it up a little bit.
This is an interesting topic.
I've never heard about this,
but some family-friendly channels...
There's a family that had a kid
doing gymnastics.
That video got demonetized
and their whole channel got demonetized,
I believe, or at least many of their videos.
When they asked YouTube about it,
YouTube said the reason for this is because...
They later clarified, but I'll just put the whole information now.
It's because your content
has children
and we detected that
there are creepers,
like sexy timestamps of your children
and shit.
It's like it's assembling
a community of pedos.
We at the YouTube team reviewed these timestamps
and found them extremely sexy,
and therefore,
we decided to take action.
Can a timestamp be considered
lewd?
Oh, that might be.
A few hours ago,
I saw a channel that I watched
and he just reads out funny reddit stuff.
And he uploaded a video
of himself singing to his hamster
and out of all of his videos,
that one got demonetized.
It's just...
It's just a video of a hamster.
Peter's going hog-wild.
Oh, shit, I used the wrong term.
They're gonna be so mad at me.
Oh, no.
Can't win.
Remember that list
of new phrases?
Like, instead of grab a bull by the horn,
say grab a rose by its thorns?
Yeah.
That was real.
That's kind of a cute expression,
grab a rose by its thorns.
I guess so.
But what's objectionable about
grabbing a bull by its horns?
It implies a violence towards the bull, perhaps.
Does it?
Does it, though?
It provides at the very least self-defense
or implies self-defense against a charging bull.
Those horns doesn't harm the thing.
I don't get it.
What does he actually mean?
Take a challenge head-on.
But the thing is, a rose is very different
from a charging bull.
They are very different.
The phrase doesn't mean the same thing anymore.
Grabbing a rose by its thorns
just means doing something really stupid.
It's dumb.
Yeah, it's a very different constant.
The phrase works.
I think you just go right in there
and grab it by the thorns.
Yeah, I think it works.
I just don't know why it needed a new one.
I don't get it.
I think the context is like
grab a bull by its horns
because it would be probably a charging bull
and instead of running away,
you stand your ground and you charge the bull
and you lift it by thorns.
I looked up the list.
They had another one.
They changed to bring home the bagels.
That's anti-semitic, my dude.
What, do you hate Israel?
What's that about?
Come on.
Because who are the real animals
if not the Jews?
If you don't think
we should have bacon,
that one makes way more sense to me
than having a problem with grabbing a bull by the horns.
Bacon doesn't imply death of an animal
and whatnot.
Fair enough, I guess.
That's just dumb.
Feed a fed horse
is the change of that one long.
That's funny.
It is funny, but they weren't going for funny.
It's like any reference to an animal
being in any state other than
perfectly healthy and content is unacceptable.
It's just strange.
In the correction one, they still used a horse
but in the grab the bull by its horns,
you have to be nice to it.
You're being nice to the horse
because you're feeding it.
Can we do an objectifying animal like this?
What if you just gently
hold on to the bull's horn?
That would be considered sexual assault
mage and you need to let go right now.
Alright, let's go to the next
voice mail here.
It's another message from our old friend
ThemSnakes.
It would be cruel to see the horse
if it was fed already.
If you're just pouring more food into its trough,
it doesn't have to eat it or anything.
It is a waste of time.
But it does say feed.
I guess.
Moving on, let's talk about another of my favorite animals,
ThemSnakes.
My favorite pile of sentient snakes.
Let's go now.
St. Bans Cathedral.
A beautiful building.
Yet there is no Bans Saint to be seen.
I have sat here
for a month waiting for a meeting
of the mines.
I even learned how to use
a fake computer for this.
Perhaps
if I want to reach you,
I must sing a hymn.
The Lord's
Prayer should do the trick.
Ah, ah, yeah, yeah.
Autobiogenesis,
ketogenic symphysis,
doctor of the chase, cut the carbs,
burn bridges, burn paths,
communist your theories where I'm at,
pop with my class, struggle,
high marks, working hard,
society apart, and re-built it
in the image of God.
I'm a saint, and you ain't.
I've seen the doll, can't build the wall,
cause there's no place I ain't already been.
I'm a lonely snake, smuggling into myself,
a living pile of fear with no hopes
or dreams.
If I don't hear, I'm back from you soon,
I'll kill everything in the room.
Red wedding, ready, set, go.
To death, Macbeth, in the hellfire.
Hamlet, venom flows into your chest.
Heart stops, mic drops,
blood in the mud puddle, time's up.
Let the games begin.
You're more where to find me, Ben.
Them snakes on discord.
I'm waiting.
But I'm so fucking scared of him now.
Oh my god.
I'll be singed by beats that fire.
That was the coolest thing I've ever heard in my life.
That was fucking sick.
Them snakes just kick things up a serious notch.
Holy shit.
It's too good.
I don't know what to do about this.
He's just supposed to talk to you, Ben.
That's what he just wants.
My instinct is to hide.
He just fuels your absence in the cathedral.
I guess I'm going to have to
grab this bull by the horns
if you're part of the expression.
I won't, but let's move on
to the next voicemail.
Who's going to follow that one up?
Ah, here we go.
The voicemail from my old friend,
I can't poop.
Let's get to it.
The opposite of Ben's problem.
Here's the deal.
If you have suds ago or so, who cares?
You guys are talking about how sometimes it's troublesome to poop.
You just can't get it out.
It's like, yeah, okay, I've got problems like that sometimes.
Yeah, I guess you could call this hashtag relatable.
But then, the very same day
that I was listening to that episode,
I had trouble pooping.
I went to bed. Okay, well, I guess I'm not pooping now.
So, I wake up. I'm still having trouble pooping.
I can't poop.
What's wrong with me? No, it's not my problem.
It's your problem. You guys,
you ruin lives. You get people addicted.
You're the reason why people are dying.
And you're the fucking reason why no one can poop.
Why can't we poop?
Just let us poop, goddammit.
Ben is pooping for all of you.
We're the reason people are dying
of constipation.
I don't know.
Get some fiber in your diet, man.
Listen to prune man, who called in the other day.
Get your prune on.
Get your laxative on, if necessary, I suppose.
Yeah, I don't know.
I've still never eaten a prune in my life.
Drink a lot of water.
A lot of water. And I mean water, not like,
soda.
May have just been proselytizing at me
for drinking soda all day.
I'm so fucking...
So it is fine, but now you have kidney stones, right?
So don't drink soda while you have kidney stones.
I mean, that is...
Don't drink soda, period.
Soda is a trap.
It's bad.
I say as I have my polar pop of diet...
No, no, dude.
Diet doc pepper, but...
Do as I say, not as I'm doing.
It's the sodium though, right?
No, it's not the sodium.
I don't know what it is.
You say... I don't know what it is.
It's all the rocks they make it with.
Good, good, correct.
Next moil...
Next moil is from
Def Jam Vendetta.
Let's get to it.
I remember that game.
Used to be you wanted to make yourself known.
You proved your worth
as a street fighter or hustler.
We don't fight
out in the streets no more.
We're organized now.
Two gangster for the garden.
So we've taken it underground.
Underground.
I'm a businessman
and this is my
business.
My soldiers are legion.
Method man, noray,
capone, luda,
red man, DMX.
You want a shot at me?
You gotta make it past these brothers.
It's a dangerous world out there.
Seems every time I turn around
there's another young buck wants to take me on.
I lay down
for no man.
You want to take what's mine?
You gotta beat me.
But nobody
ever beats
me.
I...
What's he talking about?
Def Jam Vendetta.
Oh yeah, Def Jam Vendetta.
For the PSU.
I went and listened to it.
It's the verbatim line for line.
Intro to Def Jam Vendetta.
Even Red Man?
Yeah, it's a rapper
fighting game for the PSU.
I was gonna say
the line sound like from a video game.
Yeah, Def Jam Vendetta.
It's a classic back in the day.
It's good.
I think it actually reviewed decent.
Is it like a WWE style game?
There was Def Jam Vendetta,
then there was Def Jam Fight for New York.
Wait, is it a fighting game
or is it like a rap battling game?
The first Def Jam game was
more like a straight wrestling game.
Def Jam Vendetta was the sequel
and they made it a lot more arcadey
and a lot more fun.
You create your character and you rise through the ranks
and you buy ice with your money
from winning your fights with the rappers.
You buy ice? Ice like
diamonds?
Yeah, like diamond necklaces.
It's awesome. It's a good game.
It's the quintessential human experience
Oh, yeah.
The analysis that people are really clamoring for.
Speaking of live games,
did you decide what sort of big analysis video
you're gonna do on what game?
I voted for Fable.
We're looking through suggestions.
It's...
Digi doesn't have time to do shit,
so I'm taking it on myself to finish this
Patoon video I've been talking about doing forever.
So I have to like play Fable
to do that and so that takes time.
Just watch a Let's Play at times two speed.
Well, I guess it's still a long time.
Disgusting.
That's basically what Digi does while watching you play anyway.
So what's the real difference?
I know. I do all the work and he does all the bullshit.
All right, next voicemail.
This one's from Tony.
Tony Go.
Hello, PCP.
I want to ask why
you all think Final Fantasy 7 is so good.
I've heard so much praise
about that game
and it looks like garbage.
The combat is garbage.
I just want to know why so many people think it's so good.
Please let me know.
This is an interesting question.
And I thought the last voicemail was 8 years old,
but this guy was really...
It's interesting.
I've literally never played Final Fantasy 7
and I kind of want to just to like...
That's what Gib did.
Experience it now because I know nothing about it at all.
I sure did like it
when it was new-ish.
I don't think...
I don't think I would really like a traditional JRPG anymore
in the same way that I used to.
So I don't know if I would like it as much as I did.
Here's the correct answer.
The game is perfect and flawless.
The combat system is perfect.
The fighting is perfect. The gameplay is perfect.
The material system is perfect.
The stat mechanics are perfect.
The story is perfect. The characters are all fucking great
and fleshed out and three-dimensional.
It's unique.
It's got this great cyberpunk aesthetic,
but then as the game goes on,
it goes less cyberpunk and more into nature.
It kind of works with the theme of the game
because man's disregard for nature
is ruining the planet.
It's got all these great themes of environmentalism
and spiritualism.
And the story is so grandiose.
The story is big,
but also stays focused on the characters.
So it's really grand,
but also intimate at the same time.
The characters, you fall in love with them.
They all have their own arc, their own story,
their own personality, they all interact great.
There's all kinds of great minigames.
You ride a motorcycle, you go ride a fucking snowboard
at one level, you get lost in the ice,
you can't find the map, you go around, you don't know where it goes.
The story is fucking, you know, characters
meet some grisly fates, you feel sad.
It's the fucking, you meet the guy at the end,
he's a really cool guy, he says,
oh god, my mom, he was an alien.
And he fucking burns people.
He goes crazy.
It's cool, it is good.
So you're saying it's a story about family.
It's a story about family.
I was just watching the other day.
It came out in like 2018.
It was just like some video that was like
seven secrets you probably don't know
about Final Fantasy VII or something like that.
And the conceit of it was just like,
guys, there's still shit that we are
uncovering about Final Fantasy VII
today that people don't know about.
And I can't remember any of the examples,
but one of the things was just going into
how much depth there really was
in the dating mechanic
which decides at the beginning of the game
who you go on the date with.
There's like a million choices.
And it doesn't even tell you. It's not like some crappy,
not like some newfangled thing where it's like,
oh, you got five relationship points
with this girl because you gave
Chie a gift or some stupid crap like that.
Aw, who do I pick? Do I marry Abigail
or Leah or Emily? I just can't decide.
It's organic. It's like a part of the game.
It never advertises itself as a dating mechanic.
It just happens in the background.
You just select your choices and just depending
on who you as the player organically
are inclined or gravitate towards
the other characters, that's the character
you end up going on a date with halfway through the game.
And it's like, it could be Barrett.
You can go on a date with another dude.
That's progressive. You can go on a date
with the yuffy, the 16-year-old.
That's even more progressive
in some circles.
That's considered progressive.
You know, it's cool.
It's a good game.
Can you go on a date with Kate Sith?
No, you cannot.
Here's the thing.
Did you know that if you cast Knights of the Round
on Genoves...
I think it's Genoves Synthesis, the very final one
before you fight Sephiroth,
then Safer Sephiroth
just has significantly more HP
when you fight him. It dynamically
changes the stats of the bosses
depending on what material you bring on.
There's this whole mechanic in the last boss fight
that you get to see is there at the end of the game.
Depending on how well...
The last boss fight is three boss battles
and then a fourth story boss battle.
That's not really real.
But depending on how well you do
in the first of this three-phase, massive-end boss fight,
you get to the second phase
and if you did really good,
then you get to use your whole party
in the battle for the first time in the game
right at the end.
You've got nine party members,
but you use three at a time.
They're all fighting,
and you can switch between group A, group B, and group C
to fight this guy all at once.
It's fucking mind-blowing!
It's the best game ever made.
Final, one of my favorite moments
is something that a completionist won't even see,
but is still one of my favorite details
about a casual play through
Final Fantasy VII.
It's that you learn limits
and you got to do... Getting Cloud's
Omni Slash Ultimate Limit
is actually very challenging for new players
because it takes a lot of work at the Colosseum and shit.
But
when you get to the endgame,
even if you have an unlocked Omni Slash
at the very final, like,
Kino one-on-one epic
Soul of Sephiroth vs. Soul of Cloud
out-of-body experience battle,
Cloud just... Doesn't matter if you haven't unlocked it.
He just unlocks his ultimate
Limit Break, Omni Slash,
and you just use it on Sephiroth
and think about what that implies
about the character rising up
and the ultimate version of himself to take on Sephiroth.
It's like, what could be cooler than that?
Nothing's cooler than that.
Man, I can't wait for all this
to be ruined in 10 years by the Final Fantasy VII.
It was ruined many years ago, dude.
We've covered this, Jesse and I,
in various videos and whatnot.
There's so many different, like,
mini-games and, like, games in the game,
like, different mechanics and all that.
So much love.
The Chocobo breeding is like this whole other experience
in the game and there's, like, depth to it
and stuff. And then you get, you know,
you get, like, a blue one.
They can go across rivers. They can get a green one.
They can go over mountains. You get a black one.
They can do both. You get a gold one, eventually,
if you're really fucking hardcore.
They can go anywhere it wants. You can go in secret caves.
Secret caves!
Yeah, Final Fantasy VII is a game about secret caves.
Even some of the character's back stories
are, like, secrets. They gotta be, like,
the most hardcore motherfucker on the planet
to even see parts of the story.
You gotta be hard... You wanna know about
Zack? You don't play Crisis Core.
You don't fucking buy a PSP. No one's gonna do that shit.
And that game's bad anyways.
Put a new whole new character in it. Didn't belong there.
No one cares about Jenna.
Here's a tiny piece of analysis.
Here's one tiny piece of analysis about that
thing. I think that the developers,
like, like, Vincent's story is, like,
complete. I mean, the character is secret.
But, like, even finding Lucretia, getting chaos
to the ultimate limit, all that stuff
is incredibly hard to find. And here's my theory.
Because development costs
and creating any one individual
piece of content in a game, like a Final Fantasy,
like the remake or whatever, has
astronomically increased in, like,
deep... Like, what do they have to make to make the Lucretia
like, side story? They have to make, like,
a new spooky area, like, make it
available on the map by doing a couple of crazy things.
You can only get there with the submarine, which is
a whole other mechanic. There's a whole, like, the whole
world map is doubled because you can go on the ocean floor
and a submarine and explore, like, a crashed
gal ninka. Indeed.
Considering the fact that, like, that world already existed,
it wasn't that much more work to make, like,
one new character designed for Lucretia,
which I think also shows up elsewhere in the game, too.
I could be wrong. And, like, to give her a new area
because, like, nothing happens there. It's not that complicated.
Because it was... Like, the threshold
for making that stuff
is so much lower, that, like, look at a game
like Final Fantasy XV, if you tried
to put, like, that much content
into a game like Final Fantasy XV,
it would be exponentially just
more dev hours, more work.
And, like, would those guys be able
to, like, justify it being, like,
secret and that hard to find?
They'd be terrified of doing that. Like, so much of what's good about that game
you almost couldn't even do nowadays, especially,
like you said, with the...
with how Square Enix is now, like, the amount of money that it
costs to make a, like, a AAA game and stuff.
Like, I just like a game that respects
my ability to find out
its secrets. And it's like that with Vincent.
It doesn't tell you anything. It doesn't tell you how to get Vincent.
You gotta find him on your own. You gotta answer
the dialogue boxes correctly. And the same thing with Yuffie.
You gotta, like, find her,
beat her, answer her, all of her dialogue.
You gotta, like, really, like,
play, like, this weird psychological game of, like,
okay, how would I use reverse psychology
to convince a 16-year-old ninja
to want to join me when five seconds ago
she just wanted to take my stuff? There's, like, a whole
side story of her that you can go. You can go
to see her hometown. And she's got, like,
like, a completely optional
character who is a secret, who you don't even
have to have to beat the game. She's not
even advertised in the game, really.
And she's got, like, her own story. And her story
has, like, all this depth and emotion
to it of, like, how she comes from this ruined
town that had this, like, this
culture to it. And it was, like, taken over
by, like, corporate interests and turned
into a resort town. And so
they don't, they don't have a culture anymore. So she's
going to, you know, she became a thief to
steal from people to get material. An analogy for Japan
in the post-World War II era, perhaps?
Who can say? Well, look at that. It's fucking,
it's smart. It's, uh, it's
brilliant. It is smart. It's fucking good.
It's just... And you know what it reminds me of?
I was, it's just a small last point here.
It's just that I've been playing a Hollow Knight
and trying to get the secret ending, um, or the
there's many endings to Hollow Knight, but
the true ultimate ending
of To Get of Hollow Knight
is so unbelievably challenging
to actually do.
You have to do, I wouldn't even go into it, but
it's at the end of the Godmaster DLC. You have to do
so much fucking shit and
defeat, like, this ultimate gauntlet of
every single boss in the game. All versions
of them. Uh, and then you fight
the true super version of the final boss
for real this time.
That's how you get the real, honest God ending.
And I have heard, I just, I just
hear these fucking babies
just crying about how this makes
the game worse because it's too hard.
No! Break my spine, Hollow Knight!
Make me regret being born!
I want to be punished!
I want to have to earn it, goddammit!
Make me suffer so I can feel
something positive briefly
for that shining moment at the end.
That's what I want!
And games just don't do that, you know?
Not as much anymore.
I've heard, I've heard a completely
baseless rumor about Pokemon
that it's like, the new game
it might have
um, difficulty modes.
I hope so.
And there might be a folk.
We'll probably find out in two days.
Two days? Wasn't two days.
Then the Pokemon Directs and the Pokemon Directs
Oh my god!
You guys will know by the time this comes out.
Yeah. Well hot shit.
Well there you go.
How's that for an answer to your
fucking question, guy?
Yeah. Dude, is it good?
No. That's the short answer.
Alright, moving on.
Uh, next voicemail is from
uh, Kersh Keatman.
Kersh Keatman. Okay, let's go.
Did you really think you could
disrespect anime
and get away with it?
Oh no.
That's the end of the voicemail.
I guess we didn't get away with it.
We got called out.
What was he snapping there?
Like our collective neck, perhaps.
I think he was slamming the phone down.
Yeah, I was just going to say it sounded like he was slamming.
Oh Allah,
Best Guy Ever's World Famous
No Madam President video, which is
ripping off a vine, so not actually
my original idea.
That's just a high powered
80s businessman on the phone
making a deal. How dare you disrespect
anime. Smash is on the ground.
Cancel the deal. He's calling us
on the phone. It's like a
scare. It's like a dark and stormy night.
It's like this part in the Resident Evil 2 remake
where Claire, the phone rings.
She answers it, not on the other end.
He's dial tone phone?
She just picks it up.
Operator patched me through to the pro crowd.
Did you think you could sully the name
of anime and get away with it?
And then like an old timey
phone sound of like slamming in the receiver.
Damn it.
We've got big deals with those jabs.
We can't jeopardize it now. We won't have you sullyin' them.
The emperor is on the phone.
We got the emperor on the phone.
He wants to have a word with these pro
crowd.
Hey Jesse, is the
Resident Evil 2 remake good and should I play it
immediately?
It is...
Yes, it's great.
The short answer is that it's fantastic.
I have an inclination to be cynical
and say like the original is better
for this reason and this reason and this reason.
But you know, as far as anyone is concerned
who's not crazy like me,
it's fantastic.
Is that the one with the big spooky boy with the hat?
The ex-con give it to ya.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm gonna do it like five times in a row.
Damn you did.
And I got the S-plus rank.
I made sure to get it.
And I thought to myself, alright,
this is the best you can possibly do in the game.
S-plus rank. I've conquered the game.
Surely I will get the infinite ammo rocket launcher
for my next play with you or the infinite ammo
minigun.
Oh, I got infinite ammo.
Infinite ammo handgun.
I said what is this shit?
Take it back to GameStop. I don't even like it anymore.
Is this for a handgun?
Damn.
I get you coming and going.
I said you dirty dog.
Alright, next voice mail. Here we go.
This one's from Josh.
Josh, go.
So if there is a live action one piece movie,
Gustav will be played
by Will Smith.
It's Rewind Time.
Shit, what was that last one?
Rewind Time.
Oh, fuck.
Listen, no.
We got to get Benedict Cumberbatch
and Sanji.
We got to get...
Oh, God. Who is the guy in the Nike commercial?
Oh, God.
Colin Kaepernick.
We got to get Colin Kaepernick
as Luffy.
Okay, sure.
We got to get Robert.
Oh, wait.
We got to get Michael Cera
as Zorro
and John Cena
as Nami.
Yeah.
And so on in that order.
Eva Longoria as Frankie.
Sorry, John Cena as Frankie.
That's an actual recommendation.
Oh, I was going to say Eva Longoria as Frankie.
She's got the penach. She's got the style.
Only she can hack it.
She's got the character as Nica Roche.
Wait, isn't that the character's name?
I'm 16 and I'll do anything.
Mr. Sheffield.
I want to live.
The greatest actress who ever lived.
Oh, God.
All right.
Okay, another message. This one's called
The Perfect Procrastinator's Voice Mail.
All right.
I'm intrigued. Go on.
So, uh, you guys haven't been playing
my recordings.
So I decided to make a recording
that maybe the PCP would like.
They're all eight.
Hippocrite is, uh,
should videos and, um,
gay.
Yeah, you remember this guy named
Ben St.
Voice Mailers are funny, right?
Yes.
Yes, they are.
Nick Minion, I'm like Mike Minion.
Actually, this guy's a hellboy.
Am I right in a name?
I'm so stupid.
I'm so homosexual.
That's it. That's the end.
That's the end of the Voice Mail.
Um, well, I got a kick out of it.
Yeah.
We didn't say anything about me.
All he did was ask if you heard about me.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
We just moved on to bigger and better things.
He's already in full of a bunch of
Andy Milanakis fake
seven-year-olds.
Oh, my God, Andy Milanakis exists.
Maybe it's actually him,
uh, and, you know,
all our children voices are just slight
voices he's doing.
I just remembered, like, there used to be the show,
the Andy Milanakis show, and it was, like, the trippiest
shit.
I never saw it.
Now, Andy Milanakis,
he'd be really good
as Jin Bae.
Remember how
I, in the procrastination movie,
I wanted a digitally town-scaled John Goodman
to play Hippocrite?
I stand by it.
Obviously, Tom Cruise would blame me.
We've been over this. That was, like, a year ago.
We were talking about that or whatever.
The digitally descaled John Goodman's Hippocrite.
That's the best one.
This guy's 43. He looks 12.
Andy Milanakis? Yeah.
I don't know if that's, like, a disorder or disease,
but something's going on with that boy.
Oh my god.
Maybe he'll just live forever as a child.
Remember that little girl from Batman
who was, like, trapped as a little girl's body?
Yeah.
It was a fucking sick episode.
That's the finale of the Andy Milanakis show,
where he's breaking down in the hall of mirrors
and Batman has to console him.
I hope he has that,
you know, positive and ending.
Being covered by Batman.
In better ways.
And then sent to the insane asylum.
Well, it's only fair.
Okay, we've got one final message.
Okay, and this is...
Okay, this is a strange cryptic VHS tape we received.
This is a...
It's the Lost Tapes Archive Number One
Ben St.
What could this be?
I don't know.
Oh god.
Let's prepare ourselves our guests.
Here we go.
Hey.
I'm gonna give you something.
Remember that time
you left this tape in my house?
I've been warming it under my pillow.
It smells like gas.
It's our baby together.
Let's take a listen.
I'm the P to the E and
S, A, I and T.
I love real playing,
analysis and our T.
I'm Ben St.licious.
Did I feel good for you?
Tell you what, Ben.
Ben St.
I got something else to tell you.
Every time I open my mouth
a universe is created.
What the fuck did that mean?
Um...
Was that Tara Strong?
Did we get Tara Strong in?
No, I'm pretty sure someone was just
mimicking her.
Oh my god.
That was a flashback.
Dude, I feel like I just got punched in the face.
Yes. Remember that?
Remember when Tara Strong did that shit?
Yeah, I absolutely hate
the wood smacking and the noises.
Oh.
It's a deeply unpleasant individual, but
you know.
Post in the comments if you're Ben St.licious.
Oh my god.
Did any of you see
it's from a couple months ago
it sort of
kind of blew up online.
The video of Tara Strong
yelling at her Uber driver.
No.
I think it was kind of a scandal
because they were arguing about Trump or some shit.
I didn't watch it. I don't know what the fuck
I'm talking about. I just fucking...
I just remember it being a thing.
People were mad at her because there was a video of her
kind of like
laying into some hapless Uber driver.
Okay.
I mean, I assume Tara Strong was
the Trump,
anti-Trump individual here and was just, I don't know,
like maybe they were wearing like a Trump hat.
You know what? I'll watch it later.
It doesn't matter. It's stupid. I'm sorry
to bring it up. Who cares? Fuck it.
Throw it in the garbage.
Tara, she's...
God, Tara, that's not very...
Or maybe it's very Twilight-licious of her.
We never really determined what exactly
Twilight-licious means.
This driver was just too
Magalicious, I guess.
If you know what I'm...
Oh, I hear you.
Hey, man, I sure hope I can find
a fucking SoundCloud download
of that them snakes
and rats.
There's links. I got links.
Yeah, give me links.
I'll get to you after the thing.
Maybe we'll put the fucking SoundCloud link
in the actual description.
It's just soundcloud.com
slash the-pro-crastinators, I think.
And actually, after the one hour span
from when I uploaded these
before we started the episode to like now
or whatever, two hours or whatever,
someone already commented on here,
like, holy fuck, on that them snakes video
on them snakes tracks. So clearly some people
are trolling these
archives. The SoundCloud.
So that's cool.
Yeah.
I'm fucking...
I'm running with that. Them snakes blew it out of the park
and this Lost Tapes archive
number one, Ben St, also blew it out of the park.
And the problem was,
we got another voicemail.
Ben St content is just where it's at.
There's a lot of Ben St content coming at us
all at once, I guess.
I like it to cease.
They're all attacking
when Ben's weak on the toilet, leaking water.
They know this is their time to strike.
It's the hair cut, I'm telling you.
I did not receive such a warm welcome
when I had a lack of being able to produce
on the toilet, so maybe it's
those who poop more, receive more
in the voicemails, whereas
my constipation extended
to digital content being provided
by others to me.
Okay, anyway, that's it.
Wait, I have a correction to make.
Because I looked it up after I said it
because I was unsure.
Because I said that Def Jam
was like bad
and then Def Jam Vendetta was the sequel
and it was better. I got it backwards.
Def Jam Vendetta was the first one.
Def Jam Fight for New York was the sequel.
It was in fact
Fight for New York. That was the superior cool game.
And that's
I didn't want to get called out as a phony,
so I made sure.
And so that's it.
That's all I got to fucking say.
And don't forget to fucking do it.
Unfortunately, people will be writing
the problem is, Jesse, people already wrote
the comments.
They're gonna make themselves a fool.
That's true. Because now that I've addressed it
already in the same podcast, it is they
who will look like the fool. I am
the fucking master of this game.
I am the chess master.
I am the two boys in Kingdom Hearts 3,
the opening, playing backgammon.
I am the smart guy.
Remember when that guy,
maybe he didn't get here yet, but there's a moment where
they're playing a fucking chess game
or something with rules, presumably.
One just wins, and the other guy's
like,
you fell right into my trap, bro.
And he just puts
seven more things on.
The guy's like, what are you doing?
I just put seven more guys. That's how it works.
Who are those characters?
Do they come back?
Because I looked them up in the glossary, and it just said
white-haired boy and black-haired boy.
So is this gonna be like a fucking
lost thing where the whole
Kingdom Hearts story is like their chess
game, figuring out their candidates
for something? No, it's
a metaphor. You'll find out who they are later
if you don't already know.
I'll just tell you. Because if you're gonna
rip off lost, just give up, because
you'll never be as cool as
lost.
Okay, alright.
I mean, it's super obvious, in my opinion,
but okay, fair enough.
Anyway, patreon.com
slash the procrastinators people, we need
your money. So please
give it to us, and if you send us $5,
you get all the bonus episodes,
and I think there'll be one coming out
tomorrow. But also, don't listen to
that, because today's episode is brought to
you by gofundme.com slash angels
for Ivan.
The guy got his face burned and his body burned.
Help him out. Just
be the hero, and just do both.
Just do both. Yeah, we really appreciate that.
They're equally good.
What could be more good
in supporting your favorite podcast?
You know what's free though?
Yeah. Hugging trees.
Hugging trees.
Spending some time in the woods. Yeah, exactly.
Ugh, that's outside.
Yeah, the trees.
Follow our tree-related updates at
tpcrastinators on Twitter for all your
tree news. We're re-adjusting.
This is our new brand, and
I guess we'll see you next time. There's SpeakPipe,
link down below in the description.
Send us all your voicemails, people. Keep them coming.
They're just getting better, and I'm loving
what you people are doing so far.
And we'll put a SoundCloud link there, probably, too,
if you want to go listen to them, but, you know, whatever.
Who gives a fuck? But anyway, that's it.
Thanks for being here. We will see you next week.
Bonus episodes soon. Have a beautiful day
and a wonderful life. Bye!
Yeah! Bye!
Goodbye!