Hello, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Hello, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It is February 21st, 2021. Hey, the numbers are the same. This is Ben Saint and Gibbontake's here and Trixie's here.
That's true.
Wow.
It couldn't be more true.
No.
It's got to be a good day for witchcraft.
That's right.
That's also true.
If there's all those same numbers in the date.
I mean, that makes sense.
Well, for me, it's 2102, 2021. So it's mirrored.
A palindrome.
21.
No, it's not, actually.
02.
I found out the name for, oh god, this week I found out the name for and then forgot the name for when you have a sentence that has every letter in it.
The quick ramp box jumps over the lazy dog.
That's the one that they taught me, pangram. It's a pangram.
Ooh.
But there's a better one and I saw someone use it and I was like, holy shit, that's so good.
This one is Sphinx of Black Quartz, Judge My Vow.
What?
Well, now I want to write a song called pangram bars where like every bar is a pangram.
Walt's nymph for quick jigs vex is pretty good.
No, quick jigs vex bud.
That's not as good.
Glib jox quiz nymph to vex dwarf.
The Sphinx of Black Quartz is obviously the best one.
By Jove, my quick study of lexicography won a prize.
Waxy and quivering, jox fumble the pizza.
Wait, is it like every letter has to be used on the gas?
Waxy and quivering, jox fumble the pizza?
Fumble, fumble, jox fumble the pizza.
Waxy.
No, it's not, they don't have to only have the letter once.
There are no, there are no sentences that have every letter only once.
You could really, you could have a really long sentence that has every letter like a hundred times.
Yeah, yeah.
You'd technically have a pangram, I guess.
Would there be a word for like a pangram where each letter is used the same number of times?
That'd be a challenge.
I don't, I don't know.
Because Vow is so much more used.
They call it a pangram-banandam.
I think the one with only once is called a perfect pangram.
So it would be a semi-perfect pangram.
It'll be a perfect pangram tied to the power of something.
Mmm.
Yeah, that's right.
How's, how's everyone's week been?
Good.
Well, I've been.
Okay.
I was, I was against crypto before because of, of the old like the, the stress of, of like buy low sell high.
But I've, I've taken Digi's advice and I'm doing a long-term thing.
Good.
And I've purchased, I purchased a hundred pounds of Bitcoin and Ethereum.
And they've, they've been slowly going up and I'm just looking at it.
Wow.
Nice, nice long-term investment.
Yeah.
Wow.
They went up this week.
Cool.
Yeah.
And you know what?
They might go up even more.
They might.
They very well might.
We'll all find out together here on the PCP.
I, I keep, I keep, I keep struggling with, I keep struggling with, should I, should I,
last time I invested, it didn't go super great.
Obviously selling at that point was a mistake.
And now I'm just like, should I, is now, should I reinvest now?
Or, or is it, is it, is this as high as it's going to go?
I know it's been going up for like a while, but it can only, it can only do that for so
long.
So I just, I just don't know.
At some point there will be a dip and that would be when I would buy in if I were you is
whenever there is a dip, just buy the dip, don't worry about if it keeps going down, just
worry about if it eventually goes back up.
I, I've been thinking about it in a, in a sort of different way because I've been the,
the app I'm using is Coinbase and you can, you can track like the price of Bitcoin over
the past hour, day, week, month, year and all time.
Right.
And if I look at like, if I'm focusing on the hourly thing, it looks like it's tanking.
It looks like it's going so low right now.
It's crazy how much fluctuation there is on the hourly scale.
But then you go to the weekly and it's like, Oh, the dip is so small compared to the gains
it's made in the past week, it's unbelievably small.
So like when it starts going down, the, the, the natural impetus is to be like, Oh shit,
it's going down better sell now so that assuming that it continues to go down.
And then you realize later with hindsight that every peak before it goes down because it
just is really fluctuating.
It goes down for a bit quite sharply.
And then it goes and then it goes back up in a similar like sharpness and just goes past
the previous peak and it just has been doing that.
I feel like, I feel like a lot of people are like waiting for Bitcoin because Bitcoin is
like so unbelievable at the moment.
Like the first peak was quite huge and it made cryptocurrency so normal.
Like put it on the map, put people's attention on it and that has been dwarfed by how much
is growing currently that people are thinking, Oh, if it crashes and if I invest then I'll
become a super billionaire because now I know that cryptocurrency is something that is worth
investing in.
But because of that, I don't think it would ever dip so low ever again.
Because I don't think it'll ever get catastrophically low.
No.
So I feel like it's kind of stable now because of how famous it is.
It's not stable.
Well, not super stable.
I don't think it's going to dip to 2017-18 levels.
No, I don't think it'll go that low again.
But it could go down to something like 20 maybe.
A couple of interesting things about the future of Bitcoin is that there is a limit of how
much Bitcoin there will ever be and every year there is less and less of it produced.
So eventually all the Bitcoin will be in circulation.
So there's other coins are largely built off of Bitcoin's network or Ethereum's network,
which is to propel the faster sale of Bitcoin.
It's all such a weird system where everything feeds into each other.
The more you read into what the coins actually do, it's a weird infrastructure.
But as they grow, all of them will grow because of the fact that they are connected to each other.
The existence of Chainlink and Ethereum makes Bitcoin better.
So if Bitcoin keeps going up, those things, you know,
assumably, unless something were to replace them that did what they did even better,
I don't know.
But I think that so much of it is like...
Because I know XRP's whole thing is that it's like its own separate different network
that is all about the fact that they are installed in banks.
I don't trust XRP for a lot of reasons.
I mean, we have a history there.
I had some of it briefly.
I sold it when it was up, the one time it was up,
but it always is like minor fluctuations and the so-called promise of its eventual being
so mainstream with usage in banks that its value has to appreciate,
which is just what the people shilling it say.
But so when it comes to looking at the hourly stuff,
I really think that that starts to matter to people when you've got $45,000 invested in something
and if it goes up that hour and then you sell some of it while it's up,
you're actually making thousands of dollars and those little micro things actually matter.
But I had a period where I had a system of...
I had six different cryptos and any time one of them would go up by $4 from what I started with,
I would spend that $4 in whichever one was down at the moment.
Doing that, I could make net a couple dollars a week by just the process of occasionally trading every couple of days,
but it's literally nickel and diamond, but it can be fun.
Yeah, but at a certain point, there's fees, right?
Like the transaction fees.
That's why I would only do it when it was above a certain dollar amount.
Because the more you are trading the lower the fees.
So I would only trade at amounts where I thought it was worth the fee and I'd calculated that.
I spent a week just staring at these fucking metrics until I felt like I understood the ebb and flow of them.
Yeah, that was my week when I was way in.
It was terrible. I hated it. It was so bad.
A big reason why I haven't reinvested.
I was greatly enjoying myself, but I didn't have any money to put into it.
And this was at a time...
Chainlink happened in August, which is when I was trying to do a whole bunch of other shit to make money,
because I didn't have any money.
And I was like, maybe if I get on this Chainlink thing early enough, maybe it'll give me some money.
And it did, but only enough to put back into fucking around with coins.
So I spent a week doing that I really shouldn't have at a time when I didn't need to be doing it,
but it's paid off now because I've got like an extra thousand dollars in fucking coins from that.
Pretty good. Pretty good.
Yeah, putting large amounts of money in it increases the reward, but it also increases the stress.
I put £200 in.
Mentally, I've decided that it's like, oh, this video game called Cryptocurrency, it costs £200.
I've just bought a video game.
That's a fun way to look at it.
And I'm okay with it. It is gone.
And I know that I've invested £200. This is an S-run number, so I can look at how much higher it is than £200.
The moment's at £240.
So I've made £40 if I cash out now.
But I don't really want to go in and out because I just want to watch it.
It's nice that you also don't have to cash out all your money at any time.
You can literally cash out the extra 40 you made just to spend it.
I thought if Bitcoin is on the up, but if it goes in a majestic spike and it's like,
oh, suddenly I have thousands, then I will definitely take out enough money to reimburse my initial investment at the very least.
And then beyond that, it would be like, hey, that's pretty cool.
But if it all crashes down and I end up with nothing, then I'm like, well, whatever.
It was fun while it lasted.
It was fun. I saw a number go up for a while and it wasn't stressful because it wasn't a lot of money, so it's okay.
I am cursed. I am cursed because you say the more you put in, the more stressed.
That's true, but not just while it's in forever now because I had put in a couple thousand dollars into Bitcoin for a while.
If I kept it in, it would have almost doubled at this point.
So now the fact that I'm seeing it go up when I'm not, I don't have it.
Ben, you should just buy it as soon as possible to get this fucking bandaid off.
You have to replace this sorrow in your life.
It was bad before. It was bad while I was in. It was bad while I was in and it'll be bad and it's bad now that I'm out.
I'm totally doomed no matter what I do.
Think of your first investment in Bitcoin as a child that didn't make it to birth.
He failed a botched abortion.
You couldn't make it out.
Are you going to give up on ever trying to have another baby after that, Ben?
I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, I know it's going to keep going higher, but it could also crash.
It could also crash and that could happen in a week.
It could happen in a year and I just, I don't know.
I would just be like hold until it comes back.
I don't know.
OK, I lost money on the GameStop thing, right?
I put money into my Fidelity account.
I invested it in GameStop. GameStop crashed, of course.
So now I've got like a fraction of what I put in there.
You know, I just cashed it out.
So cementing my losses once and for all, it's fine.
The way that I have consoled myself is that I think I'm going to put that like couple hundred bucks that I have left.
I think I'm going to put it into my 401K so that, you know, when that matures,
it will be worth even more than what I initially invested into GameStop.
So who backs a 401K? Is that like through your bank or what?
I have an account with Fidelity. I think they just do it.
Is that an insurance company?
I don't know what they are.
I think they're a bank and they do trading, stock trading, and like they're like a mutual fund
and they have my 401K and they take my 401K money and they have an algorithm that trades it on the market.
So it's been appreciating for over the last few years.
Are they a healthy company? Have they been doing well?
I mean, I don't know how they're like stock performances, but they're like a pretty old company for a long, long time.
What happens to your 401K if Fidelity goes belly up before you get the chance to use it?
I would assume that it dies, but I mean, I think Fidelity is a pretty established institution.
I feel like Fidelity is one of those too big to fail.
How will established are we talking?
Like how many years?
I mean, good question.
Like what's 80 years if you're going to live another 50 years? You know what I mean?
Wait, what? What's 80 years if I'm going to live another 50 years?
Yeah, like 80 years of sort of like a business having survived is like not that much in the grand scheme of things, you know?
Like you got 50 ahead of you for the world to make undergo massive change, you know?
That's true.
If we have technological singularity, I don't know if Fidelity is going to be around, but cryptocurrency will.
I mean, maybe.
Okay, well, I would say that, yeah, it's true.
Who knows what will happen in 50 years, but Fidelity won't be the first to die.
Probably not.
Other institutions will die for.
It has been around, it was founded in 1946, so it is 75 years old.
So kind of old.
Very solid guess on my part.
I what? Yeah, true.
I don't know.
I mean, yeah, Fiat currency could just become obsolete at some point.
But who knows?
I mean, if that happens, we've probably got bigger problems.
I'm going to be curious to hear what the comment section thinks of this.
The last one, there were some people who were like, yes, Digi, who quote in the latest video says,
I have no money is talking about investment.
Great.
And then there was someone else who was like, Digi, you're fighting the good fight.
You saved these boys from hating crypto.
Like it would have been a nightmare.
I didn't hate it.
I had crypto, but I had crypto before.
I just fucked up with it.
The buy low sell high within such a small timeframe that I have an issue with
because it just introduces too much negative aspects to life in general
that I just don't want to think about it too much.
Long term is much nicer.
I can just put it in there and occasionally look at it.
I don't think people should be trying to make short term investments
unless they're playing with like fuck tons of money, basically.
When Bitcoin peaked around 40 before and then it started going down
and then I was like, I can't, I have too much in here.
I can't afford to lose it.
I'm cashing out while I'm just broken even when it was going down.
I was, I read like interviews with people.
I read like articles and some guy was like, yeah, it's probably going to go down
a little bit more.
I'm going to wait until it goes a little lower and then I'm going to reinvent.
I was waiting for it to go down to like 20 and then I was going to reinvest.
And of course it never went that low.
It immediately just started spiking again.
I think what it is is that people see it going low
and there's loads of people waiting to get into Bitcoin,
but they know that it's high now.
So they're waiting for it to go low and they don't know when.
They don't have patience to wait for it to go very low.
So they start buying immediately and it just goes right back up.
People are like, oh shit, it was high and now it's going down.
This is my time.
No patience.
The ideal situation is that everybody does just continually do that
until everyone has Bitcoin.
And then people remember that you can spend Bitcoin,
like regardless of converting it back into dollars in lots of places.
Most of the other ones you can't really like most coins like are best used
for trading for other coins or just cashing out with.
Bitcoin, there's like a website that lets you just trade Bitcoin
for what are they called?
Gift cards for basically anywhere.
So you can just buy a gift card and then go to that store's online store
and use that sort of a roundabout method.
But there's like...
So actually, do you have like an actual Bitcoin wallet?
I don't have a...
Like, I mean, I have wallets do various websites.
I have like my own independent wallet that doesn't have anything in it.
I think I only really have money through wallet websites.
Are you invested through like Coinbase or Robinhood or something?
Yeah, I have a bunch in Coinbase and a bunch in Uphold,
which is Uphold is what does all the transactions for basic attention tokens.
So that's why I ended up with that as well.
I have an Uphold account.
Okay, so I mean, you don't actually own the Bitcoin.
You're invested in Bitcoin, but you don't actually have Bitcoin
to like spend through websites and stuff.
You can spend the stuff that's in those website wallets.
Like, you just get the code for that wallet and then, you know...
Well, this is what I'm confused about,
because I saw there was like an app associated with Coinbase,
which is like decentralized wallet thing.
You can put your Coinbase money into that.
And they didn't explain why I would need to do that.
That's basically what Ben's talking about is like,
if you have your own wallet, then your money is...
You can have a physical wallet that is basically like a USB stick
that you plug in and it will store the crypto literally in that
so that it would not be like hackable for a minute.
Like, if Coinbase got hacked,
somebody could take my money from Coinbase, I guess.
Whereas if it was in an individual wallet,
they would have to hack my wallet, which is very unlikely
unless they like found all the codes and knew about it somehow.
Like, you know, that's basically why.
Cyber security.
Cyber space.
Hack the system.
Hack the mainframe.
Don't quote me on that though.
There might be other reasons to have a crypto wallet.
I don't have one, so I'm not going to speak with authority on the subject.
I downloaded a Dogecoin wallet, like when Dogecoin was spiking,
and I think it is still syncing to the fucking blockchain.
Sinking?
And I don't even know what that means.
Yeah.
Like, I downloaded it and it was like, before you can use this wallet,
it has to sync itself to the blockchain and it's still going.
Like, it's still not done.
Is there a way to, like, start over, like, quit and try again?
Well, I think that would just, it would just have to do it all over again.
I feel like maybe it's failed. How long has it been going for?
It might actually, I think I restarted my computer at some point,
so I don't know if it's actually running right now.
But it was going for, like, weeks.
It was just, like, the little bar was just ticking up.
And I don't even know how to use it.
I don't even know how to purchase Dogecoin in a wallet.
Right.
I mean, there's probably a guide somewhere.
Initially, I will say that the existence of stuff like Coinbase and Uphold
has made this a lot easier because, like,
initially I was trying to fuck around with, like, all the different,
because, like, Brave has a built-in wallet,
so if you use the Brave browser wallet, you have that one.
And then, separately, I had an Uphold wallet.
Like, I thought that the Brave attention to the,
or basic attention tokens I was collecting through Brave
would be in my Brave wallet, but they were not stored there.
Nothing has been in there.
And then I had, like, separately a wallet that I first got
when I set up my Ethereum two years ago.
So, like, yeah.
Having just, like, easily accessible websites made this much less of a fucking nightmare.
But I guess it's...
I don't know the security levels by comparison, but...
Anyway, enough about fucking Bitcoin.
This is a hate currency.
Bitcoin.
Yeah, more like Bitcoin.
Yeah, fuck you.
What do we have?
$558k.
Okay, that's cool.
All right, that's only, that's...
Oh, how many thousands of dollars have I missed out on?
No, you've got to stop thinking like that.
I'm gonna fucking kill myself.
No.
Yes.
Probably, like, six grand.
Probably, like, six grand you missed out on.
Six or seven grand.
Maybe thereabouts.
Maybe six or seven.
Maybe eight, nine, like ten.
Five, five-ish.
Maybe 15, 20.
100.
100,000.
20.
14.
0.
Billions.
If only, if only I had, if only I had invested a pizza's worth of Bitcoin back in 2003,
then I would have $18 billion right now.
Yeah, well...
If only I was born in the wrong generation, I would have grown up to be wealthier probably.
True.
Yeah, if only I was a boomer, I could have gone to college for $5,000.
I could have bought a house for, like, 2P.
But gotten a job as an executive bank CEO based on my third grade reading level.
Oh, I saw that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's sweet.
You know, similar to, I think this really was brought on by the crypto was, I was like,
ah, number go up.
Hmm.
You know what else number go up?
My age.
Idol games.
I'm going to die.
No.
It was an idol game.
It was playing Clicker Heroes again.
And now, I'm vegetable.
It's like saying I'm baby, but I'm vegetable.
That happened to me last week with Minesweeper and then again today for like four hours before
the podcast when I read the comments on last week and then was reminded of Minesweeper.
I'm just playing Clicker Heroes so much.
I'm getting so many coins.
I'm leveling up my heroes.
It's so fucking cool.
I had a great run of Noida yesterday where I was incredibly powerful.
I was tearing through the game.
I was obliterating the game, but I was greedy and I needed some mana spells.
I needed some mana regeneration spells.
That was going to be like, that was going to make put me over the edge, make me invincible.
The most powerful being.
So I knew of it.
I knew of a trek.
There's a secret zone where you can go to find this magic hourglass and if you put a substance
called teleportation in this hourglass, it will bring you to a secret chamber that has powerful
spells in it.
And I was like, I could get some really good shit in there.
So I went down to the bottom of the temple of the art, which is the last normal level in the game
because there was a big pool at the bottom of teleportation because these certain wizards
bleed teleportation when you kill them.
And I'd killed a bunch of these wizards and all their blood had pooled at the bottom of the level.
So I kept going down there and jumping into this pool of teleportation with a bottle trying to bottle it.
But every time I would get a little bit and then it would teleport me away randomly.
So I kept doing that, just trying to be patient.
And then the last time I jumped in with my bottle about half full and I go down there into the pool
and then I'm in there and it teleports me.
But this time it teleports me down under the level into the lava sea that leads to hell.
And I'm instantly incinerated and I die.
And it was pretty fucking funny.
Live and learn, I guess.
Live and learn.
Hanging on the edge of tomorrow.
I didn't think it would send me that far.
Die and learn.
More like.
Oh yeah, yeah, true.
Live and die and learn and live again and become a powerful alchemist.
And don't fuck with teleportation.
Just don't do it.
Yeah.
It's a cool name though.
I like that name.
I have found many secrets.
Many, many secret tricks.
Many secret tricks to use the various alchemical substances with in that game.
And it's very satisfying.
It's very satisfying because you can find this stuff in bottles.
Just like from the very beginning you'll start and you'll be like,
why am I finding a bottle of pheromones?
What the fuck do I need this shit for?
Ambrosia?
What the fuck?
Teleportation?
Worthless garbage.
And then you find this weird stuff to do with it.
Like you find, oh, if I bring pheromone to the Hisi base and if I, if I squirt it on a healer,
the healer will become my friend and then he'll heal me and stuff like that.
And, you know, I can use Ambrosia to circumvent the curse damage that I used to go through the cursed rock
that leads between parallel worlds and stuff.
What a fucking game.
I've been seeing, there's like new additions being made to it in the beta branch
that I guess you can play although I don't know how to do it.
But they're, they're, they're adding all kinds of crazy new shit.
It's so fucking cool.
I've been watching a lot of Noida, like YouTubers.
There are a few.
It's pretty cool.
A lot of them also do like Minecraft stuff and, and Terraria stuff.
Well, there are a lot of them dabble in Noida.
But I love watching people like make experimental wand builds that do like,
that do like quintillions of damage because of all these like multiplier effects.
Big number.
Yeah, the biggest number.
Yeah.
Like if, yeah, like the, the final boss of the game,
I think he's got like a few thousand HP to start with.
But if you collect the orbs of knowledge, then he will become more and more powerful.
And the most you can get is 33.
And then when you have 33 orbs, he has like trillions of health.
So you have to like, you know, to kill them then you have to have like high level
wand craft skills that like, like double quadruple quintuple, you know,
over and over again, your damage output or you just can't even touch him.
Great game.
That's all I have to say about it.
On Clicker Heroes right now, I'm working with big numbers, much bigger than that.
In fact, it makes your own numbers look stupid.
It's tiny.
I think at the moment.
Clicker Heroes.
At the moment, I've got my, my damage output among all my heroes is 3.771.
Euler's number to the power of 231.
I think that's Euler's number.
It's just E.
I don't know what E is, but it's more than like sextillion at least.
Why would you play Clicker Heroes or you can just play Cookie Clicker?
Because Clicker Heroes has a more satisfying like strategy to like progress quickly.
Then Clicker Heroes, then Cookie Clicker.
And also it's a Steam game.
So I can, I can block it with the block that I have for Steam.
So that I, so that I can't play it.
You can't play it.
During the week, which is when my block period starts.
Hmm.
Block chain.
Cryptocurrency.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I should block, I should block myself from looking at Bitcoin prices because it's just making me unhappy.
You should chain yourself to not be looking at it.
I should chain myself to a rock and let the buzzards peck my liver out until eternity.
Chain yourself to a cinder block.
Good.
And then jump down to a pool and you teleported into a lava sea.
Teleported into a lava sea.
Ah, circles within circles.
The way, this is really cool.
The way to get to hell.
The way, or the way that I've managed to get to hell is I use a spell called lava to blood.
And I go down underneath the world to the lava sea and I fire projectiles that cause the lava to turn to blood.
And then the blood gets hardened into volcanic rock.
And then you dig through this tunnel you make out of blood and volcanic rock.
You go down through the sea and then you get to hell.
Why is it turned into rock if it's blood?
I don't know. When you when you put blood on lava, it turns into volcanic rock.
Like water plus lava makes rock.
If you put water on lava, it turns into rock.
If you put brine in lava, it turns into glowing rock.
So, and if you put toxic sludge, it turns into toxic rock.
When you're a high level alchemist like me, you just know these things.
I've never watched full metal alchemists, but I've heard that that's a good one.
It is very good. You would definitely enjoy it, especially Brotherhood.
I watched the old series. I never watched the Brotherhood remake. I've heard it's better.
I don't know which one you would like more, Ben, because the first one's a lot weirder.
The second half of it is completely different from the original and just goes into such bizarre dimensions.
I thought the first one had a really good ending.
If you like the ending of the first show, you will like the first show more, I think.
I hated the ending of the first show at the time I watched it. I haven't rewatched it since,
but everybody I know who likes the first one more is a big fan of the ending,
and that's pretty much like the divisive factor, because Brotherhood is so much more traditional.
It has like a 14 episode climax of just everybody getting their own fight,
like all the big rivalries getting wrapped up, very satisfying shonen action type climax.
That's totally nothing like what the original show had.
When you say the ending, do you mean how they go through the portal and they come to the real world?
Like I said, the whole second half of the original show is completely different.
Literally anything regarding Dante is a totally made up character for that series.
Which one's Dante?
She was like the main bad guy who sends them to the other world at the end.
Wait, what?
I don't even remember her. What the fuck?
Yeah, there was a lot of shit going on, dude. That show was crazy.
It was a lot of shit.
Dante.
I remember seeing like a fucking...
Oh, she sucks. Oh, she's pointless. I don't like her.
There was this video by I think someone who made a pony analysis of an animation cycle,
and he made a full metal alchemist video about like,
this is how the blocking of the scene influences your eye so that you notice this thing.
And I'm like, oh, that's cool.
Brotherhood is good, but it's different, and it doesn't have those scenes.
I'm like, hmm, I don't know. I kind of like full by three shows, just aesthetically.
That's kind of the main point of contention between the two is that the first one is aesthetically superior,
because studio bones really was trying to make it a really fleshed out feeling series.
There's just way more filler, but the filler is good, and it's well animated and looks nice.
There's a lot of stuff in the performance is really good.
The original series is pretty tight.
There's some filler in the beginning.
There's a bunch of side stories, like that one with the guy who makes the puppet of his wife or whatever.
That's all fine and dandy.
And then about halfway through, when it starts to be the second half, it's all very tight.
It's all relevant.
The plot just keeps rolling along.
Brotherhood is much more plot focused right from the start, where it doesn't have the filler elements.
There's strengths and weaknesses to it, because I don't want to spoil anything for Hippo,
but there's a certain very famous character death that happens 24 episodes into the original show,
like 12 into Brotherhood.
It has way less emotional impact in Brotherhood than it did in the original show,
and that's something that people will point to as one of the highlight moments.
That's the thing everyone remembers from the original show, is death.
There's so much stuff that happens later in Brotherhood that that's pretty much where the story is.
There's two different deaths that could be what you're talking about.
The story is kind of diverged around what in Brotherhood is like episode 14, 15,
and what in the original is like episode 26, but that's the same amount of story is covered in that time,
and then they completely go in different directions.
Brotherhood is 65 episodes, so there's just way the hell more, way more characters,
way more factions, way bigger adventure.
It's more like Avatar, The Last Airbender, like that kind of plot progression,
whereas the original show really gets like...
Yeah, it's actually, it felt like a lot more at the time, you know?
65 was just a more daunting number back then, I guess.
Yeah, I mean, I watched, I've seen half of Legend of the Galactic Heroes, so...
Oh, really?
Yeah, yeah, I watched.
I wanted to finish it, it was really good.
Like the climax that happened, there's like a climax halfway through that's really good,
and I was like, whoa, what a development, I didn't see that coming.
And then I meant to keep going, and I just never did.
It's a hard one to keep up with, because there's so much you got to like keep inside your brain as you go.
Yeah.
And like keep track of it.
I was engaged the whole time.
I really wanted to keep going.
I think it would be a good show for that.
Yeah, it's good.
It's a pretty good one, it's a pretty good show.
Is Legend of the Galactic Heroes the one with the man with the hair, and he's like,
I'm from the 70s, like that guy?
That's the one, I don't know.
And he's got an eye patch and a jacket, and he's like...
No, you're thinking of Captain Harlock.
Oh, yeah.
Legend of the Galactic Heroes is like the most super serious space war story ever.
It's like, everyone refers to each other with like extensive honorifics and shit, like some...
It's a little bit like Game of Thrones and space.
Yeah, Game of Thrones is a really good comparison.
Is it similar in any way to space runaway Eadion?
Probably a lot less wacky than Eadion.
Like I said, it's very straight laced, it's very like prim and proper.
I posted a shot.
Pride and prejudice and anime.
Narratively, it is pretty much just like Game of Thrones in terms of like being the kind of plot to play.
Wait, I think...
There's a lot of episodes that are dedicated to political maneuvering.
And I was like, okay, whatever, and I never went to the second one.
There's a lot of political maneuvering and there's a lot of like military strategy.
Like, oh, you know, this army was like, you know, routed from behind with a sneak attack,
a pincer attack from the other guys and all, but then a third faction intervened.
And, you know, we use this method to circumvent it and da da da da.
It's cool, man.
It's heavily based in history.
It's like, it's meant to be like a historical record of this battle that actually happens, you know?
A record of Lodos war, if you will.
It is kind of similar to a record of Lodos war in that one.
Wait, I've only seen, I've seen like, wasn't there two record of Lodos war?
I think I've seen like the second one that was like shorter and was only like six episodes.
And was just like, some like really generic like fantasy, like there's an elf and a wizard and a warrior that go into a dungeon.
It's total, the, there's like one half of it is just, or I guess one of them, because I saw it as like,
I think there are two six episode OVA's that were compiled into like one 12 episode release in America.
And I do remember like the first half just being like completely fucking boring and generic,
and the second half being like political and kind of interesting.
But like my, it was cramming a lot into a little bit of space.
So it's not like, when I was a kid, when I was a kid, and I went to that summer camp program where I got to play D&D.
My D&D counselor showed us all like one day of like one week of the program.
He like made us watch a record of Lodos war as an example of like, here is an example of all these different like characters in a party,
like, you know, contributing their unique ability to like beat the adventure.
Yeah.
And then he made us watch the sword fight scene from Princess Bride as an example of like combat in an RPG isn't just about rolling dice,
you know, it's an opportunity to, you know, like express your character's personality and whatever.
That guy was such a fucking nerd.
Yeah, that sounds like the nerdiest, but also most adorable thing I've ever heard about him.
Yeah.
He had the rule that I think more people should play with where if you ask if you can do something, you automatically do it.
Because he like couldn't stand characters being like, oh, I come to a hole and there's like, there's a cliff, right?
There's a gap in the floor.
Oh, can I jump over it?
He would be like, OK, roll the dice, you attempt to jump over it.
And he would make you follow through on it because, you know, that question is like, that question is answered with a roll of the dice and with your stats and you should just kind of, you wouldn't know that.
Like it's not, you shouldn't be able to ask the DM and get an answer.
So it's like, fuck you, I'll punish you every time you try to like met a game like that.
That's that's sort of like breaks the flow in the immersion.
Like if your character is thinking, hmm, can I jump that?
They might like, I don't know.
This is this is one of the reasons why I fell out of love with D&D.
And I don't really like it as much as I used to because kind of everybody plays like that.
Everybody plays wrong.
Everybody is always like to the DM like, oh, can I can I make a spot check?
Can I make a spot check to see anything hidden?
It's like, shut up.
You're an imbecile.
You're a moron.
I hate you.
You say, I look around the room.
What do I see?
And then if there's anything to see, or maybe even if there's not, the DM should say, make a spot check.
And then you roll a spot check because the DM told you to not because you're like, hmm, I have a I have four ranks in investigation.
DM, can I please make an investigation check to perhaps find any clues to the mystery we are attempting to solve?
Shut up.
Die.
You shouldn't be playing this game.
You're stupid.
Yeah, that's sort of playing it like a single player video.
Everybody plays it like that.
Everybody plays it fucking wrong.
Well, I mean, that's what happens when anything catches on and becomes mainstream, you know, as people are going to fucking just engage in a completely wrong way because they probably get something out of it.
But it's just so much less rich and pure, you know, than what the than what the chosen few with the experience.
Thank you.
Yes, that's people who play the video games.
I imagine they play them and then they get used to the experience.
And then they're not so much immersed in the world and the story so much as they are invested in gaining that's a good way of putting it and getting through to the next part without being killed.
And that's how they understand that that's the appeal for some people.
I understand that that's the appeal for some people.
And like, I guess it's not wrong if you feel that way.
But I mean, a lot of people would argue that's even the problem with modern video games.
Like, Ben, you don't like that in games.
You actually would rather they be more like DMs for you, right?
Like, I feel like the games you play are closer to DMing and experience for you than like purely guiding you through it the way most gamers are used to now.
I think the fact that you're really into Neuter and Neuter is not like, you know, a tailored experience.
It's an experimental one.
So like you as the player and the character in the world are doing the same thing.
Like you're not trying to save the princess because you like the princess in Mario.
You're just doing it because you like jumping.
Neuter is a game where there is a world, there is a world generated for you and there are many complicated systems that exist in the world that you can with skill and understanding.
Utilize in order to interact with the world and accomplish things.
And it's very self-directed.
Things like going to parallel worlds.
You just kind of got to figure it out for yourself or just like read how someone else did it and then copy them.
But still, even so, you got to figure it out.
Did you imagine like a binding of Isaac D and D?
You enter the room.
I look around.
Oh, there's shit everywhere.
There's a fetus roll initiative.
Okay, the fetus kills you.
The fetus pukes blood on you.
And then you go into a room and it's like, oh, you've got a thingy.
It's like a pill or does something.
I don't know, Isaac.
I take the pill.
Okay, roll a dexterity check.
Oh, I failed.
Okay, the pill messes up your face forever.
All right, cool.
Nice.
We never did the thing that I wanted to do.
Maybe at a Radcon or maybe not where we play a tabletop thing.
That was a Radcon idea that I had that never.
It's shocking.
It still never happened, actually.
Yeah, we were just too busy.
We just had too much fucking shit on our plates.
There was literally no time for it at Radcon for it.
We need to make it like an actual Kickstarter reward for the next one.
It's like a real produced fucking tabletop session or something video.
Produce meaning you just have Victor there.
Well, I mean like with intro music and fucking some, I don't know, visual flair.
Maybe draw some of the monsters.
We're all dressed up as period armor.
Or even just like having like hand drawn like maps or something, you know?
It's like stuff that would make the session seem extra cool and tactile.
Maybe.
I feel like I would want to just be stupid the whole time.
What if we did it with the 360 camera in the center of like the table?
It could be a good idea.
Yeah, and then it could be edited so that like the shot cuts from like between people,
like depending on who is talking.
I wonder like how good those have gotten if they've kept like updating the 360 camera technology.
I think that's pretty good.
I mean.
So when I had the only reason I really stopped using it is that it just kind of sucked.
It over heated.
Yeah, but overheat really easily and like you had to interface with it through the app.
It had no like they just had a power button and also not being able to plug a mic into it kind of sucked because like it's it has directional audio,
but it's just not very good.
So like, you know, I would want a better 360 camera if we were going to like rely on it.
But I'm sure they've gotten better for probably not any more expensive.
Speaking of speaking of games that are a bunch of complicated systems stacked on top of each other.
I had a I met with the endless war dev team yesterday and we discussed new features to be added in season four.
I made an official season four.
I'm not sure exactly if there is like a clear line between season four and season three, but we are definitely in season four or going to be in season four.
I don't know.
A global warming is going to be where we talked about adding global warming.
I feel like that's good.
Obviously, global warming is good and something that like everyone will be attempting to increase as much as possible.
How about this cryptid photography where it's like the museum in Animal Crossing, but you have to go to the outlands and find cryptids and take pictures of them and then turn them in to a museum and you'll get on a leaderboard if you can take really clear pictures of cryptids.
How the hell will like the including Goku, Goku is a cryptid.
How do they determine what is a good photo?
Does it just random?
Oh, you tripped and fell and it was a blurry.
I'm going to say probably yes.
And grilling.
And we're going to add grilling to endless war finally.
Oh, you could already do grilling.
You can grill anything and you can eat it once it's grilled.
There's going to be a whole trash box mutation and then you can't eat it.
There needs to be like a place where all the grillers go and just hang out and grill.
Competitive grilling.
I don't know if they want it to be competitive.
You know, you just want to grill, man.
You don't got to make it a whole contest and everything.
Just one place down and um...
No, that would be the joke is to make like just, I just want to grill to turn it into a hardcore like min-max sport.
That would be fucking incredible.
My grill gains are down. Fuck.
Grill gains?
Like there's just some sub-zone down in like Cratersville or something where there's just a pit full of grills and everybody's there.
Everybody's grilling. Everybody's bringing all their junk down south to be grilled and they all feast.
Hell yeah.
It's me and the boys.
Me and the slime boys just grilling.
Me and the slime salami.
Uh, Cratersville is... Yeah, Cratersville.
Cratersville will be the place for that.
Very base. Very good. Very exciting.
Uh, fun-
Exceedingly red-billed.
Absolutely true.
I haven't been paying attention to the happenings.
The last understanding I have of the law was that Endless War was asleep.
Like everyone was asleep because it was like going backwards in time.
And that presumably stopped and then the shamblers were shambling.
And they shambled stuff.
The shamblers were before the dream.
Okay, so they didn't come back afterwards?
I don't...
The shamblers?
Yeah, blue guys.
I don't think so.
I remember being really into shambling and like destroying everything.
I think the shamblers...
I think everyone hated the shamblers because they like...
Deleted the functionality of the game.
Yes, it was really funny.
Yeah, they literally existed to just ruin the game and make things not work anymore.
And it worked perfectly.
I don't think they came back, although I could be wrong.
But I mean, people still shamble, of course.
Because now shambling is an institution.
It was just such a...
Such a high stakes time because, you know, there are people who enjoy playing the game.
And then there is me who never really was into the game.
And now that there's a way to ruin it for other people, I was so into it.
And I would...
There was a time when I would like hide on the train.
And the train would like move from station to station.
People couldn't find me to kill me.
And I was...
That's how I would stay safe.
Because shamblers, they didn't have like a base.
So if a shambler just stood still for too long, somebody just killed them.
But if I was on a train, they had to catch the train I was on.
They never could.
I hated the shamblers because I would go into there...
Into New Los Angeles City and I would try to go to a cafe
and create zines of slime and punishment.
And every time I would go and just the cafe would have been shambled and like I couldn't use it anymore.
And I would just have to wait until somebody fixed it.
Which sometimes took a while.
So it really held up production on my zines for the zine store.
I think I put a bunch of the Load of Ghosts comics in that zine thing.
Like you could purchase the comic with slime.
Or potrons or something.
And then it would link to an imager file.
I know that I bought a copy of The Gamer and the Bear.
For my personal collection.
That's written by Gun Girl.
Written by Gun Girl.
It's so stupid.
The classic children's tale.
Zines were so good.
Who even did that?
Who added zines? Some fucking genius.
Some genius.
Thank you wherever you are.
Well, so that was fun.
I want to publish scenes and rage against machines.
Is that flagpole, Citta?
That it is.
Yeah, yeah.
I know that because of Todd and the Shadows.
It's a good song.
I mean, I'd heard the song, obviously.
I didn't know what it was called.
Did he ever wonder hit Wonderland on that?
Because I haven't seen it.
He did.
I was just thinking, did gun nuts get a noise that zines was used?
Because they have magazines and they also say zines.
But they probably say mags instead.
I know people that say zines and I hate them.
Also, there are more fucking gun zines than any other kind of zine.
There's more gun mags than gun zines.
I understand that if you see the word, it's spelled Z-I-N-E-S.
And it looks like zines unless you understand that it is a shortening of magazine,
in which case it's obviously zine.
It's obviously zine.
Foolish. Foolish people.
What if you made a Make America Great Again zine?
Mm-hmm, go on.
A magazine.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
Of course.
Well done.
Thank you.
Well, I would make a million dollars.
So I guess I should get on that.
Well, now that Trump now that Trump's out, the magas are a subculture again.
So now they have to go to look small and do presses.
They have to make zines.
That's hilarious.
They're pretty obscure.
You probably haven't heard of them.
I also played video game.
Nice.
Oh, yeah?
Other than Minesweeper.
Although I am currently still playing Minesweeper.
And I probably will be in my grave as well.
Don't get it.
Go on.
You don't like Minesweeper?
It's just...
Not really.
I mean, it's fine.
It's a brain teaser like any other small person being.
It's gambling.
It's the same thing as gambling.
I don't think...
Okay.
There was a guy in the comments who said, it's not random.
You don't have to guess.
But I am stupid.
He doesn't know.
I'll need to look into if there's a Minesweeper YouTuber
who knows the strats and see what he does.
Somebody said that there is a no guessing mode
that gives you your first pick.
Which is fair enough.
But who cares about the first move?
If you're losing the first move, you just start again.
It's the fact that you can get very deep in
and have just a binary one or the other choice
and no possible way of knowing which it's going to be.
You're almost guaranteed to run into one of those
by the end of a game.
I don't know whether that comes into mind
that you can figure it out no matter what
if you think big brainily.
Maybe that's true.
It's not that.
There's always...
Minesweeper is an easy game.
It turns out educated guessing,
but there's still guessing.
There's still randomness to it, no matter what you do.
If it was just like follow the logic,
the game would be very easy to win.
It's only hard to win because you almost always
have to guess at some point.
I usually try to just get to that point as quickly as possible
by just backing into the corners.
I went to no guessing mode and it gave me this.
It told me which one to click on it.
I clicked on it and this is the result.
Looking at this, I can tell that the best course of action
for me is to click something adjacent
to that one in the bottom right corner
because there are five adjacent squares to it
and I know that only one of them has a bomb in it.
That's a four out of five chance of success.
That's the best odds I have,
but it's still a four and five.
That's literally the odds of using Stone Edge in Pokémon.
Everyone knows that Stone Edge always misses.
Focus Blast always misses.
I'm guaranteed to lose.
I'm looking into it and it worked.
I think it might actually be impossible to always win.
It is impossible to always win.
I know I've played thousands and thousands of games.
I don't see that as inherent.
It doesn't ruin the game, but it's a different negative.
It just makes it gambling.
I get really excited if I win,
but I never feel like I won necessarily because I'm so good at it.
I feel like I won because I had a possible solution.
I'm playing on hard mode right now and you know what?
It's pretty hard.
Craig left the call.
Why?
My go-to puzzle brain teaser game,
aside from Sudoku, which is perfect, is Picross.
I've said this before,
but this is the size of the graph that I'm using.
I started a new game a few hours ago.
I really like the deduction stuff.
I guess I'm repeating myself from a few episodes ago.
But Minesweeper having so much random chance
puts it in a different genre of pastime.
The gambling aspect is so antithetical to what I get out of these puzzle games.
This just looks like Sudoku,
but with the numbers on the outside instead of the inside.
The way I play Minesweeper is just a reflexive game.
I'm not putting any thought whatsoever.
Oh, I love putting thought.
It's just pure pound through.
It's like big brain Wojak.
I hate Craig so much.
He's fucking around right now and he is going to get a pay cut.
For those who don't know,
Craig is a real human being that we kill every day.
We abuse him.
We tell him that he sucks.
Craig is Eleazar's real name, Doxt.
I hate him.
Craig is the voice recording bot who is just a piece of shit and doesn't fucking work.
We all record our audio anyway, so whatever.
Yeah, but this is how Craig is how we get secret bonus content
for the secret bonus content episodes.
So he's a vital part of the operation.
Anyway, what I was saying is,
what I get out of this and Minesweeper, if it were more thoughtful,
is the...
I want my brain to heat up and smoke to come out of my ears
thinking and looking at these things like,
what the fuck is the number?
Where's the square go?
What is it?
I just want to figure it out so bad.
I love that.
It's my favorite thing.
I like to play Picross.
To play Picross, there's numbers on the left and the top and whatever.
They correspond to, the numbers correspond to consecutive colored inboxes.
So this one image is quite big, but the one I filled in,
there's a 9, 9, 2, which means in this row, there is a block of 9,
a block of 9 and a block of 2,
and there's only so many places those boxes could be.
So I figured out by counting from the left and the right,
which blocks are impossible to be blank because of the length.
It's kind of like battleship in a way.
The ships are a certain length,
and if you find one of the boxes and you know that there's a 4,
then that box, if it can only be that 4,
you know that there's three other boxes connected to that one,
and then it's just a case of narrowing it down to making sure
you know that this one cannot be colored in or not,
and this one can,
and then the more you do, the more information you have to solve more of the puzzle
until you've completed it,
and it's just so satisfying to complete such a big, arduous puzzle like this.
Do you know when it's solved?
Yeah, when you've completed all of the numbers.
You can make them go gray.
I'll just link to the site,
pcruslyoh.com
slash pcrus.
Okay, so a number in a column means...
A number in a column and a row.
If you go to like a five by five on the left,
you can do a five by five.
It would be pretty easy to figure out,
like I'm just going to take a screenshot of the one I'm looking at.
I just love pcrus so much.
So if you see the top left column is a four,
and there's only five boxes,
so at least the middle three have to be filled in
because the four can't fit any other way.
Wait, so it's a block of four, a line of four?
Yeah, consecutive blocks, consecutive squares.
So that means that four have to be together,
and means three of them have to be like that.
And then from that, you can work out that on the rows on the right,
there's one, three, there's one, and then there's one, one, one.
The one, one, one is like individual blocks,
and there's only space for three if you have a space in between.
That row has to be filled, unfilled, filled, unfilled, filled.
Yeah, because there's no other way that can fit.
And so that one's done, and then, yeah,
it's really quite simple once you know the rules.
Okay, do the blocks, do they have to go in order?
Like in the bottom, there's the one, two.
Does it have to be a one on the left and then a two to the right,
or could there be a filled, filled, unfilled, unfilled?
It has to be in the order that it's written.
So the one has to be to the left of the two,
and on the top it has like there's two, one in the middle.
The two has to be above the one.
So on this one, all right, tell me if I'm getting this right.
So on mine here, see the middle column is one, three.
So the only way that that can work is if it's filled, unfilled, filled, filled, filled.
And it couldn't be the three and then an empty and then the one
because I would be in the wrong order.
Got it, got it.
Very based.
Okay, I'm learning, I'm learning.
It's a very fun game.
Intodesting.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I'm getting it.
I'm getting it.
So then this is what I'm left with.
So now over on the left, I see there's a one.
Oh, wait, there's a one and then a one.
Yeah, the one could be all the way to the left or all the way to the right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But you know it can't, but you know that it can't be next to the ones that you've already drawn
because that would make it a two, which is impossible.
So now you know where the gaps, if you right click that like blanks out the space
so you can keep track of where a block cannot be.
Okay.
Okay, so but so in the middle row is the one and that middle column has one in it.
So every other one in the middle row has to be a non filled because there's only the one has to be blank.
Holy shit.
Holy shit, I get it.
So fucking good.
So fucking things.
I love thinking it's my favorite pastime, but not when it comes to anything important.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ah, very exciting.
Oh, I'm filling them in.
I'm going to win.
I'm going to fucking win this video game.
I'm excited to learn about this game after I finish beating my head against the wall of minesweeper.
You will appreciate this.
I mean, you do need to think a little bit more if it is not a mindless game.
Because if you make a mistake, your mistakes are tallied.
And that's bad because if you complete, if you complete the thing without making a single mistake on this website, at least you get a rainbow pattern.
But if you even have one mistake, if you click thoughtlessly and you make a mistake, it goes like black and white.
So you complete it, you can, you can complete it, but you won't get the funny rainbow.
And that's where all the true epic gamer gamers strive for.
I got the rainbow.
I clicked thoughtlessly and I thought I had fucked it up, but it didn't go black and white.
So I just kind of got lucky there that my fuck up ended up working out for me.
Hooray.
I've been progressively getting larger and larger grid sizes on the left.
There's like, you can choose.
I would like try to complete, like get through one of them without making a mistake and then moving up to the next grid size, making it more difficult for myself at the moment.
I'm on 25 by 25 and I haven't successfully done that one yet.
On the bigger sizes, I see it's like split into like blocks of five.
Those don't matter though, right?
No, those are just for visual clarity.
Yeah, okay.
Just checking.
I've been considering what is the appeal of Minesweeper to me and I think it's basically like Valhalla.
It's like, just keep coming back to battle, you die over and over again.
It's not really about winning or losing so much as just continuing to run back into the fight, you know.
I get knocked down, but I get Minesweeped again.
I'm never going to get Minesweeped.
I've got like Viking metal music playing in my head and you're like, I get knocked down, but no, yes, it's absolutely accurate.
But Vikings didn't have Mines, that was a thing that was invented later.
That's true.
Now, our listeners have learned how to play Picross and never to play Minesweeper.
Post your Picrosses in the comments.
Unless you have a gambling addiction and you don't want to spend any more money on it, then this is a healthy alternative.
If you have a gambling addiction, you might as well just invest in Bitcoin.
Yeah, try all of these things.
Are you Team Crypto, Team Picross or Team Minesweeper?
Or Team Noida.
No, not Noida.
These are all basically the same thing when you really boil it down.
They're all just ways of feeling good.
Except for these moments I get to in Minesweeper when I'm staring at it and there doesn't seem to be any clear path forward.
And I know I have to make a guess and I just see with so much anger.
I made an okay guess.
Will I live one more click?
Yes, okay.
I'm safe.
I'm safe with me.
It's like the scene in every movie where there's a bomb and they're trying to...
Yeah, it literally is.
It's like, is the red one? There's 17 different red wires. Which one do I cut?
I don't know. Click!
And in my brain, the threat level is the same as though my life was about to end every single time.
So what else?
I was going to say that I played another video game other than Minesweeper and then I guess we started talking about Picross.
I was playing Apex Legends.
I don't know.
Wait, isn't that the Battlegrounds game?
It is a Battlegrounds game.
It has the same name as 100 different things in my head.
I know. It's like the most generic fucking possible name.
What's the game play?
It's one of those Battle Royale games.
I just played a little bit of it because my boyfriend plays a whole lot of it and so we were squatted up.
It's basically a game where you run around this map and loot shit until you run into other people and then you try not to die first.
Yeah.
And if you're lucky you might kill somebody.
Is it team-based or is it never-made?
It's three-man squads and there's like 50 of them per match.
The way I think of those games is like Overwatch League of Legends with all of the purchasing of stuff and getting random loot on the map but also fighting to stay alive.
And I hate League of Legends and all of those MOBA stuff.
Fortnite has always been like, I hate League of Legends.
The upside it has on League is that it's way faster.
Fortnite seems a little more...
Fortnite seems cooler than League of Legends.
Oh yes.
It's the random luck of finding the cool loot before someone else does and then also the stress of being good at shooting.
The funny thing is we've been playing where there's 50 people in a match and there's a plane that flies over the island and you can choose when to drop.
And every match I've played, at least half of the people will drop immediately.
The second they get over the island they all drop and then they all just start wiping each other out.
So these people are just like, I don't know if they're just hauling ass getting one gun and then going right into battle or what.
But we usually just land on the opposite side of the map in a totally secluded area and have like 10 minutes to just get whatever the hell you want and then go out and fight.
And so you really spend more of your time running around exploring and looting and hanging out in the areas.
And then if you're lucky then everybody else will mostly have killed each other so there's only a few teams left and ideally you'll run into them one at a time and pick them off.
But the ring closes as the match goes on so you're forced into closer and closer proximity.
Eventually there's nowhere to run or hide.
But usually you just get found and killed pretty quick.
I don't know if I think that the game is inherently fun, but it is fun to play with TeamSpeak.
And there's a lot of player input commands where you can be like, let's go over there or here's an item that you might like and all that kind of stuff.
So when you're playing with people who can do all that shit quickly, it's a lot easier to follow what the fuck is going on and have a decent time.
But if anybody wants to play Apex Legends with me, my name is Golden Witchfire on there.
That's to our audience.
I'm going to stick to the Thinking Man's game.
I know we've got to have some people in the crowd who play Apex.
How long does it take if you die early for you to wait around to play again?
It'll probably be a minute or two between matches.
Like I said, a lot of people do die really quick, but that's because they jump right into the fray at the start of the match.
I have not had a match that lasted less than five minutes if I was actively trying to gear up before going into the battle.
I think TF2 is like the perfect shooter game just because it's accessible and when you die over and over again, you can still play the game and feel like you're constantly getting better.
With stuff like Apex and things of that nature, I would always feel like it's too many variables that dictate whether or not I may have fallen on the right thing,
and get in the best gun or having the best position or just being lucky to notice somebody before they notice me.
But in TF2, the maps are very geared towards one direction of play.
So you can learn the maps and get better at playing on those maps and the classes and the weapons.
It feels like constant progression.
I had felt that way about Apex when I first played it.
I totally didn't understand how you're supposed to get good at this game if most of it is running around and not shooting.
And then eventually I realized your goal is not to shoot, your goal is to survive.
So ultimately you will do better if you shoot less and don't run into battle.
So it's really more of a game about collecting loot and jungling in my mind.
You get points for how long you live in addition to kills.
There's a kill leader who has the most kills, but ultimately the point is to be the last team standing.
So to me, I think an ideal match of Apex Legends would mean you only ever fought one other team.
And you don't even have to get all the kills.
Ideally they've already lost teammates by the time they get to you.
So yeah, I think that's kind of what made me start enjoying it was when I stopped thinking of it as a shooter game.
Especially because a lot of the guns are not very accurate and you get very short bursts of fire.
So people take a lot of damage, but it's not like Halo where you could keep suppressing them by emptying clip after clip until they're dead.
It's like you really have to have people on their ass because if you're in a one-on-one firefight, it's usually not a very ideal scenario.
I just don't think the game is like, it's not a game where you're trying to get headshots on your opponent, basically.
I love headshots.
I know, I know.
I know, we know.
Sniper's a good job, man.
Alright, I jumped in. I jumped in. I'm playing Noida. I'm in the Ice Caves.
I'm in the Ice Caves. I'm killing Heesey.
It's good.
Heesey?
All's right.
Yeah.
Heesey is a...
The game is based on Finnish mythology and I guess Heesey are goblins.
They're Finnish goblins or spirits or something.
And in Noida, they have these high-tech blue people that have an underground arctic base.
And they've got magic machines that drill for gold and can repair.
They have an anvil that you can throw broken wands onto and it repairs them into working wands.
And they've all got HVAC suits on and grenade launchers.
Very cool. Very good stuff.
That's all I have to say about that.
I'm on fire. I'm on fire.
Okay, okay.
I'm getting pincered.
Pincer attack. It's a pincer attack. They planned it all out.
Hey, Ben, have you played Rain World at all?
Oh, that's... No, but I saw the Matthew Matosis video about it.
That's like a platformer where you're a little monkey thing.
A little rabbit monkey, something or other that squishes through pipes.
Do I remember that?
Yeah.
Noida sounds like what my impression of that game is like to some degree.
Noida is a powerful game for powerful people.
Oh my God. Glowing Lance. I found Glowing Lance.
Yes.
Oh my God.
It's a game changer.
Well, that's gonna tear right through.
That's gonna tear right through all kinds of metals.
Ben, why are you not streaming right now?
Yeah, people have asked me if I'm playing all this Noida, why don't I stream it?
And sometimes I think I should, but I kind of just like...
I don't know.
Just getting to play a video game and not fucking do a whole thing about it?
There would be...
It would soil the experience, probably.
Well, it would change it.
I would stream Noida potentially, but I wouldn't want to only play Noida on stream,
because I like the...
I'll give you an example.
When I was on that run that ended in the lava,
I spent a long time, after I beat the last level,
I spent a long time using luminous drills to bore a vertical shaft
between the different temples so that I could easily travel between them.
And then I used the drill to carve out a rose in the temples
so that I could store all my different spells and spell modifiers,
almost like bookshelves, like a library of them.
And that took me several hours,
and I feel like that would not be riveting gameplay for a stream.
If I was streaming, I think I wouldn't do that,
because it would be really boring to watch,
but that's how I like to play.
So, yeah, different experience.
I guess it depends on how understanding the audiences of the nature of the game
and what they want to see from it.
I'm sure there is an audience who does want to watch you bore a tunnel for four hours,
but it might not be all of them.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, people...
There probably are some people who would find it satisfying to watch me lay out
all my modifier spells, lay them out in a row,
all my spells underneath them,
and make a section over here, and create a little library.
I mean, yeah.
But when I'm streaming, I feel a compulsion to keep the energy up.
I feel the compulsion to be entertaining,
to keep things moving along.
I feel like I wouldn't do that in those circumstances, so different.
If I was streaming, I would probably try to go for really fast wins,
which is not how I normally play.
I'm very methodical, very meticulous,
and I take forever because I want to search very thoroughly and find everything.
It would affect my playstyle, is what I'm saying.
I like streaming when it's a game that I'm very familiar with,
so that it's almost...
I enjoy the feeling of streaming with people in chat and talking and joking around.
If I didn't feel like having that experience, I wouldn't do it.
But occasionally, there's a game that's easy to play, and I like having people watch.
I do think that there is something there,
because on the one hand, I wouldn't do that other thing that I described,
but on the other hand, it would be fun for me to explain
why am I carrying this pheromone potion around?
Well, I'll tell you. You'll see why later.
I get to the hee-see base, and I'm like,
okay, now's the time, I'm going to find out what, and then I find the healer,
and I'm like, check this out, guys, check this out, guys.
I scored him with the pheromone, and he starts healing me,
and then the chat goes, ah, Pog, Pog, Pog!
You know, there's an appeal there.
You already experienced it, yeah.
I spoiled it, yeah, it's too late now.
People will play into it, even if they know it's coming.
Yeah.
People like Pog and Enchant.
This is why I've changed my whole thing.
Now I always seek out pheromone.
In real life?
Yes, yes, in real life, and I'm always squirting it on people
that I think will have value to me.
Based.
I haven't streamed on almost, well, I've streamed on RFCK.
I haven't streamed on my channel in like almost a year.
Actually, I had a dream about streaming last night.
I had a dream?
Yeah, I had a dream where I streamed, and the chat was nice,
and I was nice to them, and it was nice.
That was the dream!
That literally was the whole dream.
What a dreamy stream.
It was, a dreamy stream dream.
That's it, that's what happened.
I like those streams.
We should do voice mails now.
I was thinking voice mails.
Would it have been going for an hour and a half?
Yeah.
Almost.
Wait, Gib.
Nah, I got nothing.
I just like streams.
Yeah, dream stream.
That's good.
Nah, I'll think about it.
I'll think about streaming at some point.
I think now that I've become more familiar with Noita,
and now that I actually can win,
I feel like streams would be more fun now
than a few weeks ago
when I was just dying in the mines all the time
and just had no fucking clue what I was doing.
Maybe.
Okay.
So the first voicemail is called...
Oh, this one's good.
The first voicemail is called Hi Ben.
So you guys ready?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi Ben.
It's me.
Tommy J.
What?
Fucking TV off first.
Since we last spoke,
I've still voluntarily committed,
and now I'm on quite a bit of Thorazine.
Bays.
I know we can't be together.
Good.
But I still miss what we had.
No hard feelings, huh?
We had some good times together, you and I.
Is this actually Tommy J?
I can't tell.
Oh, it's spoke break time.
I don't think so.
I guess I'd better go.
Tommy J, signing off.
For the last time.
I feel, well, I don't feel bad.
I don't feel bad exactly,
but I do recognize that Tommy J
did not have the benefit
of hearing the second time
we listened to all his voicemails
and heard about them
before I went and heard the third time
and flipped my shit.
So, you know,
it was...
It's fine.
It's water under the bridge.
No worries.
Okay.
But that guy's got to turn his fucking mic up
because that was too quiet.
And his television off.
I couldn't even hear the television.
I don't know if my headphones are just quiet or what.
I'd better make him out.
Yeah.
You know what, actually, I might have...
No, my volume is at a reasonable...
My volume is at a pretty reasonable setting.
Okay, whatever.
Next voicemail is called Which is Worse.
Three, two, one, go.
Tommy J spam or Circumcision Discourse.
Tommy J spam.
Hmm, you think?
Yeah.
It's a hard stance to tell.
Tommy J spam doesn't mean anything.
At least Circumcision...
At least there's something to feel passionately about.
I guess.
Circumcision Discourse.
Circumcision just kept going on and on and on.
Circum...
That's true.
Circumcision was like a month's long process.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Whatever.
Both banned.
Next one is called Confessing My Feelings.
Three, two, one, go.
I keep trying to condense everything into the smallest idea possible.
But you just can't do that.
Some things are too complicated to say in a 90-second voicemail.
So, I just want to say...
Here it comes.
I love you, man.
Oh.
Thank you.
When did the bulk of the voicemails stylistically become creepy whispering into a mic stalker person?
Become.
They've always been.
There's definitely been a divergent evolution where the voicemails have taken a few different evolutionary paths.
Yeah.
Where they lean into different elements.
Okay, thanks.
I love you, too.
Next one is called True Facts About Oblivion Fall.
Three, two, one, go.
I remember in school once.
I was about 12 years old.
A kid asked me, hey, do you like spunk?
I wasn't sure entirely what he meant, but I figured it had something to do with dicks.
So I said no.
He laughed and said, what about cum?
Do you like cum?
Well, it turns out as an adult, why am I seeing this?
I've always heard that cum tastes salty.
And in my experience, it's not salty at all.
It's more buttery.
If you've ever eaten your own boogers, why am I seeing this?
While having a cold or after crying is basically like that.
I do both all the time.
Except it tastes a little bit like popcorn.
For us.
Jellified popcorn is the flavor of cum.
Of course, I have yet to try the taste of others cum.
Why am I seeing this?
So at this stage in my life, there's only one man, Nate, who can satisfy my desires.
Yeah.
Ben.
Join the league.
You've told Nate about the league, right?
He shouldn't have.
You showed him the voicemails.
What did he think?
Or naughty brother, you haven't showed him at all.
I would be so disappointed in you, Ben.
I don't feel like that's my job.
I don't feel like I'm responsible for that.
The league of Nate fuckers haven't even sent an email his way.
What do you expect is going to happen?
You've got to make the first move.
If you want to fuck Nate, you've got to make the first move, my dudes.
You've got to make yourself available.
As a large group.
As to the cum taste, gross.
Gross.
Yuck.
Next voicemail is called a tip for a frequent listener.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Tommy J.
All right.
Listen, listen, listen.
I know, I know that you're a fan of this podcast and all.
There's no Tommy J response.
I just want to provide for the PCP and all that.
And I get that.
You like, you listen to this and you enjoy it, but please shut the fuck up.
You were self-absorbed autist.
Okay.
We know.
The point's been made.
Now I'm on Tommy J's side.
I've had enough of people beating up on him.
We did it.
And you can't do that.
Yeah.
I already beat up on him as hard as it was possible to do.
Now we're a Tommy J stands on the PCP.
But pendulum has swung the other way.
Contrarianism wins again.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
Good tips.
Don't make too many voicemails.
Got it.
Okay.
We're up number two.
I forget what this stands for.
Ben World Records.
T-Bag.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
No.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben St.
It's your weekly reminder to catch up on one piece.
Thank you.
Oh yeah.
Weekly reminder to catch up on one piece.
I'll get around to it.
I'll get around to it after I beat Noida again.
I think again and again and again.
My advice to that caller, I think you need to make your call longer and force Ben to
memorize the acronym or else he's never going to remember that it's a thing that keeps
happening.
I think he just mind wipes it immediately after hearing the call.
This was only number two.
I think eventually.
No.
Work.
For little time ago, Eric, Eric, Eric and Eric.
After that, Eric, Eric, Eric, Eric.
Eric,
Eric, structural, вокруг for the leadership in that world.
And we have to get back up.
Caneety.
Go all Free.
Go.
have to use my last resort. I've got missiles in my hands and pistols in my eyes,
rockets in my boots, and lasers in my size. I've got lasers for teeth, and I bring them all to
fight. I'm a clusterfunk cyborg. He's at my mercy now, but he is still alive. Should I spare this
me? Why are you worried? Why are you worried about a bear living an hour's journey away from you
if you're a clusterfunk cyborg with pistols in your eyes? I feel like the bear poses no threat to
you. Yeah, I think you should spare the bear. I think you should detain the bear for the bear cop
and arrest him. Yeah, you've perhaps won his respect now. Alternatively, if you kill and skin
the bear, you can wear the bear. Then you can become the bear. You can take over his life at the
zoo and steal his identity online. Oh boy, you can take on all his credit card debt. That's tough.
Does the bear own any crypto? In which case, you might want to get some now before it goes to the
moon. It's a start of a really interesting story. You kill a bear and you gain all of its debt.
And then the debt collectors come looking for the bear and you're there.
I don't know. I feel like you have more to gain by alliance with the bear
than by defeating. I'm going to say spare. I'm going to say spare the bear. Spare the bear.
By the way, some really solid vocal melodies in that. Some good hooks in there.
I was not sure about it until the fight scene began. And then I was like, OK, OK, here we go.
Here we go. All right. Next one is called Trixie. Please fuck. Three, two, one, go.
You know what, guys, after recording that, I just not feeling it. I just was getting bad
vibes all around. I feel like I was too mean. I would say a lot of those things differently
now. You know, I'm just going to re-record the whole thing. But don't worry, guys,
it's going to come out. Don't worry that this isn't going to be a blu-ray situation all over
again. I promise you could trust me. OK, it's about the lecture. Can we just cut the bullshit?
Can you just release it? Just give us the original product. So I'm glad this is none of us.
None of us want you to start over. Nobody wants that. But you, Trixie,
for the love of God, please just release the original lecture. Please don't fucking scrap it.
I really don't comprehend this. Please don't fucking scrap it. Holy shit,
please don't do that. How can you be so attached to something you haven't seen before? I don't
understand. Just release the original lecture for fuck's sake.
Why are people assuming it's good? Why are you assuming that it's worth releasing?
Because all the rad con lectures are good. Everybody likes them.
It's not even necessarily true. I've had an unreleased one before because I didn't think it
was good. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, maybe that was a mistake.
Well, I personally think that like the also, OK,
so I talked about recording like a secondary lecture or like a shell component to it and people
were like, oh no, we want the one with like all the people and I'm like, well, why wouldn't you
think I was going to wait till the next rad con to do it again with everybody there? That's
what I mean. Second of all, like the, to me, the way that would make the most sense would be to do
a second lecture and then to embed parts of the first one into it to like edit them into one
cohesive part. The fucking thing is not done in any way, shape or form. So to say that it's like,
oh, just release it. There is no just release it. It was written in a way to be edited extensively.
There's 15 minutes of heavily edited lecture footage and then about two and a half hours of
not edited at all. So like it could be released as is, I guess. It won't be the product I intended.
It won't be a product I believe in. Why would I not just make it the one that would be good
if I can, if I have the opportunity? It's because people are so fucking impatient. You don't need
the Brony lecture to exist now. You don't need it to exist this fucking year. It could be whenever
the hell it's a historical fucking artifact thing. It's a chronicle of history. It's not time sensitive.
I think, I think that if you try to do that, it will simply never come out.
Why? Because it's been this long. It's been one year. It's been a year. It's been a whole year.
That's nothing. It's not nothing. A year is nothing to me. What the hell happened in the last
year? What literally has anything happened? Name one thing. I can't think of a single thing that's
happened in the last year actually. You're right. There was a coronavirus lockdown and we all sat
indoors and did nothing for a year. Okay. Okay, but why? Okay, you say that it'll be good if you
edit it. I think that most people would find the unedited thing good. Maybe they would. I just,
it was never meant to be released that way though. It's just not the intent of the lecture. Yours
is edited. Mine is not not out because it needs editing. Mine has a couple little flourishes
that I added. Mine is not out for other content related timing reasons. I understand that I'm a
bit of a hypocrite for not having released mine. I mean the ones you do have editing in them though.
Like the Diane Wrights one. The second one. That one had some, I mean yeah, it had some images.
It had some reference images put in. And the same with the Tales Get Strolled one did. But you
know, I mean that's pretty, yeah, that stuff's good. It didn't take me that long to do.
And it's not really changing anything. Just kind of overlaying a little bit more visual
information on top of what's already there. Like the content of the lectures that I have released
is the original content with maybe just a little bit more context overlaid on top of it.
I just, I find myself incredibly baffled at the level of entitlement that people feel to a product
that doesn't exist. I don't, I'm going to defend it. I don't think it's entitlement. I just,
I think that you are undervaluing the original product as it exists. I think it, I think people
think that the original unedited version has value. Right, but that's totally an assumption.
I mean that if, if I, people would feel that way about a lot of ideas that I have that they
never hear about and a lot of video scripts that I throw away because they're incomplete and a lot
like it's just not everything gets to see the light of day if it's not up to standard, you know.
That's true, but the thing that we're talking about now literally exists and could be released.
It could be, but would it be worthwhile for me to release it? Like what incentive do I have?
Do you want my opinion? Yes. What would be, what would it, what would I gain from releasing this
lecture? Well, I mean, I mean, I guess, hell, I don't know. Yeah. I mean, that's a totally different
question. Okay. What would you, what would you gain? I don't know. The PZP channel would get
some views from it because I assume that's where it would go. And I mean, yeah, it can also happen
in the future when the new version gets made. I actually did not originally intend to release it
on the PCP channel because I thought it would get enough views that it would be like a saving throw
for my channel. At this point, my channel is a whole different beast anyways, but that's fine.
That's fine. I mean, whichever. Okay. I mean, when you say the new one, are you talking about,
because I feel like we're equivocating here between there's like an edited version of the
original, but or like just like a different one. I mean, again, like I said, my goal would be to
record another one and then to interweave it with the one that already exists. So it would be like,
it would be like the like a duality thing, like the dark and light versions of the story, basically.
Would the second one be designed to be heavily edited as well?
It would be designed. Well, yeah, because it's going to have the other one intercut into it.
So they will both have to edit it into each other like edit the whole first one and then record
the second one and combine them. Is that what you're thinking? I'm talking about the like,
okay. So like the lecture that you guys have seen starts with me like walking out of a closet,
taking a massive bong hit, explaining basically what the bronies are and then like the historically
going through like each era of content made by the bronies. So if I were to make another clip
in which I fill in all the gaps of everything I missed, like re-explain certain stuff, add nuance
to it and then like literally edit that into the lecture so that it is a more complete lecture.
Like so it'd be just like, you know, I probably re-explained certain things that I didn't think
I did a good job with the first time and then leave in stuff that was fine and then like have the
this kind of jackal and hide attitude throughout the video of like, hey, this was me a year ago
and this is me today telling you about, you know, how I feel about what I said a year ago, you know.
I mean, what's changed about how you feel about it?
I don't know.
Even then you were already describing things that were like five years
done. Sure. It's really just a more of the presentation style of it and like
the attitude of it that I have a problem with.
I don't know. I just think, I just think that focusing on like changing and revising it
basically is just gonna mean that the original is just ends up in the trash. I think that's what's
gonna happen. Think whatever you want. Okay, I will.
I will.
Next voicemail? Yeah. Okay. Next voicemail is called funny joke three, three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, sorry I haven't made a voicemail in a while.
That's not funny.
Why are so many voicemails so quiet this week?
I don't know. I thought it was something on my end, but...
No, I'm getting it too.
By the way, I have to bring up one more thing about the previous voicemail because he said
it was comparing the Brony lecture to the Blu-ray situation, which is different in many different
ways. One, the Brony lecture is not a promised part of a Kickstarter whatsoever. None of the
lectures were. That's technically true. We didn't promise any specific lecture in the Kickstarter.
Secondly, the reason the Blu-rays ever got done is I don't know how to do it. It's not the same.
I have all the Blu-rays. I've been carrying them around for five years. I don't have the technology
or means or knowledge of how to make the Blu-rays. I still have them. I still intend to do that.
You can go ahead and think if it is dead, but if you're not dead, I don't know why you would.
Fuck you for thinking of things in shorter time spans than I do.
All right. Just as a brief plebe and the weeb, all of the first season is out edited by Jesse,
I think, all of those. What was the season situation because I thought you had a whole
other bunch. The production was for a seasons two and three, was what we were doing. We made
season two. We recorded season three. I don't know what happened to it. Apparently, a lot of the
footage was really fucked because I had the mic arm in between us in front of the camera,
and so the camera would constantly change focus between our faces and the mic arm for all the
episodes we filmed. Another one that, for technical reasons, might not ever see the light of day.
There could be a deleted episode on the Blu-ray. I'll just throw it in there, I guess.
I have no idea if Jesse ever attempted to edit them or if he did. It's possible that he
straight up did anyways. It just hasn't said anything. I don't know, but I haven't heard
any anything about that since he told me that all the footage was fucked.
Damn, damn. Next voicemail.
Okay, next one is called the Yu-Gi-Oh manga is better than the anime. Three, two, one, go.
I'm gonna say a slur. You fucking peendos.
What'd he say? Pe-pe-pe-peendos? Peendos? Oh no, did we all just slur right then? Cool.
KINGOS? I don't know what that means. I assume if I knew Yu-Gi-Oh, maybe I would understand,
but I don't know. I don't know. I know some Yu-Gi-Oh. I never heard that shit.
Mmm, fuck this guy. Next one is called Tom's Digimon lecture, mostly Digimon universe app
monsters. Three, two, one, go. The first big thing that kind of like forks this timeline away from
our world. And in the dawn of revival, we're gonna start off at a 10, my friends. All the technology
in the world goes apeshit at the same time for several hours. And somehow they figure out
that there's a life form trying to manifest itself through the circuitry of technology
for several hours. And this freaks everyone the fuck out, munchy.
Pacemakers. What about my pacemaker? Will my pacemaker work when the technology revolves?
No. Okay. You're fucked.
Uh, yeah? What was that from? That's the guilty gear one.
Uh, but I guess if you think about it, it kind of sounds like it could be about Digimon.
I don't know what app monsters is. Yeah, I don't know enough Digimon to know. I assume
there is someone who gets exactly what this is in reference to going like, hey, somebody's going
like, oh my God, it's just like that thing. Next voicemail is called sad Susie from sad about
Sonichu at 102.com. Uh, three, two, one, go.
Hello. I have waited here so long, so long, where is Sonichu?
Two, one, who, two, Ben, why have you forsaken your responsibilities, the lazy liberal that you are?
You've disappointed me so far that I became a human good try.
Okay. I like the sound editing on that. A lot of drums for a human guitar.
Well, he went over the top of it. That's what made the difference. That's what really
put it over the edge. He really. Next voicemail is called very important. Three, two, one, go.
Drinking, but then as he drinks the milk, it starts to drain from the bottle, revealing
mega sized memories. And now it's just an empty bottle with the memories behind it. And it's a
milk jug framing a pair of milk jugs. Thank you for listening to my dad. Cool. Thanks, man.
That is very important. What is that? Next, next voicemail comes with an attached image,
which I will post now. It is this. This is a piece of, this is some art by
Casol. I happen to know. I like this. The voicemail is called Ooh Woo Lilia. Three, two, one, go.
Oh, oh, Michelle. Hi. Here, what? She, she, what? Trixie's planning on, on we recording
the morning lecture. How could she? What, what a betrayal. We, we the people paid for the original
lecture. We did everyone, we all the characters we love and care about. And she's, she's taking
that from us. I, I can't possibly think of a great, ever perpetuated. Oh, what's on my face? Mayonnaise?
Yeah. What do you think now, Trixie? Yeah, citation needed. It's true. It's true. Maybe it wasn't Mayonnaise.
Uh, next one is called large nose man smells a bitch. Three, two, one, go.
I was this close to having sex with Nate and then I catch a whiff of something truly awful.
You're telling me the Trixie is not going to release the original brownie lecture.
Well, people feel pretty strongly about it. I may have to postpone my fucking of Nate
and have sex with someone else.
Such suit of stir characters. Yeah, but they got a heart of gold. Every single one of them. I promise.
Uh, next one is called this is not financial advice. Three, two, one, go.
I was listening to the discussion, quote unquote, long term investments in the last episode.
Oh, no. The right answer here is just by index funds. So index funds are basically
like stocks, except, uh, instead of like tracking the performance of a company, they just
track the performance of the entire stock market. So like, by the SMP 500 index fund,
you know, and the SMP 500 goes up, then your index fund goes up. And these are generally just,
you know, for a long term, these are like your safest and probably your best investment.
Yeah. So like, uh, you know, Warren Buffett, like the super rich guy, he made a bet,
like a million art bet a few years ago that like the SMP 500 index fund would actually
would make more money over a 10 year period than like all the best edge funds.
And he ended up winning that bet. So yeah, you want to beat the, you know,
beat the edge funds, don't, don't buy meme stocks, just, just buy index funds.
That's what Minerva said too, right? Or something like that. She had some advice about some like
index fund. Yeah. Yeah. What's an index fund and what's a bond? I could Google it, but I won't.
Yeah. See, that's the problem is every time somebody has like good advice, they're too
good at the advice and they have to make it better. Like to make it bad enough for people who don't,
who would like, assume that if I could have figured out what you're talking about, I would have
anyways, you know, like, like, obviously we've all heard someone say the phrase index fund before,
but none of us looked into it any further. You got to like really, really lead these horses to
water. You know what I'm saying? And you got to make the tree. I have like your,
you know, your cadence has to be wearing jeans, not like a suit and tie.
Yeah, exactly. Jeans? No. Your cadence needs to be wearing shorts. And then I'll listen to you.
Your, your, your princess cadence has to be wearing. Yes. Post PNG's a princess cadence
wearing shorts. How would she wear them? Would there be two pairs of shorts? Would it be one
pair of droid going all the way across? You decide. And then I'll buy an index fund.
Yeah, like I said, if I sounded solid, I would go with it. Sounded solid.
Next one is called one cool dud, five a.m. Totino's pizza roll. Three, two, one, go.
So now that we all know as of the Brad this track that Tom is clearly the
most musically talented of the bunch. Oh, he went a little, he did a little voice
warble. Everyone was so impressed. Thick, juicy, nasty pipes in pursuit of the new theme song
maybe. Also, Tom, I'm going to have to request that you stop getting so violently angry on the
show when complaining about your shitty life because it's really turning me on and I am not
entirely comfortable with, well, I'm comfortable with it. I just, you know, good things by he.
I don't. Yeah, the thing about Tom is that he's just so overly emotional. He just goes,
he just flies off the handle at the drop of a hat. And it's
passionate, sensual. I mean, the gift button debate was pretty heated. I enjoyed that.
Down to that. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, that's true.
Next voicemail is called theme song contest three, two, one, go.
This March Simpson.
More. Sold.
Eleazar, you know what to do. Oh, god. Okay, next one is called fn three, two, one, go.
Yeah, that dude's going to get fucked.
I have such a vivid like imagery in my head from all of these crazy.
I'm going to have PTSD, actually, I think, for these voicemails.
This one felt like a little tiny little gremlin, but also kind of like, what's his face from Dragon Ball?
Like, like pilaf. I'm going to have, I'm going to have a BPD from this. I'm going to have bipolar
disorder. I'm going to develop narcissistic personality disorder. I'm going to have all
the types. I'm going to have ABDL from this to this. I'm going to have ABDL for sure. Yeah.
Yeah, based. Okay, next one is called how many doge coins three, two, one, go.
How many doge coins will it take to get the original Brony lecture footage? How many?
How many doge coins? How many doge coins? What are doge coins worth?
They're worth about three pounds, not much. They're worth between five and six cents right now.
Yeah, a little tiny small. And it's been going down so long. I don't know. I'll do it for a thousand
dollars. A thousand dollars worth of doge coins. All right. Okay. That's a ton of doge coin.
Time to invest. Time to invest in doge coins. Next one is called Bing Zerk. Wait, I'm seeing
next one. Well, you got to refresh the page. This one's only 35 minutes ago.
Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I think, yeah. Three, two, one, go.
Why? Why did I send such a green voicemail last week? Was it because I binged the
gentlest holistic detective agency? What does Martin Lawrence even have to do with Sonic
the Hedgehog? Martin the Lawrence is a very funny name, I think, I thought, I hoped,
and yet I couldn't say it. Why? Why?
I didn't know Dirk Gently's holistic detective agency was a TV show. I thought it was a book.
The show is written by Max Landis. What the fuck? Yeah. Oh, God. Bummer. Bummer.
Max Bummer.
Okay, so what was Kring was himself, I guess, and what was Bing was that? And
I wasn't even going to bear a zerk from the. Oh, okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Next voicemail is called thanks. Thanks, Kring is bingus. Next voicemail is called
Neo Kawasaki pro wrestling. Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa. This intercontinental champion, Samurai-sama. Ben no Sento-san.
You contender Ichiba. For my title, I challenge you to death match
at Madison Square Garden at Shinobi Menya. You cannot if to samurai-sama. And my finishing
move, Takawasaki, Pail Driver. What do I say, Senko-san? I'm big giving you. I've gained weight
this pandemic. I outweigh you, so I think I win. Samurai, you must beat Samurai. Fuck you.
Okay. Ito vai to ramen and sayo paraeru. And until you next time, sayonara.
Until you next time. Nah, you're small. You're a small Japanese man. We really
got to have like a like a Red Corn Royal Rumble live action at some point. You're not so tough
without your Kabuto helm and your Kawasaki tempered steel. You're a bitch. I have tempered muscles.
No. Folded. My arms are folded 1000 times.
We'll see. I guess we'll see, Madison Square Garden.
Shit, I guess that's it. That's the last voicemail.
What's, are we done? Oh my god, only two hours this episode. That's crazy.
The voicemail took so much less time than usual.
The people last time knows quite a lot. There were a lot.
More of them were funny than usual, though. So there is that. Good job.
Voicemail's voicemail quality is on the rise lately. Good.
The tide is rising, lifting all ships. Send us a voicemail at speakpipe.com
slash pcp voicemail. If you think that you are funny also, like these gentlemen,
and subscribe to our Patreon at patreon.com slash the procrastinators to hear bonus episodes and
behind the scenes episodes. There's so much there for so little money. There's literally no excuse for
you. It's pretty hard to find excuses. I will also say, I will mention again that a couple people
in the comments last week were asking about Radcon stuff, and again, I will say it, believe it or
not, the stuff from Radcon 4 is still being made and will come out. I cannot say exactly when,
but it is still in production. We had a meeting not too long ago to figure out a lot of stuff and
get things rolling. There's been a lack of communication, but we're communicating,
and it's all getting done. Everything's on its way. Did you ask that one guy about the stuff?
The one guy about the stuff? We'll find out after the podcast is done recording.
Yeah, true. Okay, I guess that's it. Any final, any last words before we close it?
Watch Buffy the Vampire Slayer. It's good.
Play Noida. It's good. Join me in Apex Legends. It's all right.
It's based. Okay, that's it. That's the episode. Good night. Goodbye. God bless.
Goodbye. The end. Love you. Mwah.