I'm gonna bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Well, it's been a week since no podcast.
Yeah, it was Easter Sunday.
I hope it's been worth it.
Sorry guys, that was my fault.
I'm the reason.
You rose from the grave.
I know, I know.
Yeah.
Dang.
Ben, what did you give up for Ash Wednesday?
Did you give up anything?
There's sort of Wednesday.
Smoking weed.
You did, huh?
Smoking weed for Ash Wednesday, yeah, I gave it up for my entire life, because Ash Wednesday
is just that important.
Every Wednesday, I give it up.
Your real ash, your real ash head.
Yeah, I used to be.
I put my blunt out on my forehead and I said, oh, there's no more.
I don't need it anymore.
You did.
You did a Dr. Manhattan thing where you drew the symbol on your forehead, but you used
the blunt and you made a weed leaf.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's exactly right.
I drew the entire tetrahedra canna binol molecule, a complicated diagram, I'll do it.
I'll do a symbol that better represents me.
It will be one I respect for 20.
Recently.
It will be one I respect draws the Tesla logo.
Recently a passenger, a Lyft passenger gave me a weed.
He gave me free weed.
That's spectacular.
And a jar, just because.
That's, yeah.
Because you were based?
Yeah, pretty much.
It seems like a bad business model.
It seems like you're losing money doing such a thing.
As long as you got it in addition to payment, well, you can't jump into the car until you
actually pay for the app.
Like the app has your cards or your paint anyway, you know, so you're going to give
me money anyway.
And he is, I guess I was just talking to him about society.
I was telling him about society and the problem with society is kind of like this guy's kind
of based as you get some weed and it works out perfectly because I ran out.
So yep.
It does work.
It does work out perfectly.
Got refilled.
Yep.
Life be like that sometimes.
She gets sugar.
No.
I don't need sugar.
Sugar high.
That's what I'm chasing.
Yeah.
No more weed now.
Only sugar.
Just glucose.
What's it called?
Glucose.
I tried.
Okay.
Glucose heads.
In my pursuit of a perfect licorice, I changed my strategy up and I have created something
called rather than you sugar like a fucking moron, I've created invert sugar.
Do you know what that is?
Salt.
Yeah.
Invert sugar.
I've created anti-sugar.
Okay.
It's actually, it sounds less complicated than it is.
It's just you put sugar in water.
You ever make rock candy?
You know how when you put sugar in water and then you cook it down, it like crystallizes?
Yeah.
I have not done that, but I know that, yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, if you add a little bit of acid, I guess it like changes, it like reverses the molecular
structure or something.
It changes the molecular structure such that it does not do that anymore.
And that's how you can, you can cook sugar down into like a thick, gloopy syrup.
Down into what, down into what we confectioners call the softball stage of sugar reduction.
So shut up.
Shut the hell up.
It's not funny.
So yes.
They're so fucking silly.
These pâtissiers look down their nose at me.
So I cooked, yes, I made a jar of a softball stage invert sugar and I tried making licorice.
I tried making a Twizzler with it.
It was still too soft, but it was much smoother.
Do you believe it?
It was much smoother than what the ones I had done with refined sugar.
So that's an improvement.
Yeah.
You're kind of like a senior citizen, Ben.
Wow, I really thought you were going to say you're like Walter White because everyone
says, wow, Ben, you're like Walter White.
Oh yeah, I bet you want me to compare you to Walter White.
I bet you love it.
You'd be like the eighth person to do it, so, you know.
Is that because you don't have any hair anymore?
Because I have no hair and because I make concoctions in the kitchen.
You live in New Mexico.
I live in New Mexico.
I have cancer.
Yeah.
That's an upcoming.
My wife hates me.
Yeah, true.
Your wife does hate you.
Did he ever do any rapes?
No.
He did in a sexual assault.
I remember that.
Against Skyler?
On Skyler?
Yeah.
Well, you know.
She was pregnant.
She didn't want it and she was just going too hard.
He thought he could get a horny tie whenever he wanted.
Yeah.
And he's kind of like a wife consent matters.
I'm a cool gang banger drug dealer now.
You have to respect me and, you know.
Yeah.
Breaking Bad is pretty cool like that, where it's like, yeah, you know, nerds kind of do
ruin everything when you think about it.
Especially like, you know, drug, drug dealing.
They ruin it.
They should stay with the kitchen.
Not me though.
Not you.
No, you're different.
Not me though.
You know that roller coaster that is designed to kill you?
You mean Phantom's Revenge?
No.
Sure.
That's a roller coaster of an experience reading that.
No, you'll be dead by the end of it.
No, there's an actual roller coaster called Phantom's Revenge.
Oh, I don't know if it's called.
It's not called Phantom's Revenge.
I know the thing he's talking about.
It pre-exists the video game.
It pre-exists the famous video game.
Okay, no, not that one, because the one I'm talking about doesn't exist.
It's like a hypothetical, like designed roller coaster.
It's the thing that everybody makes in like roller coaster tycoon as soon as they boot
up the game.
Yeah, basically.
What?
It's like, let me, I'll look for an image for it, but it's basically has like a huge
ass like ramp that goes straight up into the air and it has like, it has like enough
apparently like the loops number that it chooses is enough to straight up kill you.
I saw someone tweeted out recently with the caption, yeah, I would survive this.
Oh, is it the one where like the loops get smaller and smaller and like the centrifugal
force gets higher and higher and eventually turns you into a milkshake?
Yeah, it starts really tall and it goes like a pigtail.
Yeah, I would survive.
I just wouldn't let it kill me.
Yeah.
Mr. Beast should invent, like create that with his money and then people can see how cool
they are by surviving the euthanasia coaster.
That'd be some good content.
Mr. Beast should put transphobes in it.
I bet it's a painless way to go.
I bet you passed out well before.
Do you feel it when you get turned into a milkshake?
Is that a feeling, you know?
I think you'd have passed out well before it happened.
There we go.
But yeah, basically it's this.
This is a graph of how you would feel.
In fact, you feel really like really good right at the top and then very quickly becomes
powerful.
And then quit, you would alternate rapidly.
You would feel good and bad alternating until you're dead.
It kind of reminds you of what it is like.
We're not even sure that if you drop the thumbnails really funny.
We're not even sure that if you drop a human into a black hole, they'll even feel it.
We're not exactly sure what's going to fucking happen to you.
Yeah, like if your brain is halfway through the event horizon, do the neurons firing even
reach the other part of you?
Is that like, is it just like, dude, what the fuck?
I always thought that's a really cool way to go.
There was some sort of anime where they defeat the final guy by dropping his ass into a black hole.
And he's just getting stretched beyond infinite.
And is he even feeling it?
Is it even like he's in this in between state of alive or dead?
It's so confusing.
I've tried to wrap my head around.
I've seen so many YouTube videos trying to explain what you would feel at the edge of
a black hole going into it because time stops.
Well, time dilates.
Dilates to a point where it basically is like you don't perceive anything happening.
So would you just be sitting there?
No, your time would be relatively dilated compared to an outside observer.
I mean, you would experience time for yourself moving normally.
But then like, you know, time would be moving really fast like outside of the event horizon.
You'd be falling in and you'd see like the universe die like outside.
You'd see like the entire universe die.
Well, you wouldn't see anything because light couldn't get in.
Well, no, it can get in though.
It can get in. It just can't get out.
Interesting.
That's so cool.
So like all the photons are like flying in and you've got to like catch them with your eyeball.
Otherwise they'll pass you into the infinite nothing.
Yeah.
It's the little game.
You've got to see how many photons you can catch.
That's right.
Black holes can like get full, can't they?
And then they explode.
No.
When they get full, they go, oh, I'm so full.
Oh, I'm so fast.
They're stunk.
Wrong.
No.
I don't think I can eat anymore.
They can't get full, but they can get empty.
Yeah.
What's the thing with the...
It's like a big swoosh of energy like escaping a black hole and making it shrink.
Like the matter inside of it is escaping as some sort of a thing.
It's not a big swoosh.
It's a very gradual process of, oh, what's the thing?
There's a certain kind of radiation that a black hole does emit.
And a black hole can eventually like radiate away all of its mass.
That's cool.
Which you would think it couldn't do, but it does.
I would survive a black hole.
But it's really slow.
I could probably survive a black hole.
Yeah, I played out to wilds.
I know my way around a black hole.
Yeah, I could escape.
Hawking radiation, hawking radiation.
Deep radiation.
Hypothetical particles formed by a black hole's boundary.
Yeah, so I could hypothetically survive is what you're saying.
So you're saying it's not 100%.
What if things named after people were named after their first name instead of their last name?
Steve's radiation.
Steven radiation.
That's like Steven Universe.
Yeah, Steven radiation is Steven.
Yo.
And like Newtons would be Isaacs.
The force of 20 Isaacs.
I guess it wouldn't change that many things.
But I just like the idea that it could be a force that is measured in jobs.
A more casual.
That'd be a pretty funny kind of like naming convention.
That'd be a pretty funny alternate reality where everything is the same.
It's just that now we just name things based off people's first names.
And that's just like the one difference.
Yeah.
So like the capital of the United States is just called George as is the state.
I remember there was one story.
I probably mentioned this before about alternate realities.
And the one difference between the reality they jump into is that Bob Dylan didn't create the stage name Bob Dylan.
He just uses regular name instead.
Sad.
A very disturbing universe.
An evil universe, if you will.
Yeah.
Hey, I watched a movie.
Hey, I watched a movie over Easter.
No way.
Nate showed me this great film.
You might have heard of it.
It's called RRR.
Are you familiar?
Oh yeah.
I heard it's really good and it's three hours long.
It is three hours long.
It should have been longer.
What is what is this film?
I've heard it is an it is an Indian action drama.
Well, it's like about it's sort of about like real life Indian people.
But it's like a fictionalized version of their lives where it's like they never knew each other in real life.
But the movie is like what if they did meet each other and they were best bros for life and they had anime superpowers.
And it's so good.
It's so cool.
There's there's big like it's not technically a Bollywood movie because it was made in a different language.
It's made in the Telugu language, which is not Hindi.
So it's it's something called Tollywood.
But you know, it's whatever.
It's an Indian movie and it and it's got those Bollywood style like big like Indian dance numbers just in the middle of like action scenes or like just whatever.
There's just a whole bunch of them and it's just so it's so earnest.
It's like to a Western to my Western sensibility.
It just comes off as having like absolutely no sense of like irony or like self consciousness about just like just have the characters do a big stupid dance number after they, you know, have a big battle or whatever.
Wait, but how am I supposed to know when to laugh?
The characters look at the camera and say, um, that just happened.
Um, that just happened.
You're always supposed to be laughing.
You're always laughing.
That's the that's the goal.
The job of the person next to you whenever you're watching it.
Yeah, he's supposed to poke you in the shoulder and say, did you see that?
That just happened.
Yeah.
Please laugh.
We don't need we don't need Joss Whedon telling us that just happened.
You're you're annoying friend in the theater.
Can just be did you see what just happened and you go?
Yeah, shut up.
Trying to watch the movie.
Did you just happen there dancing?
Can you believe that?
I don't know.
I want to like gush about it.
I want to like, I want to like spoil it.
I want to tell you all the all the amazing things that happen in RRR.
But like the emotions instead, maybe of like what?
Which experience?
It's it's would you say it's like funny bad good or like actually brilliant?
It's not it's not.
No, it's not bad at all.
It in no way is it bad at all.
Like none of none of my enjoyment of it was ironic.
Like I was I was laughing with the movie because it was very silly at times.
I like those.
But it's silly in a way that just made me clap.
It just made me clap and go just maybe clap and jump out of my seat and go.
Yes.
Sounds sounds good.
How do you spell it?
Is it just the letter?
It's the letter RRR.
I guess it technically stands for rise roar revolt.
In them, but in the move in the movie, there's like there's there's like chapter beginning that are like.
Okay, so the characters are like it starts with one that's like story and the R is big in story.
And then they introduce this one character who is the fire and the R is big.
And then there's another character who's the water and the R is big.
But that's not what the R stands for.
It's awesome.
They just like our they just they just like the R is there a pirate that goes R.
There is not a pirate.
Oh, there is not a pirate.
I'm sorry.
I really do want to watch it.
But there is a jungle man.
There is a jungle man.
Which is like a pirate.
Jungle man.
Jungle children.
You know, children from the jungle.
Children from a book.
I'm trying to think of what can I even what can I say without the without.
What can I say that hasn't already been said?
Would you say the unforgettable moments?
Would you say that your hatred of people with melanin?
Like you probably change your mind on it.
Like you probably like people with melanin now.
It made me.
It made me think maybe they have a chance.
Maybe maybe they maybe maybe there's something to these.
Maybe there's something to these brown people.
Maybe maybe some brown people are cool.
You know, sometimes like how some white people are cool sometimes.
You know, the movies basically about how white people are bad.
True base.
This is very woke.
This is very, very woke film.
That's awesome.
Kind of reminds me how every time I pick up a passenger who's like Indian or like a darker shade of skin.
I raise my fist in a brown power.
I tell him, you know, have a brown pride.
United together.
You pull out.
You know that shot of the guy hold in family guy, the guy holding out the skin color guide.
Yeah.
That's like if you're lighter than this, you're a tourist.
If you're darker than this, you're a terrorist or something.
Yeah.
You pull it.
You make it.
You make a fist.
You pull out the guide.
If you're lighter than this, you punch them.
And if you're darker than this, you fist bump.
Nice.
I think I think it I think it makes a lot of sense.
Cheesy.
Were you the driver in that story?
Yeah.
Oh, I thought I thought the driver gave gave you weed.
And I thought that seems a bit odd.
You know, I'm I was the driver.
The passenger gave me weed.
That's nice.
Yeah.
I mean, I thought it was either way.
So, you know, I got I got paid and I got weed, which is pretty great.
Because I kind of, you know, I'm low.
I'm probably not going to smoke it until like I do another round of pre-orders.
That's usually trying to get really stressed out.
It counts.
The I just OK, give remember when you and Munchie reviewed s cry Ed and you did a terrible job and you completely and you
completely like a normal person would and I was like, huh, what's going on?
You watched it.
You want first of all, the whole premise of three episodes terrible.
You literally did not even get to understand what the show is about.
The show is about.
Unlikely video, how to tell a bad anime from one episode.
We will give us we would be in generous.
S cry Ed.
S cry Ed is about an unlikely bromance between the two biggest badasses in the world and they're opposing
ideological philosophies.
And you didn't even get to that part.
But that's but that's what RRR is like.
It's like s cry Ed, but Indian and good, actually, even though I like s cry Ed.
So, yeah.
I don't know.
There's there's you'll be you'll be sold in the field be sold in the first 15 minutes.
If you if you turn it on, I think there's a establishes right out the gate.
What kind of movie are in for?
I really can't really can't say enough good things about it.
It showed me that movies can be good, actually.
Nice.
That's that was me when I watched the Mario movie.
I was like, oh, movies can be good now.
I guess it JK.
I guess it won a an Oscar despite being from India.
It won an American won an Oscar for like one of the musical numbers in a fair world.
It probably it should have been like up for like best picture.
I mean, I'm no expert.
I mean, it was it was my movie of 2023, even though it came out last year, I guess.
But it would probably it would have been my movie of 2022 as well.
You haven't seen them.
You haven't seen everything everywhere.
All at once.
You know, I did see it.
No, I liked our no, I definitely liked our better than everything everywhere.
Everything everywhere was like fine.
It was good.
I enjoyed it.
I thought it was very I thought it was a very twee twee, which I am not a huge fan of.
Damn.
I thought the met I thought the metaphor was a little strained.
You know, it was OK.
It was good.
It's a good movie.
Yeah, I really liked everything everywhere.
You must prefer RR is even better than must be a good year for movies.
Ben clearly has a favorite of Asian.
He prefers East Asians.
I feel like I feel like everything everywhere.
I don't know.
It felt like it was really trying to like tell you something like it really thought it had some something to say.
RRR doesn't have anything to say except India fucking rules and fuck the British and well, that's an anime is awesome.
It's probably got something to say.
It does.
Yeah, it definitely does.
The end of the movie is like a big dance.
It's like a big dance scene and even like and the director of the movie starts dancing with all the characters.
While like pictures of like Indian like political like revolutionary figures like are like scrolling by in the background.
Yeah, no, the movies the movies got politics that I don't understand because I don't know who these people are.
That's really cool.
It is pretty cool.
I wish more people would do that where like they would the cast and crew would start dancing.
That it was cool.
It's like it's like it's like it's very silly.
They don't do that in America.
They don't do that in Hollywood movies.
Yeah.
They like imagine if the imagine if the Avengers just started like doing like an Irish jig.
They just all started doing like a big jig.
But Ben, you never you never seen the show a peacemaker because that's the intro of the show is them.
Is all the cast members doing like dancing to a glam rock song.
It's a pretty good intro.
Cool.
Yeah.
I like it.
Okay.
I'll watch our just three hours.
So busy.
I can't I can't recommend it enough.
It's it's three it's three hours.
It felt like it felt like two or one hour per hour.
One hour per hour.
That's right.
Didn't did.
Yeah, earned every minute of it.
I would I would even watch it again.
I don't like rewatch movies, but I would I would watch it again.
That's how that's how serious I am about the quality of this film.
Ben rewatching a movie.
I know.
That's that's how serious.
I can't wait.
Is that John Cena?
Yeah, John Cena's peacemaker.
His mask is on crooked.
His face is no the mask is straight.
The face is crooked.
Yeah, I love this intro.
It's pretty good.
I forget the name of the kind of like animation where there's like a little
there's like anime characters.
People use it when they kind of make like little Miku music videos,
but I wish someone would like create a template out of this and you can just
put your characters dancing to it or something.
I think it I just think it would work perfectly and probably catch on.
But alas, I do not have the time.
I'm watching this peacemaker opening credits.
I will say RRR has better moves.
Definitely.
Not bad.
You know, these are all white people.
These are all white people, unfortunately.
This is white culture.
This is white.
Well, glam rock is like a pretty pretty white.
That's that's true.
There's one there's one.
Unfortunately, the one blemish on the on RRR is that there is one good white.
Nice.
But she's not but she's not that important.
There's only one good white person kind of like in Black Panther.
They have they have a good white CIA member.
She's there's one there's one good British person and it's a lady who is
maybe the maybe the maybe the dumbest part of the movie.
Damn.
Maybe the part that I think is the dumbest, but it's OK.
It's fine.
That's funny.
She is nice and but she gets she gets to dance.
So, you know, good for her.
That's good.
Yeah, I feel I feel represented.
Um, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh.
Shut up.
Okay.
You got nothing to say.
Don't say duh.
All right.
That's the end of the episode.
Goodbye.
I got nothing.
I want to talk about comics for a little bit.
Little bit of those comics have been working on Clarissa chapter five now,
but it's been a little bit of rocky.
I've I've I've gotten, you know, I don't know what it was.
I put the first volume on Amazon.com and I got some purchases and it was so cool.
And I was just sort of looking at that.
And then, you know, the the money stopped, you know, the people stopped buying it.
I'm like, OK, so that's the people who know about it.
They've got it.
I should probably like try to market it more often, make some noise about it.
Yeah.
As I'm working.
And I was like, I don't know why this was so strangely difficult.
I think it might be an ADHD thing.
I've heard like this sort of thing is might be an ADHD sort of thing.
But like, I was I was having this plan of like going to post every page from Clarissa
Facebook on my Twitter and Tumblr and Instagram, just posting the page one per day and then
having a link to where you can read it and buy stuff.
And I'm like, I could schedule tweets like that.
I could just put them all up there.
And that would be so easy.
It would be the easiest thing in the world.
And I don't know why I couldn't do it.
I was just it was staring me in the face.
It was like the most the least amount of work I could do.
You'd have to schedule several hundred tweets.
Right.
Like it's more like 60 67 at this point.
But like it's like for you post four pages for each tweet and just put it in a thread.
I could do that.
But then it would be less.
It would be less.
I mean, it's probably a smarter thing to have more more pages.
But I don't know.
Some pages are not that interesting.
But I think one page just because if they're too small, then like you can't see them when
you're scrolling past the small thumbnails.
And I think one page is fine.
That's that's not I mean, that's like probably going to take you like a couple hours to do
like 67.
Well, it's not that easy.
I mean, no, but like even doing one, I was thinking, OK, well, maybe if I don't schedule
them, maybe if I just put one up to get the ball rolling and I couldn't do it, I was like
sort of freaking out.
It was a weird experience.
Did you not want did you not actually want to do it?
I wanted to do it and it was it would be so easy.
And like every bone in my body was saying, nah, and I don't I didn't get it.
It was very odd.
And so I had a sort of maybe I was depressed.
I didn't even really feel like I was.
But I've been slowly grinding my bones into a fine mist.
And now I'm getting back to doing some some actual line art for the new chapter, at least
that something is getting done.
That's good.
I I did not I did not finish Biscopades.
Like I said, I might I did do some more.
But I didn't I didn't finish it.
You were talking in the chat like the chapter is nearly done.
What did you mean by that?
In the chat.
Just a few minutes ago before the few minutes ago.
In the DM to me.
Almost done with the new chapter.
Of one piece.
Oh, whoops.
No, I have I have some more Biscopades page.
I think I have like.
Seven more pages or something.
Didn't didn't didn't get to spend all my time working on them this past two weeks.
Like I maybe it would have liked to.
But, you know, it's getting there.
No, I know I was talking about the one piece chapter, which I has been out for a while.
It's been out for a while.
There was a break last week.
So by the time this episode comes out, there'll be a chapter.
That we will not talk about.
Great.
Good scheduling.
We're really, we're really, we're really on the ball.
I guess we should we should mention why there was no episode because we didn't actually say.
I just wasn't here.
You weren't here for, I guess I assume Easter meetup or something.
I went to my family house for Easter and I wasn't at my computer.
Yeah.
And I could have done a gift cusp.
I didn't really feel like it.
I was also celebrating and mostly.
I like now that the weather has changed a little bit.
Yeah.
And I just wanted to spend my whole Sunday just lying in sunbeams.
I wanted to go outside and have the sun on my face.
And I would look up at to it with my eyes closed and be like, oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
It was winter.
That's the best feeling.
It was winter like four days ago and then three days ago.
It was like 80 degrees at night.
I was walking around in a t-shirt in shorts in the evening.
Yeah.
That's too hot.
It didn't feel like 80.
During the day it was kind of hot, but it didn't feel like 80 at night.
The weather said it was, but it was like walk around comfortably in t-shirt weather.
It was great.
Now it's not that one.
It's a little bit breezy.
It's a bit like a random storm will come through and hail.
And then it'll be like five minutes later.
It'll be nice and bright and sunny.
It's been a nice time to be outside and looking up at the clouds and be like, oh,
imagine if there was a skypea up there or something.
Imagine if there's a skypea at me.
That's like, you know those pictures that are like regular people versus creative people?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And they just have like a bit of hair dye.
It's like the creative person, it's like the girl is watching her chicken roast in the
oven, but the creative girl has pink hair and is imagining that a dragon is cooking
the chicken in the oven with its fire breath.
That's you, creative people.
Yeah.
It's like you.
I look at big clouds and I'm like, oh, yeah.
So cool.
What if there was a man living on them?
What if there was a little guy up there?
I mean, unironically though, sometimes a cloud looks like you could climb it.
It's a snowy mountain.
Sure.
And that's, I just like looking at it.
I just like drooling, like dumb, like duh, like looking up.
That's me.
That's where I want to be in life.
Well, you can't.
What a creative person.
Yeah, that's so creative of you.
I'm so creative.
Normal people look down at their shoes all day.
They don't look up.
They don't see the real world.
Normal people look down at their phone and watch pornography.
Like Pokemon pornography.
Yes.
Disgusting.
Kids these days are more interested in seeing Pikachu choke on a 12 inch cop instead of
looking at the sky where the real beauty lies.
They look up and see God choking on a 12 inch cop.
It's like it says in the Bible.
Oh, the beautiful bird song.
Beautiful bird dong.
Man, I'm not in any comics.
I think the last one I drew was my Jesus comic for Easter.
You know what you haven't done, Cheesy?
What?
I haven't done my voice in Pagliacci.
Where's the voice Pagliacci?
I'm working on it.
You were so in a rush.
You're like, Ben, you got to give me that voice.
If I don't get that voice, it's going to throw a wrench in the whole works.
I did say.
And I slaved over it.
I did say those.
Those were my exact words.
Yes, that's true.
Just for you.
Just to keep this machine well oiled and running.
But then what you got to understand is that I owe I owe money to Fredo taxes.
And I'm currently doing double shift over here so I can pay them.
Fuck.
Yeah, I forgot it's tax.
It's tax day in like two days.
Yes, it is.
I haven't done him.
Wait, really?
Oh, wow.
Yeah, whatever.
I'll just file for an extension, maybe if I can.
I am when I went to my tax guy, I showed him like everything last last year,
which was my humble linear.
I showed him how much like how much money I didn't make.
And he's all like, wow, so basically just running everything on a loss.
And I'm like, haha.
Didn't.
Yeah.
Didn't you?
Oh, did you not have like taxes withheld from your pay checks or whatever?
No, you don't you don't get a rebate.
Okay.
All right.
I don't either.
Yeah.
So yeah, but he but luckily my tax guys is pretty chill guy.
He his office is covered in like little G.I. Joe figures.
I don't know if I talked about this guy before, but I don't think so.
He's pretty cool.
Yeah.
His office is covered in G.I. Joe figures.
He would makes like little custom ones where he like him and him and me part of the G.I.
Joe figure community.
They just give each other little parts and then glue them together.
The G.I. Joe figure community.
Yep.
They make like the GI bros.
The GI bros.
Yeah.
Little custom figures for characters and whatnot.
He really likes my comic and all the shit that I do.
So he'd be like, yeah, you're running everything at a loss, but you know, that's how that's
how it is when you're working on your dreams.
Like, haha.
Yeah.
I guess.
I guess that's how it is, huh?
That's sex.
Yeah.
You just got to pick yourself up by your bootstraps.
I guess.
Yeah.
You have to fling yourself up by your bootstraps.
You got to like, like David and Goliath swing yourself around by your bootstraps.
And then we got to right into the eye of the giant.
You have to fling yourself right into the giant yourself.
You got to escape orbit by your bootstraps.
True.
True that.
You got to have the eye of the tiger.
I am.
Yeah.
But killing tigers is illegal.
Who said that?
Is anyone important?
Did any person, any relevant person say that?
That's what I thought.
Uh-oh.
Um, what are we doing here?
What are we doing?
What are we talking about?
Let's go.
Well, I was talking about comics.
This comic.
This is the last comic I made.
And it pissed off a lot of, there's so many angry Christians at me on TikTok.
Are they really?
Yes.
Some of them are speaking in Polish to me and they're mad.
Who has time for this?
I don't know.
This is so silly for a thing to get people really mad.
It is.
Yeah, it's really funny.
And it was kind of a banger because it made me jump up by 100 followers on TikTok when
I did it.
It's pretty good.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Do you know this meme, Ben?
The Annie Man Studio meme.
It's like, it's an animated something or other.
It's like a...
These guys walk in and it's got a huge butt and they look at it.
But I don't know if that's in context.
There's this South American studio called Annie Man and they do animated gay porn, right?
Yeah.
But they kind of do it in a classic cartoon style for some reason.
Okay.
And their intros are very funny and there's one where there's like a black man with a
huge ass and he's walking down the street and all the other men are all going at him.
And they're following him and they're all bobbing to the head of the beat of the song.
Right?
Okay, sure.
Yeah.
And they eventually get into an elevator with him and they go up to some sort of hotel room
where they all have gay sex with him but they're all still dancing.
Like they're still doing like a little dance while they're having gay sex.
Sure.
Sure, beautiful.
Yeah.
It's a beautiful courtship ritual.
So why do you tell me all this for?
What's the...
Oh, it's just the most recent comic.
Okay, so this is that but it's Jesus.
Yeah, it's that by Jesus.
Okay.
The Romans are fine.
You know, it's an outside the box concept and I appreciate it.
Thank you.
It's just like how it was when it happened.
Yeah, it is as it was as the Pope says that one time.
Oh.
It's the original of it.
Forgis on the Jeep?
That's the line from the song that they use in the meme.
There's a song called Ballin' and they use like a sped up version of that song for the
meme and it just kind of works.
Oh, this looks terrible.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, you think it was a good looking gay boy?
I don't know.
This is like the proud thing.
The bad.
Bare-chested is like they drew the whole thing.
I love the...
Like each frame and it's all jerky.
I love the scene where like once they get up to the hotel room he like does it like a
funny spin and he takes off all his clothes.
I like all the guys in top hats and the wife and the big floofy just like appalled, like
dropping their monocles.
Like, well, good heavens.
Good heavens.
This man walking down the street with like the biggest, thickest ass ever.
Yeah, so people have been using this as kind of like a meme template.
Gotcha.
This is me putting my hat into the ring.
Gorgas on the jeep.
Putting your crown of thorns into the ring.
Yeah.
Jesus has risen.
He has made me rise.
You know what I'm saying?
Everyone was saying like, oh, this is blasphemy.
You're going to hell.
Someone said like, do you not know what Jesus did for you?
I retweeted a tweet that I thought was really funny on Easter where a guy just says like,
yeah, in the Bible, in the New Testament, there's a part where some of the apostles,
they meet some guy.
The guy's name is Nathaniel and they tell Nathaniel like, hey, the savior is here.
We got him.
And he's a guy from Nazareth.
The guy says like, Nazareth sucks.
No, he's not.
Why would he be from Nazareth?
Nazareth sucks ass.
And they're like, no, no, come on, come on.
And then later when Jesus meets Nathaniel, he says like, this guy knows exactly what's
up.
Like this guy is so on the level.
He's totally right about everything, including my hometown of Nazareth being a shithole.
Pretty good.
I guess.
I guess like, I guess like he was not prophesized to come.
He was prophesized to come from Bethlehem.
This is a point I was not clear on before.
I guess the prophecy was he would come from Bethlehem and Nazareth is like near ish Bethlehem.
So like, it's as if it's as if it's as if they said, oh yeah, the savior will be born
in Boston, but then he was born in like Lowell instead.
Yeah.
That's how you know.
Close enough, I guess.
That's how you know they're fucking lying to you.
Oh, that's how you would be born in Boston.
Yeah.
Okay.
Whatever you say, buddy.
Right.
Sure.
I've been kind of in like an anti-Christian mood as of late.
Correct.
But, but cheesy.
What about your soul?
Oops.
Oh, oopsie.
Oh, oh, oh, damn.
Oh, shit.
I didn't even consider it.
Oh, no, no.
Pray.
Pray now.
Pray, pray, pray.
You gotta pray the soul.
Oh, father out in heaven.
Please don't put me in hell.
Please, please, pretty please don't put me in hell.
No.
But what I mean is I've been in my private server.
I'm doing an art challenge where you're supposed to take like a superhero.
You do like the evil version of them.
And you kind of go in whatever direction you want with it.
So I was thinking like, okay, what if I did the fantastic four, but they're like religious
zealots, you know, instead of like scientists and like having a pro profit organization,
they're just like, that sounds like something that laserbot would make.
Yeah.
And they're, and they're called the fateful four is like their name now.
And I drew like the majority of them already.
Here's, here's my Mr. Fantastic.
I call them father flesh.
Like a melty gross.
Yeah.
All of them are disgusting.
All of them are kind of like body horror themes.
Here's the, he's like evil invisible woman right here.
Call her a mother transparency.
Yep.
Mother transparency.
That's cute.
I reminds me of that one Pokemon.
The ultra beast one.
Yes.
The rock, the rock poison one.
Nile ego.
Yeah.
I think I am going to like do like if I were to draw more of this interpretation of the
character, because she has like four shield power, you could do like kind of like four
shield kind of like tentacle shit.
So it looks more like a jellyfish.
Yeah.
And I was cool.
This is cool.
I got a, this is the evil human tour.
She called this one the human pyre.
Oh, these are cool.
These are pretty good.
And I'm pretty good.
Currently working on the evil thing, but I'm not too married to this design.
I might change this around.
He's like, um,
Yeah, it's hard because like, how do you turn a thing, a monstrous rock thing into invert it?
Yeah.
Wait, I've got it.
I've got it.
He's not made of rocks.
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait, he's made of rock.
The dome of the rock.
The Islamic shrine in Jerusalem.
Oh my God.
What does that look like?
Hold up.
It just kind of looks like a domed mosque.
Is that the Minecraft cube?
Oh.
Oh, it is.
It's the Minecraft cube.
It's the golden dome.
It's the golden Jewish dome.
Oh, the other thing.
Well, these guys are supposed to be like.
Well, it's Islamic.
These guys are supposed to be like Christian-esque, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going off theme.
When I drew the Jesus with the big ass,
someone's like, okay, now do Mohammed.
And I'm like, I have no idea what the fuck Mohammed does.
And I wouldn't.
Because.
He moved a mountain.
Didn't he?
Did he?
People like to.
Or maybe.
People like to do the whole.
He like had like a child bride.
Yeah.
I mean, I definitely.
Definitely heard about that one.
That was his greatest miracle.
What do you want me to do about that?
That happened like millions of years ago.
Draw his child's bride admiring his gigantic ass.
Draw his legally aged child bride.
Oh, the.
The.
Yes.
The cube.
I forget what the cube is called.
The cube is great.
I love that.
I love that they have a cube, you know.
Yeah.
It's good.
And you have to like point in that direction.
It's crazy.
Oh no.
Enderman.
No.
Someone should do.
You can't steal it.
You have to do a transformer movie where the cube is a transformer.
Like it's.
It's like another all spark.
Like we found it.
Yeah.
And they use it to power their ship.
We found.
It's just a cool looking.
It's just a cool looking item.
It's a cool.
Exactly.
And it's like what's great about it is that there isn't like a bleeding guy on it.
You know.
That's what.
Yeah.
True.
That would suck.
He was bleeding.
Oh, he died.
Oh, gee whiz.
Well, I didn't know.
He's he's a martyr.
He's a martyr.
God, I fucking hate martyrs.
Remember how you remember how they owned our God so hard?
We remember.
He came back though.
He came back.
Oh, Ben did come back.
Ben, do you not know what Jesus did for you?
I do know because I just rewatched that the Jenny Nicholson video about the church plays,
including the one where they crucify Batman on the bat signal.
That's crazy.
That's that's the real shit.
Batman does that in one of the movies, but to a criminal, he puts his body on the giant
like spotlight.
So it's so Batman kind of crucified him.
So Batman's like anti-Christian, if you will.
You know that scene in Digimon where they're crucifying not Gabumon, the wolf one.
Yeah, I thought the wolf one was Gabumon.
Is it Gabumon?
Yeah.
That's not a misremembering.
Garurumon, that's the only one I remember.
It is Gabumon.
Yeah, Gabumon evolves into Garurumon, which evolves into where Garurumon?
Which evolves into metal Garurumon?
And then ultimate Garurumon.
Probably.
And then mega Garurumon or something.
I always remember that they had an ultimate form, but then beyond ultimate is mega, which
doesn't make sense.
Ultimate would imply it's the most.
There he is.
I like how he's kind of holding his own paw.
Is this an Ultraman reference?
He's clearly like he's a dinosaur wearing like a wolf skin.
I like that.
Wow, I've never thought of that before, but that is what it is.
That's definitely what it is.
It's weird compared to like Agumon, who is just a dinosaur.
Gabumon, who is like the two of them are like the two iconic ones from that series.
One of them is just like a way more busy, complicated concept.
Yeah, I completely forgot he had that stomach tattoo.
He's got the second pair of paws from the skin.
And a unicorn horn.
Yeah, the unicorn horn.
Some of these stuff could be removed, you know?
Yeah.
That's probably why they crucified him.
Didn't remember that belly tattoo.
What's going on with that?
What's going on there?
He's like a freak.
He is a freak.
All these 17 different colors on him.
None of this is working for me.
That's why they crucified him.
Nice.
Yeah, we had it coming really.
To take off the wolf skin, never.
I'll die first, and then he did.
For our sins.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, here's Naked.
Here's Naked Garumon.
I think I've seen this.
For your pleasure.
Dumpy little guy.
It looks like a chicken nugget.
You know, without the fur, my eyes are drawn even more to his weird belly, and I don't understand.
It's like the only part of his body that has blue on it compared to the rest of his eye.
Right.
Yeah, I don't mind that he has a fur coat over himself.
It looks rad.
It's not a terrible idea in concept, but like...
The unicorn horn is like, I mean, I get it.
It kind of adds a little bit more to the silhouette.
Imagine trying to draw him.
Imagine being a kid and trying to draw Garumon.
Oh, I don't need to imagine.
I would never try to draw this guy, because he was like the worst.
I like drawing the...
I mean, honestly, this guy is...
The one that turns into the, oh, what's it, Palmon.
Palmon turns into the giant, like, Final Fantasy.
Patamon.
Yeah.
No.
I thought it was Palmon.
Wait, which one's Palmon?
Yeah, the...
It's not Palmon.
It's the one Palmon turns into.
Oh, the one that turns into Farimon, or Lilliman.
This fucking...
It's the Final Fantasy guy.
The Final Fantasy cactus.
Yes.
Okay, I did like...
I thought you meant Patamon who becomes Anjuman.
That was my favorite.
I did like Patamon.
I like Lilliman.
I liked...
I liked Anjuman because it reminded me of Yu-Gi-Oh.
That was a Yu-Gi-Oh card.
I liked...
I don't even remember their names, but...
Joey's the one that turns...
The ultimate form of Joey's one,
that is, like, the big walrus with, like, the turtle shell
and the giant...
Oh, yeah, I know what you're talking about.
That one was pretty cool.
I liked Garudaman, the...
What was the bug's one?
Kabuteremon?
Ultracabu...
I think it was Kabuteremon was the bug.
Tentamon.
Yes.
This was my favorite design, actually, I remember.
Because it was like...
It was basically aliens, but for kids.
Oh, because it was so fucking fucked up.
Oh, okay.
I wanted an action figure this time.
You meant the Xenomorph.
I thought it was alien for kids,
and I was like,
what's so, like, arerated about aliens?
Oh, no, yeah.
Xenomorph for kids.
Yeah.
That was a really cool design.
Man.
I was talking to people about, like,
why Digimon never caught on in the West
as much as, like, Pokemon did.
And I think Pokemon did a lot of pretty genius things
without simple things, you know?
Like, with Digimon, it's kind of like,
we just really have one,
and you just kind of go back and forth
between the stages of it, right?
But with, like, Pokemon, you get, like, a team, you know?
And, like, the world...
You can catch them all.
Yeah, and the world kind of makes, like,
even though they're both fantasy worlds,
the world kind of makes a little bit more sense
in Pokemon, where it's like, oh, the Pokemon
are just, like, they're animals, you know?
Like, their world has animals.
These are the animals of this world,
and you can, like, just catch them.
Digimon is basically an isekai,
whereas Pokemon is, like,
there's just...
There's no isekai element to it.
It just takes place in a world
that is fully, fully fixated on this, like,
fantasy creature concept
that your life in this setting
is devoted to the mastery of.
I also think the Pokeball
as, like, a symbol, as, like,
the visual symbol of the world is such...
It's so, like...
The fact that it's so simple,
it's, like, so fucking perfect,
and they never change it at all.
I mean, there's different versions of Pokeballs, but...
Yeah.
And another...
Literally iconic.
Another thing is that, like, the way you fight,
the way you capture the Pokemons
is the same way you fight them.
So really, there isn't, like, too much of a disconnect.
Well, like...
I mean, I don't know.
Do you capture more than...
The wristwatches...
And Digimon? I don't know how exactly it works.
No, you just get one.
You just get one.
The Digimon Digi bit,
but, uh, like, wristwatches.
They looked like Tamagotchi's.
I think also didn't...
Which didn't age very well.
Even...
That's an idea.
Even though technically Pokemon only started letting you
customize, like, your character
in the past couple of games,
you could already technically customize.
You remember from the start,
the fact that you choose what Pokemon are in your team
is a form of customization, you know?
Yeah.
Because, uh, like, when I was a kid,
I didn't give a shit about stats.
I only, like, got Pokemon that I thought looked cool.
Right?
And that's kind of...
That's another great thing is that
you could still beat the game with just Pokemon
you think that looked cool.
You could beat the games with complete trashmon.
Right, exactly.
And I think, um, yeah, I think it works.
I think Pokemon did a lot of very genius moves
that, like, made sure it kind of stayed.
And I think, um, I think that's why a lot of these other,
like, Pokemon wannabes keep fumbling.
They don't, like, really sit down
and look at what worked for Pokemon.
Remember when Myotismon...
did evolve at...
Mytosismon?
At 666.
And he attacked fricking Neo-Tokyo or whatever.
And they had the number of the beast.
They had the number of the beast.
On American TV for kids.
Beast.
Beast Japan.
Number of the beast.
Number of the beast, more like.
That's right.
The number of the beast.
The beast beast.
It roams our land.
Uh, uh, uh...
I really liked the end of the first Digimon season
really, like, left an impression on me as a kid.
Yeah.
That's shit.
It's pretty wild.
I don't know, it's pretty wild how, like,
they go to this fantasy digital world
and then they come back and, like,
the worst and most, like, deadly demons
follow them back from it and, like,
do terrorism and destroy the real world.
And then, I don't know, something about...
They go to, like...
They have to go to, like, the void
where, like, all the lost, like, data is
and they fight, like, the manifestation of all the,
all the, like, lost and destroyed Digimon data
in that big, like, polyhedron.
Fucking awesome.
So fucking epic and based and radical and cool.
Yeah, I don't...
I think I watched that when I was young
and I haven't re-watched it since.
It would probably be dumb.
It was very confusing.
As a kid, I was like, I can't believe,
I can't believe the stakes.
The stakes have literally never been higher
in my entire life.
But that's the sort of thing, like,
I think Pokemon the show was so good
and so watchable because, um,
every episode was the same thing.
You go to a place, you see a Pokemon,
you're like, whoa, what's going on?
And then you fight.
Yeah.
And in Digimon, there was a narrative
that you had to follow.
And I didn't catch every episode,
so I would just not continue watching Digimon
because I was like, oh, I missed an episode.
I don't know what's going on.
Pokemon doesn't matter.
Yeah.
And so I would watch that instead.
One thing that I really like about Digimon
is I don't know if this was done on purpose,
but the fact that the way, like, the creatures,
like, did evolve, they start out as, like,
something that a little kid would draw.
And as, like, it grows, it kind of becomes more like,
oh, like, you as an artist kind of grow
and you can draw things that are a little bit more complicated,
you know, until you're drawing, like,
your horny OCs, you know,
as you become older.
Right, when they become Angi-Waman
and Lilymon and stuff, yes, yes.
The final stage of evolution.
I kind of dig that.
I really think that's really, like, kind of cool.
You know, it's kind of like, oh, it's, like, growing up.
You know, I mean, because Pokemon do that, too,
but, like, with Digimon, it's kind of, like, more,
really not exactly sure what the next one is going to look like,
you know?
Where are you on the Artispectrum of Digimon Evolutions?
Or Digivolutions?
I don't know.
What's the one before, Rookie?
Is it, like, Baby?
Baby.
Goo.
Zygote.
When you guys were growing up, were you,
you know, like, the concept of, like,
horse girls or wolf girls and shit like that?
Yeah.
Were you, did you specialize in a kind of thing
when you were a kid in that way?
Because when I was-
Egg.
I'm egg.
I'm egg stage.
Oh, you're trans.
Oh, you're going to be trans.
Right.
But basically, what I mean is, when I was very little,
I was like, oh, I really like dinosaurs.
I would re-watch the original Walking with Dinosaurs documentary
that they made.
Because I thought dinosaurs were really cool.
And then I became a dragon kid because I was like,
oh, they're like dinosaurs with superpowers.
But, um, for some, even, but even as a kid,
I realized that I needed, I needed structure.
And there was a structure that drag,
dragons kind of lack structure.
And what I mean is that anything could kind of be a dragon,
you know, or like the, the kind of like the,
the rules of engagement with dragons like vary.
And like, I guess that wasn't enough for me to,
like, latch onto.
And then I found out about Godzilla.
And Godzilla had a lot of structure.
There's a lot of consistency between like,
like Kaiju's and the movies that they come from.
And I really like got into that.
So if I, if it was like a Digivolve evolution tree,
it would have been like,
dinosaur dragon and then like Kaiju kid, you know.
Oh yeah, I see.
Yeah, yeah.
So you guys ever,
did you guys go for something like that?
Is what I'm basically asking?
I, I mean, I remember in class,
there was the one girl who could draw the horses.
And she was the horse girl.
She would always draw horses and she was really good at it.
And I was like, that's so boring.
Where's the night on the horse?
I was always into drawing suits of armor,
swords and knights.
And that is my, I think that's my first thing
because night suits of armor like made up a little shapes.
It's like drawing a person, but it's easy.
Where did you, where do you think you went from there?
Are you still a knight kid?
I don't actually draw suits of armor that much anymore.
I mean, I occasionally, I'm trying to think cause like,
I think I sort of, I liked knights.
And then I got really into Dragon Ball.
And so I started to try and draw manga and I have like an old,
like a ripoff manga of like combining Dragon Ball
and Princess Mononoke.
And Jack and Dexter and stuff.
And I was like, oh, this is so fucking epic.
And it's like Naruto.
It's like got like ninja stuff.
But I don't know if that's like a style or like a type of thing.
I guess I just got into anime.
I was just, I went from knights to anime.
Yeah.
And then I would draw like bleach stuff.
And I don't know what, it's hard to remember.
I drew so many things.
I would draw a lot of like stuff like,
oh, I would copy things that were cool.
Like I would try and draw Goku.
It's something to think about.
Kind of like, what were the things that you like fixated on
when you were a kid, you know?
Ben, were you a kid?
Were you ever a kid, Ben?
No.
Thanks for asking.
Ben was pulled out of the mud.
It works.
He was pulled out of the slime.
Yes.
He was pulled out of his slime.
He formed and ready to draw the vapors.
By his father, Father Sate pulled him out of the slime.
And then he pulled Nate out of the gold.
The gold.
I am.
Because he's a golden boy.
He's made of molten AU.
I don't know.
I liked Animorphs.
I like to draw Animorphs aliens.
That's it.
I'll just put you down.
You're a slime kid now.
That's when I was like little.
At some point, I used to be into like space.
I was into like space and planets as a little kid.
And then I got into Animorphs.
And then at some point, I read like Lord of the Rings.
And then after that, I was into fantasy instead of science fiction.
So I was into the wheel of time.
And then, I don't know.
Definitely drew a lot of Lord of the Rings.
Then I found out about sex and I became a sex kid.
Yeah.
Then I became a Chad.
Then I put aside childish things and I put away books for babies.
And I just fucked bitches instead.
Nice.
Hell yeah.
And then I picked up, you know, I diversified my portfolio.
And picked up the sword.
I started training in the blade.
I, you know, I made a bunch of investments.
My, you know, I invested Wall Street, got Bitcoin.
Obviously, I got Bitcoin back in like 2001.
So now I'm billionaire.
And that's it.
That's the story.
Wow.
It sounds like you make nothing.
I can't believe there's a billionaire on this show.
And we never knew.
Yeah.
It's pretty ironic.
It sounds like you only make good choices, Ben.
That's crazy.
It is crazy.
Thanks for noticing.
That's insane.
I, for what, am appalled to hear that.
I know it's fucked up.
It's fucked up.
You can make all the right choices and still end up like me.
I know it's really discouraging.
It's discouraging me if I'm making the right choices.
Maybe I should make wrong choices instead.
Maybe.
I'm really, I'm really like looking like my eyeballs have turned inwards and they're
looking at my brain scanning for like what I was into and what I was drawing.
There's loads of things.
I think, I can't like remember though, like in what order anything came.
And you are like Fire Emblem.
I would draw a lot of knights and swords.
I would try drawing skeletons a lot.
But skeletons are difficult.
You never have like memories of an adult talking about you as a kid saying like, oh yeah,
so and so is really into this and that.
Like you wouldn't hear that.
I would hear that.
But what I would hear is like, oh, they're into art.
Damn.
They like drawing.
And so I'm like, yeah, I was the drawing kid.
For birthdays, people would get me colored pencils.
And I'm like, okay.
Nice.
Oh yeah.
Where do you actually use them?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure I used some of them.
It was just sort of the one thing though.
It's just like more pencils, more paper.
You never have enough.
Never enough pencils.
How to draw manga.
I remember getting that like the iconic Ha Ha La Mal book of how to draw manga with the
terrible fucked up face on the cover.
I had that book.
Based.
And I learned how to draw.
I remember reading and being like, okay, I guess I could learn how to draw this.
But I don't like how it looks.
I didn't have that one, but I had some very similar books.
Google it.
I checked out how to draw manga from the library one time.
I checked out several of them.
I thought it was like a series of them.
I can't believe.
In retrospect it wasn't.
This exists.
Yeah, that one.
That one's great.
That one's a classic.
That's the one you had?
That's the one I had.
Yeah, I did not.
What does Katie Koop draw like now, I wonder?
Oh, let's find out.
I had one that was actually kind of good.
It was this one.
Oh, these are like expensive now.
These are like, yeah, how did this, this how to draw manga is actually kind of cool.
And it's, and it even.
Oh, I remember what reading this in the one of the ones in the series.
It even talks about like, I only read the first volume because I had it, but it talks about
not just like the drawing, but like being a mangaka and like having assistance and like,
you know, be like working for an editor and stuff.
And then I had another one that I am not seeing in any of these search results.
But the other one that I had was pretty crappy and it was very much, it just gave you like
a bunch of stock characters and was like, draw a circle, draw another circle,
put big hair on the circle, put the eye like this.
That one sucked.
Oh, wow.
Oh my god.
The how to draw manga book, Katie Koop made that when she was 16.
That kind of makes sense.
All right.
Good, good for her.
Look at the art style.
This is obviously a 16 year old.
They, they have drawn, they've drawn it again.
They have a Twitter.
Oh, damn.
Time to follow the queen.
Nice.
It's not, it's still not, it's still not great.
Wow.
When was this from?
It's not great.
Mostly post pictures.
2021.
What a freaking, fucking royalty.
This is fucking, you're not only royalty, we're looking at it right now.
Wait, where?
Oh, well, this is interesting.
She, she wrote about how she was initially happy to work on the book because she was
just a teenager.
She revealed that the character on the cover was a flipped illustration that she never
intended to become the cover art, which she protested at the time.
Okay.
I mean, cool.
Exonerated, I guess.
Not, not, not really.
I mean, I mean, I'm not going to think less of her.
I mean, she was like 16.
You're 16 and the company says, oh, you, you draw that, um, anime or man gay style.
We need to sell a book about that.
So could you, could you do this?
It's like, oh my God.
She's only got the, she only got the, she only got 6,000 followers on Twitter.
Yeah.
Unless I'm looking at the wrong person.
They're, they're KT Coop, right?
Like they go over there.
Yeah.
I found that Twitter from the article that's talking about the artist and this redrawing.
I do album art, promotional materials, web design, illustration.
I'm not super impressed.
Oh, bentate.
I mean, some of this is okay.
Color me surprised.
Some of this is okay.
Like design wise and like the, the actual, the actual, like, oh, like the actual illustration
on display is, is look at these faces.
Look at, look at this face of the guy in the middle here.
Uh, the guy, not the guy in the bottom left, but the, the samurai and armor right above him.
Yeah.
She probably could add a little bit more wrinkles to his face.
It's not, it's not, it's not working.
It's not working.
A little bit more stronger emotion, you know.
Oh man.
Um, I have a, I did it.
I didn't tell you guys about kind of a little feud that I was in the middle of a little
conflict that was happening that I was going back and forth and none of it was like public.
It was all behind like DM that like private discord servers.
That sounds amazing.
That sounds spectacular.
Yeah.
Basically, um, yeah.
And Nellie is our, you could like bleep out this, uh, this group's name.
Um, because I don't want to get into too much fucking trouble about it, but, um, there's
a, there's a, there's an organization called the right.
Okay.
And basically they're, um, they're trying to help out like in the artists and they want
to do their, they're mostly like, you know, helping you try to promote your stuff, yada,
yada, but also, um, they want to make a database like a giant database.
Like a giant database of everyone's like comics, like the, as many indie comics as they can.
Right.
And, um, and I, and I joined and I even like, um, paid kind of like, there was like a membership
fee.
I didn't even pay that.
It was only like five bucks really.
Um, but basically, yeah.
So I joined and I just been in their server and, and I even submitted McPuglachy into
their database.
Right.
Um, wait, wait, I'm sorry.
It's something really funny.
There's an opportunity for BIPOC creators only for a zine called the brown recluse zine
distro.
Like, like the zine is for brown recluse.
It's a brown recluse.
I think it's funny on purpose.
It probably is.
I'm always on the fence about kind of like, oh, we're looking for specific POC creators.
And I'm like, oh, I'm specific.
Yeah.
See creators.
And like, yeah, we want you to do a so and so specific thing that I'm not interested in.
And I'm like, damn, I'm, I'm the wrong kind of POC for this because I'm more interested
in drawing goblins than like other like, melanated people, you know, I'm kind of like, I'm kind
of like, you know, he's much more interested in telling movies about goblins than movies
about Mexicans.
Definitely.
True.
Basically.
Okay.
So anyway, I submitted a McPuglachie into their database, right?
And then I got a rejection letter, which I thought was weird because and they told me
that the quality was not up to par for the database.
Now, yeah, here's the weird thing.
If you take a quick glance through their database, you get the impression that quality is on a
spectrum.
Right.
I got the big impression that quality is has varies a lot.
Where, where would I find their data?
Right, right here.
It's on the website.
But here's the direct link.
So yeah, I, if you just go through and I read a handful of these of these, if you scroll
through it, um, yeah, it's obvious that quality is on a spectrum here, you know, I was so surprised
to find out that make Puglachie got rejected, you know.
And I, yes, I mean, the not all, not all of these look like super professional.
Right.
And yeah, I didn't even got, I never got the impression that it was supposed to be like
professional at all or anything because it's indie comics, you know, right?
And yeah.
Oh, but basically here's here's a Google Drive link to it.
This is, I'm, I'm like, wait, you know, I don't want to be mean.
Okay.
Don't call, don't call anyone out or anything.
But I mean, I mean, come on.
Yeah, that's, see, that's the thing.
I didn't call out no one, but I kept saying like, look, like it seems like quality is
not on a spectrum.
It's, you know, like what's, what's the deal?
Right.
So I'm thinking like, um, oh, by the way, above, I'm just gonna get again, but here's
a, here's a Google Drive link to, to an image gallery of all the screenshots of me going back
and forth with them.
And it starts with a, it starts with my rejection.
God, I'm not, I'm not reading these.
Well, I'm just going to summarize it.
So it starts with their rejection letter and me like replying back to them saying like,
I think I, I think I disagree with what you said.
Also, another thing that they said in the rejection later, they kind of like pissed me
off a little bit, but they said, um, they said, we encourage you to resubmit after you developed
your craft more.
And I thought that was kind of a rude thing to say.
Um, I did talk to my like, I mean, yeah, I mean, look, look at what's in the database.
Yeah, like, I'm sorry, but there's straight, there's straight up amateur stuff.
And also, and here's another thing that also pissed me off.
If you go into their cartoonist cooperative Instagram, um, you will find that one of
their Instagram posts is a promotion for Mick Pagliacci, like it's up there.
Right.
And it's so weird that like, why would you promote it but not having your database?
You know, like it seems kind of a little two-faced a little bit, you know, it seems kind of
hypocritical because what if someone sees that anything?
Well, I don't know.
I mean, is it, is it hypocritical?
Like, is there a reason for this?
Do you want?
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
I mean, like, why did they do this?
Oh, well, I mean, that's what I wanted to know.
Like, why did they reject it?
Right.
Why would they promote it if they were going to reject it from the database?
Exactly.
So I asked them, like, what, like, is there, is there something specific about Mick Pagliacci?
Now, in the back of my mind, if you just go for their database, one thing I noticed is
that there's no parodies or anything with like copyrighted characters.
So I'm thinking like, oh, maybe.
Okay.
Could that be it?
Yeah.
Right.
But I don't want to suggest that just yet because I want them to say it, you know?
I don't want them to be like, oh, yeah, yeah, that was, that's totally it.
Like, I want them to like, you know, tell me why.
Yeah.
So it's just nice to know.
Basically, they just told me the quality just wasn't up to par.
That's it.
That's just it.
And if they said, if I want feedback to go into their discord, into their feedback chat
in their discord server and post Mick Pagliacci there, and I did, I posted it in there and
I said, like, hey, can anyone tell me, like, why this didn't like get in, you know?
And a couple, a couple of people gave me like some feedback, but everything at any time
they would give me like feedback, I would like question it.
Like, um, someone told me there was one person in there, there was this one guy who said
he couldn't give me feedback in the feedback chat because he doesn't like giving feedback
in the feedback check.
He said he'd much rather prefer I talk in the forums, like, like, and I'm like, can you
just, I asked him, can you just DM me the feedback instead?
And he's like, no, no, it's much better if I do it in the forums and I'm like, well,
you know, I kind of wanted feedback in the feedback chat, but I did make a, yeah, I made
a forum post about it.
So I get feedback there.
And that guy did give me feedback, um, and his, and I even screenshot his feedback too.
It's in there later in the gallery when I go over what they say in the forums.
And I feel like he only had one bit of valid criticism, which he mentioned one panel and
he said that composition of this panel could have been better and I'm like, yeah, I agree.
It could have been better.
Um, yeah.
Okay.
Sure.
But, but this was not like a guy in a position.
This is not a guy in charge of anything.
This is just some guy.
Well, it's a, I think he's a committee member.
Some of them are like committee members, right?
So they're, they're guys that are like up there.
Um, but, but here's pure, I'm thinking, but this is what I'm thinking, because I bet
I could probably 100% bet I could find a comic in their database that does not have that
good composition.
Right.
Yeah.
Like that.
I don't think that's a crazy thing to like bet on, right?
So I'm thinking it's bad composition.
Like, is that the red line?
Is that like the, the, like, oh, like this is like, you got to have good composition.
Um, someone did, someone did mention that they thought the idea was that like funny.
Like it, um, I just, it's not a funny like idea.
They didn't laugh at all.
And it's, it was like a poorly executed joke.
And then I replied.
It was a poorly executed joke.
Is that like the line?
Like if you do a joke and it sucks.
Yeah.
I, it's not, it's not like is my work good enough, but like is like, what is the, what
are the rules?
That's the, that's where the, like, if it is like mascot characters or like stuff can't
be used.
Yeah.
Uh, just a heads up.
Be nice.
The, the, yeah.
If it was, if it was because of copyrighted characters, I think that would be perfectly
reasonable.
They, I asked them about parodies and they said parodies are allowed.
They allow parodies.
And I'm like, all right, well, I just, I guess it wasn't funny enough, but look, but, but
check this out.
Look, this comic right here, um, is, is this funny?
This isn't their humor section.
Is this a funny comic?
Well, let me, let me, let me take a look at the, oh God.
Are these like, um, just individual images or are they like, uh, they're like, uh, you
can flip through them when you click on them.
Oh, I have to log in.
I don't know my login.
Wow.
Yeah.
These are, these are like recent.
These are like recent.
Um, now, now is this funny and now, and like, I don't, I get, I don't have anything against
this, but, um, is it supposed to be funny?
It's in the humor section, but, and they said, and they said, it's not funny enough to,
to be in the database, but this is, and I'm like, okay, well, what's going on?
You know?
Okay.
I, I guess, I guess my thoughts on this are, yeah, I, I don't understand the, the standard
of quality.
I don't understand by what standard of quality, something like this is like, it's the thumbs
up, but something like McPagliacci is like, nah, it's not good enough.
I don't know what criteria they could give you that by which it isn't good enough.
But maybe, maybe, maybe more.
So who cares?
Yeah.
Ultimately, who cares about being a stupid database?
Well, the thing is, I would like, I mean, I would want McPagliacci to be as many things
as possible.
And it's kind of like this isn't really like, I don't think it's any, it's no skin off their
back if they post it, if they have it in their database, like it's not going to fucking, what's
the negative effect of it?
It's clearly up to par with like a lot of things they have up there, right?
What do you, what do you get out of them putting it in their database?
When you look up McPagliacci, it pops up if it's on like, it's on like a website, right?
I mean, I guess so.
Yeah.
Like, you know, yeah, it helps a little bit.
Like, you know, when people, now when people look for their database, they're going to
see McPagliacci, you know, it helps, you know, when they look for a database of content.
Doesn't hurt as the main thing.
Yeah, it doesn't hurt.
Here's the thing, the more I talk to them, the more like, the vibe that I get is that
they kind of already didn't like me.
And I think, and I think the reason why is because they didn't like that I kept posting
McPagliacci in the promo chat on their Discord server.
Yeah.
And which is weird, because it's the promo chat, you know, what did you, what else did
you want to post it?
They gave me the vibe that they specifically wanted me to make friends first before I start
asking about promotions.
Like, like, oh, we, yeah, like you're, you're never, you're never, you're always just promoting
yourself.
You're never like having conversations in there.
You're never like making, trying to make friends.
And it's like, well, fuck, well, fuck you because how, how do you not know I'm not making
any friends outside of it?
How do you know I'm not talking to these people in the group outside of the group?
Do I have to like be discussing them in the Discord?
Do I need evidence that I'm becoming friends with people?
That's kind of the feeling that I get in a lot of like comics spaces on the internet.
They're just kind of a big social club and nobody's really there to like, nobody's really
there to like make it in comics.
They're all just there to fuck around.
Hi.
Yeah.
We're trying to create an in-group that we can exclude people from.
We're trying to be like the coolest people ever that we imagine all the, all the comics
that we idolize are in.
I think.
We have our own club because we can't be in there.
I think what I think that's a lot of where it comes from.
I think the plan with this is that and like, yeah, I have no evidence for this plan, but
the idea is that the bigger this group gets, who are people going to most likely be talking
about that are involved in this group?
They're not going to be talking about the individual people in it.
They're going to talk about the people who run it, right?
Yeah.
And if people are running it, I'm going to get way more attention than anybody else like
in the group.
Sure.
Right.
And that's why, that's why you run things.
Yeah.
Like pixel dog comic.
Like the guy who made this is one of the guys who, who started it.
You know?
So it's like.
Well, there you go.
Yeah.
It's just so.
Well, there you go.
Submit red man.
And if they reject it, I can have, I can have like, cancel, red man will cancel.
Please submit red man.
Oh man.
If you, if you get it, I'm going to get mad.
No, I'll just do what you did.
I will not make friends and I'll see if they hate me.
No, this is like, well, it's like a science experiment.
No, I think, I think, I think you're right.
I think it's like, they don't know it's that it's a club.
It's a club and you're not in it and they don't know you.
And that's, that's more important.
Yeah.
And I mean, it's, it's kind of, it's kind of a shame, you know, it's kind of a really
big shame because, because like, you know, I saw the word cooperative and I thought, oh,
these guys must be cool.
They're more cooperative in the name and well, I see some people are more cooperative than
others.
Um, but I don't, is it, is it just comics?
Is it?
I feel like comics are always like that.
It's always just people fucking around.
I think it's like any kind of indie scene kind of thing, you know, yeah, which is that
what it's like to join bands, which is a shame.
That's the problem.
Is this what it is?
It's probably like to join a band that is just fucking around.
I remember back in high school, one of my buddies who was like, who would like rap and
whatnot.
Um, he said that there was like kind of like groups of, of like little smaller indie rappers
who, who would think themselves all hard and everything or really they just jerking themselves
off and they're on the club and that just, they just kind of happened in the indie scene.
I am reminded of like, I'm reminded of like, uh, the like the Topastic forums, which would
just be like, like no one who's successful on Topastic was posting on the forums.
It was all like, it was all nobodies to maybe people that had like a little bit of clout,
people that were people that were making like people that maybe had like a couple thousand,
a couple thousand views, people that were maybe making like $95 a month on Patreon or something.
People who are successful are not posting in, they're not, they're not posting in forums
about that, talking to other like comic people about like the craft of comic making.
They're not asking for critique and they're not giving critique.
The kind, the kind of critique you get in circles like that is like, oh, this one panel
has like a, the, the, the composition could have been stronger.
Fuck off.
I would, I would die.
I would say these, um, and this kind of curtain is cooperative, I do notice they give critiques
and whatnot.
There's people like engaging and shit and whatnot and I think, I think it's ultimately
they want to like, I think what they really specifically want in their database is comics
made by them, like made in, within their group so they can show off.
That's, that's why, that's why PixelDog or whatever is there.
That's why you fucking pick.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And it's, um, yeah.
I mean, it's, it's a shame.
You're an, you're an interloper.
Yeah.
You're showing up with work and you're an outsider and you're like, include me.
And they're like, well, we don't want it.
We only like you if you're, if you're, you're our best friend and you haven't shown that
you're our best friend yet.
Oh, come on guys, please.
Be nice to us.
Be my comic in your database.
I'll be your best friend.
You got to be your best friend first and then we'll put you in the database.
My mistake was finishing McPug Lashy before joining if, if I did work in progress in their
Discord server, probably would have been a different story, but it's, it's, it's a,
it's annoying.
You know, I feel like there should be like a database for any comics, but it can't be
run by other any comic people.
It's got to be just run by one guy who doesn't make any comics and won't like, um, doesn't
have any like assumptions about anybody who just put anyone in it, you know.
Yo, Gib, once, once the perfect comic party is out, this is going to be us.
We're going to be the in group and we're going to be the only, and only our best
friends will get to, uh, only the bestest of friends, the bestest, so I'm going to be
like, yeah, I submitted my comic into a, I did perfect comic party, but they said it
wasn't funny enough, but they have a McPug Lashy there.
Uh, no, no, it doesn't make any sense, make it make sense, guys.
Can we, can we, can we put McPug Lashy in the imperfect comic party?
Um, sure.
Well, how does that, how does that work?
How would that work exactly?
Um, McPug Lashy is quite long overall.
How many pages is it?
It's split it into two ads, it's already split into two ads.
Oh yeah, it's, it's got acts.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck it.
Why not?
It'd be like, it'd be like a chapter of so many pages and then the next issue would
have the next chapter.
Not going to, not going to make me sign a contract where you own McPug Lashy now.
No, I, no, I think what you're just.
Will own exclusive rights to print your comic in the perfect comic party.
No, I think, I think it would just be, I think it'll just be like a waiver or like
a form that's just like, you give us permission to post it online.
Like we're, we're, you know, you, you, you formally say like, yes, it's okay for
my work to appear in the digital file and be hosted on this website.
And it's not exclusive and there's no like print rights or anything like that.
No, no, we'll, we'll, we'll, we'll take it.
We'll steal it.
We'll, we'll, we'll, I'll ask, I'll come back and beg for
the print rights later.
You know what that reminds me?
I was going to ask, cause I was listening to you guys talking about
perfect comic party like a couple of episodes ago and you mentioned about doing
the whole shunning thing with like the reader voting.
And I thought that was kind of, I don't know if that's, I thought
that was kind of interesting because it's kind of like, okay, but what if like,
let's say for example, what if someone, what if everyone votes?
What if people vote against the comic you're making?
Like, would you stop making Beescapade if everyone was kind of like, no,
I don't like it and they like vote against it?
No, but if, but what if they vote for me though, then that would make me feel good.
Okay, but I'm, I'm saying, okay, let's say it's any, yeah, that may
you feel good, obviously, but just any comic you yourself are personally making.
What if everyone voted against that?
You know, I think, I think that, that, that would be, we would have to ask
the question then, what is the perfect comic party for?
If it's for being a successful comic publishing thing, like a collaboration,
like a bunch of comics in one publication and we want it to be successful
and everybody hates both mine and Ben's comic and we just can't put our own
comics in our own publication anymore, then that we would have to like not
put our comics in there.
But I don't think that's the point for me anyway.
Okay.
I just want to show off my stuff.
You know, I guess I don't really mind if it's not in the perfect comic party,
but like, I guess we'll see.
Okay.
You know what, Cheesy, I do, I do think you have a point.
Like the, the, the reader surveys in Shonen Jump are like, like the
purpose of those is so that like when a comic is bad and performers badly,
they can get rid of it and like, so we don't really need, we don't really
need them for anything.
I guess it's, it's the, it's the thing, but I would like to hear, I would
like to hear reader feedback, but like, I'm, I don't, we're not, until
we're like so inundated with submissions that like, we are too many
quality submissions and we can't host them all until we get to that point.
We don't need to be voting anyone off the island.
So if it comes to a point where like Clarissa Gunsmoke is the least
popular, um, I guess it's no actual like size problem, but it would get bloated
if we just kept saying yes.
And the, the, like the PDF would get like 200 pages long every month.
Um, so yeah, I guess hypothetically I would take my comic off.
I would still put it on my own things, but like, yeah.
I mean, that's, if we want it, if we want it to be like a, just a successful
publishing thing, but I don't see it like a successful or not, not that
it wouldn't be successful, but like the purpose of it is for me to make
comics and have a thing to put it on and be feel cool about it.
I, I think, um, I think, I don't know if I, if in, in this hypothetical
scenario where piece, the per comic party ran for a while and it got really popular
and there were tons of great comics in there and everyone's, we're getting,
we're getting some reader submissions and people are voting and Biscopades is
like bottom of the pile.
It's like the least popular thing in there.
I'll be honest, I wouldn't just quit Biscopades.
I would just, I would just finish, I would just wrap, I would, I would keep
going, finish it, wrap it up.
And then when it was done and be like, oh yeah, well, people didn't like it.
That's, that's what I was thinking.
I would, yeah, I would not, I would not quit Clarissa if people didn't
like it in the perfect comic party.
I would just have it as one of my, on my website, as my little thing
that only a small niche community would enjoy.
Well, because, because I don't see Biscopades being that long, I don't,
I don't think I would even pull it from the perfect comic party.
I'd just be like, eh, fuck it.
You're stuck with it until it's done.
Well, it's going in there.
Well, I think, I think, I think that's a pretty good idea.
If you think of it kind of like when you're selling lemonade and you, you
got your big jar of money and you, you put a couple of your own dollars in there
to make it seem like you're getting business.
I mean, like, if you think of having Biscopades and Clarissa gun smoke as like
your, your starting seeds for, for the publisher, whatever the fuck you guys
calling yourself, I, I, my, my dream, my dream is just that we get enough
submissions every month that we have, you know, it's not just me and Gibbs
comic, there's like a bunch of features in there every month.
There's at least, at least a few.
My dream, my dream is that we do that for a while and then we collect like a
bunch and then we, and then, you know, we approach the artists and we say, hey,
we want to work out a print deal and we compile them into like a volume of like,
I don't know, the 50, the 50 best or something.
And we sell like volume, volume one, the collect, the collected
perfect comic party Kickstarter or something.
But that would be, you know, there's a, we'd have to, we have to make it a
success first before we worry about, worry about that.
Yeah, they're going to have to create some sort of guidelines because with,
um, I mean, with any, with any publisher, they have guidelines of what exactly
they're like looking for, how many pages or whatnot, you know?
Um, I mean, my guidelines, I don't have any, how like hard rules about like page,
page page, page length, I would say probably not more than like 20 ish pages.
And if it's longer than that, we could always just divide it into chapters.
Yeah, I think that's sensible.
I don't actually know how big a normal shonen jump is, because I've never seen one.
They, they have how many different things every week.
I have no idea.
Is it like a huge tone?
Yeah, I think it's like the one piece chapter is like 20 pages by itself.
And then there's like a bunch of other things.
I think it's maybe like, like a hundred or 200 pages is like the weekly.
Dang, the week, every week.
How do you read that?
How do you read all that?
Maybe not.
Well, I mean, it's because they got a whole, they got tons of different
authors in there.
They're all sitting in their shit.
They're on the bullet train sitting down, reading that shit.
Because they're on a first moving vehicle.
They also read.
Well, because on the fast moving vehicle, time dilates.
And so like fewer pages, you can read them and it takes longer to read them.
They have a lot of opportunities to be some, some have a lot of like certain
amount of free time and specific moments to be read, you know.
What was I saying?
Do you do the.
Yeah, I would I would like to print, I would like to print a
collected volume one day.
That's my like, that's how I'll know that the project was like a runaway
a runaway smash hit success.
I was shit.
Maybe I was done.
Maybe I don't have anything else to say.
OK, I got you.
Maybe maybe the surveys.
Maybe the surveys are not super necessary.
I would I will be making a channel in the PCP discord that's specifically
for like perfect comic party, like comic discussion and feedback and stuff.
I would like to accept feedback.
And in fact, Biscopades needs feedback.
Biscopades is going to end with like a like a call to like, hey, send,
send suggestions for the next chapter.
I think I'll take suggestions for like reader, reader commands in like batches.
So like at the end of a chapter, it's like submit as many suggestions
for things to happen in the next one as you want.
And I'll like go through them and I'll just pick ones that I like and I'll
and I'll put them together into the next chapter.
I think that's my plan.
And, you know, I guess we could accept those via email.
We could also just make that like, yes, suggest we got to do the Google forums thing.
Yes, the Google.
Yes, the Google forums thing for feedback.
There's a few little things that I've just been like, I need to focus on
something and the perfect comic party just hasn't been drawing me in.
I don't know.
Do you mean just like a few pages like the putting together the patron thank you page?
Oh, yeah, I just wanted to focus on Clarissa because it was easier to think about.
I think once once the once you finish the thing and we can get together
and be like, yeah, like run through like how it's going to look and all that.
When you say Google forums, you mean like for for like read or for submissions?
Oh, yeah, feedback.
I mean, we could do all sorts of things with Google forums.
I think I think Biscopades like like reader commands.
I think, yeah, Google forums would be a good way to to do those just to have it all in one place.
So I don't have to check my email and check the discord and check Twitter
and check all these things.
You can't have it where like you're posting Biscopades on a website
and then people in the comments are leaving feedback there.
No. So I didn't have a.
I specifically did not want a like comment section.
When I was building my website, my old website,
everyone told me like, you got to have a comment section.
You've got to have a comment and I was like, and I was like, absolutely not.
I do not want a comment section because I'm not popular enough.
Most pages will have no comments and it will just be embarrassing.
So I just don't want it.
Just throw the whole fucking concept out.
I mean, that that's obviously true.
But I was that's even popular comic, even popular comics are like that.
Like most pages just have zero comments.
Yeah, yeah, like people don't think to use that.
But also I don't like the idea of thinking you're reading a comic.
And then, oh, I wonder what people thought about this and scrolling down.
Yeah, I feel like that breaks up the flow of reading the actual thing.
So I don't want any distractions.
My site is you read the comic and then you get out of there.
Yes, reading a comic is not the place for like page by page fucking
peanut gallery commentary.
That's what I don't.
It's another thing I don't like about Topastic and and the line.
Oh, yeah, I should put things on Topastic though.
I maybe I need to advertise through permeants.
I'm a little bit.
I'm a little concerned about line webtoons, like terms of service.
Line webtoons, terms of service seems to kind of imply that like by posting
your stuff online, webtoon, like they are allowed to like print your stuff.
Like it becomes their content, print.
Sorry, that was the impression I got.
Was it is it one of the one of those lines where it's like you like they have
the right to reproduce the work?
Um, because I think that a lot of sites have that where it basically
just means we're allowed to show this on a web page.
We're allowed to host it on a web page that people can see.
You you grant you grant us with respect to user posting.
You grant us a non exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty
fleet free, worldwide, transferable, licensable license to access, use,
host, cash, store, reproduce, transmit, display, publish, and distribute
your user, user posting.
Yeah, I do not like that verbiage at all.
Every, every image hosting site has that.
It basically means, I mean, people freaked out when DeviantArt, when
somebody looked at the DeviantArt terms of service and they had that in there.
DeviantArt's word for other reasons for the AI stuff.
But like that specifically just means that when somebody loads a page,
DeviantArt, you've given DeviantArt the permission to display the
permission to display the image so that it works.
And they have to give it all those words so that it makes sense
because like worldwide means accessing from any place that you can access the
site. I appreciate that.
But like taken, taken literally, it seems like it gives them like if they wanted
to, they could like print your stuff in a book and sell it.
That's what they say print, though.
They say, no, they don't say print.
Because that's the only thing.
It looks like I'm pretty sure.
Reproduce, transmit, display, publish, and distribute.
Reproduce, but like online.
Well, it doesn't, it doesn't.
I know it doesn't specify, but like I don't think anything of that
nature has ever happened.
And like every site has that sort of clause.
I thought that when you were with user hosted, submitted content.
Well, the, well, the Tappas one.
Well, the, the Tappas one specifically said that they won't do the things
that I'm worried about.
So maybe, maybe you're right.
And maybe that's just, they all have it.
And maybe Tappas was just being extracurricular.
I think maybe there was a lot, a lot of picking wire, um, legal,
legal, like explanation about what that more actually means or what that stipulation
something to look into, I guess.
It, I mean, it might be a matter of precedent where like if they ever did try
to like take a bunch of like user submitted stuff and like print it, there
would be a lawsuit and then probably some legal precedent would be established.
It's like, no, you can't do that.
Uh, and it might not be in like the letter of the, the contract or whatever.
You're probably right.
Yeah.
Tumblr has that as well.
Tump people freaked out on Tumblr and they saw that and they're like, oh my God,
they're going to steal our art.
Every girl, everybody take your art off of Tumblr.
And it's like it doesn't, nothing happened.
That's how that works.
Stupid.
Okay.
But it sounds, but it sounds like what I said it sounds like, but okay.
All right.
No, but no, but like the thing about that though is that society has degraded so much
that it could be true.
Yeah.
It could have been true.
And it would have been just like, just like, uh, it was so believable.
The fact that I thought it was.
Yes.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Uh, sorry.
What is a, what is the perfect part of it going to be?
Is it going to be like a PDF you could download?
Yeah.
Think, we're thinking PDF.
Just cause thinking a PDF is easy to put it all together.
Squish it into a file and you just download the file.
Maybe we could make it readable online as well in some form.
Interesting.
I mean, I think if you drag a PDF on into your browser, you can read it online.
Yeah.
You don't need a website to do that.
If it's a PDF, you can just look through it like that.
I am.
Right.
I always thought it was kind of funny when I see people on like,
like certain like Twitter, like artists, people that make like indie comics talk about like,
oh, what we need is like an American shonen jump.
Yeah.
We need a magazine with like everyone's comics in there.
And I'm thinking.
That's the BCP.
It's called Marvel.
It's called, it's called the perfect one.
Well, let's see.
Well, the thing in my head, I'm thinking like,
well, because they talk of the fact that they talk about like an actual magazine makes me think,
I think you're working backwards because no one really reads magazines.
Like they still make them, but they're very expensive and they're only made for a specific
group of much older audience who still like buy them and whatnot.
Right.
So to do a magazine is kind of like probably like working backwards.
There are people out there trying to do their own like American shonen jump and they all seem
to be doing just fine.
That being said, I think that I don't know.
I think there isn't much about precedent for that kind of stuff here.
I think what one of these like American shonen jump types need to do is that
they probably just need to have like an anime or like a cartoon based on one of their comics.
And then they can get more eyes on them, you know, once, once that because what,
what usually like having a cartoon is like, oh, the formula works guys.
You know, we got a cartoon just like the Japanese, right?
But who knows?
Oh, I don't know.
Like the industry pipeline is different over here.
Yeah, it's, you know, I get the appeal.
I mean, obviously if you have a comic and it's with a bunch of other comics and they're all in
one place, then every reader of every comic will see everyone else's comic and it's like,
oh, it's like collaboration.
It's like YouTube.
How do you prepare my video?
And then you cross pollinate the audiences.
But like, I don't know, people don't read stuff like that online.
The like the perfect comic party is not trying to set out to be shonen jump.
It's just like, wouldn't it be cool?
Wouldn't it be like a nice thing?
Like I like the aesthetic of having a little publication, having a little
little like a little thing, maybe printing it out.
I think I don't know if I'd ever go down the route of having some sort of like collective
magazine with everyone's comics.
I wonder how I wouldn't have like stuff like shonen jump originally started.
If it was the same thing where it was like a handful of guys,
somewhere where they could post their comics.
Actually, you know what?
That is how those start.
Never mind.
I remember.
Maybe it was a newspaper and it was like the funny.
And it's like, what if we had a newspaper with just the funny isn't it?
And it was the funny is the comments.
It was kind of something like that.
I remember I'm reminded of there's one autobiography I read from a manga co who started
a specific genre of manga.
And he was talking about how him and his brother would be friends with a bunch of other people
who were drawn.
They they just would start their own magazine.
And it was pretty easy to like print and like redistribute distributed like back in the day,
which would have been maybe the 60s.
And he was talking about how they would have to do something like a reader contest.
Because that's one of those things that would like entice people like,
oh, if you submit this to us, you'll get like a free so and so, you know,
to kind of like get more engagement out of your readers, you know.
I mean, doing that now, I don't I don't know.
I haven't heard of any like successful someone like doing it very successful.
I mean, what would success even look like?
You know, it would look like you buy the thing and it's like,
oh, Scott Pilgrim and Homestuck in the same place.
Oh, God, that sounds like a nightmare.
But they could they could they could they could cross over like, oh, my God, John Egbert.
What are you doing in my comment?
I'm thinking about like, because it's funny how the more I learned about like,
how indeed creative people are doing, the more I realized like,
I'm literally doing the same thing they're doing.
It's just that they're more popular than me.
There was this one guy who made a post on Instagram talking about how his comic is like
published through Fantagraphics, which is one of the bigger publishers, right?
But the fact is that like Fantagraphics only sold like four copies of his comic last year.
Like only people only four people bought copies of it, which is crazy because it's like,
this is supposed to be Fantagraphics.
It's supposed to be one of the bigger publishers.
But I guess they're not like super interested in advertising this guy or they do the kind
of thing where they expect since like every like artists nowadays is like a pseudo influencer.
They expect you to do the majority of the marketing for them and they don't have to spend money,
you know, of course, Fantagraphic does market certain comics, but they only market their most
popular stuff or stuff that like, because Fantagraphic does do specific like they translate
like specific older manga, they republish very old like Mickey Mouse comics.
That's like another thing they do, you know, and sure they do publish like the indie stuff,
but it seems like they only like push the indie stuff when it's someone like popular or someone
who like, you know, already like made a big name for themselves somehow, you know.
And when this guy was talking about like his situation of like what he's going through and
how like, oh, he they only sold four copies for a big publisher.
I'm thinking like, well, maybe I'm kind of doing the right thing in a way because with
how I'm just like doing the pre-orders and and it's the self publishing that way.
I've heard I've heard like professionals say like if they were starting out now, like people
like I've heard people say like I get if they get asked like, how do I break into the publishing
industry? How do I get a publisher? And they just like don't like if I if I were starting out now,
I would just do self publishing. I would self publish everything I would I wouldn't worry about
publisher. But I just want someone to do the work for me. I want someone to do the hard part
for me. I don't want to do marketing. That's that's kind of like the annoying thing. I mean,
I to be honest, I really don't really do marketing to be honest, which is what the funny.
I know that's a funny thing for me to say come especially coming from me, right? What the fuck?
But like it's it's it's it's tough out there. I remember I'm not out there. Thank you.
Last year I was talking to I talked to a small like I talked to a couple of small publishers
and it's funny how they're just kind of already doing the thing I'm doing and I'm wondering
like why am I even approaching these guys? One guy I talked to saying like, yeah, I um,
yeah, like I told them about like one time I did pre orders for for villain verse.
I made like around $2,000. And this guy saying like, damn, we never made that amount of money
ever in our publisher. Right. There you go. And another time I was asking because I went around
I was asking for smaller publishers and saying like, Hey, do you guys um,
do you guys help me like get this specific kind of printing? And they told me like,
oh, we probably can't do that. But you should go to this printer. And the one they recommended
was the one I already used for everything else. And they told me that they use that printer. And
I'm like, Oh, why do I even need to use your guys? Like what I it's it's it's interesting because
it's like they kind of have a name locally. So I guess that's like the benefit. But it's like,
what's the point, you know, I just got the box from the printer with the copies of the rad con
dojin. The people that the people that the cut the few people that purchased a print copy from me,
I will be sending those. Yes, I found it on my doorstep yesterday. I think I ordered like 30 copies
and I think I sold like less than half of that many, including like the people that I'm just
giving free ones to because they wrote the script and drew and drew the comments. So I've got like
a bunch left. Hey, everyone, st comics.com slash store.html buy buy one of these, please get it
with the combo combo with wrote to rad con. It's the rad combo. But I already have wrote to read
the buy to please. It's fine.
This is why you should never be a distributor. It's okay. You'll have you'll have boxes and boxes
of stuff. You know what's purchased. Honestly, that's why I do pre orders. I hate the idea of
having a shillard of boxes of comics that no one's buying. I have like, oh, that makes sense.
That's smart. Yeah, I didn't even think about it. Yeah, I mean, I like you know how many people
are going to buy it. So you get exactly that amount. You know, what's my you know, what's my
dream position? Like if I had to choose where I would want my life to be is so and my big example
for this is the mega 64 podcast, they do this kind of interesting thing that's a pretty smart on
their side where like, when an episode of their podcast drops, they say on that episode, hey,
and you only get the news through the episode, it's like, hey, we're going to have a 42 hour
special on this shirt starting from when this episode drops. So you should get it now. Right.
And it's like, damn, imagine like having that big of a podcast where you could say like, hey,
we're having you could do a pre order, like the podcast episode is the announcement for the
pre order, like, hey, like, you know, you, you get the pre order for this and it's like limited so
and so at that time, right. And that kind of like, you know, incentivize people to like go buy it in
that moment, like once that episode drops, right. And that's, that's kind of like where I I think
that's what position I would like to be. And it won't even be like, I think if I if I get like,
because I do have like a local San Diego comic collective, that are pretty cool people and I
really love the people there. I would love to get to a point where that that collected on part of
if I'm not even like, I guess our own podcast or something like that, where we just announced
the stuff, you just pre order like right away, like on the podcast itself, you know,
that that's kind of like where I want to go with all this, to be honest.
Then marking which take care of itself. Yep. Yeah, exactly. It's got to get clout. You just
got to get clout. You got to get clout. What I'm thinking of doing is I make Clarissa or in the
process of making Clarissa, I get back into making videos and I make like banger videos that everyone
loves. And then I can say go from YouTube, this massive website, to my tiny little Amazon thing,
buy my comic or read it even. And they'll all be mine.
Tee hee, I'll make hypocrite videos for money. Who would have thought of such a thing?
That's amazing. Were you were you're not making it for money before?
No, I was making it because I love making videos. I thought it was so cool. I thought it'd be so
famous, famous like just like the the just like the guy with the glasses just like Doug Walker.
It's like Jon Tron. Yeah. I mean, unironically, that's why I started. Actually, there was a part
of me was like, oh, you can make money on YouTube. So it was also for money. But mostly because I
wanted to be like one of the cool gamers on the website. I think I could have done it if I didn't
hate it. If I didn't get burnt out. That's so true. I mean, what everyone needs like their own
little cash cow, like their own little thing of above that people love, they're like, oh, I love
this, I'll buy it. You know, everyone needs their own little Smash Bros, which is like tough. Yeah.
In the future, everyone will have their own little Smash Bros.
Do you guys watch Little Joel? Yeah, most of yeah, I often I haven't seen them all.
But Little Joel is the true successor to Digi After Dark.
Yeah, only good. But Little Joel made a video about like how he made a popular video.
And people make art that is your passion about it. It's like, nah, just make art is popular. So
you get to feel good about it and you get the money and it's great. I'm like, you know what,
I need more of that, that energy in my life. Yeah. Because I have spent my entire twenties
being like, no, I'm an artist. I have to do things I'm passionate about. Yeah. Look where I am now.
Well, I'm not nowhere on the Procrastinators podcast. I'm on the Procrastinators podcast.
I need to I need to get big and popular enough where like people don't like because unsolicited
advice, kind of rude, kind of cringe, right? But if you're popular enough, you give that
unsolicited advice and they'll be sucking your dick. Oh my god. They'll lap it up.
I learned more from this guy's from this guy's roast of me than I did in my entire college
career that I spent $500,000 to get. Ben, would you rather have $1 million or a dinner with
cheesy Manfredo? That dinner will pay will pay for itself every day of the rest of my life
with what I learned from it. Exactly. Because they'll tell you like what to do and my advice
would be kind of like, ah, is there anything? Is there something popular that you really like
right now? I just do your version of that. That's it. That's my advice. Yeah. So would you rather
have a billion dollars or a fortune cookie written by Oscar Wilde? I'll be honest. Something.
With that little Joel, he's talking about like he did the he did that series of three sort of
like kind of artsy like essays, the ones about like Godzilla and like global warming. Yeah.
And those were okay. I didn't hate them. I didn't really love them either. They were they were good.
Yeah. They're more heady than and then and the one you made more recently was more poppy and like
yeah clickable. I didn't like that. I didn't like the new one. I thought I thought the new one was
bad. It's boring. It's like trigger you one. Yeah. I feel like he's literally made the same video
before. It's terrible. So I feel I get I get that like yeah, his like artsy one didn't wasn't a huge
hit. And like, you know, that's fine. I don't I don't like that the lesson he took away from it
is just make the same crap over and over. Like I know he's I know he's just joshin. I know he's
kind of just joshin. He's kind of just joshin. I think it's it's just you can get like stuck
trying to go for only artistic masterpieces when it doesn't actually take that much out of you to
just throw a little crowd pleaser out there so often to keep yourself going and to make yourself
feel accomplished. Yeah. Nothing wrong with that. Nothing wrong with that. Nothing wrong with that.
Yeah. Well, you know, that's but that's not how the coolest people ever constantly were making
bangers and they were never doing anything that sucked. I feel a little bit stupid because it's
been so many months. It's been like five months since the Mega Man lecture. But like that was
kind of my plan with get back into doing lectures. Like that's that's the crowd pleaser.
And then I have not followed up lectures and then be like, oh, this lecture was sponsored by
Biska Page. Biska Page. They're great. Yeah. They're Biska Page. They're great. Exactly.
Okay. And you know what's that? I got I got to get going. Okay. Cheesy eggs is out here. All right.
Okay. Yeah, I appreciate you guys have no sweat. Now people are going to complain that Cheesy made
the episode longer. I was the one complaining the most. So yeah, I won't complain again. I'll find
other things to complain about. All right. Good. All right. Good. Have a good day. Talk to you guys
later. Later. I was going to say, yeah, the me deciding deciding to do more lectures and the
Mega Man lecture in particular was me being like, I should just do the things people like.
I should just make the things that people liked and that were successful.
And then I did it once and I was like, well, I did it. No need to continue doing that.
But I should and I really, you know, I mean, you've been working on the battle network, haven't
you? Yeah. Yeah. That wasn't the next lecture, but that's a lecture. So you're still doing a
lecture. That is work on it on a future lecture that I am doing. That's true. You know, I've been,
I've been putting off really getting to work on the net on the next lecture because
whenever it's time to work, I'm like, well, I got to work on the I got to work on Biska Page.
Got to work on, you know, get the perfect comic party. So that's. Yeah. Yeah. But, you know,
soon as the first issues out, I'll be like, okay, time to step back and the next the next thing on
my to do list after get the perfect comic party sort of up and running to to whatever extent,
then the next thing is, all right, let's let's do it. Let's do the next lecture.
I got freaking Etsy ghosted me. I ordered some stuff from Etsy for like the video for the
slime and punishment video. And it just didn't come. I paid like $45 for some fabric. And it
just didn't come. And I guess I'm going to have to complain about it. Was it was it sent but not
tracked or something? Yes, it was it said it was sent, but it was it's not they didn't have tracking
on it. And it said it was supposed to arrive by like three days ago. So we're past the time
when like, I should be complaining. But I haven't done it. It's the most annoying, isn't it? When
it's not tracked, so it could arrive as soon as you like buy another one. Yeah. It could just be
running. You don't know that it's going to. So it's like, you can't afford to wait, wait around. So
you got to kind of buy the next one. Yeah. And then it arrives anyway. And it's like, I'm not
buying. I'm not buying another one. I'm going to I'm going to complain until they refund me
because this is bullshit. At least at least it's for the slime and punishment thing, which it turns
out I didn't need that soon because I have wait, no, wait, no, before, no, before I do the next
lecture, I have to do the slime and punishment. I have to do the slime and punishment. Never mind.
I take it back. I take back the order I said. Well, why do you have to do the slime and punishment?
Because I just need I just I just need to do it. I just need I just needs to be done.
The book, the Kickstarter just needs it should have done this Kickstarter like three years ago.
Well, and I just had to start it. And then when it's running, I can be working on the lecture
while the Kickstarter is running. I don't have to spend the entire month focused on it. So that's
that's the actual order. PCP, Perfect Comic Party, then that done. OK, make a video and launch the
slime and punishment Kickstarter. OK, and then while that's running, work on the next lecture.
OK, too many things, too many freaking things on my to do list. Irons in the fire.
I yeah, irons in that. Yeah, feels better to look at them as irons in the fire.
Then then items on an on a on a list of things that never seems to get any shorter.
It never will. That's the annoying truth is that the list I've been keeping track of a thing,
like a list of things I got to get done. And it never really goes away. There's just a few
things that stay on there for so long, because it's like, that's hard. And that's like, I don't know
how to start that thing. And it's like tiny little bits, little updates to the site, like, oh,
there's a glitch there. I should go into the code and figure out what's what's not correct.
And now I got to do my taxes. I got my tax letter as well. But it said, like, you've got until
January 2024 to pay last year's taxes. So I guess I've already done my taxes in January.
I guess Americans have them in April or for the previous year's taxes are due in April of the
next year. Yeah. Yeah, I always have my tax thing like around Christmas, like, oh,
shit, I should have done my taxes before the Christmas holidays. Now I got to do them during
January. It doesn't really take that long. But it doesn't really take that long. Like, I have all
my I have all my open up all of my yeah, all the things. The thing that takes long is going back
through all my expenses and trying to be like that counts as a business expense that counts as a
business expense. Yeah. And tallying all that all that stuff up. Oh, yeah, you got to make you
got to make YouTube videos of all the things you buy, just hold them up to the camera. So
there's YouTube contents part of my brands part of my thing. It's just I got to go back
through my bank statements. And every time I see an item, if I like, was that was that for a video?
Was that for a comic? Was that for some other potential future money making endeavor? Oh,
all my all my ingredients for all my gummies. Well, I intend to. Yeah, I just ate those. But you
know, I intend to sell them at some point in the future. So that's a business expense. That's
like research and development expense. Ooh, I just got I just got a I just got a gallon jug
of blackstrap molasses. I'm going to try I think after this is going to try chugging that I'm good.
I'm going to I'm going to try I'm going to try licorice again, and I'm going to try replacing
I'm going to try replacing a priori replace the liquid sugar, a priori replace the invert sugar
with blackstrap molasses and just see what happens. Are you going to invert the molasses?
I think it's probably already inverted or it's some other kind of sugar. I don't know.
Yes, I don't know anything about all that. It's it's very food. It's very mysterious.
Cornstarch. It's very mysterious. Listen, when you cook down sugar, starch,
there is corn oil, corn sugar, corn syrup, syrup, high fructose corn syrup.
I use the non high fructose kind. All right, when you cook down sugar, you cook it,
it gets this first it becomes the softball, then it becomes the firm ball, then it becomes hardball,
then it becomes crackling out brand. Wait, no, it's like a hard cube.
The soft the softball stage. No, no, no. Here we go. Here we go. Softball,
firm ball, hardball, soft crack and hard crack. There you go. So that's that's the goal is to get
that hard crack. I'm all about that hard crack. Speaking of crack, I bought on eBay the bionicles.
You know the bionicles? You ever heard of them? Yeah. I love them and I have been missing them
for decades or whatever. I never had. I didn't realize. I didn't realize that the original six
were like cheap and like not a problem. I got the whole set. Yeah, they were a very popular
toy. So I'm not surprised they're available. Yeah, I thought like, oh, bionicle collectors,
this probably like it's and it's an old thing. So it's like I assumed it would go up in price
like a video game cartridge would. No, no, no. You just I just have them now and they're back.
They've been gone for so long. They've been gone for so long. My product my prodigal sons have
returned. There's Metsunui. There's Shiranui. No, no, Shiranui is from Okami. There's Uigui.
There's Lewa, Topeka. I've only learned these by looking at the wiki because I forgot what
their names were. Sean in Topanga. There's Gali, there's Pohatu, Onu, Onganguga. This is racist.
This is racist. It's a little bit racist. A little bit racist. But I love them. They're little masks
and the fact that their skull has the like see-through plastic. So if you shine a light behind
it or if the sun's behind it, blasts through so they've got like green or red like glowing eyes.
Hang on. They're the coolest. I love them. I'm going to carefully examine.
Wait, they have a skull? Yeah, like did you never have a bionicle?
No, never. I thought they had like a mask. Yeah, the mask that attaches like in the mouth. The
mouth is like a like a you could put a Lego stud in there. I don't think a Lego stud would
actually fit, but like imagine that. And the mask is a clips onto their mouth and their head is like
a gray like skull sort of thing. Look at what I found. The gray skull is like their brain,
which is like a crystal of a clear plastic, colored plastic. Mine too. Light shines through it
and they've got different eye colors and it's looks so cool. I found this was the second like
like eBay result when I searched for bionicle. Well, don't search for such things. I searched
for bionicle and this is what I found. It's your search history. There's a lot of they know
what you've been looking at pornography on eBay. I'm so I'm so horny. I'm going to log on to eBay
and buy some ironic sculptures just to just to rub out a quick one. Is that Jasmine from the
Disney's Aladdin? Hang on. Bionicle. No mask. Show me. Show me the mask was.
Oh, ew. Yeah, they're kind of like gross weirdos. They're kind of gross weirdos,
but their masks make them so cool instantly. It's amazing. Like you take the mask off and it's like,
oh, this guy is fucked. Oh, then you put the mask on. You put the mask on and it's like,
and that's cool. I remember there was these bionicles and then I was looking into this because
I was trying to figure out when I fell off the bionicle bandwagon and they had different like
every year it was like in 2001 or 2000 they released and every year they would be like a new
line of bionicles. The second year was these little round guys, these little circular like snakemen
and they would be also of the like six genders, six elements. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cool. And they had like an action figure thing where you pulled a little piece of Lego at the
back of their neck and their head would jump forward like a snake and then they could roll
into a ball and like roll around like Samus Aran from Metroid. I watched like a video explaining
like the history of bionicles not that long ago. Not like the in-world lore, but like the
production and like the iterations that Lego went through of like releasing a bunch of themed
action figures that were elemental. Yeah. Of which there were several different ones and
bionicle was merely one and was the most well known and successful.
Very strange. A lot of people keep. One of the most popular requests I get for what's your next
lecture going to be is on bionicle lore, which I guess there's lore there. I say that it sounds
terrible, but I don't know. Maybe it's funny. Maybe it's cool. I mean, there's enough of it
that you could have like good stuff. I'm pretty sure the comics, I've seen parts of a comic before
that came with like one of the Lego figures is like the comic looks good. It's like genuinely
cool looking. I don't know if the story is good, but like. I mean, like what's there like there's
like an animated series. There's a toy series. There's a toy set. There's a film. There's a
video games. The whole thing. That's not that much lore. I don't think it'd be that hard to
explain, right? Like it's not Mega Man where there's like 45 different video games. Oh, no, no, not
at all. I don't even know if it would be that hard. Maybe I should just do it. Maybe I should just do it.
Maybe I should. Wait a minute. Maybe I should just make a video that would be popular and
that people want to see. Oh my goodness. What the fuck? No, but my, no, but my art. Oh, my artistic
purity, the purity of my artistic intention, demand that I make my next lecture about a
fucking battle network. It's just so artistically pure. It's like in the wake of,
um, remember, remember, uh, you know, Nate had the, um, the freaking, uh, the weaponized
thickness. I don't know if I mentioned this in the, in the vlog that he made immediately
following the viral success of weaponized thickness when that video got 2 million views.
He says like, I could make t-shirts of it. People have asked me for weaponized thickness
t-shirts and I could do them and they would sell and it would make me money, but I won't do it.
I can't do it because I'm just a slave to, but it's like my pure, it's like not my pure artistic
vision. Uh, yeah. He's like, I can't, it's too commercial. Like it's too, it's too crass. He
doesn't say it in this many words. I'm paraphrasing, but basically he's like, it's too crass and
commercial and I just don't want to do it. I'm an artist. I'm not some kind of, I'm not some kind of
merch hawker. I'll never make t-shirts. Right. The nickel, the nickel. Uh, it's just weird. It's
just weird. Like why, why not just make a shirt? Why not just make a shirt? Maybe it's just annoying,
but I feel like you could easily have made a weaponized thickness thing.
Yeah. I mean, he said so. He said people, he said, he said people are asking for it.
Yes. Short-card gothic, of course. He said, he said people are asking for one. He knew they would
sell, but he won't do it because it's not art. I don't know. Before we end this section, I just want
to post the third generation of these guys. So they were like villain bionicles and they had
staves and these, I remember having one of these and that's, I think was 2003 and 2004.
I think 2004 onwards was when they just did the original six, but they had different masks
and I felt like the masks weren't as good. And so I was, I fell off. I was like, nah.
But that's when apparently, 2004 onwards is apparently where it got really big and like
there was so much stuff, those video games and all that in the movie. And I'm like,
by that point, I was gone. I was out of it. I was out of the game.
Graduated. Graduated as they say in the VTuber space. Yeah. They won't let me back.
I got a pee. You know what I mean? You know what, me too.
Hey, hello.
Sorry, I was eating a bacon sandwich. It was very yummy. That was fast.
It was only a small sandwich. It really wolfed it. I wolfed it. I wanted to get back to the show.
So much. Do you want to talk about One Piece?
New One Piece chapter? Yeah, I think so. Okay. Okay. Well, guess what?
What? There's a new One Piece chapter and it's called Chapter 1080, The Hero of Legend.
And we see there's a bunch of new fruits. 1080p.
Let's see. Okay. So it's my vague recollections. There's a bunch of the Blackbeard pirates have
a bunch of new fruits. One of their guys is an island man, and he just is the island that they're
on. That's pretty wacky. Pizarro. I don't remember if these fruits, they already had them.
Some of these I don't remember. I'm not sure if they had them already. I know the Hero did not
have the invisible fruit. They got that from the Moria's subordinate. Who's that guy? Absalom.
I remember him getting it from Absalom. Blackbeard using his, I forget, what even happened?
This is the part where all the people who read One Piece and know it are pissing themselves with
rage that we don't already know the things we're thinking about. Here's the ones. I think,
I don't remember. I've never seen an island island fruit before. I've never seen the glug glug
fruit before. I've never seen the huge, huge fruit before. Yeah, these are reveals, I guess,
of their fruits. These are reveals. I don't know if we got them recently. I mean,
San Juan Wolf is already huge. What does it mean that he has eaten the huge, huge fruit?
Well, if you look at him in comparison to other giants, he is far larger than any giant ever in
history. And so people are like, why is he so big? And it's because he's a giant that ate
a devil fruit that also makes you big. So he's just bigger than the average giant.
Do you think he had already eaten it before? Oh, yeah. I think that's like he walks along
the ocean floor and it makes him tired because he's a devil fruit user.
Hmm. Yeah, okay. That might, yeah. I guess I believe that.
Pizarro being an island fruit, it sort of feels very similar to that guy in the
Indress Rosa who has the something something turns into a mountain or stone or like the
like terrain terrain fruit or something like that. Something of that nature. So I guess this is just
the same thing, but bigger. Yeah.
Everyone's so fucking big. You just, I guess he can do it with a whole island,
but he can only do it with natural terrain. Well, no, no, no, because he becomes,
he becomes the wooden floorboards and he becomes like the brick wall.
Yeah, it's a pretty wacky because he's if he's an island, surely he feels the
the edge of the ocean lapping at his himself. Surely that makes him weaker
if he can constantly be in contact with the ocean. Yeah, an island, wait, an island is in
the ocean. What the fuck? Yeah, so that's pretty fucked up. Oh, and then this lady with the whip
whip fruit. Yes, I love all of the sword members. I don't really know what she's doing with her whip.
Oh, okay. She's just, she's whipping a building and making it move? Yeah, she's got a devil fruit
that makes inanimate objects react to her, what do you call it, like dominatrix whipping.
It's like move back boy, be a good boy and move and the building does as she's told, as it's told.
It's very interesting, fascinating. So yeah, we're on Pirate Island is Blackbeard's land
or is territory and we've got the Blackbeard Pirates just fucking around and Kobe, who we knew
was with. It's called Fulaled. Pirate Island Fulaled is what my translation says. I'm reading
the Viz translation. Ah, Hachinossu. Yeah, so yeah, Fulaled probably cooler and whatever that means.
Well, maybe it literally is that. That's localization, baby. Yes. So yeah, there's the cross guild,
Buggy's thing. I was going to say the bounty on Kobe, that's from Buggy's crew, right? Yeah,
Buggy's organization. The cross guild. Because I would assume it is a guild where you don't cross
them, I don't know. Very honestly, very cool to see bounties out on marines. I just think that's
really fun. Yeah, I like that aspect of Buggy's progression. He's always getting people to fight
for him and what better way to get people to fight the marines than to put bounties on their heads
and he's got so much power and wealth that he can afford that. It's really funny.
It's pretty awesome and they have a star rating. Apparently one star is about,
one star is one treasure chest, which is worth about a million berries.
So why not just average in millions? It is very abusing that they
pirate treasure chests of booty. Right, right.
Yeah, so Blackbeard, we saw Blackbeard's ship heading in the direction of egg land.
Yes. And so I was hypothesizing that Kobe-
I thought we saw him. No, no, I guess we didn't see him. We just saw his flag.
The things we've seen Blackbeard going on about recently are Blackbeard fighting Law
and I presume that because Kid was defeated by Shanks, Law was probably defeated by Blackbeard
and then Blackbeard is on his way after that to Luffy at, what's it called? Is it New Egg?
What's it called? Egghead. Egghead. He's on his way to Egghead.
New Egg is that website you can buy computer parts for?
That's right, yes. I mean, it's basically the same. Sure.
You can get computer parts at Vegapunks Island.
And so this, I think, takes place before that because we knew Kobe was captured by Blackbeard.
I assumed he was on the ship and we might see him at Egghead and if he's escaping now,
which I assume is before. But then, I don't know, what do you think could happen here?
Because Kobe is trying to escape. He's getting all of these other people,
these prisoners escaping is like he's being a hero. And then the Blackbeard pirates are just
fucking around and they think, haha, whatever, stupid Kobe, no chance. But then Kobe's friends,
Kobe's comrades, Nakama, they're coming in and they've really got some cool powers
and they're showing up and they're being all epic.
These aren't just regular cops. These are renegade cops that are above the law.
They're taking the law into their own hands. Taking the law into their own hands. They got a
license to kill. They're going to turn in their gun and their badge.
Oh, I really like Hibari. She's using, she's the one with the rifle.
She was using the, she was the Vegapunk flower, flower shot.
Yeah, the flower shot. That's cool. Also, I really like her weird fucking clown tights and like army
shoe combo. Yeah, she's cute. Yeah, the stripe, I like the stripe tights. Very cute. Oh, it's on one
leg. Oh yes, it's ripped off at one leg. That's fun. And she's like, haha, it's not like I like
you or anything, Kobe. Kobe's getting all of these ladies. He's surrounded by them. It's great.
Have we seen this clay man with the Prince of Groose? He looks kind of familiar.
I don't think we've seen any of these people before. I think they're all
like new, except, well, obviously, except for Garp. I don't think there was,
there was a bit earlier, Tashiki's here as well, where there was, and Helm Epo.
Helm Epo, everybody's favorite. Helm Epo alongside some other girl who was crying
that Kobe's been stolen by Blackbeard and saying, Garp, we gotta go save him.
I forget. I don't think, well, she's probably in a panel here, but not prominently featured.
She's not one of these new people. Just some steak. Yeah. Hey, why is Alkegi here?
Alkegi, if you remember, fought against Akainu and created Punk Hazard at the end
after the Marenford thing, and it was over a disagreement about the Marines and how things
should be run, and so they fought about it, and Alkegi left, and then he joined Blackbeard.
He joined Blackbeard? Yeah, he joined Blackbeard after that, and he's like,
I forgot that. Yeah, he's been part of Blackbeard's crew or an ally. I'm assuming he's part of the
crew. I don't really know what his deal is because he doesn't seem like the sort of guy who would
just join to be part of the bad guys. I don't think he wants to kill people. Maybe Blackbeard
has more of a plan than we're led to believe. That's very strange to me that Alkegi would
join Blackbeard. I feel like Alkegi's joining Blackbeard not because he agrees with Blackbeard,
but because it's advantageous to whatever ends Alkegi has. He must be doing something.
Because I like Alkegi, he seems like an upstanding fellow, and Blackbeard seems like a bit of a
scoundrel and not quite the same level of, I don't know. Blackbeard's just out for himself,
so I don't get what's the appeal of working with him for someone like Alkegi.
Being on a powerful pirate crew to insulate him from the Marines or something?
Yeah, I mean, yeah. Or like influencing him from the inside?
Maybe Alkegi just wants to join the witting side.
Could be something like that, I don't know. I feel like the fact that he let Nico Robin go
all those years ago means that he doesn't actually believe the Marines are the good guys, fully.
Yeah, definitely, definitely. Okay, yeah, well I forgot. I was shocked to see him here,
but I guess that explains it. We unfortunately do not get to see what the glug glug fruit does.
Yeah, it just makes bubbles like Glowbox and Rayman 3.
Rayman 3! No, no, no. That's the huge... That's San Juan Wolf making the bubbles,
making the snot bubbles. No, it's Vasco shot, isn't it?
Well, no, Vasco shot is riding a bubble, but the bubbles are just coming out of the San Juan
Wolf's nose or whatever. I don't think that's a fruit power. I think that guy, I think he's just
a snotty boy. Vasco, what you doing? He's gonna drink that snot later and it's gonna give him
so much power. So he's called a booze man, heavy drinker, he ate the glug glug fruit.
And he's drinking booze. I assume that means he can
inebriate people and things like that, turn water into wine and he's like,
oh my goodness, is Jesus? Yeah, I mean, it could be. I'll turn your blood alcohol
levels a little too high and then you'll fall over. It could be a logia, I guess, but probably not.
I mean, he's made of alcohol, he's set him on fire.
Yes, that would be pretty easy actually. Okay, okay. Let's see here, I mean, what's...
So the other thing about this, there's Maria. Yes, Corona and Maria.
Yeah, so Corona, I guess, is outside and she gave the keys to Kobe so that he could free Maria
and free himself. So there's like a little alliance there. I'm sure Kobe will hold up
his end of the bargain because he's a good boy, which means Maria will be back in the game in some
fashion, which is interesting. We haven't seen Maria for so many years.
Were we just talking like a couple of weeks ago about how is Maria even still alive?
Yeah, I mean, I thought he died at the Battle of Marenford and I guess he didn't.
I don't remember when it was made clear. I think it became overtly clear when
Absalom came to Blackbird and said, please let my captain go. So I'm like, okay, he's alive.
But maybe it was already made clear in some other fashion earlier than that.
But yeah, he's been, like ever since Luffy beat him,
he's been taking Ls. I wonder what's going to happen because he's got a powerful fruit.
Well, maybe he doesn't have it anymore. Maybe Blackbird stole his fruit.
Is the one that he can just put people's shadows into other things and it animates those things
and turns them into zombies or whatever? Specifically, he takes your shadow away from you
and can put it wherever he wants. He can put it in himself. He can put it inside a zombie.
But if you don't have a shadow and the sun hits you, you burn to death.
Right. Which is the scary thing about having no shadow is that you burn in the sunlight.
I forgot about that. That was the whole ticking clock at the end of Thriller Bark where
Thriller Bark, because of various things that happened on the island, the ship that's an island,
it's not the Bermuda Triangle, but it's a version of that big cloud that's constantly
nighttime and it was drifting out of it because somebody had broken the rudder or something
during all the fighting. And for the first time in a long time, the sun was rising and everyone
who didn't have a shadow was like, we got to kill Moria and get our shadows back. Otherwise,
we'll all burn to death. That was so cool. Awesome. Awesome. Awesome. Yeah. Yeah.
And then he took, he took a, right, he took Brooke's shadow and put it, and that was Ryuma,
right? And he put Brooke's shadow into Ryuma. Yeah. Okay. That's how Zora got the sword.
Ah, so many things. They all come back. Yeah. So like, I'm excited to see how
Moria comes back into the story in some small way. And Perona, obviously, she's been around
with Hawkeye, but then when Hawkeye lost his immunity from the Marines, he had to go into
hiding and Perona had to run away. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. As one does. And so like, I don't know where
Hogback is. I've never not seen him in a while. Wouldn't it be cool if like the Thriller Bark
completely forgot about Hogback? Didn't expect to ever see Hogback again.
But maybe. Yeah, Hogback. And what's the lady who's a zombie who's like throws dinner plates?
It's like the lady he made to be his wife, but she hates him even though he created her. Oh,
God, yeah. Right. And she just hates dinner plates. And I forget, I think it's because of
the shadow she has in her that causes that. I got a reread Thriller Bark. That's one of the arcs
that I have not gone back to. I've gone back to reread, look at earliest stuff. I'm actually doing
a reread with a bunch of people, including Manchi, who is now going to be reading One Piece.
Yes, I've heard about that. Very exciting. But I've not reread everything. And so certain parts
have just not gone. I've not gone over them a second time. Look at Prince Groose making his little
his little glorp, glorp self. Look at look at his little man. Glorp and glorp self.
He's making a little he's making his little boy. He's making his little boy. He's a very cute little boy.
Yeah. It's pretty, pretty cool, pretty cool.
Oh, yeah. And I guess to wrap up what happens in the chapter, Garp appears on a flying ship on
his flying marine galleon with the dog head. And then he does a galaxy fist.
Just blast their fucking town to smithereens. You're so fucking strong. He doesn't even need
to do anything. What do you think is going to happen here, first of all?
Well, I guess it's Garp versus Blackbeard. Yeah. And like, I don't know if Garp is
like every member of the Blackbeard crew that's here. And it's Blackbeard.
Yeah, it's going to be the it's going to be sword, the sword members versus the Blackbeard crew.
Like how else can this go? Well, it's going to be a fight, but like
they're going to break off into a series of one on one engagements. Maybe we maybe we won't see
them. We won't see. I think we'll hear about what happened and it'll be like a big moment.
Like if Garp is dead, that would be a huge moment. I don't think he's going to die,
but he might get defeated. He could die. He could die. Honestly, he could die. Yeah.
But I don't think and this is and this is the main villain of the series that he's going against
and he's doing it to rescue his boy. This is this is when old men die. This is when old
men die in one piece. It's when they stand up for their boys. And this is the thing.
Blackbeard ship is on its way to Egghead. So presuming that this didn't happen that long ago
because Oh, this is the flashback. Yeah. Garp wants to go save. It might not be a flashback,
but I don't know where Blackbeard would be if not here because who's on the ship?
This could be a flashback. I think it might be. But like Garp is doing this. Disobeying orders
to be part of the fleet heading for Egghead. So we know it's happening around the same time.
And if Kobe is here and Garp's here, then either Garp saves Kobe and they leave.
And then for some reason Blackbeard appears at Egghead or Blackbeard is running to Egghead
from Garp or the people on the Blackbeard ship are not who you expect or some other thing.
Whenever we get info on who's on that ship, we'll know what happened here.
Like this is going on now and that ship is just someone else. I mean, the entire crew's not here.
He could have just sent like... I don't remember who the other guys are.
Let me look it up real quick. I made a mistake. The bit where Kobe is kneeling before Blackbeard
is a flashback and currently Kobe is on the island escaping. The bit where he's kneeling before?
Like Blackbeard's there and he's like, haha, fuck you, little boy. Oh, right. When he says I'm sword.
Yeah, I'm a member of sword and it's like, yeah, that. So there's Van Algar, there's Doc.
That could be a flashback within a flashback. It could be. I think the flashbacks are usually
denoted by the background being either gray or black and this is not gray or black. So maybe
you're right and this is currently happening right now. Garp is attacking Blackbeard's island.
Yeah. When Blackbeard is not here and he's actually at Egghead with the rest of his crew.
I think so. Okay, so the crew, so we don't see Lafitte. Avalo Pizarro is this new guy that we
just met. Lafitte, Van Algar, Jesus Burgess, Katarina, Devon and I think that's it. So there's
like a bunch of people that could be on that ship going somewhere else. We know that because we've
seen recently the ship has a brig and in the brig is a, what's her face? Three-Eye Girl
pudding. Pudding is on that ship. She probably still is.
And she was kidnapped putting Sanji's bride from Holcake. She's in there.
Probably hasn't like, because we've seen her in the ship, it's probably safe to assume that
the ship contains her still and she's not here on the island. And that was going on. We saw her
when Blackbeard was fighting Law. So maybe Law could be with pudding in the brig. If he was
defeated, if he wasn't defeated, then he may have escaped. But pudding might be coming to see Sanji
again pretty soon. That sounds very likely. Okay, so apparently Pizarro was from Impel Down.
I forgot we'd seen him before. Yeah, yeah. All of the Blackbeard
additions were from Impel Down. I don't think there's been any others since.
But we haven't seen much of them. This is the first time where I think
even really seeing a conversation with Pizarro and Vasco Schaatt and stuff.
Yeah, we've just kind of seen them around. Apparently they each command their own
like shit. Their own part of the Blackbeard fleet. Yeah. They're called the Ten Titanic
Captains. Also, okay, okay. So apparently we did see sword before. Here's like an old panel of
and it's several of the several of the same people. Oh, yes. Okay, apparently they were in
they were mentioned in chapter 498 and also in 956. I think this panel is probably from 956.
So yeah, that hat guy.
Wait, X Drake might be a member?
I mean, the wiki lists X Drake as an active member of sword. I don't know. Oh, and then,
of course, the three Golems. And then, of course, the three Golems are the most important ones.
Well, I thought 956 wasn't that long ago, but it's like it's
Oh, no, it is it is 100 100 in some chapter. It was it's the reverie. I thought it was like
Fishman Island because I was seeing Fishman Island stuff, but it's Garp having a chat with
Neptune. I forgot about this apparently apparently sword was first mentioned as far back as 498.
You got to be shitting on me. You got to be crunch. You got to be you got to be insane.
That's what it says. How could something have happened before?
I don't I just I just don't know. I don't I can't explain it. The Romanized name is Sodor.
You're welcome. You're welcome for that.
Yeah, there's a I think a bunch of the people are just a bunch of the people pictured here
might just be Golems. I think they are just clay Golems. So they're not real. Don't worry about
them. Oh, yes. Drake is in this chapter nine fifty six. He is a captain of sword and he's talking
to Kobe. Huh? Yeah, I remember Drake talking to Kobe, but I forgot that detail.
I see that. Yeah, that does sound kind of familiar, actually.
Oh, that's right. This is where Kobe talks about. Yeah, he says I'm on my way to the
island of women. Corsi is Corsi is perfect place to be for Kobe. Yeah, to capture the
pirate Empress Boa Hancock because she is no longer she should be okay. Do you like Kobe?
I think I don't like him. I don't like him. I think that they made him too handsome. But aside
from that, I do like him. I think he's he's he's pure of heart and like a nice little boy. I mean
the fact that he has history with Luffy is cool. I think he probably sees him as like a little
brother kind of. I like that. I like that aspect of him. I think I just don't like how he looks.
I don't think he looks cool and they're sort of building him up as like a cool badass and he
just doesn't look cool. Now, Smoker is the cool badass Marine. Everyone agrees. I feel like Smoker
is the one. I feel like a future one. He's the way that like Momonosuke is a future cool guy.
It's he feels a little bit like like right in from Metal Gear Solid 2 where there's like oh,
there's a new like young pretty pretty boy badass in town and he's the super strongest soldier of
all. It's like, no, no, I don't like him. Get him out of here.
My god, this chapter has so much shit happening.
The new one? No, no, no. The one I'm looking back at 956 is I think it's when
at Reverie, they decided that the Shichibukai were no longer
protected by the Marines. And so all of the Shichibukai reacting to that knowledge and like
yeah, Buggy the Clown is like freaking out because he's no longer defending it defended.
So I think this is where he decides to create Cross Guild and then Mihawk is being attacked.
And then here's Edward Weevil, who very briefly was part of the thing.
Is that when we first saw Edward Weevil? No, no, we saw him before. He caused some havoc.
And they said somewhere that he became a warlord, but then they abolished the warlordness.
And now what's her face? Stussy, the real Stussy now that we know her real name
says, yeah, kill them all, kill these Marines and then Boa Hancock. And then Kobe goes to
arrest Boa Hancock, something, something, Black Bear arrives
and captures Kobe. And that's why we're in this situation where Kobe is trying to escape.
And that was 100 chapters ago. Wow. That's so many chapters.
Could you even imagine drawing one chapter of anything? I can't, let alone two.
A little on 1000.
1000 and 80. I can't wait for the 1111 chapter.
Oh, base, dab.
Well, do we have anything else to say about this, this guy?
Still looking forward to seeing what this egghead incident is all about, I guess.
Yes, they're building it up. Everybody's going to be there.
Yeah, I think I think it's probably other other Blackbeard pirates are on the ship and
probably freaking whatever. I've got a wacko prediction. I've got a wacko prediction.
Pudding has the ability to remove memories from a person's head. That's her devil fruit ability.
What if she removes the painful memories from Bonnie's head upon request? I don't want to know
about it anymore. Please just take them out of my brain. Yeah. Pudding's like, okay.
Wait, who was that girl that Sanji had a little fling with in Dressrosa?
Violetta? Violetta. Violetta?
She had a power, right? Yeah, I think her character was really badly handled.
She had the whatever power we needed for this arc power. What did she do?
I think it was something like she could see anyone around. Let me look it up, I can't remember.
Yeah, I'm looking it up. Or Viola. Viola, yeah. We're looking that up on the hero's wiki.
She looks so much better in the manga than the anime. Dressrosa just looked so ugly.
In the anime? Yeah. They stepped it up after Dressrosa, but I remember Dressrosa being so
not good to look at. Appearance, personality, relationships. What's her, just tell me what
her fucking fruit is. A very great fruit. A very great fruit. The Giro know me. Parameshia
allows her to see through solid objects and over vast distances. So she was just used as the,
I know what's happening where and I'm information. This is why I was confusing her with
pudding, because pudding has the third eye. Oh yeah. Yeah, okay. Oh, and then she sees.
She activates her. She can see through Sanji's skin and bones.
She has the power to read other people's minds, even view their memories. She's impossible to
deceive. This power is exceptionally useful for interrogation. Yeah, that's where her job was.
It was this ability to let her see through all the men who attempted to lie to her, but then
Sanji was so pure in his love for women that she was taken aback that he wasn't trying to be evil.
Me, a woman. Oh my God. I can't believe men are all out to deceive me. They're all out to just use
me. Finally, finally, a man who truly down and deep in his heart of hearts loves women. A man who
loves women with uniron. He loves big tits unironically and he will never go trans. Sanji is the
man for me. He's the biggest feminist of all and it's proven by Viola.
It's funny because like it's not.
I don't know if I'm reading too much into it, but it's is it just that like
he did he was he like in love with her or does he just love women?
I forget. I mean, he does. He loves her because he loves women.
Right. He's like I love his love. His love for me is pure. Yes, he would feel the same
towards any other female, but it is nevertheless pure. I think the thing is like
she sees that men are like scoundrels and but even though she betrayed Sanji and caught him
and then got him shot or something, he was bleeding, he protected her because she's so sexy.
Right. And she was like, you do that for me. And then it turns out that she was being oppressed
by the Dressrosa pirate crew anyway. So she didn't actually like being under them.
And she was a big fan of Sanji after that. Viola can gigantic her tears and subsequently
detach and manipulate them using them to pursue her opponents and attack them with blunt force.
Yeah, that I don't get. What the fuck? It's it's a bit odd, but I guess it's sort of like it's a bit
of you know, being over the head with a thing maybe. So Giro Giro, I guess the official English
name is glare glare, but the the meaning of the word is to a glare or a stare. So she and it turns
she's looking. That's her power. It turns. Yes, she is looking. She's a looking to human. No,
she's an insight human or in the Viz translation, an eagle eyed seer.
None of that makes me think that she can make giant tears that will bash you.
I think that was just a part of like, ah, fuck it, whatever. I just want to have like a
let's her do a punch. Like, oh, it was just like, I need her to do like a comedy moment
where she beats the shit out of someone with her own tears. Yeah. It's just like, yeah, she
can do it. Sure. Whatever. I get it. Like, she she awakened. I do feel like there were too many
characters interest for her zone. Viola was unfortunately completely sidelined after whatever
small scenes she had with Sanji. Yeah, then she was just there. And then she disappeared from
relevance forever. Yeah, her power with her. It's sort of like one of those kind of kind of felt
kind of felt like they just kind of did her again, but with pudding.
Yeah, they're very similar. I wonder if it was like an idea that Oda had.
Like putting similarly is like, I know all of your secrets. Yes, similarly is a woman that
betrays him, but decides that she loves him anyway, and also has crazy crazy. She betrays him.
Yes. And and it's like,
like she's never felt someone care about her. Oh my God, men usually abuse me. This is so fucked up.
Oh my God. I love your Sanji. Your love for your love for women. It's a good bit. You know,
you know what? It'll be funny. It'll be funny. It'll be worth it if like the series ends.
And Sanji finds the all blue and then like all the women that he's ever met who have fallen
madly in love with him because his love for women in general is just so pure and unadulterated.
And they're all just waiting for him. They're like, yes, Sanji, we're here for you. No, no more
Isle of Cross Dressers or whatever. You don't have to worry about that anymore. We're here.
We're here. You're safe. Marry us. And then he will. Yes. Yes. Sanji was nice to Kiku.
Which one's Kiku? Kiku is the trans girl in Wano. Born a boy. Yes. Samurai
acts and it presents feminine and everyone just calls her she. He I don't I don't remember.
I don't remember Sanji had anything to say about that. Yeah. I think he said, I don't think
I don't think any of there was no like overt trans like dialogue. No, they just in Wano.
I know that they say they come in the bath like in the in the in the in the gender bath. Yes.
The gender bath and it's like Yamato's in the men's. Was Kiku in there? And Kiku was in the
women's. Yeah. Right. Right. Okay. Well, nobody had a problem with either of that except
all the guys were like, oh my god, Yamato. Sanji had the eyes bugging out because Yamato was there.
Yeah. Bless his heart.
I ain't attracted to gender. I'm attracted to huge boobies. That's what Sanji said.
That's what he said. They asked him about that. You looked to the camera as he said it.
Sanji looked directly at the camera. Dear Princess Celestia, today I learned.
Today I learned about trans rights. Trans rights? What about trans fats? Huh? They're in palm oil.
Oh. I'm going to put them in my, I'm going to put them in my Twizzlers.
Okay. Okay.
Where, where, where, where are we? Oh, you're talking about viola because pudding because
yeah. I think, I think it would viola, viola would be fine with me if there was a moment where viola
came back and pudding was there also and they were fighting over Sanji in a, because they're so
similar. Be like, ah, see. Yeah. A little, a little bit of a moment like that. I want, I want, I want
a big end of the thing. End of the, end of the thing. Uh, just all Sanji's women, they're just like
we're back. We have, we have a, wait, does he, I guess he doesn't really have that many.
No, he has pudding and viola. And I guess like, yeah, there's, there's women who are
indifferent to him. They don't hate him or like him in any specific way, like Kani, the fish,
fish woman. Yeah. And, and like, uh, just people he's friends with, like, um, uh, VV. Yeah.
People he's friends with, that he, you know. He would do his like comedy routine with the
heart eyes in the background, but they wouldn't really react to it. But he's not too pushy about
it. So, you know, we can, we can, we can laugh it off. We can, we can, we can be friends. Um,
unless, uh, but, uh, maybe he'll get more. It's just interesting that like two islands in a row,
they've given Sanji a romance, like a, like a, an actual sort of like falls in love with a girl.
And it wasn't exactly in a row because there was the elephant in between. Oh yeah. Oh yeah,
you're right. But yeah, basically. But they did it, they did it twice. It's weird that it happened
twice. It never, it never used to happen. Um, we're built, we're building to something. We're
building to Sanji Haramark. Sanji is going to become like Andrew Tate. Shave his head. The
ultimate feminist. The ultimate lover of women. There was, um, I remember when the time skip
happened and Sanji had been in the isle of, of, uh, transvestites, the cross-dressing island.
The Okama, right? The Okama. Okama land. Yes. And he had not seen a real woman. Okama,
comma, comma, comma, comma, chameleon. Yes. Because they're disguising themselves as females.
But like, he hadn't seen a beautiful woman in a long time and he had nosebleeds and it was
kind of like he's going to die. He was like, he was lost so much blood. He was so backed up,
he was so backed up from not letting his nose bleed from seeing beautiful women that he was
going, he was backed up, it was clotting, it was going to die. Yeah, I thought he had to release.
I thought that the thing was going to be permanent that Sanji was going to like
every time a Caesar woman bleeds to death. And I'm like, no. Oh, right. This is, this is like,
because negative character development. He knows he's now lethally vulnerable too. Yeah,
it's no longer, oh, he has heart eyes. It's like he has a nosebleed and he has to like
try to deal with it. It's like a brain hemorrhage, yeah. But he did end up like figuring that out.
Good for him. Good. I don't want him to constantly be bleeding. That would be terrible.
I'm happy for him. But like if all of the beautiful women
are all blue and it's like, hi Sanji, would he bleed to death there?
You know, he can just have the two. He can just marry, he can just marry the pudding and viola,
because they're like the same woman anyway. So he can just have both of them.
And that's enough. I think he'll be happy with two. One with each eyebrow. One with each eyebrow.
When my, when his eyebrow is swirling counterclockwise, he's in a viola type
mood. And when his eyebrow is swirling clockwise, he's in a pudding type mood.
That's how you know. You know, Sanji, I mean, he just, he just cooked for them.
He's too much of a gentleman. He would never lay a hand on either of his wives. He would just,
he would just make them delicious roasts, because his true love is the sea.
Yeah, I wonder about all that. Like, is he a virgin? It'd be funny if.
I feel like he's probably, I feel like if I, if I investigate this hard enough,
I think he's probably canonically a virgin. I think they all are, because none of them fuck.
Yeah. I mean, I don't know about Zora. Zora, I feel like could have lost his virginity.
Who would he have fucked? Who? I dare you.
Uh, one of the zombie guerrillas.
Brooke definitely got some.
Brooke? Yeah. I mean, who knows?
Yeah, they gave him a bone or gave him a bone, you know?
Didn't, didn't, I know there's a line he said that like their, their true love is adventure or
whatever. I don't know. The series is pretty chased. I know that there's been occasional
like dick references here and there. I feel like by and large, these characters do not have sex.
Luffy is asexual for sure. Doesn't give a fuck, literally.
Is it just Luffy? Do you think it's just Luffy?
Oh, for Luffy, yeah. I, I, I mean, yeah, Luffy definitely just doesn't
have interest in living or anything. I think Frankie probably would have Robin.
It probably would have been quite dark. She was a runaway girl. She'd probably been raped before.
Oh God. She had to, she had to do, she had to do things. She had to do things to get by.
Yeah. I don't want to think about Nami either. Cause. Oh, right.
She's also kind of a child slave to Arlong. Uh, true.
No, see, this is what I'm saying. I think they just don't, I think these characters just don't
have sex. Like, yeah, I think Frankie would have sex if he were a real person in the real world,
but in, in the world of One Piece, I don't think any of them have sex.
Fair enough. That's.
I just like the idea. I just like the idea of Sanji and Pudding or Viola or both of them,
and they're like coming on to him and he's like, ha, ha, I don't know what to do anymore.
I didn't think. They go to the honeymoon. He's like, um, should I cook something for you?
I swear to God, I swear to God, their honeymoon is just, he's gonna,
he's gonna kiss their little ring fingers and he's gonna, and he's gonna cook fish for them.
And that's their, and that's the honeymoon. And they're gonna be like, come on, Sanji, come to bed.
Come on. Come on. Ah, come on. But he was too much of a gentleman.
Have never to have sex with his wife. Have never to file a woman by touching them.
That's right. That's right.
Um, that's, I think that's the, I think that's the right way to look at it.
Yeah. So Sanji would be waiting on them hand and foot. I guess since they're not, you know,
they'll get with each other, I think. Viola and Pudding.
Yeah, of course. Because that's not, Sanji would be in the chair.
It's not, it's not sex when it's two, when it's two women.
It doesn't count. Of course.
Doesn't count. So, and Sanji would.
That's a good ending.
Sanji would, uh, Sanji would, he would, he would, he would come in, he'd be like,
I'm going to do his like, his old, like a four kids dub voice. He'd be like, hey Viola,
we made a, I made you a nice fish for you at my darling.
And then he'd come in and they'd be making out and he'd just be like, what's this?
This is so silly. What are you, what are you, what's, what is, what is this?
Practical joke. What are you doing? That's so funny. All right.
You kids have, you kids have fun now.
Um, you just, there's, there's a, there's a funny, there's a video by Lily
Alexander about, uh, the, I might have mentioned this. I've stopped me if I mentioned this.
It's about the first filmed kiss. The first filmed kiss.
They, like, there is a movie that's like, consider the first kiss and it's between,
there's an actor and an actress and they, they banter and then they kiss each other.
And that one's kind of famous, but there's actually another one before that that's actually
two naked women kissing each other. And you'd think that that one would have been like really
scandalous, that that was like put to film, but it's not because reason one is that it was more
of like, it was like an art reference. It was a piece of like art reference footage for artists
to copy when they were drawing. It wasn't like, you know, disseminated as like a, a cultural
thing. Why were all these artists drawing the scandalous woman on woman kiss? And the other
thing, and that's, that's why they were naked is because it was supposed to be like an anatomical
study, but also it just wasn't seen as sexual at all because women did not have sexual desires.
They were just, too women kissing is just, that's just a silly, that's just a silly ridiculous
girl. Just do that. They just like doing that. They just, if they do it, it's not because
they like it or they even thinking about anything at all. It's just a funny, like it's like a,
it's just really funny. It's like, if like, it's like, if like a giraffe we're wearing like a top
hat, it's like, why is it doing that? That's so silly. Yeah, like literally though, it was just
a funny goof and nobody even thought about it. Like it's like two girls can't kiss that might
overturn the societal norms. All the, all the historical lesbians just sort of side eyeing
each other like, yeah, just like a giraffe with a hat. Such a funny goof. It was exactly like that.
They would play that up. They would play that up so they couldn't, wouldn't get attacked and killed
by the anti-woke brigade. That's what I would have done. I think that's probably how I would handle it.
Wait, do you like doing that?
Wait a minute, wait a minute. This is so, this is so fucked.
I think we're done talking about the chapter. Yes. And I've got to pee again, tragically.
So I'll be right back. Tragic.
Okay, sorry, I'm back. Let's, shall we do voicemails?
Before that, I wanted to talk about this little spreadsheet.
What's this?
I will screen grab it. For purposes of drawing my comic, Clarissa Gunsmoke
and The Bandit King, I have taken to keeping track of things to like to think,
put numbers to my progress. And I've, it's a very small little spreadsheet, but I just,
I just really like it. It's just really cute. And it basically tracks my pages per hour and my
average pages per hour for line art and shading slash finishing touches, finalizing of a page.
So I have a week and sometimes I don't do anything for a day. It's like whatever.
As you can see, my most recent week, I've been not doing much and I've been
ratcheting up the amount of time I'm spending. I'm going to try and aim for like a six hour day.
And that's, that's, I'm just going to keep going a bit more every day until I can, you know,
reliably do it. And then at the top right, my PPH, my pages per hour, I can, I can see.
And I put all the little code in, so it like makes all the numbers correctly. And it's very
simple. And it's nice. My, um, my numbers for Beescapades would be really bad on these.
I take, I feel like my time per page is like really awful, especially considering that like
there's not that much drawing involved. And yet it's, they still just take me forever.
And I hate it.
Is it because you keep like changing bits?
Yeah, it's because I keep like, like drawing and redrawing bits.
It's not drawing and redrawing so much as it is like fiddling around with like how big to make a
panel or like where to position it or like whether it should go in the left or the right or
or how or where to crop it or something like that. And there's a lot of like switching tabs
because I'll switch from like the, I'll use the original art, the original panel, and then I'll
put it on the page and then I'll resize and then I'll move it and I'll just change my mind
about how big it to be. And it's just very, uh, it's very like at any step of those process,
there's a risk that I might lose focus and like get distracted and decide like, I'm gonna like,
let me look at YouTube for a second. Let me look at Twitter for a second.
Oh yeah. That's no good.
It is. It is no good. So, you know, I had,
I mean, it happens to me as well, but like I just try to not, I try to
rein myself in when I notice I'm doing it.
I try, I tried to change, uh, the workflow so that like I just like size the entire page down
so that I could just draw the panels directly onto the page and then size the page up. And it,
it didn't really work because like, uh, the text did not scale correctly. Like I had to like read,
I had to like redo all of the, the text and that was very annoying because I
think that would have smoothed out my workflow a bit and it like
ended up introducing like more steps and where I had to like correct everything.
I should say that this is a very recently made spreadsheet.
This is good. This is good information to track like how many hours you're working per day
and how long it takes you to finish a page and how long for your line. Like this is good,
good stuff to know. Yeah. But it does not include, uh, the hours that went into all of the sketches
for all these pages, which involves all of that mental labor of like
thinking what size a pile should be, what shape it should be,
potentially what sort of things should be on this page. That does take a long time just thinking
about it and like trying stuff out. Usually the hardest part and sometimes the one that like
gets you completely stuck and like you can't even finish it. So if I were to, I do want to
continue this spreadsheet just because over time the average will be more accurate to like an actual
average of my like speed at drawing line art or shading. And I'm going to do a third one for
sketching and like blocking out a page because they're all different skills, but they're all
important to track, but not together because like I don't draw a page from start to finish
in one go. I like draw the chapters pages in sketch form and then go do the line art.
Yeah. Because I feel like it's easier to think how to plan pages out when they're all like
vague. And I'm like, oh, actually this page would be better if it starts with a different
panel. So I need to move panels around. And that means the previous page has to be different.
And if it's already line art, then it's like a whole lot of bunch of work. But if it's
if it's still sketch, then I can easily resketch. So yeah, that don't feel too bad about having to
think about where the panels go because that is a lot of of it's more work than you would imagine
it takes. I want to I want to try and I want to try and cut down on it in some way. I think maybe
maybe there's maybe there's some work around to the text size issue because it's really I mean
you could just you could just like what I do with just just just some decisions I could make ahead
of time to just kind of standardize it a little bit to leave less room for me to like fiddle
because fiddling I spent I can spend a lot of time fiddling on like pretty pointless stuff
if I let myself I mean what I would do if I'm sketching a page blocking it out I would draw
like the very basics of what character is there so I could look back at it and be like oh yeah
it's that character and if they have a speech bubble where it's going but you've you've got text
like underneath I think you don't need to like type it out just put like I'm gonna put some text
here and then the next panel be here and then you fill in the text later after you've decided
where the panels go yeah because you can always change the text size to fit if you know if it's
not enough space I mean I'm sure you'll you'll you'll you have plenty of space on like an A4
or whatever size sheet and the panels are not like filling it up in the same way a traditional
comic word yeah yeah yeah it's just it's just a workflow it's got a just a the just got a nail
down and a more optimal format and workflow in a way that makes pages go a little bit smoother
because they don't they're not coming out smoothly right now but it just takes a refining
refinement the sort of thing that this spreadsheet is really quite motivating for me because like
I have a good day or like next Monday this coming Monday tomorrow I'm gonna be like all right I'm
gonna try and work for more than I did last time so four and a half hours see how I do
once I've done that my goal for the day is done but then I get to put the numbers in so I work
for this amount of time and how many pages got finished in that time and you know I put the
numbers in the little thing goes up or down like is my is my average improving I think it should be
because last week I was very slow I was just sort of slowly starting to get things rolling again
eventually you'll have a time when you put the numbers in and average goes down and that's
inevitable true so don't be too tripped up when that I I will try not to I'm sure I'll feel a
little bad when like oh I had a bad week sure but I think that the longer I agree the longer I record
the data for this the more the less the average will shift like the first week that I recorded
there for line art was very productive just so happened to be because it was the end of a bunch
of other weeks of me drawing the previous chapter so I was really going going at it working quite
hard getting a lot of stuff done my pages per hour was like half a page an hour but now it's like
a third of a page an hour and I like it's gone down but like it's more accurate and so the longer
I go it'll become more accurate and so I won't it won't go up for like it won't go up or down
that much yeah each time it'll settle into a yeah an average yeah and after I finish with Clarissa
I'll be like the average line art for that I can pretty accurately say that's that's generally how
fast I can do something and then I can plan like if I do something on the level of Clarissa
how long is it going to take and I have a number that I can pretty accurately say
that's a good benchmark that's a good benchmark I can use to to count how many hours it's going to
take and then I can see on this as well how many hours I'm likely to be able to do per day before
I get too tired I want to aim for like six hours last last time I was doing really good that's pretty
is very respectable yeah last time I was trying my goal was five hours and I did do that for
like a number of days in a row so I think that's pretty doable honestly like six hours of like
focused work a day is like kind of a lot like it's hard that's a pay I mean
to do that like it is it is five days a week every week that's like a lot
yeah but you gotta put it in I mean we're we're not like competing with uh mangaka but like
they probably work yeah like 12 hours a day every day without weekends for the amount of work that
they get a lot a lot they get done yeah a lot of them probably do yeah obviously the workflows are
going to be different it's not like there's a set schedule but like I would like to be able
to say to myself I am capable of doing uh respectable amount of work per day how much
how much would it how much would it cost to pay a guy to do my
inks and my finishing and my lettering how much would I have to I have no idea
you can check rights people do that sort of thing yeah maybe on the fiver maybe on fiver
sometimes I've thought about sometimes I thought about hiring an assistant but like
for that to be worth it I would have to be making a lot of pages like if I was in the midst of a
big project and I was chump turning out pages I might think like I should hire an assistant
stupid to think about that when I'm like not actively pumping out stuff I don't know
know yeah it's easy to get discouraged for me at least when I was like I don't know
I see people working I just think they're working so much harder than me
therefore I don't deserve uh success yeah I'm like well actually you can just do whatever you can
do and shut up I mean people that are pumping out a lot of stuff yeah they usually have a team
behind them supporting them in some in some way or a lot a lot of times they do so a lot of
uns there's a lot of unseen work that goes into like many things yeah I mean for people who do
uh fan translations there's a lot of steps it's not just you read it you translate it and you
put the letters in you gotta you gotta erase all of the things already there you gotta type
everything up and you gotta make it look in the right font in the right space in the inside the balloon
and that's just translating actually drawing it in the first place that's just translate
uh you gotta have proof readers and like the double checkers too hard as a team no thanks
no thanks I just won't I'll just wing it
just don't just do it the easy way I'll just wing it for I can't think I can't think of a
thing that rhymes with wing bing the search engine I'll I'll wing it for a bing it
yeah thanks for listening to the progress this podcast do you want do you want to go
I just want to end my stupid thought and it's over now uh so let's go to questions let's go to
voicemails uh okay patreon.com slash the procrastinators uh to send a voicemail I guess uh there's
something um speak pipe speak pipe uh please okay there's not okay it's a it's a reasonable
it's a reasonable amount of voicemails thank god the first one I see is called a purposeless
searching husk are you ready mm-hmm okay three two one go
pen look through the pictures on your mobile device find the ones where you made your hair
look as bad as possible and post them if you are not craving I am craving I must see them
no so that I can discover a new purpose for myself no die die no purpose wait until November
and then you can find that purpose yeah yeah yeah November then if you still need a purpose maybe
then we'll talk uh I haven't even posted any pictures of my shaved head look even though
it looks good and fine not because I'm embarrassed well yes because I'm embarrassed but not because
I'm like oh it looks bad just because I'm like I don't want anyone to see me I don't want people
to see me posting of myself and that goes doubly for like uh uh I don't want people to think I
thought I looked okay to be posted online yeah definitely not definitely not yeah I look okay
but if I don't look like my best then I might as well look my worst I gotta wear a tuxedo if I'm
gonna appear online you got to wear the hijab to be to be decent uh next one is called heavy heavy
three two one go nothing happy birthday Ben what is it's waiting on you said happy birthday Ben
oh it was my birthday uh thank you my happy birthday when was your birthday it was uh
sunday or no it was it was uh yeah it was last no it was sunday before last it was two
fridays ago two fridays ago oh it's been a while sorry I missed it
whatever everyone else everyone else did too so it's fine no I like deliberately didn't say anything
about it um uh you know who else's birthday it was endless war we have almost the same birthday
endless the endless war anniversary is uh April 9th so it was a five-year anniversary oh my god yeah
if you can believe that endless war so old that yeah it's cracking it needs it needs a repair it
needs a refurbishment it's actually it's actually kind of bizarre it's bizarre to me to think back to
when I made when we well you know I didn't make it by myself but when we made it
and think that it's been five years since then that's that's strange that's weird to me it feels
like it's been around for a while but like when you put a number like five years it feels it feels
like two maybe three years but no I mean there's one thing that always trips me up and it's the
fact that 2021 was a whole year and not like a month oh yeah yeah like 2020 and 2021 feel like the
same year yeah they do yeah they do yeah that whole thing that whole thing I think contributes to the
feeling of like nothing happened well I mean things happened but like you know what I mean
yeah it's odd yeah it's a very odd like alien feeling I never been through a single pandemic
before that one yes well it won't be the last uh next oh boy we got it we got it we got you think
you thought that one was good just wait until you hear what we got cooking uh next one is called
death note 3 2 1 go whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa L dies uh you spoiled death note for me sorry
should've watched it's stupid uh just so you know
um uh l uh took an out
That's the biggest alley ever took me.
It was kind of an out, but he did it.
He got the he did get the W in the end.
He got the W in the end.
You think I don't think W's count from beyond the grave.
I don't think God accepts W's.
Shit.
They don't get past the kingdom of the gates of heaven.
They don't get past those pearly gates.
I have them with little spears.
There's no L's or W's in the Bible, actually.
Oh, next one is called Delving into Gibbons Psyche.
Three, two, one, go.
Are you like a Gibbons Psyche?
I was going to say, we're going to talk a lot about Gibbon right now.
Are you sexually into like, like, are you a masochist?
Or do you just think it's funny?
I think it's funny.
I don't actually know whether I'm into that.
I just thought it was because like, I'm who's that?
Because like all that they all represent like something that I want to be.
I want to be a little confident and cool.
And also women.
Wait, what was that last?
I missed that last.
They're also women.
Are you talking about your waifus in this one?
Yeah, I think I was probably talking about Risco and Marcelline.
Episode two.
Episode two of the Procrastiners podcast.
Delving into Gibbons Psyche.
I mean, true.
Your voice is so much like Therodier.
You have like a deeper Therodier version of yourself.
Yeah.
I guess I don't know if that's the right way to describe it,
but like it's it's it's mess.
Presenting, I guess it's one of those weird things
because I don't feel like I was ever putting on a voice.
No, but now that I talk like more just naturally
how I feel like it's okay to talk.
I wouldn't have talked like this back then because it's like,
oh, that's a high pitched sort of weird girly voice.
I mean, I but I wasn't like trying to do like a deeper voice.
I don't know.
I sound different now than I did back then as well.
And I don't really know why that is.
I never I never attempted to put on a voice.
I don't know if I just sound different now
or if I just have changed my cadence or something.
I think it comes with honestly, it comes with like,
I presume merely talking a lot.
Yeah, because we are on a podcast.
We talk a lot, maybe more than normal people talk, maybe.
Like obviously you talk with friends, but like a lot of dialogue is through text.
Yeah.
And so you might not talk that much.
We talk quite a lot, especially if you're a YouTuber, you talk a hell of a lot.
But like, I don't know why sometimes a voice goes up in pitch
and for other people it goes down.
I noticed and I think Aaron Hansen from Game Grumps did say
that talking so much on Game Grumps has made his voice deepen quite considerably.
That's interesting.
And I'm like, wow, what?
Huh?
I don't know anything about that.
Strange.
Okay, next.
Also, I sound more British and I don't like that.
You used to?
I did used to.
Well, I don't know.
I can't hear my voice right now, so I don't know.
Next one is an image.
Let's look at it.
Then, Saint, I'm going to put my dick into a blender.
Food and Drug Administration.
Sarah, please don't do that.
Thousands of Americans have suffered blender-related injuries to their genitals
as April alone.
Nice concern trolling Nazi blocked.
That's how it goes.
What can I say but true?
What can I say but I'll put my dick in a blender?
They're not telling me that for my own safety.
They're telling me that because they're trying to control me.
They're trying to gaslight me.
They're trying to get some good PR.
Want to put my-
Oh, we're the company that told somebody not to put the dick in a blender.
I'll buy that blender.
Dick in a blender.
Next one is another image.
Let's go.
Yeah.
I paused my Procrastinator's podcast.
Episode three, whatever, to be here.
This better be good.
Do you-
Well, my little pony tattoo on their arm?
Yes.
Trans belt buckle.
Why did they have to pause?
I don't get it.
No, the idea is that it's like a cringe like gamer shirt.
I paused my video game to be here.
This better be good.
Like, I don't like social interaction, but they replaced it with a Procrastinator's.
This is just a caricature.
This is just a cruel caricature of your typical PCD fan.
Yeah.
Why they hold in their can of soda like that?
It's going to fall out.
This guy hates our audience even more than I do.
Can you imagine that?
Speaking of which, the next one is called Imagine Playing That.
Three, two, one, go.
I don't know anything about Fire Emblem, but I like them in this mesh.
Is Ike cool?
What do you think, Gibbs?
Ike is-
He's unlike a lot of Fire Emblem protagonists because he's not a noble, rich son of a Lord
or a king or a prince or a princess who is destined to wield the super sword and save the universe.
He's a mercenary who rallies his people against the evil kingdom.
And in that way, he is very based.
That's pretty cool.
I like him.
He's a down-to-earth kind of boy.
Neat.
He also does save the world, but like-
Sure.
It is, you know, whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
There's always a magical demon or something.
There's always a demon.
The next one is-
There's an image.
No, I never watched the Procrastinators podcast.
What the fuck is that?
It's just a big bunch of trash.
Yeah, there's no- there's no tunnel.
There's no tunnel.
It's just- he's just a guy walking away with his pickets.
Just walking away from some trash.
Why did he get so close to the trash with the pickets?
Yeah, I would have avoided it.
What an idiot.
I would have avoided it much further than that.
He was playing with fire.
He's so despondent.
He came- he thought it was a mountain that he could get diamonds from,
but oh no, it's just a bunch of trash.
Next one is tiny-
It's another image.
Tiny URL.
It says URL shortener.
Oh, um-
I do not know-
What the hell is this?
Free anime girls and a spider coming through a door.
Some abstract-
There's a Rubik's Cube with like an intestine.
I don't think this is related to anything.
No.
Looks-
Neat.
It's pretty cool, I guess.
Uh, next one is called porn, 3, 2, 1, go.
What do you watch more?
Cartoon porn or human porn?
I would have to say-
What do you watch more?
In terms of videos, it would definitely be human.
Yeah, human.
Definitely human.
Like animated hentai stuff is sort of disgusting.
Yeah, animated is bad.
Cartoon- I read a manga.
A lot of the porn I consume is in manga form.
So that's not- but that's not animated.
That's not a cartoon.
Illustrations.
Yeah, when it's animated, it looks comic books.
I never like it when it's moving.
No, stop moving.
I am the one who turns the page, not you.
Yes, yes.
Next one is called this you, 3, 2, 1, go.
Eleazar.
Eleazar does have a voicemail.
Eleazar turns-
Yes.
You- I couldn't hear what you said through your tears.
I think you said cut that voicemail, cut that voicemail.
What, the porn one or?
I don't know.
Just any old voicemail.
I guess we should cut all of them to-
Maybe I cut a voicemail last time.
I don't remember.
To you, it was the day I cut your voicemail.
To me, it was Tuesday.
I don't actually cut very many.
Next one is called Funny Voicemail Idea, 3, 2, 1, go.
So, I had an idea for a voicemail, but I'm too lazy to open up Sony Vegas and make it.
Nice, nice.
So, okay.
Here's what we did.
So, that guy who left that Chad vs. Virgin, Chad vs. Virgin, Jesse, Ben St.
Fanart, if you can call it that.
Okay, so I was thinking.
So, in that situation, Ben is Batman.
And the other guy who sent in the picture is the Joker.
And then when Ben said that one thing where he said,
this guy genuinely hates me.
He genuinely hates me.
Then I would like cut to the Joker saying,
oh, what would I do without you, Batman?
I need you, Ben St.
I need you.
You complete me, Ben St.
That's, I think that would be pretty, be pretty funny.
You know what?
Yeah, good idea.
Maybe.
You know, it's a more fun way to look at it, I think.
You complete me, Ben St.
Oh, yeah, Dustin to do this forever.
This dance.
Okay, then next one is just called She-Her.
Three, two, one, go.
It's currently half 11 on Friday.
Where's the new video?
Shut up.
Shut the hell up.
Fuck you, entitled fan.
Fuck yourself.
You're lucky you get any podcasts at all.
You don't deserve it.
We were too busy eating chocolate eggs.
It was Easter.
Yeah, I had to get my black strapped molasses.
I was eating a chocolate crunchy bar egg.
I ate some and and curling up in the sunlight.
And that's my Sunday.
I eat some.
I eat some coffee groups, some coffee chocolate granola.
Snacks, snacks.
The next one is an image.
Let's look at it.
There it is.
Okay, I like this.
Is these these images at the bottom are very funny.
I have enlisted GPT Sasha cyberbullying, but it came out too savage.
If you're fragile, liberal feelings are hurt.
Feel free to skip this entire voicemail, Saint.
Who want you read yours for us?
Yeah.
Wait, is this a is this a rap?
Oh, Ben St.
The podcaster and Twitch streamer, the one known for his shitty
Blu-rays and demeanor.
He lounges all day.
A lazy man indeed sitting around stuffing his face with keto feed.
A socialist, he proudly claims Twitter feeds his constant
flames, but his work ethics rather lame compared to Nate.
He's such a shame.
While Ben tweets chat, GBT knows so much.
I don't know.
While Ben tweets, Nate earns his bread.
He works hard while Ben lies in bed.
Ben's comics.
They're always late.
Nate's success.
He does create.
Oh, Ben tried to paint his teeth for the glowing pain, thinking
it'd make him cool.
But oh, what a quaint idea he had.
Okay.
Idea he had for it made him look strange.
And now he is seen as simply deranged.
This is like a doctor's.
I mean, I know it's the eye.
Is this in the style of Dr.
Zeus?
I think that the quaint.
Strange, deranged.
Like that seems like a sort of thing you would say about like a
villain in a in a Dr.
Zeus.
So Ben St.
The man of many quirks is nothing but a lazy all day jerk with
shitty blue rays and gummy worm snacks.
He won't go anywhere.
That's just the facts.
I could see that.
It's over.
I saw malt gummy.
Delicious.
Oh, give and take.
What a name to bear.
An artist who couldn't even draw a square.
Oh, gotcha.
Oh, no.
By your ass.
Attended attended animation school to learn but ended up with
art that made us yearn.
Hmm.
Doesn't sound so bad.
Yeah, yearn for a better.
Society will learn yearn for better art.
Yeah, I think that's what it's going for.
Your Minecraft castle is your claim to fame.
But who cares?
It's just a virtual.
It's not even real.
Not even real.
No, it's real to me.
You call yourself.
Your Minecraft castle.
It's only in a video game.
Give it's only in a video game.
Some people have real castles.
Nate Nate has a real castle.
What do you have been?
You call yourself a big mommy milker obsessed with enemy boobs.
What a thriller.
That sucks.
Yeah, that's not even this one.
That's not even that's not a bird.
The first one was a little questionable.
This one's this one's these rhymes are.
We got a movie.
There's no less about you got a good one.
Your presence your presence on YouTube quite obscure.
It leaves us questioning.
What is it for?
Your failed attempts at being a comic artist makes us wonder if you're even an artist.
Yeah, this is really bad.
This is not like really bad words.
They seem to elude a vocabulary so small.
Perhaps give and take shouldn't talk at all.
I like that.
That's pretty good.
I like that one.
That one sounds.
Oh, no, my vocabulary so small.
So meager miniscule.
So give and take strive to be better.
Learn from major true trendsetter for art is a craft to be honed with time.
Not thrown together like a nursery rhyme.
Is that a self burn from the self burn from chat?
G.B.T.
Gibsters.
We're finished.
Gib sisters were finished.
Go upstairs.
Give sisters.
I'm holding my published book though.
I'm on my I'm always on that grand.
It's better than your than your book.
You can't even eat that book.
Yeah, but you can't read that gummy.
You can read it because it has words on it actually.
So it's clearly clearly labeled.
My word counts bigger than your gummy could ever imagine.
It's called concise concise storytelling.
My gummy gets in gets out tells y'all you need to know.
Pretty funny.
I pretty good.
Pretty good.
La Mal.
Okay, we got another one.
It's an image.
Sora Katakuri you're swollen up already.
Go help your mother with the grocery bags.
Dad can I be next on gamer zone?
Not this time.
Hilary on already have Elon Musk and.
PewDiePie schedule.
So I think this is supposed to be Nate and his son's or category.
I think yeah, Nate's kids, Sora, Katakuri and Hilary and Hilary on Hilary on.
Hilary on that would be a very strange name for a child.
Dad, Dad, can I be on your podcast this week?
Fuck you, son.
Elon Musk is the reason why actually.
Yeah, this is this is this is how Nate this is how Nate sees it going down, I think.
Time will tell.
I wonder how many Soros are in the world.
Because of King.
I think there's got to be some.
I think there's definitely some.
Yeah.
Here's a better question.
Well.
I wonder, I mean, is that a thing that people are like normally named in Japan?
Probably.
So, okay, I guess it's not.
It wouldn't be that weird then if someone named their kids, Sora, because in Japan,
but in English, it would be a bit weird.
So yeah, only the English ones.
I bet I bet there's some.
Category.
Okay, next one is called Timmy.
Three, two, one, go.
Wedgie, wedgie mommy wedgie.
Wedgie wedgie.
I'm such a fucking nerd.
The PCP characters are getting worse and worse.
We used to be a proper country.
Wedgie wedgie wedgie.
Mama.
What the fuck is the point of this?
What's the joke?
That sucks.
I'm sorry.
Give me a break.
Give me a freaking break.
Give me a freaking break over here.
Next one is we got another image.
Oh, my God.
Let's freaking go.
Oh, God.
More.
That's more of this.
More of this.
These faces.
Procrastinators podcast.
Oh, it's more.
Okay, good.
Welcome back to us.
This is the podcast.
Welcome back to the podcast, folks.
Today, Ben and I are here to announce our latest and greatest project,
Perfect Comic Party.
That's right, Gib.
This is going to be the best online comic platform out there.
People can submit their own comics and get published alongside our own masterpieces,
Clarissa Gunsmoke and Biscopades.
Absolutely.
This is exactly how we talk.
I agree.
And let me tell you folks,
my comic is the real deal.
It's got action, drama, romance and a badass female protagonist
who's not afraid to take down the bad guys.
Um, excuse me, Gib.
I'm pretty sure Biscopades is the superior comic here.
My characters are lovable.
My plot is engaging.
And did I mention it includes freaking beasts?
Yeah, but your comic doesn't even conform to gun control.
It does not.
I mean, how can you call it Biscopades without including some kind of gun wielding with animals?
Hey, what?
Hey, at least it's not a ripoff of Bard quest like your comic is.
Hey, Clarissa Gunsmoke is a completely original creation.
Thank you very much.
And it's going to be even better with the addition of all these amazing comics
submitted by our fans.
Yeah, speaking of which, did you see this one?
It's blowing up on Twitter.
I think it might just be more popular than our own comics.
Wait, what?
Let me see that.
Oh, wow.
That's actually really good.
Yeah.
Check all these likes and retweets.
People are flocking to this artist.
I'm so worried.
This is just great.
Now nobody cares about Clarissa Gunsmoke or Biscopades anymore.
Why would he?
Why do you even start the stupid project?
I don't know, Gib.
I had to sell my freaking Oculus Rift to pay rent this month.
And I'm making six anime Daki Macro reviews every week just to make ends meet.
Well, at least it's helped me lose some weight.
Starvation has its silver linings, I guess.
Wow, way to put a positive spin on things.
But seriously, do we, do you think we made a mistake with Perfect Comic Party?
I don't know.
I mean, it was a good idea at the time, but maybe we weren't ready for the competition.
I'm, uh, true.
But let's not give up yet.
Maybe we can come back even stronger with our next project.
And who knows, we might even discover the next big comic artist resolve.
Your fucking head.
Yeah.
These are, uh, these are very flattering.
These are very nice.
I'm scrolling, scrolling back up at their faces.
What?
Why can you call it?
How can you call it Biscopades without some sort of gun wielding animal?
Yeah, Ben.
It doesn't even conform to gun control.
My, I got a good argument there.
Yeah.
You got me a little bit.
Uh, okay.
Next one is, oh, that was the one we just looked at.
Oh, we got a freaking vocaroo.
Oh, I know what this is.
Wait, these are from Cheesy, aren't they?
Uh, I don't know.
Cause it's, cause it's, cause they're called, uh, Steve, no, an enderman, no.
Because, you know, like the block, the mecha block.
Oh, well, it might not be Cheesy.
Might be whoever's in the chat.
So, oh, okay.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Steve, Steve, it's Steve.
It's Minecraft, Steve.
Mr. Minecraft, Steve himself.
What are you doing, man?
What are you doing with that big, big boy?
A wig, pickaxe, huh?
A large, sizable pickaxe for a mining society.
What are you doing, man?
You can't mind that.
That's the sacred block.
The Mohammed Rock.
Don't even think about it.
Don't touch the Muslim tetrahedron.
Don't, don't, don't mind it.
Do not mind the Muslim cuboid with your pickaxe.
Dimeoid.
Do.
That's a dick.
Okay.
That's, that's a blue and fall.
Is it?
I mean, is that an AI voice?
It's an AI voice, but oblivion fall is, is, he loves that voice generator.
I, I, I may, it could be.
I feel like, I feel like it would be.
I guess, I guess I just don't know who else would submit such a thing.
You're right.
Okay.
Well, there's one more called Enderman.
No.
So let's go.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
The Enderman, the Enderman.
He's, he's that deskie pesky Enderman.
He's going to pick it up.
He's going to pick up the cube of Mohammed Rube.
The cube of Mohammed Rube.
This is not block game Mecca.
This is Muslimania Minecraftania.
Don't let him grasp it.
Do not let him grasp the cube.
Do not let him grasp it.
No, he's grasping.
I'm going to grasp.
Oh, it's grasping.
I will have a great time when, when that stupid slime and punishment
Kickstarter gets going.
I will have a great time telling people to pluge.
Oh, yeah.
And it works because pluge is like sploosh, like slime.
You could imagine dropping stuff into a slime thing.
It encourages people to save up a big, you know, a big cummy
load of lots of money and then just squirt it all over me on
my waiting face.
Oh, mess me up.
Mess me up.
I've lost my appetite.
Mess me up with all that cash money.
Let's me up with a big Dono's big liquid stream of currency
on patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
You can pluge or content if you want to.
Yes.
Well, what do you think?
Are we are we concluded?
I was going to talk about having finished Utana and the
Al House is finished, but since you haven't seen those,
yeah, save that for another time.
Yeah, I have not seen either of those at all.
My recommendation should watch RRR.
It's really good.
It's really good film.
It's good.
It's a good movie.
It's the best movie I've seen in a while.
It was better than better than Northman, better than ever.
Everything everything everywhere in my opinion.
Uh, those are like the only two movies I saw last year.
I think it's even better than lock the movie where a guy is
sitting in his car on his phone for two hours.
It might even be better than that.
Crazy.
I know.
Okay.
Thanks for listening.
We'll see you next week.
Go to amazon.com slash Clarissa Gunsmoke find my book and buy
it and have it do it.
Cherish it.
Do it.
Pludge, Pludge.
I mean, bye.
Bye.
Okay.
Boy.
I'm trying to, you can't do an ooh sound with a bye.
Bowie, Bowie.
You're saying, you're saying, you're saying yes.
Bowie, yes.
Yes.
Okay.
Bye.
Yep.