Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever, and oh, who do we have here shuffling through my magic card hand?
Not me.
Uh, I play Ben Saint, regrettably.
No, no. Unfortunately, I am unavailable for this recording.
That's a blessing. Not in disguise.
God's Gibbontake here.
Yodelay, hee-hoo!
And Endless Jess.
Such a diverse cast.
What? Say that again?
This is such a diverse cast. We all have a very strange-ness about us.
But it's all different strangeness.
It's a real ensemble piece.
Oh boy, let me tell ya.
Size.
These lives we're living, I've had just about enough.
That's gonna do it for me here, chief.
Hey guys, yes?
Hey there.
Face here for Nickelodeon Junior.
Do you say Nickelodeon Junior?
I'm having connection issues, but like emotional connection issues.
Let me just immediately say something to get us started right off the bat.
Alright, there's been, you know people talk about pizza, right?
You know, pizza, deep dish pizza, thin crust pizza,
Ben, pizza face, you know, the whole-
Keto pizza, Chicago deep dish, all the different classic styles.
And people generally like pizza, correct?
Yeah, I mean it's ingredients on a plate that's made that you can eat the plate.
I would say that pizza hits certain key demographics, yes.
Okay, fair, fair.
But like there's urban centers where they say the best pizza is.
Okay, some people are asshole elitists, and they're like,
oh I like grease, like olive oil on dough,
and then you put like paprika and fucking spinach,
and that's real pizza, fuck off.
I'm not talking to these idiots.
But you know, it's like the Chicago.
My favorite pizza is Papa Geno's from back home, Massachusetts area, New England.
That's the best.
You know, I have a fondness for Papa Geno's.
I don't know if it's the best.
Well, I don't know, there's probably some fancy Gordon Ramsay shit.
Yeah, it's my favorite like commercially available pizza.
Okay, point of all this is, good pizza is a known thing.
People like pizza, people eat good pizza.
I have eaten pizza in Chicago, it's good.
I've eaten it in New England, it's good.
I've eaten it in New York.
I have actually never had Chicago style pizza.
It remains a mystery to me.
I think I have, and it's completely fucking generic.
There's nothing special about it.
I hate all this pizza elitism from Chicago and New York.
They think they're so fucking,
hey, oh, New York pizza, the best pizza,
and no Chicago pizza, the best pizza.
Ah, you're both fucking stupid.
It's just regular pizza.
It's all about regular pizza.
That's true, and there are different varieties, like whatever, thicker, thinner.
Okay, fine.
All right, but, but, here's the point of all this.
Yesterday, I had, for the millionth time in my life, in Cincinnati,
there's what's known as La Rosa Pizza.
This is like the Papagenos of the Ohio, probably Tri-County, Tri-State area.
Every time when I was at work, every time we got pizza, it was La Rosa's pizza.
This is the staple.
It is the number one pizza people get here.
Okay, but yesterday, I was out with Michelle,
and I'm like, Michelle, for your education, you haven't had La Rosa's pizza.
I want you to taste it.
So let's go buy a whole pizza, taste it, and tell me what you think.
So let's go buy it, and just, just as it always is,
as it was every single fucking time they got it at work,
when there are so many other varieties available,
it is the most bland, tasteless, terrible, cardboard, little bit of sauce.
Like, it's greasy, not too greasy.
It's just terrible.
La Rosa's pizza in Ohio is so bad.
It is so unbelievably flavorless and awful.
And yet, like, the professional environment in which I worked,
these people have some amount of taste.
I know people like to roast Ohio for having terrible food,
and it's true, and it's true.
La Rosa's pizza is the most vile.
I would rather get Papa John's any day, any day.
Domino's, any fucking day.
La Rosa's is disgusting.
It's, I just, I was blown away, and the point is Michelle agreed.
I gave it to her.
She's like, wow, this really is literally zero flavor.
This is totally tasteless.
So it's been verified by an outside party.
I cannot believe, in a world of possibilities that we live in,
that for years, I worked at this company for like four or five years or whatever,
every fucking time they went back to the same fucking well and got La Rosa's pizza.
You go to a theme park, La Rosa's is the only pizza chain that's there in this area.
It's so shit when, like, Chicago is not even that far.
And sure, Jesse, Chicago, not like, there's nothing to fucking go crazy about
but it has flavor.
It does taste like pizza and it's good.
La Rosa's tastes horrible.
It's terrible.
But everyone tells me that Chicago's pizza is like weird and like it's like more like a pie
and it's like liquid and it's like a soup, just like a crust full of soup, like sauce and cheese.
Okay, to be fair, I've only had Chicago pizza one time at the airport when I was flying through
and I made sure to do it for the meme.
And that, my experience with that pizza was it was very thick and quite delicious.
So this is my one data point there.
But I've had tons of other pizza.
Look, this is the real point.
There is literally zero flavor in this pizza.
They think they can get by with like cheese, which is the solution to every problem in Ohio,
but it doesn't fucking work.
There's no flip.
And I was holding the pizza in my hand, moving it towards my mouth to take a bite
and the crust just crumbles away in my hand and it falls to the ground like the cardboard it is.
I was lucky.
The entire slice didn't turn to dust as I moved it towards my mouth
evaporating, preventing me from eating any of it.
This is just a public service announcement.
Don't eat LaRosa's.
It's bad pizza.
It tastes like ass.
You can do better.
Ohio, you can do better Cincinnati.
There is everyone don't eat there.
It's shit.
There is a pizza place right down the street from where I live and we've been there a couple times
and it's not, it's just, it's just really unfortunate.
It's really unfortunate.
Like it's, it's, the slices are like soggy.
They come out there like soggy.
You pick up the slice and it just droops.
It is just like wet paper.
Just like, and it is, it's on the toppings are good, but like the crust is just like they just failed.
They just failed.
I don't even remember what this place is called.
There needs to be collected like a national index of all the bad pizza.
So people know because bad pizza is a tragedy that could happen to anyone at any time.
You never know until it's too late.
I mean, if you've had it before, you can go, that place sucks.
But you have to fucking, you have to dive in to the deep end first.
I can figure that out.
That's very, this is an eye-opening experience to warn people.
This was such an eye-opening experience to make me aware of how much better other pizza I've had in my life was.
I get like excited when I get a pizza from Papa Jean or something.
I get dread when I realize that there's LaRose's pizza.
But yes, I'll eat it anyway because it's fucking free.
Of course I'm going to take this moment to shout out a little known chain.
They don't have it around here.
I think they maybe only have it in the south and maybe in California, I don't know.
They don't have it in New England, it's a shame.
But Jets Pizza.
I never hear anyone talk about Jets Pizza.
Jets is wicked good.
It's like big rectangles.
It's like thick crust.
The crust is crunchy on the outside.
I don't know.
I wish Jets were everywhere.
If they were here, I would get it.
Only I wouldn't because it's not keto.
That's fair.
I know that we've talked about preferences of pizza before.
There's an ongoing thick crust, thin crust debate.
But I get fantasies dreaming about like,
you know when you've got a thin crust pizza cooked just right?
So the edges of the crust have a little bit of cheese and they've turned black.
And you know when you bite into them, you're going to get that crunch
and that snap of those carcinogens passing in your body and giving you cancer.
But it's worth it.
Cheese is like boiling and you've got those delicious weird bubbles of dough
with the cheese on top and maybe there's some sauce on top.
Papa Jean has all about those crust bubbles.
I couldn't be a bigger fan.
I had a really good pizza experience when Munchie was visiting in London.
I can't remember the name of the place.
But there are quite a lot of Italians in London.
I mean it's closer to Italy so they can import all the good ingredients and stuff.
I keep saying it in every restaurant.
It's like we got all the ingredients from this Italian town.
This tiny little Italian town.
We got the flour from here and we got whatever from there.
And it is such good pizza.
It's so Italian.
I don't know how to describe.
It's that sort of like really bubbly dough that's crust that's sort of blackened a bit
because they flame it.
I don't know like the proper pizza oven thing.
But we were in like this really shitty cheek looking like plastic green and white checkerboard
Super Mario on the walls.
Pizza basement.
Pizza basement was the name of the chain.
I don't think it was a chain.
I think it was just like that's it.
Pizza basement on the top of the Eiffel Tower on the top of the Empire State Building.
We're in a like a tiny courtyard that was super cramped.
There was like 18,000 restaurants and there's like five meters square.
And then we went down into this pizza basement and it was the best pizza I've ever had in my life.
Please draw a fan out of pizza basement of the whole PCP crew.
We're having a good dinner at the pizza basement.
Let me tell you a pizza story.
So in college, I majored in, I had double majored in physics and philosophy.
I majored in pizza and pepperoni.
It was a great time.
And with a minor in pepperoni studies.
But the philosophy, every department had its own like had a budget for the year, right?
And the philosophy department just didn't do anything.
They didn't have anything to spend their funding on.
It was philosophy after all.
Because what do they do?
So at the end of every year, the philosophy department would just go take the whole department out to like a local pizza place
and just have a pizza party and just say, everyone eat as much pizza as you possibly can.
We need to spend our budget so that we don't get our budget reduced last year.
We need to spend it all on pizza right now.
Or we're fucked.
Buy a book, dog.
Buy a book.
I don't know.
Maybe they could like spend some of that money like to prank call, deliver pizzas to people they don't like.
I mean, I assume they just burned it.
Whatever we didn't, whatever we didn't spend on pizza, I assume they just flushed down the toilet the next day.
I know everyone's made this observation before, but what a silly like cost structure that like we need to waste this money.
I'm sure the party was fun, but.
It's almost like capitalism doesn't work.
Damn you capitalism.
Damn.
By the way, I watched.
One of the reasons I've been thinking about this was because the other day I watched like some like Buzzfeed video.
I don't know whatever it was.
I watched, well, first of all, I watched a Gordon Ramsay makes like a pro chef pizza, which was amazing.
Then I watched this like, it was like a Buzzfeed video or something of like three tiers of chefs.
There was like some amateur fuck boy, some like mom, like with the Italian heritage or whatever.
And then like a pro chef and like how each of them made their pizza.
And like, there was obviously scrub was, you know, I think I've seen videos like that.
It's like, yeah, three, three different like levels making the same dish and describing their different.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It was cool and educational.
And like the pizza that the pro chef made was like so advanced, like he made, he was like different brands of cheese.
He has like a whole like fucking biology like evil scientist lab where he like concocts like from like some sort of culture starter,
like bacteria or something that produces the dough or like the yeast or something that makes it exact.
And actually the mom did it too.
The middle level one as well.
I don't know.
It was pretty cool.
But like, man, there's a whole world of pizza out there.
I want to get there and get in that fancy.
There's a series of videos on the channel called Epicurious that I kind of like and it's where they have a,
they have a like an expert in a certain food and then they will bring like they'll have a series of like sort of comparisons where like they'll bring in like two,
two samples of this different food or like something related to it, right?
Like, like ice cream, right?
They had an ice cream expert and they have like two vanilla ice creams and they have the expert like they'll take it and like they'll look at it and they'll describe what they see and they'll smell it and stuff.
And they'll describe that and they'll taste it and they'll describe like all the differences they notice between them.
And then they'll estimate like which they think is like the more expensive and they'll do a reveal.
And it's just really interesting to hear like, you know, they'll talk about like the processes involved in its production and like what is like,
what is considered like higher quality versus lower quality in each of these things and like what gives a better flavor or texture or whatever.
And I like those.
They're pretty neat.
Yeah, that's cool.
They have like a pickle guy, a coffee guy, a tea guy.
They've got a bunch.
I appreciate those.
By the way, total left turn.
But for some reason, speaking about these things is to be thinking about existentialism and nihilism and YouTube.
Has anyone ever watched that one guy that Digi talks about who's the, he's like the existentialist YouTuber who talks about like how life is meaningless and pointless.
And I think he has like a turtle avatar.
You know what I'm talking about?
Is that turtle worthy?
You mean Looney Turtle?
Yes, that's the one.
That's a blast from the past.
Yeah.
All right, you know what, never mind.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Is he the guy who Digi's been tweeting a lot?
You know, I have Digi muted, so I couldn't tell you.
Probably.
I know Digi's a fan and I would watch it.
Whatever.
Anyway, that's the end of my pizza tirade.
We can jump ship immediately.
For my birthday a few months ago, I asked for like to go to a Harry Potter making of studio tour thing.
And I didn't, they didn't have tickets until today and I just went.
You went today?
Yeah, it's been a few months because that was just when the tickets were available.
But Warner Brothers Studio Tour London with Harry Potter and stuff, really cool, expensive.
But you know, it's just one of those fun things to do.
I saw Dobby, I saw Hagrid, I saw The Fibbon Forest and Aragog came from the treetops and he was a big spider on strings.
And I went, ah!
Was this like a theme park dark ride?
It was like, it's like a tour, it's like a, I mean, it's their actual studio where they film things.
So like you can walk through the great hall where they have all the things.
Yeah, the real sets are dolled up for tourists and all that.
And yeah, there was a lot of cool stuff.
They had this funny green screen thing where you sit on a broom and they film you as you're like flying around.
And you say, oh, they blow wind in your hair.
And you're like, oh, shit, I'm being chased or whatever.
I'm on a broomstick.
You should have asked them to please do that and give you the raw green screen footage so that people can like meme you onto things.
Oh, yeah.
They, yeah, I don't think they would have even, I'm not sure they would have even known how.
Because the people there just push your button and then it's done and I have to go pick it up somewhere.
But I have the footage.
Oh, can we see it?
Yeah, maybe, maybe we can see it.
Maybe you can, I mean, it's sort of like a silly stupid thing.
That's why it's funny.
No kidding.
But yeah, it was just, it was fun.
I had butter beer, which is like, it tastes like root beer, but it has like clotted cream on the top, which is really nice.
Ew, that sounds good.
It's somehow good.
Remember that candy store?
I should tell the story about me buying the one pineapple gummy.
Okay, go.
Oh, yeah.
What are the points?
Isn't that the whole story?
In the line, that's the whole story.
In the line for the counter, they had butter beer.
And I was like, ooh, butter beer.
They, no, okay, we went into this candy store.
We're all in this candy store and I just, I'm looking to, because I love candy stores and I love gummies.
Gummies are like my favorite food in the world, but obviously it's not keto, so I wasn't going to get it.
But I saw these like big, like 3D, like, like, like, they weren't just like flat shapes of a pineapple.
They were like 3D pineapple shapes and they smelled incredible.
And I was like, okay, I can eat one of these, right?
And I'm like, I'm looking around and I'm like, could I just, you know, like, you go to a grocery store,
you can just like eat a grape or something off the, off a grape bunch.
And no one, right, that episode of The Simpsons where Margie eats the grape.
Yeah, and that's fine.
That's ethical.
I was like, could I just do that?
Like, do I have to go through the rigmarole of buying this one pineapple gummy?
And I was like, nah, I'll do it.
I guess I'll do it.
So I use the tongs and I get my one little pineapple gummy, you know,
because you get the bag and you're supposed to put your candy in the bag and they weigh it at the end.
Right.
You buy it based on weight.
So I put the one pineapple gummy in the, in the bag and I go up and I go up to the counter
and I'm like, one, please, please, ma'am, please, charge me.
Please, sir, my keto diet can tolerate just one little gummy.
It can tolerate only one.
And, and I don't know, the lady behind the counter was just like, um, yeah, you don't have to, you know,
you can just have that.
You can just have that.
You can just, she said like, she said like, um, you know, you could just ask someone who's
working the floor if you want a sample and like they'll give you one.
Like they'll just let you have one.
I was like, okay, cool.
And then, and then someone, one of the guys who was hanging out with us,
like I told them that that happened and they were like, oh, so we can just have,
so we can just have samples.
And I was like, oh no.
And I was like, well, well, well, I think you're supposed to ask for,
but he had already like grabbed like a big chunk of chocolate, like out of a, out of a,
out of one of the things and was like already eating it.
And I was like, ah, fuck.
But anyway, that pineapple, pretty good, pretty good.
Well, that's great.
I also love gummies with a passion.
I suspect it's genetic.
It's definitely genetic.
With his ape-like foot and grabbed a foot full of delicious candy gummies.
He grabbed an entire fruit by the foot.
Wait.
An ape-like foot.
An ape-like foot is a hand.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, he's got, he's like the beast from X-Men First Class.
He found like a, a roller of fruit by the foot that actually can go beyond a foot
and you just keep pulling it.
He already like, like, you know, like a Looney Tunes style.
He'd put his mouth on a wimp.
He's just pulling, he's pulling it out like handkerchiefs.
Like a clown pulling handkerchiefs out of every nose or whatever.
Indeed.
Wait, it was like, it was like that one shot in, I can't remember what medium this is
from, but I, oh, I think it was Rabbit from Winnie the Pooh, who's just staying there
and's like, yep, no need for a scarecrow this season.
The crows descend.
Everything is consumed and they all rise up and it's all abandoned.
Yes.
The entire, the entire landscape is just blanketed in crows and then like moments later they
fly away and the whole thing is just reduced to a barren hellscape.
You're the expert on Pooh.
Do you remember why that happened to, to, to Rabbit?
Cause it's funny.
Yeah, but like, did he get rid of a scarecrow or what was the logic of the, of the scene?
Oh God, it's the, oh fuck.
What, was it the one with the balloon?
I remember, I watched this when I was doing the Pooh reviews.
I don't think it was the episode where he's got the balloon with the balloon that he turns
into a scarecrow.
It's, it's shit.
No, I don't remember what I, I, fuck.
Sorry.
Maybe, maybe our wonderful viewers can tell us in the comments below.
I got it.
I want to find out.
It's some, someone takes, I think it's probably Tigger.
Tigger probably just fucks something up, like knocks his scarecrow over, takes his scarecrow
away or something and then just immediately just obliterated.
Yeah.
Oh by the way.
Not even just his garden, but like the entire earth.
Is it just true?
Yeah.
That's a sympathy for Rabbit.
Everyone in that show is insane except for him.
But it's, Rabbit's an asshole.
Yeah.
But I'm, but I'm so sympathetic to like the asshole character surrounded by people who
like as you grow up, you realize they were the normal one all, all around, all along.
Yeah.
It's like, can you blame him for being an asshole surrounded by these mad men all 24 seven?
I used to, when I was in high school, I was a big like Metallica fan.
And like I hated Lars Ulrich because I like bought into the meme, the drummer, because
he like sued Napster and everything.
Like he came off like a, like a spoiled rock star or whatever and like a nerdy guy.
You know, the meme was that he was like the sucky one in the band.
And I had a shirt in high school made that was like, Jesse says the only good Lars Ulrich
is a dead Lars Ulrich.
And there was like a picture of a pirate on it.
Like to symbolize King.
That's so specific.
Yeah.
That's dope.
That is very specific.
Just recently like a conveniently you went to school with a guy named Lars Ulrich.
Unrelated.
No connection.
Lars Ulrich, the third Ulrich brother, state alchemists.
Lars Ulrich of Melnambaday.
So just like last week, I rewatched for the first time in like 15 years, the Metallica
documentary, some kind of monster where they're like, it was, it was filmed in like 2002 when
they were trying to record the St. Anger album and they were like totally falling apart as
a band.
And like James was in like rehab for a year, their basis had left.
So they were trying to find a new basis on top of it.
They were all like not getting along.
They had like 20 years of pent up like brother hatred for each other.
Yeah.
And so like, I watched that for the first time in like, since it came out the other week,
and I'm watching it and I realized Lars is the only normal fucking person in this band
and he's the hero of this movie.
And like, I didn't see that as a kid, but now like being a little older, I can see that
like, he's the only one in that movie who like wants to do their job and wants to put
together an album.
And the rest of them are just fucking off with their therapist and like, I got to, I
can only record the album until 4pm every day.
And then I got to go home to my family guys.
And you know, if you guys are working on the album when I'm not here, I'll feel like
decisions are being made without me.
And like Lars is just sitting there the whole time just like chewing his food loudly.
Like, I thought we were a fucking rock band, you know, this is fucking bullshit.
I just want to rock, you know, you guys are fucking talking all this psycho babble bullshit
and it's driving me fucking crazy, man.
And there's like one part where he just like yells in James' face.
And it's, he's like the smallest like weakest guy.
And yet he's like the only swinging dick in the fucking band left.
And he's, he's my hero.
He's a fucking, and like, there's like one part where they're like talking about Jason,
the, it's like the best documentary ever.
It's fucking hilarious.
It's like, it's like, it's like real life spinal tap, but better than spinal tap,
like more ridiculous and asinine than they could even make up.
Oh my God.
This just in, Lars Ulrich has been murdered.
The murderous final statement was, I did it for Jesse's shirt.
He was right.
The only dead Ulrich was a Lars Ulrich.
Sorry guys.
I grew that shirt until my dying day.
There's like in one part where like they're talking about Jason, the bassist who left
and like, well, you know, they're all talking like, well, I think like it would hurt Jason's feelings
if we did this or if we made this decision.
And like Lars is just listening to this, just like stewing.
And they're like talking about Jason like, well, what's Jason gonna feel like?
And like finally Lars just like snaps and he goes, he fucking left the band.
And it's like, and so like, I want that to be my new catchphrase.
Whenever someone fucking, whenever I get stressed out again, without context,
I'm just going to yell on someone's face.
He fucking left the band!
This fucking so pathetic, this is like sandbox shit.
This is like when I see my fucking, my kid argue with his friend over who gets to fucking play with a lightsaber.
Seriously.
This is the fucking sandbox.
Well, he's wounded.
Huh?
Yeah, but you know, it's up to him to mend himself and we're giving him every opportunity.
He fucking left the band!
Which part of that is, hello?
Do you know what I mean?
He fucking left the band!
I mean, period!
Explamation point!
Which part of that is forgotten?
I just, which part of that got left out of the equation?
You're right.
The fuck did we turn into the bad guys?
I don't understand that part.
He fucking left the fucking band!
Jesus Christ!
It's beautiful.
There's like, and there's this, there's this one clip on, on YouTube.
Everyone can look this up.
Look up like Lars gets his toe crushed.
Okay.
It's like, it's a scene in the movie where they're just like producing the album or whatever.
And Bob Rock in his chair just like goes over, cause like Lars does not wear shoes throughout the entire movie.
He's always just this like slovenly barefoot guy stuffing his face with food.
And so like at one point Bob Rock like spins his, his wheelie chair like over his toe.
And like the comedic timing from every single person in this 17 second clip.
It's like you could not have scripted it more hilarious.
It's just like.
I found it.
Yeah.
There it is.
Take a look.
Put it up there.
We got it.
Let me tell you something that we gotta fix drum-wise.
Ow!
Don't fucking ever do that again!
Ever!
Don't you put some fucking shoes on?
Don't tell me what to do.
You shouldn't put your foot under his wheel.
Okay.
Now can I show you the flaw in the drumming?
Don't fucking ever do that again!
Poor bastard.
And then fucking Kirk's like, no, you don't put your fucking toe under his chair.
You know, it's funny how just we're all, I mean, we're all just children.
We're all just children who are mad that our toe got stepped on.
And we need to cry about it to the people around us.
And there's no getting out of that.
We'll be that forever.
Humanity needs to transcend, become pure energy to get away from shit.
I just love like how...
But I like this shit.
Well, fair enough that.
This fucking clip is like almost, it's so, like every single line like builds to a punchline.
It's like this, the most weird thing to ever be caught on.
Because like the first line is Bob Rock like saying like, oh, I want to show you what's wrong with your drumming here.
And then he's like, oh, don't fucking ever do that again!
Don't fucking put your toe under his chair!
And then like the last fucking word of it is like, okay, can I tell you what's wrong with the drumming now?
It's like, it's like a fucking spinal tap clip or something.
I've watched it millions of times and it never stops being the best thing I've ever seen.
Lars Ulrich, you are my hero and I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
You're the coolest guy ever.
How nice, how nice.
Reminds me a little bit of Paul McCartney.
And now I know nothing about the Beatles, their dynamic,
but as I understand it, Paul McCartney was the most quote-unquote normal one.
And also like the slave driver.
Yeah, he was a slave, not a slave driver, but like he was, he was very focused on like the work.
Based Paul, you can thank him for your fucking albums, everyone.
Now, bow! Get on your knees and beg for forgiveness!
Remember that one, everybody?
I remember that.
Yeah, alright, good.
I remember when Paul said that.
You know, I just, I would really, really, really like to meet Paul McCartney before he dies,
but I don't think I'm going to get the chance.
And this fills me with a little bit of sadness every day.
He's kind of, he's one of my heroes in this world.
I don't give a fuck that he's some corporate shill asshole now.
He is my fucking administrative managerial...
Wait, is he a corporate shill?
What's this?
Well, okay, frankly I don't know anything about him.
Personally, other than he was the like slave driver of the Beatles.
But that's enough.
I want to meet the man who whipped these fucking asshole, crazy people into shape
and made them produce art for the world to enjoy.
Because without the managers of the world, the lowly Arby's employees wouldn't be serving anybody those sandwiches,
and then where would we be?
He is my favorite manager in history.
I know he wasn't literally the manager, but you know what I'm saying.
I take some comfort from his existence, and I would really like to shake his hand one day.
He's getting fucking old, so I don't know what my window is like to...
Well, you've got to go to a Paul McCartney gig, and then you've got to jump onto the stage.
That's exactly true.
I should do some...
Yeah, that's true.
I should do some amount of research into how I can meet the guy.
But then on the other hand, I think to myself, like, how much effort do I really want to put into this?
These are my conflicting emotions.
I mean, yeah, if it's like a casual chance to meet your hero, then it's like, oh, it's just suddenly a decision I can make.
But it's like, I wouldn't really go out of my way to try and figure out how to become, like, I don't know,
to meet and become best friends with someone that I like.
I just want to look at him, you know?
I just want to look at his body.
I want to gaze at him up and down, and I want to say to him, hey, hey, lad, remember when you go...
Why would you talk to him in that accent?
Because that's the only language he understands, Gabe.
I've done my research.
I'm aware of how to speak to the man.
Oh, I mean, the lad is in Liverpool.
We recorded music, and then we played it, and that's about it.
Tell me more, Nate.
I didn't know you were there at the time.
I was there, and I am him.
I feel like I'm the reincarnation of Paul McCartney.
That reminds me of...
I saw a Wang video the other day about the fake...
Oh, God.
Hold on.
Who's the drummer from Dream Theater?
Drummer from Dream.
Mike Portnoy.
For a period of several months, there was a fake Mike Portnoy going around, like, sleeping with other men,
and then robbing them under the pretense, like, stealing their wallets and shit,
under the pretense that he was Mike Portnoy.
And he even, like, weaseled his way into, like, industry events with, like, other actual rock stars
because he looked like Mike Portnoy and he had a really convincing...
Like, he had an incredibly thorough knowledge of, like, the band's entire history and, like, touring schedule.
Fascinating.
Yeah, and he, like, really...
He really duped him.
But then, like, rock stars would be like, I knew something was off because, like, you know, I was hanging out,
I was at this thing, I was at this party, like, all these other rock...
Everyone was telling me, oh, yeah, Mike Portnoy's here.
Like, other famous people were like, yeah, Mike Portnoy, here he is.
This is Mike Portnoy.
I was like, oh, Mike Portnoy, great to meet you.
Yeah, you look just like him.
But then he started drumming, and he just sucked.
It's like...
Like, what's going on here?
You know, sometimes I feel like if I tried, I could maybe meet Jimmy Page or something
because... or Robert Plant.
Possibly.
No, because specifically my dad, his...
On his side of the family, there's a guy...
Yes, Uncle Jeff.
Uncle Jeff was like a roadie tour guide with Led Zeppelin,
and he knows them personally.
Right.
And I was, like, young when my dad explained this to him.
Like, I was getting into, like, Led Zeppelin stuff,
and my dad said, hey, your Uncle Jeff, you know, he toured with Led Zeppelin.
He was, like, the road guy.
And I was too stupid to, like, really understand what that meant,
so I never really got close to him.
But, like, if I tried, I could probably, like...
Like, I don't know.
I could say, at least, that I'd been in a location where a guy who knows a guy was cool.
Yeah.
I mean, that's kind of the other side of this.
It's like, you know, one of my heroes, Nobu Uematsu, music composer
who made, like, all the Final Fantasy music for a million years.
No, it's Uncle Phil.
Excuse me, Uncle Phil.
Uncle Phil?
Okay.
Like, in Fresh Prince?
That guy.
I gotta look up his name.
There was, I mean, I didn't meet Nobu Uematsu.
I did meet Hiro Nobu Sakaguchi.
No, sorry, not Sakaguchi.
Yoshaka Amano, the artist who did all, like, the logos and the early Final Fantasy art.
I shook his hand with his right hand, his drawing hand, and I felt his power flow into me.
That was in a New York anime convention years and years ago when I was in college.
I looked at Nobu Uematsu because I went to a distant world's Final Fantasy music concert,
again, in college, and was fucking sick.
But you could have paid extra money to go backstage and, like, do, like, a meet and greet with, like, Nobu
and, like, the band or, like, the conductor or whatever.
So, like, that's, you know, like, yeah, you can do it if you just, like, are willing to throw money at it,
which, you know, I have someone, I guess I could do that.
And then I would really want to meet Sakaguchi one day as well.
And he's a younger man, so I feel like that's pretty doable.
Plus, he's like, he's out there doing his Mist Walker studio stuff.
He's at events.
When I was at Comic-Con, there actually was an event.
Sorry, not Comic-Con.
Anime Expo when I went with Digi.
Like, there was another thing.
If you just waited in line long enough, you got to meet Hirotomo Sakaguchi.
But I was just like, fuck that.
I'm in the building with him.
That counts.
So that's the one I haven't locked eyes on yet.
But that's the trifecta, the Final Fantasy big dicks.
I guess no more meeting him would be kind of cool.
He's made some cool games.
I always feel like when I imagine meeting, I have thought of like,
oh, what if I could meet Jimmy Page?
But then it's like, who am I to him?
I'm just some kid.
What am I going to do?
The only way meeting Jimmy Page would be cool is if I could jam with him
or musically impress him in some way, or just be really cool.
What you did with Lauren Faust.
Giving your card to Lauren Faust, like with your artwork on it for your comic,
that was like, you know, that's like you being like,
hey, I'm not just an asshole, you know,
ooh, I want to suck your dick, Lauren, like everybody else here.
I mean, on the one hand, it's like, it's a power move.
But on the other hand, she was there for a very long time,
and I was the one guy who didn't pay her anything.
So like...
Well, I mean, I don't think she's upset about that.
She'll probably be like, oh yeah, you didn't pay.
Like fuck you, like die, and she rips it in front of me,
throws it in half, throws it in my face.
I mean, Lauren Faust is the person.
Lauren Faust is the person who reached out to the main six guys
who were making Them's Fighting Hooves,
and like offered to do of her own volition character designs
because Hasbro wasn't going to make them.
Them's Fighting Hurts.
Well, it got changed to Them's Fighting Hurts.
No, before it was Fighting His Magic.
No.
Yeah, it was Fighting His Magic, and then it got changed to Them's Fighting Hurts.
It was never Fighting Hooves because that doesn't make any sense.
Oh, oh, Shari, oh, okay, you're right.
You're right, I said the wrong thing.
I wish it was Fighting His Magic became Them's Fighting Hurts.
Right.
So she's like, even though she made like, you know,
pony shit and is a big dick and all that,
and you know, helped make Faust's imaginary friends
and a bunch of other stuff, like she still has that like,
I don't know, came from Tumblr charm, like Rebecca Sugar,
or like she has humble beginnings, you know, like many of us
and can appreciate, I think, people trying to make their bones
in the industry in whatever capacity,
which is, of course, changing all the time.
It's online now more than like TV shows and stuff.
So, yeah, I don't know.
But by the way, I was gonna say, I said before quickly
that I think I'm the reincarnation of Paul McCartney, which I do.
But also, you may notice Paul McCartney is not dead,
but the thing about that is there was a new video this very day,
September 1st, from Kurzgesagt,
which was like an animation of a story by some nibba whose name I forget,
but it was like, it was called The Egg,
and it was basically about how, it was like a story where a guy dies
and he goes to meet God, and he has a chat with God about,
yeah, this is the afterlife, you're gonna get reincarnated.
That's what happens.
And the guy's like, oh, I guess that means like Hinduism
or like Buddhism's right?
And he's like, nah, it's all basically right, whatever, man.
And he gets reincarnated as like a Chinese girl in like 500 AD.
And he's like, whoa, whoa, whoa, you send me back in time?
He's like, well, yeah, because actually what happens is
you're every person who ever existed on planet Earth,
and you're gonna get reincarnated as every single person
who has ever lived and will ever live on Earth.
And once you're done, you will evolve to a God like me,
because actually there's other gods too on this like higher plane.
All of Earth, this entire universe,
exists as an egg for you to have these experiences to transcend
and become like a God like me or something.
And I was wondering, what the fuck is the point of this story?
I don't understand what he's getting at or anything about this
because reincarnation isn't real or maybe I'm just misinformed.
I mean, the story is about something like every story has metaphorical
like connotations in the person who's writing it.
I mean, it's called the egg, right?
Like just a cool uplifting thing.
Yeah, like what if the end of the universe would be nice
and you could, we all turn into one guy, we all returns to nothing.
What if we're all one and the universe is us, man?
This reminds me.
I guess that I think it's an aspirational tale
that maybe our existence has some greater purpose
that we don't understand.
That's probably true.
This reminds me of one of my favorite albums when I was in high school,
Metropolis Part II by a dream theater where Mike Portnoy is from.
And it really annoys me thinking about it
because it kind of seems like cool and inspirational and uplifting.
And it's a story about a rock opera, I guess you could call it,
about a guy goes, he travels through the mind,
through his own memories, he discovers memories of a past life
and he goes back and he solves the murder.
Basically, he just remembers who killed him when he was in a past life
and it solved the murder.
And it's good, I guess, but it has this tone of like,
he has this big revelation, he's like,
oh my god, turns out, yes, everything's gonna be okay
because we don't disappear when we die.
We all reincarnate, we will all live again, right?
Eternity is real.
And it's like, oh, that's great, it's like, wait a minute,
you just made this story up.
This is all fictional evidence of this truth.
If I'm supposed to be uplifted by this revelation,
what am I then to do with the fact that, oh,
all the supposed evidence for this revelation
is just a fictional story that you wrote.
This does not uplift me, actually.
This is just like, sure it would be nice if that were the case, shrug.
There's some things that perhaps was intended
that we can take away from it.
I don't believe in reincarnation, I don't believe in the soul,
I don't believe in any of that, we're sacks of meat.
But actually, I find that Metal Gear Solid 2,
a source of deep inspiration for myself
because while I wanna have kids, pass on my genetic legacy,
that's cool.
But also, perhaps significantly more importantly,
it's the memes, Jack, it's the memes.
Pass on those memes, bro.
Passing along the ideas of ourselves to future generations,
in that sort of way, we can continue our legacy.
So while reincarnation, literally not real as far as I know,
there is a semblance of immortality if we...
When Solid Snake was talking about passing on memes,
he was specifically talking about rare pepe's.
Yeah, pretty much.
It's just this character having...
He's like, after we've gone, the spirit carries on.
This character has this revelation, he's like,
yes, everything's fine because now I know that reincarnation is real.
But I don't know that, I'm just depressed.
I wish I'd had this revelation.
I like to take a charitable interpretation of things.
I'm gonna assume he meant the memes, Jack,
because that's the only thing that makes sense.
You know, I hate this idea that reincarnation
is in any way an uplifting philosophy
because it's fucking horrifying.
No, it would be epic.
In Buddhism, the idea is that you get closer in your body.
Every idea of the afterlife that people can come up with
to try and make it seem less scary
is actually way more scary if you give it even a moment's thought.
Like, oh, okay, life goes forever
because I'm gonna be reincarnated as everyone.
Sure, we're all the universe experiencing itself
and we're all just one soul being reincarnated.
That's great, that's fine and dandy.
So I'm gonna wake up and lose all my memories of being me
and I'm gonna have to be some other fucking Jack off
and probably get tortured to death in a fucking brazen bull
in fucking Rome in, you know, the 5th century.
That's great.
That's a real great fucking afterlife to look forward to
is being every fucking tortured, miserable ape
who ever fucking lived on this horrible planet for all time.
Wow, I'm so glad I have the faith in reincarnation
to make me feel so much better about death
knowing that I get to suffer for eternity
as other assholes who aren't even me.
Great.
I just came up with a new...
I mean, if you think life is just suffering
then why don't you just kill yourself?
Yeah, well, I mean, life would be suffering
if I were anyone but me.
Okay.
Guys, I know this has been done before
but I just came up with a new,
My Little Pony, Frederick's Magic, OC, the brazen bull.
He's got, you know, he's brazen, he's, you know...
He's just iron will, but recolored, recolored,
and given like sick Pikachu ears and turned yellow
and he's, you know, the greatest character ever conceived.
I just thought of like the most depressing idea
of what happens when you die
is that you don't actually stop existing.
You just do your entire life in reverse
until you're a baby and then you do your life forwards again
and then it just keeps going back and forth.
That's just what Carl Pilkington said.
He said they need to invent.
It's where when you die,
you actually just age in reverse and become a baby.
Is he wrong? You might not like it,
but he's spitting facts, man. These are straight facts.
They really do need to get on that.
He has another like pansy-ass excuse for an afterlife
that I think is lame.
It's when people are like,
oh man, we've got to work on like uploading our consciousness
to computers and stuff
so that we can live forever.
And it's like you fucking idiots.
It's not living forever. It's not your consciousness.
It's a copy. I don't want some fucking copy of me
living on without the real me.
That would piss me off even more.
I would come back from the grave to kill my copy.
Yeah, right?
I'm with you. I'm with you on that.
There's no immortality for us unless we perfect our bodies
in some magical way that we won't.
Play the game Soma, our gamers.
There's always the argument that like,
isn't your brain like copying itself
because the cells die and then get remade
every decade or so?
I think so.
It's an illusion of continuity.
Even if the computers are so perfect
that they can perfectly replicate your brain,
isn't it you?
Yeah, but then that's sort of like a cuck thing.
Like I'm dying and then
my brother is going to take all of my
all of my memories, all of my relationships
and he's going to have all of the good stuff
and he's going to live forever and I'm going to die.
No thanks.
He's going to smash the computer.
He's going to come to life and fuck my wife, thank God.
You know, I have that
existentially horrifying thought
every night just before I fall asleep
of like, what if every night we just die
and then a new me with my memories wakes up in the morning?
A new version wakes up the next day.
I would never know. I would just fucking die forever
and I'd know it would go.
That is in fact what I think is happening already
and I've just accepted that
I'm pretty comfortable with the illusion I got.
Everyone just has like a 24 hour lifespan
I mean, honestly, I think we have
like a quote unquote
lifespan of an infinitesimally
small slice of time and then
that next infinitesimally small slice of time
you are in fact literally a new person
and this just continues.
I mean, I think if you take the idea that your brain
is copying itself to its logical conclusion
like your brain is continually
in flux and like
you at any instant
is not identical to any instant
of you at any other time.
I believe in the immortal soul.
Not for everyone else, just for me.
I'm the only one who has one. That's how I get through life.
That idea of like
dying when you go to bed
has never resonated with me on a like
oh yet dude, I feel the same way
because I've never understood
like if you believe that
then yeah, the logical
like
logical extreme or logical
follow through is that
you're a different person every time you blink
like you die and then you're a different guy
like it's so like
unimportant to anything
that you can completely forget about it. The only reason
it'll freak me out but then
I'll have like a more pressing fear come up
yeah, there's more pressing fears like
there's a bee, there's a fucking bee
oh shit. Yeah, like yeah
like what if a spider touches me while I'm asleep
and I don't know because I'm sleeping. Oh god no!
What if a spider touches me and I become
Spider-Man?
These questions are exactly why
I made the video where I took the little
section of Casey Neistat's video
where he just says, he gets a question
what's the meaning of life and he just says
existentialism is a dangerous thing
like stop thinking about it
and get back to work. Yeah.
Because where are we going with this?
Are you like doing deep...
if you're like a researcher
but that's implied in the work, if you're actually making
meaningful strides on the question
then great, keep doing so. But if you're just some asshole
who can't get to sleep
that's a creepy, weird
utilitarian answer.
I think it's perfectly logical. Casey Neistat
creeps me out. He's got a weird
face. He looks like a rat man.
He is the rat man.
But I feel like
I've listened to this
talk multiple times.
It's a John Cleese talk where he talks about
what was it? The...
Creativity? Yeah, he talks about creativity.
I can't remember the terms. Dude, I watched that again
last week to get myself
to fucking sort myself out
and get myself working on Vapors again
which I did and I have scripts written now.
It talks about
having the playful
mode
and then the serious mode.
You need both. You can't always be
utilitarian because
then you'll never think of anything interesting
or come to good solutions to problems
and you'll just live your life
doing the same thing every day.
And you can't be thinking
like pondering
and being creative all the time because then
you'll get into existential dread and then
you'll come up with ideas and just wallow
wallow in your
fucking big mean
thoughts that you're having. So you've got
to cordon them off so that they're separate
and figure out how to get into
one and then get out of it
and then get into the other one. Makes sense.
And it's
very important to have both.
You know what Casey Neistat looks like?
He looks like a wet koala.
You know, he does swim quite a lot.
He's always jumping in pools.
That's true.
Even when he's not wet, I mean
the shape of his face is like a wet face.
He does look like
a goblin. He's definitely
some sort of ghoul or ghast from
the grave.
I just want to shame
Casey Neistat now. I just want to be a
shit commenter. You know what?
I've really
I need to apologize to everyone
ever because I've
discovered the joys of being a shit
commenter. And it's completely
turned my life around.
Because
I don't know how it happened. I think I got subscribed
to some channel by accident.
Some like
fucking screen rant or something.
This is like these inane
theories about movies that are like
clearly not the intention. It's just fucking filling
the air with vapid noise
to fucking, you know, get their clip quotas.
It's all stuff like fucking like
what if Rick is secretly Morty?
What if
Luke is a ghost the whole
time in the movie and not just
at the end?
That would mean he's his own grandpa
like that song. Also like Futurama.
What if Rick
and Morty, Star Wars, Stranger
Things, Squarespace,
NordVPN guys
Why and why is there a stop sign
in the Aladdin Sega Genesis game?
And like
time paradox. Every time that one of
these comes up in my feed, I click
on it and I watch like the first two
seconds of it and I just have this
overwhelming like this cathartic
need to just type like
you make me want to kill myself
with these fucking just the titles of these videos
alone make me want to fucking die
stop it kill yourself stop die
die die die like I get it now
like I totally get it I've just become
a shit commenter and I'm embracing it
I mean I definitely understand that as well
like it's not even that
you want them to understand you just want to say
shit bad because you want them to see
that someone didn't like it yeah
like I know I know I subscribed
to it I guess you could
say it's my fault but like even if I wasn't
subscribed to it it would still exist and so
it would still be a problem yeah that's why I feel like I
have to be subscribed I have to be the watcher on the
wall to see these fucking videos come
up so I can just see them and know that
they exist and that this is the bad
that exists in the world I have to always
be aware that the world is a bad place
because what if Rick and Morty
Stranger Things 11
Star Wars what if they were all the same
guy nor
VPN guys you know unfortunately
the commenters are mostly
like I disagree for some
very specific lore reason not
you know what you're doing here is damaging
the human race and the human experience you know those
comments the comments that try
to be constructive on those types
of completely terrible videos like you know
they'll never learn that they're doing
this because it yeah they're not made to be
good try stop trying to be constructive
they don't care I would love if there was
like a like a guy
like literally a watcher on the wall who
just goes on every bad video
and types video bad if it's
bad and then he like becomes
like a like a like everyone
like that one guy Justin why or whatever
who's on every yeah so someone like that who
becomes infamous for like making
making it like labeling the videos
as bad and then
people just suddenly you know you get
million upvotes we should make an account
eventually there will be a million
eventually there will be a million accounts of that
it'll be like a movement of all of our watchers
on the wall you know protecting the
internet let's make a fucking
let's make a fucking account on the pcb
called commenter on the wall with like a certain
icon and make that icon like
a link to that picture in the description
of that channel or whatever so everyone
can go download it and make a channel exactly
the same way and we can all be the commenter
on the wall except once you make it everybody
the pcp is now officially
pro bad comments
finally
thank god did you isn't here to fight back
this is the arc of the whole show we've done it
we've done a heal turn full circle
or is this full circle
we went from the heal to the hero like a
double baby face turn
we're a bad baby right now
we're a bad dragon
god fucking screen rent you know
I think I subscribed to this because I think it's
the channel
there's this one guy on this channel
or some channel like it that does like
these like movie
pitch meeting videos that are like sort of
popular there's like 500 of them
they're all the exact same video but they're kind
of funny okay you know it's like
they all start the same it's
like a guy pitching a movie to like another guy
played by himself they start the same
they end the same but there's like little jokes
and like observations about the movie they're kind of like
little like reviews but like
done in a unique way you got a link to
any of them yeah I mean just type in
pitch meeting you'll find a thousand of them okay
so like I got into that guy
and it was you know I watched like a
bunch of them and they're really funny and they're really
cool I like the guy but like I started
to notice like an insidious
thing creeping into the videos
which is like
um catchphrase creep
it's it that's my new fucking term for
a thing that I hate because like
man nice catchphrase
yeah it started off
you know it like the beginnings are the same
and the ends are the same but everything in the middle
was unique but over time
he would say things that commenters would say
I like the way you said that so he'd like keep
saying it so like he keeps
he keeps gaining more and more catchphrases
every couple of months okay
so like and one of them he must have said
like hey this will be super easy
barely an inconvenience so then that
became a catchphrase so he works that joke
into every video and then the one he has
the other guy go like oh
thing is tight this is tight
and then that became a catchphrase and now that's
what they tell you to do and like the youtube
like god I'm sure it is
YouTube Academy or whatever it's like it's like
create little in jokes with your audience
or whatever yeah so then that's too
and then recently he started going oh I
need you to get all the way off my back
about this and then that became a catchphrase
so now like it's just like it's at a point now
where he's at like critical mass where
every fucking line in the videos is a
catchphrase they are they've become completely
about to collapse into a catchphrase black hole
yeah he's like he's slowly
he's draining himself
of all of his creativity and all
of his like observational humor
it's all just being replaced slowly
by catchphrases and now the entire video
is just
oh that thing is tight I need to get all
the way off my back about this super easy
barely an inconvenience
and everyone in the comments just types
the thing he said again like oh
he said that thing again
like the videos are just like ruined
now it's just like
the insidious cancer of
catchphrases creeping into everything
even remotely interesting or unique
and ruining it I could see that
ah youtube
fucking youtube man I can't
take it anymore these these thumbnails
alone I'm noticing a pattern of they just take
a picture and make the eyes really big
and also the mouth sometimes that's I mean
that's just loving that that's like
that's like a gaming the algorithm
taken to its logical extreme
you got the title season 8
you make the face as big as possible
big eyes because big eyes are endearing
or whatever and eventually they will
all just be the exact same script
he won't even be talking just like changing
the name of the movie and the exact same
video
all the way up my back
yeah
I want to see youtube thumbnails
go to the point where it's like
it's just
just a big face
but photoshopped to be grotesque
and then with a like a color
in the background and then a one
and then for the youtube that's the first
video yeah then the it's the exact same
face but with a two
in a different color and then they just
do that forever
that sounds great it sounds like
right right now it sounds like the
present I have ideas like to just
people and you like you know like
totally like off the wall
fucking like to just make like make a
real video like a long
an actual sincere
think piece on something and have it like
be like a real video but just make the
thumbnail like literally a picture of a
guy's thumbnail and like not
explain it at all there's got to be
yeah I mean that would probably just
get you views and then people stick
around because it was a good video
probably probably god
I hate that that would probably work
or just like or just name it like fucking
youtube video and just
like it it's like a real video about a
real thing but you wouldn't know it because it just says youtube
video and it's a picture of a guy's thumb
and then you click on it and it's like a fucking
like a five hour is it a thumbs
up reminding me to like subscribe
and click up no just just a guy
we maybe he's got like a hang nail like
hanging off his thumb so you really
get that if this is a fucking thumbnail
but I guarantee I mean because I'm doing it
right now I'm speculating about the deeper
meaning of this thumbnail even though the whole
concept is that it has no deeper meaning
but I would you know what they might as well
just be honest and have every single thumbnail
for every single video from now on be a
picture of like the logo for Squarespace
or Nord VPN or Harry's
Razors or some fucking stupid
shit like that that they have to fucking
I've seen videos where like they say it
three times in one video like at the beginning
the middle and the end or
and like the same one too
I'm so sick of it
these fucking I don't I don't blame them
for this but I do hate it and like
look at this next one I just look at the thumbnail
I'm not looking at this video but it's I know Captain
Midnight's Game of Thrones Game of Thrones season 8
is a train wreck it's just big Tyrion
solid color big words
I mean I don't have any better
ideas for a thumbnail but
does this not just strike something
deep inside like oh it's just
homogenized like they all are going to
look like that eventually okay
okay so my the
Sonichu lecture has been getting more views
than than than usual
lately and I was considering
if maybe alright so the thumbnail is like
it's my face Sonichu
and my logo
right and I was wondering if
maybe it would be like more clickable
maybe it would be better if I changed it
it's like having my logo there doesn't really add
to clickability it's just there because there was space
like what if I
just put like a big big bold text
that said like Sonichu 101 or something
like I feel like that might be more
I mean that would definitely be a good idea
I think to get more people
clicking it seems like
I mean I think generally it's better to have
the thumbnail be more about the thing than
about you because nobody cares about that
that's just sort of the problem isn't it
if everyone's becoming homogenous then
you you will retain no viewers
like people will come and view it
but nobody will subscribe because it's all
everyone's all the same
that's also true
I wouldn't take my face off there
I would just maybe cover the logo because I don't know if the logo really
accomplishes anything
and I feel like text is
I mean the logo is a brand and it's you
I don't know why would you get rid of it
if you don't need to
you know it's like the
eternal curse of my
stolen by everyone in the fucking world
like updates video right which has been
uploaded to Facebook pages
thousands of YouTube channels usually with
you know with my name taken off sometimes with the whole
entire punchline cut out for some
fucking reason you know always in like
240p you know terrible fucking
quality you know when my
fucking original version is still up there
and like on
YouTube now there's an option I found out
we can click and see like all the people who
have been content match to your
video really a big list
and I clicked on that the other day and just like
it was just an endless wall
of my video uploaded by
like thousands of channels
over and over again and
so many of them have
like higher view counts than my
original video and the reason they
have higher view counts is because the original
video has a real name and
a real thumbnail that no one fucking cares
about and all the fucking reuploads
and stolen versions are called like
man man at windows
10 wow windows 10 updates
really bad frowny face
and it's just like a man
n-word video mad
Obama fuck you Obama
in all caps like totally ruining the
joke yeah like sucking all the humor
out of it yeah because these fucking people
don't understand humor and don't understand
the fucking comedy of the video
so they just want to suck it out completely
with their inane fucking titles
that ruin it but those are the
titles that people click on this is a fascinating
concept no thumbnail just up just
the image from the video that's what people are clicking
on just inane fucking bullshit and
meanwhile the original my comedy
that only exists because of me because
I am funny because I am a fucking
improvisational god damn comedy
mastermind you know yeah
I'm getting I should be I should
literally be a millionaire from
that video alone because it has been seen and clicked
on billions of times
but it's all just everybody else's
bullshit clickbait versions of it
and not the original and I've made
fucking nothing off of it can't
you on in that list of things
can you not like try to claim
uh add revenue from
them or something
yeah you can't know you can you can
claim them and you can take it down
and like in the beginning
when I first saw people stealing
it everywhere I would do that I would take it down
but they just fucking beat me down
they wore me down because it was too much to keep
up with you cannot keep taking
them down it's is it just an endless
ocean of it so I just gave up after
a while like fuck okay
you win internet it belongs to everyone
I guess you've taken my art
and you've taken my comedy and you've sucked
all the fucking life out of it you sucked
all the joy and fun out of it and you can
just have it now congratulations
you took something funny and you fucking ruined
it good job people
of earth let's not forget I mean this
video is one minute and
48 seconds long if there's not
that much to like clip out and
you know make it so like if you had like
I get why people take hour-long
podcasts and cut like five-minute
sections I mean guys like Joe Rogan do this
and they but they have a channel where they
upload their own highlights which seems
like the reasonable we have one too on the
PCB very rarely used it seems
reasonable like I I don't
I don't find it crazy for other people to
upload like I did with Casey Neistat
took like a long video took five seconds
and look I I pretty sure I did
monetize it but if he objected I
whatever man that's on him but
I feel the context is different
this is a very short video
and I have no moral objection to anyone
like like
demanding ownership of their property in this
way and I feel it too my my galco
video was uploaded a million other places
I have not looked into this tool to see how
many content IDs it be I'd be very curious
to do so but
yeah I feel I feel like it's kind of like
places like the New York Times
have like investigative journalism
and they actually sent out reporters like
you know really do news work
I'm not defying them I'm just saying this is a fact
and then like all these
outlets across the entire fucking world
they like you know reference the article
they clip it they capture some piece of it
and they say and we're reporting what's
New York Times reported this what's wrong
with the New York Times
well I have no feelings one way
or another but like there's
it's just that they are doing the groundwork
and the people are profiting
off their work and I don't know
maybe there's some sighting going on I doubt
I don't know why you had to clarify I'm not
I'm saying they do real news
but I'm not defending them Ben the point is who cares
I don't care the point is
that people are profiting off other people's work
and I like is this
just the natural progression of the internet
feels kind of shitty when people can just take
your stuff I mean it makes me feel like
if you can't beat them join them like I might as well
make a bunch of dummy accounts and upload
my own video with a bunch of stupid clickbait titles
it's like and reap all that
you know I might as well just like change
the title to something more clickbaity anyway
since everyone else is going to fucking reap the profits
off my shit by doing that anyways
it's you know and they all fucking just
they just ruin it because people are so fucking
ignorant and they just like
this like death of the author shit of everyone
trying to like title it whatever they want
and change the fucking point of the video
where they call it like Windows 10 rant
it's not Windows 10
every fucking comment every fucking person
who uploads it man mad at
Windows 10 because they can't fucking
fathom that every operating
system does this you know it's
Windows 8 in the video that's what I'm using
I didn't fuck you know but
it's just like oh Windows
something about that just fucking annoys the shit out of me
that they're just ignorant and wrong about it
in such a small way but it drives me fucking
crazy and then like the other
thing is when they like they put the punchline
in the title like Obama
you nigger and it's like
mm-hmm yeah that's not the
fucking like that's not the funny part
the funny part is that it builds to that
because I'm angry and angrier
and angrier and then I say something offensive
and then the punchline is saying
I'm a racist you made me a racist
it's that's the shame of it the punchline
is saving it with my
shame you know
and I if it just
ended on the n-word I wouldn't have
ever uploaded it because that's not fucking funny
it's just fucking weird and racist
mm-hmm you made me a racist
is the funny part and people I've seen that
I've seen it uploaded with like that part
cut out or like with the n-word
censored which just ruins it
it makes it not funny they
they just take it and they fucking they think they
can dittle with it because they think it's community
property and they can just fiddle with my comedy
and make it less funny
that's what defense me the most is just
making it less funny because
no one is funny no one gets
anything I think the problem is
some things I think qualify
for people to fiddle around with in some ways
I don't know I'm happy to take
pieces of things and like edit them together
in funny ways or whatever
but but where's the line I mean I there is
no I mean it's clear that the
they just want to profit off of the funny
video yeah they're not trying
they're not trying to do anything creative
well yeah I mean in this case I agree
they just want money from not doing
the work but I mean people just give
themselves license
I don't know there's no
when I feel the same way there's just no
when you're fucking when you are
a creative actually making your
own shit you lose and
for the rest of your life that's the moral
it's like you okay
tons of the profit will be siphoned away and taken by
other people but like you know you can still
theoretically earn some
revenue on your own are you willing
to do that so that the world
can profit so much beyond what you've
done with your work I mean that's a
question everybody has to make for themselves
or that's to answer for themselves when
they decide to do this because that's what's going to happen
and frankly like I
I'm not like I do
have some self-awareness of the fact that
like okay I guess
this video makes me
a nigger guy forever
like I get like
I'm not exactly happy
that the most viewed video
on my channel on the front page
is forever going to be a fuck
updates but at the same time
not bats oh wait that's on the other channel right
yeah but at the same time I don't want to take it down
either because it has to be up so that people can
know where the original is because it's been everywhere
so it's like
this weird mode where I'm like
normally if it had just been like a video
that got 10,000 views or whatever
you know eventually I might have been like okay
this is an old fucking video
it's fucking I'm embarrassed by it now
you know unlisted or something
so now it's like I'm simultaneously
I'm embarrassed
enough about it but also proud enough
about it that it can never be taken down
I know what you mean I know what you mean
my lolly is the greatest love of all
video yeah I don't even think it's like an amazing
video but like I'm not just going to take
it down because because because what
like yeah like I know someday
someone is going to try to ruin
my whole life and career and because oh he's
called Obama the n-word
in fucking 2010 in a windows
ranch or something but like I mean
yeah okay it's a little embarrassing
I take it down but you know what
it's also funny and it's also
mine and the principle of the matter is
that it's mine and so
I can't take it down because
all you motherfuckers are going to steal it
I mean I find it enough to be yeah
there could be a social cost to pay perhaps
but like it's a joke I'm caught between an n-word
and a hard place
it's a joke I feel the same
about my video it's a joke I mean what
what's the issue here
I don't know
I just hope everyone dies
is the point of all my stories
now that's something we can all get behind
I have another story but if anybody else
wants to bring up anything feel free
well I I fucking
smashed the fasc yesterday
oh yeah tell us
I went to the straight pride rally
to protest oh yes I saw you attending
the the straight pride rally
and we won
and we won and I got a little pepper spray
in my in my mouth
did you get pepper did someone pepper spray you
they I mean they didn't pepper spray me
I was near someone who got pepper spray
and it you know dissipated into the air
and I breathed some of it you know who was
doing that and it was epic
the police yeah yeah
oh okay I thought the oh yeah yeah it was the police
I see I see all right well I guess
I can give like a rundown sure so we
we like um
also munchie and Kazi showed up briefly
that's cool all right at the end
because they were just in the area and they just came
to hang out um so we met up
at and the Boston Common
which is like close to where the parade was
by the way uh so the deal
with this thing is that it was like the
lowest effort like weakest trolling
attempt by the alt right
or whatever it was just
a just like a mean spirited
you know parody of a
gay pride parade and they didn't even try
they rented one float they were like
200 guys tops
that showed up for them we outnumbered them
like 10 to 1 uh
literally epic so so you you're saying
this is a shitposting attempt basically
that was the thrust this is this is this is
a shitposting attempt and I'm kind
of and I'm mad and I'm mad that they got a
permit for it because it's so
stupid and it was so
like lazily done and poorly thought out
and just such an obviously bad
event like I wouldn't care
what was the float the float just said
Trump 2020 uh so
it didn't even have anything to do with being straight
now you see you know you know
stupid here's the thing I think the straight
pride parade could be really funny
if someone who was funny did it
they could make it in a really funny way
um like
I don't know like making
floats that are just like make that are
like making jokes about like being
vanilla or something like maybe a float
that's just like a loaf of white bread
or something or I don't know
something something like you know that's
someone else could have a better idea but just like
you could do like a satirical way and it would be funny
and maybe I would like it but this was
just boring and just uh just
you know just mean spirit and bad
so like I don't think they should have got a
permit I'm annoyed that they got a permit I'm
annoyed that the police showed up to like
such stalwart defense for this stupid
event I'm just curious
why do you say it was mean spirited
why do I say it was mean spirited
yes what
how could it be anything else
okay gotcha
like like
no I mean that like I believe you
like the the the
you're like it's
how do I even put it how do I even put into words
um like
straight people don't need a pride parade straight people
are not are not oppressed they claim like the
people organizing a claim to be the oppressed
majority which is like
like they can't possibly really believe
that I agree this is just this is
this is the this is the like oh they
it's a it's a it's a spite parade
it is yes it is a spite it was a spite
right but anyway we all met up at the
at the commons and you know we fucked around
we all got along on the streets we waited for
the parade to start there were so many cops
there were so many fucking cops
out they were like riding down the
street on their motorcycles and like blaring
their sirens even though nothing was happening
just to like I don't know
subdue of the crowd or something with like
ear damaging levels of noise
um they did all that
the parade started it lasted like a minute
because there were like 200 guys in one float
and like one car
um we followed they had like oh
Milo Yiannopoulos was there he was on the float
I see he was
he was wearing a MAGA hat blowing kisses to
the crowd so a gay man was
on the float of a straight pride parade
well not just any gay man
the gay man
yeah yeah
patient zero
for gayness
the origin of the virus
I saw him up there
and then we all kind of just gathered around
they had a police barricade
so many fucking cops they had a police
barricade they did it in like the city hall
plaza we couldn't hear them
they were they had like there was a
stage and there were speakers but like
we could not hear what they were actually saying
and we just like hung around for the whole thing
just booed them a whole lot
you know chanted
that they suck and should go home
um and uh you know
it's pretty good and then
how little do you have to accomplish in life
if you have to be proud of being straight
that's right
right it's really there's really no
there's really no need there's really no need for this
like yeah either it's
you know as it seems
a big shitpost spite parade
or it's incredibly pathetic and should be
mocked anyway
I think it was mostly the latter
and maybe a few people in there
are the former
I mean Milo known provocateur
I mean I don't know how people feel about him
these days haven't heard much about him lately
but I know he's trying to make people mad
I think that probably some of the people were
just like sincerely like
I do feel persecuted for being straight
and those that's just even sadder
that's even sadder to me
boy I was in that float
for me boys
I mean this is just like that
that that thing the the flyers that were going
up okay like technically true
okay technically it's fine to be
proud or whatever of being straight okay like
those posters that we're saying it's okay to be
white okay yes technically we all understand
it's technically fine it is okay
to be white but you know it's it's
clearly in response but we don't need we don't need
to fucking march about it yeah don't you have your
whiteness in my face I'm doing just fine folks
it's just lame everyone's a fucking
loser if you feel oppressed stay in your
fucking house that's the fucking
solution
you don't need to fucking go out on the streets
and be annoying and show everyone what a
fucking sad loser you are by fucking
pick it and this goes for anyone not just
for fucking the people that are that are bad
you know anyone fucking picketing
or making a fucking public disturbance
for any reason anyone going outside
going hey look at me I'm this fucking
group you're all fucking losers just
stay inside and stop bothering normal
people frankly if you're not
making pipe bombs I question your dedication
to the cops I unironically
believe that if you don't have the courage
to fight kill and die for your beliefs
and fuck your beliefs
fuck your group fuck your parades
there enough bunch of fucking losers
yeah so there were 34
arrests I saw maybe like
maybe like 10 of them okay
and I didn't see what any of them were getting
arrested for I just saw people being like
you know like taken away and like
escorted I saw one guy
he was being like four cops
each one was like grabbing one of his
like arms and legs and just like carrying
him like like down the street
I don't know what he did to get it I didn't
see it actually take place I just saw them
carrying him away it was quite a spectacle
the one thing okay at the end
after like the rally was over
you know we all yell and go home and whatever
the rally was over they're all dissipating
that's what I would
and for some reason people kept
hanging out and they just
they didn't leave like the crowd didn't leave
for a while they were still just sort of like waiting
around the barricade
and at this point like the police come in
and they do like a police thing like they're clearing the street
they're clearing the street and some people did
not get out of the street and clear the way
for the police and this is what I this is
when there was pepper spray employed
they just like people wouldn't clear the road
for this police envoy or whatever and
they just they had they had to spray him
and it's it got kind of dicey for a second
it seemed like it seemed like
the crowd all had to like push back from the
street and like it looked like
there was like a brawl breaking out and like it
looked for a minute like there was just going to be like
fighting like breaking out in the sidewalk
have you ever seen like I don't I don't know how much
of this you've ever been to like a big like
potential fighty kind of thing I've never been
in fucking a situation like that in my whole life
one of probably the closest thing
I've been to but but I didn't actually
see the pepper spraying because there was a crowd
but I did I did you know like I heard
people saying they're spraying they're spraying
and then I like breathe something
in and I was like my throat
felt all like weird and spice I was like oh god
I can't I can't breathe right what's going on am I going
to die but it was fine
it wasn't a big it wasn't a big deal
and then but some some guy
some guy who just had like bandanas
you know like the band like the bandanas
people wear over their faces and stuff yeah
yeah and he was and he was just like he had
a box of them and he was like here like put this over
your mouth put this over your mouth and like I took one
and like I was breathing through that for a second
oh it was so during the pepper spray to help people
yeah he was like here breathe
yeah you breathe through this it'll
help maybe quit I don't know if it actually would have
helped breathe this you know
bash the bash and that's
that's all there is to it bash the bash
I don't know by that point the rally was over
so I was just ready to leave
of course the picture you uploaded of
yourself in the in that crowd on that
website yeah I'm really glad
some website I put it on
Twitter some website got a picture that like you can
you can see me
oh yeah Colcorona was there too
Colcorona's there giving the thumbs down
aww that guy he gets around
he's always involved with something interesting
he's having a lot of adventures
he's he's a loose cannon
oh dude that arm band looks like a
fuck what is it it's like a wild cherry
black monster or something
it does yeah if you're right it looks like
you know what maybe Antifa had some
good ideas after all that's all I'm saying
the ultra the ultra black
that's the one that's the one
anyway it was pretty it was
pretty cool it was pretty cool
and um you know some shit
I want to I want to go get
pepper spray I want to be involved with something
that that has violence in it some
some you know some people said like don't show
up like this is what they want and like sure
I kind of agree I think it's
true like they obviously did this with
the intention of trolling
and riling up a big group
to like you know be mad you know triggering the
libs right and I guess
in that way that succeeded I guess this
is probably what they want so much for the tolerant
left here we go once again there
was there was like during there there was a guy
at like because like the police barricade
was like a big sort of space they kept like a
big space clear between like us and
them and there were a couple of people
just like hanging out at the like other
end of the barricade like you know waving straight
pride flags at us there was a guy with a
microphone who kept like yelling stuff at us
but it wasn't loud enough when we couldn't hear
what he was saying so it was I don't know
I don't know what but they were
they were just they were loving the attention
they were loving it it was great so I guess
in a sense this is what they wanted but
I think that the net effect of it
is good and I'm glad that I went because I
think that it's a good thing to show
up and make the statement that like
there's more of us than there are of you
we think you suck we don't want you here
and like hopefully this is like
I mean hopefully this is enough of a disturbance
that they wouldn't grant permission for a similar
shitty event like this in the future
because they're not because like the mayor
said like he oh he had to approve this
event because he had he approves them based
on operational feasibility and not on
politics but like what does that mean
you're obligated to approve a permit
for any event that well I mean can
happen fucking the fucking KKK
were given a thing back in the day and I mean
you know that's like a free speech issue right so I mean
if those guys at some point at
but they had at some point someone has
to have the ability to say
like this event just sucks
well you know it's different actually
they can't they can't I don't know
exactly what the chain of command is that approves
or denies permits for these things but they can't
be obligated to allow
any event that can occur
to occur I was gonna say like
if I submitted one that's like
utterly retarded that has no
basically if I'm sincere in my beliefs
and making it like okay I will the KKK
those guys probably believe what they say
they probably were sincere in their
you know hate to minorities and what not
so that's like a real thing I guess
they're really trying to say but I mean
these guys are far more shit posty
I would imagine but like
maybe they made a good faith argument like
no we are argument at least is we're really
just trying to say it's okay to be straight
which technically fine
so I don't know the logic
they're pretty it's pretty clear
if you read their Facebook page that this is
you know just like a dumb
if I was there I drew down people who seemed like
they were just fucking around yeah and like it's really
like they didn't even make it try to seem like a real thing
and I don't know I really don't buy the excuse that
oh I just had to I don't know
why this got approved and I don't think it should have been
I want to get in on this I want to
you know I think if you
forget everything I said before about if you
take part in either side you're a loser I take it back
I think that if you have the opportunity
to participate in civil unrest
you should take it because it's fucking cool
regardless of what side you're on
you know I want to go to one of these things
and I want to just be holding a sign that says
I'm just here for the violence
I want pepper spray
flying I want bricks
flying I want to be right in the middle
of all of it baby I want to fucking
thing around I want to fucking mask around the bottom
of my face so I look cool I want to fucking
be running around punching random people
in the head oh you know oh getting punched
in the head I don't care either way okay
okay in I just want to say in that picture
with cold corona next to cold corona
is a guy he's got the face mask on he's
wearing sunglasses and the black hat okay
yeah thing about that guy is he was right next
to him you can't really see him but there's like a big
like fat guy who's also in like a black hoodie
and as we're standing in
that line like right across from us was the
police barricade they were like standing
along the parade route preventing us from blocking the street
and these two guys
they were literally doing
like a antifa
Abaddon Costello routine
and they were doing like a little like back
and forth like jokie thing like they were
they were like talking to the cops about like
like oh like you can you like oh you can see
these guys don't want to be here and stuff and they're like
oh look at these I don't know they were just
okay they weren't that funny but what they were attempting
to do was like a sort of
ad hoc comedy Abaddon Costello
they were putting an image in your
brain that you could make funnier and it was
just funny because there was like a tall
skinny one and a short fat one and they were
they were just like they looked
like a they looked like a comedy duo
and I I appreciated
the effort at least you know like I
obviously I'm a man with a lot of
straight pride let me tell you I'm just filled
to the brim with straight pride and
but but you know
like in something like this it does seem to me the guys
are obviously shit posters whatever they don't need to parade
maybe it's fine I don't whatever I don't care
I don't really blame anybody for coming to protest
because obviously it's it's the like
thing of like getting real close
like I'm not touching you I'm not touching you
you're like real close at a certain point
it's just gonna trigger a response and
like I'm happy to see I didn't look at a news reports
everybody here looks pretty reasonable
I don't blame it for booing or anything but like
I see the girl in the front with the like we
support cis people straight people normal
people that's not like saying like fuck
straight people so like
I just seems like a positive
message overall and they're not
you know in any way being overly negative at least
the guy's putting on the guys like
from the tone of the Facebook post and
like the history like the guys the guys
hosting this event are like the same guys
who in 2007 they hosted a quote
unquote free speech rally which was
just a it was just like an alt-right
like trolling event basically they're just
sure they're they're not
they're not they're not good dudes
they're not they're not doing this in good faith
push back against the term alt-right being applied
like is Milo really alt-right I mean he's very
right I'm not even I'm not even talking about Milo
although there's other
I don't like Milo either yeah all right
so so yeah I got pepper sprayed and it was
epic that's my story
regarding the like
giving them what they want though
I feel like
it's so like giving them what they want
is like they want to trigger the left
ease because they think it's funny
allegedly presumably
I think
it's it's so much
like worse to like not
go for fear of making them
laugh like giving them a jolly
yeah like oh
like oh it's kind of no way to win really
no but like the them winning
isn't that much of a big win I think we
want to like the failure it would be
if we just let them do it
yeah yeah if they if they just if we
just let them do it
then like yeah hey cold corona
always picks the winning side
look look I just
I just think it makes the statement the
it's the right statement to make that like
10 times more counter
protesters showed up then like actual
attendees look that's fine
like I'm sure people like Milo will
spin it as like we triggered them
so like it's so few of us triggered them so
I mean what does it really mean but like yeah
it seems fine seems reasonable
well that's the thing I don't blame anyone
for going but just just consider the reality where
like this wouldn't ever happen but imagine
if literally no one showed up to observe
that would itself be a statement that
you know but they would they would then also
spin it as like obviously I see
what I see what you mean like that they
were too scared to come and fight us but
yeah right like it's always gonna be
something yeah I mean you know when you've
got an agenda no matter what side you
find yeah
I mean that would be pretty funny if like
they're like nobody even showed up to
counterprotect but like yeah that wasn't
gonna happen and we're not there yet
like I think in a perfect
in a perfect world probably nobody would
pay any attention to this kind of thing
but like these same these same people
they put on like they said they are
they did another thing like this in 2017
they're gonna like keep doing it yeah
yeah yeah like I said I don't know if I
have any straight pride specifically
but I do know that all of the
pride I do have is very
straight all my pride is very
straight I have no pride
I feel you on that and this was oh and
also while I was there this this is
happened to be the same day that Munchy
was moving into his uh his new dorm
because he's starting college now and I
mm-hmm oh today is the day today's
or was it yesterday yesterday he's
moving and I think yeah yesterday yeah
yesterday moved in when I went and saw
his dorm and you know just saw the play
it's okay I'm really jealous
because he's on like the he's on like
the little like a building with like a
bed and like a floor
okay he can he can literally
see endless war from
his not from his room but from like
right outside his room there's a window
in DC
no the canonical
endless war is the Bunker Hill Monument
oh I gotta google that okay which you
can yeah we visited it at the
rfckcon and
he can see it from his like hallway window
oh my he can fucking see the site
oh wow that does actually fucking look exactly like
it yeah he can fucking
see it from his fucking window every
day yes living in the belly of the
beast now I know or is literally
every day I know I wish
I got I wish that were me
incredible
yeah um well hey that's
that's that's dope but listen people
I have another in the continuing saga
of Nate's
Adventures at Theme Parks
because yesterday I took my
my little old self and Michelle was Michelle's
birthday yesterday and we went
to Coney Island a much smaller
but uh also New York
uh no no there's of course there's Coney
on to New York but this is a little amusement park
based on like
uh named after that but it's just a
fucking amusement park okay it's not is there
just a lot of cones everywhere there's plenty
of cones absolutely um okay
but here's here's the thing hang on let me pull up my
fucking notes it took some notes on this okay here we go
so I'm coming off obviously the
greatest moment in pcp history
my diamondback story forget
brony con forget ben bash in the
it was all about Nate
top diamondback the rockets bursting in
air it was incredible so yesterday
Michelle's like hey let's go to you know for my
birthday let's go to Coney Island have fun okay sounds
great so we go now
this would come to be known later in the
annals of history as
uh uh scholars recount Nate's
story as the day of pain
the day of pain uh as you
know to continue the spirit of munchy
so the first thing that happens in the
day is we're both hungry we get there and we
decide to eat some food now
we cannot find any healthy alternatives
so we get a couple of corn dogs
and we I see I see deep fried
twinkies on the menu
and I just think to myself well I've gotta
buy those I have to get in on this
action so I do uh Michelle
takes like a bite she's like this is disgusting I never want
this near me ever again I so I'm like okay
I'll eat yours and I eat them all I
consume all the fried food this
would throughout throughout the day my
constitution score
dropped like 20 points I am dying
it is don't do it don't
listen to your base or instincts be
an intellectual being and don't eat
fried food ever it's a mistake every time
okay so this is the
so this is the first step in my my path
of pain on the day of pain of me
experiencing agony throughout the entire day
okay um so later on I go
into a bathroom and I just notice that this
is an omen of the future I notice
the words uh fuck
god carved into this to
the wall and also uh
what was it oh there was a swastika next to it
and then also the words tiny
Tim is a fag I don't know
exactly what that was referring to
but oh and I have pictures of it
living in the sunlight loving in the moon
like having a wonderful time
was it was it of course uh our boy the
the Christmas Eve man I I don't know
I'll never know but uh so so
this is again the the the omens the darkness
is continuing to progress
so um let me see where was
I okay so we progress throughout the day
I'm experienced we do all the tilted worlds
all kinds of crazy shit it's it's a bad time
for me my stomach is churning I'm dying
I want to puke but I don't have managed to hold it
off until then until the end here
so the end of the day is coming we're
about to leave I'm still feeling sick
and uh we went to the water park
there and as we are leaving the water park
we're about to leave I did my swimming I'm
having a high I'm feeling good we notice
that there is a diving board
and there's a high dive as well
now I don't know if you guys have been on a high dive before
but it's pretty fucking high
it is like I don't know maybe 10 feet off
the water and I think of myself will obviously
I've got to give this a try
so I go to the high dive it hurts
I do a dive it was fine no big deal
I'm too I'm too pussy to a
fucking normal dive I do a cannonball
cause I don't want to hurt my body
um okay so that went fine
if I were diving off the high I'd be afraid that I would
over correct and like go upside down you know what I mean
indeed like your feet
extend beyond your and you rotate
oh you wouldn't want that one could only
and you land on your back
oh yeah that's that's this is a
nightmare this is a nightmare to be
avoided at all costs so I think
of myself you know what that first cannonball went okay
I think it's time to do an actual dive
so I go I do a dive goes reasonably well
still in pain that's okay now from
this moment on I'm witnessing the little
children are gathering around and they're all
they're not looking at me they're just they're just doing the diving board
and I'm like okay I'm just going to do a couple of dives
for fun off of the
like the lower boards I'm doing this
for a while and then I see the children start
to do flips and I've decided my quest
for the day my diamond back for the day
is to do a flip
is to do a flip off the diving board this
has become my quest
this would result in the
day of pain coming to a gruesome head
one can only imagine
so I'm practicing my flips
I'm doing it over and over I'm getting nowhere
uh one of my early attempts
is is and I'm doing like a twisting
jerking motion I'm scared I'm I'm in
fear now Michelle was actually a diver
for like many years like a swim team
diver so she knows exactly what she's doing
and it's roasting there from the sidelines
you looking real gay out there Nate you
gotta get your shit together and
things of this nature
uh you know when you're doing dives
you're if you hit the water wrong
the the pain the pain begins to
rise and you feel the soreness creeping
all over your body so I'm sick
I'm scared the fear of God
is in me Satan is amongst me and
I'm increasing the damage over my body
but I will not give up because I'm seeing
children of like five years old
do flips all around me and they're having
no trouble whatsoever and so I've
committed I must do a flip
over and over and over again
I think I'm gonna do it Michelle gives me
a couple of pointers I I I managed to
rotate like 80% of a flip
but this results oh no in
you know exactly what you just mentioned
man a big hit the water
no it's my my
side is a shearing red color
Michelle tells me she reports back to me
that at this moment everyone audibly
winces in the in the crowd
gathering around and they see me fuck up
this bad even the lifeguard
even the lifeguard but I've
decided I will I will suffer
the pain I will continue to rack up agony until
I can do this fucking flip like these babies
now I could this continues for another
like I don't know 15 20 minutes of me just
throwing my body over and over again
just my HP bar is depleting slowly
like I've got the poison status
you just kept doing it I just kept doing
it I had to do your HP
bar is depleting but your limit break
bar is rising you know
but you are so right Jesse you are so
right because after after another
big flop a big searing
activity might people can see people don't
want to see a man hurt himself in this way
over and over again at a children's
amusement park so so
nobody wants to see a grown man
cry no no the children
at this point are in fact
cheering me on and they they have taken
notice of my activities and so I
make a little great gang of conspirators
co-conspirators the ones who are good at flipping
they're like dude okay you gotta do it like this
you gotta tuck your body Michelle's giving me advice
and even after a while the lifeguard himself is like
bro you gotta rotate your arms up you gotta
extend your arms to get more momentum
so you'll stop fucking killing yourself
what an event the whole
community got involved in my quest
Michelle's just sitting there I come to sit down
for a while she's like you cannot sit next
to me until you pull off this fucking flip get the
fuck out there you are embarrassing me in front
of everyone okay you got it chief
so I go back to work
now okay eventually
that trick about the arms extending
that the the fucking
lifeguard gave me it finally bore
fruit my limit bar was had its max I
had finally learned the technique I tuck
my legs up I do my arms
extended upward and I do a flawless
perfect like
I don't know 360 degree
rotation jump into the water
everyone's like Nate you are the coolest fucking
guy you fucking did it
lookin good Nate and at this
point frankly lads I'm cocky
as hell my limit bar is still
full so I think you know what
let's get back on that fucking high dive my dude
I know the technique I do
a correct flip one time and I think to myself
I'm a master
easy shit easy I have literally
achieved god mode
fuck this I'm going back high
so just like a fucking sultan I strut
up to the high dive
I fucking run off that shit I do
I use all the techniques I've learned
away I'm sorry I forgot I forgot before
before I get to that in the middle
of my of my session the lowest point
as I was I was on my learning
montage there's a moment where
I've learned a couple of skills I've done this a couple times
I'm getting to the end of the board
but all of a sudden panic strikes me as
I'm afraid that I'm gonna fuck it up and increase my pain
it's just the agony is gonna rise over and over
and as I'm I'm like I've got like one
toe loony tune style I'm dangling off
the end I'm trying to pull myself out so I can
fix my posture and I just yell to the heavens
I'm gonna goof it
and then I slowly tumble off
the edge and fall and this was the
this was whenever this is the big the big flop
that no one was no one was on my side
but as I said
I immediately turned against you started
pelting you with garbage that's exactly
what happened okay but as I said
I eventually I managed to do one solid
flip and I'm cocky as hell so I go off to the high dive
okay I'm on the high dive
everyone's cheering the applause
everyone's saying this is the boy this is the golden man
he did one flip and meanwhile
there was like this girl who did like triple fucking front flips
and pirouettes off the fucking
thing it was embarrassing nonetheless
now is my time to shine I go
I climb the high dive I attempt
to do the perfect dive
I've studied the techniques I know what I'm doing now
I feel myself launching off the
end of the board I'm rotating into
midair 90 degrees 180 degrees
what's after that
270 360 but
but oh god
I'm still going I haven't hit I'm
overcorrecting I'm still rotating
my back is literally 180
degree parallel to the water down below
I
I rotate once more or something like
that and my my I feel myself
time stops I am floating
spread eagle arms
wide legs wide hanging
floating one inch above the water
a perfect belly flop position
and then time begins
again and I hit the water
the impact
of this of this impact
now this was a successful flip I did
a successful flip but the cost
the cost of this this is
what's been known to you know that people
in ancient Rome
people in ancient Greece they speculated the source
of thunder they did not know what caused
lightning to happen it was this
it was this is what God was
doing belly flops and this is exactly what happened
to me off the 10 foot fucking
high dive the impact
of this again was reported
to me later to cause every woman
in the vicinity to lose
all chance of giving birth at the sheer
lack of sexuality present
in this environment they're all fertile
they're all infertile forever all
the men all their dicks were treated into
their bodies and the sound of this
happened all the nearby children
and I I I emerged back
to the surface literally unable
to move my arms due to the searing
agony in every part of my fucking
body and if you
look close if you look close
at the image I'm uploading right now
you can see that in fact not a lie this is
100% accurate I am literally
bleeding out of my nose because the
impact on my face and skull
fucked up my neck and
fucked up my face my nose was
actually damaged and it
bled for a good long while after this
everyone
you see the blood there's blood
in that nose yeah you can see that
just a little just a little
blood there just a little
little bit of blood look at the little blood
that's that's all you need
that's all you need and
you know I did it because
I did my fucking flip I did
my flip off the high dive you should
quit while you were ahead the consequences
now I don't know if you can see this you got to raise the contrast
but the red was on my entire
body it had begun to fade at this point
but my whole body
is seething I feel it right now my right
leg is gone
it doesn't exist anymore it was destroyed
by the impact the force was too much
anyway that's it people
I did it I fucking did it but this was
this was the peak moment of pain
probably in the last I don't know
10 years of my life or so well I
was smashing the flesh Nate was
splashing the flesh
oh that's right Ben that's right
and that's why I'm a winner
I didn't give up though
I'm a champ I did it but the cost
will haunt me from never be the same
that's all there is to it well you know I also
have a I also have a story
of great triumphs and great falls
speaking of you know pushing
your body past its physical limits
of being proud of accomplishing something
instead of just being straight which anyone
can do the gays are pretty bad at it
though to be fair I finally
started going to the gym every day
I got a membership I started kicking
my body's ass into shape oh my god
that's great I was I started going there with
one yeah going for a couple months
he looks great he's lost like he's been
going every single night he's lost like 30
pounds fantastic great so
I messaged them I'm like hey one let's go
I'm going to the gym with you today and he's like
hell yeah dude so I fucking
go there you know I'm a guest the first
couple days but I get my membership
I'm hanging out in the massage chairs afterwards
you know and like he's there to like help me
and motivate me it's so fucking easy when
there's like a guy with you like a friend
it's a huge benefit no doubt
you know like I've never like
I've never had the courage to go in
the gym but once I was in there
I was blown away at how fucking easy
it is to work out it is it's just so
boring when it's when you're by yourself
yeah it's a drag so
I've been going there every day and I'm
and I'm you know I'm doing my I got my
fucking my blue raspberry pre-workout
I got my fucking muscle milk
post-workout I'm fucking pumping
iron I'm getting the fucking pump
I'm fucking I'm making
all my own meals I'm cooking myself
just fucking meats and fucking steaks and shit
I'm not eating any garbage except
the other day my mom got me a fucking quarter
pounder that I had to eat so she wouldn't feel bad
yep yep but that doesn't count so I
I know the feeling well
that's fantastic once you're the hardest
thing by far is getting the momentum
up once you're in the swing
that's that's the golden zone and I was
I was so I've been so proud
of myself and like like experiencing
legit the first good
mood I've had in like four years
it's a legit mood booster it is working out
and the pride you feel from doing it
I've been working out for maybe two months
now and like and yeah
I definitely just feel like
more positive emotionally
it's great yeah like I like
right after the first day like I
thought that like I'll I'd be
I'm gonna be tired at first and it's gonna like
really make me miserable I'm not gonna want to go
immediately like I just like I look
forward to it every day it's like
the best part of my day I come home
and I feel like I did something with my day
no matter what else happened and fucking
this makes me so happy the fucking you know
even the soreness it feels good it feels
proud to feel sore yeah
yeah yeah yeah it was just
fucking cool and I have a good time there and it was great
and so I've been going every
day we've been working out we've been fucking
motivating each other it's been super cool
the only bad part of it
is the only bad part of everything
in my life which is other
people coming up talking to me
bothering me being fucking weird
being autistic being freaks fucking
mutants I am a mutant magnet
everywhere I go in my life everything I do
someone's gonna fucking come up to me doesn't
matter if I've got fucking like earbuds in
you know someone's gonna fucking start
talking you know and like especially going
with one because he's like a social
butterfly and he's been there for a while so he knows everybody
at the gym so all of his like gym friends
are coming up also talking to me
and like trying to there's like this one guy
who like the one
guy who was not
super bad but he was
like fuck you know he was just like
talking to me about stuff I didn't care about like
Star Wars like oh the new clone war series
is gonna be great I love Darth Maul
and like getting like like slightly
too into it we're like
Darth Maul you know he's real evil let me
tell you how evil Darth Maul is and why
Star Wars is great
and fucking I'm just like yeah Darth Maul
cool you know I'm being friendly
I'm doing my version of attempting
to be friendly and he's
like you know the first part
of my winter soldier costume came I got
a knife in the mail
and I'm like oh cool
but then like as I'm leaving I hear him like
talking to the gym workers
telling the same story like ah the first
part of my winter soldier costume came and I got
knife and I'm like okay this guy's
really proud of that and then as I'm getting
in my car I see him at like another
car talking to another guy in the parking lot
telling the same story a third time
ah my fucking winter soldier costume
came and I'm like that guy hadn't heard yet I guess
and I'm like oh okay
I mean I sure do hate people fucking talking
to me but I'm not bothered by it
I'm just I'm having fun at the gym
it's gonna I'm gonna so I
I can't stand that just as an aside
like that I can't
understand that and I definitely don't
like the
I hate repeating myself whenever
I have to tell somebody something yeah
and then somebody comes in the room I'm like oh for fuck's
sake you I have to say it
to you as well like it
if I hear if I say something and they don't hear
me and then I say it again and they don't hear like I
have to say something a third time I'll just say fuck
it I don't it doesn't matter who cares it could be like the
fate of the world it could be like press the blue
button or else we all die and I would
not say it a third time I'm like you didn't hear
bro just let us all
fucking die um
yeah people's fucking bizarre need
for friendliness and fucking coming up
you know don't be friendly to me
don't I hate friendly people
I fucking I'm not here to make friends
I'm just here to kick my own ass
so that I can take my shirt off at the beach and ride
a surfboard and enjoy my life for the
first time ever and not hate myself
for the first time in my life that's all
I'm here don't bother me you know Juan
can bother me Juan can fucking talk to me
all the time because he's my he's my guy
he's the dude I'm there with it's awesome
you're on the right yeah you know so I
think like it was two days two nights ago
I went there and
this time I got there early
I got there before Juan so you know
usually like we hit the treadmill and then
we go to the weights so
by the time Juan got in I was done with the
treadmill so I was doing the weights before
him so I was you know getting my workout
my workout was just about you know done
my arms retired I felt good about
myself but then Juan's just starting
his time on the weights so I go to
join him and there's this other guy next
to him that he knows this fucking like huge
like really beefy like clearly
like a veteran gym guy
he's there and him and Juan are
fucking working out together and lifting the weights
and so you know I joined them and I
am saying now now keep in mind
Juan is fresh as a daisy
I am like at the
end of my workout my arms are fucking
tired so I'm so I'm
fucking struggling a bit you know with
even like the 15s I'm struggling
because I'm fucking I'm done
but you know this guy
with Juan who does not know me
at all we've never met ever
is like he starts
like nagging me like the whole time
like giving me this like this
this like patronizing
Confucius says gym wisdom
like control the weights
don't let them control you
thanks that means absolutely
fucking nothing did you read that at the
back of a fucking cereal box asshole
you know and so I'm
you know I'm just like trying to ignore it like
okay this guy's fucking annoying the shit out of me
but and then he's like starts when he's like
come on man work your muscles
don't play with them and I'm like what the fuck
dude that's embarrassing
yeah and like
I am a beginner and it is embarrassing a little
bit to be around like better no I mean
him those things he's saying are embarrassing
yeah I know they are
yeah and like so I'm just
ignoring and he just keeps going with this fucking
Confucius says bullshit
and just fucking I'm just getting a fucking
migraine from listening to it and finally
like you know we're all like standing
with the little ways doing a little bicep curls
and in a line by the mirror
and I'm fucking you know I'm struggling
with mine because I'm tired and I fucking I'm like okay
I'm doing seven I go down to a lower
weight and do the rest of the ten and
just so and
and he starts like really fucking
like nagging me and he's like
what do you hear for
why are you here why are you here
what do you hear for and and like
I've never had shit like that
I I fucking snapped
and I just I looked at him and I said
are you trying to motivate me right now
and he goes yeah and I
go don't and I just
fucking walked away and I fucking
I would you know and I
went to the I went to the treadmill
and I just did my fucking mile I
did I did like this I did this angry
like stone cold walking to the ring to
stun or somebody the most pissed off
mile I've ever the easiest mile I've
ever fucking walked because I was so
pissed off I couldn't feel my legs burning
I just wanted the world to fucking burn around
with me so I just fucking did my
mile and I left I didn't even say goodbye to Juan
I didn't say shit you know I just you know
I fucking I just
told the guy fucking don't don't fucking
do this don't talk to me and I just
fucking left and so then
I'm driving back home
in my car and I'm feeling pissed off
and
you know and Juan messages me
and he's like hey what happened
man where'd you go I'm just like nothing guy talk
to me like an asshole so I left
you know like I'm like it's
one thing if it's you
you can say whatever you want to me dude you
can criticize me you can help me you can give
me all the pointers you want
but this fucking guy does not know me
you know there's a balance
to be found there for sure
I wanted to shove the fucking dumbbell
down his fucking throat because you gotta
establish a rapport with someone before you
yeah do that
to like sit there and try to like to try to
patronize me like I'm being lazy
like you don't know like what it took
for me to even get to this point in my life
when I am here at the gym every
day at all doing as much as I am
this is the most I've ever done I'm fucking
proud of myself don't fucking stand
there and try to take it away from me
you piece of fucking dog shit
asshole cock sucking mother fucking moron
idiot I'm sure he had good intentions
I'm sure I
I don't like
I don't like how he did it I don't like
it either yeah I mean if somebody said that
to me I'd be like what the fuck are you talking about
dude that that kind of shit
guys like that that that is exactly the
reason I didn't go to the gym for
the first 30 years of my life and it's
exactly the reason why millions of people
don't because it's fucking
embarrassing and patronizing and
like mean and shitty
like I get that like you know
one knows the guy so he can you know that's
one thing for one it's motivational
and that's what he said like one's messaging me on the way
home he's like yeah he didn't mean anything he's trying to
motivate you and I'm like I know dude
and it you know but he doesn't know me
and I'm fucking pissed off
and then you know one such a sweetheart
the coolest guy ever my brother
you know one's like you know
well you know I talked to him
and I stood up for you and I
and I told him that and
you know I hope this doesn't stop you from
coming in and I'm like
buddy it won't don't worry I'll be in
there tomorrow same as every day and
then you then I went home and I
watched Detective Pikachu and I cried
because the fucking emotional toll
was so fucking I was
I was feeling really hormonal
because like the combination of my
of my rage
at this guy and like my
love for Juan and his brotherly kindness
standing up for me in the gym
after I left you know I don't know exactly
what he must have said to the guy but I'm assuming
that what he said is that the guy said
hey weird your friend go man
and I'm just assuming that Juan looked at him
and in his best Lars Ulrich
voice said he fucking
left the gym!
hahaha
oh baby there you
go
you know I don't know about you guys I have a lot
of faith look I've been in
decent shape like okay shape
for last several years but this like meme
it's like a stereotype of guys like
getting hot in their 30s getting like
swollen ripped and stuff it fills me
with a lot of confidence that no matter
what I do I will inevitably
be swole in my 30s this
is where my thinking goes I don't
know why but it seems to like happen
it makes sense it makes sense every time I see
a guy in his 40s he's got that like
that weathered like rip
shit body yeah
I believe it I think it's just a natural
thing there's natural progression
you get fucking swole
I knew a girl growing up
I guess I won't say her name but like her dad
was just so fucking
swole it was like insane he's just like some
normal like super nice guy
he was like a leader in our Boy Scout trip
weird how much hotter he was
than like every other person around
what a fucking badass he just did
Bowflex every day I don't
I don't remember who you're talking about
but okay he might have been
he was like a younger guy's dad
so he might have joined like after you left
or something I don't know I don't know
okay whatever whatever should we go to
voicemail yeah I think we're ready
what do you have something
um well I have one quick
story sure feel free
but it's really just like a change
I cut my hair
oh my god how short is it
I have short hair now
do you have pictures
I don't like
showing pictures
okay just give us an idea of how short
well it's not like a buzz cut
it's okay
my I don't know
what like shaving things
are called like are we talking
Ronald Weasley length Harry Potter length
I'm using examples you'll understand
those are like the same length
uh nah
it's like they said it was a number
six something on the razor
okay that's yeah okay that makes sense to me
so
you know it's it's the
strangely doesn't feel that different
I thought it would be like oh my god my head
can move in so many other different directions
it can't it's the same
um some people expecting a big power
upgrade yeah I was expecting
I was expecting like I was like
you know taking off the weights and now suddenly
my neck could go 100 miles an hour
you're like Goku and Krillin taking off the
turtle shells yeah exactly
um
apparently according to
my mom
and also and also some just
random people who were at a party a few days
later I looked younger
and I looked good and dude
I assume
I assume they're telling the truth
we'll tell you the truth
dude we'll fucking roast you
we'll kill you
we will murder you
this is this is why I was like a little hesitant
about like saying yes to posting
the uh the wizard
flying on a broomstick thing because I didn't
wear a hat and you could see
you could see my fucking hairline
I must see
uh
I'll think about it I'll think about it
I don't actually have a picture yet
you're just gonna hide your face until it grows
back and pretend nothing happened
yeah yeah that's that's
that's the plan
any uh any reason for the change in
particular um well
I've been feeling like
I don't do anything
with the fact that my hair is long
like I just have it long because it's been long for
a while and
really it started
at secondary schools like like
almost a decade of having
long curly hair
and I got bullied for it and I guess
in my in my efforts to
like defy bullies
I just didn't do what they wanted me to do
and get normal hair
and so I had weird hair forever
and uh some people like it
but um
I'm tired of not being normal and having
people stare at me all the time
fair enough fair enough
also it's really hot and it's just like
yeah you know I understand now
why it's a good idea to cut it
I bet it looks good
I have I'm optimistic about it
I agree
that's why I want to see it so I can confirm my suspicions
okay
yeah I'll take a picture I'll take a picture
yeah yeah yeah do it
yeah yeah excellent not right now
I'll do it after the show okay
fair okay well in the meantime then
we will let let's let's move things along
we'll get back to this uh speak pipe
people link below leave us voicemails
uh make a good or fuck you
one one last note if you want to see
if you want to see my pictures
from the protests uh
follow me on twitter at it's also ugly
with two else I did actually
already link the your tweet specifically
in the notes so uh yeah click those links
then you'll be at Ben's page yes there you go check them out
okay uh all right
speak pipe here we go we've got
a voicemail first from rad
lectures
uh okay let's hear what he has go
PCP
uh I was really intrigued
you guys talked about rad con last episode
uh I got pretty hyped
um question was
about lectures and basically
every single one of you provided some
sort of idea for what you want to do
besides one person
uh Nate you completely dodged
the fucking question
but a bigger question for you guys
as creators as a whole
do you like to hype up
the creation
of a video
or piece of work that you guys do
or do you like to keep things
secret because I sort of
get that vibe more from
Nate more than anyone here just because
of that last question
I do not like to hype stuff up
ahead of time but if I have
an opportunity to do so I
will sometimes do it
because I think it's a good idea
even though I don't like to do it
it's not it's not fun
I enjoy
um the feeling of having
a hype thing that I could tell
people and I like keeping it
special for the people
who are like cool like if I
if I meet like um
like lemon tart I met in London
he was he was a cool guy and I like him
and you know he showed me around
Madrid and so he was asking me
about stuff and so I told
him a few plans I had and they
weren't like fully formed yet but it was
just sort of like you know
he's he's really nice and he's
in person I think this is a good time
to like to allow that like it
seems strange to do it
online because
um people bullshitting
online it yeah much more
like like nobody knows
what they want and when you show them
the coolest thing ever then they're
just just good it's just good to keep it
under wraps until there's something
substantial but in person
I feel like if it can make for good
conversation then I'll I'll hype someone up
that's fair it's it's
you talked about this too
uh speaking of hype I guess
I was thinking about whether I should
do this but I do need
to hype this up and I I think
okay I can't 100% guarantee
this but I am almost ready
and I think that maybe
a week from when you are listening
to this podcast the Vapors
Kickstarter 2
may be live so
a week from right now
you might hear me saying hey
go to Kickstarter right now link in the description
the Kickstarter is a go because we are
I am I like I said
I yeah that that
John Cleese lecture I watch that because
I was like I need to get my shit together
and I watch that and I was like I feel better
now and now I understand what I have to do a little better
and I've been doing it and I have written
four out of the six
scripts that I needed to do
for the for the guest strips so we are
almost ready and possibly next week
the Kickstarter will be launching
yeah so the hi I
don't really
I don't really like doing hype even though
it's a good idea like it's a good idea
to hype up a thing before you do it
yeah I like just
putting something out there and having people
see it that that's the
good that's the fun part not the hyping
is the is the reaction to the thing
I think the the best
way to go about it is to hype
vaguely so like
I'm gonna do a thing on this date is like
what what what things are you gonna do and that makes
that builds that builds hype
for people to be
anticipating something
but they don't like have an idea
of what they should be expecting necessarily
I mean you know if you make
want if you make videos or comics
or whatever they're gonna be assuming
it's one of those
but they you know the the Vega
you keep it it feels like a lot of
brands are doing this as well
and movie trailers as well
the very
maybe not movie trailers I don't keep up
those trailers that are just there are just
for example just a logo like bayonetta 3
yeah we saw and and and
Star Wars is like there's nothing in the
trailer like I've seen it I was like
well cool I guess
nothing there's nothing there
maybe there's nothing in the movie
but it's still it still builds
hype just as effectively because people are being
reminded that a thing is about to come out
and when it comes out they will be
ready and willing and able to listen
and watch rather than if you
just posted it people
might not like catch on
because there was no nothing you know to
to remind them to pay attention
that's true
you know
on the subject here I mean first of all
the person astutely noted I did not
comment on my thing that that is in fact
deliberate because I didn't want
I mean whatever like I just
as exactly as you said I like to keep
things secretive and I'll tell you
there's multiple reasons why one is because
I find the hype cycle
both kind of counterproductive
I mean in this way of like tell like look at the ghost in the shell
thing when it's kind of counterproductive
and like it
can it put and the other things it puts
expectations
on things that I think are not actually helpful
and I almost think it's
almost kind of immoral
in a sense to like
like what if you fail then it's like
you've kind of disappointed
everyone and like they were wrong
to it's almost like you lied
if you have promised something then you don't deliver
what people expect I don't know that one's a little more bullshit
yeah I very much
I very much dislike the
stress of promising anything
like once I
once I like let it known
that I'm going to do something then it becomes
an obligation and I don't want to do it
yes that's a big part of it too
whereas when I can drop something I just prefer
to surprise people yeah that's all positive
there's no expectation and it feels good
and I think everyone's kind of better off that way
but I will be super clear on another
reason why I do it
another reason why I hate to announce project is
in case
they fall through or I fail
or it isn't as good
as like I might have
hyped it up to be things of that nature
I do not want to be
the guy who fails to live up to
expectations I want to be the guy
who provided something even if it's only
mildly entertaining because it's
a lot better than failing people's
expectations in my in my opinion
on the other hand hyping
a thing up it it it affects
me like part of
like saying that I'm
going to be launching the Kickstarter
next week makes it a lot more likely
that I will actually do it
that's definitely true that all right
that's a thing but like
I mean assume
not as much about it is like
a creative process it's mostly just like to
actually create the Kickstarter and do all the
busy work well it's half and half because I
have to write the scripts but right
but like I feel
like a hyping up something that you have
to be creative for
is a little more like
nuanced and how
like variable and how well it works
because you might just lose
like your focus or like you won't
have an idea or you won't be able to think
of something creative enough if you still have
to do like all the creative work
before the thing is realized and like you don't
really know how it's going to turn out
while you're hyping it
but you know on this one thing I am
somewhat assuaged in my fears
by the fact that like
for example when we were planning Radcon 3
like one of my worries was that like we'll
make things that are bad but like
I've really have come to the
conclusion during Radcon 2
2 but like working with you guys on
that content I was worried to be bullshit
but like it just seems to almost
magically happen that we just
make good stuff so like
at this point I feel comfortable saying like
if we did Radcon 4 tomorrow I'd be like
guys give to Radcon 4 I know it will be
good I have all the confidence in the
world we will make things people enjoy
even though I don't know at all what those things
will be we just produce
products that are enjoyable
and that's a pretty powerful
thing that makes me feel good
you gotta believe in the process
at some point at some level you kinda just gotta
have confidence and believe in yourself
and to say and to promise like I'm gonna
make this thing you kinda just have to like
trust that you can do
it and like a lot
of the time just believing that you can
do it will empower
you to do it I feel good
I also have acquired
a sense that like if I sit down
and decide I'm going to make a project I
feel confident that I can
make almost anything I wanna do
good and entertaining and enjoyable
but the issue that I
have with all this is like the logistics
and the time management of making
sure I get to these things and get them done
and like now it's like I gotta
make money while doing it cause it's my job and stuff
like will I be able to
balance all those things?
That for me is the big variable question
cause you know like I wanted to
have like a big video out every month
once I was like pro doing this stuff
but like I've had tough time managing
my time with we Aguas and doing other stuff
it's like I have not done that yet and it's been two months
so like that's that's this is
my big concern with stuff like this
I okay do you guys
remember that idea I had for a lecture
I mentioned it in the chat
do you remember and I'm not sure if I should say it
why don't you type it
we will not say it but if you type it in the chat
I will say it in gross disgusting audio
okay
does that ring a bell
a little bit
oh yeah a little bit
I'm not sure should I say it
I forget what it is
I don't know what that is yeah
but it would
oh
oh that's right
um I mean up to you dog
I don't know I think it's unlikely
you'll actually do it personally but
oh that sounds like a fucking challenge
I don't know I'm not sure if it's
I guess I would have to actually
do some work and start like
taking notes for it and like
figure out whether it would make a good lecture
I agree
but I find it personally compelling
is the uh
alright I'll just say it
I'll say it with the caveat that I
guaranteeing that I will do it but it is on the table
is um
projared and holly conrad
thing their whole affair and whatever
it was predicated
like they
had characters in the same d&d campaign
and like this
their characters in the game
crossed over into real life because
like they like
the dimensional merge is literally real
the dimensional merge took place it started with them
they kicked it all off
Chris didn't know but this is what started it
and because like
Heidi was like texting them and talking
about their characters fucking which leads
to the inevitable conclusion that they were doing
like roleplay fucking in character
as their d&d character and I thought
it would be pretty funny to do a lecture
doing like the history
of their d&d characters
and like like where and all that
and how this whole
like the same way that like the
sonichu lecture is talking about sonichu
and in doing so
you must discuss Chris
this would be an in-character thing about the narrative
of Diath and Strix
and like who they are and what their story is
and you know it would inevitably cross over
into the real life
story and I thought it was a funny idea
it's a funny idea
I'm just curious about it
I think we spoke about this briefly but like
did Jared's recent video where he
made at least a pretty good comeback
many people say it seems
true to me too
no I watch it I was just curious
did that move the dial for you much
I already knew everything
that he said in that video
because like
I'd been following the story and like I talked to
Bedhead Bernie as he was making his
he asked me for like my input on it and stuff
I see
that was all stuff I already knew
and I don't think it exonerates
I don't think Jared is like 100% exonerated
of everything he did like I still think having
like Nude's fan tumbler is gross
but I do think that a lot of the stuff people
were saying about him is like
just like bad faith and wrong
and should be
and should be dismissed
I happen to watch H3's reaction to his new
video I think earlier today and I have not
man that boy was like he had said like
I had already dismissed the things
because there was enough evidence but he was
really mad at him for having this fan
server thing
I will not defend the fan server
I don't well I defended the sense that it's legal
but not in the sense of anything I would ever do
yeah sure it's legal
lots of gross things are legal
that's true that's true
fair enough
but you know what I will say
interestingly enough is that his wife
at the time clearly knew about it
and condoned it
that's absolutely true
let's not forget that if we're taking sides
fair enough
well shit let's go into our next voicemail
let me get it right here
okay this one is from
our boy Mozilla Fennekin
is writing it again now if I remember correctly
did we just send him to jail last
I think we sent him because he was the one you had
the human core guy right
yeah he said that the most human core thing
is having a toilet
factually inactive
I just want to say
completely debunked by the existence of pigs
because pigs like
a known fact about them is they always
shit the furthest away
in a specific place the furthest away from where they sleep
and eat
that's true but we found an article of like animals that do this
animal latrines
animal latrines is like a phenomenon in nature
fucking idiot
a lot of species do it
let's see if he has any defense for himself
okay go
hey guys Mozilla fuckface here
just taking a good shit I got on this litter box
I got for myself in voice jail
you know I gotta say it's actually pretty nice in here
there's literally no security in here whatsoever
so I used my white girl privilege
to ask to speak to the manager
but there was no one around
so I guess that means I'm the
manager now
anyway I've been rethinking this whole human core
thing and I think it's super human core
to be looking at drawings of people
but they're not actually people
and there's so many drawings that it looks
like the not people are moving
it just got me thinking uh what's
your favorite anime hit me back I want
to know more about what human core
really is
he's clearly having too easy
a time in jail we gotta confiscate his
litter box
he's reveling in the attention he gets
from being put in jail
he's not okay
we gotta send like what's the word
isolation tank
is the PCP hail
yeah start the pcb hail in pcb jail
let's see if he can pelt it with
rocks of ice and shit
all right uh moving on
let's go to I don't know
that I even have a favorite anime
um I mean it's I don't know
we're deliberately not answering this question
we're deliberately not I mean you could
but no it's I just maybe think like I don't know
if I even have one I know bakumon
is my favorite manga but I don't know if I have a favorite
anime the thing about this question
is that nobody asks it sincerely
so I'm not gonna give a sincere answer
exactly the right attitude looks like
I fucked up
all right we go to in my PJ's
by the freeway okay go
all right
so real quick wanted to go over
some things that are more human
core than just bathrooms
or something like that yeah
so we've got let's see
there's
sweating sweating to cool down
human started doing it because
they needed
the evaporative cooling properties
because they were endurance renters
uh like they used it for
hunting uh and so the only
other animal that does it uh
that sweats as much as we do to cool down
our horses and uh
really like we could
do it better than them if you if you like
trained to be an endurance runner you could
outrun a horse um yeah wait
what hippos also do it like over
overall like for sunscreen so it's like not
the same thing hippo's horse
humans hmm yeah we also
keep pets which is pretty human core
um nothing else
really keeps pets uh
at least that I know of symbiotic relationships
or a thing but like
there's a type of toad that keeps spiders
as a pet think about it
uh also munchy I'm an RA uh just so you know
um if you want your
RA to hate you just don't be the loud dorm
or the one that smells like weed
uh yeah that's about it
adios
do you say frogs keep spiders as pets
there there's I've seen an image
of a little toad and like it on a blog
a while ago and it was really cute
uh there's either it was a large
toad that kept
like a small tarantula as a pet
that would eat bugs and bring it to him
or it was a large tarantula that kept a tiny
toad as a pet um
I don't know I don't know the situation
but they both eat the same thing
so I suppose there's just sort of like
you know their buddies
like like the tarantula drains the fluids
out of it and then he gives like the husks to the frog
something something of that nature
like they they both hunt the same thing
and like one is fed with the thing
or it might be like the toad utilizes
the spider's web
something strange and funny super cool
uh but the domestication of animals
is pretty human okay I
yeah I feel like there's a lot of misunderstanding to me
okay just something that humans do
is not human core sweating
yeah I know humans sweat and we are
not many other animals sweat like we do
that doesn't that's not human core
human core action is an action
that humans are driven to do
for no other for no
like good purpose
that does not serve any end so like
the domestication of animals I would not say
is strictly human core because animals are domesticated
for like practical purposes
but like keeping like house cats
or something or keeping like keeping
pets just for fun like that's human core
I definitely agree
I definitely agree yeah
is fun is having fun
for fun sake human core
dogs play though
then again we made dogs
by humans so like we shaped them in our image
maybe a little bit you know in our image
yes you guys ever you guys ever just have
a moment where you're like what the fuck
is this podcast that I'm on
um yes because
that's all I feel when I'm hearing
well you know humans are the only
people who sweat but also horses
sweat so I guess it's not totally giving
a lecture on like what animals sweat out of
their buttholes or whatever and I'm just sitting here
like how did I get
we're just doing what screen ranted we have to come
up with catchphrases to engage our audience
and human core is one of them so we've
got to be scattershot and just say shit
like I found it interesting that
hey guys and hippos are all lumped
together in one or else
I'm just being cool
we're the reason people are dying
you know what what was that
cool catchphrase I came up with the other day
I can't quite it was something like
uh having sex
with women and licking pussy
iconic
that sounds right that's my
famous catchphrase
I'm gonna work that into every conversation
this podcast is no overall theme
it's just we've got to touch on we've got to touch
on all the all the big winners hey guys
sorry I'm late I was just
having sex with women
and licking pussy
oh you're always doing it
that's no excuse
alright let's go on to retarded
hermy frog man
okay uh go
wait that guy sounds cool
hey pcp thought I'd provide some intergagement
please yeah last episode you guys
talked about conspiracies and I got a story
for this so I want to say
two to three years ago
when Alex Jones was like more of a
big meme you know there's really
there's really popular clip going around
I noticed as a young lad
back in high school
he said something kind of insane
you know he said
the water is turning the frickin
frogs gay
he thought that was a pretty insane statement
at the time right
you know back in the day
fast forward
a year or two
senior year in high school for me
I take a zoology class
okay
study of animals and stuff
and I gotta say
it's
fucking true
the water is turning the frickin
frogs gay
I don't remember exactly what it is
but we had a guest come into our zoology class
who explained something
about like how chemicals in the water
legitimately turns
frogs into like hermaphrodites
okay this is the worst voicemail I've ever heard
and it was insane it was like the most
insane revelation for me
like last year with me
and my friends we were like
holy shit
this sucks really bad
seriously
that's garbage
we all know
a lot of frogs are naturally hermaphroditic
I mean that's literally the plot of Jurassic Park
it's literally not
the same thing as being gay
so there's no connection here
man
there was so much build up
I knew exactly where this was going
the moment I heard his name
and frankly I'm shocked and appalled
I had suspicions
people put so much
emphasis on stuff that Alex Jones says
like he's so crazy
he's the modern day Nostradamus
people just
you know he clearly has
a sense of humor
he does exaggerate these things
he is on some level being funny
when he says stuff like
the water's turning the frickin frogs gay
he's not a totally sincere
he's just exaggerating for
comedic effect
he's saying that there's bad chemicals
and pollution that are messing up the environment
but he's saying it in a funny way
and everyone takes it completely seriously
because people are literally
much stupider than Alex Jones
this guy could
have done a little bit of research
to find out what he was talking about
but instead
he just says hey guys
remember a guy told me one time
that this thing was sort of
adjacent to true and I can't
elaborate on that at all but isn't that crazy guys
no
it sounds like the problem here
is the conflation between hermaphroditic
and gay
that's a problem
it's just the old plot point
from Jurassic Park where they're like
we had some missing building blocks of the DNA
so we used frog DNA but then Ellie Sadler
was like oh but some of the frogs can turn hermaphroditic
but all the dinosaurs are female
but then some of the life finds a way
he says Jeff Goldblum and then they fucking
the hermaphroditic frog DNA
makes them into penises and they have
dinosaur babies damn it
that's everyone knows that shit
wow that's like
biology 101
okay well whatever
fuck that guy next one
we got Mr. Bones speaking of bone
here's Mr. Bones old friend
okay go
what's up my n words
Mr. Bones here
call me because I wanted to pick your brains
about streaming
we've seen renowned creators like
Demo D star and German
move to twitch and leave their youtube channels
to gather dust
most of you have been involved with streaming to some extent
so I'd just like to know
if you'd ever think of transitioning from your current
style of content to mostly streaming
it is ostensibly
quicker and easier and makes more money
so I can see the appeal
but is it something you do full time
as your main source of content
also on top of that question
I'd like to give you some warm congratulations
on the last episode of the PCP
which managed to not have a 20 minute political
shitfest sandwiched somewhere in the middle
you're welcome Mr. Bones
I'm going to treat my vile layer now
slice and dice brothers
I have
people seem to start people are starting
to notice in the comments finally
that
when Jesse is on the podcast
magically it seems to be much
much better every single time
and that when he's
off the podcast for long stretches of time
everything just slowly
devolves into shit
it's all about you Jesse
these Jesse stands in the comments have got to go
it's all tribalism
yeah
and my tribe needs to win
to the guy's question though
so the thing about
I think about streaming like this
I almost feel like streaming
take H3HB for example
you have to build up a reason
for people to give a shit about you
and that needs to be done with
projects that matter
things you do that influence people
and then you can coast off that
by streaming
I don't think that's necessarily true
I don't know if anyone has just gotten
famous purely through streaming
on Twitch
but nobody's famous
for that initially
are they?
absolutely
Ninja was a big just came out
he was a Fortnite streamer
but there must have been something about Ninja
that made people gravitate to him other than
just the fact that he streamed on Twitch
no that literally is it
there is more
he was a literal competitive
to semi-professional
if you go on Twitch
and you just search for the game that you're interested in
and a guy comes up that's how you
find people on Twitch
YouTube does not have a monopoly on discovering people
though it is easier
well
I follow this guy
T90
who was a Twitch streamer
who does commentary over
people doing
competitive Age of Empires 2
things
unironically incredibly engaging
and I love it
it's my favorite game
but at a super high level
and his streams are good
I don't watch his streams
but he started uploading to YouTube
and now I know him as a YouTuber
where he uploads entire streams
or entire matches
from his streams
you can easily go from one to the other
he didn't do anything before Twitch
there was just a guy who got popular
because he was good at what he did
and he did a game where there was a strong
community
the only reason I'd like
right now
my Twitch is basically like an interaction
vehicle for people who are interested
and then also like an excuse to play some games
and do bantery stuff
so like it's fun but it's not my prime focus
I could theoretically see myself in theory
becoming a full-time streamer
for example if
was gratifying to do
and was creatively
fulfilling in some way
and also made sense financially
if that was the case I'd consider it
but I feel like I'm always going to want to do
like right now I'm doing a lot of
Viagra's
what I want to be doing all day
is editing fancy big videos
that I have a little bit of time for
I'm working on fixing my schedule and stuff
but this is what I passionately want to do
so that's always going to be there
and that's why I fucking quit my computer science job
everybody fucking programming job
like if I'm just going to do a job
that's not like better than that
that's just equally just fill in time
and be in a drag and just got to put in the hours in
like I could just do my much better
paying programming job
so I got to make us you know
I think I started
I see streaming as like
kind of a yeah I wouldn't want to do it
full-time it doesn't seem
it's not very creatively fulfilling
and I kind of just see it as like
a time during the week when I can like
interact with like you know
the people in my discord and stuff
because like I'm in my discord a bit but I'm not like
I'm not like chatting a whole lot in there
just here and there so I feel like that's
my time when like people who want to
you know interact with me
or people who like
you know are in you know
my extended community or whatever
who like maybe just want to like touch
base with all like that like that's the time
when I do that and it makes a bit of
money be just because I think some people like
you know have twitch bits that they
you know certain people prefer different
platforms and some people want to
would rather donate through twitch with bits
or something than they would through I don't know
patreon or kofi or whatever
and you know that's it's you know it's
that's another reason to do it to diversify
your platforms so
I guess my short answer is no
I don't want to do it like I wouldn't
transition and I don't
I don't know if it makes more money
I don't know this Mr. Bones
you know with all due respect
Mr. Bone I don't know if you can say that twitch
just makes more money I mean for some people I'm sure it does
but it's definitely not the case for everybody
that twitch is like a more
lucrative thing
from what I understand to be big
on twitch you need to stream like
every second of every day of your life
yeah so like
the like the workload floor
is incredibly high but at that
floor the pay is a lot better
than youtube so like
most people on twitch
for like I mean they're working the long hours
but they're working like not very hard
like comparatively like
they're not being an editor and a director
and a and a voice over
guy or whatever they're not animating anything
to be in a fucking stream it is it is
pretty exhausting but like
there's the yeah you said obstin obstin
obstincibly and I think that's the word
that's correct it's obstincibly
better money
on youtube
I feel like the workload floor is
much lower
but the
the point of which
you can be successful
by not doing that much work
or like putting in the hours
I'm trying to think of a
like a phrase for this
off the top of my head
like if you get a viral hit or something
I don't know
like I don't know what people
viral on twitch in the same way
not really
they have to be like even ninja
I know was like
streaming for a long time and then
suddenly like like sort of
exponential growth because of
algorithm or whatever it was over there
like you just he was playing the right game
of the right time and
everybody shared him with everybody else
and then you became the biggest thing on twitch
um but
uh
I forgot the point I was making
I'm still with my boy Dr. Disrespect
his production values are insane
I think everything
there's one great streamer it's Dr. Disrespect
he has changed the fucking game I'm so
impressed I don't watch it that often I did
for a little bit I mean I think that you
I think that streaming can be
you know a creative medium
and can be just fulfilling
when Dr. Disrespect works
for I'm sure he works with editors and like people
preparing stuff and they like make a really
cool effect that he will unveil
like at some point like like him I told
the story before about like I was watching he press
the button boom camera transitions
now it's like it's literally him
like standing small he's not he stands
up out of his chair now it's like he's like
shoved into obviously green screen
thing where there's a skyscraper it's him
walking out onto a helipad on top
of a skyscraper in a big city
and he's just like on his headset now you can
see him like small in the corner next was helicopter
with like twitch HQ it's it's like
basically New Los Angeles City
in the fucking background and he's just like
yeah you know just made another million just close the deal
just you know doing some sponsorship gigs
just you know make another billion dollars
on the on the market today that is what is
and then he presses another fucking button
and he goes back to his gamer chair and it's like
I when he's there's a
lot of work involved for sure in
preparing those things
then there's like when he's
on when he's actually streaming wherever he can like
push a button and boom unveils this really cool
thing that he's prepared and then he you know
goes on but the meat and potatoes of
it is him sitting in front of a
camera and pause is standing up occasionally
and just like saying shit being funny
telling jokes and like playing
games for like you know I don't know five
six eight hours a day whatever it is
I don't know a schedule and that
could definitely be taxing and doesn't
really sound that fun I don't know
yeah I don't know
I like me I wouldn't want to you know
you're a full-time streamer you know you're basically
doing what you do at an office job which is sitting
in a chair yeah for you know
doing it seems and like
at least you like you can slack off
you can slack off at an office
if you're like on twitch you have to be
like engaging the entire time
well you don't really have to be engaging the entire
time you know
like people people definitely
put it on in the background
and they're not you know there's no
there's no like
culture of being incensed when somebody
isn't on their A game because everybody
understands that if you if you
you know it's just sort of like a window
like you look over to the window
and there's like a thing there and it's always there
and it's reliable and you like it and you subscribe
and you like and favor it because
you like looking at in that window and if they're not
there for even one second you go
you go crazy but if you look there and they're there
it doesn't really matter how
well they're doing you're just
it's just sort of like a I don't know what it is
oh oh
about about twitch okay
so I think I don't I think maybe
I want to do this after
I think maybe I might
announce my plan to do this
in
sonichu lecture number two sonichu
102 advanced
history is what I'm planning to call it
but like after that like you know
a philosophy tube did his like
reading the entire works of Shakespeare
right for charity I kind
of want to do a charity stream where I read through the entirety
of sonichu
do you think it would take a lot of tape hard
to say it might
be a long time like
it could
I mean some chapters would probably take
several hours
as if I'm not like blasting through I might
take like 10 15 20 I don't
I don't know that would take that long but I could see
it taking like a huge a long time
I don't but I want to do a charity
stream first but I don't know what charity
I would do it for I would
we would want to be something funny
patreon.com
all good ideas
I'm sure you could find one
and you know in the time to
not autism speaks because everyone says that's a bad charity
lol okay fair enough
fair enough
I don't know dog
just
I like the idea yeah that's
something I want to do
and that is a twitch a twitch plan
yeah that's kind of what I want
like I know inevitably I will
do another nuzlocke and people are going
bananas they want another nuzlocke
I mean the last one was a triumph
it was a success I like by far my most
lucrative streams as well because people want to be
those Pokemon so like
it's definitely what I will do eventually
I just gotta just gotta carve out some time lads
because that last one really ate into
my schedule of like we Aga was
and other stuff yeah
did a lot of work behind the scenes
yeah they did they did it was good
time and I had a lot of fun like preparing
like the god fight against you know Ben saint
himself or the saint as it was
known as yeah it was dope it was
really sick and the graveyard little skits
we did the music I prepared
lots of fun there's totally fun things and
creative stuff you can do yeah
yeah I like I like twitch
I think it's cool I don't want
I don't want to be a full-time streamer but I
like I like I like
using it occasionally just to
just to be there and doing something
it's fun agreed agreed
all right well how many more
we got that's it that was the last one
oh thank god I mean more
darn leave more people speak pipe link
down below in the description we listen
all of them so leave us your shit
we're getting fewer and fewer well not
really but yeah we need more quality
ones you know the bigger the net because
we keep putting them all in jail
yeah you're not all the quality ones
have been jailed yeah
all right well running a prison
prison state the prison industrial
complex of the PCP is growing every
every time and it feels good
we're getting cheap slave labor
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
new bonus episode is out now
but not for a couple of days and it's
quake 3 this arena
rematch people from remember radcon 3
we're fighting and we're playing games
I will redeem myself
from my piss poor performance
in radcon 3 arena we shall see
we will like to find out
$5 pledge on patreon.com
slash the procrastinators for all
29 bonus episodes
that's worth 5 bucks that's worth
5 bucks and more forever
and they're all there
they're all good listen to them especially let me shout out
ASMR episode
let me shout out what were some of those verses
ones we did back in the day it was like
Jimmy Neutron versus the slurm guy
from Futurama that's not it
but you know something like that
whatever we should do that one though
that's a good idea
Jimmy Neutron versus Slurps
for Kenzie
I like it
oh what's that drink purple
the drink purple flurp in Jimmy Neutron
it could be a battle of the drinks
versus a fuck energy drink
this is all could be
relevant to this I mean I have some brand loyalty
there well okay fair
it out we'll see we'll see what else we got
at tpcrastinators twitter updates
releases and stuff check it out people
um that's it patreon
speakpipe voicemails twitter
thanks for listening everybody
and stay tuned for stay tuned for the
Vapors 2 Kickstarter coming very soon
indeed let us know
answers to our questions and stuff
in the comments whatever fuck you
alright see you next time bye