I want to bless that guy, that Son of齣.
How do we start this episode?
It's already started, by the way.
But how do we start it?
By my book, so we can start it.
Yeah, okay.
I did, by the way.
I did buy the book.
Yes.
Thank you.
There's a Gunsmoke Volume 1 on Amazon, and what's it called?
On Amazon, Paperback, and eBook.
No, Kofi.
Oh, and Kofi.
Kofi is for people who don't need an eBook Kindle version.
Right.
Which is potentially lots of people.
And I get a lot more royalties through Kofi than Amazon, but of course, Kofi cannot print
stuff.
I mean, I want the physical.
Yeah.
I think the majority of orders I've got, at least the ones I can see, are physical prints.
I want to ask about numbers.
It seems a bit rude, almost.
No, I've got some numbers.
The one thing I can tell you is that it's not showing me current up to the minute numbers
for all the orders.
I don't know the process by which it decides, okay, this order has definitely gone through.
It's been finalized, and now we can put it on the spreadsheet.
But it's taking like one to two days for an order to appear.
So I'm getting things from yesterday this morning, and it's only a few.
And I know it's more actual sales have happened than are being shown to me, because of the
amount of people who have said they're buying one.
Do you not get a notification every time you sell one?
No, I don't know why it is.
I think that there's a grace period.
This is a conjecture.
I haven't actually read this from Amazon.
I've tried to find an explanation.
And there seems to be third-party software that can track it more closely.
But it seems to be like the reason is there's a grace period for if somebody wants to refund
it before it actually gets shipped out.
So they don't want to give me the information until the money has actually been finally transferred
and cannot be refunded.
I guess that makes sense.
Yeah, so I don't have a cool number or a cool graph to look at.
I think I'll look into third-party stuff just so I can look at the number go up, because
I am excited about that.
So far, it has counted eight orders, and I know there's more than that, but eight, six
physical prints from United States, one from here at UK, and a Kindle version that my
mom bought to try it out on her iPad, which was useful, because I didn't know what it
looked like on a phone or an iPad through the Kindle.
It looks great.
I'm sure there's more people listening that want a copy of Clarissa Gunsmoke Volume 1.
Yes, I didn't really really talk about what it is.
Get those orders in, folks.
It's the first volume of my comic Clarissa Gunsmoke and the Bandit King, which contains
the three currently out chapters, plus the unreleased currently, as of recording unreleased
fourth chapter, the fourth one.
The fourth one.
Hey, may the fourth be with you.
It's March.
It's March the fourth.
Pardon me.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Cinco de Marcho.
You said you were, I was amazed when you told me the profit margins.
You said, you told me it was like $7.
You make like $7.
That's like almost half.
Yes.
And that's like on a $15 book sale, like that's, I would expect, my expenses for printing
a book like this would be at least, I would probably, including like printing the book,
getting it shipped to me and then mailing it, even inside the US, I would expect that
all to cost me at least $10 maybe more, which would leave me with only like $5 or less in
profit.
Yeah.
And on like foreign, on like international shipment, forget about it.
Shipping would be $20.
Yeah.
It's a whole big fuck.
I have for ebook.
It just makes me so jealous.
I just want Amazon, I just want Amazon's infrastructure.
I just want to have access to the fucking means by which they ship things so cheaply.
Why do they get to do it and I have to freaking go to the post office and pay $25 to send
six ounces of packaging to the UK?
It's evil.
Because they bundle up their packages and then they have it like lashed together with
rope and then they have a slave driver and he's does his whip thing and it's like in
the pyramids of Giza, they roll the packages on logs into the post office.
Why didn't I get a slave?
I don't know.
They got slaves.
You should have worked harder than you would have done.
Maybe I should have pulled myself up by my bootstraps if I wanted a slave.
They ship them in the big metal containers like the ones in the dock and in Disco Elysium.
The one that freaking Everard has his office in.
Yeah.
One of those.
But yeah, the royalties.
The royalties are a little interesting.
For paperback, quite simple, there's 60% royalty minus printing fees and for printing
this book, it's like two bucks.
Yeah.
Really?
So how many pages is it?
74 pages.
That's really cheap.
That's really cheap printing.
That's cheap as fuck and that is because it's like non-color.
I think if it was a color book, it'd be a little bit more expensive, but not prohibitively.
I think I'd look to the tables, it'd be like three to five dollars depending on how many
pages and if it was hardback and stuff like that.
When you...
Okay.
I mean, so the buyer doesn't have to pay for shipping because I bought one and it went
into my...
I assume if you have Prime, you get free shipping, you get on everything if you have Prime.
I don't have Prime, so I usually have to...
As long as I buy more than $25 worth of stuff on Amazon at a time, I get free shipping on
most things.
So I put it in my cart and I got free shipping on it because I added $10 worth of other stuff.
So I effectively paid nothing for shipping.
Yeah, it's great.
So...
Wait a minute.
It's finally a way I can send merchandise of my artwork out into the world without it
being too expensive for people to say, oh, I don't know about that.
I actually can't believe this because like $2 for...
I mean, I assume it's because the pages are black and white.
So I assume that that would cost more if it were in color.
But for $2, I mean, I would pay more than that to print, for example, a copy of the
Radcon Paradise Dojin, which is only 32 pages, black and white, cost more than $3 per copy
to print.
So that's...
It's almost...
Oh, God, I'm going to make myself sick if this is true, but it would be almost cheaper
to simply buy print-on-demand copies one at a time in bulk from Amazon and ship them
to myself than it is to buy a bulk order from Kaplan.
No, that can't be true.
Oh, you haven't even heard the best part.
Well, it's not the best part, but a cool thing about that is I, as an author, as the
author of this book, I can request Amazon send me a bulk order physical that I can then
sell by myself in person.
So if I want to go to a convention, I can pay just the price of printing, not like the
actual cost of the thing, send it to me, and then I can have like 100 Clarissa Gunsmokes
printed by Amazon at that price.
Do you get a discount or same price?
I think it might be a discount and check, because I didn't need that.
Because if there's additional discounts for printing in bulk, then that's just gravy.
Yes.
It's already cheap.
I would imagine there might be, but didn't check that exactly.
But that's cool, because if I ever need, like, oh, I'm going to maybe see if I can get a
table at a convention, I need a bunch of my book.
Yeah.
Amazon can just send it to me.
It's great.
Wow.
And you can have it, too.
It ships everywhere in the world, everywhere.
Can I, the consumer, order 100 copies and get a bulk discount?
No, I don't think so.
I guess you can get a shipping discount.
Nice.
If you buy two enough things.
Hell yeah.
But yeah, I'm going to have to look into this.
Damn it.
I was hoping I wouldn't have to look into this, but I guess I do.
It's so good.
Okay, so there's 60% royalty for paperback, but they have an extra thing that I checked.
So in addition to that, expanded distribution networks, so like Amazon can have the book
listed for schools and libraries and bookstores to purchase and put in their store.
And I get a 40% royalty on that.
So if Barden's a noble, know that Clarissa Gunsmoke's hot shit and they want it in their
store all over the world, all over the country, I guess, they can order it from Amazon.
And I get money through that.
So it's even less work I have to do for, not likely to happen because Clarissa Gunsmoke
is like a complete nobody right now, but that's cool.
If that were to happen, if you were to get copies ordered for libraries or bookstores
or anything, I mean, I would want to know about that.
That would be awesome.
I guess I understand how that Amazon could offer that as a possibility, but I'm sure
you have to promote it yourself, like they're not going to promote it for you.
No, well, they don't promote it.
The marketing is all on my end.
But they put it in a catalog or something.
They put it in a catalog and it can be listed.
So like if a librarian is just scrolling through and I see Clarissa Gunsmoke and they're like,
ah, that looks like something we need in the library.
So just download a copy.
I mean, yeah, order a copy or three.
You wouldn't download a copy of Clarissa Gunsmoke.
Oh, wait, yes, you would from Kofi.
Yes, you would from Kofi, where I get that only takes 5% of the sale for a Kofi store,
Kofi store.
I looked at Gumroad, by the way, Gumroad takes 10%.
So like Kofi is just better.
I didn't actually know you could sell stuff through Kofi.
It might be relatively new, but yeah, it's quite easy.
You just take 5% of every sale.
And if you're like a special member of Kofi, it's like you get 100% of the sale goes to you.
Are you a special member?
No, I'm a free user.
But 5% is so low, that's great.
Yeah, I made a Kofi for the PCP, sort of as like a secondary support alternative to Patreon,
the idea that we would advertise it in the perfect comic party.
You know, I think it's Kofi.com slash the PCP.
I think that's the URL.
Wait, what's your Kofi?
Oh, yes, my Kofi is Kofi.com slash Gibbentake, same as everywhere else.
Right, right, right.
Oh, and Amazon, Amazon has given me, let me check, because it was a little glitchy, but
like if I search Clarissa Gunsmoke,
and it comes up, Hell yeah, it comes up, that's so fucking cool.
And then I click my name.
It's my name.
Oh, it doesn't work.
It doesn't work in the UK.
I think in the US, I have like an author page in US, Amazon.
So if I switch to, switch the fucking,
oh, whatever.
But I have an author page, so I can put like a profile picture and say, oh, I'm an author.
This is about me.
Hmm.
Learn more about Louie Batten.
That's my full name.
I was not sure whether I was going to do my full name or an internet pseudonym.
I saw you put it as Ms. Louie Batten.
Yes.
Ms is such a funny, such a funny, such a hype, such a specific use case for an abbreviation, Ms.
But yeah, I think just because it maybe seems more professional and more like legitimate to have
a person's name and everyone does it.
Everyone does it.
So it's like, I don't know, if on the off-chance that Enormy is learning about my comic,
they won't be slightly put off by Gibb and take internet name.
Right.
Yeah.
Maybe.
They'll think of it as, oh, it's a glorific novel.
Who made Scott Pilgrim?
It's not like whatever username.
Not Radio Maru.
Yeah.
It was Brian Lee O'Malley.
You see.
All right.
That was his Tumblr handle.
Lol.
Yeah.
So yeah, I'm jazzed.
I was very-
Pretty jazz worthy.
I was very frustrated last week.
It was difficult to get everything working.
I bought a paperback for myself and it looks great.
And there's no problems anymore.
I can't wait to see mine.
Oh, it's so good.
It's like, what if you made something?
You, what if you drew something on a computer screen and then you have it in your hand?
No way.
Shit.
I think I'm going to have it on Friday.
I think mine's arriving on Friday.
So it'll be the day this goes up.
I'll have it hopefully, maybe even sooner.
This is the beginning of my girl boss CEO arc.
I'm starting it.
I'm starting an industry.
I'm starting an empire.
It'll be Clarissa Gunsmoke to start.
And then I'm going to put, I think I might,
the next thing I put on Amazon will be the Belle Jape book.
And that'll be like, you can get a paperback or a hardback,
because that's going to be like hundreds of pages, I think.
Do you have that made or do you?
It's half made.
It's like started.
I started it back a while before even the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
Because like, you know, I love those home stuck and problem sleuth books
with the little commentary at the bottom.
What if I did that?
With my silly little thing.
Yeah.
So I have the beginnings of something.
But yeah, translating it takes a long time with all the gifts
and posting multiple versions of, you know, the different frames
and completely different experience.
Well, now I have two potential segues into topics of conversation.
I could go, I could branch off of, oh, translating something
from digital onto a page, or I could go like print on demand
versus like backlog print runs.
Do the second one.
Okay.
So I have changed the, I ordered the PCP Radcon Paradise Dojin.
I ordered, I think I ordered like, I only ordered like 30 copies,
because like I wanted to give copies to all the artists and to the writers.
And I only got a, I only got a handful of other orders,
but like it's not that hard for me to order more.
If like, I get, if I get like 20 more orders tomorrow when I run out,
I could just order like a dozen more copies.
And it, it, it costs me like 10 extra dollars in shipping.
It's not that big a deal to just, to just get like a few more.
So I ordered a bunch of those and I have offered on St.
Comics store page.
I have offered, I've, I've offering a combo.
I call it the Rad combo.
It's for the, the, the, the Rad, the Dojin and the Road to Radcon for like,
I think it's like eight or nine dollars off the whole thing.
If you buy both as a combo.
And the reason I did that is cause I have like 30,
I have like 30 leftover copies of Road to Radcon.
And I really just like to get rid of them.
I don't need, I don't need 30 copies of that in a box.
Please buy my Rad combo.
It's, it's, it's a combo deal.
Super size it.
Road to Radcon is good.
You shouldn't, it actually, it actually is pretty
funny. If you, if, if, just a reminder, if you haven't read it,
you can read it for free on the new PCP website at theprocrastinatorspodcast.com
slash stuff.html.
It is pretty funny.
And the cover art by Michi is gorgeous and it's a nice little novella.
Yeah, a little doodles on the inside.
The doodles on the inside are nice.
The cover is a, is a, is a real masterpiece.
But I don't need 30 of them.
Please buy them.
Yeah, that's another great thing.
Don't have to do any shipping at all.
Amazon will do.
Yeah, that's, that's.
International shipping is so expensive.
I never have to have a bunch of crap, a bunch of stuff in my room.
It's, it, I feel so clean.
I feel so cool.
Having, and having to go, having to go to the post office is such a,
such a freaking, such a freaking drag.
I hate, I hate that shit.
Oh, I gotta, my PO box is about to expire.
I have to like renew my PO box soon.
The other thing.
Okay, I want to say it.
On the store page, the plebenweed blu-rays.
I think I might have mentioned this last week,
but I'm going to be discontinuing them.
I'm not going to be making any more
because it's not worth it to make more.
So the, the lat, those will be, those will be coming down
probably sometime in the next week.
After the, after this episode goes live.
There's simply, there's simply not enough demand to, to justify
continuing to order the stuff I need.
Don't want to buy any more DVD boxes or anything like that.
So what I got is going to be the last, the last of it that I make.
And then, you know, sorry if you miss out,
but like you should have, you should have bought it earlier, guys.
So I don't know, jump on that if you want.
Uh, there's no blu-ray for Clarissa Gunsmoke yet.
We should put, we should put the rad content on the blu-ray.
We should, we should put the garling house lecture
and the garling house diss track.
And we should put all that on, on its own blu-ray.
Everything should, everything should be on blu-ray.
Everything should be, you know, the OVA, everything should be on blu-ray.
I don't put blu-ray discs in my blu-ray player.
Physical media only.
I mean, I don't even, I like physical comics
because you can pick it up off the shelf
and you're already reading it.
Yeah. A DVD, you've got to like put it in your freaking machine.
A DVD, you need one, all of the material,
all of the technology required to make it work
to be currently functioning and the disc itself to be undamaged.
And then even then after that, it's like, I don't know, it's fine.
StComics.
Try to watch a YouTube video again.
StComics.com slash store.html for that while supplies last.
Time is, time is running out.
You will be gone soon, no longer available.
Or here's the thing I forgot to say.
Oh, sure.
So royalties, the ebook on Kindle, the royalty is odd.
There's two versions I could have chosen.
One of them is like 30% royalties.
And I don't know why it's like so low.
But the other one is 70%.
But they reduce the money you get for the size of the file of like the ebook.
So if you've got a big ebook, the megabytes weigh it down and you get less money.
Really?
Yes. I think it's just like people don't want huge files on their Kindle.
Just to incentivize like lower.
Yeah, compress compression and like, I mean, usually you would have text,
so it'd be small anyway.
So if you're doing a print book or a color, like a book with images,
you want to compress that as much as you can without it being shitty looking.
Is there like a threshold and like as long as you're under this threshold,
the royalties are better?
No, no, I think.
Well, I chose 70% because like, I still get more money that way,
even with the size of my ebook.
As opposed to the 30% of the sale, which is just flat and the megabytes doesn't get involved.
I mean, yeah, 70% is better than 30%.
But how did you qualify for that?
What did you have to do?
What do you mean qualify?
Well, you said.
Well, you said, I mean, the choice between 70% and 30% seems like a no brainer.
So like, what's the catch?
Well, the catch is that if you have a big file size,
I think there's something else for the 30% that I didn't really understand when I read it.
It's something, something, something, I'll have to go back and check.
But it's some technical thing that is like maybe good.
But like, I just want more money.
I don't give a shit.
Maybe it would like convert it into different types of Kindle things
and more people could read it on different places.
Well, I don't, well, I don't use, I don't use a Kindle or like ebooks or anything.
So I don't know how any of that works.
But sure, I do understand why they would want low file sizes.
Definitely.
Yeah, but I still get like from this, the 999 ebook on with that stuff,
minus the file size is $3.11, obviously, that's not bad.
Obviously we'll put a link in the description to where you can purchase Clarissa Gunsmoke
volume one.
Oh, speaking of links with, I put the link on my website.
I have a little button underneath Clarissa Gunsmoke that says buy like a paperback or buy digital.
They're links to the different stores.
But the Amazon one goes to theamericanamazon.com instead of .couk or like .de or whatever.
And it doesn't automatically adjust.
I think there is a way to have a link to Amazon automatically adjust to your region.
Because if I click on that, it goes to amazon.com and then it says it doesn't ship to me.
But if I switch regions, it will say that.
So I've got to update that.
I've got to find that link and I'll send that link and that should be the link under the description.
But if you search Clarissa Gunsmoke on Amazon, you will find it.
And it'll be in your region if you do it like that.
Yeah, yeah.
So it's all good.
But it should ship to everywhere.
Yes, anywhere that Amazon has a website version, which is many countries in the place in the world.
You've gone global.
I'm global.
I'm a global published author.
I was reading.
Oh, you know who sent me an interesting document?
It was those guys from the Cato anthology.
Remember them?
We had them on when they published.
They kickstarted their anthology comic.
Hoodie from Cato sent me their document, which was it was because they had heard us talking
about copyright stuff for the perfect comic party.
And they sent me their agreement for inclusion in their stuff.
And I read through their document and it was interesting.
And then I looked up a bunch of terms that were in it and I was googling around,
trying to learn more about copyright stuff.
And I found out there's a lot to it.
You can sell the rights to all different kinds of things with your work.
When you publish something, you can sell someone the right to be the first to publish.
You can sell someone the right to be the first to publish in a given country,
which means you can sell the same rights to another country.
You can give someone the rights to be the first to publish in a certain language,
which means you can then do it in a translated language with some other publisher,
and you can sell those rights to them.
The right to be the first to publish is its own thing.
Sometimes it comes along with a stipulation that you will not publish elsewhere for a certain
period of time.
There's archival rights, which are ongoing rights in perpetuity to host and publish
the digital rights.
The electronic rights are separate from both from all kinds of printing rights.
So I don't know, it was pretty complicated.
And I came away thinking, I think what we got to do is just worry about the digital version
for now.
And I think the agreement should just give us permission to publish and archive
your submission electronically.
We will host it for free, and you will give it to us for free, and we will host it for free.
And that's the agreement.
And there's nothing else to it until, if we ever want to print in the future,
we'll contact you and we'll work something out for that.
I see.
I think that's probably how we should move forward
with the digital PDF version.
There's lots of different publishers.
So what's hypothetically, if we wanted to do printing, what's the complications?
Well, it's basically a separate agreement.
I was kind of hoping that we could have it all ironed out.
If someone submits their comic, they are giving us the right to publish it in whatever form we
want, and maybe there would be certain monetary compensation involved.
If we decide to take it to print and print it as an anthology, maybe we would have already
agreed to compensate them a certain amount ahead of time.
I would like to have gotten all the agreements out of the way upon submission,
and there's no more need to worry about it.
I think that that was a pipe dream.
I think it's too complicated for that to be possible.
Is it like, it sounds like a weird, bad, sneaky contract thing, but what if we want to contact
you about, we're going to try and print it, but certain people just never get back to us?
Yeah, that's what I was worried about.
Do we have to put in a thing saying, if you do not get back to us upon our initial thing,
but within a certain amount of time, then we're just allowed to do it?
I feel like that's a little bit of a sneaky small print thing.
Yeah, I think, I was worried about that too.
It's like, well, once we have it in the publication, what if we then can't get them
on board, or we can't contact them again, or they disappear, and we want to publish
their stuff in a print anthology?
Maybe just leave them out of the printed version?
My gut says, okay, it's probably putting the card before the horse to be worrying
about print rights when we're not even thinking about printing anything yet,
when we're just worried about a digital publication.
Maybe we need to worry about the digital and electronic archival rights right now.
And yeah, I think it's just going to be probably if we want to print and we reach out
to the author and we say, hey, let's license us to print your stuff and sell your stuff
as part of an anthology, and they don't answer us.
I think we're just going to have to be like, well, we can't do it, which would suck.
But I mean, I don't know if there's anything else for it.
I guess. I mean, for any individual person who has a comic,
I would assume they would want the ability to do print their own thing, archive their own thing
in addition to whatever the perfect comic party will be.
So I guess the perfect comic party being unprintable is not a terrible tragedy in my eyes,
as long as, I mean, I'm going to be printing my comments.
I'm not saying it's unprintable.
I'm just saying.
Well, it would be difficult.
Well, I'm just saying we wouldn't.
But certain issues would be unprintable if we just can't get the person.
Well.
Or if it's people don't agree.
Well, yes, true.
But I think that's not too big of a problem, because I'm still going to be able to print
my comic.
It's not going to prevent other people from printing the comics on their own terms.
Yeah.
The collective will not be able to be printed.
I'm not interested.
I'm not interested in stipulating anything for submissions that are like,
if you submit, you agree you will not publish this in any other.
Oh, no, no.
That's not what I mean.
Yeah.
Of course.
I mean, if I was going to stipulate that, I would expect that we would be paying money.
And I don't want to pay anyone money.
We're doing this free.
Unless if we're not selling the book, then I feel like it's OK to ask people to submit for free.
But I wouldn't feel that way if we were like, well, if you give it to us,
then you can't publish anywhere else.
No, of course not.
That would never be part of the thing.
Because I mean, the idea of having a printed version of the perfect comic party is just like,
oh, that'd be nice.
Would that be nice?
Well, it's nice.
That's about as far as it goes.
Well, no.
No, you idiot.
It's not just nice.
It's about staying in the black.
It's about the dollar-dollar bills.
It's about stacking Benjamins.
It's about.
Then if that's the case, the contract needs to be a little more like it can handle that.
I just think potentially print copies are an avenue to turn this venture into
something that generates revenue.
But for that, yeah, we would need additional agreements with submittees.
But since the idea then would be that we're selling it, I feel like I don't think it would
be sustainable to expect people to submit their stuff for free for us to then sell.
We would have to draft up some standard licensing contract, but then in the here and now,
we would be paying people money for content that we would then be publishing for free.
We'd have to operate at a loss in preparation for potential future revenues.
Oh, so you would pay them like a flat fee when they submit it?
For example, yeah, for example.
And not when it gets sold?
Well, we could stipulate something like future compensation before print.
Yeah, I mean, we could do it in like a, we promise to pay you a certain amount
at such time as we make them available for physical sale, that seems reasonable.
Okay, you know what, you know what, Gib, that's not bad.
That's not bad because I would rather promise to pay someone in the future than pay them now.
Yes, the only thing is then when we're like, okay, let's print.
Oh, we've got to pay this many people this much money.
Oh, we can't afford that law.
Well, sure.
In which case, maybe we do pre-orders of the physical version.
It's a whole bunch of crunch.
It is a whole bunch of crunch.
I couldn't have said it better myself.
I hope this isn't, you know, I started talking about this stuff on my stream the other day
and my viewership like cratered.
So I hope this isn't boring, but I mean, I think it's really interesting.
I think it's a fascinating puzzle to try and solve this,
put these pieces together in a way that forms a money-making machine.
For me, it's like the curse cloud from Okami.
Every moment I stand in there, my health bubbles are going a little smaller.
I got to jump out of there and run around in the dirt.
No, I'm in there.
I'm in the cloud.
I am the cloud.
I am the cloud, baby.
Okay, okay, okay.
You know what?
I like that idea.
So let's just let's explore it.
Let's explore it for another minute or two.
When, if we stipulated some of the...
Okay, you submit, you give us the rights to electronically publish for free
and we will make it available for free.
However, you also agree, you agree to not necessarily first publishing rights,
but you agree to allow us, you know, print rights.
Okay, I feel like we might have to stipulate some kind of time frame.
Like, I feel like it might not be okay to just be like,
say that and be like, at some point in the future, like maybe 50 years from now,
we just said, oh, well, we still got the rights.
Maybe we can.
I mean, if it's not an exclusive deal, maybe we can just be like, yeah,
we're allowed to do it.
There's no exclusivity deal, but we're allowed to do it.
Okay, okay.
So maybe we say, it's free electronically.
At such time that we make it available for publishing,
you will be entitled to some amount and we could do it some flat amount per submission
or we could do it, we could do it like per page.
We could do it on a per page basis as well.
Oh, but that means verbose people get the big cash.
Yeah, that would, that would draw really small.
That would perversely incentivize you to like stretch your content out over as many pages as
possible, which is, I mean, other publications have operated on such a business model in the
past.
It's not untenable.
But yeah, is it, is it incentivizing the kind of creator behavior that we want?
Maybe not.
I mean, I think most people submitting are just going to do it because there's like, oh, cool.
Maybe my comic will be seen.
Maybe this isn't a good excuse to start drawing my comic.
You're absolutely right, Gib.
We should pay an exposure.
Yeah.
We own the means of production.
They have to give us a website.
A website to host what files on.
They give us some, some, some dirt on themselves.
And we expose the dirt if they don't comply.
That's the paid in exposure.
You have to tell us one.
You have to one.
Cancelable secret.
One dirty little secret.
All right.
You can submit your comic, but we will only accept submissions if you record yourself
saying the n-word and you submit a pen.
We will, we will release it if you break your contract.
This is part of the standard agreement.
Standard agreement.
This is standard industry procedure.
This is how, this is how the world works now.
It's all about that cancelable currency.
Cancel coins.
That's right.
Cash your cancel coins.
Get this person off the line.
Off line.
Get him, get him hiding.
It's, it's a, it's a, it's a trust based economy.
There's nothing more valuable than the ability to destroy some of credibility.
Based economy.
Oh, right.
Liz, that cutie.
Okay.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
I'm stinking.
What do, what do we offer?
I don't know.
What, what's a reasonable amount to offer in such an agreement?
Like you give us, we will pay you 50 bucks.
That seems low.
Do I get 50 bucks?
Will we, will we pay ourselves 50 bucks to put our own comics in our own?
No.
I mean.
Why would I even be a part of this?
Why would I be doing all that?
I'll just sell my own comics.
I'll give myself 50 bucks every day.
I, okay.
Look, here's, I, there's, I feel like there's going to be submissions.
Some, some, we, here's, here's what we get in particular.
Some submissions are going to be worth more than others.
Like some will be more substantial, more professional, you know.
So, so I, a, a, a, a one, a one size fits all standard, you know, contract remuneration
amount seems a little weird.
Well, that's why we have like a, we, we decide who gets in.
Sure.
I mean, yeah, that, that does kind of.
That's sort of how it works in general.
But what if they're all bad?
Like the idea in show and jump is, or yeah, any comic, the show and jump has multiple
different, I guess Marvel does, but they sell individual, whatever.
Right.
The idea is that they have an artist say, can I please have this marketplace?
Can I please have eyes on my art?
Platform, please.
And, and show and jump is got a big platform.
So it's, it's attractive to artists.
It could be a career maker to get on there.
Perfect comic party is not that.
That's certainly not at the beginning.
No.
So there's no incentive other than wouldn't it be nice?
I mean, there is a little bit of incentive because there's.
We have a very, we have a, we have a tiny little, we have a little, we have a tiny little.
We have a tiny little.
We have a little platform.
Yeah.
It's one of those platforms that if you stand on it, it'll fall into lava.
It starts to shake.
It starts shaking a little bit and you got like one second.
Yeah.
So my screen, my screen just turned off.
Okay.
I'm back.
I forgot where I was going with that.
But show and jump says, we need you to keep our reputation high.
So you can't suck.
So you have to be very good.
And all the artists, they say, okay, try their best.
Here's, I think that in concept, the idea of free for now, we might print later,
but we'll pay you if we do.
I think that's a sound idea.
It's a sound basis for an idea, but you have to look into how to actually draw that out.
It's a, it's a sound basis for an idea.
And just the balancing act there is like, what's the, what's the amount that is,
that like incentivizes quality submissions and doesn't like bankrupt us to offer it as like a
standard submission, you know, accepted submission contract and isn't like insulting
to people that made like real comics.
And I like, and I like, for us, for us to, for us to like print them.
Also, I don't know, I feel like if we print, there might be, I mean, I, you know,
I would like the ability to print in perpetuity.
And if it's not exclusive, I feel like that would not necessarily be unreasonable.
Yeah.
But also that seems, it seems like that would be expensive.
I don't know. It seems like maybe it'd be more affordable to offer people like,
well, we can print your stuff like for a year, but I don't want to have time limits.
I want it all.
I don't want the exclusive rights, but I want the perpetual rights.
I, give me your content.
Give me your content, people.
Let me gobble it up.
I put it into my, into my money making machine.
I feel just a little weird about the whole idea of just of, of like
contracts and, and being an arbiter of quality to be on this potentially lucrative enterprise.
Like the idea for me initially was just an excuse to, to get work in, you know, a motivating tool.
Ah, shit.
And, and you're thinking of it as like a, as a, you know, a money making venture.
Yeah.
And I don't feel like I'm qualified to be like an arbiter of quality for a comic thing when my
comics are, you know, they're fine.
But like, I don't know.
I don't feel like I'm the right person for that sort of a job.
I ain't no publisher.
I ain't no market analyst.
Maybe, maybe it's, maybe it's best to just think about, to just worry about the electronic rights
for now.
I think so.
All right.
At least just for now.
Like I need to get my foot in the door of, you know, making money off my art.
That's where my mind is at.
True.
Oh, speaking of, I started, I started working on Obescapades again.
I'm on it.
I'm on the case.
Nice.
It's getting, it's getting there.
How many pixels?
Hang on.
Let me count.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Very, very, very low res images.
Oh, should I?
I lost count.
Hang on.
I guess I'm right.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
The images are only like, they started like, I think it's like 190 by 270.
And then I blow them up.
I'm sort of laying them out.
It's actually really hard and kind of annoying to like fit them to like a page.
It's because they, okay.
I had a couple of, I had like a handful of images that I had put on my Twitter,
but that I had not published on my website.
So I started there and I tried to take those and like just put them to a page
and be like, how do they look on the page?
And I managed to figure it out.
I managed to get them looking like, okay, this is readable.
It's, it's very, it's very annoying.
It's very annoying because there's not like a standard way to do it.
I kind of have to like size every image and be like, how big should it be?
Where should it be?
What order should they go and where should the words be?
I kind of had to just figure that out as I go every time.
And it took a while.
And so I did a bunch of that with those existing updates.
And then I started drawing a couple more new ones.
And I don't know, I hope, I hope that I can sort of streamline the process
and it'll get a little faster as I get a little more used to doing it this way.
But I'm glad to be drawing again, even though I've only really just started,
but I did start and that's the hardest part is starting.
Yes.
Well done.
Thank you.
You put the pen to the paper.
And I, and you know what?
I remembered that Biscopades is cool, actually.
And yes, that's how it was always how it happens.
Yeah.
And nobody actually go back and you're like, oh, I would read this.
I did read this.
I made this.
You know what?
Well, you know what?
You know what the thing is?
I don't know if I, well, some of Biscopades as it currently exists,
I think is good and I would read some of it is bad and looks like crap.
But where Biscopades, I might have, I might have gone on this spiel already.
So I won't belabor it.
But Biscopades has not revealed what it is actually about yet.
Biscopades has not showed its hand and the ideas that I had for when that happens.
I don't know.
I find them really fun and cool.
So when I'm excited to get there and then I'm excited to right now, I'm like,
it's all, it's all set up.
It's all set up.
Nice.
Yeah, I'm just very excited to make that happen.
And I don't know.
I don't even know what I don't know exactly what it's going to look like.
But I am, I look forward to finding out.
I had some ideas about.
I'm fucking around right now.
And I stop finding out.
Yeah.
I had some, I had some ideas about,
I had some ideas about what gluttony could be used for.
I almost don't even really want to talk about why I thought my ideas were good.
Because they sort of figure into like the real, like what, like the actual like purpose
and concept behind Biscopades, which is sort of not even really apparent yet.
So I won't even go into them.
But I had, I was walking the other day, I was walking here and I was like,
oh, it could do that.
Oh, that fits perfectly.
Oh, yes.
That makes perfect sense in the future.
In the story concept, as I understand it.
And I'll sure I'll do that soon.
Okay.
You know, when it comes to story concepts, I've been, I've been really deep.
Well, not really deep, but I've been very excited about using this program called obsidian
to write all my notes down.
Isn't that like a, isn't that like a planning app or like a scheduling?
It's a planning and schedule, but it has this great feature where
if you do, if you make a note, whatever, and then you put two square brackets and some text inside,
that creates a new note that links from that word.
So it's a hyperlink to a different note document.
And I've been doing that to build up the world of my comics of bell,
jpe, and, and Lord of ghosts and stuff and adding like character entries and then a link
to what other characters they know, things they've done, and like places they're from.
And I've started to build all graph.
And the great thing about obsidian, let me get a picture,
is this graph view that shows the links you've made between notes
in a little thing like this.
And I've colored them based on whether they're a character, a location, a comic,
or a jewel, an endless ruck.
What, what the fuck?
So you got here, you can see like bell jpe has like
all the characters from bell jpe and the places involved and things.
I go into like, if I go into the jewel of the jewel of splish is an endless rock.
Did I know that already?
I might have, I might have heard that.
I've definitely explained that, but like, I don't think it's been like well understood.
It's part of my big lore, you see, but if I click on the ostrich cathedral,
this is the note and it contains things like this.
A big, oh, this is cool.
And it's just sort of, I, I, I, I sprawl it out from there.
It's like building, building the wiki, but in such a simple way that I can easily add pages and,
and stuff.
This is just like, this is just like the, the freaking,
I don't even remember what it's called.
The thing in outer wilds that lets you like track the things, the things you found.
This is the thing I was playing out to wilds doing the DLC.
And I was like, ah, this is just like that program I saw like a few weeks ago.
Because my brother told me about it.
I'm like, I got to do it.
I got to do it for my thing.
And so I'm doing an outer wilds connect the dots database of all the stuff that happens in the
comic and all of my ideas for different things that have not currently been shown.
So for bell jpeg two, that'll be instrumental in figuring out where it goes.
Yeah.
And Clarissa gun smoke and whatever adventures she has after that.
And anything else.
It's great.
This is very interesting.
My, my dad always used to try to get me to use like, not stuff like this, but like,
he would always buy me like little like calendars and like notebooks and like planners and stuff
and try to encourage me to like write down notes and stuff and like keep track of things.
And I always and I always spurned them.
I like always hated that shit.
I like this is just a cool.
This is I mean, this is more interesting than than that.
Is another another trying to try and try and try to load a ghost's
comic.
Oh.
So it's gotten the secondy and like a calm over there.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to decide.
I'm trying to decide if this would be useful for bescapades or not.
You know what's going to be very useful for is figuring out how red noir fits into the Lord of Ghosts.
Red noir.
I'm glad I'm glad to hear you mentioned red noir again.
Yeah.
Such a good name for such a short lived little project.
Yeah, glad.
Glad that's not completely forgotten.
Yeah.
Yeah, I reread it in the process of putting it on my website.
Give and take dot site, newly revamped.
And I was like, wow, this is good.
This is a good little red man comic, but a noir.
Somebody somebody commented and said like nice job, Ben, nice job on the website.
It's very, it's very, it's like, I think they said it was like simple and clean or it's like nice and
simple.
And I was like, thank you.
Yes, that's what I want.
I just want a freaking easy to use website with a couple of pages to find the stuff you're looking for.
That's all that's all it is.
And that's all I was trying to do with it.
And I think I succeeded.
And reminder, if you want the episode MP3 is a lot of people use like the podcast apps.
If you want, if you just want to download the MP3 is and listen to them on an MP3 player or
something, they are all except for the last like two up on the PCP website, perfect comic
party dot com, the procrastiners podcast dot com slash episodes dot HTML, I think.
And you can also get there's I have zipped collections.
You can download zip files and then unzip them.
And it'll have like every episode of the podcast that was on the PCP channel.
Every PCP episode from a certain year, all of the Digibro decompression chambers, etc, etc.
I hope those are convenient for people.
There's a lot of work.
It was a lot of work just putting that all together.
And if I missed it, and if I missed anything, let me know in the comments if I missed if
there's any collections you'd like to see or stuff that I didn't didn't get.
There might be other like random crap from the channel that I just totally forgot about.
They got the panel casts.
We got the Nauru cast.
We've got I don't even remember what else we got guys isolation training.
You know, what the hell was that?
It was one time Nate did a did a decompression chamber and he called it isolation training.
Yeah.
Oh, you said panel reminded me of one other thing that's cool.
The Kindle create is like the program you use to turn like a PDF into a Kindle ebook.
And what it does, there's this fundal function.
If it's, you know, graphic novel, you can auto auto generate panels.
And so when you're reading on a phone or a Kindle or whatever,
you can double tap on a panel and it'll zoom in and full screen that particular panel.
So you can switch, you can flip through the panels rather than full pages if
if the pages are like too small on a phone or something.
Instead of having to zoom, you can look at a panel and it was like scroll to the next one.
And I did that for Clarissa and it like pretty well like I only had to edit a few of them matched
the panels on the page to little little rectangles that it would zoom in on.
Wait, so it so it like auto finds the panels and like makes them their own thing?
Makes them their own like individual image that you can scroll left and right through
if you want to.
And then you double tap the panel to go back to full page view, which is a pretty cool.
That's actually very interesting.
That actually sounds pretty cool.
Yeah. You don't really need it for Clarissa because the text is quite big for that.
But if it's like a traditional comic book with tiny little text, then it's quite useful.
But yeah, I've learned so much about Kindle.
I've never used it.
I don't think I will use it, but it's cool.
But also by the PDF, if you don't care about that because I get more money.
And then by the paperback because it's cooler to have something on your shelf.
And then by the Kindle as well.
I can't stop. I can't stop consuming.
I want to consume all forms of the content.
I'm the chef and you better eat your greens, which is my work.
I have been trying to create twizzlers.
I'm trying to duplicate the twizzlers recipe in my candy making workshop.
And it's hard.
It's hard.
And I bought a jug of glycerin.
And I'm going to try putting that in there and see what happens.
Oh, is that licorice you're trying to make?
I am also.
I also got some stuff for licorice.
I was just talking about cherry twizzlers, just the consistency.
Yeah.
I am going to get some licorice extract and like once I know how to make them,
I will like make that with them because I like that.
But I got this stuff.
Okay, I found this stuff.
This was so amazing.
There's this stuff.
Apparently it's a naturally occurring salt.
It's called sal ammonia or it is ammonium chloride.
And I guess they put it in certain licorices.
It's like salty licorice flavoring.
And listen, listen to this.
This is the second paragraph from the Wikipedia article on Sal Ammoniac.
Pliny in book 31 of his natural history refers to a salt produced in the Roman province of
Sirenica called Haman, Hamaniacum, Hamaniacum is so called because of its proximity to the
nearby temple of Jupiter Amun, Greek Amon.
However, the description Pliny gives of the salt does not conform to the properties of
ammonium chloride.
According to Herbert Hoover's commentary, in his English translation of George's
Agricola's Deire Metallica, it is likely to have been common sea salt.
In any case, that salt ultimately gave ammonia and ammonium compounds their name.
Herbert Hoover, the president of the United States,
translated this ancient fricking Roman book about the nature of metals and salts.
And he's excited here in this Wikipedia article.
And I did a double take at that.
So wait, ammonia because it's close to a temple?
Okay, yes. This salt that Pliny describes was called Ammoniacum because it was near
to the temple of Jupiter Amun, like that's where the Amon in Ammoniacum comes from.
And that name for that particular salt that Pliny describes is where, yeah,
the chemicals Ammonia and ammonium get their names.
It's so funny how words are just used.
Even though it literally is not what he was talking about.
He was talking about something else.
He was just talking about salt, regular salt.
It's fun when you realize how human history is so much.
All these names, it's like, oh, that doesn't sound like anything.
They're all derived from just like looking at something and saying,
what's that, the big hill?
But you say it in your language and that becomes the name of a mountain.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Isn't that?
And it's like, that's how world-building is.
I should do that for my world-building thing.
I should come up with the reason people call them certain things the way they is.
It's just cool.
Because they just saw a place and they called it the big place.
It's just-
That's why I called my town something town.
It wasn't because I couldn't think of anything.
It was because they just-
That's just how you name things.
And then it sounds cool in another language when someone calls it
that in your language, but they don't know what it means, to them it's just a fancy word.
And that's where names come from.
Honestly, I always felt like really dumb when I was trying, when I was younger
and trying to come up with like fantasy names for things.
I'd be like, okay, just throw some vowels in there, some consonants,
like lots of consonants, more than usual.
And an average ratio of consonants to vowels will simply not suffice.
Yeah.
For the fanciness, for the fanciness of the concept I'm trying to convey here.
It's like Lord Blu Targoth and the Kingdom of Smyr Skalosh.
Got it.
I mean, that's funny.
Got it in one.
I like Smyr Skalosh.
Yeah, it's not bad.
But like, you know, you would try and copy Lord of the Rings and come up with things
that sounded a little too close to everything else, Elven stuff.
Right, right.
And you didn't have any basis for the reasoning.
You're just like, what sounds like a place that isn't a real place?
You ever watch, you know, oh God, what's his name?
Krusty the Clang.
No, it's that Jan Misali.
You ever watch Jan Misali?
Yes.
Have you watched any of his older, what are they called?
The ones where he takes a conlang critic.
A conlang is like a fake language that somebody made up.
And he has a series of videos from like a few years ago where he like goes through
various popular ones and like analyzes them and like ranks them on like how good or shitty they are.
And some of them are really weird.
I've not seen those.
Jan Misali is the guy who did that video about the
anime song that everyone knows, but it was actually Swedish.
Yes.
He did do that.
He did do that one about the not Numa Numa.
Caramel Dancin.
Right.
I had to go through the lyrics in my head to get to the end to be like Caramel.
That's the name.
Got it.
Yeah, he did do that video.
I had found his channel a little bit before that because he did one about
how many Mario games, how many Super Mario games are there.
That video blew up as well.
And then the Caramel Dancin video really blew up,
especially because there was like a big like legal thing about it.
Is it still taken down?
I think that's sorted out.
I don't know.
Well, it's a good video.
It is a really good video.
Find it if you can.
But yeah, the conlang critics are interesting and he does like,
you know, he does ones like from Tolkien and he does ones from Song of Ice and Fire.
And he does other like weird ones that were like made by like various people in history
as like a genuine attempt to create a universal language.
And those are all terrible.
Well, a lot.
Most of them are.
There's that one.
There's that one that's like it doesn't even have letters.
It's made of like knots.
It's made of like lines that like tie into knots.
And like the number of like twists in the knot is like what determines what it means.
That one's awesome.
Like like a like a like a piece of rope or like a drawing.
Well, it's a draw.
I mean, you maybe could do it with.
OK, it's called Kellen with with a line over the first E.
And it looks like this and I don't know how to read it.
Oh, that's like that looks Celtic.
It does look Celtic.
It might be like Celtic inspired, but only in like visual design.
So what's this word?
I don't fucking know.
Yeah, I've no idea.
Is that like an actual end and start like it starts like that?
Look, then swirls all the way around.
Look, I I I couldn't I can't explain anything about this to you.
Other than that supposedly this is what Kellen looks like.
Well, I'll choose to be offended by it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You can also write it.
You can write it fancy and then it looks like this.
It mostly just looks cool.
Like I think it's not.
I think it's not like that useful as like a language for communicating.
It's like an art language.
It's like a language that's made to it's made to look pretty.
And it does communicate something, but it's like it's it's art first and foremost.
Yeah, that's cool.
I think that there is like obviously for humans, this is incomprehensible at a glance.
No, you well, yeah, yeah, because you don't under because you don't know it,
but you could learn it.
Could you though?
Yes.
But you said you couldn't figure it out.
You're so stupid because I didn't you have to you would have to learn it like a language.
You have to I don't know.
There's a freaking code you got to I just think I just think when it comes to like
knots, that's one of like the hardest things to understand at looking at it.
Like when you see a tangled mess of cables,
you think you think that knots are the hardest thing to understand?
No, I mean like for a person, a letter or like a kanji or like a thing
is easier because each one is like by themselves.
You know, that's why like right joined up writing or like whatever is it's harder to
read and things that are like, where do you where do you begin with that with this line?
And that's why you can't untangle the Christmas lights.
And that's why learning how to do knots is difficult and tying your shoes.
I'm just saying lines, big long strings are like the enemy of human thought.
That's an interesting.
That's my hypothesis.
Interesting way to look at it.
I feel you, I agree with you.
Obviously, listen, I'm not going to I'm not going to argue that obviously
this is not the most intuitive way to put to put concepts into like into like writing.
But I feel like that they took a non-standard initial conceit of how to do it and ran with it.
I feel like that's no, I do.
I do like I think it's pretty neat.
It is pretty neat.
Where I was going with it, though, is like, what if there's an alien that finds this a lot easier
to comprehend than single like separated elements like letters?
What if they can be like, oh, yeah, I know what that is.
Like even if they don't know the language, they can learn it real quick.
But if they try to learn like if the alien was like a worm and like they had to like
Yeah, a little worm aliens.
They understand things like length and like getting tied up and twisted around and stuff.
They get twisted every day.
I don't know why that was so funny.
Yes, they get you.
Oh, you mean like they get they smoke weed and they drink and they get they get twisted.
No, no, I mean they tangle themselves up because they're wormies.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, would you still love me if I was always a worm?
Would you still would you love me if I was a worm and I was like an alcoholic and a stoner and like
I couldn't and I was all disoriented all the time and I kept tying myself up in knots
and the knots said offensive things in in Kellen just by coincidence.
No, and then you get canceled on worm Twitter.
That would be the line.
Listen to submit the line to submit your worm comic.
You have to submit a photo of yourself saying the N word in Kellen.
Let's ask him easily how you write it.
I bet.
Yes, a YouTube comment.
That'll be that'll work.
Hey, hey, hey, Jan.
Big fan got a got a question for you.
Say I wanted to write a certain word in Kellen.
Here's here it is.
All right, let me know.
Bye.
Why did you even get on this topic?
I something about I don't know.
You brought up Kellen for some reason.
I don't even remember.
We're talking about world building ammonia.
Oh, it's not name and stuff.
Name and stuff.
Name and stuff and Tolkien and yeah,
the sound and like Elvish and whatever.
Whatever.
I just like those.
I just like those videos.
That's all my notes, by the way.
I have I have no more subject.
I was reminded of something.
I forget why.
But I wrote it down.
Turkey 2000s.
Okay.
Oh, because we talk, we talk, we talk about Turkey Twizzlers.
I saw this tweet of yours, by the way.
Yeah, you said Twizzlers.
And I was like, oh, Turkey Twizzlers.
That was a famous school lunch cafeteria food
that was really bad for you.
And it's famous because Jamie Oliver got it banned
and everyone was mad.
Cringe, I want one.
I think they look good.
They look all right.
Well, they look like meat in a swirl.
And I don't think I ever really liked the taste
more than like normal nuggets or normal.
They had turkey dinosaurs.
That was the other thing.
Turkey nuggets in the shape of dinosaurs.
And those were better.
And then they had like the potato smiley faces
and spaghetti hoops and, you know,
all sorts of these like kid friendly processed foods.
I had smiley fries.
We had smiley fries.
I walked over to my refrigerator
to get one of my attempts at a Twizzler out of the fridge.
Not successful, much too soft.
But yes, I remember and because I hadn't thought about it in years
and my brother was over for the weekend and he mentioned it.
And I was like, oh my God, I remember those Turkey 2000s.
Turkey 2000s was a turkey nugget.
I don't know why so many things were made of turkey.
I think maybe it was just a it was a recipe
for really cheap like bullshit.
But like Turkey 2000s was the number 2000 connected, you know.
So there was like a big long thing with holes
so you could see the O's and the two.
And it was around the turn of the millennium.
They would have these in school dinners
because it was like it's the millennium, you know.
They just made them in the shape of the number 2000.
They made turkey nuggets in the shape of the number 2000.
They were called Turkey 2000s.
Why wouldn't they just make them in the shape of twos and zeros?
Because that's too many different parts.
I don't fucking know.
They wanted to make one mold instead of a billion.
I mean four or two.
I guess one mold instead of two actually.
Yeah, yeah.
But then you could make 002.
You could make 020.
You know, you couldn't actually, it wouldn't be 2000
unless the child placed them in the right orientation.
Well, you just make three times as many zeros
and then it'll work itself out.
No, but what if one kid doesn't get a two?
Like they get like a ladle full of fucking-
Of zeros?
Of zeros.
Then he gets what he deserves.
I'm sorry.
Some people just don't deserve the two.
I know these existed.
My brother remembered them.
And then we went on a nostalgia, like find this stuff.
We found some other things.
We found like school dinner cake, which I will find an image of.
Think of like Google the exact phrasing.
Yes, school dinner cake.
It was a sponge cake with sprinkles and like white icing.
And apparently it was just called school dinner.
It was just school cake.
School cake.
And they would have it and they would have custard or nothing.
But that was like a cafeteria like staple of primary schools
and secondary schools, I guess.
I definitely remember those a lot.
It was always nice when for the dessert,
they had those because they were tasty.
We found other things.
We found the turkey dinosaurs.
And we found a forum where somebody mentioned Turkey 2000s,
that exact phrase.
So we know that there's at least three people in the universe
that remember Turkey 2000s.
But I could not find a single image on Google
or any listing in like top 38 most nostalgic school dinner items from the UK.
And I'm like, why is it not there?
That's such a weird thing.
You would think there'd be.
Yeah, like I Google that and I can't find any pictures of it.
There's no there's no simple way to get it.
Because like I type in Turkey 2000s, I get all of the knowledge,
all of the articles about Jamie Oliver and Turkey Twizzlers,
which were more popular and they weren't just about the year 2000s.
And there's plenty of people who are nostalgic for post Turkey 2000s, I'm sure.
There's only a certain amount of people who are at school
in the right age bracket to even know about Turkey 2000s.
And it's like, this is the biggest mystery of our generation.
I'm determined for someone else to please tell me the information
because I couldn't find it.
Anyone out there in the audience, if you remember Turkey 2000s,
might have just been a UK thing.
I would assume they didn't have like a worldwide thing with this.
It's very silly.
But like maybe any other countries, any other people from other countries
know about the Turkey 2000.
I think it's probably a UK thing because we didn't even have,
we didn't have Turkey Twizzlers.
We had smiley fries.
Could be other European countries.
But yeah.
Anyone else remember that?
Because it was so frustrating trying to Google it
because there'd be Turkey dinosaurs.
Nostalgic things would come up with buzz feet articles about lists of bullshit.
It's just like, oh, remember this from when you were a kid?
School cafeteria.
Beans, sure.
Potatoes and beans.
Oh, smiley faces.
We all like those, the smiley potatoes.
Because they have mashed potatoes inside.
I want some of those still.
Yeah, they're still good.
They had like potato waffles and just bad food, but cafeteria food
and old food, nostalgic food, and it's just too specific.
And there's too many things that are similar to that search result,
but not the same thing that you just get led off in the wrong way over and over.
I couldn't find it.
I searched for a whole 20 minutes.
It's impossible.
I mean, I can't find it either.
And it seems so visually bizarre and idiosyncratic
that you would think there'd be pictures of it.
But what I need is some sort of lead that I can follow up on.
Some sort of like, what were the company's names, the branded company's names,
that sold all of this stuff to school cafeteria's in the first place?
Is there a name for a company?
Is there a series of companies?
I don't know where to start looking for that information.
But if I can find that, then I might be able to get a product list.
I might be able to search a way, like avoid searches for nostalgic image board
article bullshit that is distracting and filling up my search results with nothing.
I know they exist.
This is my white whale.
This is my Turkey 2000.
Are you sure they weren't Turkey 2000?
Just such a funny name.
Are you sure they didn't have a different name?
Maybe like, I don't know, Millennium Turkey?
I typed in different things like Millennium Turkey.
But then I came up with the Country Turkey and something about the Millennium.
Turkey 2K?
No, 2K was a much, that referring to a year as K is such a 2010 thing.
It was, I've never heard that before, like more recently.
What about Turkey Twizzlers 2000?
Well, it wouldn't be a Twizzler.
It wasn't a Twizzler.
But it sounds like it might have been the same company that made them.
Honestly, it could be.
It might have been processed in the same factory.
It could be, but they tasted different.
They tasted more like the Turkey dinosaurs.
If I know who made the Turkey dinosaurs, I could probably be like,
you know, that company based in like Germany made,
squished Turkey stuff for the whole of Europe.
And it was great.
Well, it was the best of times.
Google tells me that the first result from Google is like a brand called Bernard Matthews
Turkey Dinosaurs made by Sainsbury.
Sainsbury is okay.
That is a UK.
Sainsbury Turkey 2000.
But then it would be like, oh, buy a Turkey at Christmas from Sainsbury.
It's like, no, it'll never, it'll never show up.
Is it a supermarket chain?
It's a supermarket, yeah.
Buy this, buy that.
Yeah.
Like, how do I search for the archives?
Sainsbury's archive, they don't have that.
I think you hallucinated it.
No, I absolutely did not hallucinate it.
I think there would be pictures online if this was real.
I think everyone's forgotten, except for the people on the forum.
I think you are abusing your platform to try and spread a false rumor.
Bring back Turkey 2000s.
You're trying to start a Mandela effect in it.
If we need Turkey 2000 and 23s, we need Turkey 2000.
There's no way.
It can't possibly have happened.
It can't be real.
It's too stupid.
No, it's so stupid that it has to be real.
I remember eating them.
I'm like, wow, this is fun.
That's a pretty, that's weird.
Why do they make it?
Because it was like, it's a millennium.
Nobody has seen a millennium ever.
Nobody has seen a millennium.
I remember eating them and thinking,
hmm, I love living in a goofy alternate timeline
where we make stupid Turkey shapes like these.
They made Turkey dinosaurs.
They could make a number 2000 for like a brief marketing stint for a millennium.
They haven't had a millennium for a thousand years.
They were excited.
I wonder if they made 1000 turkeys for the first millennium.
They didn't even have turkeys back then.
They might actually not have.
They might have had the one or two.
They had, is Turkey like an American bird?
Like in the Americas?
I want to say yes.
I want to say, yeah, it might be.
It might be a native North America.
They may not even have had chicken in the year 1000.
They would have had no nuggets whatsoever.
Yeah, they probably didn't have.
Well, maybe only in like China.
They had the, or whatever the commonly domesticated breed of chicken.
I am absolutely 100% certain this is the most certain I've ever been.
Turkey 2000s are real.
I might have a name wrong, but they were a breaded chicken or turkey nugget
that was shaped in the year, in the number 2000.
What if I just go 2000 nuggets?
You'll get McDonald's menu.
No, no, actually I get the basketball team, the nuggets.
There's too many things called the same thing.
The Denver Nuggets.
Denver Nuggets, god damn it.
I assume it refers to gold nuggets.
It might be a college team?
Probably.
Denver Nuggets.
Did you see the college hockey team?
I forget what city, like the San Jose Sharks tweeted this like
a very like informative thread about like alternate gender identities in like other
cultures around the world, like various Native American tribes and like Mesoamerican and
stuff and like cool, but like why did the San Jose, there was no explanation for why
the San Jose Sharks were tweeting, they just did.
Uh, and yeah, I still don't, I don't understand it, but cool, I guess.
I just want other people to be like, oh yeah, I remember those.
It's weird that I can't find them on Google.
Please comment that if that's the truth.
Don't lie.
Chicken nuggets, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I'm going to solve this.
I think it was just because chicken 2000s doesn't ring a bell and turkey 2000s really does.
Are you, are you ready for me to solve this conundrum?
I'm going to do it right now.
Oh my God, please hang on, you're going to have to give me a second.
You're just going to download an image of a metal finger and show that to me.
That's what you're going to do.
Here's your fucking turkey 2000s motherfucker.
There's minions shaped turkey nuggets.
See, I think the fact that it's, they could shape nuggets into shapes brings credence to this.
Here we go.
Chat GPT.
In the UK, were there turkey nuggets in the shape of the number 2000 made to celebrate the new millennium?
Yes, it is true that turkey nuggets in the shape of the number 2000 were made in the UK
to celebrate the new millennium.
The product was called Millennium Turkey Nuggets and was produced by the Bernard Matthews Food
Company. They were made available for sale in the UK in the lead up to the year 2000,
and the idea was to create a novelty food item that would appeal to consumers looking for something
special to mark the occasion. However, the product was not very successful and was eventually
discontinued. So it was Bernard Matthews.
Bernard Matthews is the turkey dinosaur person. There's no images on Google. This is a travesty.
Did nobody take a single picture of the whole time when it was happening?
Okay, it could be lying. Yeah, if we can't corroborate it with proof, then the fact that
Chat GPT says it's true doesn't mean anything.
I believe the AI when it agrees with me.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it's just that Google can't find the image. I think it'll be on a website that's
outside of Google. It'll be on the dark web. The dark web will have what I need.
Yeah, I mean, if it was real, there must be proof somewhere. What about? Okay, what about?
Um.
Millennium turkey. Bernard Matthews, a millennium.
It's just that they have like turkey nuggets and minions, a turkey dinosaurs and minions.
Listen, I appreciate that turkey nuggets can come in any shape that one can imagine.
And anything the mind can dream, a turkey can embody in their nugget form.
But damn, if you can't freaking find it on Google.
Wait a minute. The free library. Okay, here's link page citation. Can I go to that link?
Page URL. Oh, this is the page. Okay.
Uh, identifying a children's product to signify the millennium was difficult for Bernard Matthews,
Fugu's limited. But for the, but from their research, Turkey 2000 was born. Turkey 2000 is
a frozen shaped product with chopped turkey made into 2000 shapes and then covered in crispy
crumb. The 360 gram pan, which contained on average six very large shapes is already available
for sale. This is from September 1st, 1999. I don't know how. So it contains an average
six free large shapes is already available for sale in a metalized film pack. And Bernard
Matthews believes this is the first time such film has been used within the children's sector.
Well, tasty toasties is the name of their anytime snack. These are two ready to cook sandwiches
filled with cheese sauce and turkey ham. Okay, this is just information, but where is it from?
Okay. Chachi BT says they were called millennium turkey nuggets. This article says they were
called Turkey 2000. I remember 2000. We're getting to the bottom of this. No portion of this article
can't be reproduced. So copyright, copyright 1999, food trade, press limited. So this is an excerpt
from that in a website called the free libraries. I'm just going to link that.
I'm going to link that shit. Okay, hang on. So this is from a library that has saved this
information, which I am sure is gone. Otherwise, unless they made print versions of that magazine
and somebody saved one. No. Okay. Wait, Bernard Matthews.com. Maybe they have.
Maybe they have. I doubt it because they're not selling them anymore.
Product range about us. Contact us. Will I contact them? I might. They made turkey twizzlers.
They made turkey twizzlers. That makes sense. You're right. I knew it. I knew it must be the
same guys. Can we get Bernard Matthews on the podcast? Does he do guest appearances?
Oh my God, the Bernard Matthews among us. They do turkey unicorns, turkey teddies, turkey minions,
turkey sandwiches, turkey balls. Okay. Well, great. Good for them.
They have sliced turkey. Like a little nugget in the shape of a sandwich.
I think there's stuff inside it. What was that? Hamwich. Cheesy hamwich. Okay. It's not turkey.
Ham boys? It's a ham boy. Okay. ChatGBT does not have anything help, any helpful advice on me
for where to find pictures of the millennium turkey nuggets? This is... We could try Bing.
I'm going to try Bing. I've never Binged anything before. Oh my God. I hope you don't cring.
No. Wait, what? Oh, yeah. Me too. Bernard, Matthews, Millenia.
Maybe I'll go to their Twitter. I will go to their Twitter. Bernard Matthews food.
At them on Twitter, Bernard. Where are the turkey 2000s? Right. Yes.
No, Bing is returning largely the same.
Largely the same image results.
See turkey twizzlers, turkey twizzlers, turkey dinos. I see... Ew. This has got to be a joke.
I see chicken twizzlers, but they're branded the same way as twizzlers the candy,
so I don't think that's real.
Was there... I wonder if there was a licensing conflict between turkey twizzlers and the candy
twizzlers, which is... I learned that they are owned by a company called Young and Smiley.
All right, I've added Bernard Matthews on Twitter. Please confirm the existence of turkey 2000s.
Cannot find any images on Google, but I know they existed.
Exclamation point. I'm very serious.
What if, hang on, what if we just use the Google, the Twitter search function and like
search for like turkey 2000 and just filtered by images.
Okay, I see your tweets are the latest results for turkey 2000s. Okay, and this is not...
Of course, I'm the biggest. I'm the turkey queen. I'm the 2000s queen. I'm both of those things.
Turkey millennium nuggets. No photo results for turkey millennium nuggets. Jesus.
It's more... It's like... Somebody disappeared it. Somebody disappeared the millennium nugget.
Like that picture of Stalin with Trotsky. Yeah, yeah.
Somewhere out there is like just a picture of like a plate with nothing on it.
Or maybe some peas. Peas to the side.
Well, that's a mystery. It would be so funny if they actually get back to you about that.
I would love it. I would love nothing more. Let me see.
From top results.
Yeah, yeah. A bunch of results about the country turkey at Bernard Matthews. Wait.
Bernard Matthews on Twitter only has 500 followers?
I mean, it's a turkey product. Okay, but it's like a corporation. Okay, it's not even verified.
Oh, I mean, they don't give a shit about Elon Musk. I can respect that.
Wait. Oh, did they get rid of... Well, no, they haven't gotten rid of legacy notifications yet.
I got their Twitter from their website, so it is the correct Twitter.
I mean, they've posted it. Okay, they post like once a year.
They'll see my tweet. I don't know. They'll see it eventually. I maybe.
I don't think it doesn't seem like they maintain a Twitter presence.
The one guy who's in charge of the Twitter will log on to like promote the new Christmas turkey
something or other. Oh my God. And then they'll see my plead.
They'll get excited. They'll finally have someone to talk to about it. Oh, the latest?
Okay, the latest tweet. I can see why they're not on Twitter.
Their latest tweet in January 2021, they brought back turkey twizzlers,
but they're like different. They're like a different recipe. And all the comments are like,
fuck you. We hate the new turkey twizzlers. Like bring back the old recipe, cowards.
Oh, it's sad. Yeah, people are evil. I mean, I get it.
These look completely different. And I yeah, they don't look.
They're probably are worse. They probably are worse. I don't want to I don't want to.
I don't want to Kate for Bernard Matthews food is limited.
No, I don't care either. But I never liked the twizzler. So I could imagine the people just have
rose tinted taste buds for that. Yeah, well, I just think it was the best thing ever when it was
actually just filled with salt and fat and they like that. It was and you were and you were a kid.
It was it was full of salt and grease and you were a kid and times were good.
And you like that. And that's fair enough.
Yeah, great quality, honest prices since 1950.
It's respectable. What a legacy. Oh, man.
Contact. Oh, they got a they got a physical address. I should go see them.
Wow. Yeah, like they they tweet like a couple times a year and all the replies are just like
people that hate them. They just don't like what they're doing. Oh, this is odd or no or no replies
more often at the very bottom first site. They've got navigation. They've got about us terms and
conditions 2021 gender pay report. And then something something slavery and human trafficking
statement 2022 Bernard Matthews. No. Are they gonna say what are they gonna say? Introduction
to the new new and improved Turkey Twizzlers. They're back now with 75% less slave labor.
Yeah, it's basically we're proud of the steps we've taken to combat slavery and human trafficking.
Oh, God. No, our supply chains. We get majority of our protein from UK farmers
with additional supply from Europe, South America and Asia. Okay.
How are you going to human traffic? We remain committed to minimizing the risk of modern slavery
or human trafficking. It's so bad. It's so bad when your press statement has to talk about slavery.
And it's in caps at the bottom of the website. It's very funny. Nothing else is in all caps.
We're so anti slavery guys. I can't believe you think slavery is funny,
Gib. I can't believe you think that's something to laugh about.
Hey, I'm an Amazon author. All right. I think it's funny now. I'm I'm I'm only the only thing I'm
a slave to is the grind is the is the grind is the sigma grind is the rhythm is the rhythm of the
jungle bees. I don't know what that means.
One day, no, I'd like to try an old Turkey Twizzler, but maybe I'll never get the chance.
No, I think they'd gone. Just get a regular Turkey and twizzle it.
Just twizzle that these these these this is this first attempt at recreating a
Twizzler was not even close. I don't know exactly. I don't know what it's missing.
There are there's the main ingredients in a Twizzler are corn syrup, wheat flour, sugar,
and corn starch. And then past that, there's like a couple other things. There's like,
there's palm oil, there's glycerin. There's, you know, flavoring, obviously, citric acid.
So it might be the palm oil that gives it that like
rubbery consistency. I don't I don't know how you get that. Like I'm not I use the
first the four top ingredients, and I didn't get anything like that at all. So I don't know.
I don't even know what's going on there.
It's a smooth like a like a Twizzler is like perfectly smooth surface and it's and it's rubbery.
It's mellow and sweet. And boy.
Well, we got close, but I still want people to send letters, physical letters to Bernard Matthews
to us them where the Turkey 2000s went, bring it back. We need to go back.
The 2000s was the best time because I was small and I didn't have to do anything.
Soy lecithin. Why is there soy lecithin in Twizzlers? That doesn't make any sense.
What? What do they need to emulsify?
What? Explain this to me. Explain this shit to me.
I'm not a Twizzle master. I don't have soy lecithin. You think I do?
You think soy lecithin just grows on trees? I think I have soy lecithin lying around in
this economy. No, I have sunflower lecithin. I have soy like a normal like a normal person.
God. Soy. Maybe we should get mad. Maybe Bernard Matthews should introduce some soy Twizzlers.
What do you think about that? I think it'll be hard for soy on its own to maintain that shape.
I can use the bathroom. Let's break for a minute. Okay.
Okay. It's time to crack into a diet birch beer.
Birch beer. Yeah. Like the wood?
Yeah. It's kind of minty. It's kind of licorice.
It's delicious. It's my favorite. It's delinci. It's a Leonardo delici.
Is it too early to jump into one piece discussion?
I mean, I don't have anything else to talk about by my book. I don't have anything else to talk
about. That's basically what I've been doing. I made my book real and I've been happy.
And now next week, I think it's chapter five. I'm going to start drawing.
Oh, I think I should make also a little video for advertising the book. Maybe.
Oh, yeah. You should announce it on whatever platforms you got.
Yeah. I've sent it to all the discords. So next thing is video.
So. You should definitely make a video announcement on
Hippo, Cread, and Give and Take, I would think. Yeah.
Yeah. Good. That's a good idea. But yeah, one piece. Unless you have anything else to talk about.
Oh.
Trying to freaking feel. Did I take any notes? Did I take any freaking notes on my week?
Hang on. Hang on. PCP weak. Weak notes. What do we got here?
The pretty weak notes. Pretty, pretty weak notes.
Oh, God, I can do my freaking taxes. That's like soon. Fuck.
Okay. That's not a that's not a thing I want to talk about. That's just a thing I have to
be wary of in my life.
Um, PCP topics. No. No, those are notes from last week. Ah, fuck it. Never mind. I'll think
whatever. Let's talk about one piece. Chapter 10 79. No, where's Luffy?
Where's Luffy? Where's Luffy? Not even once did Luffy appear.
Except in the in the opening and the whatever you call the that one page at the beginning.
The title page. Yeah.
Those are great. I don't I never really think about it, but like having a little like the
logo and then a little thing with a chapter name. I don't have chapter names really for
my comics. Maybe I should be nice. Yeah, I think they're nice. I think they're good.
Um, the Vapors has chapter names of all three chapters.
I think it's because I initially drew it and wrote it without the thought of chapters. So
I guess whenever whatever comic I start next, I'll try and do that.
So, uh, yeah, no, what was it? Luffy cover request by Sunflower Shop from Tokyo. Luffy
watering a lion mistaking it for a sunflower. Very, very cool. Very nice. Yeah. So, okay. So we see.
So we see. What's your name? York. I couldn't remember her name all week.
So York is, is got a plan. So she wants to become a Tenri Bito as she conspired with or, you know,
against Vegapunk. And she was the one who gave the orders to all the seraphim
to kill everyone except her and pretend to kill her for to keep her cover pretend to kill her.
It's okay. So she said, don't kill the Stella. Why does she not want to kill the Stella?
Is it because she'll die if Stella dies?
Yeah, I don't know about that. Because like, I think
that she would not have gone through the whole thing of like, yes, marines, yes,
Goro say, I will help you kill Vegapunk because then she'll die.
Yeah. Why, why, like, I think that isn't a thing. I think that there's just like a
give him to us alive stipulation that she's trying to abide by.
I mean, weren't CP zero there to kill him?
So yeah, so the government wants to kill him.
Oh, maybe it's because yeah, the government isn't just after Stella, they're looking to
eliminate her. So that's what she's talking about to these guys. Don't kill Stella.
Maybe she wants to use it him somehow.
Maybe. There must be, there must be some reason. It's either of its,
it, I feel like it might, it might be like if, like there one being and if he dies,
she dies, but it might not be that there might be some other reason.
I do, I do like that the order she gives to, there's an area of the lab, I don't want you to
damage and it's, I don't know what type of what area of the lab, it might be the secret area where
the papa data. No, I think it would be, it's either a place we don't know about yet or
the place where she currently is with her gun and she shot checker in the head.
Oh yeah, the place that she's storing all the agents. I mean, that would be a sense.
Yeah. It's either that or another place. But what I'm, what that means to me is that later,
in order to defeat the stellar, the seraphim, if they stand in that location,
they won't be able to fight back because they don't want to damage anything.
And they'll be like, oh, I realized that you don't want to damage anything.
Now I can kill you. Now I can get you. That's what I think will happen.
That's, that's, yeah, that makes sense. They, I mean, they would then,
I suppose they would just have to engage solely in hand-to-hand combat and not use their,
and not use their beemo. True.
That would just be what the, what they have to do there because those,
it's the laser beams that they fire in like a fraction of a second or like the really
scary part. They can get you from anywhere in like no time at all. Yeah.
So the evacuation of egg head is continuing. And people are getting out since tomorrow is just,
just chilling with wounds. And then we see, we see a ship approaching.
First first first I want to say look at look at this look at kuma's chin
Yeah, since when is his chin like that?
forever
It's like I thought he had like a big. I don't know. I didn't think it was that pointy
Well, maybe this this particular particular one is pointy because it's a robot. Oh
It's like they like enhanced his chin. Yeah, they gave it some armor plating hmm
You know anything is possible science technology share is amazing. What do they what do they think of next? I?
Actually, I actually didn't catch I actually skimmed over this panel this next one that it's blackbeard coming to egghead
I didn't catch that I didn't even notice that that's so bad
Yes, all right. I have a big like
Is he gonna steal the know me know is he gonna steal the know me what if he steals the know me know me know me
Lamal I
Think it's more interesting than just that okay. I have a big reveler
I
Realized something seeing blackbeard here, but let's continue the chapter and I'll tell you afterwards
Maybe he wants to wait. Maybe he wants to infuse himself with green blood. Maybe he wants to steal Lunarian DNA
Maybe maybe he wants
I'll tell you my theory. Okay. Okay. Okay. It'll involve the rest of this chapter sure
So then we switch over to Elbaf with the kid pirates and
a bunch of a bunch of funny-looking weirdo crews and their captains
Who are like shanks aligned?
Mm-hmm, and this is cute. They're they're like kind of pathetic and the reason they're in the shanks the red hair
Pirates grand fleet is because shanks is nice to them and protects them. Yeah, I think it's cute sure
It's different from everyone else
I mean, they might be tough
They might be they look stupid they look stupid, but you know so do so do you and I don't make fun of you
All right, buy my book for reparations everybody I I bought your book so I can
Book so I can cool you stupid and attack you so I can attack you. Yeah
Yes shackles for heckles
We should do another one of those one of these should
We will we will eventually I
Prom maybe to sell maybe to celebrate when the when the perfect comic party is done. Oh, yeah, that'll be nice. Yeah
Actually, yeah, that would be a good thing to stream about when that's out
It's like hey everyone you can go read the the thing and let us know what you think give us feedback or whatever
But okay, we're I'm getting distracted
Yeah, so kid pirates with captain kid and he's like what the fuck
I'll kill him. Yeah, shanks is telling them to retreat. He's gonna go deal with it himself
And he's got all these these
New we haven't seen any of these pirate crews. I don't think yeah, all these new faces. They're all friends with with shanks
It's cool cuz shanks has always felt very isolated when it comes to like
Yonko, yeah, he hasn't felt like the only person we've ever really seen him with is me hawk
And that's it wait
We saw him with me hawk
Yeah, like way a long time ago before
War at marin for it before the time skip
There was like a scene where shanks is just having fun with me hawk and then he's talking about I refuse to believe that
Me hawk would ever have fun under any circumstances. Well, he's he's having a drink
He's doing the Zoro thing where he's having like like quite was he was he drinking?
Quiet yeah quiet fun. Was he drinking a giant flat bowl plate? He wasn't I think he was drawing drink in a normal size
Normal size little hand sake thingy. Oh fair enough, but a shanks was talking about Luffy and
Me hawk was like, oh, I meant Luffy. He's with this cool sword guy Zoro little punk-ass kid
It's like, oh, how's he doing? How's my little boy Luffy doing you saw him and that was just a little scene. Yeah
Good stuff. Good stuff. I
vaguely remember maybe
All right, but so yes all these weirdos work for shanks pretty cool. He's got the fleets
Seriously, he's got he's got boys. He's got boys. I
Think it's cool though that like the fleets notoriously weak and shanks is just so
Intimidating that people don't fuck with that weak fleet anyway. Wait, where do they say that?
I mean kid calls them jokers and says like oh, is this supposed to be no, it's it's when shanks is walking up the
steps to the ship
All right
And it's like the real reason shanks has to deal with them is because the fleet's notoriously weak and it's like
Haha, you're not supposed to say that out loud like everyone knows it. Okay, so I read this. I read this really fast
I didn't I didn't catch that. That's really that is really sweet actually
Yeah, he has a weak fleet because he just takes weak pirates under his wing to protect them
Yeah, and it also makes him appear so much more powerful that he doesn't need a strong fleet and that they're all fine
And happy because of how like his reputation as being strong
Keeps enemies at bay
Which is really and because his fleet is just really big
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if it's bigger than any other fleet. Oh, okay
Cuz like big mom has her whole family and stuff and kaito and stuff
But white beard had a huge fleet of like bunches of different captains. Yeah, I don't know if this is bigger or like typical
Mmm, he's got a lot of friends. He's makes a lot of friends that shanks. Hey, I just there's a cute
Girl here. We got to stop everything stop the fucking presses. There's the one that looks kind of like piranha. Yes, the the the
Bargain bin piranha, you know what if I can't get the real one. I'll take this one. I guess I like this one
Yeah, mm-hmm Oda continuing to innovate in the field of women
She's got two algers laws hat. Okay. All right. I'm gonna distract. Yes. So there's yasop
Yes, I can't believe it. I can't believe we're actually seeing yasop in the flesh
Yeah, have we not seen him in like panels with the crew? I don't know if we've
We might have seen him like one other time since like did we did we see him like in the very beginning like in romance dawn?
Oh, of course
But like him multiple times after that. This isn't the first time we've seen him since no
No, I know I know I know we have seen him before but like
It's very rare. He's a very rare yasop appearance. He he he shows up
He's like third or fourth on the list of shanks crew members to draw
Like the big boy and I mean it's it's a
Backman lucky lucky lucky roue Beckman and maybe yasop is third after them. Yeah. Yeah
Anyway, like beard is on the move we know that because we saw him traveling to egghead
and
You know
Shanks is doing his Wikipedia looking. He's looking at the wiki to see what this kid character is all about
And
Kid isn't isn't pulling any punches. He gets his big weapon out. I think we saw that in whole cake when he used it against big mom
I forget exactly
But it's a gun. I'm pretty sure he used a big
gun before
Yeah, probably
And shanks in his super hacky you can see is so far into the future that he's able to respond to this before it can happen
Yeah, which is interesting. What is the name? There's it's
Armament hockey is the one that like you use for attack and defense conquerors hockey is the one that you use to like pass out
Intimidate and what's what's this one called observation hacky observation hockey and it's the same as they have a different name for it
It's skypea. They called it. Was it like?
Yeah, I can't remember
Yeah, it was like wasn't key
No, it was some like multiple syllable world. I can't remember
Rayatsu is the bleach thing
observation hockey
Shandra, is it Shandra? No, that doesn't sound right mantra mantra similar
Mantra. Yeah Shandia or something is like one of the names of the island the kingdom the old kingdom
You're probably right
Okay, so
Where was I? Oh, yeah, he was making the gun
He's making a gun sees the shanks sees the potential future. It's odd cuz like I don't know if this has been shown before
We know that in
In
The battle between kata curry and Luffy Luffy learns some more observation hockey to see things a little earlier than they're gonna happen
So he can react. Yeah, but I don't know whether he can react so fast that he can stop it from happening
I think Shanks is just like a level beyond that. Well, what I mean, what's that? What's the point of?
Have being able to see a little bit into the future if you can't I mean, it isn't like the point that like you can react like attack me
But you block it this time
I think it's just the fact that he can see further into the future than Luffy can sure yeah because he's like this
He sees all of these ships being destroyed, but in the end they don't nothing gets destroyed
Mm-hmm. So it's not even like the weapon went off. So it's like really ahead
Which makes sense. Yeah, yeah observation hockey being more powerful means you can see into the future a little bit. Yeah, definitely
You must be seeing at least like several seconds into the future
Yeah, although he is he is jumping he is pretty quick and he's like
Scrambling because he's worried that he won't get there in time. Mm-hmm. So it's just about to happen
So it might not actually be that far in the future
But anyway, he jumps right into kids face and he slices them with a divine departure
See all okay slices right through the gun. He's cuts cuts the gun right in half
And kid gets whacked does he I don't think he doesn't slice kid in half
He just like cuts him
Yeah, hurt some hurt some
I'm gonna Google this quickly because I think somebody said divine departure was like an attack that gold Roger used
Hmm
And I just want to check that
Whoa his oh my god his conquerors hockey even knocked out killer I
Thought it was saying that like killer got sliced by the sword slash
And I think it's saying the killer got knocked up by the conquerors hockey
It's like wow
Okay, I Google divine departure
One piece Goldie Rogers swordsmanship
Divine departure Goldie Roger launches divine departure Rogers make move name in Japanese is Kamasuri
Okay, Odin was hit by this attack
Yeah, it's one Odin from the from from one oh from one oh back story flashback. Yeah, okay
So yeah, he learned that from Roger and Roger was a swordsman. So yeah makes sense pretty cool
Interesting must must must must be a pretty good technique. I guess
That technique that hi that
We didn't mention we didn't mention that the OVA is out. Oh, yeah, whatever
I
Read listen to the commentary read though buy my book. I don't do that
Become a patron become a patron listen to our we recorded like it's like it's not just we didn't commentate it at real time
We paused it and we discussed the OVA
It's what we see
Yeah, I think it's like a 45 minute video or we just like talk about
What the fuck is going on here?
And that was fun
Yeah, that's on the patreon. Okay, so I
Scrolled ahead a little bit
So shanks defeated kid in one attack
Yeah, or so easily and then they did his crew is like scaled and
They give him the road pornographic rubbings that they got at the end of
one oh
So they had to I think he's he's freaking got him. So I mean
He's got does he have all the
Ponyglyphs that he needs now is that well, all right here. This is part of my my
Realization so I think he has just these two he might have
One of the other two he doesn't have all four because if he has all four he wins and he's found rough tail
Yeah, I love tail. Yeah
Although shanks probably would know where it is. So maybe it moves and that's why you need the
Ponyglyphs. I mean, does does anyone know where it is?
Well, yeah, the people who were on gold rogers crew. Oh
Traveled there. So like silver's Rayleigh would know buggy and shanks
Did the whole crew go there before I don't
Know you might be right actually he was there and like everyone found it
Roger left. So
So, I mean they know
What the one piece is?
Right
You know, I it's confusing. I don't really think
We're supposed to have any understanding of whether or not we know
That they know
Exactly, like maybe the one piece. It's just too many things. It could be that we don't you know
Like why would they want to be the pirate king? Why only now is shanks trying to be the pirate king? Yeah
No, I think what's what's all this stuff about?
Yeah, I don't I'm really I'm kind of lost. I don't I don't really see any reason why shanks
I don't I mean, I don't think any of these people like really need like the title of pirate king like that's not
Important to them. I don't think shanks would care about that
He's gonna go
He's gonna do some shit. I don't know. He must he must be going to Raftel
Because there's something he can do there that he needs to go there
Yeah, whatever whatever the one pieces will enable him to do it
There's so many things that I don't feel like I can even speculate on what one piece is yet
All I know is it made gold Roger laugh and that's funny
Did it did I love one piece so shanks leaves and then
Yeah, Dory and Broggy do their special technique that we saw so long ago that technique
What's the what's the brother sister brother sister? What do you call them?
What do you call your brother sister?
Sis no Nissan Nissan Nissan that technique hi. Yeah, okay
Right they use the Hakoku sovereignty
Yes, if you remember when they met the Dory and Broggy the store has met them on the island with the big
Skeleton of a dinosaur
And that's when Nami got like the the sickness that need they needed to go to Drum Island to get a doctor after that
Yeah, yeah, yeah
They use that to blow a hole through a giant goldfish that was gonna eat the ship
They use this this this yeah, that was like a the final farewell and their weapons broke after that
Because they've been fighting for like a hundred years or something or 50 years is probably thank you for the reminder
Did not remember all that yeah
It's it's such a cool like ah this is like back then it's like whoa giants are so cool
But now it's like wow giants are in the main story. They're still so cool here. They are yeah
Yeah, so
Kid I mean, I don't think kid is dead, but his his fleet
I mean, I guess he just had his one ship and now his ship is just gone
Yeah, his ship his crew his crew and his like pirate ambitions are for the moment like toast
Yeah, this is a little defeated by shanks very easily
LaMalle
now this
learning about
shanks doing this getting the the road ponyglyph rubbings and
Remembering the blackbeard was recently fighting Trafalgar law. This is my realization
Giving at the end of 1.0. They shared road ponyglyphs like the store has the kid pirates and the heart pirates
They shared their road ponyglyphs
So they all have each other's rubbings
They don't have all of each other's they had they shared the ones the ones yeah, and they shared the one from
1.0, I think wait wait that was before big mom
No, no in 1.0. It was after now. You're right
but
Yeah, so that there was one at the very bottom of
1.0 if you remember Niko Robin and Trafalgar law found that and they were being escorted there by the old shogun
And before that Brooke Stahl
This is such a cool move by Brooke. He stole the you got a rubbing of
The one in whole cake when he was captured. Oh
Like he was captured like big mom was like sleeping with him and her bed
It's like oh, you're so cool. You're a little skeleton. He hid the rubbings in his skull
That was the joke like he had he did the rubbings of the ponyglyphs and then he hid them inside his skull
Okay, and so after everything was said and done it was like oh
Shame we couldn't get the ponyglyph and then he was like, oh, look at this
Where is where was the ponyglyph?
If you remember there was a big
In whole cake island
Toto land the kingdom
I can't remember the names of the main places but like yeah, there's a big room with three ponyglyphs
one of them is a road ponyglyph and
They were all in big cages and
Only Brooke was able to get in there and take the the ponyglyph before he got captured and then she put him in
In her bed, okay, I mean I yeah rings about I don't remember the ponyglyph being in big cages
But I do remember that he had it in his skull. So yeah, they were they were in like a lock-and-key sort of vault area
Yeah, okay, so they have the 101
They have big and the whole cake one the whole is that is that all they got?
Yeah, it was the same ones the kid has
Those are the ones the kid has and those the ones that law has
Mm-hmm, and the straw hats have those plus the one that was hidden inside the elephant in zoe
So they have what I don't remember that
At all. I'm so bad. I'm so bad at reading. It's okay. I once I read this chapter
I went I realized this wasn't there one wasn't there one in skypea
No, the one in skypea was not a road it wasn't a road ponyglyph. There was information
But yeah, Nico Robin was like, ah, it's not it's not what I was looking for not void century
Yeah, she's looking for the Rio ponyglyph, which is like the information the big one the key missing link
Is that her big goal wait?
so there's
So if you have the is that one like more important than the road ponyglyphs
The road ponyglyphs there's four of those before the four road ponyglyphs point to Raftel and what is that?
Yeah, Raftel. That's what I said
What is the what is the Rio ponyglyph point the Rio ponyglyph contains the information about the void century?
Okay, so like it's in some ways the main one that will explain everything connect all the dots and the rest of them are either
Like yeah, unimportant or tangentially important or like some of them
She finds lead her to the locations of like the ancient weapons like pluton and Poseidon
Yeah, I think pluton was the one in alabaster
It
I don't remember one of those. I think that was the one I mean Frankie had the plans for Poseidon
Yeah, something like water seven
And I don't know yeah, the blueprints. Yeah, I remember. Yeah, there was one in alabaster that I remember that
Right, okay, okay, so so that's the real ponyglyph. It's not anything to do with the left tail. Okay. I
Okay, so there was a third road ponyglyph in
Zhao but wasn't and that was after whole cake. So no, no, that was before so why don't kid and law have it if they all shared
There and they didn't I don't think the store had shared that one unless they did
I don't think they would I feel like
They'll let me too much cuz it cuz like they fought together as a team
from
Like whole cake. I'm I'm I'm not not even with kid. Just just law
I might be being too like nitpicky here
But like I mean I look at this image and it looks like there are four
documents
It does
It really does but like if they have four then they already have all of them so it's like there's no way this four there
That's why I thought they'd like doubled up and there's two of them
It looks like four, but they could just be folded in a way that makes it look
Like that or maybe or maybe maybe because the the it's a cube so there's
Yeah, there would be multiple sheets. There would be multiple sheets for a single. Yeah, glyph
Yeah, that makes sense as well. I guess I don't know how many kid has I assumed
He would have at least the two right they would have at least the 101
I don't even know whether they would be sharing the the whole cake one as well
But regardless
Well, they say well, they say I mean this translation here says take our load pony glyphs
Implying that there's more than one. Yeah, so they probably have two
Meaning there's two more and I looked at the two more the other one is in zoe
Yeah, and as far as we know that has been safely hidden by the minx
Even Kaido couldn't get in, you know, they didn't give them up
Because remember Rizzo the samurai ninja was hiding in the elephant as well
Right, and they didn't give him up because they're friends and like honorable
doggies
Yes
So that's three the fourth one would have been used to be
Under the sea at Fishman Island and it has been moved by the time the straw hats get there
It is no longer there. It is presumed lost. Nobody knows where it is. At least the wiki doesn't have any information
hmm
So there's three
That the straw hats have they are looking for one more road pony glyph and it's just and we just don't know where it is
We don't know where it is. Damn. Um now first off
The fact that blackbeard is a traveling here
Means that he's probably I think after
Luffy's
Rubbings of the pony glyphs
Because if he's here that probably means he beat law and took his
Ponyglyph rubbings the same way that shanks just beat kid
I think that's a fair assumption to make law might not be in as bad of shape
but I think he probably was defeated and
That's why blackbeard is just traveling. He's just going
That makes a lot of sense. So blackbeard would have I mean at least the wanoglyph
Maybe the the whole cake one
Probably not the the Zhao one
So he might have one to three glyphs already. Yes, but yeah, I mean there's probably some he could still get from Luffy
Um, yeah, I mean
So and he's learned learned the information by fighting law that they were they shared the Ponyglyph rubbings and stuff
So it's like Luffy went this way kid went that way law went this way and I fought law
Not only this there's so many things going on blackbeard is also he has pudding right now in the ship
In the in the brig and
Kobe was captured by blackbeard
Oh garp
Traveled out to find Kobe if you remember I mentioned that a little while ago that the many multiple moving pieces
Garp might be on his way to egghead as well after blackbeard because he's got blackbeard
Yeah, if if blackbeard has Kobe, I think he probably does. I'm not sure. I don't remember seeing him with
pudding or anything
But the idea that garp will be traveling to egghead following blackbeard
um
Is funny because he was supposed to be going to egghead anyway with the other marines and the admirals
Oh as part like along with Kizaru and the
I almost called him Jonathan Joestar Saturn Saturn Saturn regalia or whatever his name is. Yes Saturn Saturn
I
Forget his name completely
Saturn Garcia Jerry Jerry Saturn
Jerry Seinfeld yeah, okay the the Gorose
Gorose gay right so
Yeah, okay, I remember that he was like nah heck those guys
But now he's probably headed the same way. Yep. I think that's that checks a blackbeard blackbeard is on his way
Um Kobe is probably with him and if he is with him garp is on his way
Um garp probably hasn't held meppo with him and that other lady that I forget what her name is
Oh
You mean the other marine to take a place
Not to Shiggy. She's not a smoker and smoker. I don't know he might be with like the fleet which will be fun
So the fleet is coming and they're coming after blackbeard possibly also after garp and
There's all of these pacifista on the islands ready to defend but like blackbeard's got us. He's pretty strong
Yeah, it's quite strong. I can't even really think about what is gonna happen when he arrives
But it's gonna be big. I mean obviously they said it was gonna be big last chapter. It's got like
Yeah, wait, this is gonna be the big incident. Yeah, this is one day from the egghead incident is okay
Blackbeard was part of the crew along with buggy and shanks with the gold gold Rogers crew, right?
No, he was part of whitebeard's crew. Oh
He betrayed whitebeard, which is why ace went over to to get him back because he a blackbeard found
The like the whitebeard crew found the darkness fruit the yomi yomi
I think yeah, and blackbeard stole the guy
Oh, yeah, and stole it and ate it and ran and that's why it's like that's a big crime
You can't do that. I would say so ace went to fight him and that lead led to ace being sent to
The Marines that caused a whole bunch of stuff
I think blackbeard literally did that just so that he could invade in Pell down and recruit all of the biggest guys
Yeah
um
Which worked out well for him
Um, it sure did. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, so he was not on the the gold Roger crew. Did he
Okay, do we we don't know anything about him before he was a part of whitebeard's crew though
No, okay, aside from sbs snippets and I haven't read all of those so I don't really know
Yeah, okay. He he once was a boy. I assume he was once a boy
Um, when he was a boy
He was a boy to play down by the sea
You know that song
Yes, okay, just it's munchies favorite. Uh, it's a good it's a good song
captain
Yeah, we don't want to get copyright struck
We don't want the steam power giraffe
Notoriously litigants
A copyright claim in our videos
Where were we?
Okay, so blackbeard, um blackbeard. So blackbeard's doing blackbeard's doing this. So law is possibly defeated
I assume he might not be defeated. He might have just been
like
He might be on his way. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He might be following blackbeard
Like we got to get those he like he got knocked around and the pony glyph stuff got stolen if they shared the pony glyphs
Then if blackbeard beat law and got his glyphs, I feel like he wouldn't think he needed luffy's glyphs
Well, this is why I don't think the straw hats shared the zoe one. Okay. Well, but but but but would law know that they
Had more glyphs that they didn't share
Yeah, but like they agreed to share the ones they got as a team
Okay, like fighting the the the emperors and stuff. I see I see
Um, well fair enough. So yeah, okay. It's plausible
I'll need to reread because like it would be pretty pretty
It would be a lot if they all three of them had three of the the road pony glyphs
Yeah, and now blackbeard and shanks
Have three out of four. And so I mean it might be that way. So then it would be like blackbeard has three out of four
Just all there is shanks has three out of four finding the last one would be the only thing left
Shanks has three out of four. Luffy has three out of four and luffy is currently not completely destroyed
So maybe shanks and blackbeard are gonna go after luffy
But the reason I want I'm thinking that luffy has a different one is because that makes him a target
Yeah
Um, which is yeah, why blackbeard would appear because why the hell would blackbeard come to egghead?
Just to fuck him up
it would
Yeah, no, he he
Would make sense if he's got that that extra rubbing and nobody else has it
It's like well, we got to get it from that guy
Yeah, and also I'm thinking this is my theory. I think that the fourth one was stolen or like
removed
From fishman island by shanks the redhead pirates and put on elbaf and under the lock and key of the giants, which is why
um
They'll they'll be an ark in elbaf and usopp with his giant like
Like he's he's he's in with the giants
He's in with dorian broggy and oi mo and kashi and they love him and so
God usopp will get them the fourth road poneglyph
That they need to get to to laugh tail and that'll be like the coolest thing ever
Why um, why do you say that shanks moved the road poneglyph to elbaf?
I may not have been shanks, um, but I just think because he's friendless with the giants and
You know big mom had one
kaito had one
Maybe shanks wanted to keep it from oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah when you say yeah, okay the fact that he's an emperor and the other two emperors had one
actually
did I mean
Because it was relatively recently so you think it wasn't moved within like the last hundred years it was moved
Like it was there until recently. I remember the the in fishman island
King neptune mentions that. Oh, yeah, it used to be here. I don't know where it went
I don't really remember but the the the one in wano has like been there for a long long time
Right. Oh, yeah, because the the the the poneglyphs come from wano and the one
Oh, that's right
But what about okay the one in whole cake? I mean was that moved there by big mom or was that well? Yeah
Well, I I assume. I mean, I don't know. I think just because there's three different
Poneglyphs in the same room that they moved in there
They're very heavy and difficult and impossible to destroy
And damage but they're probably like like light enough that you could move them
Did she just take it? I mean, do you think she like took it from wano because she's
A emperor and just wanted it
I don't know that she got it from wano. I think I mean a lot of
That there's poneglyphs all over the world
So there used to be that the country wasn't closed that wano was a nation that traded with the world and
Well, not necessarily from wano
But I mean you think she just took it wherever it was. She's just like well, I'm the I'm the emperor. So I'm taking it
It's a treasure
Yeah, it's a treasure and it's mine and as as long as I have it under my watch the other guys can't have it like it seems like an obvious
Then I don't know that the thing was in wano. I don't think
But he probably goes to wano to stay there because it's strategic
And there's probably a lot of secrets there anyway, right only the old the old shogun knew about it
And kind of didn't know about it. Okay
Yeah, I mean
So do you think that shanks?
Yeah, in uh, yeah, when you put it like that it could have been shanks and he is an emperor
So like he his status befits
him having one
So I mean that would mean that he must have the rubbing so like
He then would he would only need the zoe
Yeah, which is which means which means shanks is also gonna have to come after luffy which is like
Narratively, yeah, like dramatically the coolest way the things could be going not just that luffy has to fight
Um to win but also to be hunted by everyone
Yeah, at least everyone who is the most powerful people ever. Yeah. Yeah
Um, so I I think what's gonna happen is the big bullshit is gonna happen at egghead, but lbath
Will be the where they get the final roadponic with
I mean, I don't know what will happen in between, but I feel like I feel like that's there
I mean, it just seems like a cool big place for it to be it feels like such big like defenses
It feels like everything is pointing to lbath right now like all like the ohara records are there and you know, I mean
Dory and brogue and shanks is shanks has apparently been there for a while and he's he's been doing something there
And yeah bringing the roadponic lift seems like a reasonable thing. He might have been yeah
Makes a lot of sense and uh the uh would be
As like a place we've been hearing about for like so long it kind of
Works as like this is kind of where it all shakes out. Yeah
uh
I
I think I think that's where they're going right is that the plan
Or do they they don't even know where they're going when they leave egghead
I mean narratively they must they must go to lbath. Surely they must at this point in the story go to lbath
But like they don't know that yet
Uh, yeah, they don't have a plan. Okay
I think I think the way the oda likes to write
His stories is to have like yeah, you know, they're gonna do something but like the way they get there is like
They're not just gonna finish whatever they're doing here and then leave and then just arrive at lbath
I think it's gonna be a different sort of arrival. I mean
Is are they gonna fight shanks in the middle of the ocean on the way there is shanks gonna be coming for them
Is shanks going to appear in this egghead battle?
Because he's he's just you know, he got kid
And she was just leaving the island anyway. He was just saying
Surely he's not close enough to get there by the time the egghead incident happens. Well, here's the thing
Okay, uh, maybe not but here's the thing
They traveled
From wano the three of them all three in different directions
Uh kid went to lbath
Luffy went to egghead
Law went to I think pirate island where blackbird was or was otherwise
I think it must be pirate island because if blackbird was there and he's just left black pirate island then
Those are the three locations. So they're close enough to each other. Should I know what pirate island is?
It's where blackbeard head is giant skull base of operations like wily
Yeah, it looks like a big skull. It's cool. It's just so it's just it's just blackbeard's hideout
Yeah, okay, it's his it's his base and
Yeah, if the three of them left wano at the same time
And arrived at these three different places shanks was on lbath blackbeard is in egghead now and was on pirate island
That must mean that shanks is also close to egghead on the other direction
Or like close enough
He's not around the other side of the world. This is like it could happen
Hmm
And we still don't know what the hell kuma's doing climbing the red line. What's he doing over there?
Haven't seen him in a while. Yeah, I'm still waiting to find out what's in that damn memory paw
It's just a lot of creepypastas
It's just uh, it's actually the entire internet. Uh, that is they're using it to train chat gbt to um
To tell us about turkey twizzlers
Somewhere in there is the secret of the millennium turkey
Um, the turkey that's that that's the that's the one piece. Oh my god, turkey 2000
That's why roger left. It was so fucking stupid
Why would they make it? Why would they make this it would only be relevant for one year
That's what he said they almost went bankrupt because of it. He laughed
slavery
modern day
to human trafficking
Fishman trafficking fishman. Oh, that's fine. I mean that was like what 30 years ago. Fishman didn't have rights then
It's probably normal. I mean, that's that's true. Right didn't like fishman liberation only happened like recently
Yeah, but like
Cool people weren't racist against them. Oh, yeah, I mean sure. Yeah, probably actually you're right
Um, it was just but but it was probably yeah, I mean probably roger would not laugh at it
But it probably was widely practiced
Oh, yeah, yeah
All the characters you like weren't into it, but all of this the dumb citizens who didn't know any better
They were like, yeah, I guess fish people from the black lagoon. They're scary. Yeah, yeah, put them in the water
I put them back. No, this really does really does help the economy. Just keep this guy
Just keep this really strong guy around
Like working for us. Damn
This is great
I love racism
um
Yeah, so
I'm super hype. I'm super hype
About what is going to happen next
Everyone's here
There's so many people already involved in this like scuffle. There's more people coming
Yeah, and now blackbeard's here and garp potentially and potentially shanks and potentially law if he wasn't completely fucking destroyed
Like kid was
Yeah, I'm just gonna say do you think do you think kid is like basically like done?
Or do you think he's gonna do more stuff?
I think he's done in the same way that gecko moria was done
Yeah, like his his thriller bark was destroyed and like hogback and what was the
uh
Pesson what was his name the the invisible man?
pit
Oh, uh
picar
uh
Nah, I don't say I'm right the the leopard
Leopard man. Is he was he a mink?
He may have been part mink, I guess
But like maybe started as a human
um
Either way like hogback left thriller bark with like gecko moria on a little raft
Yeah, so he basically started from square one peron of just fucked off and left
um
And we never saw hogback again, I guess I don't know I think gecko moria was murdered by don flamengo at the war of marion ford
Wait, really?
Yeah, he was just
This is like during the the the the the all of the stuff happening moria was there and then to flamengo just like
Did a little creepy smile and did like a thing
Ha ha I gotcha
But I don't know if he's
dead. I think he's like
really hurt
there's something going on with moria because
There was a there was a thing much later. It wasn't there with like black beards crew
Uh
Yeah, I'd be more like the invisible the invisible man the invisible man went to
Blackbeard and said please give me my captive back. So I guess moria is like a prisoner
I guess blackbeard has a lot of prison people
Yeah
I mean, didn't he he had um bonnie, right? Wasn't bonnie his prisoner?
Bonnie was his prisoner early in the
the uh
Yeah, when the as the time skip was about to happen
Bonnie was in the new world all of the people in the new world except for the store hats were in
Different places training. Yeah, and bonnie was like
Like beaten by by blackbeard
Yeah, but she bounced back I guess
She doesn't really have a crew anymore. No, I mean she was one of the um
Oh, fuck. What are they called the like newest generation?
Is that is that what you call like all the all those like young like up-and-comers that were at uh
At the at the show body that one time. Yeah, I think that they were called the worst generation as in like yeah these youngsters
they're so
Crazy, they're they suck
Is it that they suck or that they're like wild and like and like the wild and and and they don't care about like
um
Like they like I thought I'm yeah, I thought I meant they're like they're real
I thought it meant like they're just they're real like they're
They're they they they fuck shit up. Yeah, they fuck shit up
And they're like toppling the era that came before which was getting old like white beard is getting old
Big mom's getting old everyone's sort of like normal and
And status quo is sort of reigning supreme and the worst generation are coming in
Which does include blackbeard apparently and they're fucking everything up and I mean it includes it includes gang bees
Who looks like older than kaito?
Uh
I don't know. I don't know if he actually is but like he looks older. Yeah, he's in his 40s or something. Yeah
Um
Yeah, yeah, but okay the worst generation the
Didn't wasn't didn't they have a name like like the I want to say they were called like the millennial stars or something
Or now you're thinking of turkey two thousands. I am thinking of turkey two thousands, but are they the
I'm I think they were the millennial say
I thought there was a name for like those there is another name. I can't remember those specific like eight pirates
luffy gang
Diaz drake killer killer
uh hawkins
Fucking up scratchmen up who?
And like bonnie bonnie
Uh rouge the skype or yeah. Yeah. Yeah
That guy's cool
All these guys
All these guys over all those freaking guys go. It's like I guess we've seen a bunch of guys
Diaz was on
Was on was on beast island. I mean kaito. I was part of whatever
He was part of the the troop though
I guess we've seen most of them. I haven't seen orug in a orug in a while
Yeah, apparently he was like defeated by someone
on
On big mom's crew
We didn't hear about anything after that. I would I'm just gonna show up during whole cake
Yeah, I would imagine I would imagine that this
Means for kid that like like he'll still be around and he'll probably still like follow luffy
But he's not like his his ambitions as like one of the contender for pirate king are pretty much done
Like bonnie. Yeah
Unfortunate. Yeah
I wonder I feel I don't think he's gonna suck it up and like be
Part of someone else's grand fleet though that that's sort of
Doesn't seem like he would accept that it doesn't seem like it, but I don't know. I mean what else what else can you do at this point?
I mean, I think he will just refuse. He was completely defeated by kaito and he was imprisoned
Yeah, until he got out and you know, yeah
They they got back together. They got the back gang back together and these tried again
I think then shanks killed him
He's been killed by every he's been he's been owned by every uh yonko that he's met
Well, no, I maybe not big mom
I don't think he's met big mom
Right. Oh, no, no, he made the he made the big gun. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he's not big mom
So he's one for two. He's one for three, which is like
I mean he's met luffy
Luffy's and luffy's technically one
We call him one. He hasn't fought luffy since he was called one though, but I mean, I guess you're right
Yeah, they were allies. Yeah, so he hasn't had a battle
Okay, um
Uh, yeah
I mean lots lots to
Take from this chapter kid is I liked it kid isn't kid isn't rough
I mean, he would need he would need a new ship for him to get back on his feet. He would need a new a new ship
Uh, yes, where's he gonna get that?
Wait, why doesn't he just make himself a ship out of freaking magnet metal?
Duh, I guess why not?
Yeah, maybe it's uh, no, it would be buoyant. It would work. He could do it
Maybe it'll just take a lot of his concentration to do that. Yeah, and if he loses his concentration just falls apart
I mean, he's just owned
Uh
Well then now there's a guy now, there's a guy who can get around
If he needs to ship or no ship all he needs is some scrap
Uh
Exciting chapter good stuff. Um, yeah
This this the egghead incident
God, yeah, you're right blackbeard garp those guys. I think you're right. Those guys are definitely
Coming
We didn't like if we didn't we didn't there was no indication before this that blackbeard was on his way, right?
He was like doing something else now to see him here is like
Oh, I think it's
It's because we we saw blackbeard recently and now we see shanks. I'm like, I'm I'm thinking I'm thinking law's fate is the same
Just by this one panel
Is this the implication and that's cool. I think that's pretty cool
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm
I I mean, I feel like the fact and putting in shanks are gonna meet if if if this goes if this gets like extended
It's like a big thing. Oda loves law. I don't think that he's gonna have law. Just get get defeated off-screen
No, he wouldn't be defeated off-screen. I don't even think kid is gonna be defeated off-screen, but like
Like kid kid was just forever going kid was just defeated on screen
No, yeah, that's what what I mean is like he's not gonna be out of the story completely
Um, because he's I mean, I mean, no, no, he's a fighter, you know, I'm like Hawkins
We'll definitely continue to see kid and we'll definitely yeah Hawkins is a little weasel
Um, uh, we'll definitely continue to see kid and we'll definitely see law again
But I don't think he's gonna show up and be like, uh, yeah, uh, I lost my lost my my crew lost my ship
I'm just your assistant now
Uh
He he's not he's not gonna lose in a major way off-screen just because Oda just
Like likes him too much, you know, it'll be funny was that and I don't expect it
But what if he ends up on buggy's crew?
Along with me hawk and uh me hawk wait wait no that would be like the perfect fate for like kid and law
and like yeah
Just anyone anyone super strong people and then buggy is like, oh my god, they could kill me in one second
Yeah
Actually, you know what I I said, what's the alternative? Yeah kid joining buggy's crew is like I could I could actually see that happening
um
You might be cut it might be like people like me hawk
People like me hawk and you know what and crocodile now that i'm thinking about it
buggy
might be like a formidable like
Like um penultimate boss for the straw hats. Oh, definitely
Like like especially since me hawk is there for zoro. That's his ultimate fight
I could I could maybe and the thing the thing that's going to be so cool is that like
Buggy has a rapport with Luffy. They could talk in some somewhat equal standing
um
In the in the fact that they have history and then all of like buggy's crew will be like
This guy this guy can talk on equal standing with Luffy the the like the conqueror
Yeah, this this this like super powerful yonko. I mean look buggy's got
credentials he was on
He's been to raftel
He this guy is like a freaking. I know it's it's funny that he's so pathetic. Yeah, this is an accomplished sea
This is an accomplished seaman we're talking about here
It's always going to be so funny
Like the fact that he has that clout and he's
He was at the beginning of stupid clown at the beginning of the manga just fucking around blowing up buildings in small villages
Yeah, yeah doing doing real like petty real like petty pirate shit
um
Yeah, so um
Howard maxing I could I could Howard maxing I could almost see
I could almost foresee like a situation where buggy is like the true actual
Like final threat like the buggy crew is like actually and
Becoming I don't know like even like a bunch of people who are like, oh
We got to kill straw hat and then it's like it's kid. It's it's law. It's me hawk
It's crocodile me hawk was defeated by the straw hats, but like they all have a reason to like fight them
So be like, hmm
Yeah, I'll do that buggy. I agree with this war. Let's go to war with the straw hat pirates. Yeah. Yeah, and uh
Blackbeard joins the straw the buggy crew
Blackbeard's too big for that I think yeah, like I mean blackbeard's too big. He's too. He's he's too big for that
But blackbeard is like the expected final boss
Yeah, in terms of like an an enemy pirate shanks is probably gonna be stronger to fight
But I I've always I've said this before
Then blackbeard, but I think I've said this before I don't know if I've said it on the pcp
I've said on the pod decast I think
um
Maybe not the ultimate fight
But the ultimate competition
And not not the ultimate anything but like one of the major things that will happen between the straw hats
And the red hair pirates is not going to be a combat. It is going to be a davie back fight
It is going to be a davie back fight. Oh, just like with foxy
Yeah, because that is a traditional pirate
Um competition it would be cool to see the davie back fight come back. That'd be interesting
What did that entail? It was like it was the thing where you have to like wager your crewmates against each other
You wager your crewmates against each other. You can wager your flag
And
I don't know. I feel like like the the the the like the gentlemanly pirate, um
Like that's great. I I hope that's true. I hope that happens. Oh my god. That would be a better trade
They should trade just like seeing who could kill each other. Trade jinbei for yassof so usopp can be with stat again
Finally what would happen what would happen if shanks won like the first three and he takes
Like I don't know. I mean that happened with foxy. Yeah
I don't it shouldn't be exactly the same as foxy
But I just like the idea of that being like a thing rather than seeing who can beat the shit out of the air
I'm sorry, but they should trade. They got a they got a trade jinbei trade jinbei for for beck beck beckman be like
Hey beckman, what's your deal? You always got that like gun over your shoulder like tell us about that
Yeah by jinn
Yeah, well, that's not the thing that they can I think they if you lose the game
The other person can take something. It's not like you'd make a trade. No. Yeah, you're right
I mean you could you could potentially wind up in a draw that just ends up you can wage your stuff. Yeah
You can say okay, um
I mean it's like it's like it's like best if I can take these two
Isn't it like best out of three and that's why like they lost they lost a bunch and then they gained some back and stuff
Yeah, and then the foxy agreed to like a big final thing
And then Luffy won and he took
foxy's flag
And he gave him a shit flag
Right
uh
What if shanks steals the straw hats flag? That's probably what shanks would do. It's like i'm taking your flag
How you can no longer use this how could you
How freaking could you it's and Luffy would cry harder than if he was dead
Hey, I feel i'm an idiot. Was that hat was that gold rogers hat did shanks get it from gold roger
shanks got it from gold roger and
I think
there's like some sort of
connection to joyboy maybe
I mean, do you remember in
The emperor of the world in oh, you mean the guy with the eye in the darkness. Yeah, the guy with the eye
he had that that
mysterious compartment in his throne room area
where he was looking at a picture of uh, the
Of Luffy's wanted poster and he sees in this big room a frozen giant straw hat
And we're like what a frozen giant straw hat
It looks it looks frozen. It's it's frozen as in it's just in a really cold room and it looks like this snow
There's a giant straw hat. What? Yeah
um
Why would there be a giant straw hat?
Because the straw hat has symbolic significance
um
Because they're built because they're building a duplicate Luffy but 10 times the size and they had to build a giant hat for him
Well, here's what I this is my assumption after that. I think was
A giant a very significant giant. Maybe the first joy boy or something
um war a straw hat like that
and
um in similar in the way the ace
made a hat
made a little
He made a he made a big hat for a giant
He made a wano hat for for oras
Who did um or oras jr. I think who made these hats?
ace um
Monkey de ace wait wait. Oh no gold de ace wait
Ace made hats
He made a little hat. Um, it was it was uh for oras jr. You remember
Oras from thriller bark sure oras jr. Was friends with ace and ace had gone to wano and learned how to make these hats
And made one for oras jr. So he could keep the rain off him and oras jr
Was the big giant that came to save him at the execution and he held open like a gate or something
And he was probably killed
He's very sad
So the so the art of making these straw hats is like a wano thing
No, the straw the hat that was made is like a traditional like cone shape
Oh, okay. Okay. What i'm thinking is that in a in similar to that
gold roger or
I don't know whoever made the straw hat in the first place
Made that straw hat in a similar way
To another person who had a similar hat. It was sort of like a hat lineage sort of reference. Yeah, sure
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah, of course. Yeah, it's like, you know, it's like a hat lineage, you know, like like it's a
It's one of those one of those had lineage situations
Like gold roger had a big friend called big giant joy boy the giant and like he had he wore a straw hat
Gold roger was like, oh, I'll make a hat like that. That's cool
And then he gave it to shanks and then shanks gave it to luffy and then
Ian was like, wait a minute. This straw hat on this boy looks just like this giant straw hat
I have in my throne room secret entrance special room with snow inside and he said, wait a minute
Wait a minute. What does the D stand for?
D's nuts
D's D's hats
D's hats
Um, okay. Yeah, totally forgot about the giant straw hat. That's uh, yeah, okay
Okay, okay. So there was a yeah
Marishwa's straw hat a straw hat is kept in a freezing room in marishwa
It is very large rivaling the size of him
The person the guy wait have we have we seen like how big he is?
I thought we just saw like his eye from the darkness
No, I think in the in the chapter you can see him walking around
You don't see his face. You see him in like far away
You see him his hand holding the the wanted poster and you see a shadowy face eye thing
So we can presume that he's like a normal ish and he's got like a big
Hat oh, he's got like this is oh, yeah, he's got the big like fucking Dark Souls crown
Yeah, right
straw hat
Duh
There's so much like what the fuck to that hat, but I think it's some some simple thing like
Roger liked a guy who had a hat like that and in reference to him
He made an epic reference by making a similar hat or like bought a hat that looked like it
Because he was a big fan. He's like a big nerd and it's like hey, hey, that looks comfortable
That looks like it would keep the sun off me. Yeah, cool
Yeah, I can't imagine that there's like special powers related to it. It's just a hat
But it's it's probably it's probably special
in the way that it's personally special to gold roger
And that's why it started as a gift that he would give to shanks his special boy and shanks gave it to his special boy
Who
Who is him?
Um, as far as we know, he's the ultimate authority and power of the marines and the world government
World government specifically. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but like but like who is he?
Um, what's what's what's his freaking deal?
He's like some sort of an emperor king a guy who likes power. Yeah, but like yeah, but like
But like he was elected. Hey, he was elected officially
We've counted the votes twice right
He is
Our guy
Look look at this
He received the pity vote he cornered the corner the pity vote was elected the lord of ghosts. Look at look at his arm
Like look at where his arm is positioned relative to his body
Either his head is
like
The crown is the top of his head or
His head is very weird shape. Yeah, he's got very very long arms
I think the idea is he's got very long arms
I mean, they're long, but it's like he has really long like upper arms, but his forearms like like his
I don't know
I can't really tell like how much of this is head and how much his body
Maybe it's he maybe he's really ugly. Maybe he's a real freak. I mean like that giant thing is not his shoulders
That's the top of his head and that's like hair these proportions. That's his hairdo these proportions
I don't know. I just it looks like he might be some kind of freaking freak
Uh, okay. Here's how they you can sort of see his
So his head is kind of his eyes are kind of up near the top
Of the the lump it's the lump there. Wow, I don't even know
It's a real funny guy. What's going on with this
person
I I cannot wait to see them
I can't wait for him to be very funny looking
What was um the five elders?
Saturn Garcia
I I don't remember but yeah, probably
Uh
Take hit arc
Vegapong j Garcia Saturn j Garcia Saturn. Okay. There we go. Okay. Um boy
What how many fuck it it's it's funny
That it's been so long since we've known about these old men and now
This the first time
One of them is being involved directly. Yeah. Well, did we learn about them?
I mean, we knew about them before fishman island, right? We knew about them a long time. Yeah, the this is like
Pre any's lobby, I think
Yeah, seeing them standing around with their really long legs just in silhouette. Yeah
Uh, oh man
The egghead incident
It's freaking gonna be big
I gotta pee again
Then you want to do voicemails? Yeah, let's do voicemails. All right, it's a
Okay, I'm back
Okay, okay
Voicemails over one piece over no more one piece more like zero pieces
um
First send us a voicemail speakbip.com slash pcb voicemail
Uh first voicemail of the day is called
Three two one go best and worst pcb memory
The the worst pre cb memories. I don't want to think about
Yeah, I I can I complain about I complain about pcp memories all the time
On my stream and elsewhere. So, you know, whatever it's but well trodden ground
I honestly my best pcb memories are like
Like well when when we're hanging out together at a ride con
And I don't know if there's anything specific we're doing is usually in between content that is the most fun
And and and like arriving at the airport and everyone going ah
Pug that that those are fun. Those are fun moments
Yeah, that was all that was always pretty good. Um
Trying to think if there's one I mean it's hard to say I think just one, uh, I mean I liked the the fucking
uh
Going around radcon three house and doing like the gopro stuff
That was really that was fun, but it was also really it was stressful. It was a little stressful. I guess I found I found
Radcon arena quite stressful. I found radcon four more stressful and I did really and it shows because I did really badly at it
Yeah, did you you did the task at stroll lecture during I mean, I oh no, I mean specifically the like the shooting. Oh, oh
Like the the the actual
the shooting, I mean
Yeah, I don't remember
Did very poorly at that. I don't remember thinking
about
Like doing well. It was just like ha ha isn't this stupid
No, I was I was trying to win, but I was not good
It was not good at the skills required. I love playing with toys everybody
I sure sure
Um, I mean, I mean, uh good
I don't know. Yeah, that's just hanging out on streams and stuff. Just uh
Yeah, probably just chilling probably just chilling at the radcons in between
Chill and max in between
relaxing all cool
Yeah, oh, you know, you know what mad bull mad bull was a good one
Oh, yeah, watching that and being and freaking out as we were all watching it together
Available on the plebe and weed blu-ray for limited time stcomics.com slash store.html
out of stock
soon to be out of stock
It's also on it's either jesse's or or
Yeeg studio lamal. It's on one of those channels
I don't
The first episodes are on one of the channels and the like later episodes are on the other channels and I don't remember which is which
Uh
Yeah mad bull is mad bull was really fun. Really hype. We all got fucking we all lost our minds
Oh
Okay, genuinely watching the the the rumbles
I think the one that the one that brunswick won was like I was out of my fucking mind for that one
Uh that oh, that's that's a contender for like hypers
Most fun like single events in mpcp history
That one might be it. I also I have very fond memories of the ape escape. Let's play where me and jesse
Beat ape escape one late at night. Yeah
Yeah, that was fun
I think everyone was there. I think is that's is that still up on the channel?
I think a lot of people have asked about that. That's still up. Isn't it?
I mean, I hope so
I'm pretty sure it's been downloaded because if it went and it did it definitely came back
A bunch of people
um, have yeah a bunch of people have mentioned that to me like a lot of
Old pcb heads seem to like that's their favorite stream. Yeah six years ago four hours 43. This is the the radcon radcon 2
Yeah, I think radcon 2 is my favorite radcon all things considered
um
Yeah
It was there were the expectations were not that high and there was not a lot of like we got to do this
We got to do this. We got to do this
We were all just kind of hanging out
I mean, I guess I guess plebe and weeb was filming
At the time but like I was not really like
I was only occasionally was I actually doing stuff
with it
That was most I mean it was mostly like vik that was like
Uh, like I mean those are like do the setup and stuff
um
It was but like they would be filming episodes in the in the the not the garage the the the weapon room or whatever
And meanwhile the rest of us would just be yeah hanging out and streaming or what making a making a rumble characters in the living room
And that was a lot of fun
Oh
maybe
You know, it's hard to to say a favorite radcon actually. I think radcon 3 had more
enjoyable downtime moments
It did have a lot of that radcon 4 did not have a really nice environment
To it. Yeah, I agree. I agree. We did that was that was added a lot
Just hanging out in the snow sometimes
It's it's hard
Wait in the snow. Oh, yeah. Yeah in in Sharon mass, right? It was snowy
Yeah, two and three were both really fun
Four was four was fun
But there was a lot more stress
Um, yeah, it's hard to pick
Two I think two was
Oh, I was like
I like had to arrive late and like leave early
Oh, yeah, honestly. I mean, I mean my like life at the time was pretty shit. So like radcon 3 was like a like
Beautiful respite from all that
Uh, uh, so that was nice
But also it comes at a time in my life that I was kind of like under I was I was not I was not feeling super good. So my
You know, I wasn't as happy
Uh, I was very carefree at radcon 2
Yeah
I'm gonna I'm gonna say my favorite memory is the the brunswick
Brunswick wins the rumble
Okay, okay. Well, we spent a long time on that one. Uh, next one is called. Oh, it's a it's a vocary link
Let's go
Guys, I did it. I finally did it. Oh my god. I had finally had sex
With a real real woman a consent woman
a sane woman
I did it
Ha ha ha just kidding
You should have seen you good one
You got us. Why would our faces have moved that much?
You didn't see our faces. This is an audio only
You should have seen the little face on the gravestone light up. Does it still do that? I don't think it does that anymore
no
Uh
Hey, good good joke. Okay next one is called
Um, well, it's like yes, and then there's an image
No, and then there's a frowny face
So this is the yes
And it's a fat cat it's a squishy cat
That's a nice that's a nice little cat
I mean, I
Yeah, it's fine
I mean cats don't need to do much to be pretty good
Yeah, I sure
I mean, I just
Was this really worth making a voicemail about? I mean, it's pretty normal. It's pretty normal cat video. I don't know
man
I don't know. Oh wait. There's no there's audio that goes with it. Uh, three two one go
I know Ben doesn't like anything good anything fun, but true you guys want to see my cat
Oh, it's your cat. All right. Well, let's be this nice nice cat
Uh, yes
Thanks
Next one is called Nate edits one frame per day question mark, uh
three two one go
I I just
Why the fuck did you two release the paradise? Oh, like why did you participate in the paradise?
Right, like I don't did you
Was it ever supposed to be good?
Why is it coming out now?
Like I don't
Because people pay for it in this video. It's a fucking virulent poison. It's like a like a curse
That's that's just a fine wine aspect. All right. I mean, why is it coming out now is because it wasn't done until now
Uh, I mean if the choice, I mean, are you suggesting that we should not have released it?
Like we can't do that like we had to release it because we said in the people pay for it and some people are happy
So, you know, and that means it was worth their money. Even if you know
I mean, I get I get be I totally get and I would agree largely like
This took three years to make like I get it
But like I mean, I'm not embarrassed. I'm not
It's funny to laugh about how embarrassing is I'm not that embarrassed about it. I think it's kind of a funny video
I don't care that I'm in drag or that I was like doing stupid stuff on the beach or pretending to be a girl that lost my top
In the ocean
We thought it was stupid and funny at the same time and I still think that
Yeah, yeah at the time filming it. I was like, this is so stupid. Ha ha lull and then watching it again
I'm like, this is so stupid lull
And it's great
Yeah, it's fine
I don't I don't get
I don't get the I mean, he's like, what's the problem? He's chocolate. He should be giggling
Because the funny video
Okay, I I saw I just I saw a lot of comments. I saw some comments that were like, why would you release this?
And it's like, why wouldn't I why wouldn't we release it?
Maybe maybe they were asking in a tongue-in-cheek way and just didn't come across
I think that's mostly what they're saying. This is like, this is so cringe. How could you live with yourself?
How do you sleep at night? Yeah, that's one of the funny things easily
Simplest simplest thing in the world
On top of uh, how much was it? $15,000
$30, $35, $34,000? Wow
Yeah, uh
We used we used most of it. Well, we used like more than half of it. I think
Um, next one is called, uh, oh, well, there's voicemail. So let's listen to the voicemail three two one go
Don't you want to see my other cat? Oh
Yeah
I clicked it and it's showing showing his vagina
The video is just a close-up of his vagina
No, this this is uh, look at this
This little gremlin is getting scratched. All right. All right. Cool. Cool cats
Nice slanted nice slanted ceiling in your room idiot. What do you live in a freaking attic?
What do you leave it a fucking pyramid?
What do you live in a freaking house with a roof on it? You fucking poor fuck get out of here
Um, I have a roofless house so I can look at the stars
Yeah, so I can be closer to god
Next one is called is that gamer's tavern three two one go
I
Tell you what y'all ain't gonna play this
I got out won't say what I was going to do. They'll get me a two-liter cup
That's gonna go out to liquor store and get me a small bottle. You know, just a little big bottle and carry around
Well, here's how I go to I go to the
McDonald's I'll get me a large coat
Yeah, I drink some of that out
And then I gotta buy like five me rob a blade and go out to liquor store
Do not get a little balling lost me
I'll do it. I'll put me a little bit my trip. Yeah, right around a little bit, but yeah
I made that down
And you know what I did?
I said girl. I wanted just a large straight to go because okay, so I went to pull money out
I left my pipe in my pocket. Well, it crashed through the counter top
I'm not so I picked it up pretty back in the pocket
Now when mother fucker with my bills were and guess what, you know
My medicine was in there, so he hit the counter and went girl. I'm sorry about that. She goes, that's okay
I got my large drink and I got that. Yeah, what other no, I wouldn't know. Yeah
I got a date first and that
A real voice and I had an onion on my belt, which was the style at the time
Oh
No, this is this is out of wilds
It's out of wilds noise. Oh, no, not out of wilds. Um
Thanks, I couldn't follow what happened
But I like he was talking about going to the liquor store and going to mcdonald's and and he got a date
And he had an onion on his belt
Nice next one is next what is called des a desiccated deprived husk three two one go
What's this a new upload from the pro crest natus? Yes
Oh
Oh my god
Nate
So juicy
So luscious a date a deprived nate fucker. Yeah
Raising good
Yes, they sure are
They got a whole 15 minutes and well not at all. It wasn't in every frame pieces of
pieces of 15 minutes of chunks
Of nate sprinkled generously
throughout
The next one I don't want to listen to so I will not do it
I'm gonna do it. I'll just turn my it says getting get got kind of loud
I'll I'm gonna listen to it. Uh three two one go
Yeah, yeah, woohoo that beginning part with them was kind of
Yeah
Hey, I'm glad you like the video. I'm glad you like he enjoyed the video game. Uh, what video?
The ova. Oh good. He enjoyed it very much
Uh, okay next one
Uh, there's another cat one
Oh, uh, I don't see the cat
No, it's a new cat. Yes
This one has a pendant in the frame
Let's let's listen to the voicemail three two one go
Okay, guys, but for real though, what do you think I should do about my chronic foot tonight? Just kidding
I want to see another cat I found on this tree
He is a cute cat. It's rolling over in the dirt. He's got his belly up
This one's just rolling around in the freaking gutter. Why does he have a?
What is this street cat have a rug?
Where'd he get that?
A rug steal it from ike. Yeah, he's like on a rug. Oh, no, no, that's a curb
That's the stone. He's rubbing himself on the stone curve. Yeah
It's very funny when cats are
Dirty little bastards
That's that's this guy. He's filthy. Oh, he's getting
He's getting filthy
All right. Yeah, cool. I guess uh, next one is called an uplifting story. Oh, it's a chat gbt story
starring ben saint
All right, I guess I'll read it
um
Ben saint had always been a bit of a loner
He spent most of his time browsing the internet arguing with strangers about politics and vaping lots of vaping
It was his escape from the mundane reality of his life
But the more he spent time he spent on the internet the more he fell into a spiral of self destructive behavior
The arguments would escalate quickly. He would lash out with insults and threats losing his sense of reason
The cycle would repeat itself over and over leaving him feeling more and more depressed
One day as ben was browsing a forum. He stumbled onto a post that caught his attention
It was from a user named magical gnome 43 who claimed to have the ability to grant wishes
Ben rolled his eyes at the obvious troll but something made him click on the profile anyway
To his surprise the user had left a message to him specifically ben saint
It read I see or in need of some magic meet me in the park tomorrow at noon and I'll show you what I can do
Ben dismissed it as a prank, but he couldn't help feeling curious the next day
He found himself in the park at noon looking around for any signs of a mysterious user suddenly he heard a voice
Hey there, buddy. You must be ben, right?
Then turned around to see a gnome with the face of george w bush smiling up at him
Who are you ben asked trying to keep his cool?
I'm magical gnome 43 of course and I'm here to make our wishes come true
But first let's play a game of jenga ben was taken aback. This was not what he was expecting
But he decided to go along with it
They set up the tower and began playing ben was doing well carefully selecting each block and placing it on top of the tower
Just as he was about to make the final move and win the game
The gnome pulled out a remote control toy plane and flew it straight into the tower knocking it down
ben couldn't believe what he was seeing
Hey, you cheated he yelled at the gnome cheated nonsense the gnome replied grinning
I just used a little bit of magic and now I've shown you that sometimes things don't go as planned
But that doesn't mean you should give up keep playing the game and one day you'll win
Ben was confused, but he couldn't deny that the gnome had made a point
Maybe he was too focused on winning the argument and not focused enough on the process
Maybe he needed to take a step back and try a different approach
As the gnome disappeared into thin air ben realized he felt a sense of hope that he hadn't felt in a long time
He was still struggling with his bad habits, but he was willing to try something new
And who knows maybe there really was a bit of magic in the world after all
Wow
I really learned a lot. Gnomes don't exist
I really learned a lot too bad too bad toy planes and jenga are the only big mints of my imagination
Uh
He's just used a little bit
I like the idea that he's magic example is
Be flying a toy plane into my jenga tower
He's not magic you could have just had that
I just you some and I said you see you see ben
This is the sign that you always just got to keep trying and never give up and one day you'll get one day
You won't get a little toy plane smashing your jenga one day one day it'll pay off and I said hey, yeah
That's true. Actually that isn't that me
I feel feel a lot better about I like the idea as well that
It's it's like chat gbt is like
I don't know what the prompt was
But it's like trying to tell an uplifting story
About how you should not be on twitter so much and it thought I know what this needs a gnome
It needs a little gnome. I didn't meet the looks I didn't mean I met the gnome on a forum
I met the gnome on a forum
What forum am I browsing?
I was thought it was like is it george w bush because bush did 9 11
So he made the plane fly into the tower like is that is that
Is that what it's going for?
Hey, you cheated cheated nonsense. I was just doing a 9 11
Nonsense. I was just uh getting us embroiled in a never-ending war in the middle east
Uh, you sly devil
And I learned nothing
I I
Good thanks for the tail. Uh, did I mention did I talk about how when chat gbt told me about munchy minutes it described
The the thing about kyle and the other guy like how they had to do the fusion dance to merge into the monster
Yeah, and then it gets like oh, yeah, yeah, so then they had to fight against the monster
It's like what are you what like it has no idea what it's talking about
um
Next one is called ben's stream chat
Uh three two one go
Hey ben when are you gonna do face cam also wears munchy
Speaking of munchy, why aren't there any new pcp episodes on spotify?
By the way, you should play one step from edith. Have you heard of it?
It's almost as good as this other game
Rainworld check it out if you like battle network
Anyway, while then you're a vtuber now change sides. I guess
lol
It really do be like that sometimes um
It's like seeing ghosts
If they're they followed me they followed me over from twitch
uh
Just true next one is called the blu-ray question
Uh, wait a sec. Did I download that one? No, I didn't I got download that one next one is called the blu-ray question from
At yes.com three two one go
If you ask me
No one ever does
My only problem with the manifesto
That it doesn't go far enough
I think
If you really want to right the wrongs
of Trixie
Save the pcp brand
You need to record season two
We got to make season two of pleave and the weave it was promised after all god give you up for it
Was that even a tail?
What was what was the pleave and the weave even about?
Also, no, I don't want to do that. Also. No
um
I mean if it was like watching a
Like a whole show of an anime
It probably was I think they watched the first like four episodes. I remember watching the kaon movie when on the episode
I was on but like
Trixie and like Jeff
And jesse were like watching a lot of stuff
They were cramming. I think it was that they watched the first couple episodes and then for the final fantasy one
They had to watch like a couple movies
Um
Yeah, uh, by the way, this guy's referring to my blu-ray manifesto at stcomics.com slash
brm.html
Uh, that's read it. Um
The uh
You know, they tried to um, I don't remember if who told me it was Trixie or jesse or who but they said that like
I think after rad con three
They like like jesse like stayed with Trixie for a while and they like tried to film rad con uh
pleave and weave season two
But they just like gave up and like threw the footage out that they had like recorded. Yeah, I guess they I guess they didn't like it
I remember Trixie saying something like it wasn't very good or
And then did Trixie go to see jesse and they tried to record more there
I vaguely remember. Oh
Maybe it was I
I don't know. I could be misremembering. I thought it was after I thought it was after rad con three
It would have been it would have been like um when Trixie was doing road trips for the first time
And then one of them was jesse to do a bunch of pleave and weave
She did a big loop around the the country and yeah, I think she yeah, maybe it was then actually
It was before may I guess may was right at the end of all that
You mean may the person yes
No, it was not
Oh, you mean it was before like the breakup. No, it was before they had met that there was a road trip that led to
Like one of those stops on that road trip was meeting may the first time you you're totally you're totally you're totally whack
You're totally whack. You're totally wet. You're wiggity whack right now because may Trixie knew may even when she was living at
Digi house and that and like that was like pre rad con three because remember Trixie wouldn't wouldn't not bring may to rad con three
I know that I'm saying that the when
Trixie tried to get
Went to jesse's house to do pleave and weave stuff. I vaguely recall that being like part of that road trip
as as she recalls it Trixie Trixie was with
May
Before I moved out of digi house and that road trip was well after
I had I was gone from there like a digi house wasn't there like a first little road trip and then like other road trips
I don't remember I mean there were I I listened to like uh digi bros and listened to these stories
And that's about all I know so I mean if that if that were true
If that were true then that would mean that like oh, well, I guess that would kind of
So they tried to film it like
Not even that long after like that would have been like pre rad con three. So that would only been like a year
That would only been like a year after
pleave and weave was recorded. Yeah, or like maybe a year and a half
I think there was just it was just wasn't working some reason
I don't know. I can't remember what they said about it
Wasn't wasn't the last episode of pleave and weave not released until after
Radcon three or like it took like almost a year to to get all made
Yeah, it took a while for them all to get edited because
And I mean radcon three was like like only a year involved
Yeah, and because jesse had like his house flood and stuff that delayed him
but but like radcon three was only like a year after radcon two so like
Pleave radcon, I mean, I mean pleave and weave he was jesse was editing rad
pleave and weave like
The whole time so they couldn't have tried to film season two until like that was well
over
I think I mean they could have tried
I think I think that I mean maybe I think the idea was
Radcon two ended but they still needed to film another season of pleave and weave
So Trixie drove to jesse's to try and see if they could do that for a bit
I just I just gotta say I just gotta say
Uh
I'm not gonna dwell on it, but I want to say that if
If if Trixie
Or jesse had been like just more transparent about like the the blu-ray thing and just been like i'm sorry
We fucked up
We we we can't make the blu-rays. We we misallocated the budget. We didn't know what we were doing. We we fucked up
I'm sorry. I probably wouldn't have been that mad about it. I would have been like, okay people make mistakes
What made me upset about it was that they just continued to lie about it and continued to like deflect
And like pretend that it was still happening when it obviously was not if they had just
not lied about it
I would have just let it go. I swear
I mean they could have always in the back of their mind thought we'll get around to it
But I mean it was just to an extent. I think Trixie probably did
But like she wasn't
Yeah
She just wasn't it was it wasn't it was not true. It was just not true
Um, and there were no steps being taken towards her ever doing it and in fact
Steps in the other direction were being actively taken, but like I said, I don't want to dwell on it
But they did want to say that
Yeah, uh next one is another image
It's better not be another fucking cat. I swear to god. It's a different format
Wait, is this is it more than one image or is this just an image?
Okay, me listening to ben and gibb talk about one piece even though I know nothing about it, but it sounds like they're having fun
Oh, yeah, that's great. Thanks. Thanks for enjoying the rambling. That's that's why we're here man. So you can
Do this
Next one
Is uh another imager if you can believe it
Um
NATO, Ukraine. Oh, I saw this one of the great epics of this. Oh this tweet
We are harry potter and william wallis the navi and han solo
We're escaping from shaw shank and blowing up the death star. We are fighting the harkinans and challenging them
I'm glad I don't know what the harkinans are
um
Thanks, thanks for the rocket for the rockets like what what on earth is going on with that whoever
Made that tweet
What is wrong with them?
um
What on I mean, I get going on I I I understand the urge to like I understand the urge to like
Relate, you know a an ongoing political
Thing to you know a pop to pop culture. I understand that impulse
but like
To just
Yeah, I don't know
There's a line and there's a line and you've crossed it here. It's it's just so it's like
When people do this, it's usually pretty cringe, but this doesn't make any sense
This is like ready player one. It is. It's ready player one. Remember harry potter. Remember braveheart. Remember han solo. Remember shaw shank
I do
It's just like all your favorite movies and tv shows
But it's war in real life
The challenge they should have they should have stuck with one thing. They should have just said yeah
Imagine if Putin was Thanos now. Do you see why we gotta send you know what?
You know what that's still not that's still bad. I know it's still bad
But at least it's funny because then you couldn't have like purple
Putin
They should have just posted a picture of Putin edited to look like Thanos to just give him the fan. Yeah
Like that. I don't need to read the people can enjoy even when it's bad
Yeah
Yeah, they should have just had him
they should have just have him
snapping the freaking glove
And uh, the freaking donbas region just turning into into little little turritos
uh, or whatever
The liberated
Thanks for the rockets. Yo, just fucking mentioning han solo. Thanks for all these rockets. It's not even the main guy
He's not even the main guy
Wait, what do you mean? We are haunts
Because because solo a solo story was coming out of han solo memory or whatever
This is so fucking stupid. It doesn't even make sense because han solo is not under attack. Han solo could have
Just left and he decided that he was going to do the right thing and join the conflict. That's that's not the narrative you're trying to
The idea is that is that uh, uh,
Ukraine is the underdog being attacked being bullied by this this greater power. Yeah, it should have been they're they're the rebels
They're the rebels
Yeah, they're the rebels. They're the the luke sky. Han solo is not a rebel until later. So princess lair
Isn't william wallace a real person?
Only like an yeah, honestly comparing compare. Yeah comparing it to william wallace the historical figure who people know from brave heart
Is like perfectly reasonable like that's a they should they should have done that. Yeah
Yeah
That that's no objection. I know william wallace from the age of empires 2 campaign
We play as the scottish
I just know i'm from that movie
Uh, uh next voicemail is called in case you wondered three two one go
I'll never go trans
nice
Keep up the good work
keep well
Well, we'll get you
We keep listening buddy keep listening to the pcp and we'll get you
ha um scoff guh guh
Next one is called uh, whoops three two one go
so, um
About that
I just saw the ova and
Okay
I just saw the ova
Sorry all of these losers look like cute girls. Maybe I could
That's what I thought
crossing my arms
I could look that good in a
One-piece swimsuit if I wanted to if I was on a podcast
If I was on a podcast people wouldn't even care what I looked like
Next one is called bge's spicy salts a threat to nate
Oh, no
Wait, I gotta
Did I download the last one? Uh, yes, I did. Let's go download this one. Okay, three two one go
Nails
Oh tow beans tow beans. Yes, I just got it. I figured it out after maybe maybe a third of the way in
Because he was talking about
kittens or something
Uh, I probably probably can't play that because of copyright
Oh, really? Well, it's a song, isn't it?
Unless this person made it it's very good. I but it sounded like they were recording it off their phone from like a thing
Uh, I if it's if it's a
If it's a parody cover, I don't know what the original is
So maybe you're right, but you know cute
Nonetheless, he doesn't love a good tow bean
Nice
Next one, huh? Next one is called, uh, it's an imager
Oh, okay digi brony
Okay, brother and pony. Oh brother and bony
Brother and pony become brony digital and brony becomes digi brony digi brony becomes digi bro
Digi shortened to digi and then what transliterated or whatever into trixie bridgey bro also
It's it's not actually it's not actually how it went
This is this is not quite historical. Yeah, because digi digi the the name digi bro predates digi brony
Yeah, I think digi bro comes first. It was 21st century digital boy
um, yes
Which I which is from that which is from the the the bad religion song
Is it I thought it was like the the the manga
There well there is I mean there is a there's a bad religion song called 21st century digital boy
Oh, you're right, um, what was I thinking of the 21st century boy?
Yeah, um the one by um 20
The one by the guy who did billy bat and the one that he does the the man band guy 20th century boys
Yes
So it was it was
No, I think it's from the song
So 21st century digital boy and then I don't know exactly when that became digi bro
But she shortened it to digi bro. She made it as a
for
Username probably on some thing or forum
Yeah, probably and then uh the other thing I mean correct with ney and digi bro and and digi into digi
But trixie is also short for for Beatrice
So you would have to so it's not actually derived from digi
It's partially derived from digi in that it's also sort of I mean
She told me
Say trixie because it kind of has like the same vowel
Configuration and like it kind. I don't know. I don't know. It's like a weak connection
But it's like there if you want it I guess
Uh, so, you know
It's still it's funny to funny to see the the etymology
Worked out, but it's just missing some links, but it's okay. It's a good it's a good effort and I appreciate
I appreciate the attempt at etymology
And uh, I'd like to see an updated version. Oh
The next image I'm looking at. Okay. Let me let me let me scope it
Was this me at um brony con
Yeah, why are you you look like you're in like a airport
Well, I had the dyed hair
so
It must have been a
I feel like it was a I had that hair at brony con. I think this is a brony con
um
Or it might be
I mean, it's around that time because my hair looks
like that. Oh man
I'm I'm I'm
I'm just
This is not relevant to the meme
I'm distraught that like I'm distraught that my beard is graying so fast. I look at this and I'm like
Oh, I had hardly any grays at all
Uh, it's over. It's over. But uh, like a like a salt and pepper beard looks cool
I know everyone says that everyone says that uh, but they're lying. They're lying through their teeth. They don't know
They don't know the gruesome reality
No
It's fine. Stop lying
Everyone says that until they get some and then they have no it's not cool. It's bad when I start to get white hairs
That'll be funny. That's what you think
Oh, I'll laugh. Oh, no, I'll I'll film myself laughing about it. You think yeah, we'll see
We'll see anyway. Okay. Everyone was mad at me
I mean not people weren't even that mad at me. All right, because of the whole like
Because the whole uh, cheesy said oh andrew callahan asked multiple times for sex
And I said well, that doesn't sound that bad. Yeah, I think it was
What was it being framed as like I would agree that it's harassment
But I think it was framed as it depends on how it's done
And I'm like, okay, there's the words mean different things. I don't know whether it counts as abuse
Technically, it really depends. It's bad. Absolutely is bad. I mean, it's like not a good thing for a person to do
Okay, it's it's at it's at its most benign
It's a it's a bad look and it's and it's annoying and it's embarrassing and like
If it's like over text like it has literally no power to do anything like over text
And like you literally she can literally just stop us replying or block you
So like in that case you just look like a little whiny bitch and and like
You know, it's not good
But whatever in person I can totally imagine
How it's like how you could do it in a way that is pushy
That is, uh, you know potentially even threatening. Yeah, or something like that
so like I get it I
I just as I said as I said at the time
I didn't have all the details and I didn't know the entire context for it
And perhaps if I knew I knew the details and heard like the full report from the the accuser
I'd be like, oh, well, that sounds terrible. That sounds awful
uh
Why are you upset asking again doesn't invalidate your previous lack of information
It's simply a new request after all it is possible that you've changed your mind since my last request for your consent
I will of course respect your answer for the purposes of this limited exchange
The past entered not necessarily inform future
In reality, it is a mark of my deep respect for you that I consider it possible if you'd have undergone the necessary character development
If you've reached my question with a fresh perspective, I think otherwise you deny your life your self interpretation
That's our our tropics takes of a change of character story. I put it to you again. Will you have sex with me my peepees?
I don't know what the next line would have been my peepee so big
My peepee is enormous. I can't
My peepee go poo poo
Gross gross. I hate that. Um, that's I'm gonna throw up. Um, oh god. Oh, I really hate that. That's how that's how we counter it everybody
Yeah, just just have your peepee go poo poo and then they won't want to have sex with you anymore
Uh, next one. Oh wait, uh, did we just look at that one already? Okay. The next one is puppy girls versus cat girls
Three two one go
Really a six hour podcast. Yeah, everyone complained this year. He would have cut the podcast off at its knees
He would have let it die like the hero god that he is
I love nade true. I want you to come back on the pcp nade. Are you a fucking coward?
Why won't you come on? I love you. You power for not, um
recasting or whatever you call it his twitch stream
Um
Rating
Rating you refuse to raid
Refuse to raid in another act of cowardice
They just keep piling up. Sonsu's art of war states that if you don't rate a stream you're a little bitch
That's true. Yeah, I remember that I remember that
um
This wasn't about cut puppy girls or cat girls at all. No
Okay, next one is called
Oh, it's called a hoo boy
Uh three two one go
Can we check in really quick just just for a moment and and confirm that like
When you when you ask for for
Sexual favors over and over again. It doesn't really matter whether or not it's coercive
Uh, because it's still sexual harassment to do that
Like like yeah, I'm very sorry to to bring this up
But like I feel like it's kind of fucked to just leave that at like
Oh, that's kind of annoying, but it's fine. Like no, I do feel like if you do that
um
Kind of like cheesy said you're not uh, you're not accepting
They're like
They're no
So annoying on a normal on a normal basis. You're
Asking over and over again, which is fine over and over
He didn't say over and over like a sexual topic and a sexual advance that has already been rejected
And that's I'm sorry. That's sexual harassment. I don't care that it doesn't immediately violate their consent. It's
It's it's still violating their consent to like having a sexually like
Explosive interaction. It's probably sex. It's probably sexual harassment. It's probably sexual harassment. I think in dms
In in a similar way. I'm sorry. It's fucked. No, it's probably sexual harassment. I would say it is
Uh, you think it is probably about it. Well, I mean, okay, just because the terms are vague like, okay
I cheesy said multiple times and like, okay. Well, how many times?
two times or ten times how long but it elapsed between them, uh
a minute a day a week, uh, you know
Yeah, I it it's probably bad, but like
there's a there's a there's a there
You could I could I could if you I could construct a scenario that the that that the the way it was described to me
Accurately fits that I would not consider sexual harassment necessarily
Uh, but if it's yeah, I mean
Well, like if you make a comment like hey, hey, and then they say no and it's like, oh come on like that
That's not that doesn't go over the line into sexual harassment. That's just like you're say you're you're DMing you're DMing
You're like, hey want to have sex? She says no. He says come on
You you know you want to have sex with me because I'm so sexy. She says no, I don't want to have sex with you. You say please
no
I mean
It's a little needy
It's needy and pathetic
I wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't even call it. I mean, it's a proposition
And maybe you and maybe you should have dropped it after the first one or two
But is it what would I call that sexual harassment necessarily? What's the number?
I would say I would say probably pass two. Yeah, I would say pass two is sexual harassment
You get you get one extra little little pathetic
attempt
To you you get one attempt to save you get it you get a savings
But what if she says no, but in like a but in like I'm just kidding kind of way when she goes no
No, come on. No, we can't do that. No, but it's like she doesn't really mean it though. Oh, that's you know
You know
Uh, women women are all women are always saying no, but they don't actually mean it. You know what I'm saying
You know what I'm talking about? I know. I don't know what you mean. Yeah, everybody. Everybody knows what I'm talking about
Everybody knows I'm talking about. I'm just kidding. By the way, don't quote me. Do not definitely don't quote that out of context
Definitely don't tell anyone don't let anybody know that I said that under any circumstances
um
No, everyone everyone her rang me and made fun of me
Yeah, it's bad. Yeah, it's it's in most cases would probably be sexual harassment in some cases
It could be done in a coercive way. Yeah. Yeah, you're you happy. Are you all fucking happy? You're never happy jackals
I mean they all sound pretty happy when they're chuckling as they say these things like
Did you I mean obviously
I don't like the chuckling. I think it is those chuckles of contempt
Those are chuckles of contempt even when you're right chuckling when you say are you sure?
It's unacceptable
I would I would consider chuckling to be a violation of my consent because I didn't you didn't ask me if you could do that
Isn't there somebody forgot to ask
Me just doing anything
They should ask
They they would they ought to ask me multiple times if they're allowed to chuckle
So that I can say no every time
Okay, next voicemail. Yes, it's called kill the intrusive thought three two one go
Oh
You know I've been having this intrusive thought lately and I've already watched the show
And you're talking about one piece. I'm like they should have me on the show
They should have a random person on the show to be their facts checker and to answer all your questions
Give those to too many facts. Please kill this intrusive thought for me
Please do it
I'm being cringe. I'll kill you. Um, I get it though
I get it. I mean, yeah facts is
it's if it were
Like a proper like attempt at being like this is a podcast about one piece
Fact checking is probably important
I didn't need to do that for the podcast because Nate would have facts
But then again, he would also make things up and get things wrong sometimes
He would have he would have I've heard people say that he remembers things wrong. He remembers things wrong
I mean, I know he has like a tendency to like
Say something and not realize he said it incorrectly
But if I don't know what the truth is and I don't check him on that
See, so that's fun. This is why I'm the superior one piece because I don't know anything
You listen to the listen to the last hit. I don't remember shit about what happened
I'm like a little baby with a fresh a freshly laundered brain just like
What now wait, there's a wait there wait the the minks live on a on an elephant. Oh, yeah, I think I remember an elephant
Yeah
That's the name of the gun
Isn't it zao
Zo is the island
Zashina is the name of the elephant
Oh
I think there's a I thought the elephant was the island
Don't the minks live on the elephant
They live on the island on the elephant
Look what?
No, the island
I thought the elephant was just walking through zuneshia not zashina zuneshia is a big fucking elephant
Zuneshia is a big and he has carries the island of zoe on its back. There you go. Oh
Oh, all right. Okay
Gotcha see I see I've got the facts
I don't even I don't even pretend to know what I'm talking about now
But now I'm in the position of being the nate where I think sometimes I have the facts and maybe I'm getting things wrong
And I'm just saying and you're being like who might believe it. That sounds that sounds reasonable
It turns out everything I've said this whole episode has been wrong. You've made you've been making it up
There is no there is no treasure tree atom. That was never a thing that existed
Uh, uh, there was no there's no frozen hat in in marriage. What like what like of course that was just a fever dream
Uh, there's no such thing as the turkey two thousand nuggets. There's no turkey two thousand nuggets
Look, they were never real. I've got to search through the one piece wiki. That's my one piece
The turkey two thousands. I left it there. That's your all blue
That's my old turkey
Uh, and then the neck there's a wait, is there any more last minute voicemails? No, we got the last one voice grail
Sure, I'll take it three two one go
Nice, what's your first?
Nice, guys, what's your first? Uh, hi guys, what is uh, yeah, guys, uh, guys
What's your favorite?
Favorite what favorite anime?
Yep, another fucking masterpiece of a voicemail
My favorite anime is that was not me that was part of the voicemail by the way
That was not me saying that I thought I actually thought that was you saying I knew you would I knew the listener would but no
That was part of the voicemail
But it but it is what I should say in real life
But it's already been said for me. My favorite anime is
uh
The owl house
Shut up
And it's good
Continues
Um, I guess I'd probably have to go with fully cooly or maybe gurren lagen. You've said that before that was a joke question
You must give a silly answer
Oh
Actually, I like how house. It was just a new answer
um
I like that I like that one anime that that one guy in russia has been making for 40 years
The one about the technicolor dreamcoat
Is it in black and white?
Yeah, it's been going on so long. It's not even technicolor. Have you seen that at that atrocity guide video about the
Well, I haven't seen the video but I've heard you talk about it. I've seen the gifts of it
Yeah, it looks really disgusting
I actually hate how it looks. It's horrible. Um
It'd be so uncomfortable actually watching that film imagine
Uh, that's a good anime though
um
Wow, I wanted this to be a short one and it still ended up being like it's still almost four hours. Yeah
We just can't help ourselves. We did. I did have a lot to say about the one piece chapter. It was very hate. Yeah
It's pretty, uh, but I guess we're done
You want to call it?
All right, uh, spend send us a voicemail speakpipe.com slash pcb voicemail become a patron
patreon.com slash the procrastinators and buy clarissa gunsmoke volume one on amazon or kofi
Get it on kofi if you want a pdf if you want the paperback book go to amazon. It ships in like a day
It's really quick. It's great
I'm gonna have it soon 15 bucks or your regional equivalent
It's pretty pretty good free shipping with prime or
If you have a full cart
That's how I do it chapter is one to four with clarissa gunsmoke. I'm gonna start working on chapter five. I think next week
I think that's what I have next on my plate. It's kind of hard to imagine
Do you want to start?
I mean, I'm still working on biscapades. Do you think you could maybe start like I don't know
doing some like
I don't know. Like is there anything else that the the the the magazine needs
I mean those cover design interior page and stuff
I guess I could
All right, I mean
I guess I haven't decided on like fonts and and stuff
right, okay
I mean, that's somebody's got to do that at some point
um
and then
Shit, is there anything else?
Are we done?
Buy my book. Buy the book by Clarissa. Okay. Bye end of the episode. Thank you
Mwah