I won't bless that guy that son of a bitch.
Hello, I'm the Angry Video Game Nerd.
And I'm the Nostalgia Critic.
And together we are...
These farce floor on the mic.
These Nostalgia Video Game Nerd Critics.
Yeah, it's 2023.
Yes, Happy New Year, Merry Christmas.
We didn't make an episode a week ago.
And you're just going to have to deal with it.
Because we were both...
Well, you were traveling. I was also kind of traveling.
We just like...
It was like already Tuesday past the Sunday we were supposed to record.
And we were like, when can we record?
And it didn't want to.
We would have had...
Like if we had the Nostalgia...
It would have been on Christmas Day we recorded the episode.
And it was like, I don't want to do that.
And I don't want to do the day after or the day after.
Because I got stuff done.
And they don't want to do the next week on New Year's.
So here we are on the second.
January 2nd.
Yes.
Almost the anniversary of my favorite holiday.
January 6th.
It's not as funny as 9-11.
They're going to do it again?
No, it's not as funny as 9-11.
No.
9-11 has a better ring to it as well.
But then again, yeah.
But then again, you know what it is.
What could ever be?
Oh, shit.
I shouldn't say 9-11 in the first two minutes of the episode.
They'll catch that.
They'll catch it.
Okay, so I guess how was your Christmas?
Okay, so that's it.
Now let's go to the one-piece recap.
I mean, we want to talk about that.
That's cool.
It's very cool right now.
It's so cool right now.
I'm so glad I got back into it when I did.
Because everything else sucks except for the current arc,
which is good.
Yeah.
The end.
My Christmas.
Yeah.
What the fuck happened?
Let me briefly explain the logistics of my Christmas.
So, all right.
Now, I, like many of you,
have a mother and a father.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
So, you know, I got two sides of the family.
So on like the 17th,
my dad's side of the family usually does a Christmas Eve celebration.
And we'd had to do that early this year
because one of my cousins was going somewhere
and some uncles wanted to visit him or something.
So we did it early and that was fine.
And then I did like a family thing.
My, you know, my Nate and my sister were not in town.
So my Christmas Christmas was just me and my parents,
which was, you know, fine.
And then my mom's side of the family usually
does a New Year's Day, get together.
And so yesterday I got on a train
and I went to go to Connecticut to go and see them.
And that was okay.
A lot of these people I haven't seen in ages and ages.
And, you know, that was all, that was fine too.
But I'm sort of relieved that it's all done.
Yes.
Because it's sort of a lot of work.
It is.
Traveling different times.
It's funny how like Christmas is like a moment of cheer
and everything and like, oh, it's a holiday.
It's a time off.
But it's like the most stressful, like work-intensive holiday.
It's actually much harder than just normal living.
If you think about it.
There's all sorts of events that you can't,
you just have to plan around and people you got to see
and you got to say hi.
I mean, I don't dislike saying hi to relatives.
No.
I just don't like getting in a car and driving somewhere
or going on a train or getting up early.
I don't like any of those things.
I'm less bothered by it than I used to be.
But I still don't really love, you know,
I got to spend my, got to use my day to do,
got to do that with my day.
And then I got to like prepare for it.
Rather just.
And I got to like make myself look normal.
Like I can't look like a freak.
Right.
That's the whole thing.
I mean, not, not that hard.
Not that, not that hard in my case, but the.
Oh, very hard for me.
I know.
Some of us have a, some of us are,
what's the phrase?
A normally, normally challenged thing.
What did I get for Christmas?
I got an immersion blender.
Immersion.
Imm, in bur, an in burgeon blender.
It's the, it's the kind of blender.
It's like a, it's on a long stick and you put it down into like a fluid and you blend,
you stick it into the liquid to blend with rather than,
rather than putting like stuff into a blender and blending it inside of the blender.
Like it's a weapon.
You could use that to get someone.
Yes.
You, you, you thrust it like a, like a fencing saber at your opponent.
And it blends whatever part of it strikes.
Could you, could you drill inside of a watermelon and then blend it from the inside?
No, it has to be, it has to be liquid.
It has to at least be mostly liquid.
Hmm.
Then what's the point?
Sorry, there is none.
What's the point of anything?
You know, my sister got me gummy molds, shaped like skulls.
So that's cool.
Hell yeah.
I'll put drugs in those ones.
No gummies.
Just drugs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just hard press, like cocaine dust.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll probably think of some other things at some point.
One or two other, like kind of neat things.
Okay.
What about you?
What was your-
My stupid holiday.
It was much of the same. I also have people with sides of families
I went to see actually only want to see my mom's side of the family this year
That's how the family you know doing all this stuff. I admit most years
I will often just only see my dad's side of the family
That's why I had been so long since I'd seen my mom's side in a lot of cases
Which I feel kind of bad about cuz like they're just as valid, you know, they're just as valid. Yeah, and they miss me
You know, they they've been denied. They've been denied and my presence. They've been denied my presence
You know, I feel I feel I feel bad
I feel bad because because it had been so long since I'd seen some of them
I felt a bit awkward, you know, I try I talked to a bunch of them
But a lot of you know, I think I was more quiet and I think I ended up talking less
Overall to the that side of the family that I had seen less of even though I kind of needed to do more catching up with them
Yeah
Yeah, it's this a classic like
So
First of all, who are you? I don't recognize you. You don't want to say that and then right?
What have you been up to? Oh the last 10 years of your life. That's a lot to talk about. Yeah
It's like you don't want you don't want to approach that they don't want to approach that so you just sort of nod
Yeah, yeah, I mean, that's that's exactly that's exactly what happened
Well, what are you gonna do? Yeah
I'm it's it's got to a point for my family stuff. We're like
There are younger children around. Yeah, and like some of them are cousins
Mm-hmm. Like like you formally apologize to
To deadly comics on the last episode. He said that your cousin's kid is your
Cousin once removed and I said it's your second cousin. He was right. I was wrong
Yes, cuz it's yeah, I still I can't wrap my head around it because the names are too similar
It actually it actually makes sense. Okay, imagine you have
One common ancestor and then they have two kids and those are siblings
And then if you step one rung down like each of those siblings has a child
Those are cousins and then if you if those cousins have kids
Those are second cousins and then if those cousins have kids those are third cousins
So if they if they are on the same rung of the
Generational ladder, they are first second third fourth fifth cousins
But then if like if if you're talking about one generation removed like your second cousin's father is your is your second
second cousin once removed and your your second cousin's son is your second cousin wait
You've lost me no, you're you're your
No, it'd be your uncle you're your cousin your second cousin's
Father is your second uncle once removed and your second and your second cousin's son
He is your second cousin set he is your second cousin once removed
But but he but you are his second uncle. No, he's your second nephew fuck. Oh, no
See, I think I think the person the nerd who came up with all these terms didn't even have a family
They were just fantasizing about they were they were just thinking about what if they were just thinking
I wouldn't it be funny if I made it up
named like this
Nobody else had even thought to try
But oh, yeah, that was the thing that the young kids in because I was usually the youngest cousin there
and then one of my uncles finally had children and
Now there are cousins who are in my same like quote-unquote generation
They're first cousins, but they're like they're like 10. I see
They played pumpkin alley. We had they had their laptops there and they played the video game
Oh made shit. Did you did you like tell them about it there and they were like, oh shit
You made a video game. Can we play it? Yeah, and that was that was really nice
That was a really nice moment cuz they loved it. They really got into it and they
It was really gratifying and and and stuff seeing them play
And like was like figure out the controls was Henry there
He was too out of it. I think to want to go
It's a long drive. Oh, okay, so you're younger cousins were into it. That is pretty cool
That is pretty cool. And I watched them like figure out
How to play the game like they got stuck in places and then he walked around like what do you do?
Oh wait, and then they saw like I mean the part of the level that I had made
Like just deliberately to like guide them towards the solution and they figured it out and it's like, ah, yes
Level design. I did it. It worked. Are you 10 year olds can understand pumpkin alley?
That's pretty good. If you if you're 10 years old right now, are you a zoomer?
Or are you whatever comes after zoomers? I
mean, I
I don't know what the I think generations are like vague. So like yeah, sure I
Would assume the generation that comes after zoomers is ones that are born of zoomers
So this is the new generation. No, no, it's not quite that the generations like
Millennials parents are boomers and
And
Like gen gen Z's parents are our gen Xers. So it kind of like skips one. I think right
So I feel like the zoomers are like 20 now
Zoomers are like are like teens and 20 now
But I'm only like I'm not even 30 yet. So like I
Guess I'm on the cusp of zoomer and millennial maybe
I'm like a late millennial. I think you're
Yeah, yeah, that sounds about right
Anyway, I just whatever I was I all I wanted to ask was like I just wanted to refer to these cousins as zoomers
But then I thought they might even be too too young to even be zoomers. But anyway, I just want to
Well, that's
Well, you know that the nomenclature in our fck right for the generations
I forget there's the I mean, there's the original people like the first generation
Oh, yes, and then there were the two the tumors were the people that joined in season two
And then there's the three tards
Season three and oh shit. I forget the one and
There are like sub ones that like the ones that joined during the negapause. There was between one and two
There was a name for those people to the dead dead born or something the born dead
Yes, the born dead. Yeah, the born deads because they joined when there was when everyone was a ghost and then the
Four necators from the season four. It's something like that. It's something like that
But but anyway, I just wanted to know had these kids
Were they familiar with like that kind of game?
Like have they ever played they ever played Jack and Daxter Banjo-Kazooie or whatever?
I know like oh, it's one of those kind of games or were they like what the fuck they had no commentary on like
Oh, it's just like this game. They just were playing it and like oh cool
Yeah, yeah, so I think
It certainly didn't confuse them they they saw it was a 3d game and you're a pumpkin you jump around
You got a little person
That's pretty cool. That's pretty cool. You can pick them up and throw them. That was fun
I mean people asked me like what I've been doing and I did you know, I
Would tell them
You know, I made a I made a big huge video on YouTube that did pretty well
Got a bunch of views and then sometimes I would say oh, yeah, I'm working on a book
I'm working on finishing a book of a graphic novel that I drew a couple years ago and everyone would be like, oh, that's cool
You know, everyone everyone can mostly comprehend those things
Did get into like a discussion about like the YouTube algorithm with one of my cousins
She she showed she showed me a tic-toc that she had made a few years ago that had gone viral
She's pretty funny. So, you know, that was cool
Yeah, didn't like didn't like show off slime and punishment or anything because that would be embarrassing
Yeah, I showed off
Clarissa gunsmoke. That was the two things. It's like, oh, what are you doing? Oh, I'm just sort of in between
Work and I'm working on like a little comic project. I'm doing Clarissa gunsmoke. I fill up my website
I show them things and I'm like, oh, this is really good. They say I'm like cool. Yeah. Yeah, they say
and then there's pumpkin alley and that's like
It's like, oh, yes
This is funny. No, I can I can I can see like you can show that to anyone
I mean, I feel like anyone can immediately appreciate like, oh, wow
You made a whole video game and it actually works and like this looks like
That's the way I would have made pumpkin alleys is so that when I go to family gatherings
I can show them something and I don't have to talk
Look at that. Look at the funny colors. That's not true. That's the only way you don't have to play the guitar
It was funny. My grandma was watching the kids play and she's like didn't understand couldn't understand what a game was
And she's like, oh, this is quite a long film. Isn't it like she thought I'd made a film
Oh, come on. They were playing she was I mean, she's a little
Okay
Is she like
All right in that case, I guess it's understandable, but like
Old people know what video what is she not? What is she not fucking remember Pong?
What is she not remember fucking Pac-Man and Donkey Kong like give me a break old lady?
Oh, she's like saying you're staying here. Stay in your fucking lane. It's like 80 something. Okay. Well, she was she's
Sure, but that means that she was like only she was only 40 when like Donkey Kong
What I'm so I'm not 40 year olds didn't know they did yes
They did 40 year olds would they would see Pac-Man on the news because it was a craze. They would see they would see
You know, it's not like she doesn't know what a video game is, but she just didn't in that moment
She was just sort of like lapsed in like understanding. It's like we made a game
She's like, oh, that's interesting and then later. She'd be like this is quite a long story like she doesn't realize very funny
Like it wasn't that's her. That's her little anyway of saying this is boring guys. This is boring
Yeah, well, she couldn't do anything about it. She was in the ha ha she's old now and she can't
The future is now
We sit and we play our film and I brought COVID for her for Christmas terrible shame on you shame on me
I didn't know I was perfectly I did catch I did not it wasn't COVID
But I definitely caught like a cold or something from my early Christmas Eve
Family gathering I was sniffling for a while after that, but it was fine. It wasn't that bad
Hmm
You know
The thing about being a dude at these sorts of gatherings is once you get your salutations out of the way and you've kind of said
Hello to everyone most of the time
You don't really have to talk because a football game will be on and you can just sit down and watch the football game
And that's perfectly acceptable and and then you don't have to like talk about stuff
You can just be like oh man that interception. Oh, he blew it. Oh, he blew it. Oh
Come on, man. Why don't you root? Why don't you why don't you why don't you bring one in for the home team?
You fucking said oh, this guy can't catch. Oh, this guy. Oh, he's got no range. He's got he's good close range
He's got no long-range game. Ah, what happened to Brady? Ah, geez, you know, it's just it's so easy
It could not could not be simpler
It's funny as not usually like a sports game on during one of those gatherings
Maybe the sometimes some sometimes during the summer, they'll probably be like I don't know if like some sort of thing
during a I don't know if maybe I
Feel like it might be an American tradition and the reason I say that is just because you know foot football season is in full
Is in full swing during the holiday season. There's always a game playing on
on Thanksgiving in
Christmas, maybe not on Christmas Day, but but on
Well, no, sometimes they're there probably is around them
You know, they probably do play on Christmas Eve Christmas Day New Year's like it's right the lead up to the the playoffs so like
Things are things are pitch. I mean the last
The last like
Football like soccer thing right that ended and that yeah that ended so I mean so, you know, it kind of would yeah
I guess yeah, so that would make kind of make sense that like that's a thing that we do just because the seasons are
lined up for it, but
Yeah, but anyway that makes it very like
Make makes it makes it effortless
That's my version of playing guitar, so I don't have to talk to anyone
Is just sit down and watch the game, but it's sort of yeah, there was a guitar there
I did play the guitar. I didn't know what to do. I'm just making fun of you. I was I was looking pretty good
I was looking pretty good. I had like some makeup on and I was like
Some people knew that I was trans and some people didn't and so but I didn't feel like correcting people and
it was just so it was it wasn't like I
Don't have any relatives that are against that. I don't think even my grandma's just sort of like okay like she's just
That's a very um, that's a very long
Gender you've got there. What's what's what's going on with that? Oh
Wait, that was a that was a call back to say that okay, I understand now lol
um
Yeah, yeah, I I looked good and I felt like because I looked good
It was easy to chat with people as opposed to when I look like a weirdo
And I'm like, oh these people are normal and they have like normal lives and stuff and
They're gonna hear about me talking about my art stuff. I'm doing and I'm like, I don't know
Yeah, I guess I don't know I gotta hey
Yeah, I don't know like that's that's all of it. It's always been like that
Like ah, but it was nice. It was like I had like a glass of wine. I was chatting with people
It was normal. I was so normal. It's amazing. That's a me. That's I'm happy for you
My my big takeaway from the holiday season has mostly been I
Mean I kind of already knew this but it sort of was hammered it into me even more
so all my relatives not all of them, but like most of them are quite bougie and
I
Truly am an insect just an insignificant worm
You know all my uncles and stuff most of them got like big houses and stuff not like mansions, but like
Some of some of them kind of have things you might you might describe as mansions
My cousin bunch of my cousins ones around my age got houses
They're they're like they're renting their houses to tenants and stuff, you know, bunch of a bunch of them are married
Bunch of we're having kids and whatever and I'm just like, ah jeez my I
Just I feel I feel a power differential forming there. I feel like I am lower on the societal
Totem pole. I feel like if it came to it if it came to some sort of conflict some sort of like battle between us
They would they would crush me they would defeat me because they have more institutional power in the form of
Capital and that
Upsets me that upsets me quite a lot. I
Want to crush my enemies. I want to crush my enemies and I want to know that if I need to crush someone I can crush them
Do you understand?
I do understand. Then we are then we are then we understand each other and then we are
Yeah, I mean trying to think of my family, there's a few of my cousins on my dad's side are like
Like one of them got into banking and he's like super wealthy and he's got his own house and it's all like
Was that a cousin you say a cousin? Yeah around around your age or a little older like five
Six years older. Yeah, okay, and he and he he studied really hard at school, and then he got back into like banking and stuff
And it's like that's some big money
Sure, and it's it feels weird talking to him because I'm like, what am I I'm like on the other side of the family
unemployed basically and
I
Draw a bit and I make some music sometimes and animate and yeah, yeah
Yeah, I don't know how I can hold a conversation with him even though
We were like quite close when we were little
He showed me he showed me Grand Theft Auto
He showed me Vice City when I was like six. Yeah
And I played that in his room and it was like, oh my god. I ran over someone. Ha ha
Interesting that was cool. Yeah, and it's like now he's he's not different. It's just like I feel a little
Inadequate, I don't know and and yeah, so I so I understand the feeling
Yeah, yeah, sounds like pretty similar
um
I mean, I guess um
I guess my options are you know one
Just cope just cope and sieve
Cope and sieve and that's and usually that's what I would go
But let's explore alternatives here
Uh, I mean you can cope and grin. I can I can
Forgo the sea I can see this is important. I can cope and grieve cope and grieve. That's pretty good
Um, but no, I can I can just cope with it and be like, well, you know
I'm a I'm an art guy. I'm an internet poster guy. It's okay
It's okay that I don't uh
But I haven't bought a house or whatever
Whatever, I'll just be the indie. I'll just be the indie cousin man. It's fine. Yeah, and that's that's whatever that's okay
um
I could sell I could sell out
Is it you kind of it kind of makes me well
Kind of makes me want uh, it kind of makes me think again about that thing that I might have mentioned before about maybe
Maybe I should look for like a job with a studio or something
Maybe I should look for some kind of some kind of like some kind of slightly more legitimate
employment
you know
uh
Get some dental insurance now and like, you know, I've said this before
uh, I wouldn't
Wouldn't want to do some bullshit like uh, every time I every time I talk to my dad
My dad's always like you should work for oracle bet like you should like I know lots of people that work for oracle
Like they're always hiring you should work for oracle like why the fuck would I work for oracle?
What are you talking about?
What's oracle? Uh, some like technology or maybe they like cyber security or
Uh, internet browser or something, you know, they do some fucking stupid internet
He's offering some nepotism
I guess I mean, I don't think he has any connections to oracle. I mean, I guess he
He might have some patience. I don't think he could get me like a foot in the door
um
But I mean, why would I why would I want to work but think of the fact stack spin?
What would I what would I do for oracle?
I mean, you'd you'd hack into the mainframe. You release the secrets you'd whistle blow
I don't think that's a good way to get paid
Uh, you get paid first then you do it one paycheck
Um, uh
All right, so I mean
But you but you know what I'm saying like I don't want to do that
But um, but I would I would kind of like to say oh, yeah, I I work for someone I have a job doing something
I just
man
I don't know
Is it really just for the benefit of like a social awkwardness moment in a family gathering not not really
It's not really about that. It's not about being embarrassed
It's because you know, I didn't really feel that embarrassed. I didn't feel like my cousins were judging me super hard or anything
I didn't feel like oh no. What do they think about me? It's not like that. It was about
You know, just the the things they were talking about
Uh, just made me
I mean, I'm sorry, but it leads me
Literally what I said about like they could crush me and I want and I want to be able to crush them first
Um
Yeah
You could crush them with a train become a train driver. I'm sorry, but I'm just I'm just
Out to a crew as much as much power as much power as possible and I feel like um
I have I have I have behave suboptimally in that realm. It's not about right. It's not about money
It's not about it's not about buying things
Except that it is because capital will protect me
And will be used and I can wield it as a weapon if I need to
So it is about money, but not in the sense that I just want to buy things with it
Uh, I feel like this this could slot into the meme
Of you hiding behind the table and something coming through the door
Like family members coming through the door who have money
What's what's coming through the door? Is it is it a is it a bunch of
Job offers being like come out and come out and accept your paycheck
I hate capital I hate capital or uh, something something like that something like that
um
Okay, I don't want to I didn't want to uh, uh, I don't want to drag this point out or anything, but uh, that's
That's for a man. Hey suggest. Hey suggest in the comments
Suggest to me in the comments
Uh, what what jobs should I apply to that I can uh, you know work as a creative professional
and also a crew capital and uh
You should become a professor become institutionally powerful a professor of weird internet shit at a real university
They'll probably have a course for that. I'll just do that. You know what?
I saw a tweet the other day and I don't know if it's true
I don't know what this person's bona fides was
But he just said like you used to be able to just send a letter to a university and be like
Hey, I just want to study so-and-so
Give me a job as a professor so I can do that and they and sometimes they'd just be like, okay
You know not all the time, but like if you had something legit
If you had a nice jacket you had a nice I do I do have a nice jacket. Well, it's kind of old
Maybe I should get a new one
But um that you know, I think like nowadays
I don't even know how you'd go about doing that. I don't even know how you'd go about doing that these days
Probably it's just the same. It's just everybody thinks it's not doable
Send a little letter so hand written letter
and you and like
And then uh better than hand written better than lipstick kiss like a lipstick kiss on the bottom xo xo
Better than hand written
Assemble the letter from cut out letters from different magazine articles
And then attach like a photo like a crime photo, you know the ones
Sure. Well, first I have to commit a crime to take to take a photo of it. Oh, oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, I'm like scenes of the crime. I think yeah, here's me doing a crime just unrelated to the letter
Yeah, just to let him know
That I love crime and that I'm a democrat and that and I wouldn't do crime here if I was employed
I could I could do crime if I want to but I've chosen to work for you instead
So that's so that's my Christmas a yearning for
About
The only other thing I have to say about Christmas
Is that I got very drunk on
Christmas Eve
Cool, and I was hungover for the whole of Christmas day
That's pretty I was like I was about I was like passing out like I got us. I got to lie down
When we were all open in the presence, which kind of ruined the moment, but that's okay
I uh
because uh
I felt better and that's the end of that story
Spectacular I
I didn't really I didn't really have any hangover. I drank a little bit on like uh Christmas Eve
And a bit I don't know why I was hungover because I like hung over at all. I got like I just like
This was just a few glasses of red wine. It was like four to five now in my in my experience
I feel like wine gives you worse hangovers than other kinds of uh
I guess so I'm not sure why that is or if maybe it's just a coincidence or I was even imagining it
That's just that's just the feeling that I have for my experiences
Like maybe I should have been on the the spirits or something
Definitely definitely switch to the heart definitely switch to the heart. So yeah the eggless
Just pouring drinking straight rum out of a tumbler. Yeah, I call it eggless. No
That's good. That's good
um
But you didn't try you didn't have any egg nog
Nobody nobody had any egg. It's just not a thing
It's good though. It's so good
Look, it's like a nutmeg milkshake
Bre
I am
I have lots of leftover meat. I have lots of leftover meat and cold cuts from the the new year's gathering
So that's cool. That's protein
Yes, I am protein
Uh, I am
Yeah, I guess so
um
My lifts my lifts
I'm gaining weight, but that's fine. My lifts are coming along
They're not amazing yet, but they're getting they're getting back to a somewhat respect. I mean not even respect. They're getting back to a
an okay starting point
um
One of my new year's resolutions is to keep lifting and a deadlift 300 again
Uh, that's how I that's how I'll know
That i'm really doing it
um
I guess
My new year's resolution is to lower my testosterone to the correct amount
Because of my moment to raise my testosterone. Give me some of your excess
Sure. I don't know how to do that
Siphon it out
Send me your blood. Send me your blood
I used to need to take all of my blood and then like filter out the testosterone and then put my the blood back in
And then you can have the tea all all I want for Christmas is gibbs blood
Yeah, I don't know what are you spit it out nothing
Nothing nothing. How's your new years? Is that any different from Christmas? Was it the same sort of thing?
I mean in the evening the new year's evening
I just hung out at the the munchie house and there's a couple people in town visiting for that. We watched. Oh, we watched um
What's that movie? Sorry to bother you. You know that one?
Nope
It's a boots boots Riley. I think oh shit
Is he the actor too or is he just the director?
I don't know
um
No, he's just the director. Um
Uh, it's about um
Well, I can't really I honestly I can't really explain what it's about without
Spoiling it, but it's that one where the black guy joins the like telecommunications
or the telemarketing
job
And the guy tells him to use your use your white voice
Use your white voice when you're calling white people to sell them shit
And uh, he's his white voice is voiced by david cross
It was pretty good pretty good kind of fucked up kind of kind of some weird wacky twists and turns
But it was a good watch
And that's held. Yeah, it's pretty much. It's pretty much all I did pretty much all I did
We got chicken and waffles went out for breakfast. I got chicken and waffles on new year's evening. That was great
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum
Uh, I mean, you know, yeah nothing much
Nothing nothing nothing much going on
I did the uh, the new year's stream on on twitch, right?
I played a video game fleshed away on ps2
Wait, remember that fleshed away
The movie the um the art movie the game
Right. Okay. Is that a is that a 3d collectathon or is it a 3d platformer collectathon?
and it's it's
Like but it's bad, but it's kind of okay. Actually. It's fun and it's really funny looking
I watched that movie at christmas like two or three years ago
I think and I really like and I really liked it. Yeah, I thought it was great
I don't remember it. It's like I know
Is it hu grant ret?
Yeah, I think so. I think so and he's and he's doing his hu grant voice
Hugh granted his hu grantiest
and and
And so he goes into the sewers and he's a rat
And and he has to learn to be
Of like a shit rat instead of a clean rat. Hmm. That's the moral of the tale. That's that's it
Uh, yeah, I thought that movie was great and was just a good clean a good clean
Uh, you know compelling
You know three act heroes journey
not not in like a really like
The the like the structure is boring
I like they obviously stuck really close to the structure and and I and it takes me out of the movie
But I'm just like, yeah, you like solid just really solid solid storytelling
Yeah, and I just enjoy enjoyable the whole way through
Pays pace perfectly is quite good. I don't remember flushed away being bad. I just
I remember the the most
The thinking the most
interesting aspect of it was the fact that it is cgi the first cgi ardman animation
Um
Before that they were all like plasticine and stuff and clay
Um, and it's like they made it look like it was clay, but it wasn't
Yeah, so aside for it. So in terms of the story, I actually can't remember whether it was like terrible or fine
It's good and I guess I'm here to tell you it's good
Good my mom didn't like it. She thought it was gross. She doesn't like gross out
Stuff the slugs and slime. I guess so I guess so. Yeah
um
But it was fun stream. I kind of want to stream more often. Oh, that's another thing. Yeah, I want to uh,
I don't know if I hope I haven't said this before but
Okay, I have been in between holidays
I've been really trying to work on that book and I said I was gonna get the book done by the new years
And I didn't and it's kind of my fault, but it's also kind of the fault of my shitty internet
Which has been even worse than usual
It's been almost unusual unusable like a lot of the time and it's really fucking me up
So I'm gonna get that fixed and then once my internet is fixed
I am gonna start streaming and what I'm gonna stream is I'm gonna stream myself playing
Uh mega man battle network. I'm gonna play the whole yeah
Yes, I'm gonna play the whole battle network series and I'm gonna stream it because I should have streamed myself playing all the mega man games
And I feel like it was a bit of a missed opportunity that I didn't stream myself playing 45 different mega man games
Because that would have been content and I would have got donos
So yeah, so this time i'm gonna do it because I gotta play those games because I gotta make that video
But I might as well do it on stream and so I will and it's gonna be fun
And it's gonna be fun god damn it and you're gonna watch it. You're gonna watch it
Oh my god, I better watch it. You're gonna watch it
Is that the lowest you can go?
The lowest?
You're gonna watch it
I was trying to do the um, uh, mr. Plinkett
Yelling at nadine
You're gonna you're gonna watch the star wars movie. Oh, yeah
Speaking of
Mr. Plinkett speaking of the angry video game nerd. I've been rewatching a lot of angry video game nerd
Yeah, I've just been putting it that's just sort of been my like put it on in the background while I do other stuff
content lately
and I think
In the hot take I think
I think we as a society
need to
Need to start to be okay
with admitting
That it's bad even though
We think that uh, uh, uh, what's his name is a good guy, right?
Uh, the show is bad james, uh
Is his name james, uh, rolf james rolf. Yeah, I think I think we need to admit to a society that
Yeah, I guess it's charming or whatever. Yeah, I guess he's got enthusiasm or whatever
But like the content is bad the comedy is bad. He's not a good comedian
Uh, it's a bad show. We liked it because it was unique, but it was bad
And it's okay to admit that even though james rolf seems like a decent guy and a family man
And oh, we don't want to offend him. Oh, no
We don't want to compare him to dug walker because dug walker is an asshole and an incompetent stooge and a hack
And we don't like dug a dug sucks and that's true and we don't feel that way about james
But we should we we should we should be able to look ourselves in the mirror and say
The show was bad
uh
I I mean, I would agree that there's plenty of episodes that are just certainly
Like un un good. They're not good. They're bad. Yes. Um, I'm what
Did you watch like from the very beginning?
I've been what I've been sort of just skipping around watching watching the old
I mean, I've been watching the like the full season compilations
So like I'll watch season two and then I'll watch season 12 and then I'll watch season five and I'll watch season 11
There there I a few years ago. I was watching
All of them again, and I'm like I there's definitely a point beyond which
It's like there's a golden era where like mostly episodes are fun and good and then
Something changes and it sucks. I'm and it's sort of like this kind of the same but it just sort of feels weird
His delivery is a bit like annoying
And at like after a certain point
I'm gonna say even even though I kind of know what you mean
I there is sort of a difference in delivery
But I honestly don't think it's that
Much and I think that the early show and the late show are more similar
Than they are different. I don't I think it's I think it's kind of
Hasn't really changed that much
I'll I'll believe that I still will watch them because I'm nostalgic for those
Yeah, my feeling I think you know, I watched a bunch of
I think I watched a bunch of newer ones like I started on the latest season
And I watched through it and I was like lol, okay
And then I went back to an early season and I was like wasn't that
Wasn't that different
He's kind of always been
If I if I if I just gripe like
A lot of his delivery is is weird and his timing
Is really weird and a lot of his jokes are like not even jokes like when he'll just
And this is the thing he's always done. He's always done it where like
he'll be like
I don't know read
Read in the box of the game like oh this game
This game lets you uh, uh
You know, uh, uh, this game lets you bomb Hiroshima and Nagasaki. Yeah
This game lets you bomb Hiroshima and Nagasaki
Yeah, and like that's the joke the joke is he like repeats something and then he says yeah, and that's the joke
Yeah, I mean
I don't like those and it's not even he he does it all the time
He does it all the time. He does it all the time to the point. It's like that's his style of comedy
Here there's a and it's hack. It's really it is. There's a like an upsetting amount of like references
Like taken in their entirety and maybe changed slightly to fit the whatever you're saying
Um of like things he likes like movies and shows and stuff things. I didn't understand. I didn't see them as references
I thought he was being smart
But no, he was just quoting something and it's like so much of of what he did was just quoting something
A lot of people around that time. Yeah of like internet content creators. It's just like hey
I know this movie. I'm gonna say a line from it. If you know the movie
You're what you're you're great. You're a cool guy. Yeah, that's true
That's true, but it's it's not the main issue that I was noticing on the same on the same vein as what I just said like
You know a lot of the time
A joke will just be
That he just says what's happening in the game and he reacts with like inquiry. He's like, oh, man
They're like, oh, yeah, or like damn
and like that's
There's no joke
It's just in noting what he sees and then well saying damn or something like that
I mean and then sometimes he'll say
This is a poopy stick
On a on a dog's anus or something and it's like, okay. Okay. At least that at least that's something
At least you've made something out of it. I don't have like a problem with like just having the gameplay and then like
Like responding to something. Yeah, I think
The delivery changes over the course of what the decades or something and he sort of goes deeper and more growly and it sort of like is
Unnatural I like the earlier ones because it sounds like he's just a guy in his room playing a game and you're watching him
And he's like fuck
That's how you would say that if you were playing it. I only really feel that way about like season one
I think even by season two. He's become like fully
Stikopher. Yeah, maybe I haven't watched them in a few years
There's a mark difference between season one and season two
Oh, yeah, definitely season one doesn't even feel like a show. It's just like yeah
It's like a vague sense of a character. Mm-hmm
It also it's this is this is a neutral point. This is not a complaint
I just think it's very interesting that James Rolfe's idea of a stereotypical nerd is someone that drinks rolling rock
Like that's like that's a key element of the angry video game nerd characters that he likes to drink beer
And that's just such like a non-nerd drink in my opinion
I mean, I I remember him talking about like that
The reason for the beer specifically
Is that like he made the first one or he's just talking about cosylvania 2
It's like what if some guy was still angry at a video game all these years later?
Isn't that a funny concept me and then he did that and then he's like, all right
Now i'm gonna show him on screen
So he did dr. Jekyll mr. Hyde where he was dressed as a nerd stereotypical like glasses
All right, the first one didn't have video
The first one didn't have video the second one is like now i'm gonna like amp it up
This is like the sequel to that concept. Yeah, and he just was like so what if
This guy is so obsessed with this any ass game that has ruined his life to a ridiculous degree is such that he's drinking himself
Uh like silly
That you know, it's like such a strange idea that someone would be so obsessed
So he just picked up whatever he had in his fridge and it just happened to be rolling rock and then from then on he said
I guess that's a character trait. I'll bring it back and then that's his thing and that's the reason that's so silly
I mean, so it's almost like he he was he was trying to invent the trope of like
I mean, he kind of did invent the trope of like uh to this reviewing this game is so hard. It's so bad
I have to drink to get through it. Yeah. Yeah, I know like ironically he invented that
But he never really sells it because he never seems like he's getting drunk
He's never seems drunk or like he
Maybe i'm forgetting but like it's it's just a few episodes. It feels like it's something that he's doing casually
Yeah, it seems like just
It causes me to drink but then he continues talking normally. There's a few episodes where he gets so drunk
And then it's it's a bit
I don't even I don't remember that ever happened. Well, actually, you know, I think
The only one I can think of is like the the return to dr. Jekyll and mr. Hyde where he has like a big like
glass
Like what do you call them?
Mug
No, it's like a thing with a stuff a glass stopper in it and it's got alcohol some sort of a spirit
Oh like a
A canteen
Not a canteen a flat
It's like a huge thing. It's the sort of thing you would have like very expensive whiskey in
And he was drinking that and he was getting super drunk
Playing dr. Jekyll and mr. Hyde. Okay, so it sounds like in that episode. He actually did
Do the I have to get drunk to play this video. Yeah, okay, okay
um
But yeah, it's funny that it's just like
Ah this I hate this game sip
Like that's that's the extent of it most of the time. Yeah, it that's what I'm saying. Um
Yeah, I don't know, uh
I guess it's just you know
I don't have my favorite moments
But I don't I don't like go up and say oh, you've got to watch all of angry video game
It's just like I would never say that the feeling I have mostly found it pretty you know pretty enjoyable
Pretty an offensive to just have it on in the background
Just let it play lately like it's fine like I keep doing it
But I I have to say that in my opinion
A lot of the a lot of the a lot of the content that I feel is meant to be comedic
Is sort of not even really
Successfully executed joke. I think a lot of what I would describe as the comedy or the attempts at comedy is is hack
Uh and like a writer like a comedy writer could have made a joke out of this whereas the
Angry video game nerd will simply go. Yeah
Imagine that continues playing video game
That's it. Yeah, that's that's that's all I gotta say about uh James Rolf and you know, I want please
I'm sorry. Listen. I wish the man I wish the man nothing but the best. I know he's a family man. Okay, like I know
I know he's got a family Ben. I know I know and everyone's like, oh james. We just want him to we just want him to
He's he's uh, he just wants to be with his family now
He doesn't have time to make the angry video game nerd and like that's cool man. That's cool. That's good. You know
Good luck to him
um, my favorite moment
Of the top of my head from the angry video game nerd is the batman episode
where he's playing the batman games
and he's playing like
There's this one game where he has to use a grappling hook
To get to get somewhere and he's really really like getting really screamy angry like what the fuck?
Why is it not working?
There's something about the rant there that's like he's really blowing out the mic
and it's it's more
It's more than just sort of like a
I don't know like a throwaway moment
And I was like, yeah, that's great. And then also
Mike Matei playing the joker. That's probably my favorite joker
He's so better better than uh, not Ethan Hawke. Um
Heath Ledger, but not better than Heath Ledger. Yeah, but like he's he's like
I love him. I love him as the joker. It's so like it's annoying
But like for the in the in the show in the in the thing
He's just forcing him to play the shitty games and he's just going
And then he gets them all shoved up his ass at the end
there was a really
Funny moment and it was kind of unintentionally funny because I was watching the episodes out of order
And so I I got to one where you know, Bugs Bunny comes back
But it you know, I watched that
Before I watched the actual one where that like introduces Bugs Bunny
And so when Bugs Bunny Bugs Bunny just shows up and he goes
What's up doc and the nerd reacts to the mirror like appearance of Bugs Bunny with an immediate like
Furious like I'm gonna kill this mother fucker. Like I hate you. I hate you
Beating the shit out of and it's like what
I I knew that like, you know, I know that there's context there
But it didn't feel like it. It just feels like wow this guy just hates Bugs Bunny like for some reason
Uh, uh, uh, who knows why? Um, it's I mean, it's kind of like that in the in the original one as well
It's just like he's playing a Bugs Bunny game
And then it's like, yeah, it's Bugs Bunny Bugs fucking bunny and then he starts punching him
And I think the implication is that he doesn't like the shitty video game
Yeah, but like he goes straight to like beating the shit out of the bunny before he's even said anything
Is that right? Is that is that his first appearance? No, no, no. Well his first appearance is
Bugs Bunny's birthday blowout or something
Yeah, and I thought that like Bugs Bunny just comes in and they're just
Commentating on the game and and they get in a fight over how bad the game is or something
No, I think I think I remember it being like
He's playing the game and he's losing. It's like, ah, fuck this game and then
Bugs Bunny comes in. He's like, yeah, what's up, doc?
Maybe I'm thinking of that. Oh my god, it's Bugs Bunny. And then he just punches him
That's the joke is like he's not happy to see you. He's angry to see him. So, okay
Really? That was his first appearance. I just thought like
Okay, weird. Okay. No, I guess it was funny on purpose for the same reason that I found it funny. So, you know, good job
Yeah, I like the fucking the violence the Bugs Bunny stuff
Yeah, there's there's lots of nuggets of gold. It's just there's so like there's there's a point beyond which he's clearly like not interested in
Doing the show. Yeah, because of money reasons. He's like, well, I got to do one every month every two months
Uh, let's just do it and it's just sort of
I think I don't like it. I don't like it after a certain but I forget when I think but it's just sort of yeah
Yeah, generally like I watched the the kingdom hearts one where like he's playing kingdom hearts
Just because it was a big game at the time and like he he never even played the there's no nostalgia there
Uh, uh, and and it's
But he just kind of treats it the way he would play any other game
And I don't know I feel like the fact that I you see him like just kind of give the same
What were they thinking? What the fuck? I don't kind of it's like, oh man, you can just
This shit kind of just writes itself actually like you could literally just give the same treatment to any game and it wouldn't even matter
Uh, I kind of cheapen kind of cheapen the shtick
In hindsight a little bit
Uh, see seeing him do it also to these games that are not really worthy of it
You know
Yeah
You know, I just want
Capital so that I can destroy james so I can destroy james rolf that I can like ruin him ruin his personal and professional
Sort of get him it's only get him before he gets me
I want to you know, I want to step into into the anger video games nerd nerds room and he'll say oh
Ben sainte you made phantom revenge that game was a fucking dog zainus shitting out barf
And then he'll just jump and start kicking my ass and then I'll go like uh, I have a team of lawyers
I have a team of lawyers who are going to destroy you for this and he'll go
Oh, no, and then and then and then my and then the repo man will come and they'll just start carrying all his video games out
And I'll stand there and I'll be like ha ha ha. This is what you get
This is what you get because you didn't make enough money
You didn't make as much money as I did nerd and now you're going to the poor house
And he'll say no my family and I'll say I'm taking them too
And that's it. You have the money to buy them
And it's and it's just the plot of um and from there. It's just um
the um, uh
That song
It's that it's that music video. It's that song. Um
It's it's uh, it's thank you by dito. It's just um, it's just a music video for thank you by dito, but it's
But it's angry video game nerd. You know what I'm talking about. You know what I'm talking about
No, I you know you know you come on. Come on. Come on. You know
The song thank you by dito famously the song stamp sampled in m&m's song stan
uh is uh
Is a song that ironically juxtaposes
Uh, someone having a bad day. They describe a bad day that they had
Uh, but the chorus is saying thank you it's saying thank you to an imagined character
That is the their lover or loved one of some kind and they say it's the best day ever the best day ever because uh
Because you know, you gave me the best day ever because I was with you
Then the music video is dito is singing this while like her uh, the repo men are coming
They're just like kicking around her house. They're taking everything, right?
Uh, so it's that
Epic. Yeah, thank you. Thank you
Um, it's a good song though. You know who should do a music video about that
I mean, you know who should do a video about that as um, and I say this knowing that it's wrong
Um, Todd in the shadows should do a one hit wonderland about thank you
The only song that anyone knows by dito and only because it was sampled in stan
And I say that knowing full well that I'm sure he would be like um actually dito like charted on the top 40 like a dozen different times
Back in like the early 90s and I'd say I don't care
I don't care idiot. I don't know any of those songs. It's about my understanding
I mean, I mean, I mean, I'm not I'm not wrong
I feel like the average person if you ask them dito, they would be like who the fuck is dito
And then you'd say, you know, they did thank you and they'd be like what the fuck is thank you by dito
And they'd say and you'd say giving me the best day of my life and they'd say oh stan
Oh stan by m&m and they go. Yes stan. Yes dito is the one that made stan by m&m
You don't what what what I've never listened to m&m. What the what the fuck? I know the spaghetti song
I think that's what it's called actually
Wait, you mean um, you mean lose yourself lose yourself. That's the one
I know that because I was around when I was young and it was big and I was like, oh, okay
I mean stan was um stan was all over the radio
But I mean that's when I was uh
You know like an or a young teen or maybe in my maybe like 12 or 11 or 11 or something
I think uh stan is the one
It's really good stan is that it's like a sad song about um
It's from the point of view
Of a fan of a of a of a a fanatical fan of m&m writing him letters
Like saying like I want to meet you. I want to meet you my life is falling apart
But like my love for you m&m is like the thing that like gets me through the day and uh
Well, I won't spoil the ending no spoilers for the song
Okay, well, maybe I will spoil it then he fucking dies, okay
There you go
Bam the end of the song the final verse is m&m finally writing back and in the course of writing the letter
He realizes that a news story that he saw about someone driving their car off a bridget committing suicide
Was about the guy whose letters he never answered there you go and in the middle it goes uh place
Thank you by dito
And that's what everybody knows d dito from
Wow now you understand now I understand my multi-layered references now
I don't need to watch or listen to anything now. You don't need to listen to thank you by dito
You don't need to listen to my stand by m&m. You don't need to watch the angry video game nerd anymore
You don't need to listen to the pro crass nators podcast ever again
You got all the context and none of the content just the way it should be
yes
2023 is the year of nothing the year of no content. It's the year of no content, baby
I have I have big I have like simultaneously big plans and also
No plans for 2023. I want to
interesting I want to
No, I guess I guess I could say the same about myself in a certain way, but go on
I've I've got like Clarissa gunsmok on on the on my mind. I've got the the the the
the murmurings of bell japes sequel
the murmurings
There's things with like the whispers. There's there's stuff with uh pumpkin alley
um
and also
Stuff with red man and gun girl that is all sorts of comic and story ideas, but then also
I don't want to worry too much. I think a lot of last year. I was worrying
And the year before that as well just worrying worrying about
Am I gonna make it? Am I gonna be good? Is everybody gonna like me?
Am I gonna get money from this? Is is is any of this worth it?
Am I gonna do anything? Is everything gonna go be okay? Like I need to shut up
Just draw some some stuff and not like think too big
about the repercussions or the potential
failures or
Whether or not I do anything with my life from all of these stuffs
Hmm. I just need to just I just need to chill out
I need to chill out that's my my vibe. I guess I'm gonna go for that
My tea's gone cold. I'm wondering why
Got out of bed at all
Money and brains outside. It's a good song. It's a good song. What were you saying?
Um, I was saying I'm gonna kill you again saint. No, I hear I hear
Um, um worrying is bad. Yeah, so I sure hope I don't worry
Good one good one, um
My plans are big because I have as I you know, I
I don't know. I do have plans for things finish the book stream
Finish finish man finish the book stream battle network
Make some more lecture videos including a battle network one, but also it probably
I would think
I think it would be great if I could make at least three more lecture videos this year
I hope that's not like too ambitious
Feel like I should I feel like I should aim higher than that
uh
Even though I might aim high and fail that's the that's the way to do it
I mean if they were all you know, if they're all as long as the mega man video that would be impossible, but
They don't all have to be that long. So maybe it might be doable. Um, we'll see but um
So there's that and the streaming and there's the book and then
I don't know. I feel like that doesn't account for a whole year
And I keep feeling like I need to do something
I need to change what i'm doing. I need to change
Uh my life around I need to find something new to do with myself
In addition to not that I don't want to abandon any of these old things
But I feel like um, I need I need
Need to find need to find some new shit need to find some new shit to do
Some new shit to work towards and I don't know and I don't know what that
Would be or look like so
My plan my plan is find something to do
I mean you could always
Like a a simple-ish one is just to find like a some sort of a craft hobby to get into
I have a craft hobby. I make candy. You make candy. Yeah. Yeah, I have a craft
I have a crafty hobby like that
I mean I can get more into that get new molds try and make get fancy with it
Find new experiment with new recipes. That is something that I plan on doing
um
It's not exactly it's not exactly a goal
maybe um
Maybe try and get like uh, I don't know
Maybe try and get that shit like sold somewhere
Maybe maybe get like shit packaged and try and like try and make it a somewhat commercial venture
I don't know, you know, I think I did I mentioned that I think I might like kickstart those might do like at some
Point after the book is done. Just do a separate kickstarter, you know
Maybe just for like a couple thousand dollars or whatever and not a not a big production
But like let people buy like bags of candy
That I made. Yeah, I think kickstarter is the only way I know how to do anything
I mean the difficulty I guess is just
Selling food across
Like borders is very difficult. I I don't is it though?
Well, I'm just assuming I don't know like the laws or the regulations, but I'm sure
I actually think it is because it's not
Liquid and like shipping liquids can be kind of hard. Yeah, but like this this is this is this is, you know
Solid food and it's just you know, I mean shipping any package internationally is quite annoying and expensive
Unless you're amazon
I guess I'm thinking of like if it was like a branded product
And then getting the license to then sell that product in another country is a whole big thing
But simply sending a package to a human being directly is is simple
It's so so Kickstarter if you're doing it. Yeah, it's expensive and like labor intensive for you
Yeah, but yeah, I guess it would be the same as any other thing
for Kickstarter
That's that's something that
That's not like
Oh, that's what I want to do this year, but it is something that I keep thinking about like hey, wouldn't it be kind of funny if I did that?
Hey, wouldn't that be fun? Maybe
something that I want
thinking about trying
Could be could be a
See what happened though. I would want to get it like
If I did that I wouldn't just like send people shit and like ziploc bags. I would have like
I would have some level of like pseudo professional like oh, yeah
That would be an investment if you get like a little packaging machine that can like do the the ridged like press at the top
Whatever that is
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Little little plastic baggy. I would you know, I wonder
I bet something that could do something like that is not even that
I mean like a big industrial one would probably be really expensive, but like just one
Like maybe an indie one up up to like a hundred bucks for something like that. Maybe
That's
peanuts
nothing peanuts
You could even you could sell peanuts you could sell peanuts shaped gummies
I have worm I have worms now. Oh, I got new I got more worms because I already had worm molds
But I wanted to be able to make more at a time
So I asked my mom just get me some more of the same worm molds so I can make more worms so I can increase my product my rate of production
Uh, and she did and now I have
More worms
So watch it watch out
Waiting for the worms
That's my that's a pink floyd song. That's my reference. That's my musical reference. I know I know
I know that because I watched
A video about uh, I think I learned it from a dan dan olson's video
About about uh, the angry not the
Doug Walker. Yes. Yes. Yes. Sorry
Fuck that's the cursed cursed cursed directly like cursed
Lineage of knowledge. It is
It's fucked up that that's I only know things. I only know things
Not because I I only know things from
Angry video game narrative Doug Walker not because they talked about them because other people talked about them talking about them
And how they talked about them wrong
This is how I learned
So so much
So much I'm looking at the slime and punishment cover. I think I'm like mostly happy with how the cover turned out. I don't know
I don't know if I haven't seen that yet
Um, I uh, this is not a final
This is not a final design, but you know, I showed it before
And it was kind of it had like nightstar. I was gonna put like nightstar looking down
in the background
From the sky
I changed I think I'm taking her out. I think I think maybe I want to do something a little more like
this
Is it sending it is sending. Oh, yes, I do remember something with the the phantom core in there
Yeah, well, I I was just gonna draw buildings, but then I was like, what if I just
I think maybe it's a little more honest to put a bunch of like photo bash buildings like this in because like that's how it is
in the book like most of the backgrounds are
Edited photos and stuff. So this is like
Maybe more representative of the contents. I guess uh, in a way
Where's strawberry milk? He's been he's been fuck strawberry milk
He doesn't get a fucking slot on the cover. But if this is the moment this is the moment when you get pushed to the portal I
Don't give a fuck
This is strawberry erasure. Yeah
It is
What are you gonna do about it? So I'm gonna I'm gonna have too much capital
I'm gonna I'm gonna write a petition and then your capital will be all mine
Shit
if this
Making a petition
If it gets 10,000 signatures, I think ben sainte should give me all his money and I
Oh, no, I hope it doesn't get 10,000 signatures. Oh, no
That would I'd lose all my money
Ah
Elon musk making a poll. Hmm should ben sainte give give and take all his money
Oh, no, they voted yes. Oh, no, I gotta do it. Oh, no, then I gotta do it
Ben sainte says I will abide by the results of this poll
I will abide by I will abide by the results of any poll and any uh a petition
That is put in front of me. I will buy by any rules that they stipulate no matter what
That's the ben sainte guarantee
True
Trying to think anything else happens
Uh
The answer is no. No, I guess not
My internet's bad. My internet sucks and that makes me angry
Do you want to go all my roommates are like we gotta fix our internet
We gotta order some new internet and I say, yeah, we do gotta order some new internet
I agree. I'm glad we're all on the same page and then nobody orders any more internet
Nobody orders any new internet
And I'm certainly not gonna do it
Don't be ridiculous. Oh, okay. Where are you saying? Where are you?
Uh, I was just asking if you wanted to go to the one piece
We could yeah, you could talk about the new two two chapters
Two new chapters 10 70 and 10 71
So, oh, it's that one piece corner everybody block your ears
Unless you want to know years for the next two hours of the pod. Yeah, just just everybody nobody should listen to this part
Not even if you like one piece ab so loosely
Oh, no, um
That's really weird. I complained about my internet a second ago
Even though it was working fine and now it's uh now it's broken again
Now it doesn't work anymore. Well, it won't it won't load. It won't load 10 70
Even though
You know, usually most days
Oh, no, it went
Like I said, most days my internet at like 3 30 p.m. We'll we'll cut out for a while
All right, here we go 10 10 70. All right
um
All right, so uh the strongest humans there's this uh bunch of scientists on the cover. Let me try and uh identify these these people
Oh, I think there's no we don't know who they are aside from vega punk
No, these are definitely um, these are definitely um, I think that's gecko moria
Caesar clown and uh germa
Uh, which one's gecko moria? I think that's him on the left
Dang, you know
I mean, he looks he looks a lot different, but I think that's supposed to be him
Why does Caesar does Caesar clown have horns?
Yeah
Okay
Man, I just I just like like didn't think about this
But yeah, I don't I think right. That's that's germa, right? I mean, wait, is that his name or what's what's the germa dad's name?
the germa is his
Kingdom and then it's king judge
I think that's king judge
And then I have no idea who this woman in the hat is carmen san diego
looking at it's uh
Some sort of lady. That's that's correct
um
Oh, i'm getting a message
What?
The guy on the left is queen queen
Queen queen
You know queen is a scientist
This is before that's the big fat guy, right big fat guy and kaito's crew
Hmm
That would make more sense because moria is like
I don't know
What he has a different pass that I think we know some of yeah
Okay, I mean i'm prepared to be wrong about that. Um
So so okay, I mean i'm i'm looking i'm looking at queen and uh, okay
The only real resemblance I see is the eyes kind of
Sort of a mouth a little
Maybe it's the pants that you're supposed to think oh, he's got striped pants just like queen
Um
I think when it comes when it comes to like because I think we know that queen knows like scientist people
And he's like the the scientist guy
The scientist engineer of the kaito crew. He's the diseases guy, right?
Yeah, he made the disease thing that nearly got everybody and so this is mads which was
The thing from the last that there was a ship
That we saw on the previous chapters like cover page
With that one guy who I don't know who it is and then this these guys are in mads, I guess
I think I think so
I'm sorry. I'm I'm comparing him to queen and I just don't really see it
The the resemblance is uh is is passing at best
Uh like um
Oh, I didn't even read the thing culvert of urge
Promising scientists gathering for the sake of of the world and all mankind. But why do they have guns?
What's up, huh? Wait, wait, who sent you a message who sent you a message that said it was queen?
Uh secret secret message
Okay
Don't worry about it. Uh, I won't I won't then
Um
Yeah, it's like the scientists around them like surrounding them
Yeah, and they don't have guns and these guys have guns. Are they like attacking?
the
Looks like they're
Defending
I guess we'll know the next time
The promising scientists that have gathered for the benefit of the world and mankind
Uh
Well, I mean we can look at the next chapter in the next chapter. There's
Wait a minute. There's no, uh
There's no intro page in the next chapter. No, it's uh, it's like an early copy. What it's secret illegal early copy. Fuck
I see
Um, all right. Anyway, uh, so last chapter
Uh luchi and luffy were fighting and uh sentomaro got sliced not dead not yet
And uh
Basically luffy's to be in fighting. He's he's being fine. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
And we get to see the antics thing
We get to see the seraphim like doing some stuff
And then jimbey the jimbey seraphim uses
The swim fruit
Yeah, um, Frankie recognizes as being senor pink's fruit
Which was can you remind me what the swim fruit does?
Does it just let you swim through anything? Unless you swim through matter like you're a swimmer. Yeah, I guess. Yeah
Um, but he's doing like an awakened version of it, right?
I I'm not sure. I can't remember what senor pink was using it for it. Maybe the exact same like as depicted here
Um
He says
He recreated the same devil fruit
Uh, when it comes to art only only the zoan type can be manufactured
Okay, this
Uh, I think I might be reading a bad translation
Translators note the special fruits that vagabunk is referring to here are the mythical zoan types
Uh, he didn't mention mythical zoan per se although the df images shown here are the mythical zoan
devil fruit included kaito and
Wait, what what mythical devil fruit shown here? I don't oh he see oh he shows the fruits
Oh, I see just like sees his outrageous smile. Yeah, that person should just die already
Wait, this is this is a different fucking
This is a different translation
Then the one you read then the one that I read even though I read it on the same
It's like they changed it
All right, that's odd. I'm on tebc. Was it yeah tcb scans
tcb typical cracker behavior
Yeah
Uh, yeah, and when I read the original
Time it said uh, he vagabunk said like yes Caesar can make smile, but I consider that unacceptable
Yes, this one in this one. He's saying just like Caesar's outrageous smile
Hmm
They have a large amount of money in time the special fruits can also be reproduced whether you can awaken them is still
Unconfirmed. Okay, so he's all right
Yeah, he's saying you can you can reproduce zoan fruits even the mythical ones
probably
It's difficult where he tried logias. It was difficult trickier than expected, but it doesn't say he failed
Uh, which is uh ominous
And then there's an alternative of paramecia types
I found you can synthesize a blood additive from a paramecia user's lineage factor that will grant their power once transfused
That's what you see running through their arms. It's I call it green blood
He made blood so
you what
It's kind of it's kind of strange that frankie is so
Freaked out by the thought of making blood
Like this is like a big taboo or something
I think it's it's just sort of like the the playing god like you're making humans
Like there's there's so much more to this than just it's a robot
It's like it's got blood. It is
It can use devil fruits
Yeah, it's uh, it has a personality kind of even though it can be controlled. It's like
weird
And not like the same as building a robot. I'm um, I'm looking and like
We get this close-up of I think it's uh, like young bonnie's arm
With like the green have we
That's not bonnie. That's that's um
a boa handcock
The one with the close-up of the arm. Yeah, because you you see a couple panels later. She's doing the mellow mellow
No, you're right
But it's a close have we
Has this been a thing? Have we been able to see their green blood like
Before this I don't remember. I haven't looked closely enough
I know I kind of want to kind of want to go back and I just want to go back and look at them and just see like
I just want to see
Since when since when have they have big like gaps in their
body that showed like green blood
Uh load please
I'm so kind of cool
Yeah, see like freaking green goo in their little in their little arm tubes
Yes, please
Uh
Oh, no, they are there. Yeah chapter previous chapter. They've all got on their right arm a little band that
looked like an arm band, but it is in fact a glass
Like open area where you can see the blood flowing
Unlike the the upper arm or the the the I'll just
Screen yeah, just show me
Uh
It's kind of I mean, I guess they're all like
Wearing clothes except for
Hancock
I mean, she's wearing clothes, but she has her arm uncovered
There it is
Uh, let me see
Huh, yeah genuinely just missed it just
Yeah, I mean doesn't really look like anything so I guess you wouldn't think if if it was the anime if it was in color
I feel like my eye would have like shot right to it like what the fuck is that green shit
But uh, this is
I didn't even didn't even notice there was anything there
They've also mentioned that these are children so they're gonna grow stronger potentially and it's like
this idea that these
these uh these
This being this new race of artificial person
Is so powerful probably the most powerful beings in the history of the sea
Yeah
Like yeah, come on. Why'd you do that? Why would you do that? Why would you do that?
um
I mean
Because they can control them
It's gonna be like a big
Like problem
For somebody. Yeah, I think so. I mean imagine how Jinbe must feel about this
Yeah, Jinbe has got his little guy you cloned. Oh you cloned me
There's a little young clone of me running around with green blood and superpowers
Okay, and any any
Obeys you and will like and he's under orders to kill me at all, you know at any cost. Okay
Fine and and everybody and impaled down. They have access to that devil fruit. They can put them inside
The seraphim. Yeah, well, well the paramecies anyway
Yeah, at least those I assume the rest but
I haven't explicitly said that it's sound him saying that like logeas are difficult
It sounds to me like he has not been successful at logeas
So they can recreate zoan fruits and they can transfer paramecia abilities with
Green blood if they have access to their the did you say the lineage factor?
Yeah, I don't know what that means. I think if they have
Blood of the original user of that devil fruit. So they got like senor pink's blood
Yeah, they can turn that into green blood and give the devil fruit ability to appear a seraphim
That's what I think is is being said
so I wonder
Okay, so if a seraphim
So I think a seraphim will automatically have
The fruit ability of the person that they're a clone of right because like Hancock has the um
Well, we don't know that's the reason it could be that they have Hancock's blood as well
That's true. It could just be they they just gave her the same
fruit power
it's interesting though because
Uh, what happened to Hancock didn't wasn't there like a thing
that happened with her like
the
The war like garb was garb go go to amazonia or something. No, um, well, maybe but like, um
Hancock the the the warlords was dissolved and then her the amazon lily was like no longer a safe haven for her
Yeah, and and so they were you know marines came
But I forget what happened. I don't remember
Something happened. I don't I don't remember either
um
I mean, maybe we could maybe we could look it up. Uh
boa
Hancock
Oh my god, this article is so fucking long
There's so much every character. There's a billion things
Can you
Is is there not just like a a history section?
Okay. Well, this is actually
harder to uh
This is actually harder to find out like what's going on with her right now than I thought
uh
relationships
my worst enemies
I feel like
There should just be like a in this arc this happened, but there isn't
No, yeah, there's a body
There's a body measurements section
Yeah, I saw that Hora Oda responded to a fan saying her height is 191 centimeters
Wow, how how tall does that maker?
Uh six foot three and a half
wall
Da da da her three measurements are blah blah blah ha ha jake up breasts epic
That sounds about that sounds about right. Yes
Why is that oh history it's a whole tab that's different
Is that yes, it's kind of it's it's kind of funny that Oda will just be like
He draws he draws these stick figure big boob ladies and then when asked like how big are their tits?
He's like other they're j-cups. They're just so they're up there. They're like triple. They're like double h like
Oh, yeah, they're they're like, um, you know, they're like an eye cup
They're okay. You just pick a random letter from around that point. I mean he gives like specific
Like measurements he does and then it's it's great. He's a man after my own heart. Yeah. Yeah
okay, so
Why no country after the seven waller systems was abolished Hancock told the subjects not to worry
Uh about the incoming marine fleet the fleet and reminded them the reason the waller position has been offered in the first place
Was because of how strong they were
Then they had a battle the marine successfully breached the island when the black beard pirates also arrived
To take Hancock's ability. Yes, I vaguely remember that
Cody pleaded with her
to leave with the marines
She refused to surrender and petrified most of the marines
And the pirates she was about to attack Kobe when black bid grabbed her and nullified her ability
She warms. Yes, he was holding her
Hostage and and she and it was like a mexican standoff and it was like if you kill me
I won't like reverse the petrification on all these
People or something like that. Yeah condemned his crew mr. Permanent petrification
She did agree to restore the marines and pirates if they left the island
But teach refused to trust her
Before teach could kill her Rayleigh arrived and drove the black bid pirates and the marines out of Amazon lily
So
Yes, dang. Okay. I do I do remember so she's
She's okay like Rayleigh Rayleigh. I guess got got her. Okay
So weeks later believing the marines would come back to Amazon lily and caught question where she should go
Before concluding she wanted to marry Luffy
Well, of course, then she listened uh as
Shaku yaku. Who's that?
Isn't that the vega punk uh daft punk guy shaka?
Or is it shaku yaku?
Discuss vega wants to acknowledge
Wait
She was there
Who
Who is this it says it says like weeks later believe the marines would come back
Hancock questioned where she should go before conclusion. She wanted to marry Luffy second sentence yaku
She then listened to shaku yaku discuss vega punks technological developments
Oh shaku yaku is that lady who's with rally?
Oh shaki. Yeah, I think that wasn't her full name
Oh my god, is she gonna arrive is she gonna appear in this this arc everybody's going to egghead right now
Yeah, for real
All right, so that's what's going on with her
Uh, who could forget gloriosa
Me
Former empress of the kuja tribe from one generation before shaku yaku
Two generations before an unknown coup. Sorry. Who's kuja?
Three generations before but oh, oh, it's the it's the amazon lily tribe
Wait shaku yaku is from the amazon lily
What
Shaki is a former empress of amazon lily. What the fuck?
I don't remember that part. I just remember her being like it. She's just the lady in the bar
Yeah, that's what that's all I remember about her is that she hung out with rally
Okay, well, there's a
Yeah, there's an even there's like an old grandma who was an even formerer
Empress of the kuja tribe
Called gloriosa or elder neon
She's the old lady, right? She's a little little old lady with a snake staff. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, well, that's
This seems like
It's really fucking crazy. Uh that uh shaki is just an empress and just like oh, okay
I left I just left
Yeah, I um
Big thing to forget
So the fight continues, uh, we know we now know about greenblood
Greenblood's cool. I like that
Luffy with his like gear. What is it? What does he call this?
The white boy mode, but like what is it? What does he call it? Is it is it gear fifth?
I guess it's gear fifth
I don't remember. I don't remember if he says anything. He just sort of did it and he he has the big smile
And he's doing the goofy shit
And he's really like easily bodying
Uh
Luchy right now. Yeah, it is a wakened zone for him
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm
And so they they they're all going together
They go on a rocket ship. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. What?
Uh, vagapunk. I mean what vagapunk says
Is that it's possible to replicate a mythical zone? I mean somebody else he could give someone he could replicate the hito hito
model joyboy
If he wanted like somebody else could could could be joyboy
Now that would be fucked that would be like then it would be like the marines are trying to get Luffy's blood so they can do that
And then yeah, yeah, no Luffy you're bleeding
Actually, that just occurred to me
But like they would definitely want to do that because the the the government knows that like the joyboy fruit is like the best fucking fruit
Hmm
terrifying
Think about it. It'll be a right at the end of one piece. It'll be like, oh, there's Luffy. Oh, no, it's evil Luffy
I obey maybe blackbeard will get it
It blackbeard will get it and he'll be but it'll be a different color. It'll be black
Just like how uh
The the kaito's fruit was duplicated for Momo, but it was pink and vagapunk was like, ah, fuck. It's worthless. It's wrong color
I'll make black joyboy
That's my that's my prediction
Calling it now calling it
It's a little over the top, but sure
I think it's plausible. I think blackbeard already has
A lot of power with his accumulation of multiple devil fruits within one body
What does he have he has the the the yami yami no me and he's got the darkness the gura gura no me
And whitebeards and who knows what else? Well, I mean I've well, yeah, who knows what else? I mean his crewmates have
I've heard people say that they expect him to get three fruits because of his like three-headed
um
You know flag
That could just be
I mean why stop it too?
Why stop it too?
Maybe after three you die
Maybe that I feel like that's already the case though
Like if you have a devil fruit you eat another one you will die. That's part of the lore for that
Yeah, that I don't know where we learn that but I definitely think that
I think we learn that in any slubby that if you eat a second fruit it just it kills you or you explode or something
Yeah, I think you die if you eat if you are a fruit user and you eat a second fruit
So so still still a mystery how this guy did it with do we even know we like have no idea how he got a second fruit power
We know that he did something they put it under the yeah covered whitebeard in a big cloth
Then he did a magic trick and then he's like ha ha
Good trick. Maybe he needed to suck his dick. Maybe that was the reason you covered it up
Definitely, I don't want people to see this. Come on. Definitely. I want everyone to know that I'm a super powerful
Fruit user, but I don't want them all to know that I'm gay and I suck dick. So
I don't I don't want them to know that I'm gonna suck whitebeard's
Legendarily massive dong from that one meme that everybody knows everybody seen even though it's like it's like he's dead
He's like standing dead
Yeah, well when that happened. So it's like a dead penis
So it'll be even worse
Blackbeard doesn't mind that's okay. That part's fine
So then everybody gets swooshed right up to the frontier dome
Luffy says uh to sentomaro. Yes, I'll protect vega punk
Sentomaro is like unconscious now and then the seraphim the seraphim are back under the control of cp nine cp zero
Uh, they're back in the control
Uh, we
They do wait. No
Well, cuz sentomaro is like unconscious or dying or dead
And you know, you can't control them from a distance
So now the sentomaro is out cold. Yeah, no, you're right. You're right. I forgot what's happening. Yeah, they have the the funny
controller things
Okay, and I mean I guess uh
What's what's the what's the
pika pika nomi fruit guy's name?
Uh kizaru kizaru kizaru says um
Send the warships to send the warships on the warships to egghead
We're gonna we're gonna kill them
Okay, so there's
I like how he says
Oh, the serahak crew has allied with vega punk on paper
That should make for a straightforward escape as we all expected
But boy, they are for a surprise
Because that this arc is not as short as it may have seemed at first it's gonna continue
You the you the reader might think that that makes uh that that's like well, obviously, you know, they don't
stand a chance, but
You will find the complications will arise. Okay. Yeah
And it's I did think that I thought like that
They gotta leave because yeah
No, no, but yeah, they're on their way. They're gonna fuck they're gonna fuck it up
So the marines and also vega punk is like, please can I come on your ship as the only way I can survive?
Yeah, makes it makes sense
so, okay
Well, actually, I'll I'll I'll save my thoughts generally until we go over the next chapter
chapter 10 70
Sorry, I got
Something in my throat
chapter 10 71 a hero is offensive
A hero is offensive a hero is offensive. Yeah. Well, I mean it's contracted with like a hero
Oh, I see
But it's it's sailing that you like a true hero is someone who's not afraid
To speak his mind to to you know to tell the true the true hero is one who's not afraid of cancel culture
Yes to tell the truth about about the show biz industry like Dave Chappelle
uh, uh, you know
It's like Dave Chappelle famously said
if it's
Italians it's the mob if it's Japanese it's the yakuza, but if it's the jews, it's a coincidence
That's what they want. That's what showbiz wants you to think but Dave should
Why am I even talking about this? Okay, no one
Nobody nobody cares nobody cares about fucking Dave Chappelle. You've you fucked it Dave
So
Someone who we knew was coming
Blast all right. He
crashes into the red line
crashes into the base of the red line
And then he's like
Everyone's like, oh my god, it's Bartholomew Kuma. You know that guy who we're all like we know about and he's a he's a slave
And what's what's going on?
and he's like
Like it looks like he's struggling
He's he's definitely breathing heavily and he hit his head very hard
But like what is going on with him? Is this place?
Are is he like right near marriage?
Well, like if they climbed up that wall would marriage wall be like right there
I think so. I think this is one of the places where like the people arrived to go to reverie
Yeah
So
Yeah, that's right. So he smashed into the wall and he looks up at the red line the world government thing
And I'm like, I thought he was going to egghead, but if he's going to marriage wire, what is he gonna do?
Is he go is he returning home due to orders?
Yeah
I guess I guess so or
I just I mean I just don't know
My first thought was like, oh, he's going to to see his daughter because of some sort of thing
Um, and I feel like he could have gone over the red line if he wanted to
But he hit the red line. Maybe he's like struggling against his robotic compulsions to go back
Because he wasn't fully like
Cyborg'd when he left
Yeah, oh right because he was with the uh, the with the in the Kamabaka kingdom
Everyone was trying to rebels with the rebellious revolutionaries. That's right
Like he's he's gotta appear there's it is Bonnie's here. Everybody's here. Um
I notice um, he's looking
Well, this is this is actually back on on um egghead, but like in the last chapter the big cloud around the uh
The dome the punk records had us had a 99 on it and this chapter. It's got a 100 on it
So it's like counting up to something
There's like a big like orbiting like like num numerical display
I don't know. I'm just
Wonder what the the number means I guess
I guess, I don't know
How many how many chapters of egghead are we in now not not that many only like like 10
10 12 maybe yeah 10
It's I mean it feels like not much, but yeah, it's a lot of a lot of drawings a lot of pages sure sure
Um
Kuma yeah, I have no idea what kuma is doing
We
It's it's so it's so all right. There's so many moving parts in this chapter
um
Vega punk and all the other punks all the other vega punks. They're all gonna go on the same ship with the straw hats
and uh
Oh, uh, then they're like
Uh, we need we might need help from that other person that mysterious other person
Uh on the island and then vega punks like yes, let's call him say please help
And we don't know who it is
So there's a there's a there's a mystery person who's gonna appear who is presumably strong. He's gonna help
Won't you be risking them too if we ask for help?
wait wait
Wait, uh, oh I got confused does vega punk and his sentences with quasar
Um in this uh translation apparently maybe they just in the other translations. I've already doesn't do that
I thought he was asking
Someone named quasar for help, but yeah, it's not the case. Okay. I see
Um, so it's just someone we when we have no idea who it is
So yeah, so bonnie is gunning after vega punk. She wants him to turn
Uh her dad kuma back into normal dad. Yeah, and he says he can't but there's a reason
There's a good reason or there's a reason
I'm assuming that it's because this is like part of kuma's plan like kuma wanted this for some reason
I I have to assume that because you know him being part of the revolutionary army
um
and they're being like
Him being part of a special race
There's a lot of mystery around his intentions
So yeah, his him having some sort of ulterior
Long game plan
It's so weird that like yeah, he's got all these plans and he's got all these like secrets even though he's like
He's almost like not he almost doesn't even exist anymore
He almost like is not even a person and yet he's still like enacting all these
It's kind of like in death note when uh when light like
Made itself on kira
And yeah, and then he kept he kept carrying out his own plans even though he didn't know them anymore
Yeah, it's like it could be maybe like oh
Let their guard down. They think
I'm under their control so I can do some something that
Would be impossible otherwise
Hmm
Yeah, and then I get the death note and I write the names of the the gurus say in the death note perfect genius
Masterful gambit sir
So the frontier dome goes offline
What is the frontier dome?
I believe it's the force field that stops people getting in maybe it's the thing that was counting up to 100
maybe um
But it goes offline
And just for just long enough uh for the three
Uh jumpy people from cp zero to jump up there kaku luchi and stussy
And then they're they're up there. They see the straw hat ship
And then we get an epic uh sword slice moment
It's the rematch. Yeah, luchi and luchi had a rematch and now kaku and zoro are gonna have one
Yeah, it's yeah
Ace just is so cool. Um, I love one piece
Uh
um, um
Yeah, okay, they're they're leaving
They're leaving with vega punk
Uh, bonnie is attacking him
Yeah, and then uh, we're at uh the
Fuck is it the kid pirates? Are they just called the kid pirates?
I yeah, I think so the kid pirates
Hey, um
It's is killer is killer. Uh, didn't he eat like a smile and it drove him crazy and now he laughs uncontrollably
I yeah, I didn't seem like he seems fine. He seems totally fine
Maybe maybe he forgot about it. Maybe they found a cure off screen. I I can't remember
If they did anything like that
Well, they're at elbaf and that's cool. Yes
They believe they're at elbaf. They probably are probably are that's just like a little aside
Um kid is at elbaf
And then we don't actually see anything about elbaf except that they have giant fish there
Oh, yeah, it is a big fish. Yeah
Isn't that fish bigger than normal? Hey, you know where things are bigger than normal elbaf
And also the entire grand line
Or
Yeah, but like even more
Even bigger things are even more things are even bigger on elba. Well, it's like america
You know everything's bigger in america, but in texas everything's even bigger
So elbaf is like wow the grand line. Yeah
That's what they say
Trust me. I'm an american
Meanwhile in g14 naval base
Which is apparently very close. Is that the place that they like broke out of?
Who?
Uh, no, I'm thinking of um
There was an anime only like filler arc where they had to
They landed in a in a jail and they had to break out of a marine base. Yeah, this is not bad. This is new world
This is I think the place where
um
smoker is based
Like the g14. I like uh skypea was not was before the new world
Yeah, that's great. No, no skypea. Yeah skypea was it was on the grand line, but it was not in the new world
Okay g14
That's where smoker have we seen this place before?
Uh, we have not we have seen this place before we haven't like explored it
It's just sort of like we know smoker and tashiki and a bunch of marines from g4
14 I think
Were the troop that met up or were at punk hazard and all that stuff and they're like
Battle hardened marines. They're big burly boys. Um in the new world. Um
And
Yeah, we got we got garp
garps here
Helmepo is crying
Helmepo and there's this black haired lady that he's talking to on the phone and there's this other girl
Who's this other girl this crying one?
Um, she I think there was a few chapters ago. I barely remembered it, but I went back
Um, this is vice admiral or vice. I can't remember something doll. I forget her rank
and this other character who is like, uh
Um the same rank as kobe friends with kobe. I guess we haven't seen her before I don't think doll is the black haired one
Yeah, and then this other girl, which I don't even know her name
Yeah, um, but they're like sort of looks familiar
Uh, it's kobe helmepo and her
buddy kobe's been kidnapped by black by black bear. So his garp is gonna go fight black beard
So, yeah, instead of going
Instead of going under kizaru's orders with warships to go to egghead, which is close by he's going to go instead
To get kobe back from black beard
um
Who had a confrontation as we spoke earlier
with bower hancock and rayley
and
kobe was there as well
and yes, and he yeah, he was yeah, he was the one that was like
Yeah, he yeah go with the marines. Uh, so that you don't die from black beard. Hmm. Yes. And she said no
So there's there's all this sort of stuff happening
And um, uh, it's a lot
But
There's a bunch of warships and kizaru on their way to egghead. I can comprehend this easily
There's kuma coming garp is nearby, but not going there black beard is
Going it's somewhere black beard is going
Okay, black beard
Failed to capture bower hancock. Yeah, and other than that. I don't think we know what he's doing
Um, well a few chapters before that I think or not before that
But a few chapters ago
He fought law didn't he?
He fought and he turned
Yeah, do you remember he fought the law and the law one thought I don't even know what happened
Uh, black beard and his crew
Came up to fight law to steal their
rubbings of the the poneglyphs
And the the doc q turned them all into women he did the gender
Oh, that's right
He did just very funny. He's I'm sorry. Was that a virus?
Did he does he have the does he have the freaking uh fruit that does that?
He has a fruit that does some sort of virus thing. Yes
And he just made a new virus and the virus was a turn you into switch your gender virus switch your gender virus
And everyone was like it's supposed to fluster them. Ha ha
Yeah, so it's like so it's like uh, it's like uh Naruto's sexy nojutsu
But instead of flustering the opponent by turning into a sexy lady and making them aroused
You fluster them by turning them into lady and making them confused
True interesting. Okay. Yeah, I do remember that now that you mentioned, you know, and
I know it would really have sucked
Uh, if if black beard got
Boa Hancock's fruit like he planned because then he would have the love fruit
And people would fall in love with him in a in a really weird like
I feel like him doing the pose
Yeah, and everyone going like heart eyes would be very strange
It's yeah, it's weird that he wanted that fruit. It's just
It's not I guess it's super powerful
I mean
It it it it's
Okay, hang on. Does it just make people fall in love with you or does it turn them to stone or does it do both?
It turns them to stone literally. Um, and I think it's praise on your
your uh
affection
Like it doesn't work on Luffy because Luffy is like asexual. He just doesn't know what sex is so it wouldn't work on anyone
Because everybody hates black beard and ugly so it just wouldn't do anything
That's the odd thing. Yeah, maybe I don't know idea. Hmm. Maybe you just wanted to hope that people would love him
I do you think maybe it was just hubris like he just thought like oh a fruit that's really powerful the more people love you
Oh, well, everyone loves me. Do you think it's just like he just thinks he's fucking awesome
And so he thought the fruit would be really good for him. Hmm
Interesting interesting
So, yeah, so this garp
It's I think it's just a lot. Are there any girls on the black beards team? Does he have a girl?
There's there's that one lady the this is like an old lady, right?
An older lady from impel down, right pirate. I think like
Yeah, I remember an L
I don't remember like what she does or anything. She's like a big nose, right? Yeah. Yeah, okay
like they're pirates
crew members
fucking
Katarina Devon that's her
Oh, of course who could forget Katarina Devon
She has not done anything yet
that I remember
Extremely tall pale skinned well endowed woman law
Of course, okay. You got it. We've got it. Yeah, but how well endowed is she?
Uh, well well, well, well, what do we got here? Who's a sexier old lady? Is it uh,
Katarina Devon or is it um, uh
Chopper's old mentor whose name is escaping me at the moment
Um old lady with the from drum island
Drum island. Yes. She's hotter
Just because she's got she's got that that swag. That's that's cool. She's got the the black leather
Well, she's the boots. Well, she's the glasses
Yeah, what's her? What's her name?
I can't it's not it's not kooja. That's the first thing kureha kureha kureha
Yeah, I would say kureha is harder if it's just my it's just my opinion because kureha has a slender build
Whereas this Katarina has kind of like a barrel-chested like muscular build and you know, it's just my personal preference
It's my personal preference that uh, uh, uh kureha
sexy
Yeah, kureha gilf everybody. I would say so. I would say so
It's I think i'm just yeah, uh, the fact that they just have a page of the kid pirates
Arriving at elba and then another page or double page of garp going on an expedition during all of this egghead stuff. It feels like
they're
it's sort of um
Like
It feels like they're building to
Ahead and they're having all of these things happen
Simultaneously, so they'll like culminate but like what the hell could culminate. Why are we learning about all of this stuff?
in this chapter
Is is something gonna happen in a few chapters where they all converge, you know really like oh my god
So they're all they're all going to different places
That's the thing. That's why it's like a little confusing. It's not confusing. I can comprehend it. It's just sort of like wow
Yeah, what the hell's gonna happen? It's a big mystery. What does
what does kid being on elba and
kizaru being on egghead
and uh
A garp and kuma being at the red line
kuma being at red line and maybe and marriage wa
and uh
Garp being wherever blackbeard is
I mean, maybe blackbeard is going to one of these places as well. So like maybe
I mean, maybe blackbeard and garp and kid will all end up at elba
uh
Just because
So blackbeard could show up at any one of these places at any time
And there's there's always the possibility that
kaito and big mom aren't dead
Because big mom had a whole thing with elba. I always expected her to like appear. Oh, that's true
At the giants because she's got such a connection to the giants
um
She's not from elba. Is she
I don't think she is maybe she's I forget like if she has like some giant dna
I don't think so. I think her parents are normal sized and she's just a freak. Yeah
And she learned about the giants and there was a giant at her town
They came and they were like friends
But then she had one of her like weirdo moments when she didn't get enough food and she fucking ruined everything
Yeah, yeah, and then the giants were like, um, this kid's too much get the fuck rid of her
I think that was the gist. Oh, was it the lady? Was it the lady who worked at the orphanage? Was she a giant?
No, no, she was small normal size. Hmm
Who was the giant in any event that I think they came to the
Where her village?
Or maybe she stayed with a giant the giants in a giant village because that was like a good place for her. Yeah
Uh, they I vaguely remember that I got to reread that part. But yeah, um, she's got
Uh an obsession with having a giant in her crew in her family
And she's been like banished from from Elba because she wants one of every race to be in her family. Yeah. Yes
Yes, understood
So I feel like I feel like big mom is definitely not dead just because that needs some sort of resolution
100 100%
100%
And then I think I guess it could be like kaito and big mom
They skulk away with their the remains of their crew and then they actually do form the new rocks pirates and they come back together
And they could they could clash on Elba
Yeah, there's so many fucking that would make sense for them to show up there. I think oh my god
Damn
And there's cobing. There's fucking x drake
There's all these marines going around doing marine things drake
Had like a falling out. They was working with basil hawkins, but then they like split up, right?
No, hawkins was working with kaito. He was like full full kuk mode
I'm just gonna be subservient to kaito. Nice. And deus drake was a undercover marine the whole time
Literally me literally me when I think about accruing power and accruing capital
It's time to go kuk mode. It's time to go kuk mode and be conservative because it will it would be a subservient
Because it will uh because it will it will generate capital for me
Who generate capital it will advance my position unless the straw hat pirates come and destroy everything
Right that would be bad
He'll be really bad to spend time working for kaito only for the straw hats to come and kill my boss
I like it. I like one piece. What can I say? I would say uh
Yeah, I've been telling anytime one piece comes up in conversation lately. I say I feel like it's as good as it's ever been
Yeah egg head egghead arc is really cool
And uh the story feels like it's got a lot of momentum right now
It's pretty exciting
How does he do it how does he do it how does he do it um
Nobody
Nobody knows
You I would be curious. He's a deal. He's got he's got the he's got the manga manga fruit
Oh my god
True. Mm-hmm. It is
it is
Like um, I would be really curious to see a manben episode
Of his holy shit. Can you imagine?
I mean, I yeah, it's it's just like clearly he's
Like a lot he's got a lot of stuff he does but he's definitely got assistance
He's definitely got a studio because there's no way
His arm would fall off his his entire arms would fall off
I think there's definitely like assistance. This is just speculation, but like for for backgrounds and stuff
Yeah, of course
Like and some of this it's just it's great
But how does it how does how does he do it?
Um
Every week basically
Dude a man a manben about
With oda would be a maid. There there was um
Okay, where there's some new manben's that came out or did some new episodes get translated like not that long ago
I think I think they got translated. I haven't seen them because yeah, because a new episode
You know
It's kind of useless to me unless it's been translated
So I kind of don't really care about new episodes coming out
I care about more episodes getting translated someone read not that long ago told me there were new episodes
And I haven't seen any of them
Join us next time on the pro crass there's podcast one piece corner
I feel like
At some point during that
I've had an idea popped into my head of something else
Some relevant shit that had happened or I was thinking about that I wanted to bring up and I thought
Not until after the we're in the one piece segment now
Oh
I remember
Uh, I was just wanted to mention that did a little slime rinalia holiday thing for uh for r with rfc k
If you could believe it
Uh, yeah, I actually actually drew some stuff for it if you can even imagine
Ben saint drawing
It's true. I know it's true. I did a little um
It was um one of the mods slash devs. Uh demodunk suggested to me that I
Do a little uh grinch
steel slime rinalia
villain
thing
So I did
But um, let me to briefly explain it. There was there was recently
a
A hack on the droplet which is some I don't really understand
I think that just means the bot. I think like the drop the droplet is like the code for the bot
It got hacked. There was like a leak. They had to do repair a bunch of stuff. It was kind of a hassle. Um
So I thought uh, hey, what if what if there was an item called the droplet
And it was like an endless rock. I actually think it was demo's idea that would be an endless rock
So we use the power of the droplet to cancel slime rinalia
um, the way that the way that I did it
was um
Well, there was a um the
Demo, I think was suggested a grinch thing, but I went a different way with it. I went um, you know, you know the movie the santa claws
Uh tim allen
That's the one where santa falls off the roof and tim allen puts on the suit and he becomes the new santa claws
I've seen a like an ad for that in a vhs, but I know what's the film
Yeah, I watched it as a kid, uh, but um
Yeah, so in the lore, uh, okay
first of all
The the the the lore the lore about slime rinalia is pretty you know, there's there's a febus aka slime and victus who is basically
mlachacom santa claws
But instead of giving you gifts he comes into your house and he steals all your shit
but
If you read between the lines even a little bit, it's pretty clear that's that slime and victus is actually just munchy
Sitting on my shoulders with a robe over us going around to juby's houses and robbing them
um, so
So in this in this in this new lore
Oh, uh, turns out there actually was a real febus
Oh, like oh, shit. He was real after all he does exist
And I and I caught him climbing up my roof and I yelled at him and he fell to his death
And I and I and I and I put on his robe and I cut him open and I found the the the endless rock in his kidneys
And now I'm the new and now I'm the new febus
Even though I already kind of was
And I cancel slime rinalia forever
Wow, and I drew some
Images of me announcing this
Becoming uh, let's see him. All right. I'll all right. I'll post him. All right. I'll freaking post him if you want
Yo
You're you're shrouded. I am shrouded. This is me
As I this is my the beginning of my announcement
I started at shroud and I started telling the story of the christmas miracle
Uh, and then I found uh, I found his business card
Found his business card as I was scavenging him
And then I reveal
The droplet
Wow becomes st. Invictus is what I'm calling myself now
Is that the the the endless rock? That is it. Yes. That is uh, that is the droplet
Layers within layers
See it's a kid see I found it in his kidneys. It's like a kidney stone
Because that's like a thing and anytime that I reference a kidney stone. It's funny because it reminds you the listener of the horrifying
Traumatic medical condition that I had that one time
Yeah, and that's funny. I'm so nostalgic for that. Me too. We have to go back
Uh, oh, why did I just switch to a new server? Uh
That's weird. Okay
Anyway, yeah, I drew these
drew these the other day
Then I made a big post in the auditorium, you know ruin the holiday for everyone, you know just for fun
Just for fun. It was my first it was like the first time I'd like uh, really like done any like
Are like rfck any like rfck interactions in a while. It was pretty fun
It was pretty neat
Had had fun with it. That's it. That's that's my and that was my other my other holiday
Story, how was my holiday? Well, this was part of it. It was part of the celebration
Thanks for asking
Okay
All right, let's shall we go to questions. I suppose we'll go to questions. I mean to voicemails. Well
Yeah, uh, they are often
Questions, but also not. I feel like I have a feeling we'll probably
I have a feeling at least one rfck
oid will probably uh
Mention that in the voicemails
um
So where are we? Uh, oh god
This one there's one just I'm looking for the latest one that we listened to
I think it's might be this one called yo slammer nailia
Yeah, so it'd be after that
There's a youtube link, but there's no description. So we skip those
Yeah
Is
Yeah, okay, I think the first one is called automation good
All right
Yeah, okay, let's do it
From blah blah at hotmail.blah automation good three two one go
So ben on episode 340 of the pro crest nature's podcast
You said something along the lines of I think that work bad and automation good
And while I can recognize some level of uh hyperbole in that statement. No, it did make me think because
Um, isn't that to some degree kind of a uh anti marxist settlement?
You know since from a marxist perspective, I'm pretty sure
capitalist criticism is not only because
uh capitalism exploits workers, but also because it demeans work in the sense of
Making it valuable only in the sense of its end product as opposed to
valuing the process of creation in and of itself
Uh, you know, I feel like
Automation valuing automation over work at all times. It kind of goes against that sentiment
Um, of course, you know, that doesn't mean you can never use automation, but
Like with a ir you know backgrounds fine, but you know don't overdo it
Yeah, no, I I get I get what he means though. I kind of I kind of don't get what he means
That's kind of the argument I had for like
Not against AI art, but just appreciating that there is
Value to be had in the creation of art for your own sake or like just it's fun to do
And so you don't have to automate stuff. You it's fun to draw. So like draw sure like you you were saying
It's good that you can automate stuff if you don't want to draw
Yeah, so I don't think they're
Like incompatible
Now I'm I'm no I'm no Marx scholar, right? I know I mean in in
In conquest of bread kropotnik is pretty I feel like kropotnik would say
Like yeah automate away as much work as possible. We should we should we should uh
We should automate anything we can because work is bad
We should like organize society to reduce the amount of work that needs to be done
um
this
I I feel like no, I I really feel like Marx would agree with that. I really feel like Marx would say that
The the need
I feel I feel like what did he what did I think this is prince
Uh, I think he said that like
Is it demeaning labor? Is it demeaning labor?
to
Reduce the need for it. No, I think what's demeaning
Is insisting that labor be done
When it's unnecessary. I feel like that is what demeans labor. I feel like to honor it
you would
you know
Expect that it'd be useful and like to simply
Expect that labor be done even in a context where we could
Choose not to do it without any loss
That's what what seems demeaning to me and I
Feel like Marx is is pro-automation in that sense and he I think I think he would agree with me
It sometimes it's fun to like dig a hole and plant a flower by yourself
Um, but it doesn't mean that there should not be automated ways to do it
Right as well. Right
You should have the freedom
To not be required
To or to to to dig the hole
But you can if you want to that's that's kind of what the ar thing
is. Yeah, I mean I
absolutely
Don't overdo it. No do overdo it. I mean I don't overdo it because because by definition that's like
doing too much of it, but like
Do do as much as you do as much as you can do as much as automate as much as you can get away with without
incurring any consequences
whether that be like legal
in that you're stealing someone's work or
uh, you know
Aesthetic and that like, you know the the piece you're making suffers because ai is not equal to the task of producing the thing you wanted to produce
um
Yeah, I don't know man. I I think it's Marxist as hell and I stand by everything I've said
Yeah, automation good work bad. No high no hyperbole
um
But and if it's a task that you want you simply want to do if you just want to draw a picture
I mean, I would argue that that's not work. That's that's leisure
Which is good leisure is good
Yeah, uh work work is
effort expended and you know to produce
Value to generate some sort of like economic
Return I think
um
Next one is called another question
Braps at official.com 3 2 1 go
Also, I have another question a completely unrelated one and I mean this in the kindest most positive
This is gonna offend me deeply isn't it?
I have question for this particular person this particular other person that calls into the pcp
And they always sound like they're speaking from a tin can yeah, that is hotboxed with like
40 400 milligrams of weed that they're also currently I think it's tom. So I think it's that guy tom this person who comes in like
Hey
Yeah, um, and I want to just ask that person
um
Am I correct that you're calling from inside a tin can and am I correct that you're usually
Blasted out of your mind in one way or another
If not, what's up?
You good?
Yeah, you you want to hang out?
Yeah, I love you. Yeah, that guy's delivery is weird. I'm not sure if it's like a language thing
He's always always it sounds like he's mumbling
Yeah, I guess I would say that guy like like quit mumbling freaking annunciate and also freaking like know what you're gonna say
You need to like you need to be jumping up and down when you when you're speaking
Yeah, fuck that get that blood pumping. Yeah. Yeah
um
You know fair question fair question. We'll probably hear from that guy, you know as we continue
Next one is called last edition
I think it's another from prince uh three two one go
Petition to have the tin can weed man t.m. Give his opinion on the war in Palestine
Do you believe in a two-state solution? Okay, goodbye
Okay, well we can't wait to hear his answer
Uh, next one is called how could I call myself?
A never donated never subbed three. Okay, three two one go
I fail
I didn't get costume quests to whatever that is. It's him. It's him. Epic game is give you a free game every day
And I lost one
I'm a failure as a scammer
Do you know what he's talking about?
uh
I missed I missed what he said
I did the gang coaster quest two
I did the gang coaster quest two whatever that is. What the fuck is he talking about?
I don't know
I don't want to accent shame
But I don't know if that's the I don't know if that's the issue here
I don't know what he's saying. I'm sorry tin can man
Um, next one is called. I want to be like you give with the png character three two one go
Give
Yeah, yeah
I do
I just saw your stream and
I didn't comment or anything. I just cut the tail into it
I've been meaning to ask somebody who does it. How do you uh
Make the little character and get it to bob up and down when you talk
Oh, uh, that's a program. Thank you. Uh, let me get so what a pretty pretty straightforward question
Uh vido tube mini vido vito
V e a d o
So vido like weirdly saying video
V e a d o tube mini
It's a little free program. You put a png in it and you can like set the parameters for how much
Like what what it you know, it switches to a different png
So I just drew a mouth open when it gets to a certain audio threshold and you can make it shake if you want
Uh, it's very easy to use interesting
interesting
Well good answer
Um, did I download that? Uh, yes I did. Okay next one is an imager
link
Uh, let's see
What we got here
Ew
You got that's that stretch. Oh, I
my
I look hideous, uh, this would be ben saint if he could resist the urge to tweet at elon musk wrong
There are many other failures that I would have to overcome
Uh, do you even want to end up looking like this though that face
You know what it is? It's it's because uh
He wanted my chin to match the chad's chin
But then he wanted me to give me a big forehead. So to do that, he had to smush my face down really far
Um, I do want that physique though. That's why I'm lifting again. That's why I'm lifting
Um, that'd be pretty cool pretty cool. Next one is uh
Do do do do do it are fast ck from prince isolation three two one go
RFC k endless war is a free to play mmo rpg playable entirely inside a discord server
That's what I've heard in it. You collect slime in order to kill people
You can revive from the dead and make funny slime oids
To say you beat in the game you would have to do all these things as quickly as possible
Ending with a total of 20 mega slime
For years players have attempted to push the game to its limits and finish faster and faster
So they never have to play that shit-ass game again
Until in january of 2023
One gamer beat them all
Here is that run
And then you play the fucking funny summoning itself. I was gonna say you should be playing and then we should be really funny
Should be playing that song
I knew the name of that song very funny at one point
You should probably google like summoning salt music and find a playlist. It's um, I mean, it's just one
it's just one of the songs that um
I think youtube just recommends it. It's like in the youtube playlist. Did I um, did I uh
Share the fact that my dinner with andre ends with the sad youtube song
No, I don't I didn't remember. No. Yeah. Yeah, the end of the movie it play
You know the the song i'm talking about
I there's a there's a number of sad youtube songs. I'm not sure. Oh god. It goes like
I've lost my focus. Um
it's um
Do you remember the name of it? Uh, I did know it. Uh, I can find it very quickly
No, okay, uh song from end of
Uh, uh
My dinner with andre
I can
I can playlists like look at this from there
Depressing songs for depressed people one hour mix
Oh, I think it's this one
Songs for different sad vibes
Bart I see i'm a simple man. I see bart simpson. I laugh here it is
uh, it's called
You will you will immediately recognize this song from youtube
Ellie is our play put it in
Oh, yeah, yeah
Yep
I mean, I know it's in a bunch of action button reviews. I'm sure it's in other videos
I've definitely heard it in other videos. I've heard it in an anime or two. I think
Really?
It's the sort of thing that would play and it's like, uh, beautiful scenery
I'm pretty sure I've seen at least one show have that as like a
Like an actual thing. Hmm. I I associated specifically with youtube
I mean, it isn't like it's a very old song
So there's probably lots of things that it's in
I guess I guess you know what I guess you're right, but um
Yeah, maybe andre wasn't even the first one
But yeah, my the the ending of my dinner with andre plays over, uh, this this song as well
Lamal
Uh, why did I?
Uh
What's hang on? What's the summoning salt song home home? We're finally landing. Yeah, that's the one. Yep
Next one is called crunchy crypto crap
three two one go
You ever notice how the fdx guy kind of resembles munchie?
Is that like upsetting at all?
the I mean
There's uh, sam bankman freed the guy who was uh
Basically the
I guess he's he sort of bears a passing resemblance to munchie. I kind of see it but like not like
To a degree that I find uh, unusual. No, it looks more like some other guy
Yeah, um, it's uh, he uh, sam bank. fdx was the big crypto exchange that like was
I think a couple like a month or two ago like went completely belly up because it turned out the whole thing was in
Solvent it was all just like fraud upon fraud upon fraud
Uh, and it was like like billions and billions of dollars were just like
Embezzled and like disappeared uh, and this this this sam bankman freed guy was like the CEO of it
And he was like
He's like a 20-something guy and like he would show up to like meetings and he would go on like talk shows
And he would be like and he would do it all in like his pajamas
And he would do it like all while playing league of legends and stuff
And the guy was like a complete hack and he had no idea what he was doing
But he just sold it
They just sold him on this mystique of like, oh he's some he's some mad genius like young prodigy or whatever
And his hair is unkempt. We must he's probably like smart his hair. His hair is unkempt
He's looks he smells like cheetos like he must he's must know something like what does he know?
um
Yeah, exactly
And it worked uh for a while
um
Yeah
Okay, the next one is called poo poo poo
three two one go
Give based off of older episodes. I need to know do you still have
Only one monitor
Uh, if no, it's pretty good, right?
having more
Uh, if you if he has
If why would you why would you end your voicemail like that?
Uh, yeah, I have two monitors
Uh
How long ago did I have one monitor?
I don't know that's like years and years ago. I've had two monitors for a long time
I see
Uh, I mean, I've got I've got my regular monitor and then I've got my uh tablet which also functions as a second monitor
Uh, okay next one is an imager link
So let's fucking go
Okay
Oh my god
So girlfriends go into go into youtubers, but the pious christian gamers
They get I mean not much
What do you want? Yeah, and what's the problem?
And then we've got fucking f n g r commentating live commentary over this scene that is playing out
Uh
I mean, it's just true. It's just true and honest
Is this because nate's uh getting married
Oh, yeah, I saw I saw michelle posted a ring picture. You know, I should
I should give them a call. I I did talk to them like on christmas. They did like they had a family call and they did like
Mention it to us at christmas
I should like give them a call or send them a message and like wish them like a personal
Congratulation. I haven't done that yet
um
Yeah, michelle posted that picture of the of the ring lol
Pretty epic pretty epic I guess
Fuck pious christian gamers
Yeah, I wouldn't I wouldn't date him either. Why would you what's the hat say?
I
Is it just a color shifted maga? It might be
Why is this color shifted?
It says
Yeah, it's just it's just a maga hat. I don't know why it's green
He's like an environmentally conscious pious christian gamer
That says one he allows himself one progressive value and he cares about the environment and good for him
okay, uh next one is
Uh, it's another integer
Speaking of my monitor situation my monitor
Some things on my second monitor like like windows will like freeze and like show what is in the window behind them
That's been happening more and more often and it makes me cry
um
I have no idea what that is
Ellie it's eliot roger
Oh, no. Yeah. Yeah, I was referring to oh, oh, oh my tech my technical problem
Yeah, it's only on the one it's only on the the tablet monitor
but anyway
goal d roger
elio
elio elio elio t elio elio d elio d
elio roger
elio
roger
I mean
What more can I say how he's got a car?
Of course, he's king of the pirates. He could just drive to the to to write to one piece. Yeah
I could drive there easily
um
Okay, the next one
The next one is from
Well, it's called homogenous as too homogenous and there's an arrow and they're both vocaries
um
Hang on. Hang on. Wait a second before we listen to this. I'm gonna do something
Absolutely fucking insane
I'm gonna do something
Doesn't sound very ridiculous. Okay. Okay. No. No. No. This is gonna be so fucking epic
Um, all right. All right. I gotta put my scale. I gotta put my little kitchen scale right here on my counter
And then
All right. Here's the kicker. All right. I'm gonna turn it on
All right, okay, and it says low battery, but I know that it's lying the scales a piece of shit
It tells me it's battery is low all the time and then I just turn it on again and it works fine
all right, so
I'm gonna take some cheese
0.7 ounces
Whoa
0.7
points that I know and then I'm gonna take some pepperoni
It's 1.2
Pathetic and then I'm gonna eat it
And now I know exactly how much I just ate and I can put it in my calorie counting app
Wasn't that crazy?
So you weigh every bit of every morsel of food. Well, what when it's when it's something that
It has like variance to it
When it's something that like if I'm eating like
Serial
Like I measure out a cup of it and then I don't have to weigh it
But if it's like meat or cheese, yeah, you know weigh it you know weigh it and find out how much it is
I guess so
How else would you know how else would you know?
I don't I don't think about it so strictly. I just that's right. You don't think about it. That's right
I put in like a vague like approximation
Fringe
I'm doing science here
I'm doing science here. Yeah, I'm gonna do it again
One point. Yep 1.5. Okay. So each slice of this cheese is 0.7 ounces and each piece of this pepperoni
Well, how can you be sure every single slice of cheese is exactly the same?
Well, because I just weighed the second one
And it was also 0.7. You gotta weigh every single one
That was my last one
Don't they get like
Are you getting food all over the thing?
I put a paper plate on it. Oh, okay, then. I'm a genius. All right. Wasn't that crazy?
Uh, no, wasn't that epic? It may be epic. Thank you. Okay
These are my leftovers my leftovers from the new year's party
Okay
Now we're ready to listen to homogenous chapter one
Uh, three two one go
This episode of the pcp has been and give
The episode before has been and give
The next episode will also have been and give
Every gibb-a-sode is a benesode
Every benesode is a gibb-a-sode. Mm-hmm. It's all very
Homogenous
Um
Yep, that's the pcp guarantee every episode every is a benesode and every benesode is a gibb-a-sode
Yes, that's a good
tag
I
perfectly normal
perfectly normal for a podcast to have the same
Cast everything that's why they call it a podcast
Because the cast
I like peas in a pod. I like peas in a pod. There you go. Perfect. Thank you. You finished my thought for me
We finished each other's sandwiches. Okay
Uh, you didn't even let me finish that sandwich. I didn't trust you to do it
I knew you would fucking up. Okay, the next one is called
Well, it's uh, I gotta download that one. Fuck uh
Download uh, the next one is also homogenous, but with capital letters this time
Okay, are you ready? Yep. Okay three two one go
5,615.4 divided by one free free seven is 4.20
What is mr. Conference of cock the square root of 4,761 is 69 try to keep up try to suck dick
Did you know the orbital period of Pluto with 7.82 billion seconds? That's too slow get in the fast lane get in my ass
You're a hot guy. I bet your draper point is 69.99 degrees kelvin square of the one carry the two
You've got an equation for the male persuasion
First the cum blast then the brain blast life's good when you're a homo genius
I get it
Okay, I was really what what's okay. Okay. Okay
And that is very homo genius homo genius. I mean in that he spelled it wrong
It's spelled it's spelled wrong in the in the voicemail, but that's okay
An equation the male persuasion
Uh, what is the circumference of cock? Nobody knows nobody knows scientists have been
trying to find out
Okay, all right, um the next one
Oh god, it's another
God, it's another vocaru. Okay, uh, three two one go
Oh
Is this demon days
It's like that is the intro
I'm just sort of expecting a fat beat to drop
Hmm
And then track two
Yeah, it's a big beat like oh bass. Oh, oh, it's me 2d. We're the gorillas. I love 2d. Uh, we're the gorillas and we're here to say
Nothing I'm a homo genius. I'm a homo genius
Uh, I mean it's nice, uh, nice soundscape bro. Nice little uh, nice little uh
Well, it's an audio environment you created there for me ominous ominous
homominous
Next one is called zero
Wait a minute. We have to download that one
Okay, there we go. The next one's called zero three two one go
What's the best digibro video best digibro video
Hmm
The best digibro video
Probably measurement man
That's not digibro. That's modal soul
but
uh
Dang it. I mean there is no good video then
I mean unless I mean, I don't know I
I was thinking of ones on the main channel. Yeah, like about an anime
or something
I I would say
I mean, um
If it counts as one video, I guess I would probably say the asterisk war sucks is pretty good. Um
Is there another one that's like comparable to that?
There was this sort out online
sucks
Your anime sucks series. There's a couple asterisk war is asterisk war is better
Asterisk war is the best version of that
I like that one and then um, the the mamoru oshii
a career
Like history one is pretty good. That was that's the last good digibro video
Yeah, I I can't remember any specifics except for the big ones like the
The we have accepted mediocrity was pretty good. I think
You know what?
I'm gonna say in hindsight it actually wasn't good
Because it came from a place of she had no idea what she was talking about and like she didn't mean anything that she said
Yeah, I like the video though. It's very well edited. Davoo did a good job
I actually I'll be honest. I kind of don't really even remember like what happens in that video
It is it is it is a rambling thought stream of consciousness, but it's it's a cool experience because of the editing
Hmm when it comes to like an analysis of an anime
I
Mean I don't really watch the enemies that are talked about so it's hard for me to remember
Yeah, I never really watched the ones that were like here are my thoughts about an anime because I don't
Yeah, wasn't don't watch them how to tell if an anime is bad in just one episode that got a lot of views
I don't remember if I enjoyed it. I don't think that one's as good. I mean that one's fine
It's just it's just a recommendation for like oh drop shows early if you aren't enjoying them. Yeah
Yeah, I mean, okay. I have I have no issue with that
What was the one about like like steins gate versus regular gate?
Oh, it was a show called gate that had a really bad intro
And it was about like the the knights of yore and the tanks
Fighting what wasn't that the how to tell a bad because because how to tell a bad
No, how to tell a good anime is the one with that's about steins gate
I just remember there was a steins gate versus regular gate and that was a funny joke
Because it's not called regular gate
It's called gay vaguely. I vaguely remember that one
um, I'm gonna go with I'm gonna go with asterisk war sucks and
The mamoru oshii I can't I can't really think of another are there
Are there any other videos that she did that were like the mamoru oshii like the story of this guy's career because like
Did you do one about hidi eki ano?
I don't recall one about him, but um, there was this one about this
Uh painter or like background artist
Who's you know, like oh that that guy I don't remember his name
Oh, that rings a bell
Just looking through like the the backgrounds of this particular anime background artist
Because nobody thinks about background guys
But I you know
If you remember thinking
I think I remember feeling positively about that one. I'll didn't leave a huge impression on me
Okay, I think we've answered this question sufficiently. Yeah next one is called hey man
Uh, hey man cool podcast three two one go
Dude Ben, why didn't you tell me what a podcast dude? I'm gonna kill myself. I'm gonna kill myself
I live in fear of this the hypocrite and the cum zone guy
That's awesome. Like hey, you want to come on my podcast sometime? I think it'll be great and I'll pay your share of the rent
For that. Oh, well, okay. Maybe I can show to like, you know promote the ben's roommates podcast
Hey, oh and steve said we need more tp. You're good for it, right?
Thanks, dude
I mean
I mean this was supposed to be a parody but like if he's gonna pay my share of the rent like fuck
Yeah, you can come on my stupid podcast like yeah, of course
I like the fact that they know hypocrite and the cum zone guy, but they don't know you
I think yeah, I mean I think
Yeah, if they knew if they knew both of those people I think they would definitely know me that's probably true
uh
I mean
I'll just say it again like
Yeah, if someone wants to pay me money if someone wants to pay me money to be on my podcast or have me on their podcast like I'm
I'm more than amenable
to such thing
So you don't don't get the wrong idea. I'm not here to not sell out. Okay. Let's make that abundantly clear
Um, next one is called. Well, it's an integer. It's an integer link. Yeah
Let's say I made this episode's thumbnail
Didn't unless maybe he did let's see
um
What I think they're they're assuming we'll talk about brazil
Why would I talk about brazil because the the new guy is like
Left leaning and the bad guy the the guy who lost is like refusing to admit it and there's like some news about that
But I haven't really been keeping up with it
I guess I did um sort of hear about I didn't realize they had had like
Right, they had to do like a runoff election, right
I have no idea. I just know that the the old guy is like cranky about it. He's like pissed
I know that they had an I think they had an election and lula like won
But he won by such a narrow margin that like it didn't count so they had to do like a a revote
which has now
Turned out that has won again
And I mean I did yeah, I did want that to happen, but like I'm not I'm not following the story that closely
I don't know who these girls are. Why is this playing on the on the thing?
I don't know man
I don't know is wait swing swinging a mess with this thumbnail
Try again try again
uh
Submit one every week
Until we use it and then you win
Uh next one is another integer link
Uh-huh
Some cake it's time for some cake my dear. It's time for some cake my dear. It's time for some cake my dear
Um, I still don't know what these drawings are from
Have we not got any like comments?
You know about it
I have not
I I never I didn't uh read the
Comments on last weeks or two weeks ago's episode yet. I've kind of been meaning to and I haven't done it
So maybe somebody did
Say an answer, but I haven't seen one
And yeah, I still don't know
Uh, and I I know
Somebody somebody knows somebody knows what this what these these
Big boob cat girl ms paint characters are from
Uh, but it's not me next one is called sorry if it is too fast. Also. Do you know good text to speech?
three two one go
I'm so baffled and frustrated with all this AI art today
Artists who stand against AI art are like workers who stand against automated factories
No, shit. It is bad for you, but guess what it is good for humanity
Let's imagine a scenario where AI development is so rapid and good that it can literally replace an artist
Like you think of an image and it creates it from your head or even better and stylizes it and you can transform it in any sort of way
How is this bad for artists? Sure, you maybe don't have a career anymore
But now directors writers programmers and authors can quickly and affordably create any visualization they need
It frees aspiring non-visual creators from necessity of having a bunch of money and connections to make their work seem
In the old day musicians could not record without gatekeepers or record labels who would give them access to recording studio
Now digital software costs nothing and allow you to produce top-notch recordings
The same is with art
But benefiters are other creative people having said that artists are not just factory workers
They are creators too
Yeah, I cannot replace them 100%
Because even as hired contractor artists job can be to elaborate on design produce concepts experiment
I personally have an artist that makes art for my video game
And there's so much creativity that he brings even though I have a pretty solid vision of how things should be
And if I can replace such artists too aimed at almost the real intelligence
And if it is a final point of AI development
It seems like those artists from art station flash mob want to sacrifice the ultimate progress of humanity for the sake of their job security
How painful
Who will god i mistake on this podcast his opinion on such topics was always so on the other side from years that it created interesting conversations
who will
Wait, what was that last bit?
Uh, I wish Nate was on the podcast because his opinion was so different from your guys that would create interesting conversations
And then he said it. Ooh
I guess I mean, what do you mean like?
I don't think he would be on these opposites. It wouldn't be on the opposite side for me. I think we'd be on the same
I think he was probably
Well, you know, actually, I don't I don't know
I think he would probably agree with me that automation is good
I think that the reason I push back against it is just because
Um, I think it's good to argue for your job security
because
Uh, yeah, what are you gonna do if there's no way for you to make money?
That sucks
There's no there's no system in in place to allow for people
To be okay with their job security being threatened
They need money to live and they need a lot of money because things are so expensive right now because of the war and other things
I would say I mean, I I guess the one
Thing I would maybe say about that is that uh, it's it is yeah, I do think it is good
Even though even though it might cost some people jobs
I do think it is good
To remove the need for it's it's a net good to remove the need for labor
Even if it eliminates jobs because I think reducing the need for labor is good with with the understanding
That like the thing that replaces that labor can't be privately owned by some
Capitalist it has to be something that
It has to be available to
people yeah in
In a in a demo like like what the bitcoin people say what the what the ai people say that it's democratizing art like yeah
If it actually does that that's good
It it doesn't do that if like you own the software and it's proprietary or if anyone owns it
If it is out there and anyone can use it and it makes things more. Yeah kind of like
studio a soft software music software studio
Made it possible for people to make stuff that could have made it before
Then yeah, it isn't that good even if
It's bad for some people so I agree listen to caveat, but um
My problem is mostly with capitalism when it comes to like ai making things easier, then yeah, I'd agree
Yeah, like generally yes
Because like
I mean
I don't know. What do you what do you think would would you use a software that like you didn't have to like draw you could just
Type in some prompts and it wouldn't steal anyone's work or anything
But it would just like use some smart things to like just know what you were thinking and like produce the image you were imagining in your head
um, yeah, I would
if there's no like victim and
It's saving me
I don't know like moving my arms around or needing to to be better at drawing
If it if it's like oh you put this chip on the side of your head and you can imagine something and it will appear as an image
It's like that's that would be great. I would love that
I
might use it sometimes. I think um
I do think that like draw actually drawing yourself
Probably creates a sensibility
That is irreplaceable in terms of like appreciating
Aesthetics and that that aesthetic sense is part of what would let you imagine an appealing image in the first place
also, I mean the
Sometimes an image is enhanced by like especially in physical media like
The physical material that produces it sometimes like the texture of that material
forms a part of the
Image and it's aesthetic and enhances it and AI can't replicate that unless you build a robot to do it in physical
media
I would still I would still get
It's it's the same way that like, you know, we ascribe value to things
Arbitrarily and if you know something is hand drawn
um, as opposed to AI generated
There's there's just an in like
The viewer the audience will ascribe meaning
Based on that to the to work like even if it's an identical thing
If a computer if a computer can identically create something people
generally just have affection for
things that are more personal
So like yeah, I would I would still draw just because I I like drawing and it's nice to see something that I did
If I could imagine if I'm like, oh, I'm listening to this song
And I'm imagining a music video and if I could turn that into a real music video
That would be great because doing all of that extra work to really make a music video for that
song
would be like months and months of
Backbreaking labor that I don't want to do
Right. I mean, I mean, do you do you think like when you see a music video and you like it?
Do you think like, oh, I really appreciate what I really appreciate about this music video
Is that I know that a team of like two dozen people
Had to like, you know spend weeks and weeks like getting together in a warehouse and setting up sets and setting up shots
And choreographing it all and setting and someone had to edit it and someone no
Yeah, I mean, I don't think that but like I I think that
It would matter to me for I don't really feel that way about drawing
Like because things that you're drawing yourself. Yeah. Yeah, like if I felt like a computer was
I mean, it's a it's a weird hypothetical because it's like
At what point is it really
The computer if it's my imagination like I don't know how
Yeah, if you I mean you have you have full you have complete control over what the image is
You don't actually have to draw it, but the computer can just translate yet
Can just translate your thoughts exactly onto like like like the way I imagine it in like right now
Is I I imagine the drawing in my head and then I use my motor
Skills with my penmanship to create the drawing with my arm
And then using a computer
Like interpreters a different way of doing this exact same thing
So I guess I wouldn't feel differently about that
I think yeah, I think if if if I like I I could imagine a scenario where
I would just want something to be legitimate
Because I know everything is AI generated and I just feel like it would be it'll feel a little special
I if something was not that
I do think I mean
Art out of adversity. I I do feel like the the limitations
And the compromises that come from
producing an image
Especially in a in a physical medium is like is air is air does give something irreplaceable and and AI can never replicate that
Uh, that's not
And that's something that's mostly in like in like painting
um
Digit if you're drawing digitally
Still I think there are you know
You just people talk about like like happy accidents like sometimes you'll be drawing and you'll draw something that you didn't mean to draw
You make a mark you you live the line some way and it looks good
By accident and then you go oh, I kind of like that and then you just go with it
And you know those kind of things only happen if you are
Fumbling around with your fallible human machine that you are attempting attempting to manipulate
in order to uh
Give instructions to your computer to interpret into an image on screen
Um, I think that kind of stuff is not
Reproducible by AI. That's the kind of thing that a person does. Yeah, I also think that the argument that
Like AI is is is like being held back by artists
it I feel like AI is not
trying to progress
Enough in the in that way because it really it still currently relies on stealing artwork
in order to train itself
And people use the ability to steal artwork
Um to like get a specific artist style and then make money off of selling
I would say it's it's maybe not exactly a lot of grifters in the scene that are sort of also holding it back in a different way
They're not they're not thinking
Maybe in the future we could imagine things and make them real because
They just want to make money right now
Yeah, yeah
and that's
If like if that's the
When that's that's the whatever we have now cannot be the end point because it sucks
It is not
It's not good enough. No, it's not good enough
It's it's not it's not good enough
As far as I can see it's not really good enough that it can exist as like a standalone thing
That produces things on its own it needs to be
It can all it can only be used as a tool in like interpreting
An artist's work and extrapolating from an artist's work and to do you either have to produce what it is interpreting
Or you have to steal it from someone else and interpret what something someone else made and seems like that's where it's at
Um, which is fine. Um, I mean not the stealing part
Okay, uh, I think you want to go to the next one. Yeah
You there? Yeah. Okay. Uh, next one is the cringis three two one go
Yeah, what job is she?
He tell me
Kringis bingus the third. Yes
Confrontational cringis
Okay
This week I cranked at
The latest episode of the pcp
No, fuck you Ben made a fool of himself from the comics. Oh my god. It was kind of cringe. Fuck you
I do this for you
Alice in borderland season two
It's really good
Kring confrontational Kringis signing out
Borderlands the game. I guess so I haven't played it
But I've seen it
Uh
I didn't know deadly comics thinks I'm cool
When I asked him why don't girls like me he thought I appreciate this man's honesty
He's relatable
People don't understand that I'm doing a bit people don't understand that anytime I do anything embarrassing
It's a it's just a bit just a character and I did it. I was just playing a character
I was just doing a bit. I was doing it to get a laugh
And if you don't appreciate that then you don't deserve it, okay
Then I'll cry if you don't appreciate that then I'll cry you shit myself. I'll cry a little bit
Yes, I will cry. Yes, I'll cry out of pity for you. I'll cry out of pity for that
You don't get my human humor. You can't appreciate it
And I'll shit myself
in protest
It'll be deliberate
And it'll be a part of the bit, but you won't get it
You'll go it'll go way over your head. Okay. Next one is called. It's too big for my own good always cause a tiny bit of bleh
blue
What a world at humble brag dot com three two one go
What does your perfect christmas look like?
Mine looks like doing my wife by the fire
And not hurting her massive penis
That would be a christmas miracle
I I missed what he said. He said what does your perfect christmas look like?
Mine looks like doing my wife by the fire and not hurting her with my massive penis
Oh, I thought he said not hurting her a massive penis. I thought it was a twist. I think
He's saying he hurts her. He's humble bragging about his penis is too large to
Engage in copulation with his
wife without uh causing injury
That's abuse that's spousal abuse right there. Not if she's gonna have to quit quit it
You're gonna have to cut it out
Not if not if she's you're gonna have to hit it and quit it my friends
Not if she likes it and is consent there's consent for injury
Then it's good actually
It's better
That's all I have to say. He's gonna sign a waiver. Congratulations on your huge penis
But uh, you know, sorry to hear about your weak wife
Sorry, you have sorry you have to deal with that
I'm sorry. You have this problem that you have to deal with or your wife keeps getting injured by you
You know, that must be really hard on you
Uh, next one is called moider or assassino
three two one go
I'm not a crazed gunman. I'm an assassin
Well, one is the job and the other's mental sickness
Thank you for your
Reference. What is that a reference to I've heard that before it's from the tf2 meet the sniper video
You know those it's not even it's not even that funny of a line really
Yeah, I mean it's okay. It's characterization
um
Next one is uh
My name's your link. Yes. There we go. Uh, don't do a reverse image search of this picture worst mistake of my life
I can't do it on firefox. How do you do it? Well now I gotta do it
I mean, I'm seeing a bunch of the same images
I'm seeing a bunch of other
pictures of dinosaurs
Oh, I just realized the murder or assassin thing was referencing when we were talking about that in that previous episode
Like what is considered a murder or an assassination?
But that was clear that up. It's just a reference
Uh, okay. Well, I yeah, I do remember that actually so I see the
See what they're going for. Um, yeah, I'm gonna admit. I don't like see anything
I don't see or really see anything in the in the
search results
I mean, I almost feel like maybe I should find just the original image without the caption and reverse search that
Oh
Um, I think it might be because
I think it might be the name
What's the name it's it's uh, I think you'll understand when I say it
I think it is called or at least it is someone's called the niger the Niger sorus
You get it
n i g e r c a u
I mean, okay, he looks pretty shocked to hear this
Yeah, he's a fan. I can't believe they they caught like a real like like dinosaur that's alive with skin
Yeah, and then they called him a slur and it offended him
He's like you can't believe he was I can't believe he was such a live
Okay, it is a real dinosaur. Okay. All right. I get it because it was discovered in
Niger gado gado fawah in Niger. Yeah somewhere
Well, that was a funny joke. Uh, you got me
Uh, the next one the dinosaur youtube guy loves those silly little pictures three two one go
Hey y'all, it's fucking
4 20 in the morning. Let's go. Let's go. I just finished the eight hour unique name of sorus video because I hate myself
And I'm an idiot not the dinosaur guy even though he has sorus and it was bad. It was a fucking fugue
I don't know what to do
Every now and then he'd talk about the folding ideas line go up and it was like a moment of clarity of like
Oh, that's a point that makes sense
And then he'd just show more he showed so many tweets. I know you're probably sick of talking about this
but I was like
Is it as bad as they say?
I guess. Um, yeah, I mean I haven't watched it and I never will my
Impression of it is that yeah most of his argument boils down to like some people said some things that he thinks are mean
Hmm and that that makes NFTs good actually because people that don't like NFTs are mean
Yes, I remember
Skipping around to see if he mentioned the line goes up video
Yeah, and then he did and his response to something was like, well, that's stupid actually
So I was like, okay. Do you remember what it was? I don't remember. I don't remember
I think it was just sort of like a weird
Interpretation of what dan Olson was saying
And so I'm like, okay. I can disregard this whole video. And so I didn't watch the entire thing
the um
It's funny when you say the dinosaur youtube guy, I do not think of unique nemosaurus. I think of tray the explainer
Do you know tray the explainer?
No
I mean he has a
Fucking dinosaur
Does he explain that
Uh, probably
Probably at some point, uh, he's good. He does a lot of like like archaeology
And like history and like anthropology sort of stuff. Uh, and he's good
Next one is called one of adult swim unmisses three two one go
Watch uh, yolo crystal
Crystal yolo crystal fantasy really funny
Yolo crystal fantasy crystal
Don't know what that is
Yolo crystal fantasy
Uh, I I do see it here
Okay, now I've seen this somewhere
Oh michael cusack
I'm gonna be honest
I do not looking at it my immediate impression is that I do not want to watch it
Michael cusack is the guy uh, half of smiling friends. Yes
Oh
With ony
Wait, is it ony? No with with sack
Psychic pebbles. Yes, right sack hadle
right
Um, I could be good
Uh, it could be good. The you know, it's one of these
It's got that look about it. It's got that look about it. That is so
It looks like looks like one of these fucking uh, you know adult animation with uh, you know
Simple animation and I have nothing against that other than every fucking show looks like that
And I just hate media
Yeah, when are they gonna make when are they gonna make um, uh, uh
Thunder cats
They're gonna make thunder cats
Exactly, that's exactly what I'm saying. The next voicemail is from at killer prince 9 30 3 2 1 go
You know what fuck off. I didn't like the last guy's tone
I heard the next guy also skin babies
What you didn't like the next guy's turn
And he's killing babies the last guy's tone. He didn't like the last guy's tone
Oh, it's like it's just talking about whoever came before
This one is called at killer prince
Does he does he know that prince isolation roasted him like how would he know that?
uh
A e-guest is a big guest. It paid off though
Well killer there's no killer prince prince is a rowdy
So what's going on? Is this just a weird coincidence? I'm not probably okay
Well, the next one is an imager. So let's fucking look at it. Why don't we teacher?
I'm giving you easy homework this time even a complete dumbass will be able to solve it
Kid named complete dumbass
If you're
If you're not aware
That is tectonic improv from the uh, uh, linkara
Atop the fourth wall lecture
Which you should watch if you have not watched it. It's good. It's a good lecture
Um, all right. Next one is another imager
I was just green it was green verification
Because of slime. Oh, right
Okay, this is um
Elon I can't do it. I want to keep it alive not only uh, even if you laugh at a lot of
I'd be happy to do it for $40
Great. I also dozen years running a podcast
If you even if you laughed out loud at this
I am a hundred percent certain I could be the very at very least help immensely with prioritizing
rollouts that maximize growth in the shortest time frame
And I would be happy to do it for $40. Why $40? I know the the cornering said he would do it for free
Uh, well, you know, he's got some dignity $40 worth. I have I have exactly $40 worth more dignity than
Than the quartering that sounds about right
Anyway, next one is uh, I can make the sound better, but the explanation was great in
three two one go
All right. So what you're gonna do is take your dominant hand
pinch your own cheek
The closest to the hand
a little bit back
Not on the
right beside the mouth
You open your mouth on the same direction only a little bit
and you pull it
and
reach back and repeat
Not it I get it. No
Uh
I'm not doing it. I mean, oh, I also didn't understand the instructions because I'm a visual learner
Um, I don't know what I mean. I heard him. I heard him making the sounds
I don't know how I'm making it correctly right now. I'm trying. I'm trying my best
Oh, it's mr. Plankard
All right, we're gonna watch
That's my best. That's my best. This is my best shot
Next one is called unnecessary correction to a forgotten conversation
Really just recommending isokan again though at anime.base three two one go
No, my fucking autism four weeks ago on episode 339
You said masaki yuasa was a studio trigger guy, but he's actually not at all
I missed it made a mistake said was true though
He did work on space dandy and azokan and you should fucking watch azokan
It's short and it gets the creative passion flowing. It makes me come every time everybody says it's really good
And I should probably do
It's a nice little show. I I like them. I like us. Uh, us. Is that is the is the devil man cry baby
devil man cry baby, uh, the thing with the white people, uh
Uh, the sotami to tomi galaxy to tomi galaxy
You seen that? Nope. Oh, that's pretty it's pretty good. Um, next one is called i'm stupid still watch isokan though at anime
It's not based three two one go
Oh, no, I'm stupid. I listened to three more seconds and you corrected yourself. Oh, oh, oh, what an idiot
What a freaking jerk
Gotcha kill this man
Uh, next one is called pussy triangulation
Uh, it's a it's a
Ah fucking vocaru
You're you're turning us into vocaru refugees right now. Mm-hmm. Okay, three two one go
Oh, no, where are we?
Oh
What a second or the funny fucking second
What the fuck
Shut up. What the fuck?
What the fuck is going on? What the fuck?
Oh
This frog doesn't understand
What the fuck what the fuck
Fuck is going on
I still don't have an answer. I don't know. You still don't know what the funny fuck is going on
Sorry, man
Next one's another imjolink. All right, let's uh, let's freaking do it
They're all women now
Yeah, lol, lol
Uh
Haven't seen that picture in a while
That was from
Probably like 2017 or something
Wow 100 years ago that approximately a hundred years ago
uh
next one
Lamal next one is an
Injure album. Oh my god a whole a whole freaking album. I think it's just one image. Yeah, okay
Sasuke
When are they gonna get back to Sasuke? When are they gonna get back to him?
I mean true. That's this fucking tiger man. Probably some filler episode loser
That's what happened. It's just like Sasuke left
They tried to get him back. They failed and then there was a bunch of filler until shippuden
No, I mean there was a bunch of filler in shippuden
No, no, no, there was like two like a hundred or something episodes. Maybe not that many
Um between the ending of the arc where Naruto
uh, neji
Choji
Fucking dog boy and uh, shikamaru. They all go to get Sasuke back
And I maybe messed up who was there, but like they fight a bunch of urochumaru's like underlings and stuff
and uh, they don't and then it ends with um
I think it ends with Naruto and Sasuke at the waterfall and they have that epic battle. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and then that's like the end of
Main Naruto, right?
Yeah, but in the anime there's a bunch of episodes after that, which is nothing
That's the filler like dead zone. I'm like, when are they why are you fucking around?
I just watched them all because I didn't know what filler was
I thought it was all important
I like this little stick figure of my icon my pony icon
All right next one
Not hyper though not even I like it
Oh
Okay, extremely important opinion on muscle girls
No, no, thanks on what girls muscle girls muscle girls
I think it's cool to have muscles not really but like bodybuilder muscles in general
I'm not really into they look weird with the
With the many too many there's too many muscles there. How'd you get those extra?
Yeah, yeah, I guess I feel I guess it's true. Yeah, kind of true of men also
Uh
Sure
Next one is there's so many images. So many these images are freaking links
my god
Joe Joe vote for someone or else I will release the epsin tapes
epsin jay
I don't know why these are so funny
Uh, they're really doing it for me though
They're really doing it kidnapped epsin tapes
Very popular in school
Um, okay, and next one is I hope he likes me wait. No, there's another amateur. Yeah
Yeah
Teacher today, we're going to talk over lethal
Kid named lethal or made by elia rott elia roger
That's how she felt on the pcp. Look at how the sun
The sunlight turns her purple hair blonde and her purple dress green
That's the sun for you. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but you gotta
I understand that it could be a little hard to break into the I understand that it could be a little hard to break into a conversation sometime
but if you're just if you're just gonna
But if that's but if that's how we talk and then you're just gonna sit there and you're just gonna be like
um
um and not and not break in
And then and then just complain about it later like i'm sorry like you're you're the problem
You you got it. You got to adapt or die
Uh
And and did she complain about it?
not
Okay, maybe I mean not like all the time, but
A handful of times I think a hand I think a handful of time. I mean I complained about it as well
Yeah, and you're a bitch
So, you know
uh
No, I think this is maybe like I'm thinking maybe like one or two
You know, it was probably more even more like viewers. There's probably more commenters being like stop talking over me
Yeah, I remember that
She can't talk. She can't say anything. Why are they so mean?
Die hypothetical commenter
I've created you in my mind for the express purpose of telling you you're a bad person
You should kill yourself. Wow so strong
Exactly. That's how strongly I feel about that guy that specific guy and no one else
um
Next one is
a uh vocaloom
Okay, three two one go
You believe in fools having fun
I do not like you
Oh, that was the hypothetical commenter
No, that was his comeback
What?
Come on. I just told you to kill yourself. Do you have to be mean?
About it. That hurts my feelings, man
Come on. It's just a joke
All right fine
Uh, next one another of our crew
Okay, uh pussy triangulation returns. Oh my god, it's the big it's the big return
Here we go. Three two one go
Pursuit
Triangulum
What do you mean?
Wait a minute. I'm an idiot. I read I read it as triangulation, but it it was triangulon
Before as well. Let's triangulon in this one as well. What does he mean? What? Yeah, what does it mean?
Like it's like a triangular shape
Of a pussy yes
Yes
Called the pubis mons
May perhaps you familiar
I I don't know okay. I don't know
Next we've got we've only got one more. I thought we might have like tons and tons
We did have kind of a lot, but we got through them pretty fast. Um, only one more
Imgur album
Saint family reunion, uh, we got um
We got all the all the guys
Goku
This is the guy from like jojo season one. I think right no, isn't that uh, the
Oh, no, that's the strongest seven in the heavens a thousand fists something or other
Song of song of the south song of the south
Fist of the north star. Yes
got song of the south
Joe one of the the one jojo
Jojo star
The jode. Yeah, the jojo is jojo
Is that is that bockey the grappler?
I don't know
He looks grappling. I think I think bockey bockey's supposed to be short
I think it's bockey the grappler, but I think he's supposed to be like kind of a short guy like wolverine
Uh, and then of course there's me
And what am I like a little like girl with a that that's gone in the night
That's the male protagonist from the high school of not high school but that high school assassination classroom
assassination oh
Uh, cool
So this is how they feel right the their power
over you
Their wealth manifesting in huge muskles. Oh, you mean
Oh god, this is because I like I said the same thing about the last like christmas party like everyone else is powerful
Yeah, yeah, I see I see
I
Very prescient and you know very very good that I complained about the exact same thing again on this episode and now here it is
An answer to my prayer
I mean at least I've got a gun
What is here in your mouth?
No, the knife is in my other knife. Yeah, no, I was wondering what it was. It looked like a green thing
Oh, no, it's uh, it's a it's a knife. It's a knife. Um, I mean
I
Like it, uh, thank you for the voicemail
I think that's it. I think that's our last one unless unless we got new ones. We did we just got one a minute ago
You serious? Oh, it's an amateur
Yeah
One minute. Holy fucking shit. What literally a minute ago
So, I mean, yeah
It's sparkling sparkling water here. It's literally right there. It's literally
That's what he bear wobbly at
Oh, you know what I was saying
It's literally I could just grab it
But you're you're happily striding the other direction
There's water on the sweaty ass. Yeah, that's sweat drink the sweat from the ass. So I mean, it's not like there's no argument for the ass
but um
It's sparkling
Yeah, but what flavor though if it's if it's
If it's cran raspberry, uh, if it's if it's tropical, I would if it's tropical. I would probably go for it
Or your strawberry kiwi
That that does that does tip the balance a little bit
Okay
Well, that was the last one. Yeah
All right, how do we feel how do how do we feel after navigate?
Navigating that gauntlet and I feel pretty good. We're almost well with three and a half hours
Pretty good size for an episode
Uh, hey, you know what you know what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna put a link in the description
I'm gonna link the
Minecraft
PCP
Uh
Minecraft
Yeah, because I said last time
That the server is free and open now and that's true
And I think the problem is just that maybe people don't know how to get to it because a couple people have asked me like
How do I get into the server?
So I'll just put a link in the description to like click that and it will join you to the
mind the pcb Minecraft server
And I think you will have access once you're in there, but if not, I'm sure maren can just give you the role
Because because to get it you have to get in there and you have there's a whole there's like a document
There's posts that explain how you install it
uh, and then
You know, that's the the hard part
so, uh
Just in case anyone wants that wants to get jump into the pcb server, which is free now
Belongs to the people. Yes. Um, I will link it. I will link that in the description
for you
Uh, just to try and make it easier because I think some people were
Confused a bit by how how it how did how do you get it?
um
I think that's it. Yeah, I think that's everything. All right happy new year and uh
Happy new year. Merry christmas. We missed christmas. We did say christmas. Oh, no. Yeah, we we didn't make an episode for christmas
But yeah, right we mentioned at the beginning
Uh, that's it happy good time for me time to to go
Work time for me to get start my fucking grind for me to start my fucking grind and finish this book and get my fucking internet fix
And start streaming these are the things that I must do resolve very soon very soon
Hopefully there will be progress made on them by the time this episode comes out because I cannot fucking stand
I cannot stand
My situation I must I must finish my projects and accrue more capital
With which to destroy my enemies and defend myself from attack
The attacks are coming. They're coming from all sides and I need
armor
I need capital to armor me against blows
blows for my enemies
Do you understand? I understand. Do you understand what I'm saying?
Okay, all right. I'm sorry
Are we done? Are we ending? We're done. Okay. Thank you for listening pay become a patron somewhere
Go to patreon and search for us. I'm sure we're you'll find us somehow. Okay. Bye. Bye drone in the description
No, yeah, you can check the description also. Okay. Bye