Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best guy ever and today we've got Hippocrit.
I've got the Oscar fever. Hope you got it too.
Got Tom Oliver.
My brain is full of blood and all I do is suck blood.
Get that blood out of there, Ben Saint.
Get that brain out of here. That's so fucking nasty, man. That's so fucking nasty.
Munchy is present.
Hi guys. Hope you're ready for some comedy gold on this podcast where I'll be exclusively quoting The Loco Bandito by Mike Matei.
That's a rich bounty there.
Holy shit, says The Loco Bandito.
And of course, Endless Jess is here.
Bitch, me, I'm laying on my bed like a teen girl in a sleepover. I'm gonna lay down on my tummy with my feet in the air.
Nice.
Is that what sleepovers like? I never went to one.
I always wanted to go to a little girl's sleepover at a little, little bed, little teeny-bopper bitch.
You've been to a homoerotic male sleepover though, surely, correct?
I mean, of course. I mean, I invented the homoerotic male sleepover.
I mean, I grew up straight.
I had a pretty homoerotic male sleepover, but with one guy and he just slept in my bed.
But with his feet near my head and my head near his feet.
Oh, so you didn't know the position, right?
We were like ten. We didn't even understand what was weird about it.
We had lab dicks back then.
I got a funny story. I got a funny story that happened just yesterday, so I'm hanging out with a couple of friends.
I'm not gonna say what their names were to protect the innocent.
It's friend A and friend B.
You've never been this cautious before in your entire life.
And for the story, you said they're like their full name.
Well, I don't know. There's a mild chance that one of these three people might actually hear the show, so that would be embarrassing.
But it was really funny because there's friend A, friend B, and they have a mutual friend, friend C, who's not there.
Friend B is like, hey, A.
So yeah, you know, friend C, yeah.
It was really obvious when I met him that he was like into me in like a gay way.
And friend A is like a ghast.
He's like, no, dude, no.
Friend C is absolutely not gay.
He's like my best friend.
He's totally not gay. That's totally impossible.
I mean, look, I know he's fucked around with it.
Shut up.
Like, I know he's like, I know he's fucked some guys before, right?
But it's always been in like a straight way, right?
Like, it's always, this is not a joke.
He literally said like, I know he's fucked guys, but not, but in like a whole heterosexual way.
This gets down to the fundamental.
I believe that there is a heterosexual way to fuck a man.
There's not.
You and fucking friend A.
Get the fuck out of here.
Listen, I doubt that's what happened in this situation.
Here's a real situation.
You're at a glory hole.
You get your dick sucked.
Turns out it was a guy.
That was a sexual encounter.
Okay, well that's not gay.
Your intention doesn't matter.
No, no, intention is everything.
Of course intention matters.
Yeah, intention matters.
But no, no, that was a gay act, but you were not being gay.
Munchy, you're insane.
Of course intent matters.
There is a distinction between, like, I had this argue with Michelle just the other day.
It's that the act itself, you could call gay sex between two men,
but the, like, to call the individual gay depends on their intention, I would say.
If someone has fucked dudes multiple times though,
you only get so many get out of jail free cards in my thoughts.
Well, at a certain point you can doubt,
if they claim that every time was an accident,
then like, if that's true, then I suppose that's fair.
But one can doubt the credulity of these claims.
Alright, I have a strong opinion about all this talk of is it gay or not.
All sex is just like rubbing meat parts together.
It's all fucking gay.
It's all the same shit.
Fucking a woman is the same thing as fucking a guy.
I'm saying it.
Well, it depends how much you care about gender and sex, I suppose.
Well, you're just slamming into each other.
You're just slamming into each other in some various, like, you know, twisted pretzels sort of way.
And like, ultimately, you're just feeling like the hot, sweaty meat action with, like, that's what sex is.
I mean, you're just throwing out the whole question of is it gay or not.
You're saying that it doesn't matter.
You're basically just dispensing with the whole proposition of gayness to begin with.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
I gotta cover my angles.
Hippo has answered the GQ.
Yeah, that's long last.
We've been searching for it.
And I realized that it's pretty much the same question.
Remember when we were arguing about, like, the sort of, like, the trans-bathroom debate?
And then Digi's like, why even have separate bathrooms at all?
And I was like, that actually makes sense.
That seems like the way to go.
I don't want poop where a girl can hear me.
Well, that's, you know, not to make it an issue, but I actually did hear recently that, like,
the thing about that is that sexual assaults have actually gone up in, like, non-
or, you know, like, group gender areas where they just say everybody goes to the same bathroom.
But you know what?
I don't know.
Maybe it's an imperfect answer.
I mean, that's probably true to some extent.
I just feel like the whole, like, I don't want to poop near a girl.
I mean, just because I poop away from a girl doesn't mean that that girl will like me.
Well, no.
That's not what it's about.
I just don't want to do it.
I mean, there's nothing more to it.
Perhaps if one dug deep down into the motivation behind that feeling,
you'd find that it's, you know, kind of centered in these, I don't know,
attraction dynamics of gender associations.
Yeah, or we could just accept that I just don't want to do it.
But I'm going to take it a step further and I don't want to poop anywhere that anyone can hear me.
I don't want to be near anyone's vicinity at all.
That too.
But it would be way worse if it was a girl.
Let's just, let's just, let's just rip that band-aid off right now.
Good ol' Ben, the binary.
Good ol' Ben, cisgender, cisgender's only please.
That was in quotes.
That's my middle nickname, Saint.
Hey, speaking of Ben and genitals, I heard about a phenomenon recently
that I'm wondering if you have any experience with Ben.
It is the phenomenon known only as Keto, it's known as Keto crotch.
This is the name of the phenomenon.
Well, well, Nate, describe it to me and I will tell you if it speaks to my life experience.
Certainly.
So it, it's a phenomenon where the keto diet supposedly has a,
a onerous effect on the smell of women's crotches.
Well then why the fuck would I have any experience with?
I'm wondering if perhaps there's some overlap with the male experience.
I mean, we all know that Ben's odiferous lifestyle is a thing of legend.
Odiferous lifestyle.
You know, it's, now of course that was established long ago,
but perhaps there's been some change.
Perhaps it's had some kind of total change.
Are you saying like Ben probably smells like a woman now?
What do you say?
Totally over, totally overblown.
Everyone agrees.
A few, everyone took like the one time that I was at Digi's house for three days
and didn't get so naive.
And wasn't, and wasn't there and didn't have my own deodorant and yeah,
didn't shower cause I was over someone else's house.
Yeah.
And so I smelled kind of bad and everyone's like, uh-huh, Ben smells so bad.
Well, you know, fuck you.
Okay.
That, that was like a one, that was like a, that was like a specific incident.
It's just that Ben, in my opinion,
I would say every time we have met over the last several years,
were those all outliers?
Cause I would say that pretty much all of those times.
If you're telling me that I smelled weird every single time we've met over the last several years,
then I'm just going to call you a liar right to your face.
That could be an exaggeration, but that, that's my general impression.
Perhaps that's, you know, not specifically correct every single instance.
It's not.
It's not correct.
There you go.
But, but I mean, don't you think the fact that I have an impression says something about the situation?
No, Nate, I think you're dumb.
And I think, and honest, I, Nate, I literally, I know this is going to be really insulting to you.
And I think honestly that the fact that it happened like the last time has like colored your, your perception.
But I was saying it before that dammit.
I was saying it long before that.
I think it's also, um, that it's funny to say it, and that's what you want to believe.
Well, there's that.
Yeah.
It's true.
This could be a biased position, but.
Nate, you're like the, you're one of like two people that say it.
And the other one is your girlfriend.
And I think, and I think the two of you just think it's funny.
Honestly, I think that's it.
Yeah.
We plot.
Um, she is sensitive to smell though.
So I mean, you know, sure.
She's got quite the nose.
Well, Jesse, were you, were you commenting on this?
Oh, I just feel celebratory like any time that anyone is told that they smell and it's not me.
That's understandable.
Smelling bad is like my worst fear in life.
It's the worst thing that can happen to a person.
I'm so mad at the foot that this episode got off to.
Honestly.
Well, that's unfortunate.
It's the worst thing in the world.
Listen, my, my, my disappointment is immeasurable and my day is ruined.
That's all I have to say.
When you're sorry, Jesse, when you're in your house and you're not planning on guests and
you're in your own funk and you're in your own smells and you're enjoying it, you're
just living your smelly life as a smelly person alone and everything's fine.
You know, and then someone just barges in and says, Hey, it's me.
You're fucking friends and let's take you someplace out in public right now.
It's like, no, I smell bad.
Go away.
But they don't listen.
You know, they take you out.
They just, they just barge in.
They throw you in a car and kidnap you and you've been sitting there.
You haven't showered in like three weeks as you didn't want to see anybody.
You didn't, you just wanted to be home and be smelly and be in peace.
Just, but no one.
So they take, you know, and then, and then it's all like, Oh man, this guy fucking smells
like, yeah, I was happily smelling bad alone.
And then you took me out to a place where people will notice it.
You scum for, you know, for, forget gender.
I would say that scent is in fact a social construct that we are being held to a
standard that there is no, it's all society that imposes this need to smell
decently or even look decent.
When I'm alone and there's no one around to judge me.
I love smelling bad.
It's really cool.
Yes.
The same.
There's a certain pleasure.
All right.
Maybe I'm crazy.
There's a certain pleasure in hot boxing and your own farts in a small room.
Am I right?
Ladies and gentlemen, I feel so much better about myself.
I'll beg you.
The Nate facade is beginning to crack and it rode away and realizing that he's just
as degenerate as the rest of us.
I'm able to put on a social veneer when I leave.
So that's the difference.
This is what happens when you don't have a job.
You go from Nate to us.
The mask gets crumbled.
Fair.
I can't shower for even like three days.
I get dandruff and that just ruins my life.
I just get dandruff and I get greasy.
And so if I do that, then my life will just be ruined.
It's not even like a like, I can just like not do any, like do no hygiene thing into my
life will be fine.
It just actually makes me feel like I am a gross potato.
Yeah.
I'm the same way.
I got like a, I got a three day window tops for him just like, nah, this is just untenable
even for me at this point.
Yeah.
If there was like a comfortable way to wash your hair without getting the rest of you wet,
I would like never shower again.
Cause that's all I really care about is make sure my hair stays.
It's true.
There's no way to do it.
You can't like, you can't like pull up a chair and like lean over the sink like you're
in a salon.
Like that's gay.
It's not straight.
I hate to bring up a, I hate to bring up a topic from last week, but, but this, you're
almost making a case for baldness right now.
Oh crap.
I am.
I take it all back.
Let's all just shave our heads for next episode.
Let's all just embrace it.
Yeah.
We'll be clean shaven.
You know, when you get your hair cut and you ask them to wash your hair and they like
they'd lean you back and that like sink thing and they wash their hair for you.
I want, I want, I want a butler just so you knew that every day of my life.
Yeah.
I really liked that.
I haven't done it too many times, but it's good.
The one time I did have it was like, um, you remember when I had like hair or like really
big fat, like too long, like Jesus times two sort of hair and a really big beard.
It was like uni days where I was like, I don't know what a haircut is.
I don't know how to go to a haircut.
Um, yeah.
University days.
You know, what are they?
No, no, no.
I know.
I say uni over in the brick bar.
I'm just saying, uh, not days is in days, but as in days, like, where am I?
Oh, yeah.
Just stay between college and university period.
I think college implies that it's cool.
Well, in America, I think you can, they grant doctorates, universities grant doctorates,
I think.
Uh, is that a different distinction?
There's a slight difference.
There's some overlap in what you can get on as masters, whatever.
That's not the point.
You know, it's like a better though, right?
In general, the point is I had big hair and I went to like my mom said, you just gotta
go to a fucking salon or something.
And I'm like, oh, okay.
I went to a thing.
There was this old guy who was into Led Zeppelin.
So I could actually talk to him about something for once and he was like, oh my God, you got
too much hair.
We're going to have to take it off like in parts.
We're going to have to amputate.
We're going to have to take this off in parts so that you don't like overcompensate like
your neck movements.
It's going to be like a tattoo.
It's going to do it like a tattoo, like you got to come in for multiple visits.
Yeah.
It's just like he did it slowly.
And I assume he's felt this before when if you take like so much weight off of your head,
you'll feel dazed and smash your head into the wall or something stupid.
But he was really, he was really good at doing the salon stuff.
And there was so much hair.
It almost couldn't fit in the sink.
But it was really nice.
Dude, isn't it the fucking coolest shit when you go, especially, oh dude, I don't know.
I don't know if any of you know this.
I don't know if I was seen with any of you like in real life during this time.
There was a brief period of time where I had hair down to like below my shoulders, like
below like, like the bottom of my shoulders.
It was really, really long.
And you think a munchie.
You think like, oh, you know, it's got like Steven Universe kind of poofy hair.
When you have ethnic wavy hair and it's long, there's no poof.
It just is straight fucking like nightmare fuel.
It's straight like the worst.
Okay.
If I could give any advice to children, it's cut your hair.
If there's like a psychological, like you, you create a real ATV field when you have long hair.
And you just think, you can hide behind your hair and it won't even matter.
You know, I'm a kid, but I'm so cool.
I think he means an ATV field.
Yeah.
An ATV field.
It's an altering vehicle field.
Yeah.
You can go anywhere.
Dude, you can go anywhere.
Finally.
You have no hubris.
You have no humility, I mean.
So it's, it's, it's not a good thing.
So anyway, I had that and I went in for a haircut one fateful day.
And the amount of hair that was on a, just on the ground, the corpse of my, my hair.
And I was down to a small haircut.
It was a, it was, I can make like an entire wig out of it.
I can make maybe two wigs out of it.
It was copious maths.
Hey, cool.
I just want to say, incidentally, I'm posting a link in the, in the audio links chat.
I just want to point out, I was just brought this meal by Michelle that is a poke bowl,
which is like cut up fish with like this weird concoction of sauce on brown rice
and a filleted fish.
And it's just stupendous.
And it's before me right now.
I'm going to be eating it.
You think I don't know.
You're like shit.
I don't know about poke.
I know about poke.
I don't know.
It's some island shit, Michelle.
I thought you, I thought you were talking about like a Pokemon themed food.
Like a poke bowl.
It's made of magic harps and rice chan.
That's my favorite Pokemon.
That's the result of all the magic harp jump.
You have to train the perfect magic harp and it's ripe.
Every, every, every time you, every time you're, you're loses.
Every time you take a magic harp to the championship league and it loses,
you cut it up into a poke bowl and then you feed it to your next one for a little experience.
You induce, you induce the stress by torturing it.
And if it survives, that's how do you get a Gyarados?
All the ones that die become your food.
Hey, incidentally, like a few minutes ago, somebody mentioned butlers.
I was just thinking about this today.
Here's a real question.
Life sucks because what the hell happened to like having servants?
You could be like middle class and have a servant back in the good old 1800s or whatever it was.
What happened to that?
Why don't we have slavery mate?
No, it's literally not slavery.
I'm talking about like New England servants in like...
It's that, it's that god damn, it's the god damn politicians and their god damn raise in the minimum wage agenda.
I think it might be something like this.
Yeah, basically.
I'd be happy to pay a minimum wage for a servant, but I don't think that like exists.
Well, Nate, you can have like a person to come clean your house for like, you don't need to be fabulously wealthy to have someone do that.
I want a live-in Alfred style butler who's fiercely loyal and will keep my secrets and sit brave with me while we conspire.
That's expensive.
Nate, I think you've stumbled upon a new market.
Hear me out here.
Uber for servants.
Ew, I don't want a gross millennial butler.
They will fuck everything up.
I want an old English gentleman who, you know, fought in World War II and was a fighter pilot.
You don't want one of these kids doing the shig economy.
Butlers are, butlers are men.
You want a maid with a nice booty.
Yeah, completely grits, Jesse.
And sexual fighters are definitely men.
Well, okay, never mind.
That's definitely true.
Cassie's dad has a maid for his apartment.
Okay, there.
And it is like, from what I can understand, it's like the greatest investment that you can have just to not have your house dirty.
And because he cooks a lot, his kitchen's completely fucked 100% of the time.
Because he's making really complex shit and just every pot and pan is all over the floor.
So she takes care of it then?
Yeah, she takes care of it.
Just like all the bodies and all the people you guys are to kill.
I don't even need this now.
I want this like in 10 years.
So I want to prepare the market so I'm ready by the time I actually need a maid.
It's moments like this when you realize just like you're not living real life, you know, like, like peasant life is just so far beneath what could be.
I don't know, man.
They're pretty luxurious.
It's literally just like, I don't want to clean myself.
Please do it for me.
Right.
There are people who just like they don't drive.
They don't clean.
Like all these like grindy aspects of life are just so unknown to them.
It seems to me like like the bar has shifted.
Like obviously somebody like, I'm sure Jeff Bezos has people who like, you know, clean his house or whatever.
So obviously that's the number one guy in the world.
But like, didn't there used to be like a middle class equivalent?
And sure, we've got this literal gig economy made thing.
But like the classical person is really just a case of like the population of the middle class has just increased.
Like middle class used to be more, more rare than it.
Yeah, I think it's just at some point.
Yeah, at some point, like what was considered middle class, like what was considered normal was like, you know, we probably think maybe we like shrink that wealth gap a little bit.
But good, but good news.
Good news.
The wealth gap is widening again.
So soon we'll have soon we'll have a big old underclass that can be the upper class.
You know, there's been because I was actually thinking about that.
And I was, I heard that, you know, the wealth gap is the widest it's ever been.
Does that mean that?
Okay.
I don't know about the widest it's ever been.
But it's okay.
But it's widening.
I mean, you know, considering exactly how rich Bezos may be, it could well be.
I mean, he, you know, it's such ridiculous wealth that guy has compared to other people.
Okay.
Anyway, by pointing to the issue is that the people at the bottom are being a condensed group.
So that group doesn't have enough play between the top and the bottom to get that kind of made servant culture thing going on.
Because the top people, of course, can afford this kind of a thing.
But it's not like wide.
Okay.
You know what?
Never mind.
No, I think like, imagine like the middle class that like, if we're in that bracket, like the jobs we could do, we wouldn't become butlers for the super
rich above us.
But we totally could.
And then we would get to be like hanging out in a really cool house a lot of the time.
All that we would need to do is clean up.
I was a tour guide in some of the Newport mansions, which are some of the craziest, like, they're like America royalty mansions, basically.
Some of the biggest spildons in America.
It's always been interesting to me the idea that, you know, the Butler is like a lower class person doing a job and stuff.
But they get to live and work in a really, really upper class amazing place.
Yeah.
And if they have a nice like employer, then it seems pretty cool and pretty great in every aspect.
It could be worse for sure.
I guess it's almost reminds me like the house Negro versus the field Negro and how the house one would often be fiercely loyal to Massa.
Because, you know, to protect his privileged position relative to the others, despite being a literal slave.
As made famous by Django Unchained and nothing else.
I'm not sure what to make of this conversation.
I can't tell.
Like, are you like, are you like, I can't tell if you guys are talking, are you talking about this is a good thing or a bad thing?
I mean, I wasn't thinking of slavery, but now I am.
I mean, no, no, we're not.
We're that's a whole other ball game.
I mean, obviously we're all for that.
But I mean, I suppose thinking backwards, if the reason for this situation, me decrying the fact that I can't easily acquire a butler is due to a fact that the middle class has condensed and possibly like lowered relative to total wealth of the population.
That I suppose that is a bad thing.
No, no, here's what I think.
It's not that you at your current wealth level can't acquire a butler anymore, whereas maybe in the past you could have.
In the past, in those times, you would have just been poor and someone else would have been richer and maybe they would have hired you as a butler.
Why? What do you mean?
Because I would have been like, I'm not a noble or something.
You're not you're not high enough on you're not high enough on the food chain to like if the wealth gap were to widen to the point where like servants were a thing we're seen as common for like quote unquote the middle class.
Or the average family.
You're not high enough on the totem pole that you'd be above the gap if it were to open again.
If we just take it back.
If that if that if that gap were to open that you would fall right into that chasm.
Okay, but our dad like is a doctor when I think about like doctors in the olden days.
And again, maybe they're like he wouldn't have made it because doctors are not would never like rich people.
The richest people in all this businessmen to get a servant of some kind in like I don't agree with that.
I don't think so.
I think there were all like entrepreneurs and businessmen and people who were born into families who had that stuff already.
This is a lot of talking out of our ass.
I mean, have you been on this podcast before?
Munchie research informed statements.
No, no, no, no.
I want to distribute my my energy on the most efficient things possible and like do in my dishes feels like a waste of time.
I would be happy to pay someone to do that so I could spend that time doing other stuff and that's.
You can buy a dishwasher.
I'm pretty sure.
Nate, I'm pretty sure.
I mean, like.
I mean, there were times like lazy, but I just want to do more work is the thing.
So, you know, there were there were times when our dad like would hire like a maid or something to come not on like a regular base.
But like to just come and like clean the house or whatever.
And and I mean, I mean, they my point is those things do exist.
Those jobs do exist and people do.
Of course they just seems like for the for the yes, but I want like a regular person who's there every day to do the cooking and cleaning that and I will be happy to pay.
Well, that just well, that just seems inefficient because they're not going to.
They're not going to have to do a full house clean every single day.
You don't even need to pay for that.
That's called a wife that knows her place.
Well, that's fair.
But like here's but I don't believe it's tough to control a wife.
It's much easier to control an employee.
So I'm happy to just use that mechanism.
You're just you're just not malicious enough to get the control.
That's possible.
Why control with your wallet when you control with fear?
Fair, fair.
Ben, I know I know this episode start.
Oh, you want to finish this conversation?
I just going to say, yeah, you want someone to do your dishes.
You can hire someone to do your dishes.
Wait, have a son.
Have a son.
I guess that's the way to do it.
I think unironically having children seems like the American way.
You can never have a son.
In time.
Well, it never works for our dad.
We never did our fucking dishes.
He will use dishes and he will not wash them up and then you'll have to wash them.
Well, that's unfortunate too, I guess.
Okay.
Ben, you didn't like the way this podcast started out, but I've got a segue for you.
Free of charge, although you do owe me interest.
I heard that you ripped me off and I heard that you followed my footsteps
trying to eat some of the same glory that I achieved in the procrastiners' pockets
and you went to a political rally.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
I did.
Yeah, I went to a Yang rally.
That's boyish.
Yeah.
You know, a lot happened this week, like way more than usually happens in a week for me.
So like, I'm like forgetting some details, but yeah, I went to a Yang rally.
Thursday, I think.
And I just barely missed the chance to get a photo with the guy.
I'm so pissed because I didn't think he was doing that.
I didn't think I could shake hands and take a photo with him and I really had to pee,
so I went to go find a bathroom and I came back and I saw,
no, he was fucking taking photos with people and shaking their hands.
Not wearing a diaper to the rally.
So I got in line, but it was too late.
It was too fucking late.
He was sick of us, I know.
Ben, Ben, did you see the article that I tweeted like two days ago?
The hologram.
Yes.
How he wants to have used like the hologram technology to have rallies at multiple locations.
Oh, like the Miku technology.
Yeah.
That's pretty funny.
I'm not sure that's real.
Like that he's really going to do that, but it would be really funny if he did.
As long as it was marketed as like, it's not really me guys, it's a hologram.
That sounds great.
That sounds fine.
That's really going to appeal to the Midwestern truckers,
whose jobs he's out to protect.
That's how you get through to those people.
I have to ask you Ben, because I want to know how similar it was to the Bernie rally.
Because Bernie was, there was a lot of build up to Bernie.
There was like hours of just like, you know, people warming us up with the crowd.
And then Bernie came on and he just said,
I'm Bernie Sanders.
Here's what I've said.
Here it is again.
Goodbye America.
And then he left.
How old was Yang?
Did he have any personality?
And then he left America and pledges loyalty to Putin for once and all.
Okay.
So the Yang rally was basically like, I got there a little bit early.
I was just going to hang in it.
We were just going to hang it out around sort of a pagoda munchie.
Actually, do you remember the place in Boston?
Of course.
I know exactly the way.
I saw one, I saw like, like just the zoomed in shot of Yang talking.
I could tell exactly where it was.
I know exactly where.
We made our slime court pact that we've never acknowledged what the logo looks like.
Yeah, that's right.
It's the, yep, that exact one.
He was, he was, well, okay.
So I got there and at some point they like got like a group of like tastefully ethnically
diverse, like you young people to get up there with Yang signs and like sort of stand as
like a backdrop sort of up on the podium, just sort of looking nice.
Was the crowd just a few too many white faces out there to make everybody comfortable?
A lot of Asians actually.
A lot of Asians in whites in Boston.
There was like, the crowd was like almost half Asian, I think.
Yeah, okay.
But anyway.
Is that how I take people to the fast one?
Yeah, yeah, true, but he doesn't push that.
Like he almost like, he almost like deliberately backs off from like that.
Like whenever, when anyone ever asks, when anyone asks him about like, you know, being
an Asian American running for president, he, he, he's like, you know, I'm not really,
you know, like that's not really.
Well, everybody knows the identity politics stack Asians do not fare well because they're
doing so well in America.
So, but okay, fair enough, fair enough.
Yeah, whatever.
But anyway, so he's, so there's a bunch of people up there and then this like young,
it's like maybe like 25.
So like girl is like, she's like, she's like out, she's asking people like, you know,
crowd in around the podium, crowd in around the, the pagoda or whatever, like getting
closer.
And so we do that.
And then we wait a little while and then she gets up there and she's, I don't know,
she's tired.
Oh, there was one like troll guy walking around with a Keckistan flag.
But he didn't.
Yeah, but he didn't do anything.
That was, that was me.
I don't know if I mentioned this, but at the, at the brand rally, there, there were some,
there were some, uh, maybe make America great again, had men.
They were reasonably well behaved or something.
So like, what's their game?
Like, okay, I understand you might want to just be informed or something.
And you want to show up and just hang out and see what the opposition has to say.
But like, then you, then you dress up in the cosplay and I'm like, well, you don't do anything.
I literally heard some people like pointing out the Keckistan flag guy and be, and like
talking about him.
And like they knew who he was.
He like went to their school and he was just like a troll or something.
Apparently he like goes to like left wing shit, uh, around like just to troll people.
So like pretty lame to just like be, uh, the object of like the opposition, but to not
be doing anything.
Just be like, I'm here to remind you.
What should he do?
Firebomb the stage?
No, I mean, it's just people are empty.
That's, people have no souls.
All they want to do is just be a nuisance.
It's the same argument about everybody going to support Yang.
They're just going like the hell.
I was annoyed when I saw him, but he didn't do anything.
So in the end I was like, well, whatever.
It's fine.
What I'm thinking is like, it's equivalent to like putting on a specific like anime or
like pop culture t-shirt and walking around and hoping somebody will talk about it.
Okay.
The thing is though, that literally defines my entire adult life.
I get that they like people do these kinds of things because they think that they're
trolling, but it's like if you're just going to a place where you know you're not wanted
and dressing in the cosplay specifically just to make people mad at you, then you're not
really trolling.
You're just a faggot.
Well, you know what it was.
The reason he did it, the reason he did it is because of any kind.
You're totally inside.
Sure.
Because those guys knew who he was, right?
They're like, oh, it's that guy.
It's that guy who shows up to the damn rallies with the Kekistan flag.
So like, you know, yeah, yeah, it was, you know, I've got a reputation now.
He's that guy.
Everyone knows him as that guy.
Everyone knows him as having like a reputation of like, oh, that famous guy who, you know,
doesn't-
Oh, yeah.
Everyone knows that guy.
The Kekistan guy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We all sure hate that guy.
We all sure hate that guy, but damn if we don't respect that guy.
The way to steal that, the most charitable interpretation is maybe he is here to like,
literally in his own way, politically advocate for whatever he, you know, the, I don't know,
the left or something.
I don't know.
I guess maybe, you know, I don't, I mean, it's fine.
I'm sure that's fine.
Either way, it's fine.
It's all fine.
Yeah, okay.
It's all good.
There's a guy.
Maybe they'll see the Kekistan flag.
Maybe they'll realize that their policies are stupid.
Maybe if they see this funny meme, then they'll not see it.
They'll not see it.
You could argue that about every individual action anyone takes in a political space.
So, you know.
But it's about the...
So, the way that, the way the rally went, right?
Like that, that like young woman talked for a little while.
She just, I don't even remember what she said.
It was like inconsequential.
She was like sort of hyping the crowd up a little bit.
Then like this, I'll just, I'm just going to say it.
I'm just going to say the F word.
Fat woman.
This fat woman.
This, this, this.
She came up on the podium and she...
She's still fat, Ben.
She's still fat.
Okay, whatever.
She, whatever.
She was like, she runs like the local like Yang gang, like, like chapter meetups or something.
And she was like, she's, you know, she sort of introduced that and her organization.
Oh, and they were hyping up them.
They were hyping up that Yang was going to be on like a CNN thing.
Like right before Game of Thrones.
So, they were...
We're just tonight, by the way.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Well, so, okay.
Then maybe before Game of Thrones, tune in an hour early and see Yang on CNN or something.
Tune in like five days ago.
They were, they were pushing, they were pushing a thing like, like share the Yang CNN thing
and like organize Game of Thrones watch parties, but like start them an hour early and like
get people to like, or like have a, have a sort of a combined, have a Yang little like
Yang viewing, combine it with your game.
Combine it with your Game of Thrones.
Gang of Thrones.
And then, and then hashtag it, tweet about it, you know, invite everyone.
You know, that, that was so part of how they were promoting it.
Is, is being, is being a fat woman and being in political like actions like that.
Is that the left-wing equivalent of running around with the Kekestan flag?
Like, it seems like the same thing.
To take the most possible interpretation of politically active fat people, they were
not able to master their own like physical self.
And so they're like, ah, we'll fix society, that will fix my life for me.
You could say that about anything a fat person does.
Totally uncharitable, totally unfair.
Very mean.
It was, it was all for the games.
But, but anyway, so she talked and then she introduced some guy who I had never heard of,
but who was a business guy, question mark, question mark.
Donald Trump?
Don't know that guy.
He like, he, he had like known Yang for a while and he got up there and he was like,
yeah, we met at a wedding, a mutual friend a while ago.
He got married.
He told me he was running for president and I said, you're crazy man, better you than
me.
Haha, that's my anecdote.
All right.
Anyway, give it up for Andrew Yang.
What is this shit?
And Andrew Yang comes out.
Hey, so I know Andrew Yang.
He says he's running for president.
You know, that's cool.
Anyway, see you later guys.
Nice to see you.
Follow me on Instagram.
So, so, so here's Andrew and then it was really funny.
Yang comes out and he is sort of like, he sort of has maybe a little bit of like a rockstar
affectation about him.
I know.
I saw a clip.
He's like, okay, Bernie's behind a podium pound, pounding the podium, acting like a politician
and then Yang's like destroying podiums that bring out new podiums one after another.
Yeah, exactly.
Yang like jumps out.
He's where he like kind of runs out on those.
He's like, hey, and he's wearing like this big like American flag like scarf around his
neck and it's sort of hanging and it's like, you know, it's, it's, it's kind of, it's
a little bit cool.
Open mic night.
It was really weird.
He has, he's okay.
I mean, he mostly just sort of repeated his normal talking points.
So yeah, like he didn't say anything new, but like he, he, he, I mean, he wasn't all
stuff I heard before.
Like he did a bunch of like, I mean, I can't.
I mean, I can't remember him on the spot.
He's basically a single issue guy.
So like it's fair.
Well, not, not, not really actually.
I mean, he's got the, he didn't, he actually didn't emphasize the UBI that much.
Like he, he mentioned it sort of in passing, but like that wasn't like his focus, his focus
on like, you know, technology and, and fucking, you know, job security and speaking to the
Asian crowd.
So he knows they're fine for money.
Don't need to emphasize.
He talked about, you know, like student loan forgiveness and Medicare for all, Medicare
for all.
And you know, he mentioned the UBI, but it wasn't like the thing he focused on.
And he said shit at one point.
Oh, he dropped, he dropped an S-bow.
Holy.
Uh-huh.
And he was just kind of like jokie and like sort of casual about it.
Did he come off as natural and cool or was he sticking the mud?
He was pretty dumb and drool.
I guess he was pretty natural.
No, no, no.
This is what happened.
He was just hanging around doing this thing, being, being cool.
And then all of a sudden-
He's just being cool.
He pulls out his just being cool.
I was going to say he unbuttons his blazer and under there is his, I'm just being cool
T-shirt.
Be like Yang, everyone.
Is that Ben Satan the crowd?
Let's get him up here, ladies and gentlemen.
He's just being cool.
So am I.
By the way, I want to say I was wearing my homemade or my self-made purple like Yang 2020
like, like sunset pattern like T-shirt to the rail.
Yeah.
Right.
And uh, wait there.
Okay.
I, I like him a lot.
I like all his policies, but there are a couple of things that he does that I kind of wish
he wouldn't and kind of wish think are hurting him like he has this line that he says all
the time.
Okay.
First of all, him, him leaning on the math thing, like I don't get the sense that he's
like a real like, okay, he's an entrepreneur and a businessman.
I'm sure he knows math.
I'm sure he's good at math.
But all right, I was, I was talking to some of my other friends were there at the rally
with me and, um, we were talking about it and one of them said like, you know, I get
the feeling like from his college photos that Yang's not like a nerdy Asian.
Like he's like presenting himself that he's more of like a cool Asian who wore like leather
jackets and like looked good and was crazy rich Asian, one of that crap.
And I, and I, it kind of seems like maybe the whole math thing is just sort of playing
into maybe a stereotype that he thinks would play better.
And I don't, I don't, I don't really get the sense that he's as much of a nerd as he's
like making himself out to be.
And the one thing that I wish he would please stop is at the end, like this is sort of his
line.
He says it at the end of everything.
He says the opposite of Donald Trump is an Asian guy who likes math.
And I think that is like the cringiest, stupidest line.
That's really awful.
It's really dumb.
I get it.
I've never heard him say that.
I've watched a couple of things that he's done.
He said, he said it in a couple interviews and he said it at the end of this speech.
And every time he says it, I'm like, please stop leaning on that.
I know it's like, ha, ha.
It's a joke about my ethnicity.
What happened to his other catch for the catch phrase I've heard him say a lot is like, it's
not left or right.
It's forward.
And I thought that was.
Oh, sure.
Well, he, he says that too.
Something that he just said once and then some campaign manager was like, yes, keep
saying that.
Say that over and over again.
People will love it.
Which the Asian thing or the left, right thing?
The Donald.
The Asian thing.
Probably both.
The opposite of Donald Trump.
He plays well with a certain crowd, but I hate that crowd and I don't want to be a part
of it.
Agreed.
You know, again, so not.
I kind of like, I think his whole math thing probably plays well with like a nerdy, like
Reddit, like a self-proclaimed nerdy, like Reddit browsing, like, fuck yeah, science
kind of crowd.
I hate him too.
I will want to say that through watching the bachelor and the bachelor, I've concluded
that every single normal person on earth would describe themselves as a nerd.
I don't know.
Not me.
Deliciously.
I'm post that.
I'm post.
Nerds are cool.
You're an actual nerd.
He's older than you.
Is what I'm saying that normies think being a nerd is like quirky and cute and they'll
describe.
Yeah.
Such given.
Opportunity to do so.
You ask anyone off the street.
They'll say, yeah, I'm a nerd.
I've like read a book.
Yeah.
No, I know.
I know.
I know that you're right.
I am so anti the watering down of the word nerd.
Like nerd.
I agree.
Should be an insult.
It should be an insult.
It should be the worst insult ever.
If I see someone who's just totally socially incompetent, just a slobbering, like more
chins than they have like follicles of hair, fucking, you know, stomping down the boulevard,
you know, a person who's on 4chan all day, you know, who's just shit.
That's a nerd.
You should be able to say, hey, you're a fucking nerd without people co-op.
Yeah.
I'm a nerd because I watch Game of Thrones.
No, you're not.
Yeah, exactly.
You're just normal.
The words are evolving.
They're just changing.
They're shifting under our feet.
Can you believe?
Press B.
Press B to go back.
Oh, man.
Press B to stop the evolution.
You see, you see, dude, I'm so, dude, I'm so hype for a, I'm so hype for Shazam.
Yeah, I'm such a nerd.
Yeah.
That's my whole thing.
That's like my whole thing basically.
I don't want to see that movie.
It looks pretty good.
Hey, so I went, I've done a little further research since we last spoke about Yang and
it was just that all I did, nothing incredible was I watched like the Ben Shapiro versus Yang
debate.
Yeah.
I haven't seen that.
That was, that was, I liked that one in particular because it was definitely adversarial.
And so that was like good to see someone on the opposite side debating him.
Yang came away looking pretty good overall in that.
I think I'd probably like him more than before I watched that.
I agree.
He really does lean into his business side in a way that is comforting for someone like
me who is my alarm bells of just like, oh, we're just trying to like, you know, siphon
money away from people who are, you know, whatever, doing better to people who will
just fuck it up anyway, which I mean, still could happen.
But I don't know.
There's lots of questions about if this would work anyway.
But yeah, I don't know.
So the thing about Yang and really all politicians, and I don't say this to really shit on Yang,
but your, your description of him coming out like a rock star really makes me think about
how like, God, I hate the reality that we have like, it's the cool kids.
It is now officially the cool kids who become our leaders and politicians when God, I yearn
for the Nixon era.
I want a curmudgeonly weird, slobbery old nerd, a fucking weirdo freak asshole.
And sure, maybe Nixon was a bad guy, whatever.
But I want a freak.
Sure, you had some faults.
You know what?
You're over that.
Yeah.
Nate, have you seen that movie?
Oh God, I think it's called Frost Nixon or a little, hold on, hold on, that's the interview.
It's the interview, right?
It's a, it's a, yeah, it's called Frost Nixon and it is a, it's a movie that is like based
on the interviews.
I saw much of it.
Yes.
I watched it.
I think YMS recommended it and that's why I watched it.
Okay.
All I want to say about that is that, yeah, in that movie, they like, like Nixon is a
pretty old man.
Like he's got to be like 60, but like, they pushed the idea that Nixon is like really
sexy.
Like they say he's sexy.
Like, no, like, like, yeah, like, like before, well, it's just funny because like, like he's
still old, but like they, like, I think before Nixon ever, it's like before anyone sees him
before he appears on screen, like the love interests, I remember, she says like a sultry
way.
They're talking about, like, wait, we're gonna be, we're gonna go meet Richard Nixon.
You mean president Richard Nixon?
You know, I hear he has the sexiest voice.
I am not a fucking...
Well, and then in the movie, he is played by someone with like an extremely dulcet,
like baritone.
Well, that's a little odd.
I mean, power is sexy.
But it doesn't, but it doesn't sound completely unlike him.
So like, it doesn't, it sort of works.
They sort of pull it off, but like in hindsight, you're like, boy, that was really weird.
They sold me on this idea that Nixon was like the sexy guy.
And you know what, maybe I'm a little, I didn't live through the Nixon era, obviously, but
like maybe I'm being sold in a completely opposite direction that he is in fact, like
a weird old troll, but that's, that's what I've come to understand.
But my point is like, I want academics and like scientists and like smart people like
that.
It's just that those people are doing things.
I don't think a scientist has ever been the president.
I don't think like, like a real academic has never been the president.
I think like Eisenhower made a lot of sense.
Like World War II, you know, leader or whatever.
And I think he went on to become president.
That seemed like a pretty good choice to me.
That guy knows what's up on like the world stage and whatnot.
This like, I don't know, businessman like Wall Street stuff.
I don't know.
Obama was okay, I guess, is like a pick.
But I don't know.
I want someone who's like a real old fuck.
Who just knows shit.
I want an old, I liked an old fuck for president.
Yeah.
Make that a shirt.
Make that a shirt just like the American flag in the background and like an old 2020
and an old fuck for specifically not one who's been in nothing but Pollock.
I want like a general.
I feel like generals are a good choice.
I don't want a fuck.
I don't want a military guy liked by anyone because as soon as a candidate is like, then
they have a group.
And once they have a group, that's when, you know, groups breed stupidity.
I want a president to get in somehow with no votes.
I want them to just take over.
I want to say, Justin, you seem to be an object of democracy as a group.
I want Ebenezer Scrooge to rise from the grave on a pale horse and take America by force.
Ebenezer.
King George III needs to arise from the grave and be like, look what you fucking retards
did.
It took a while, but the whole system broke down.
You know, the reason why Eisenhower comes to my mind is like a good, it's because like
he was like a World War II general that like everyone in the world is like, oh, those were
the good guys.
But like now what we have is like, I mean, to a degree, it's like, oh, let's go invade
some more Middle Eastern countries to acquire more resources.
I don't want one of those guys.
This is why I'm kind of, I don't know.
You know, I've only seen a little bit of, oh God, is it Kamala Harris?
Yeah.
Kamala Harris, she's a veteran, right?
No, you're thinking of Tulsi Gabbard, I think.
Tulsi Gabbard.
Yeah, Tulsi Gabbard.
Gabbard.
I don't know if it's just that everyone, whatever, I've heard it both ways.
Well, I don't know if it's maybe just that people ask her about her like, like, like
foreign policy opinions more often, so she ends up talking about it.
But every time, every time I hear her talking, she's talking about like some fucking foreign
policy, like military shit and like, I don't care about that.
I don't want to lean into that.
I kind of think maybe we should not have a veteran for president.
But Ben, but Ben.
I don't want a military guy.
I don't want to fucking care about that.
We got to pull out of foreign entanglements, please.
That she wants to do less of it is her whole point.
That's why she's talking about it.
That's like her main.
Is that her main thing?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, I spoke out of turn.
I spoke out of turn and I made an ass of myself.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Well, I want to say Buttigieg is also a veteran, but I've heard him say, like, we need to like,
you know, end foreign entanglements and like do less of that whole like foreign fucking.
Yeah.
I mean, obviously, I think we've most of us are here, but.
Okay.
Nah, I'm for war.
More war, please.
Yes.
The ever popular for war position.
I need four wars per year.
Yeah.
I'm four, four wars.
Four wars.
Year.
You can make like a Japanese haiku that's like, ah, yes, in the fall, I commit, I commit
war in the winter.
I commit second war in the spring.
It is time for more war.
And in the summer, I settle down to yet another war and life goes on.
It's like the hobbit and Lord of the Rings, like, yes, but what about second war?
We defeated so about second war, we need to fight again that literally happens in the
books, too.
After they have second war and they fight Saruman.
That's true.
They just can't get enough of those greedy fucks.
Well, we blend a lot here today.
Did you include everything about the Yang Gang rally, Ben?
Oh, yeah.
Any closing thoughts on that?
Oh, I mean, that was pretty much it.
That was what happened.
That was what the speech was like.
Was it fun?
Did it not make you want to die?
Like how the burning rally made me want to die?
That's a fair question.
No, it was fine.
The only thing that made me want to die is that I missed my chance to get a picture
with them.
Yeah, fair enough.
And you know, I don't know, like, I'm not even with, I don't know, I don't even feel
like I came across particularly anti-Yang here or anything like it's just like political
the political arena is so inherently, I don't know, like it's all it's very unfortunate
that it is like, like it is.
If you know what I mean, ladies, people don't think it'd be like it is, but it do, but it
absolutely do.
And no one can argue that fucking try and prove me wrong.
Stephen Crowder sign.
Some don't think it'd be like it is, but it do change my mind.
Yeah.
Okay.
Anyway, I knew what else is going on ladies and gentlemen.
So yeah, that's it.
Yang Gang, pretty good, better than Bernie, I would say, by a narrow margin, but a narrow
but undeniable margin.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Hey, I went to that.
Oh, well, I can let someone else talk.
I've been going for a while.
I know what you're going to talk about and I do want to circle back to that.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hey, last point on this like, I don't know, political tinged discussion here is I was
Ben, I realized there's one area of this whole communist ideology that you 100% are for and
back.
Yeah, that's right.
And I realized that the prospect that you are always on about about state mandated GFs
and equal distribution of sex.
I'm all for.
Wait, hold on.
And you might say, but how are you going to handle like what about the consent issue
of state mandated GFs?
Well, that's exactly why we need equal distribution of consent as well that I'm all for.
Spread it thin.
So like everyone's sort of okay, you know, you know, in this country, but Ben St. doesn't
consent.
Well, is it not rape?
You know, the gulf, the gulf is white.
The consent gulf is widening in this country, you know, 1% of the people receive 99% of
the consent.
It's not fair.
And what is that?
It's literally true.
Nothing at all.
We have to fix it.
Yeah.
And I mean, you know, when you, when you got your state mandated GF, she'll be thanking
you for impregnating her so that her state imposed explosive collar does not detonate
because it detects the pregnancy.
So really you'll be doing her a favor in the end of the day.
Wow.
You thought of everything.
It's a brave new future that I'm looking forward to.
But that's all.
That's all.
So you got my vote, Yang.
Yeah.
Man, I'm going to vote for him twice now.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, what do you got?
What do you got?
I was going to talk to you about something hippo and you too Nate, because as we, as we
know, something happened yesterday, yesterday, what happened?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, of course.
Now I remember.
Yep.
Okay.
I'm with you.
Oh, yeah.
It's sort of unfortunate that we titled the last episode Homestuck because truly this
is the Homestuck episode because the first Homestuck epilogue came out.
Now I was a vocal.
I did not think this would happen on 4.30.
I did not think that it would ever happen if I'm honest with you.
I gave up.
But it did.
The first thing came out and we have some thoughts on it.
Wait.
It's the 10-year anniversary of Homestuck.
Yeah.
4.13 yesterday was 10 years from the release date.
Wait.
And what happened?
Basically nothing.
Basically.
All right.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Yeah.
Well, I'm just going to tune out for this part then.
It was the beginning of a series of epilogues to Homestuck, the prologue of the epilogues.
And by the way, it's only written word, no images.
Yeah.
Written word.
It's a sort of like written as if it were a fanfic about Homestuck but written by Andrew
Hussey and two other people, one of which is also an actual like Homestuck fanfic guy.
I learned.
So he teamed up with a Homestuck fanfic guy and someone else to write a post-canon but
still actually canon epilogue to Homestuck.
And it details a little bit of information about like John and Rose talking about John
doing a thing that happens in the comic that we didn't get to see in detail before.
So you know, it was an interesting like jokey sort of, what's the word, display, like in
the form of a fanfiction, having all this stuff, he had a whole like first page with
a bunch of like tags, like Archive of our Own, which was a nice touch.
Yeah.
And I read it and I kind of liked it, but a lot of people are just mad because it's they
hate Homestuck now.
That's me, baby.
Right over here.
It is exactly what it may sound like and that's weird, flowery fanfic tier writing.
Absolutely.
But it's on purpose.
It's a big brain intellectual that's like, well, you're the idiot for not getting it.
I mean, it wasn't like written as if it was a bad fanfic.
Like it's still like competent.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
They're trying to like, I don't think, okay, it only comes across in the, in like the format
of it where there's pros and then there's dialogue sections and, you know, obviously
the whole like aesthetic way it's presented.
But I don't know.
I don't really get the sense they're trying to make it like a fanfiction, though I guess
I could be wrong in the sense of like writing because it doesn't, they don't lean into it.
I wouldn't say it.
I think you just presented it that way.
What do you mean they?
Wasn't it written by Andrew Hussey?
No.
I said two people.
Andrew Hussey and two other people.
Oh God.
See, this is what I hate about Homestuck because it's not written by Hussey anymore.
Well, the parts he did write are like maybe the worst parts of it possibly.
He wrote the title.
Wait.
You know what?
I think Homestuck's dead.
I actually don't know who reward I assume he wrote the title.
I said, you know what?
I think Homestuck's dead to me.
I mean, that's how it feels.
I mean, I was, I was thinking about like how this feels like I would be mad if I thought
Homestuck was still alive, but it feels more like an autopsy, but not even like in a bad
way.
I'm just interested to see what, what comes from this.
That's, that's fair.
I wasn't really, I wasn't really waiting for the epilogue.
I wasn't really like, oh, I really want the epilogue.
It will fix everything.
I'm just like, well, now it's here and I'm reading it and it's like, yeah, all right.
People who say like they were waiting for the epilogue to fix things have a completely
like a different understanding of what made Homestuck bad than I do.
There's nothing to fix.
I don't give a shit if you like, oh, they go by and they'll go, they go back and fight
Lord English, which is what's happening in this epilogue, like, like we have, like we
just literally see the fight.
Oh, don't, Homestuck's fixed now.
That's completely separate from the issues.
You can't like, the only way to fix Homestuck is to literally just rewrite it.
I don't care the structural plot.
I care at the moment to moment dialogue that just tanked and went to shit and is still
bad now.
That's fair.
I mean, so there's a lot of meta things going on with it that I don't even hate it.
It just was boring to me.
This epilogue, like, it does not enrage me in the same way an axis thing was where I
feel like I'm just completely wasting my time.
It's so short and just boring.
It's just boring and I don't, I don't care.
And I wasn't expecting the same way.
It doesn't matter.
I give it a little more criticism specifically because what is attempted, like, okay, there
are specific, in the dialogue, they talk about like, okay, the first thing is when John talks
to Rose, I guess spoilers, go read it's like three, it's several pages long or whatever.
It's like three pages.
It's nothing.
But they're really long pages.
But whatever, take a couple minutes.
Like, so when, when John talks to Rose, they are discussing like how there's a danger happening
and the way that it's introduced is like in the lore of this new Homestuck epilogue thing.
They're like, we exist outside of cannon out.
That's what the character say.
This is a real tangible concept.
We are outside cannon, which you can think of as the story of Homestuck.
That was a thing released on this website.
They are outside that now it's a, it's a joke.
It's like real to them, whatever.
They're talking about John needs to go back and go in there and several things are discussed.
One is that like the danger they face now is that their current existence faces the danger
of like, they say, I forget the exact words they use, but like fading from effectively
relevance, which I understand we talked about this to me and Gabe.
I get the idea that it's that, that the audience will stop caring and that we won't think
about them.
And so like they won't exist to us.
This is the meta point being made that like, oh no, if we don't make more Homestuck content,
we will be forgotten about.
We like extended universe.
I don't know whether that was, I don't know whether that was literally the point.
Oh, that was absolutely intentional.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
Well, that, that wasn't, I guess, an intentional, I don't, hmm, I'm not sure that was like the
message they were trying to get across with that.
I think it was just sort of like, in an epilogue, the idea that if these characters who are
in an epilogue, which is not part of the story, and, and John has retcom powers, and is like
shown to go in back into the comic after he completes it to do something, then like, what
would the character, why would he do that?
Why would the characters, like these characters who are no longer part of the comic, who are,
you know, effectively happy and fine, and nothing will, you know, bother them.
It was like an exploration of what if the characters in the epilogue knew that they were
not part of the story anymore, and I was just sort of like a thing.
I mean, that's exactly right.
But Hussie has chosen to make it a thing for these new characters that, I mean, we know
as readers that these are the same character.
This is canon in real life to us.
He has chosen to make it a problem for us by continuing the story that we, the audience,
will forget about them.
That is the problem they made into a tangible danger for the characters.
That's the way it was described.
It's definitely intentional.
I can't, I don't know how, like, you, okay.
Maybe I just didn't realize.
I mean, the solution to this problem, the solution to the danger is to not write this story.
That makes it not a danger.
And then in our minds, the characters just quote unquote live happily ever after in whatever
way anyone chooses to think about it.
He's choosing to make this an issue and he doesn't need to.
So cynically into that thing.
It's a really honestly interesting thing.
But it's true.
That's so clear.
No, no, no, no.
I'm saying we can take it like one step farther than that.
Okay.
This, okay.
This could be like almost like, you can read into this a lot of things, one of which could
be like, it sort of factors into this media in a way where it's like Andrew, Buddy, people
are losing Homestuck.
They don't care about Homestuck anymore.
You don't see that many cosplayers at Anime Expo anymore.
They're losing relevance.
You got to bring them back.
You got to do the epilogue that you tease that one time in one sentence like two years
ago.
You got to do that.
It's been three years, by the way, since it ended.
Okay.
Three years.
So you could read like, you know, John's being forced into this scenario just sort of out
of the blue.
He doesn't like, he is not.
John's being forced to dance for his money like a painted up horse, draw it out across
our computer screens again.
Yeah.
You could read that maybe Hussie's doing something similar.
And John is, John like Hussie is so cucked of a character.
He is alone.
He is sad.
He's let his relationships dwindle in the 10 years since Homestuck ended.
It is, it's every nightmare I ever have about a character and the way to fix this is to
just not write the story and let me imagine the happy ever after.
That's the solution.
Okay.
But he's choosing not to.
I want to know what the like, the intention, like what is Hussie trying to convey?
Make more money, please, Viz Media.
Capitalize on the brand.
Hold on.
I just mean like, John was like this, he was like a weird sadistic, obviously not as pronounced
or like explicit, but he was like this in the, the Snapchat stuff.
He was like a weird loner that no one talked to.
And like, I just want to know because I'm genuinely interested, like, why?
This was never a thing about John before.
Why is he sad or depressed?
Maybe it represents Hussie's feelings about his own life.
I don't know.
I mean, there's no like contradiction with that because John didn't have like nearby
friends.
He only knew people online.
But he talked to them.
What do you mean?
He talked to them.
No, I know that.
I mean, ten years is a long time.
There's been parts of like John's like sort of like repressing of emotions.
Like he doesn't let himself feel a lot of things or like, he doesn't say things when
he feel, when he's thinking things like, the time where he sees his dad, dead, killed in
front of him and he barely even reacts at all.
He does talk about moping about how his dad's been dead in the ten years since the end.
Is it explicitly said that he represses it?
Because I believe there is dialogue that said that he just doesn't feel the way that other
people do.
I believe that was explicitly said.
Well, the thing is, kids say that they don't feel emotions, but they do.
I feel like that would have been, there was that time on the meteor when he like thought
the corner was shit and he sort of had a breakdown and went insane.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just like, he's a teenager and a lot of homestuck is about growing up.
And John is just sort of like things about things that he just didn't, didn't have like
the, the emotional capacity to, to react to properly, just sort of made him, I don't know.
Hey, but how about the section of the epilogue though, where John is, is understandably questioning
what exactly is the nature of the relationship between Roxy and the Calliope.
And I mean, I've been wondering that all along too.
And I mean, it clearly establishes John and Roxy, despite the obvious intention for them
to be an item, did not get together.
And you know, that's okay.
That doesn't violate anything.
It's just unsatisfying for me, but that can be intentional.
I mean, yeah, John, John is like a real fuck.
Like it is.
I don't feel like it's too, I mean, it's very sad.
It's very sad and like upsetting that John, our good blue boy has, has been like having
had this realistic, upsetting, unsatisfying, like growing ups period of his life.
I mean, he's a guy.
How much of his life has to be realistic?
Oh, okay.
It's weird that John and Roxy were even implied to be a thing and then not followed through.
John and Roxy did not have like an organic like, like romance blossom between them.
The first conversation, John talks to Roxy, there's immediately like the boy for material
joke.
They want to bone in their first month, does not develop whatsoever and then they are implied
to be a, they're implied to get closer and closer over their thing through the retcon.
And then it does not pan out for no reason.
It's not like they have a conversation where they decide they're not going to be together
or where Roxy decides that she will be with Cliope or not.
It just is built up out of nowhere and then dropped out of nowhere.
That's acknowledged.
And the only comment on it is like, John's like, yeah, that was a thing.
It's acknowledged that happened and it's really sad that it didn't work out for whatever
in canon reasons.
Well, hold on.
I think that's bullshit that you're just like, well, it didn't work out.
And then like, no reason given.
Like it's like, I think it is weird, I don't know.
I think what the reason for it is that why is it so fucking bad?
John, there's nothing, there was nothing fucked up about John.
Like he was fine.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Like what, what, what is this?
Well, he was fucked up after the time skip.
He was just kind of a weirdo.
Uh, I don't know.
John's always been a bit of a goober.
He's not been like the most normal person of all time.
A goober is not like an anti-social loner weirdo.
No, he's not.
He's never been like that ever.
I don't know why any of you are saying no.
What about, what about the fact that his friends only existed on the internet at the beginning
of Homestuck.
And he was perfectly sociable.
He was perfectly sociable.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, for fuck's sake, John has been, he's not an outgoing
social dynamo.
He is very chill and relaxed and people come to him.
And I'm just saying, like Roxy is more of an outgoing person and John, John wouldn't
initiate things.
She would probably be waiting for him to, because she's a girl and that's what girls
do.
And he just didn't do it.
Like, I don't, I don't see, I don't see John being a loner as like, I don't see John
being a loner as completely out of character for John Egbert.
I mean, I agree.
I agree with that.
I think, I think it's something that can happen and probably happen to Hussie and that's
why he's written it like that.
I don't think that, like, like, like in theory, it makes absolutely no sense and is a betrayal
of John's character.
I feel like it came out of nowhere, it was not probably set up and goes against what
I perceived the character to be like, I think, pretty rational.
I mean, and it also, it also just sucks.
It also just sucks.
That's a perfectly reasonable point.
In Homestuck, yeah, you're right, John is not the most popular kid in school.
He's not a social dynamo.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying that John was already, like, let's say that like, even the physical distance
was greater, like it was pre the game and he could not fly to people whenever he wanted
to.
He would still talk to people because that's what he did in Homestuck.
You're right.
He waited for his friends to initiate the conversations, all, but not like exclusively.
He talked to people, he responded and was completely agreeable.
I feel like this conversation is honestly pointless because we could speculate all day
about whether or not it was characterized correctly of John, that he would react this
way.
But the fact is he did and you can either like that or not, I just don't think, you
know, I don't know.
I have one nugget of info from the, the, the, the author notes of act five, act two that
I read.
Okay.
Um, where Hussie was talking about how the romance that, uh, was set up immediately
between Karkat and Terezi and how that didn't go anywhere.
And the reason he put, he said that he, uh, that it didn't go anywhere in the end was
because the fact that it was obvious from the start made it kind of less interesting.
And so he didn't want to follow through with it.
That sounds rather capricious as an author to just not follow through because things
are too obvious.
Well, well, I mean, he explained in why it being too obvious just wasn't very interesting
to him and he was like, you know, I mean, it works about the things he likes to write.
And I think certain realistic, like unsatisfying real life things, he likes to add into things
like this.
A lot of acts six is about, you know, whether you like it or not, he likes to make things
that just don't have payoffs in the way that you want, want them to like roses, like play
the rain sort of thing.
He deliberately threw that under the bus because people were expecting it and he's just kind
of an asshole.
I mean, I would make a distinction between satisfying character arcs and like adventure
potential threats that are not significantly built up that don't ultimately get finished.
Well, it's just, it's just a quirk about Hussie as a writer is what it was just a quirk that
he intentionally writes bad, badly.
No, it's not that he does.
Well, I mean, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not defending it.
I'm just explaining that this is why this thing with John is probably happening in this
way.
People like to build up.
To make John have like a realistically upsetting, unsatisfying real life.
But hang on, that word realistic, I feel that you might be using to say that reflects more
accurately your depiction of how life might go for him versus like if he just like got
the girl.
No, I don't mean that.
I don't mean that.
I mean, like in real life, character arcs don't necessarily complete and happy endings
don't necessarily happen.
You know, the road, the girl doesn't necessarily get the, the guy doesn't necessarily get the
girl at the end.
You know, it's just like, um, you know, real life is not like a fiction and Hussie likes
to put that in fiction.
Yeah, man.
We're not, we don't have arcs.
We're people.
We're not characters.
Yeah.
That, that, that literally that right there is like a very obvious, you know, I don't know
what I don't really like it, but that's just how I understand Hussie.
I mean, I'm absolutely in the camp of it totally sucks that John and Roxie didn't get together.
So that, I mean, that's just ultimately, it just sucks.
That's all.
Well, but why?
I don't think they necessarily had that much chemistry together.
And again, I think it came out of nowhere.
But what they just met, they met for the first time.
Why?
I know why do they instantly want to have, okay, I guess they didn't even, they just
worked together.
It's, it's not even weird.
Well, like, what's the point of that whole, like part of the story then, like the whole
thing is that like John and Roxie are having like this, this, this romance or whatever building
up during the thing.
And like to have that come to nothing, it's like, well, why did I even fucking bother reading
it?
Why don't we just skip to the end?
Hussie, does Hussie plan out every little thing about like how a character, you know,
the relationship will progress?
He used to.
Yeah.
I mean, things kind of spiralized.
It's funny.
It's funny because it was satisfying when he didn't plan things.
And then by act six, he probably was planning out everything.
And so like act five, act five.
I mean, frankly, I think to say that he planned out everything and then have this Roxy thing
aside from some world building things he had in mind, like a lot of act five or the troll
like, you know, he didn't have it all mapped out in his head and it was really, really
funny.
And it was really good.
What's striking about this Homestuck epilogue is how played straight it is.
It just is like, okay, two things.
First of all, there are jokes, quote unquote.
And I said this in a text chat with Hippo where, but they operate at such a low like
frequency and such like a low, like, like they were like three, I could just even think
of and they were so, I don't know what the word is, but just like non-infectual whatsoever.
It was a depressing thing.
So I could be like, like a, um, like a Twitter joke on your timeline or she's like, you know,
I guess it's a joke, you know, I read your story as it's intended to provoke humor and
then you scroll past it immediately.
It definitely feels like a dilution of hussy humor with a fanfic Homestuck author put in
there and someone else like it definitely feels like a three person thing.
Um, I, if I was being extremely generous, which generally I didn't, you know, I like
to be generous, but I don't actually think this is the case in this, but this is an idea
I had is that, um, the fact of it being a fanfiction, uh, is part of the reason why
it sort of isn't that funny, uh, like Homestuck because fanfiction writers often don't stick
with the tone of the original work.
Like if they take like a happy thing, they write a gore fanfic, like everyone's dead,
like cupcakes.
Yeah.
Stuff like that.
They go completely off the wall, crazy or super dramatic and it's like not in line with
the way the characters are and it's, you know, just because a lot of fanfics are written
by teenagers who are just, um, moody and depressed and horny and that's all they're thinking
about.
So they just take the characters that they like and make them do things that they wouldn't
otherwise do.
When you're dealing with a, if I'm being extremely generous, fanfiction, you're saying that fanfiction,
you're saying that fanfiction writers don't think that it'd be like it is, and this,
this, this thing that's happening in this fanfiction is like, um, you know, roses on
drugs and like having visions and John has like a choice to make and his emotional, his
relationships have all fucked off and he's really depressed and he maybe will go somewhere
and never come back and never see his friends again and it's all like kind of depressing
and dramatic, which is like a fanfiction would be, but I don't know whether that was deliberate
or not.
Okay. I haven't read it. I'm just going off of what you guys are saying. Is this a cry
for help from Hussie?
I don't think so.
It's hard to tell, but I don't think so.
Yeah. I mean, I'd say that's unlikely, but maybe. I mean, who knows? Uh, maybe all the
homesick.
I mean, Hussie's probably been crying for help ever since, uh, in his life.
Yeah. Ever since, uh, the, what is it, the odd hat man?
The odd gentleman.
Yeah.
Ever since then.
Shout out to, shout out to Hiveswap Quest by Shaddock.
Yes. Quite good. I'm going to go link that and chat right now. Hold on.
Okay. Good. Hey, it details the, the tremendous, um, fuckery that is the, the release of Hiveswap
act one and the fact that it's completely delayed and everything sucks, but it's, it's
funny. It's a funny little animation.
Poor Hussie.
Uh, hey.
Shout out to the odd gentlemen for their great work on King's Quest five spectacular as known
on a steam train, Game Grumps.
Oh yeah.
Um, I did want to just shit on this epilogue in one other way, uh, which we a little bit
got passed or, I don't know, maybe people were trying to excuse a little bit, which
was just that like there is specific mention made of how, uh, like one of the things that
John needs to do is go back to like what's described in Canon, I think by Rose or maybe
Calliope, I can't remember. It's like they need to like, quote, fill in the gaps like
in Canon.
So we're just literally talking about like answering questions that were not addressed
like that. And I know like, yes, doesn't like ruin or fix home stuck to do this. I could
put that aside. It's just that like, this just reminds me of, oh, it sure sucked that
like the whole way that Lord English was defeated, I barely understood it all. And now we're
going to go answer that question, I guess.
Uh, cool.
Just in time.
Why totally still can't word English and homestuck, like fucking Ultima.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
Just like, just like Ultima.
Yep. Yeah.
Maybe it's it's deliberate.
I don't understand.
I've been sitting here for the last like 45 minutes.
Yeah.
I wouldn't expect anything less.
Um, so I just want to say that like sure is embarrassing that home stuck didn't like
write itself well the first time and now needs to go back and like fix things in
actually even worse if this is what is to be the standard.
Yeah.
Like, so this, this is what I'm supposed to call genius of 4D writing to just like
not make it satisfying the first time and go back years later after it's done and try
to fix it.
I would never like, I like to understand why things are the way they are. I don't like
defend anything that I've been explaining. I don't think Hussie is a genius for writing
some ways.
I would say he is. It's just that he's made mistakes.
Hippo said he doesn't think this is a genius move.
Okay.
I think is in the chess game.
I mean, the past is the past. He can't like fix home stuck even though he tried to with
John's retcon powers, which sucked and I hate, um, and he changed the whole website.
I think that was a change like tried to fix home stuck. I think it was just like a narrative.
Well, you're right. He didn't try to fix home stuck. He in fact fucked up home stuck by
changing old panels with his epic 4D retcon panels thing, which I don't even dislike. What
I just don't like is that the experience of reading the comic will never be replicated
again because it's been changed due to narrative things later.
And now the books are printing with those retcons in.
I think that's fine. Like that with the hand, the hands, that doesn't, that doesn't take
anything away.
The armors are your hand.
I'm totally okay with the arm retrieval.
Well, okay. The one thing that it takes away is the, the, the change that you would experience
if you were a current reader reading along, I'm going to argue against that. I actually
think it's better to print with it because now you probably won't notice them on your
first pass through.
Or even if you do, you will just, you probably will just like dismiss it and not know what
it is.
You might be right about that.
And then when you get to that part and you're like, wait a minute, and you might flip back
in the book and be like, whoa, it was there all along.
I didn't even know.
I agree.
I'll agree.
The story is probably better for that. And I don't mind it. But the thing I do mind about
that is I don't like the potential credit that Hussie will receive for people thinking
that he thought about that ahead of time when he did not and does not deserve to, you know,
be rewarded.
All right.
That's my issue.
You put a lot of,
That's dumb.
If you're writing a narrative,
Because it wasn't in the comic.
That's how you think ahead of time.
People lack like it.
Jesse, this is this is one of the things that we know anything like it's never happened
before.
No, because Jesse, we read the comic and the comic itself changed as part of the Lord.
He could have planned to not write it in the panels ahead of time.
Nate, you have, I don't know whether this is like smart or not, because I just generally
don't agree with it. But like you put a lot of like emphasis or like cloud on somebody
planning something ahead of time or not. Like if you can't prove that you planned it ahead
of time, then, you know, they don't, they're not allowed to get like credit or like artist
credit.
What can I say?
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
I just I just generally don't think that that really matters because it's like how much
you care about like how much how many good boy points you give to the author.
I don't know.
There's a kind of social currency and narrative intelligence currency that people care.
Well, Nate, if he had written the whole book on his own without putting it online, right?
If he'd just written Homestuck by himself and then released it all at once, then he could
have like thought of the arm thing later on as he was writing and gone back and added
it in.
And it would be normal. So like why is it not fine for him to think of something to
add to the comic later on and go back, add it in and then print it as though it was there
all because like that's just what writing a book is like.
I mean, you don't have to, you don't have to think of everything in order.
I mean, that's totally fair. But for one, it's simply the fact that like any number
of things or people or ideas could have influenced his process since it was released piece by
piece as it went through. So, you know, and I'm aware of this like boiled down to like
how much money the person deserves to make.
No, it's actually not about money at all. It's about it's about like social cred or
intellectual cred. That's that's a personal thing.
I care immensely.
I understand that you care immensely about it, but like you bring it up in arguments
with other people who may not have, who may not give a shit about like that amount of
maybe the audience level.
It's like, it's like, it's like, well, wait, hold on, we got to make absolutely sure not
to let this author get more credit for this thing.
Like we got like, we can call this thing good, but we got to qualify that like this was good
by accident.
So we shouldn't we shouldn't give the author credit for it.
Yeah, yeah.
No, God, stop. Don't be with me. What are you talking about?
It's not like it's not it shouldn't be regarded as even impressive to foreshadow, which should
just be a given. And if you can't do it and you have to retroactively put foreshadowing
in that wasn't there before, then you failed as a writer and you shouldn't be praised.
That's so stupid.
You know what? I don't know.
There's like, when you're when you're writing a book, like the web comic format, the format
that Homestuck came out and did not allow for that, people write big ass novels, they
spend a year and they still don't just shut up, shut up, they spend years writing a novel.
They have all that time to go back and rework and re-edit youth like people don't just people
it's like you're expecting him to get it right on the first try. Nothing's ever right on
the first try.
Movies go through drafts movies go movies go through fucking a thousand drafts before
they release novels get rewritten and rewritten and rewritten and like it's fine.
I get it.
I don't think you do get it because if you did get it, you wouldn't you wouldn't think
this weird thing that you think it doesn't make any fucking sense for some reason, Ben.
You are equivocating between two very different mediums and assuming that the like everything
that's involved in one needs to be applied to the other when they're completely different
and not.
Isn't that what you're doing?
Why would you judge them differently?
Because they're different mediums. Why don't you judge a painting and a song the same?
They're basically the same thing, right?
Because it's an internet thing that came out weekly and he didn't have as much time to
maybe edit it for years and years each time that he couldn't have properly foreshadowed
the first time because it was coming out weekly.
Right.
Listen, listen.
The nature of this foreshadowing thing.
The hippo let me fucking talk.
If that were a requirement, then if that were a requirement, then what you'd be saying is
it's not okay that he decided on something later to go back and add in because it's like
what?
Because like he didn't think of it soon enough and like once and once and once and once you
and once.
I think it would be impressive if he had.
Okay, okay.
Well, I'll agree that it's not as impressive that he didn't have it all planned out for
the start.
I think he was agreeing.
I did it.
I mean, yeah, you did it with some of the aspects of the horseshoe stuff.
I'm better than Hussie is my point.
That's the whole thing I was getting at this whole time.
I figured.
I figured as much.
But okay, just to put a final point at it, the reason why it actually ties back to Digi
and Destiny's debate they had the other day, which is like imagine you've got two Manga,
I'm thinking of Manga right now for whatever reason, but like you've got two Manga because
like Oda supposedly will find out when one piece is done.
I don't take this on faith, but he says he had the ending planned all along and when
it comes out, we'll see if it's good or not.
And we'll be able to judge it until then.
I remain agnostic as to how good it was.
Whereas like let's say like something like Naruto, the way Naruto ended was clearly
not the way things like were intended all along.
A lot of stuff was kind of made up as a way like the importance of Sasuke was conflated
to be like the rival of Naruto.
That became the focus and like what we can learn from this, I think and again, we'll
judge Oda after it's all done is like what we can expect from the quality of the writing
of the person when they write their next thing.
It's how impressive do we expect it to be or like someone who's a game developer who
makes a game that's like broken, but then when they make DLC, oh, like that fixes it.
Well, okay, great.
But now when you make your new project and maybe that doesn't have DLC, we can possibly
expect it to have some holes or not be fucked up or that stuff.
I think this like leads into like just managing hype, right?
So like George Lucas, he made Star Wars, but like a lot of the good decisions weren't
entirely his.
So when he had complete creative control, people thought because George Lucas made Star
Wars that the prequels would be really good, they weren't because Georgia is like kind
of not that good at writing as it turns out.
So like what you would like is for people to be more skeptical about giving certain
creatives very much high amounts of praise when they may not actually deserve the praise
so as to mitigate hype in the future so that people don't get burned.
More or less.
Yes, it's about managing consumer choices in terms of what you want to invest your money
and expectations for personal enjoyment.
Okay, I mean, a lot of the time where I don't agree with you on things like that, it's really
just because whether or not they deserve the credit, they're basically the same level
of artist.
I don't think Oda will be a complete hack if something about one piece is not good when
so much of it is brilliant.
Well, sure, but that's not really what I mean.
I mean, maybe it is in the sense that you're talking about things that aren't planned,
like hockey.
All the time hockey was not planned and there are some like some holes that I feel hockey
creates a minor issue.
The sport hockey?
Sorry?
What?
No, I'm not the sport.
Conquerors hockey.
Well, hockey.
H-A-K-I.
So it's an anime thing.
It's an anime thing.
Okay, well, you know what?
I think the people have heard enough on this.
I think they get our sides.
Well, there was one point that I wanted to say before we move on about it.
I just want to say that this entire thing seems like the bane of my existence and this
is metanarrative at any cost.
We will do anything as long as it's metanarrative.
You're talking about Homestuck.
Yeah, I'm talking about Homestuck right now.
Okay.
The Homestuck epilogue.
Sacrifice everything for the sake of a meta, whatever it takes.
Yeah.
Homestuck in the beginning was not like, okay, it was meta in a few ways, but like it's not,
its goal was not to be as like meta as humanly possible, which is what everyone latched onto
by the end.
Just like the only reason to read Homestuck is that it was so fucking crazy, it plays
with narrative structures.
I mean, just to put one point on there.
I would argue that Homestuck has done the best job of thoroughly exploring the fictional,
not meta, real concept of time travel.
It has done a far better job than any other story I've ever read and like that's not
a meta concept.
That's just great storytelling and it was sick and dope.
Agreed.
Salute that.
Like I would say like meta can like can enhance a story, obviously.
I'm not saying that being meta is bad, but I'm saying that it was just used sparingly
in the beginning and then ballooned into a larger portion of what the story was about
than I wanted.
And now it feels like it's consumed like this entire thing is just one Rose and John text
up about, you know, philosophical, philosophical quandaries, you know, are we canon, we're
forgetting, we're fading, da, da, da, da, da.
Whereas I would like to have just heard some of the funny rich dialogue that was in the
beginning.
I just miss that.
I don't like that.
Seemingly, the Husseys just now played into the fact that Homestuck is a meta thing and
that's all that we must pay attention to.
Yeah, it's like it started off as a comic about four kids stuck in their homes and their
quest that is like metaphorically about growing up and then meta stuff also was there and
now it's completely shifted that's mostly meta stuff and there is no character back
and forth at all.
I mean, I think that because Husseys talked about many times about or like we've speculated
on arm retrieval famously and elsewhere that like, Husseys doesn't care anymore.
Like the thing he does care about is I think Husseys is interested in telling meta stories.
I don't think he's particularly interested in these characters and, you know, their stories
are done.
And so I like maybe he really has been or like encouraged heavily by his media to go
back and like make more and he's turning it into a meta thing that he does find interesting
with this whole fading from relevance, you know, plot line.
I don't know.
And that's not even uninteresting.
But I think as much as saying when you intentionally or not, because you want to or not, when you
sacrifice the things that guys like me and Munchy and Gib and Ben and everybody fell
in love with, which is like the witty snarkiness to like for the sake of getting more meta
stuff out of there, I just think it's natural to lose some excitement and some of your fans
in that process.
So yeah, that's where I'm at.
I also want to say that no one agrees with me.
No one, no one, no one in this call.
No one agrees with me in the world that the homesick art was good and then it became bad
and that's a problem.
Everyone's like, oh, fucking, you know, whatever.
No one even read.
No one even looked at the drawings anyway.
Do you?
Well, thank fucking God.
So I don't I don't I don't shit on me.
I think, you know, you tried to point out some like sloppy panels in like the later acts
and like, yeah, they're there.
But like, there were always some sloppy panels.
It's not like there were some bad in axis.
It means the overwhelming majority of them were terrible, especially towards the end.
I assume you mean aesthetically, right?
Yeah, I mean, in terms of like skill.
Yeah. OK.
Aesthetically, I think we can that that could be a serious and skill and as well.
And with that, you might see some pushback on.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't I don't I mean, I don't know.
There's always had it's always had its wonky art.
Homesick always had its wonky art moments.
No, it wasn't.
It wasn't wonky.
It was just like unkempt and rushed and sort of like slapdash.
Like he drew a really good drawing, but he left in like little mistakes.
Like when he raised things, he would leave like little like stray pixels around.
And that was just like part of the look.
There later, everything's like actually a little cleaner.
But it's just like the the the the the structure of like like the poses
and the gifts and like the layout.
So just boring and uninteresting to look at.
Exactly. Overall.
There is no shortage of iconic panels from mid homestuck.
That is of course.
Yeah, of course, there are. Of course, there are.
But the the completely.
That's a fair point, Munchy, but you know, let's leave it there.
I think the people can can judge that one.
And OK, I don't know if we get anywhere.
I mean, I mean, I don't know.
Munchy, I'm going to say I think that maybe if there's fewer iconic visuals,
if there's fewer iconic moments in X6, it's probably just because the story
sucks and not because the art like took a huge downhill.
It took a downhill.
Maybe not the hugest that we're exaggerating it.
Not as huge as the writing.
Well, sure. Yeah, definitely, but it's 100 percent palpable.
Definitely, Palpatine, speaking of which,
Star Wars, Episode nine is coming.
Well, I can't wait.
Well, no, no.
Oh, yes, Episode nine is the most disappointing thing.
I was just saying my car here.
It's me, obviously.
But I'll tell you an opinion.
I'll give you a fucking spicy opinion right here.
Please. I just I want it to be over.
I don't like Star Wars, and I hate it.
And that's it.
It's not that. I think that's so spicy.
I'm here.
I don't know how spicy it is.
No, you're right.
It's not.
I didn't see solo.
I haven't seen anyone else.
I just like like when I saw it when I woke up and I saw that there was
a new Star Wars trailer, I just felt angry.
Just like, yeah, no, not again, no more.
I mean, you knew it was coming.
I knew it was coming.
But like, I wasn't ready.
I wasn't ready for the discourse.
That's what I was not ready.
It's not it's not it's not even the movies themselves that bothers me.
It's that I know there's going to be a new wave of Star Wars discourse,
and I'm not fucking ready.
That's true. That is true.
I can't I can't wait for the hundreds upon thousands of thumbnails of
reviews. Yeah.
Hey, hey, just a question.
Whether the media did not make a last Jedi review, right?
The last one, the last they did.
They did.
It was OK.
Wait, wait, they made a flinket of that.
Played. Yeah, Mr. Plinkett did a completely
straightforward review of the last Jedi.
And it was weird that it was not at all.
Yeah, it was not like it was not because like the old Plinkett's when they first
came out, they had a purpose because nobody had gone that in depth before
about these Star Wars prequels.
Like now it's just another fucking YouTube video.
It's this video, the YouTube algorithm.
It was called the last Plinkett review because at the end,
I think he goes on about like how there's no reason I did this because
everyone else has done it.
Oh, but I did it anywhere.
Oh, that's a that's a rough.
He said he suggests he says something about a boycott, but it's like it's
obviously not because clearly he's been swallowed by the YouTube algorithm
and he's going to really make another one.
I mean, I don't mind having the bags on on the Star Wars because I like
it just feels different.
It's appropriate. Plinkett should be.
Videos, not stars.
That's honestly the thing about boycotting.
I mean, fucking what's his face?
James Rolfe with this is what is it?
Like he's Ghostbusters, boycott, little carnivores.
That's fine.
But boycott, the real big boy thing to do is indeed boycott like any social
media discussion or interaction with the thing that you're boycotting.
And you can't like hashtag stay away from the Jedi or because all you're
doing is drumming more attention.
It's almost at political levels.
Like I hate Star Wars talk almost as much as I hate hearing people talk about
politics.
It's that saturated that it's getting to that point in my brain.
We're like, I hear it and I just want to know what the weird thing is, dude,
even Democrats and Republicans like red lights, say, but blue lights.
Wow, you got it, dude.
The thing about Star Wars is, and this is the thing that really pisses
me off about it, it feels like there's the most rage and anger about it.
And the most like waste of everyone's in the time world for the least
amount of content that has been generated.
It's like one movie, like at least with Marvel, there's like a movie
every six months or whatever.
So like, I get it why that keeps coming up.
But Star Wars is so, there's so little substance in Star Wars.
It's every one episode of Star Trek has more intellectual content than
any individual Star Wars movie.
There's like, there's like, there's like, there's like, there's like, there's
got to be 12 Star Wars movies at least.
And there's like two good ones.
Two of them are good, only two.
That sounds about right.
Episode one, Phantom Menace, episode three.
No, I mean, episode two is the best memes, sand, it's coarse and gay.
I like Empire and I like Revenge of the Sith, and that's it.
That's, you don't even like a new hope.
You don't like episode four or whatever.
A new hope is boring as fuck.
That is a boring fucking movie.
What?
No, there's a spicy take.
That is a spicy take.
That's the take we were looking for.
Yeah, I'm surprised.
A boomer such as yourself would.
Star Wars is the most boomer shit.
It's the most boomer core shit in the world.
Everyone even talking about Star Wars is a boomer.
Wait, wait, there's two things.
I can think of two things more boomer and that is Gremlins and Back to the Future.
I guess that's fair.
I guess they're a little more, more boomer than Star Wars.
Nate, you mentioned Star Trek.
Yeah, let's let's diverge immediately away from Star Wars.
Talk about Star Trek a bit.
I saw a clip on YouTube of Data and Klingon Man, a dwarf, whatever his name is, Wharf.
I don't know anything about Star Trek,
but it was a scene in which Wharf sort of dismissed like Data is acting captain
and Wharf like was first mate and he sort of dismissed him in front of the crew
and Data pulled him into another room to explain to him how you're not
supposed to do that as acting as his first mate and you know it was like Data is a robot
and you know he said it in a very robotic way but it was sort of you know just
explaining what his role is and then Wharf like oh I'm sorry captain like he just took
took the criticism like a man like an alien man and then they parted on good terms even though
it was just like really interesting a clip and then in the comments everyone was like
I ah I remember this scene I learned so much about honor from you and you know if it was
spooty old Star Wars then that conversation would go with Wharf being like I'm falling
to the dark side I'm gonna become evil the rage is building inside me one of the things one of
the things I love about Star Trek so much and at least of the two of the three seasons I've seen
of the original of next generation and I mean I've seen some of Voyager not counting that
but uh fucking Deep Space Nine is the insane actually this is a little bit less in Deep Space
Nine because that takes place during like a war but especially in the next generation the consummate
professionalism of every member of the crew they know their duty they do their job they are these
are military scientist people they are there they do not defy orders unless there's some like really
good reason to do it it's not about being like a rogue it's about being a member of a fucking team
and it feels like there's something so refreshing to just be like ah like there can be order there
can be like a social cohesion between people and people can just be nice and do good things to each
other and like fulfill their responsibilities watch the next generation and just feel the
historic feeling that society is worth fighting for and it can feel so good sometimes that's always
been the point of Star Trek especially TNG it was like showing humanity in the best way and being
like look look what can happen if we aspire to greatness and like commit to it exactly and that
moment you said right there like that literally could be a moment I'm just saying like data was
acting captain against Klingon Klingon alien uh uh androids with data is technically two different
species uh like this could be like a like a racist moment I guess it'd be a speciesist moment or
whatever and like sure you could go to HR or whatever and you could like complain to someone
but instead of doing that he takes them aside they just discuss this as professionals
wharf has a bias as many people do in the next generation against data but the thing is for
people who don't know so a lot of people know about Star Trek and and data and there's an
android just so people know data was not constructed by anyone to be a star fleet officer data was
constructed as an android with free will who independently just lived his life and decided
yeah is he is he x is he just x basically he's basically x he just like is the maverick hunters
and then uh were founded and then x decided to join them because he wanted to do that data just
decided the best thing he could do with his life to fulfill his own personal goals was to go through
the the academy the star fleet academy as every other student did he was just a student work hard
and earn his commission as an officer and then he became a second officer on the flagship through
his pure merit through no like being like built for the purpose he just decided to it has inherent
gifts and that's and that's why when he talks to wharf in that scene and wharf says like hey
fuck you man i'm not gonna work some fucking machine data says you don't understand wharf
i earned this position i am the captain we have a machine there's an order exactly well i'm paraphrasing
uh he asserts that he's the captain and that war like they need to abide by the roles of this like
military order of star fleet in order to make sure that everything runs efficiently
and if this is going to be a problem like i think he says like let me know like i'll have you step
down and i'll put someone else you know in first officer positioner i think that was implied at
least so i'm just saying uh so it's the best so it's the best well you know uh uh basically it's
that scene in uh game of thrones when uh janice slent when uh uh john john snow gets elected lord
commander of the night's watch and janice slents like fuck you and john is like i'm commander and if
you know it's the death sentence to fucking defy the lord commander and janice is like yeah well
fuck you anyway he's like well i'm gonna i'm gonna behead you then and then he does that it's basically
like that only i think this is so it's pretty much i think they've outlawed the death penalty in
star trek little known i will maybe people know this uh people who are criminals are treated as
mental health cases and are like treated to like fix their broken brains and uh that's what they do
my favorite thing about uh star trek yeah i really should watch it i didn't know that i did not know
that about star flea it's true and i there's just so you know there's a couple cases of people who
brains they can't fix and like those people are the ones they keep in jail but it's very very rare
those kind of people but yeah sure my my favorite thing about star trek uh every time i see uh you
know a clip of like the bridge and them just walking around you won't believe how much you love
star trek when you watch it i'm just saying but anyway well it's it's the fucking carpet it's the
fucking carpet and the lighting and it feels so it feels like a really nice comfy like friends house
bridge enterprise is home i want to live there every day yeah it's got it's so it's so it's so
nice to see like the ideal like the idea of like a spaceship but built to be furnished so that people
are relaxed and calm and it's nice yeah oh and which will hold up more sense than than just like uh
we're in space so you know dude really really cold blue lighting and stuff the thing about that is
you know that very ship like when they make star trek movies they they redo the lighting to make
everything look like professional and like movie-esque and fancy they just completely fuck up the
lighting on the bridge to like be like weird spooky like mood lighting because it's a movie now
we need to look cool we can't look like flat even comfy lighting like on the movie and everything
about first of all it's not canon second of all it sucks and it's try hard bullshit so uh star trek
is just so thoroughly patrician and star wars absolutely literal baby shit like i know you
can like both it doesn't have to be comparing the two it's just a nerd thing to compare the two but
god star wars is such baby shit it's just like why does when when sparta when the star star trek
star trek being patrician doesn't like it doesn't exclude star wars from being baby shit you know
it would be baby shit if star trek didn't exist that's true but you know when when sparta from
devil may cry was young he fought with the demon king mundus he was his right hand man but then
quote he woke up to justice when i was young i was a big fan of star wars you know i fought on the
side of star wars then i woke up to star trek that's what happened to me and now i'm on the right
side of history god when i when i put on any episode of star trek any series whether it's the
original or next generation whether it's deep space nine you know i put on any episode of star trek
and i just feel like i'm in a in a good place i feel like i'm in a company and i just wake up to
justice i wake up to justice let's have a shirt in the store that says hey i woke up today that's a
good idea this is a fucking star fleet logo on it oh yeah we can play into the waking up to
justice you know what you gotta do next legally distinct star fleet logo legally distinct star
fleet yeah oh my god we should have the bottom say joined legally distinct star fleet today wake
up to justice um the next the next thing the next thing that sparta did is he he in that in that
passage he woke up to justice and he stood against the legion alone that means you have to go fight
all the fucking episode nine videos now and talk about how star trek spades with us
like being uh uh uh uh a dis Privileged Minority in this country it's been but one non-star wars
fan standing against the whore at every fucking couple this it's basically the cultural equivalent
of the the oppressed gamer it's the oppressed star trek fan it's like the new crusades like they're
just going in slaughtering everyone who doesn't adhere to the church of star wars and corporate
corporate America is an in-club everyone who is a billionaire loves Star Wars
indeed and if you don't like Star Wars you can't be their friend and they
won't let you make money why that's how it is that's that's that's nepotism damn
right it is why is no one crony capitalism why does Star Wars never
get called out for being fucking corny cuz like you mean like the originals of
the new ones cuz like you know like Kingdom Hearts 3 came out
and all anyone said was how corny Kingdom Hearts is cuz oh it's oh it's
the light and then the darkness but then the light in your heart makes you good
but I don't want to be dark in my heart that's exactly what Star Wars is it's
this is a fantasy for autistic people who see everything binary black
and white you ever notice when you get those comments on your videos from
someone who you can tell is really autistic and they think that you're
just a bad person cuz you use like the word retard or or something you use
that yes like naughty language is it you're a bad person that's the kind of
people who see the world in totally black and white everything that is is
either bad or good light or dark that's what Star Wars is that's why it's so
popular it's a fantasy for autistic fucking retards who see they have a
question in terms of light side and dark side oh no I'm falling to the dark side
the space wizard is gonna make me turn to darkness in my heart shut the fuck up
oh my god we might have got stars over here which is all this like you know the
high concept actual stuff that's like a moral dilemmas that people can actually
like form like arguments for and think about philosophically and then you got
Star Wars over in the corner
yeah don't don't do that one dark sabers it's just Kingdom Hearts it's
exactly as stupid as Kingdom Hearts I've heard the comparisons to Kingdom Hearts
yeah yeah for sure for sure it's I mean is there any more comparison that's just
the low IQ version of the story versus the high IQ version than Star Wars and
Star Trek I don't know I don't know I mean like Star Wars is the low IQ in
Kingdom Hearts Kingdom Hearts well that's what are we gonna get the
Star Wars movie by Disney here well I'm that's true blue pill Star Wars sheep
over here well I'm so red pill that I'm fucking playing Kingdom Hearts like a
boss yeah it's 2009 again baby god I want to go back well that was that was
thorough good job team anything else going on I went to a thing I went to a
fucking comics yeah no not that no not that I went to this thing called the
Boston going gang meeting is pretty much like going to stand up comedy if you
know what I'm saying real clown at the podium if you know what I mean
much did you want to say something I do want to say something first of all check
out the enter the gungeon episode of endless war or I'm sorry of our yes so
you get some backstory and get some some I talk about yeah I talk yeah I want a
whole bunch about this in that episode yeah was kicked into shape in that
episode and and force and force to walk down the royal road and try and reach
up to his idol Tim Buckley and become the most proficient among on earth yeah
and yeah and the night but I told him on the episode that I would remind him
every single night to go that Thursday and I did and the night before and I
believe the night of as well I told him today is the day and and you went and
you and you reply to me quote it was fine so yeah we talked extensively about
the pros and cons of the comics roundtable and about how could you you
know can make or break things and how is pivotal that you were to go that's not I
don't exaggerate I think yeah that's I'm saying though to have our
incredibly long conversation of it turn out to be you know it was fine you know
I'm not just I want to hear well here's the thing well here's the thing really
that's kind of why I didn't want to go cuz I was like I'm saying that I think I
might just go in and might just be like no there's nothing really going on in
the episode you describe how it might be fine and there and then you would feel
like you have no more options left do you feel like you have no more options
left now yeah yeah now I'm trapped okay now I'm trapped now I'm trapped in the
cage of my own life options for what I don't get it what's the no escape well
the idea was that like I hadn't like been going out very much well there's this
thing that I could go to I used to go to it and it was fine anyway that it's it's
just like a club thing it's been running since like 2006 before I moved in with
Digi when I was living here before I went for a little while and like it was
pretty good I met some people it was fun and then you know they left and I came
back and I just I never got around to going back to it and now it's like it's
like every week at like I just like maybe another time maybe another time well I
went back this week and it was like I was kind of dead and I think maybe because
there was like there was like a gallery there was like a gallery opening like in
the building where it was happening not sure if that had anything to do with it
you know here's the thing right I get there and and it's a bunch of freaks and
I say that in like the most yeah loving way possible I say that in the least
judgmental way possible everyone's a fucking weirdo probably me you know
probably me too okay I'm really surprised that you would say that as a
majority because if there's some I would imagine that you would love to see
freaks and geeks well there's friends that are fun to hang out with and friends
that are you know freaks I mean freaks I don't know there's like alright there
were a couple I get there and there's a couple of there's a couple of non-binary
people talking about just how non-binary they are right in like they're
they're loving it and I don't think either of them even draw or write so I
don't know what they're doing there but they seem to be the ones in charge
okay like right off the bat that's pretty good good start then there's this
guy he looks maybe a bit younger than me he comes in at some point it becomes
clear that he's on the spectrum he uses he uses the word retarded to describe
see I start going off on a rant about spirit science and the love battleship
right of course I start I start talking about aligning my Kundalini and he's and
he is like you know amused by this and says like you know oh that's you know
that's retarded and one of these one of these non-binary people who seem to be
in charge of everything says like well she softballs him right yeah they saw
they softball him right and and they're like well you know I'm not gonna go full
SJW on you but you know don't use that word it's offensive and he is like he
tries to argue it and it's really uncomfortable so I leave for a while
and they go to the gallery opening and I steal and I steal some of their free
cheese platters that they have out okay they have so much cheese I eat so much
free cheese at that gallery oh bent that was the best part about caramel apples
do you remember the caramel I remember I remember I remember the caramel caramel
flowed like water that night yeah a good thing was before I went keto but but
um so there's a you know there's a couple of like older guys and girls who are
like you know like 50s 40s and 50s there maybe they seem to be a little more
serious about it you know they're fine they're fine there's like one other
like non-binary person question mark who seems like kind of less grating and
obnoxious than the other two she seemed fine but they seem fine but they didn't
say much they they were like new and then this guy who's next to me though he's it
comes out that he's on the spectrum at some point he says that and then he tells
me literally tells me about how his thing that he's been working on for years
is that he's just rewriting Naruto he's just rewriting Naruto and do I want to
read his manuscript and I say I'm sorry but I gotta go I really you know it's
time I think it's about time I should be hitting the old dusty you know I hate to
say it but in the real life a lot of people just suck and are very unimpressive
out the world sure it's unfortunate you know that's true listen listen listen
like when I used to go there were these people right there were these same
people like these guys who was just rewriting Naruto like this is not this
ain't my first rodeo yeah alright like it that doesn't bother me it did bother
me I don't know like before it seemed like they were more like mid-range age
people like 20s early 30s now it was like there was like this one one or two
like college kids and then like a bunch of like 40 somethings and I'm like I'm
gonna maybe I won't give up just yet maybe this is just a slow day or something
yeah yeah like it's possible because they were a cut I remember there were a
couple people that used to go that were pretty cool and I was kind of
disappointed that they weren't there anymore but whatever I'll stick it out
um so you're going you're going again yeah yeah I'll be going back okay I'm
looking forward there we wait there was shit there was one other thing that I
wanted to touch oh okay interesting thing it's it seems to me for my like
appraisal that the only person there who is accomplished at all right the only
person there who has like any sort of a presence or any sort of like a like a
thing going yeah is this person is this person I I don't know if I should say
their name I guess you're on the side of caution I suppose if you know you're
praising them aren't you I suppose well kind of well I don't know I just it's
just weird I don't know you dogged all right whatever their name is LB right
they go by LB they are non-bind right now this this is a different LB the LB
stands for Looney Brain and okay this person like wrote a book right it's like
a prose book but it has like illustrations in it right so it's like an
illustrated word like whatever so they made this book I don't know if they
kickstarted it or whatever but like they published it I looked it up there on
they're not they're not on Twitter but they're on itch.io is where their work
is or something yeah that's that's strange that's strange but whatever
that's fine but they were talking about an article that someone had written
about this person and in the meeting they were say yeah they did this great
article right up on you it was like yeah about like the best comic artist you've
never heard of right that's what they said sure and and I'm like okay so I go
online and I look up the name of the magazine that wrote this article up and
I look up the name of this person and I find the article but the full article is
titled the best comic artist you've never heard of is eight people and I read it
and it turns out that this person shtick or their deal or their thing is that
they have headmates or dissociative identity disorder okay I think the
article mentions dissociative identity disorder and they I think their work is
about living with headmates and that's okay so headmates is like the fake
version of actual dissociative identity disorder I don't know I don't know okay
I don't know what's fake and what's real anymore I'm happy to believe someone
has this but but this person this person's like got a patreon and stuff
okay and and like they're caught they're comparable to me they're making like
comparable amounts to me they're my only competition so I gotta kill them I gotta
you gotta you gotta use eight bullets to take this guy out cuz I gotta be the
biggest fish in this tiny pond or else of or else what do I have to live I know
the feeling well mm-hmm well that's interesting so so that's so that was my
that's my fucking Boston Comics roundtable story if you live hey if you
live in the Boston area the listener stay the hell away from me don't don't
fucking show up at these things in the show to be able to read a page of this
LB person and I want to say before I post it it looks like it's also ugly
art no it does no it looks like it looks like Erica moans art is what it
looks like it reminds me of you don't even know you don't even know who that
is I don't is that is that an actor on the room um yeah you got me ways is this
engrossed is this in the audio yeah yeah I don't mean to be money I fucking hate
you this does not look like my art at all I'm legitimately insulted I'm
legitimately insulted listen hold on I'm gonna get some it's okay this is not
a gem of your current or even to say that this is like only did you say it's
did you say it's also ugly yes well it's better than that it is better okay
no I'm not okay okay yeah you know what you did you did and I misheard
however no Erica moan is the Ojoi sex toy girl and this looks exact this looks
exactly like that yeah you're kind of right but not even that much worse it's
just very very simple you know there's like you know how like DC and Marvel
have like their house style there's like a house indie style which is this yeah
like there's a ton of artists who do this kind of like work it's very weird
yeah how that kind of just happens well maybe Erica moans not the only I just
have a quick question about am I supposed to I'm just wondering like am I to
believe from reading of like this comic that this is the the actual author of
this is does indeed have a split personality and eight people live inside
of them and this is a picture at least some of them is this the idea of like
that the comic I'm reading the comic not necessarily just for the quality of it
but because it's being written by a person with a split personality or the
dissociative identity Nate you know your guess is as good as mine on that okay
okay just wondering you know Ben much much like much like much like Sparta
himself you must stand against this Legion alone look good luck man you know
you know I don't know I'm not I'm not I'm not trying to be all like look at this
fucking look at this look at this shit look at like everyone's all like it's
all pandering it's all pandering to like queer identities and like it's all
identity politics it's all like a mental illness it's all like pandering to
like some weird thing I don't care right like if people like the stuff then
it's fine right nothing no there's no such thing as art that's not valid sure
right it's it's all it's all cool it's all good but it's very it's just very
perhaps it's it's kind of like Tom was saying like it's just it's just I wonder
if comics are even for like can I can I dang sis white guy can I can I under a
kind of white guy wake up in here in a downtrodden sis white guy even make it
in this comics world or is it just for is it just for people well you know Ben
I honestly like I look I look at it more and more and more it seems like this is
this is how you make it as comics it's like is when you're too fucking
disenfranchised and too much of a fucking weirdo no no offense for like
traditional or traditional or traditional publishing then like this is
what you get and this is where you find your audience you know they know where
you'll be they know where you'll be flushed out of the mainstream system and
where you'll fucking come out the drain here to making sequential art like a
fucking like a fucking peasants it's definitely become like a selling
that's all you deserve trans and I have people living in my brain you know to
like preface your art with that it gives you a kind of a built-in audience
it's stacking the deck with like social conditions yeah it's like yeah I mean
you know when you're a when you're a when you feel like you're a fucking freak
that no one understands yeah and then you see someone writing and they're
writing it's like hey me too you know I get it that makes sense yeah but I feel
like like Ben to correct me if I'm wrong but don't you feel like socially
different from the normal people like you're an outcast is there's no label
for what Ben is because he's just there's no label that's so yeah I was like
but the there's no there's no there's no adjective there's no there's no there's
no well-defined like category or group or like or like mass noun for the way
that I feel that I am I'm just gonna put on the Star Wars fan in my Patriot
you know what actually that's it that's it you saw you solve the riddle you see
that on someone's resume hire this genius immediately we need him on staff we
need this diversity of thought everyone else here's a damn Star Wars fan this is
a truly oppressed minority one one day I'll find one day I'll find some sort of
label to apply to myself that other people have already claimed so I can be
a part of a group identity follow this logic and have a built-in audience
follow this logic with me real quick I do believe that just for example like
every sexuality is on a spectrum and so one could relatively accurately assess
that there's no such thing probably as like purely straight or purely gay or
like anything like it's probably all in the spectrum including me so is it such
a stretch for me to like on my college application or job thing or whatever it
says like choose sexuality for me to just check bisexual or pansexual like
I'll take that I'll take that wider categorization is that such a crazy
thing to do can I get the ladies and gentlemen I don't think I don't think
you can argue against yeah do you really get cred for being right now I think
there's really hate the bias your softball and with that one there's no
downside to just telling people that you're bi yeah there is yeah well the
only thing that I know is that I know people who are gay don't like bi people
because they can pass as normative and so you're actually you actually kind of
go lower if you're bi cuz like even the minorities don't like you because you
can pass as a majority so you kind of get fucked from both ends you might come
off as a little you might come off as a little exotic to some extra straight some
extra extra square straight that's true I mean that's how many people like are
but about the fetishization of you know your girlfriend being a little bit
girls as well you know whatever yeah that's a thing you can you can you can
you can benefit you can there's there's some cred there's some cred to be at
least for some social capital to be a crude a little bit and why and I mean
just I'm just saying why not a crew as much as possible every little bit you
can get why not zoom it up like a classic yeah tactic you know I'm just
saying well I don't know if you get not not I say anyway so so the point is
that I go you know it's not even that I felt alienated or anything I didn't
feel weird like being surrounded by by you know by these by the drinks of
society I mean they weren't all that there were a lot of them but they weren't
all that or anything and you know I didn't feel like I didn't I did not
feel like I don't belong here I'm a cis white guy like it wasn't like that no
one was like making me you know cuz like I mean frankly that comment about don't
say retarded that's what makes me feel uncomfortable in a you know you know I'm
get why people don't like when you use that word I get it I get it that's don't
like it so like and you know she wasn't even that aggressive about it and like
the guy the guy should have just said sorry and not argued it you know I think
because he said he was I mean I think the reason he didn't do that cuz cuz he's
was on the spectrum and that's why you don't you don't always know how to
deal with a social situation that's takes a little bit of finesse and you don't
have that finesse you know who get a real pass on these issues just for
interest people with Tourette's people with Tourette's got a complete blank slate
pass they get the password pass they get the you know the f-ball pass they get it
all hey funny thing I was just like looking at twitch the other are you
talking about sweet Anita the girl with with with crazy Tourette's who will say
fuck my cunt muffin you know all kinds of things just I don't remember her name
but yeah she would she would say stuff like that probably sweet yeah but but
she would just I mean that wasn't really that weird cuz she would just say that
stuff like when she lost she was playing um you know Bennett Foddy getting
over yeah yeah and you know just like when she lost progress she would just say
these really weird swears and like you know that's not weird to swear when
you're losing at a game but the thing is she would make like she would like
click her tongue she would like she would like click her tongue and then she
would do like sort of a bird whistle like like I can't whistle but you know
you know what I mean like that she would she would do a little like bird like
tweet tweet like sort of whistle yeah thanks yep that's her she would just sort
of do yeah yeah and I was I was like that's that's funny I'm laughing you
know I'm laughing all the way to the bank you know it's it's well I mean she she
was like making a thing out of it right like it's like I guess it's kind of nice
in a way that you have like a disability but you like turned it into like a cute
gimmick that well her story popular on twitch you know it's really bad of me
but I don't know when I when I watch people with Tourette's I think that's
fucking annoying like well sure from me Tourette's person you're annoying you know
it might be cute to like watch a YouTube clip that's haha so funny imagine I'm
nothing against her anybody with it but like imagine living with that it's gonna
get annoying and I know it's bad cuz they can't help it obviously yeah I would
not want to be around that person for five minutes and that probably is why
they I mean for her she like couldn't get a job cuz like her Tourette's is like I
mean I don't know how advances but like she'll like slap people's asses when
they bend over and apparently she can't wait wait what I mean that's what she
said she'll like hump people's ass she will hump them if they like that sounds
like she's just using her disability to her advantage I mean I don't know I
assume I don't okay well maybe that sounds like she was okay if I have to
live with this like I can't stop swearing thing then I'm at least it's an
oh oh I also can't help touching asses and humping people that's part of it too
guys well like if this was like a man and like an ugly man I mean she's a cute
girl basically so I feel like it feels far less if this were a man if this were
a man he'd probably be locked up let's just be I mean maybe certainly likely but
I mean I mean he would be he would probably be like I don't know they true
people treated I'm just saying like what if she I actually have not heard her
make any like like racial epithets or anything like that but like what if it
was just to say like the end word or something with like Tourette's if a man
just streamed with all he would get is like you're an autistic piece of shit you
suck you're retarded go die probably I mean maybe we was really put together I
mean she's a cute girl you know she's got her she's you know that does looks
nice yeah skin yeah no looks normal and then just she has like a thing white
white as can be oh thank God you know so that's I mean imagine no like for real
like I'd probably be a lot harder it'd be it'd be a lot harder on her if she
wasn't white I mean I suppose I suppose I imagine so but I mean in the capacity
of like judging how like what like dangerous she is like why would that
matter on Twitch because that's what she's doing maybe if you're in general in
like her life you just you just get more shit you just get more shit and people
are like people like use it as an excuse to like fuck with you I mean that I'm
sure that's if they want to yeah that's probably that's probably fair to say
okay but the point is well I don't know what the point is fine her story oh you
know what I heard one thing that she said though that was like the reason she
she twitches streams is because like it's hard for someone with Tourette's to get a
job and like when she was younger because like she has all these impulses she
can't control she would have to do jobs that like allow her to be alone so she
would like walk down by the beach and like gather sea glass and then would go
to like the road or something and would sell seashells by the sea show that's
exactly correct that's exactly correct and I was just thinking to myself like
wow what a what an entrepreneurial spirit what I just found a place where
her disability was celebrated instead of shot oh yeah yeah I mean it's like if
you're a woman if you're a woman with a beard you don't get to go work at like
a regular people place you got to go to the circus where they want a bearded
lady they need yeah yeah sometimes you gotta go where everybody
streaming the circus also known as twitch yeah that's the circus of the
modern age that's that's I wonder if there are like bearded lady twitch
streamers oh but there are bearded ladies that stream on twitch probably you
know what I mean I mean I suppose with the rise of the the trans you know
awareness there's probably quite a few I'm not talking about a trans thing you
know you had they had bearded ladies in them in the in the circus no I'm with
you I'm with you I'm just saying how they probably migrated to twitch probably
more common than ever considering that's where people go to get their
entertainment now you ain't wrong you ain't wrong I feel like I feel like we
just accidentally created a dug standout bit wait a minute wait a minute now now
I'm wondering though yeah try it like trans culture like gender culture being
what it is I wonder if I wonder if bearded ladies are just have like a whole
different like outlook now I wonder if that's I wonder if I wonder if they
would probably just maybe just go ahead and identify as a man certainly pop I
mean who like do we know the specific like gender characteristics of the
bearded ladies I'll bet some do I'll bet some do but I bet not all of them do in
fact guarantee it guarantee not all of them do some people are probably just
like I'm yep I'm a woman and I got a beard and it happens and don't even
worry about it and follow me on twitch.tv
Ben saying all right well whatever enough of this bullshit we can go on
forever why don't we get to the voicemails already
unless somebody else got on top of it I wanted to bring up there's one time I wanted to bring up that I want to ask Tom because me and Ben on the endless war anniversary stream we played a
zoomie game oh yeah you know about that yeah yeah yeah we played we played a
zoomie so it was really cool been sucked at it been it wasn't hey Tom no I don't
suck your fucking controls are fucking sloppy it's fucking floaty it feels
like I'm walking on ice all the time and had to get back to fix it to play the
game okay slippery controls that's all I have to say where is a zoomie game going
from here what's the future of it look like it like I know you talked to me I
don't know if you said it on anywhere probably not in games but you said you
you've thought about making like a 3d game do you have any plans for that now
this is like a proof-of-concept way do you want to you want to work in the same
like you just like build levels on the same like engine all with all the assets
you've made just can have a sequel or what are you what are you thinking um yeah
I mean it really it really depends on like the reception of the game cuz like
it's only been out for a couple days I think like maybe a little less than a
week at this point and I'm still doing like a little bit of updates and shit
that like I increased the I increased the reach of the sword due to feedback
from the voicemail in the last episode and things like that so I did a little
bit of tweaking here and there but I mean if it gets like big and people are
really into it I'll probably start building it out and adding more levels
but like the end goal has always been to make a 3d character action game with
Izumi and like get the knowledge to do all that which is like insanely
complicated and over-the-top and will take years and years and years to develop
if the people I'm looking at who are doing things like that is any
indication to go by so I got to learn more about 3d like modeling to make
like better models that'll animate and deform better and then you got to learn
like animation and rigging and how to get the skeletons and stuff and then you
got to learn like all the coding that's and then it's just a huge fucking
process to do like a full 3d game like the engine I did Izumi in was not real
programming so you can do it really quickly that's why I was able to do it
like you know two or three months to get it like builds like the groundwork of
it so like at this point like I could go on to build a full game with it because
the majority of like the foundations there like it just matter building more
enemies and building more levels so I could probably do a game in a full game
with that style not super quickly but it would most of it would just be like
conceptual work of just like how do I want the levels to be as opposed like
having to learn more things to make it happen yeah so yeah I don't really know
so obviously okay so the end goal is a 3d game but obviously there's a there needs
to be a big leap in your ability wait wait wait the end goal is a 3d game not
a 2d platformer yeah I mean like like obviously this project was just like a
learning a learning experience but like I have like a whole big design document
for the final 3d game and I know the entire story and all the characters and
all that shit so the question is and I doubt it's the case but is this the last
we'll see Izumi before you just go away into a cave and like read a bunch of 3d
modeling textbooks and how to pull it pull a diva pull it I don't think I can
pull a diva just because I would go I would go full diva if I had money but
I don't so like to go to do would mean work a full-time 40-hour job and then
just not talk to anybody and do game stuff on the side I make no money it's a
solid plan to do such a thing so I don't know I just feel like like
DeVu made this fucking amazingly sick game and it's great and everyone should
play Automatus if they haven't already um yeah but agreed the problem with the
the going full DeVu is that like you have no base to be your evangelist to kind
of get it out there do you have a gay working for Digi of course that he does
the whole time right but what I mean is that like DeVu because DeVu doesn't
have a sweetheart deal and it is a good deal but like because DeVu has no
online presence really anymore like by his own design like when Automatus
dropped it was basically up to us to let people know it existed that and and like
I would want any like project that I do to have some semblance of success so like
it's not a matter of just building a big 3d game it's also like building a
brand around that game so like when it happens people give a fuck and that
requires constantly sucking the social cock and like making sure people don't
forget about you so like you can't just do one thing really unless you're
super god-tier talented which I don't think I'm at that skill level you know
what Tom I think I'm gonna argue with you on this because I think that's
something that a trap that I fall into is spending too much time on you know
sort of like ancillary side things you know just trying to like you know keep
keep keep up to date with people keep in the public eye you know be be streaming
on Twitch be like you know tweeting on Twitter liking people's liking people's
tweets you know being on this fucking show or whatever you know and like I
don't I don't know I'm like I've done a lot of it and I wonder like how much does
it like past a certain point how much does it really well do you think
like I don't think I don't think that being on the show anymore is getting my
name anymore out there than like it already is you know I mean it's both
theoretically if you dropped off perhaps that number would recede somewhat I mean
I just wonder like if I think I don't think if you just worked on the vapors
and that like and didn't talk to us and didn't do any of that shit and just
worked on the comic I don't think if you did a Kickstarter probably would have
succeeded as quickly as it did or if at all well you know your audience would
have been much smaller I mean what I would do I think there's a third path
here I like theoretically of you know ghosting and then just releasing it or
you know constantly maybe hyping it up or just keeping people like I'm a big
believer in like basically like release parties like a pomp and circumstance I
mean this is kind of what like like we Agua one sorry I mean sorry like like when
I did me a math I mean like that like I prepared media to come to make it an
event and I think people you know like I prepared a theme song ahead of time and
I prepared like you know art for obviously you've done that already but
like something and I am aware that's totally different from like a comic
release like a game release a totally different thing but I like I would do
something along those lines maybe like construct a website for it and to like
not even when the game releases but like to let people know the game will release
on this day like maybe it's already ready maybe it's and I this is why you
know they announced you know Final Fantasy 15 like eight ten billion years
before it actually comes out or whatever and then you know they keep you
interested with trailers a good strategy for working on a big project's gonna take
years and years because I watched I followed tons of indie game devs and
obviously we don't have the resources for all that jazz it's just documenting
your progress you know and like yeah like that becomes your content like if
you just let everybody know what you're working on daily you know there's like
there's an artist minions art she's working on a game called Astro cat I've
been following her for like two years and like I don't even know how much
progress if any has been made I just know that it's being worked on okay they
do they do that in tutorials and make thousands of dollars on patreon or how
about how about our beloved our beloved yandere dev right oh I don't like seems
to have fallen into a bit of a trap of yeah yeah actual game design development
someone someone who decided to not learn about proper programming is well you
know he is among other things I'll take his word for it wait who's yandere he's
yandere simulator yandere simulator it's like a question I don't know it's a
game that people liked and streamed on twitch and on YouTube it actually got
banned from twitch because it's too too edgy too saucy that's correct really
there's like there I guess maybe I don't think he appealed but they said no they
don't want it on twitch so I mean he's been through some issues but I'm gonna
get on D live not you know not even to shit on the model but like it does seem
like a potential trap like I don't know when you're a pull up when you're a
politician the trap is to like be corrupt or whatever when you are a game
developer using crowdfunding to support ongoing development of your game
there's probably gonna be some pressures to like you know why why rush it you know
this is going pretty well I'll just sit here and you know maybe goof off a little
bit not work as hard but to the contrary that point there also is gonna be
unbelievable pressure on you all the time to get it done and that's also I'm
just saying that for me that far outweighs yeah yeah yeah oh I got
because like for me my brain works like if I'm not releasing something I am a
failure once you said that there will be a game my only question for the
developer from that moment on is when do I get to play it I don't care about
anything else I want to play this game that's been prophesied and promised to
me so yeah it's gonna be a tricky spot same like a movie I guess or anime when
can I watch it it's tough cuz like you're doing like I if I could I would
love cuz like there's a couple options I could go full divu and just make a big
3d game and just like drop off the face of the earth and just do nothing but
CG cookie tutorials for the next like year and a half yeah get become God and
just start building this huge game cuz that's like what m.strange it is right
and he's like my big like inspiration artist guy he's been working on this
big platformer game for years and like every like seven or eight months he'll
resurface and be like here's a vlog k bye and and that's it and like I don't
know what he does I don't know how he makes money time job he must I don't know
he doesn't he's never talked about finances even when I press him because
I've talked to him you know one-on-one for it and he refuses to answer that
question about how he makes money crowdfund development of his games no
he's never crowdfunded ever so he must so he must in some he there there has to
be something right but he just refuses to like you know let anybody know how
it's done probably to like keep his air of mystique up because he just seems like
this guy who like fishes doll heads out of gutters and makes movies about them
because that's what literally happened with his first movie but um like that's
one option another option would be to keep making smaller projects build up
the brand and get it to a point where like if I asked for like hey I want a
programmer and a you know a soundtrack designer and like work on a team with a
bunch of people to make a big game and I have the cloud to actually attract people
to do that then I could offload a lot of that work right and focus on like the
creative part that I'd like actually enjoy the most which is like that's a
long game so right but it's I mean it's all a long game like to make a full
3d action game even if it's just like at ps2 level like a ps2 game still costs
millions of dollars back in the day you know full development teams make so
yeah and now you're doing it by yourself so you're like it's probably like a five
plus to your project easy and that's after I've learned everything so like it's
just like such a moonshot project I don't even I don't even have enough skills
to know to quantify it yeah I know what I'm a boy with a dream you know that's
that's it I know what I would do and it's because what I did do it's like I'd
work a full-time job or whatever and just like do it on the side I that's just
me that's just me I would prioritize like my financial stability with the goal
of eventually being at once like I've I've checked my boxes oh Nate you and
your ridiculous dreams about financial stability you and your crazy
seems like more of a moonshot than making a video game to me at this point yeah
I can't even I'm just saying it seems like our generation has just said like you
know fuck life I'm just gonna make art and if I die or I don't know like you
guys are literally what I said I think I've literally in the mirror like
looking at like looking at myself like like like like peel like peeling down my
eyelids to look at like and like my red eyes and stuff yeah and like shaking
dandruff out of my hair I've been like fuck life I'm just gonna make art and
if I die from some like sociologist guy and I don't remember the specifics I'm
probably gonna mangle this but he had this theory that like the the last four
generations have perfectly mirror the four generations before them and how it
sort of goes in cycles how like you have a generation who's all like who's all
entrepreneurial and then a generation that's all political and then a generation
that sort of detaches and becomes artists and then a generation after that
that sort of does whatever the fuck and how it mirrors so and like the I think
like the millennials were like compared to like sort of like I don't fuck it
remember like the lost generation from like the 30s like before yeah okay and
and the zoomers the new silent generation that's fucking fake news I
mean I think the greatest generation it was an interesting thing so whatever I
mean I mean I mean I would read I would read that article I would read that
article because that doesn't surprise me that like it seems like a that you
know yeah cuz like each generation is a response to the last yeah yeah in a way
so yeah I mean because everybody everybody says that like to go on the
the social media thing I had a thing I wanted to say that oh it's right here I
found it sorry okay link it like in the in the link link link that show while I
speak Strauss how a generational theory and I'll link it word cool the social
media general like a presence thing and and like either social media or like
working full-time on the thing going a full devout which I like this phrase I
don't know how he will feel about death of the victim I feel like so much like
having a social media presence is it's like the more you put into it with the
less you have to show while you're into it the less effective it will be like if
you have one game and you build your social media presence it making a brand
will be so much easier than if you have a game in development or no game and you
try to build a social media presence because people will want to follow you
but you'll need to have something and so you'll have to create something for them
to gather around even if that is just like you as a like a personality or a
vlog or whatever so but then they will become accustomed to knowing that thing
rather than what you actually want them to like in the future which is your
products your games your art your webcomics and stuff so the more stuff
you already have doesn't matter whether it's like the best thing you'll ever
make or your magnum opus the more stuff that you can link to them when you do
the social media or like like a press tour you know like how people go on to
to talk shows and say yeah I got a book out you know that that's the sort of thing
I think is the best way to do it is to only be social when you have something
to tell everyone you know and if you you know is the perfect example like the
on that far side of the spectrum who gravitated from content less social
media and then just completely flipped Spoonie of course is drifted over time
and just flipped those two to being zero content 100% social media interaction
that is the most taxing on the viewer's patience I mean that's kind of
different because I don't know what Spoonie wants I assume he just wants to
kill Donald Trump as I understand it and God bless him in his quest like he
clearly doesn't want to make videos anymore but he's an internet person
now so it's kind of difficult for him to leave that but like it I feel like it
would be worse to have build a following that likes you for certain things and
then when you release the you finally have you know you've spent half your
time social media half your time on the thing so it's taken twice as long and
now you finally released it and your audience they're not not necessarily
going to care about the thing because they know you for something else yeah
you know perfectly real on the subject like I'm perfectly aware of kind of how
I'm taxing the patience of my audience many of whom have expressed in no one
certain terms like okay Nate Gurren Lagann reviews are really good when's
the next like good project coming we're all we patiently waiting Ghost in the
Shell was how many years ago that was announced any day now would be real nice
Nate so I mean I feel I feel this tension as well yeah I mean in the few
in like if it continues in whatever fashion your audience will be comprised
primarily of people who care about we Agua and when you drop a big video they're
gonna be they're gonna watch it a little bit but it's not gonna be the thing they
were craving so you gotta think smartly about like what kind of audience you
want to build and are you doing that yeah with your shit so yeah it's a good
point yeah I mean the issue like I think I mean Nate I mean you you can
probably relate on this cuz of what you started doing with those big reviews is
that like in a perfect world you could do that and be fine you know but like if
you're trying to like build an audience online like everybody now with social
has like the attention span of like a goldfish like if you're not like throwing
your face in their face and like letting them remember that you exist
they'll just move on to something else because like no one's starved for
content you know so like unless you're at like the super high top tier like top
5% of just like raw ability that every time you do something it's like a
fucking bomb going off in the social media landscape yeah like you can't
really just like disappear and only come back like every year or so with
not good enough you will be forgotten I've been working full-time the entire
time I've been doing it now but like maybe not the very beginning but close
to it and yeah like those original projects while I was working like took
six months to make so like yeah that's totally unsustainable for that although
I mean I still believe that like those guys like like John Tron's videos I know
he's already got a big following but like they get kind of an unbelievable
amount of views when one drops and I think people just love the production
value but you know what never mind he's a terrible example because like he's
already basically made it and people already love I mean there was there was
a time when you could do that and get away with it I just think yeah starting
now like it's impossible I still I don't think it's impossible but I think the
bar is significantly high yeah it's yeah it's it's very very very difficult and
like so I'm just like being realistic with myself is like I don't have that
kind of ability you know I'm not that good yet so I would have to either you
know get a job which is not as cut and dry as it sounds just because the way my
student loans are when I get a job I'll automatically lose over half my paycheck
just to increased bills so like I have to juggle the fact of like and then my
my tax return I start owing way more my taxes because like there's just the way
taxes work with like some self-employed income on top of like working a job
because like when I did nothing but do patreon and made like no money I got
money back but the next year when I worked full-time for like two-thirds of
the year I owed like three grand so like doing all that math out it's like
getting a job might actually make me poorer and not richer as fucking weird
as that sounds yeah so like like it's it's and you're not gonna figure it out
for like a year until you get fucked on that so it's just it's a cluster fuck it's
really real at the bottom of the like the income tiers there like I just
actually yesterday have like this huge list of like all this different like
content I would have to make like like podcasts and videos and like a YouTube
channel and like all this stuff on top of making the game just to like be
relevant and like have people not forget and it's just like a huge it's a huge
undertaking like you have to be a brand today you know I'll just come out and
say it Tom I mean I I think you should stay on the podcast here I think that's
going great I'm happy to have you as all that big most of us are like if I had a
personally give you my recommendation I would say find some decent job and do it
on the side and like and then you have total freedom like I think the podcast
keeps you relatively in the public eye you know hopefully you can earn enough to
escape that trap again I have no idea maybe I'm talking out of my ass oh he
was just talking about getting a job making right but like I don't like he's
got a degree in graphic design or something there's probably something out
there that's pays well I don't know maybe I'm totally wrong and there is no
opportunity for it I keep I keep thinking about I keep thinking about what
if I what if I tried to land a job doing something that like a studio or
something or what if I what if I could like storyboard something that'd be
cool I have no idea where to even begin yeah I mean I've been thinking about
because like I have to learn programming anyway and I was like I actually asked on
Twitter yesterday like because I know Python is a really in degree in demand
language I get a programming job like I'd probably be able to like escape the
bell curve and actually like get a net positive I was doing something beyond
like flipping burgers or whatever yeah that's oh my god oh my god as as a as
opposed to you know escaping the bell curve what you want to do as it says
now you're begging people to ring that bell you the bell is omnipresent in your
life but just depends on how you you know you treat it if you want to skip the
curve then you got a job but if you want to stay in presence ring that fucking
bell below his video right damn now everyone we're all we're all trapped
under that bell ain't that the truth bring that came crashing down well I
don't know Tom I I hope I didn't sound like I don't know I don't know I mean I
think about all this all the time yeah it's always like juggling
different calculation is it would be great to have a job if it would make
things better right that's pretty much my point yeah well if it would make things
better right right now well I don't know life's hard we're all gonna die hey
viewer hey viewers tell me tell me where I should tell me where I should
apply to be like a storyboard or something yeah what do you got people dude
fucking do something universe dot com do something useful you know this this goes
against a lot it's been built up in the PCP well maybe not I'm sure I'll be
guys like it but I'm like excited to have like a normal job I think that will be
cool at least to do for a while that like pertains to art in some way I think
I'll be really nice and I'm just looking forward to it is all I gotta say I I get
I get excited thinking about the prospect of being like a storyboarder I
think if I could I think if I could have a job for like a studio I would like or
like a real job like that's what I would want to do I think that sounds great and
I know people do it but like you know I think those jobs are really in demand yeah
despite like for like a real lot of Cal Art graduates out there looking to draw
a whole bunch a whole bunch of people with more art with more art art you know
education with more degree you know then the degree the degree might be to
somebody's edge but a website that hosts one's body of work could I don't know
perhaps that's even an evening factor if you've got actual I mean it can't hurt
right it can't hurt certainly not of course not anything I mean I don't know
if I was hiring I would just want to see that they like had like I don't know
who's better that that's what they say that's what they say like a degree
doesn't mean anything if your portfolio isn't impressive like it's all about the
part yeah yeah all of it when it comes to the art I hear that it's all about the
portfolio it's all about the portfolio and it's also not in like the like
interview since like whether you're my job but in order to get into interview
it's more important to have like connections you know I wouldn't want
the degree itself does not help you I mean I'm just having the people like know
like where to go and what to do my only connect too bad my only connections are
you free that's fair although I mean like theoretically if I was like applying
for like a managerial position somewhere you know what I do I would cite my
experience like not running purely but like doing the account like they quote
unquote running the PCP like I get everybody together for calls you know
doing all the account work distributing pay like on a relatively
consistent basis of a couple days here and there but you know and I'd like to
think that people would like I would show them the income like this been
generated and then when people like whoa there's actually like some decent money
here this isn't like a little bullshit baby diaper poo poo pee pee adventure
you're having on the internet here well I wouldn't go I wouldn't say that it is
bad let's not go over for it that's fair but it's just classic instant laughter
that's all you got to do ladies and gentlemen put that down in your comedy
portfolio put that on your resume I mean so I just my point is like for your
application to clown college yeah like all the stuff that we're filling out
right now right in the show for years and like running our own YouTube channels
and all that stuff I like to think that it could all be leveraged as to show that
at the very least that we're go getters in various capacities so I often sell
myself short when like explaining to people what I've done like I brush over
the internet stuff when I really shouldn't I should think of like a way to
say it more normally I think that's the struggle because the amount of work I
have put into my YouTubeing stuff is so disproportionately high compared to
every other pursuit I pursued in my life that like an employer should know
that like you have that kind of I mean you just have to be honest yourself and
just like yeah I'm running a business yeah I'm an entrepreneur and like you
always you always see like that guy who like talks himself up all the time and
like you kind of think he's a cock and he's annoying like oh I did this and I
did that like I was watching an interview with Enzo Amore who's like a wrestler
yeah and he was just talking about like everything he's got going on like super
positive about everything like I'm the coolest guy in the world man I can do
this and I like like well that's a lot of accolades he's building himself up as
having but then like when I think about it I'm like wait a minute who's to say I
couldn't just say that about myself and say get myself all those accolades that
I do have I have done a lot of cool stuff I just never say cuz I I never
like act proud of it cuz it's yeah that's that's that's the way you sell it
shameful but if I wanted to I could just as easily go around and just like you
know like train my brain to be more of like a go around every day like hey it's
me I'm this guy and I do this thing it isn't that fucking cool and said I'm
just I go around every day I'm like don't fucking talk to me leave me the fuck
alone who the fuck are you get out of my fucking way I mean it reminds me of a
little bit thing I've heard Tim Poole say a few times which is like just when
comes to selling like here I got something to sell you guys
Hydric acid please sign my petition Hydric acid has been known to kill
millions over countless lives it has it poisons of people have been known to
ingest it and die over a certain amount you know it's ruining environments in
certain locations it's displacing entire populations and Hydric acid is
water so let's ban water let's ban Hydric acid boom I got you all to sign
the position you've been finessed and outgenious by me cuz I'm just is it the
dihydrogen monoxide that's the one that's the one yeah it's no good it's no
good for anybody but it sounds scary cuz it's got the word acid in it and all
those things are generally true so yeah I mean salesmanship is everything for
something like that I think our whole generation needs to talk itself up more
and like there's a lot of like I want to die jokes about millennials and stuff
and this is why I roast I feel such strong contempt for every Twitter user
with a self-depreciating Twitter bio I when I see that they're like I want to
die I have no skills it's that the funny have to like there's a self-deprecation
economy you have to put yourself down or else people say that you're an ego
you know I mean people like that claim about me too I am called the best guy ever
but I don't know I hate you talk yourself up and talk proudly about
yourself at all the only people who hate that I call myself and so amore yeah
while I was watching his interview being like man this guy's really he's done a
lot of cool shit people hate him because he has the nerve to say yeah I'm great I
do great shit what you can't you know who you know but you know who hates them
yeah fucking losers if you're hated by losers who fucking cares I mean that's
there you should care because there are more losers than there are now there's
can still be customers made of losers losers are the majority vote what they
think about you is all that fucking matters in life because they can and
will destroy you all you have to do is get to agree with you I mean as soon as
the internet was created as soon as social media became a thing the world
was irreparably taken over and co-opted by losers losers are the driving force of
all society the driving force of your life they will destroy you if they deem
that you're not as much as this guy is successful right like he's clear he's
got all this shit going on and it is working so like how how effective is
the cries of the loser masses other than like a smear campaign before they like
oh but this guy we got to take down next you know like again attention span is
like not because everybody hates him I mean yeah but like if enough people hate
you then they can just fucking lie about you and then that's it doesn't matter
what you've done your career is enough people enough people yes but I mean if
you are able to build yourself enough of a shield to avoid that that's one thing I
mean for me the biggest hate I feel like I've ever gotten was on my fairy tale is
dead time to dance on the grave that's the only time I really remember when
people to this day still get mad at me for shitting on fairy tale and being so
excited that it is dead and this thrills me and they're like best guy ever more
like worst guy ever am I right ladies and gentlemen of the jury you should you
should be proud you should be proud of shadow I feel proud I feel very much
proud but no don't let don't let anyone take that away certainly not certainly
but like but that's the if I just I don't know let's say I made a video saying I
love Star Wars the last Jedi it's my favorite movie and that makes me feel
good that the things of this movie happened these events transpired then
you know like yeah good man you are the best you can be like that kind of guy
who you can just be like oh I don't mind the haters I don't pay attention to them
they don't matter yeah you can tell yourself that and you can even believe
that but it's not true the haters do matter if they matter something about you
then that's you that the haters matter but like I mean I object I feel this
about myself I just don't feel I generate enough haters for it to be a
problem and that's that's at least partially by design like I do try to not
come off like an asshole all the time so you know that that's a tactic one can
take it might perhaps it's inauthentic to some people though and like they just
are more acrid in there in their day-to-day so maybe that doesn't work
for everybody to still feel like they're really being themselves but I mean I
just don't feel like I get that much hatred or anger on the internet because
I'm relatively easy to talk to or get along with I don't know tapping you know
I was so I was at this thing I was at this this comics thing and you know they
were like you know new people introduce yourselves and you know he got to me and
I'm like you know I could like what do I say like I say like you know you know I
should say I'm on a podcast so I should I say like I got like I'm on Twitter I
got like oh I got like thousands of Twitter followers like should I say I
got a comic at well I could say I had a website or say you know I was thinking
maybe I should mention that like I did the successful Kickstarter last year like
that's a thing like that'd probably be around and finally I was just like I don't
want to as like as like you know if you know they'll find you know you know what
maybe they'll find out about this later you know better better to undersell now
and have them like learn impressive stuff later that might there's stuff that
might impress them later so I was just like yeah my name is Ben Saint I make
comics on the internet I draw and I write and make comics on the internet I think
that was my whole thing I was like you know what the line between more can more
can come out later more more info can can come to light at a future date
where is the line perhaps being proud of yourself and if I didn't work it like
it's in the mind of the moment I guess yeah and everyone's different and
everyone's stupid yeah well that's you're not allowed to be proud of yourself
as my point you're just not allowed to have any pride in anything you do at all
or else you're an egomaniac and you're an asshole and your piece of shit and
you're I definitely feel this a lot because like like I I find like I do
this to myself like I always my brain just kind of mentally downplays
everything I do as a defense mechanism because like like raw like gross
egotism revolves me so much and so I overcompensate to make sure I don't come
off as that but then I just come off as pathetic so it's like you got to find
that balance yeah I mean that's the true your own self if nothing else I feel
the opposite I want everyone to be an egomaniac I want people to just be I
want everyone to just be like I'm great I like I want to be confident I want to
have pride why won't you fucking lose right it's the most powerful thing
everybody down to your fucking level you were like fucking crabs if you can
give me like a choice between like do you want skill or do you want confidence I
would absolutely take confidence because I was confident I can I would believe
that I could like build my skills and I wouldn't follow through and actually do
it confidence is the most powerful weapon in the entire world and it sucks
that mine's not up to par yeah I suppose I feel like I feel like an APS
adventures dot site to read a really good webcomic bail Jake with a fucking
animation coming out very soon I've been and it's really good and I like a dangerous
game to be saying stuff like that why I need I don't know I mean well all right
the animation coming out soon dangerous understandable but it is like it's not
going to take I mean I've been saying oh spelljeeps nearly had done for a long
time but I didn't realize what I was going to do at the end when I first
started saying that and it has changed but now it has got to the point where
half the line art half the keyframes and in-betweens are done and it will take
relatively less time to finish the second half of it and then color it in all
right well cool I'm thinking I'm thinking like you know a month and maybe maybe a
month from when I say this and it'll be I just I just like to keep mentioning
that I have a webcomic because I feel like people like I appear on podcasts
and people just don't really know it's good yeah it definitely feels like
obscure hippo it's it's that I don't know I feel like it goes back to sort of the
thing with the website where it's like APS adventure that just sounds like oh
hippo one day decided to do it for fun and he made it like a homestuck clone
because it would be funny to do on stream and people don't like take it
seriously I feel like you got to push it more for people to and try to make it
more interesting they'll take it they'll take it seriously when they see the
animation because it is sick and a lot of the shots I've already finished are
like oh that's so good I will talk about talking about that's the good thing
right there yeah talking up good stuff you've done I mean it's not done yet
obviously but now we will be he's working out right now I mean I derive
almost all of my confidence in life from the fact that I have done the things I
just think back to like I don't know I don't know like when I was younger it's
like man like I don't know talk to this girl I don't know what she's gonna like
me and then I'm like oh yeah remember that time I fucked that bitch I could do
that again let's just talk to this girl no problem and then I do and you know
it's okay and I'm not saying that makes it super easy or anything but it just like
it's like I just think back to when I did the thing that I'm about to do before
when I think back the things I've done I think oh god I'll never be able to do
that again maybe that's the difference right there it's like it's the focus on
the positive or the negative I don't know I feel like I was just like I was
born with like a natural confidence like I think I've always just naturally been
confident but like my entire life all anyone's ever wanted to do is just crush
that confidence out of me and my whole life I've had to stifle myself and
stifle my true potential and my true greatness to try and fit in with the
rest of the fucking meat sacks walking around here who just can't handle anyone
being proud of themselves for anything I just want all human beings to die all
everything's got confidence because I'm sick of them I'm sick of them holding me
back holding each other back it's all they're good for every once in a while
beings are just worthless and should all die fair enough but you know who's got
comments and doesn't deserve to die commenters on my galco video such as
the one who just commented who left this comment galco Chan who I praise endlessly
in the video galco Chan is literally me just in blonde it makes me happy to
finally have an anime representation this person has the right kind of
confidence to make in this world they see themselves as a shining god all I do
is endlessly talk up how wonderful galco is and here's a person like it's
literally me incredible just stupendous as always YouTube commenter with that
said I said I gotta go in like 40 minutes so I would love to move on to
voicemail yeah yeah I just want to get yes or no okay Tom I feel like I asked
this question but I didn't get I didn't get an answer so are you continuing to
do you zoom me in any way like are gonna make a game yes or no or undecided or
undecided Tom I think Tom stepped away he must have stepped away for a
minute Tom just oh he said BRB came another person yeah yeah it's not it
sounds like a weird like I think I think he took off his headphones unlike it was
the playback coming through his audio or something I think he's gone full the
right I just got hold on is there isn't I'm confused is Tom maybe not
continuing 2d is zooming wait yeah I'm asking Tom are you can I listen all I
want is yes or no question or undecided are you continuing to do me as a game
are you just gonna stop a zoom me until 3d happens or you're gonna continue it
just kind of keep the consciousness away the public consciousness aware of a
side a little 2d thing and I will I will be continuing it if for no other
reason than to continue using it as an exercise to get better programming and
stuff God bless voicemails okay there you go all right first let's check in with
our quest as ever to find the pizza party podcast let's see what we've got
message from I I don't know I just I think it might be a fool's errand but
now it may be let's check in with I don't know if it'll ever happen
has some update for us so let's see what he's got you people make me sick to my
fucking stomach although I actually have sick for unrelated reasons you people
are actually going to waste innocent lives on this stupid little quest to find
this supposed podcast sacrifice everyone you're the only person who's
aware that this thing even exists but since you don't know where it is how do
you even know it's real to begin with now since you have faith real you have to
become the pizza party podcast Ben think about this way I can't I don't have the
glory than the real podcast don't have a pizza and try to stop you oh that's
true they'll have to expose themselves to you and you'll find them that way
huh fair hey you know what this reminds me of Tim Poole just is filing like a
lawsuit or something because he's got like a he's like his branded content
it was under like the heading subverse and like a week ago or two weeks ago a
porn like website group of developers launched a Kickstarter for a porn game
called subverse and who knows if it's like intentional to like fuck with this
guy I mean I don't know if they've had like some interaction in the past or is
it just a complete coincidence and like the result the search results have
completely crowded out Tim Poole it smashed like a bunch of records on
Kickstarter it's got like six hundred thousand dollars right now or something
and the term subverse has been completely co-opted by this point what's the
original it's it's like the the website that Tim Poole does like for news or
something don't yeah that's like the gist of it it's like it's okay like this
guy Tim Poole is like an independent journalist it's like his news YouTube
basically that's it so I don't know like so that it did trigger a response from
from Tim when this person made this other thing so if we just go create
okay so I will so I will I'll just have to start you know I'll just have to start
doing a segment that is the pizza party podcast the only podcast called the
pizza party podcast on the internet that's the selling point and I mean I
got I don't know what it'll be about like pizzas I don't fucking know like your
review types of that's gonna be dude oh you know what first episode of the new
and improved one and only pizza party podcast I will review Arlo's low-carb
pizza crust recipe that's a good idea and if that falls through I'm uniquely
qualified if that falls through you can always do like train like railroad
track reviews and go click-and-clack down the track okay next up we've got
another another piece of party podcast related this is from hide the podcast
robot okay go
hello procrastinators it is I hide the podcast robot I find it only fair that I
inform you of the fact that you will never find the podcast me and my elite
team of automatons will stop at nothing to obscure the location boss I found
someone who is trying to say where the podcast is kill them that's like all we
do why do you need to console me on this well I thought like maybe whatever you
thought was wrong this will come up in your next performance review leave
well PCP I'm off to go suck the spines out of humans who know the location
was ill-offended can watch out God God God God speed you're doing God
it's gonna be an absence of spines in the man maybe I don't know I find the
part yeah that's true we've got actual enemies to fight against now and our
ongoing I don't I love my spine well I wouldn't say you might say I'm kind of
attached where I keep all my spine goo they can take my spine my spine's been
broken for months and I don't want it anymore fuck it they might be doing
here's but I'll find the Pete I'll find the pizza party podcast and I'll
convince them that you're me and they'll suck your spine out that sounds
fair and then I'll be on Scott let's do it okay we got another one this is from
proud the greats the great spine okay so here's our first real voicemail it's
proud echo quotes Jew ham boy so proud ham boy let's let's see what this is
about I thought it was odd that Ben was so focused in the plight of the Jewish
people a few episodes ago so I decided to do some investigative journalism I
hacked into patreon.com flash Ben St. found a list of his top patrons Gal Gadot
Jerry Seinfeld Woody Allen the list goes on it's just as expected by God Ben's gay
liberal outrage actually just a Zionist dog whistling we also see it I
could have told you that all you had to do is okay that's some good that's some
good what happens we don't brag about your people get confused to what your
true motives are okay we've got another mail from some engineer hope they
engineered a good mail hey members of the PCP cheers from Columbia I wanted to
develop a actual PCP bot that will be able to take some scripts and convert it
into an actual audiophile with your generated voices during to sit you can
share it some of your clean audio with me or maybe I could take it from some of
your videos but it will be ten times easier if you could give me some of
your I do folks I will leave my mail or additionally I could message you on
this court although I don't use it that much additionally I hope you're doing
well and I hope man the best for your family I'm not used to a genuine
there's no ridicule there's no there's no joke it's just like hey so this guy
normally it's exactly the sort of thing I hate which is him asking me to do
anything but luckily we've got a solution which is the editor contest like
files that we produced you know several episodes I don't like two months ago now
or something that were in those episodes you can just use those files and that
doesn't have every single member but there's like six or seven of us in those
so go grab those from a couple episodes ago this requires no effort from us and
all on you which is exactly how I like it would that be any or with which I
mean which episode with it's in the description there's links to the editor
contest stuff so if he looks back at the lat like go like five or six episodes
ago and then maybe go back one or two you'll find it quickly it's there
somewhere maybe if I'm smart I'll remember to put the link in the
description but probably not by the way the editor contest is a thing that is
yes that that's true votes have been tallied and we are in the process of
talking to yep that's correct everything's going swimmingly it is
progressing smoothly we have actual ranks of people and stuff now so expect to
hear updates very soon everybody keep your ears peeled okay next one is from
fat fuck faggot let's hear what this guy has for us
I have been destroyed it's in the line it's in the it's in the works please you
call you called it though you you meant you called it earlier but I bet you
never expected to be asked by this no by this towering but this towering model
of a highly unprecedented to be asked about that yeah one of these days just
just one of those days okay I just put it I had a sick you did I respect him
yeah I also just really love digitally altered low-pitched voices they're
really funny I agree completely it's different it's different it's different
it's different from having like an actual baritone yeah sounds like deep
throat or you know the only thing you have to do to get on the voicemail seat
please just have a voice modulator well okay we created and then finish it with
a kazoo solo we've expanded the list of like you have to end your song with the
music you have to like voice modulate throughout you have to like I don't know
play a character you have to zoom zoom zoom on or off the stage or whatever
there's speaking of which we haven't heard from a riddle my ass Batman has
could his reign of terror have come to an end it's possible it's possible let's
check back in with him in a bit but first let's hear from fabric man who's
who's calling in to I don't know say some words I guess do something yeah
I would just like to know given how I created the pcb when I can be let back on right
well Kevin we got your portfolio we got your your interview like shut up my
fabric maybe let me um
he's positive oh no is that it okay he wants to hear about fabric and he wants to be invited
back on the pcb which he created here here's what I gotta say about fabric it's dumb it's dumb
fabric don't care for it oh I remember oh hippo you know what I like you again
for a moment that you were my sworn enemy yeah but but but but but then but then you
quoted sweetie bell and I and I liked you again wait is that a sweetie bell quote
yeah remember dumb fabric no I don't but that sounds good what's the one with the dream is that
the one with the bad dream no it's an earlier than that it's like season two I don't remember that at
all dumb fabric she was she was trying to learn how to to be like rarity to get a cuny mark and
oh that was sister who's social isn't it no no it was when they were trying to make a
like a put on a show a show okay and everyone was got got the wrong job
okay so it was a CMC episode okay I'm with you I'm with you oh and they had that terrible rock
concert oh dude it was great it was a dude um that was like the worst no no it was fantastic
okay apparently skooloo's voice like or say you apparently skooloo say you say you uh uh recorded
the song and stood to hasbro and they're like this is not bad enough singing you have to do it
worse please do it again oh that's good that's good yeah wait okay so I'm just so that show has
been dubbed in Japanese I assume you mean her English voice actor not her Japanese okay yeah
just check it yeah well I mean I don't know what I don't know if there's another word other than
say you so there's no that's just the limit remember how dope and squeaky squeal uh fucking
sweety bells squealoo uh sweety bell's voice was that was great that was great work loved her
okay anyway moving on uh yeah before she hit puberty and then she wasn't that's exactly right
I wanted to say which I was just saying when I thought his voicemail ended but no he just was
silent for no reason yeah that's correct uh uh uh we we we have your we have your resume Kevin
we're looking at it over you know you have a great shot so you know we'll let you know we'll let you
know what the old yaki yaki said might become canon real soon your portfolio frankly blue yeah yeah
yeah you are talking tinder trust me it was unbelievable uh next voicemail is from an individual
known only as hap birth so uh let's see happy birthday to you happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear homestuck hey happy birthday to you just in time I'm having a birth babe and the baby is you
I can't wait until hussey decides to remake home stuck in HD yeah that'll be exciting home
there won't be any like pixels on screen it'll be it'll be fully anti alias
yes I can't wait for that it'll be it'll it'll be like you know when you when you play like um
when you play like a ds emulator you can turn on like a setting that will like smooth out the
pixel edges and it looks really weird it'll look it'll just be that yeah okay next voicemail is from
what do go hey pcp yo i've been trying to make content for years but i delete everything right
before it's finished out of sheer hatred from my own work what do i know that you have to stop
you have to stop making these
uh i think we all have an idea yeah i have an idea stop deleting it okay what you should do yeah
when you find yourself in this situation okay like i know the feeling of like completing a project
like 90 percent and then that last 10 percent you know generally like takes 90 percent of the effort
or whatever like just for the sake of the exercise forget the quality forget the art you're making
you all you have to learn this skill just finish it because you like swore on your father's grave
with his samurai sword clenched in your hand that you would finish this project and then release it
and just detach yourself from it being good or not finish it specifically to grind the skill
of finishing something let that be your motivation exactly exactly nate uh ghost in the shell best
anime ever best one correct that's it yeah that's that's the thing yeah literally do that uh it is
it is definitely a skill to finish it is you are in you are in the you are in the bad mental habit
of deleting stuff of working on stuff not finishing it and then deleting it and you gotta you gotta
break that you gotta break that habit in your behavior so like if you're you gotta practice
you gotta practice a better way some people worry that like their projects maybe they're like a
little bit older than other people or something they're like oh man like people younger than me
by contemporaries are already so good like if i start just for example like drawing now it'll
just be like embarrassing to release any of this like stuff now you gotta get over that you have
to get over that because if you're serious about it you will improve rapidly and uh you know it's
like the you gotta generate the first thing the first thing that you put out will be bad no matter
what yes but the 50th thing you put out might be good and the 50 so get there as fast as possible
unless you put out the first thing exactly that's a great way it's like our boy jake said sucking
it sums the first step to being sort of good at something yep exactly uh yeah that's that's the
way you gotta break that mentality uh okay that's those that that's what do thanks for the call next
is uh michael reeves theory uh i i i have i have pcp email like no figure yeah yeah on my phone
and i saw it so i was like we can't wait to hear that well let's get into it here we go
oh my fucking god you guys i think i found something pivotal something extra ordinary
important today on the podcast monchi mentioned some guy right nobody knows about him michael reeves
right no one knows the next day next day she releases a video right it's called if you can't
drink fast enough this cup tastes you great video 10 out of 10 but something but something very
important happens on exactly 51 seconds in of the video let's hear it oh my god he's a procrastinator
oh my god he's a procrastinator he's been out he's been out we got him boys
entrapment successful we've captured it i love i i love the like like he shows his evidence he's
like oh my god member our procrastinator confirmed i like i like the voicemail's enthusiasm for it
yeah it's great uh i'm excited too this confirmed like guys i didn't want i you know we didn't want
i have it be you know we wanted to have more pop in circumstance but you know we're invalid
michael reeves official 10th member of the pcp you know we're like 13th member now well yeah good
good enough close enough we did it we did it last 14 15 something like that i've lost track
um welcome to fold good to having the family uh next up is uh the all new gender inclusive pcp
how exciting uh go all right it's 2019 and i feel like it's high time the pcp expanded its
spectrum a little bit uh introducing the all new gender inclusive procrastinators podcast
with members like best person ever hippo switch munchie wears a variety of hats them
saint digi friend lethal aurora vage tommy all of them hey
thank you
gender inclusive procrastinators podcast oh it's gonna be here it's good to be here i feel
purified i didn't even understand the jokes of her um i mean you know tommy all of them all all
genders right female day and day yeah we've eliminated the gender binary completely uh
it's antiquated and to hell with it now well well now we'll finally we'll stop alienating everyone
oh wait no we said retarded and faggot in this episode well and that's a hundred percent of our
audience those two groups it's a work in progress you know yeah we'll work on it little baby steps
this is lord if we if we flip the switch completely we wouldn't be uh we'd be ignoring the spectrum
that we're trying to respect so we have to ease into it slowly all right here's what i want if
you're trans press one the comments if you're gay press one of the comments if you're if you're
straight unsubscribe this is our call to action for everybody yeah uh okay next up is an urgent
message to munch lax uh let's go here we are i'm not gonna like this hello procrastinators
as you can hear the water behind me uh you know that i've taken a vacation to pony land i was
deeply hurt by my message not being read on the last procrastinator's podcast however i'll stand
strong and i'll stand strong in my message that you munchy can in fact join the tcp as you do meet
the age requirements set in the tncp rulebook it states that in order to become a member of the
tncp of true zoomer you must be the age of the anime girls that digibro wax off to
the thing i didn't realize they are all actually 18 years of age that's right baby
you spearhead on we're all in we're all in be the parkour dude to our deagle nation
what do you think send me a link send me an invite give me the address i'll punch it in a map
quest and i'll fucking sprint to your location as soon as i hear the call i am ready i'm willing i
am prepared to fight for the zoomer cause we are the new silent generation but we shall be
silent no longer guys drop the sandbag guys drop the sandbags on it right now go into preservation
mode i i love the tcp so i know oh my god guys let me in we'll record a podcast i'm not joking
we'll do it you whoever you are mr teen man spooky voice teen we'll do it together we're
it's we're gonna have the the the teen cp ill happen send me the discord immediately and i will
so glad that the munchy i can't wait you're gonna feel so old you're gonna have a taste of what it's
like to us you're gonna you're gonna you're gonna you're gonna you're gonna suffer as we have suffered
oh my god okay all right all right i i will do at least three episodes of the teen cp at least
three and then we'll do our contract i'm locked in now send me the discord link right now well
shit it might just be you and him so far but maybe you get that's fine that we'll get more
members we'll get more we'll get more it's fine fantastic uh okay and i don't i don't i don't
like this i don't like it a lot i like it a lot well i don't know if it'll be able to top that
but it's time once again boys and girls to check in with her old friend riddle my ass batman once
again no he's back his reign of terror continues
holy i can't think i want anything to say batman i'm picking on the supplies now
i'm being generous batman how to say we'll give you an easy one this time i don't take the easy
mode of life riddler give me the hard one give me a strict hard mode name riddler very well riddle
my ass very well batman riddle my ass batman pilot pilot pilot she's kind on the pcp everyone
says please be interrupting me tell me batman who is she it's wait do you say she yes batman i
said she but i took the pcb was entirely opposed to dudes i don't know this one
five four three two one no uh cold corona batman i've been here the whole time in the furnace
room
his life is in your hands
the minion what is her me may just a girl
no it's okay i don't have this yeah that was a plastic there's a there was she was having an x and
a pcb to the next time to find out same pcb time same pcb channel yeah god god batman dropped the ball
really fucked up batman is a fake fucking fan
i fucking know what all batman thinks he knows all the deep lore that such as mage is a girl but
um batman if you're so smart what happened in pcb episode 200 i mean uh 75 what did we discuss
what did munchie say in that episode question now batman tell me in comments that's what i
thought smart guy you got nothing to say uh yeah bring out the fucking gun bring out the fucking
gun shoot him in his eyes each one all right ladies and gentlemen that's it leave us your
voicemails at the speak pipe link down below click on that and live as your voicemails because
they're just getting better every time so up your game batman sure hope you don't become
blind as a bat bang bang oh shit dead has no eyes anymore the old bullet in each eye trick
every time patreon.com slash the procrastinators five dollars for 24 that's two full years of
bonus episodes and uh one dollar to join the discord get in there support us we'd appreciate
very much more podcasts to come next week we'll be back with another one more fun
discussions about all your favorite things how exciting we'll see you next time ladies and
gentlemen
suppose
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't wanna do it