This episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast was bought to you by our bonus episode.
Go to patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators and pledge $5 or more to get access to all our bonus monthly episodes.
The last month's episode was impromptu Q&A.
Hottie Creek says, why would you do this?
Well, the answer to that is of course, I don't think it's funny and it's annoying.
I don't get the joke there for it's not funny there for Ben.
Oh, you're gonna police humor the world now, Ben.
Yes, Nate, what's your criteria for what makes a joke good?
If you say it in a funny voice, that's all you need to do.
I can feel the pressure building to smoke weed and I don't want to.
That's patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators, giving you a bonus every single time.
Hello and welcome everyone once again to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am your guy, old and boy, Nate Bestman.
What's going on everybody?
And we've got Tom Oliver here.
I am now returned to the podcast with 10% less spying.
Hey, there you go.
Boo Spine.
My skeleton is officially banned from the skeleton war.
It can't participate anymore.
All right.
Well, you thought he was spineless before.
Wait till you see that.
Yeah, you don't even know.
I suppose the spine jokes are just far too easy.
I'm super spineless too.
I'm about to go kill the cell juniors now.
Let's go with time.
We've got Ben St.
There he is.
What's up everybody?
Welcome to the working class.
We got Nate Bestman here.
Yeah.
Feels good.
Feels right.
I'm below the poverty line.
We've got give and take.
There he is.
You may have heard some baps, some booms just because I'm getting shot at right now by a fireworks demon.
So sorry if that happens in the future as well.
Tell us more.
Damn it, Mulan.
Is that it?
All right, great.
And we've got Digi Bro.
I'm the real Ben St.
It's all a ploy.
I've been running for years.
It's been one big troll on everybody that I am making happen.
I'm the real Ben St.
You are just an act I've been putting on.
I can talk out of both sides of my mouth at the same time and do two different voices.
That's how we're on the same podcast at the same time.
What about the times when you've been in the same room together?
What happened?
What's going on?
I'm Shadow Clone Jiu Jitsu.
There's a little known new technology.
It's known as GUI-G.
It was a GUI-G maneuver.
Haven't you ever been to Disney World and been on one of those rides where they project the ghost images onto things with planes of glass?
Yes.
Or simply a hall of mirrors.
Ben has simply been a mirror, like a warp body shape mirror.
For Radcom 3, we warped out the double-wide rounding mirror.
I mean, think about it. Do you really think Keto works?
It doesn't.
This whole transformation on Ben St. is probably just tweaked the algorithm a little bit.
It was just a chain of curvature.
Yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
That's all it was.
Quite a subsurf modifier.
It's like when you're in front of one of those mirrors, when you just squat down and it completely changes your body shape.
It's like that.
That's why they say you got to do your squats.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It all makes sense to me.
Got to adjust that focal point.
A lot of stuff's happened since we last talked.
Yeah, guys, have you seen, I'm going to post it right here.
Have you seen the new Pokemon leaks?
I saw the blue one.
Whoa.
I've seen some.
This is good.
These are beyond anything I ever expected.
Oh, no.
I like them.
We got debt.
These are the best Pokemon leaks I've seen in a week.
And that's annoying.
Boy.
It's like when a quadruped turns into a biped, but it just keeps going and he turns his flips back on.
So he's got his belly up.
And then the other one is platute and taplu patuta.
When a Pokemon of the last type is like really different and annoying and sexual.
Just becomes a guy.
Yeah.
That's why it's hard hitting Pokemon commentary.
When Ken Sugumori runs out of ideas, just make it a furry.
Just make it a furry.
Just do it.
I did happen to see what seemed to be fairly legit looking leaks of the final evolution of the main guys.
Were those?
I only saw what I believe to be the sobble.
Same here.
That was the only one I saw.
Was it like a tall, thin looking motherfucker?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
I trust nothing until I see officials.
But these are official.
These six images here.
Everyone was saying in like the immediate wake of the reveal of the starters that sobble would grow up to be a spy.
And indeed this one I saw looks like a spy and it looks like the official artwork.
Why was that a speculation?
What is about...
I don't know where that came from.
I mean I heard people's...
It's because he went invisible, right?
Yeah, but there had to be more to it than that.
No, no, no.
Spy from TF2 goes invisible.
Same thing.
You're overestimating the creativity of the internet, Ben.
I mean, sobble is just sob and wobble.
I remember seeing people be like, okay, yeah, it goes invisible.
It has like a cloaking mode and the idea was like it starts out like shy and it becomes like secretive but also like confident, right?
Like it becomes like a...
Sure, sure.
I don't know.
But it's still.
That's true.
I like it.
I think it looks like it is true and it's cool.
I do like it, but like there had to be...
Because I saw that speculated on a lot in lots of different places.
There had to be more info that people had because that was everywhere.
That was all over the place.
That was the word on the street.
It seems like there's a thing they're trying to do now of like having an evolutionary line have like an evolution in personality.
Like with the owl guy, the grass owl, where he starts off as like a pompous like a...
Nerd fucking...
Well, he's like a...
He flips his hair and he's like, I'm better than you.
That's not the owl.
The owl is like a sphere.
He's like, oh, watch me, the owl.
Your owl starts as like a dweeb and then he becomes kind of like a fancy boy.
Yeah, the second form is like a prince guy.
You know, he literally like does the hair flip.
Sure, sure.
The anime thing.
Oh, I think a Google house code from Log Horizon.
I mean a little bit.
But then when he gets to his final form, he's like a total badass.
He's like, oh yeah, fucking...
I have truly lived up to my noble lineage by actually becoming cool.
Which is why he should have been in Smash Bros.
We need a grass type starter Pokemon to be a fucking to complete the set.
God damn it.
What, two fire boys?
Charizard and Infern?
And to Plupa Tuta.
If only Charizard was also fire fighting type.
If only.
He does fight in battle, so I guess he is.
Everyone.
Every Pokemon of fighting type.
Retroactively, every Pokemon who's ever been in Smash now gains a third fighting type on top of whatever it was.
Seems fine.
Note to the editor as we wrap up this Pokemon discussion.
Do not put Pokemon in the title of this episode.
Correct.
No need for that business, no need for that.
I literally only brought it up because of my funny drawings that I made.
Those are good.
What?
You drew those?
I thought that was the least.
Oh shit, I gave it away.
What the fuck?
They look so convincing.
Do you like the bullish on the man?
Yeah, that was really what sold it.
I was like, that has to be legit.
You see, in my head cannon is that actually the body of Plateaut becomes the bulge and then the rest grows out from the bulge.
That really recontextualizes the whole design.
That's unfortunate.
And it just grows a new, completely separate head.
I get it.
Well, I mean I just heard...
The fucking monkey, drum guy, that's fine, whatever, who cares?
I don't know.
I got to look at the fucking, I want to see...
Okay, here you go, here's what I got.
It's in the gross disgusting whatever.
This is what I found.
You got the water guy, you got the grass guy, I assume these are real.
And I know I saw the fucking fire one around.
It was just like a soccer, it's like a tall bunny, I don't know.
Everyone said Grookey was going to be a drummer.
Yeah.
Naturally, naturally.
That's...
I think that's one of those drum guys.
I think that's cool in concept, I don't like this design.
I'm not a big fan.
I like it, the drum guy.
The drum is a bit strange though, it's like a log that both has Tom Tom's on the top
and is a bass drum as well, kind of.
What else am I looking at here?
What are these other fucking things?
Those are like meows, evolution or something?
Okay, that one on the bottom left definitely does not look like a Pokemon and I do not believe it.
These could be fake, I don't know, I have no proof, you know.
Those meows are...
They don't make any sense, what would this be?
Like baby form meows?
Like a different type of cat maybe?
They could be split evolution or something.
Yeah, I mean that would make sense I guess.
Is that a farfetched with just a really big leak?
Oh my god, it is!
What the fuck is that?
Yeah, that's definitely...
That's got to be baby form.
No, there is a real thing of the galolan farfetched.
I have seen it.
Galarian.
So that's what they meant by leaks, I get it now.
Oh shit, but the evolution of farfetched is I think totally sick.
I'm gonna say that this is probably just Galarian meows and an alternative evolution,
because they already gave Zigzagoon an alternative Galarian only evolution.
Which is sick, oh shit.
Yeah, yeah, Zigzagoon evolves into Galarian, Zigzagoon evolves to Galarian.
I mean if that's what this is, I like this meows and it's weird evolution.
I like it, but I don't know why so many meows.
Yeah, fuck meows.
Meows already has a doubled special.
Why would meows evolve into something that isn't a Persian?
I don't fucking know, because it's a generic cat.
I'll defend that because nobody likes Persian.
I'm not upset by it, I'm just wondering what the reasoning behind it will be.
Polytoad is like the most, why would you have a triple evolution that is a tadpole,
that never stops being a tadpole, but I still find polytoad a very weird creature.
He's clearly meant to represent the wasp of youth and how you want to cling on to it, you know?
Yes, he's a man trying to...
You're saying that polyrath is an incel.
I'm saying using a water stone, you're forcing him to grow up
and he's desperate to cling on to his childhood by not fully forming the role of an adult.
Funny that a water stone adds a fighting type and not the alternative.
It's because he's fighting against social conditioning.
As opposed to a king's rock where polywhirl or whatever accepts the heavy crown that is the patriarchal burden.
And he takes over and...
Does polytoad evolve with a king's rock?
Wait, I think of a slow king. Shit, it evolves with something else.
Polytoad might take it too, I don't know.
Okay, whatever, someone fact check me on that.
Alright, enough Pokemon talk.
People...
Raiding is poison.
Oh, did you guys hear Toby Fox is making a song?
But I'll tell you what's not Raiding's poison.
Let's talk about climate change.
That's good stuff.
It's bad.
Big fan.
End it.
Let's change the climate away from that by just saying that it's cool that Toby Fox is making an age song for Pokemon.
Toby Fox is making new climate?
Who cares? That's boring.
It's not your fault that that news is boring.
It's the news's fault.
Guys, we have to plant 20 million icebergs by the end of the year.
Oh yeah, that's true.
What if we all went out and planted a little ice cube from our freezer?
Dude, yeah, just turn the fridge on.
Just turn the fridge on, put it in the water.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It'll make infinite ice.
We're just going to do what they didn't do to trauma.
Just keep dumping ice cubes into the Arctic and it'll all be fine.
It worked in that one scene in Summer Wars when they had to keep that big computer cooler.
That's true.
If it's good enough for Summer Wars, it's good enough for us.
I agree.
I insisted upon watching that movie while it was still summer to feel the good summer vibes.
And it was the right decision.
It was a great choice.
There you go.
You guys, too late.
Now it's full time.
You guys see that there?
Did you actually have something you were going to say?
I've got quite a few things.
I do.
Yeah, Has been Hotel.
You guys see Has been Hotel?
I did watch Has been Hotel.
Yep.
What do you think?
It was okay.
I think.
Pretty okay.
What I think is that me and Nate made an entire hour long discussion video about it that
you can watch on our new channel, Cantant!
Epic.
That's right.
Link to below.
Do that.
It was pretty good.
Would you want to spoil what you thought of?
Wait, how long is the podcast?
It's like an hour long.
How the fuck do you talk about Has been Hotel for an hour?
Well, there's two of us.
Think about who is doing the podcast.
That's why.
That's true.
Their job is literally to be long-winded about things and make money off bad revenue for
it.
That's true.
Let me talk to you guys.
Oh yeah, go on, go on.
You know, my favorite PCP discussions are always to shop talk.
So let me get into it a little bit.
Because I have discovered that, I mean, we've all probably heard before that like YouTube
promotes you more based on watch time rather than view count.
Not to mention you can stick more ad breaks in, which I'm a big fan of.
Yeah.
I don't do ad breaks because I have a Patreon and I feel like it's a conflict of interest
in a way.
I disagree, but okay.
I put ads at the end of the videos and the start, right?
Which, by the way, if your video is over 10 minutes long, make sure you put an end roll
ad because it will, you're just making more money and nobody cares.
Make complaints about the end roll ads because they usually stop paying attention if that
actually gets to the point where it plays.
Or they're watching it in a playlist and it's just two ads in a row, whatever.
But it definitely seems as though not only does YouTube reward you for longer videos
or for play through to multiple videos, but it increases the actual amount you make from
the ads.
If you look at the CPM of videos with better viewer retention, it seems like it's much
higher, CPM being the amount of money you make per 1,000 views.
And so I figured all this out because I was sending Nate all the money for the Shield
Hero videos that we did and they had all made.
At long last, he's done it, everybody.
He has done it.
So you let him off the hook.
Look what I found on Twitter.
Oh, yeah.
There's the fire boy.
Okay.
We'll put that with the other guy.
I still don't think, I'm not convinced these are real.
I don't really like it.
I don't even want to get into my opinions in a serious way until we know the real designs.
We could just be criticizing some fans, shitty interpretation.
That's a fair point.
True.
We should get the confirmation.
But these, I like the blue one and I like the other two.
That's my hot take, everybody.
In any case, so as I was sending this stuff to Nate, I realized that all these videos
that were super long had made more money than you would expect based on the view counts.
And so it's like, if you can get people to watch super long videos, then you'll make
way more money than if you just get them to watch like shorter ones.
Everybody seems to think it's like, oh, 10 to 15 minutes.
That's like the ideal sweet spot.
And I think that on some level it is, but if you can get people to watch a super long
video, that is the real sweet spot.
I feel like times have changed.
I feel like now the longer stuff is doing better.
I don't know.
It seems like that's what's Google's rewarding in the algorithm.
That's what they want.
Oh yeah.
They want people to just stay on the site for as long as possible.
That's true.
If I were to put out like a five hour analysis video.
Because if we're at home watching YouTube, we can't be out unionizing.
Very true.
Speaking of, did you hear about what Google is trying to do to like fuck over the internet?
A little bit.
What, again?
What an unheard of thing.
They're like, they're changing the way Google works and how Chrome works to hide URLs.
So the only way you know how to get to websites is finding them through Google to push more traffic.
I was thinking, I need to stop using Chrome is what I thought when I read that.
People didn't tell me to switch back to Firefox for a while.
I did switch back to Firefox like a year and a half ago and fucking Google is increasingly
making their shit not work on Firefox.
Like everything works much worse than it does on Chrome.
This is why you need to use Brave because Brave is a Chromium fork.
So everything that works on Chrome works on Brave.
Hey, there you go.
But it has a built-in ad block and doesn't track you.
But it looks so bad.
No dude, they updated the UI.
It looks exactly like Chrome.
Okay, well then I'll get it.
Hey, there you go.
Get it immediately then.
Brave.
I'm literally downloading it right now.
Do it.
Yeah, me too.
I've been using Brave for over a year now, fucking rocks.
And it's also on Android.
You can use it on Android as well.
It has a built-in ad blocker for Android as well.
There you go.
Fantastic.
How much of my crypto are they mining while I use Brave?
Actually, do you have a crypto built-in?
Did he was getting to a point?
What were you going to say?
He certainly was.
I got interrupted so many times and now I'm downloading Brave.
You were saying that things from Chrome?
I was going to say that Google's apps continually don't work on Firefox.
No, before that I was talking about how I think the way,
and I could be completely wrong about this,
but I'm imagining how the YouTube logic might work.
And it might be that if you were to post six 10-minute videos,
then YouTube would recognize the viewership of those
the same way they would recognize one view of an hour-long video,
because it's the same amount of time.
So it might be that 10-minute videos are more likely to get a huge amount of views
because not as many people are going to sit down for a super long video,
but if you do make, because I get pushed a lot
of these super fucking long analysis videos.
So there's like five hours of dissecting Oblivion
or that long-ass Pokemon Ruby analysis,
and these things get really good views,
because it's such a defining, like a monumental video.
People are like, oh my god, five hours about fucking Oblivion?
That's got to be the most in-depth video of all time.
Then they go watch it, and they're like,
they'll sit through the whole thing because they want it to have something long in the background.
Just so you could say you did.
I think that's the way of the lay of the land right now,
is to make longer, more in-depth videos,
but I think that can-tent allows me and Nate
an opportunity to make really long videos
that are entertaining all the way through,
and I think it's a perfect for SEO optimization going forward.
Especially I had like a brain blast moment when I realized
that in order for you to get monetized on YouTube,
you have to have 1,000 subscribers and 4,000 watch hours in the last year
in order for you to even enter the approval process.
And I've had several channels that I had to,
if you only make, let's say, a 10-minute video every two weeks, let's say,
then even if you got like 5,000 views on that,
it's going to take a while before you make 4,000 watch hours.
Well, we put out this hour-long Arrow Manga Sensei video,
and it immediately occurred to me,
we only need to get 4,000 people to watch this all the way through
to get approved for monetization.
And guaranteed that's going to happen,
aside from the fact that this is a brand new channel,
unless I promote the fact that it's here,
people aren't going to come here.
But all it would take is like one hour-long video
for us to get just 4,000 views on, and we are approved.
This is clearly what YouTube wants.
This must be what they're hoping for,
is that you make the longest videos fucking possible.
Sure.
It certainly seems to be.
I mean, I guess the question becomes like how,
what they wait more,
unique impressions or aggregate watch time,
it seems like they're leaning more towards aggregate watch time at this point.
Yeah, time on a website or something.
I think because they want people to get addicted to YouTube,
the kind of people who are watching that long-form content
are the people who are replacing TV,
who don't watch anything else like me,
who literally only watch YouTube.
They're going whale hunting, they want those whales,
they just watch YouTube all day and do nothing else.
Can I just make a quick little detour and critique can-tent?
Sure.
I've been saying it wrong this whole time,
I thought it was content as in a play on the word,
play on the word con as in a ruler or king,
and that's what you guys were, you were kings.
Whoa, a ruler or king?
That's what a con is, especially in Asian countries,
being the weebs that you both are.
Asia.
Oh, that's clever.
I love Japan.
It's really funny you're mentioning this,
because May was like,
I hope nobody's going to think that the name is racist
because it has con in it.
And I was like, what are you talking about?
She was like, you know, like Genghis Khan,
because like a third of all Asia is like offspring of Genghis Khan,
which is what, and I was like,
no, we call those Mongoloids, not cons.
I did, I mean, of course,
my association went immediately to,
I'm sure was named after this concept,
con from Star Trek, the original series,
and Star Trek II, the Wrath of the Con.
That also entered my mind.
I immediately went and downloaded that movie,
which I have now, and I'm trying to figure out
how and where I can use that as part of the branding.
Just him yelling con, and then you yell ten.
Yeah, exactly.
I already went and I found the clip,
and I've got it prepared,
of him yelling con in beautiful 1080p HD.
Eric, but I'm trying to think of another clip
of someone saying tent, that I can pair up with it.
I don't think there's a lot of instances in media
of people screaming the word tent.
They're already screaming.
It could be like a one high intensity,
one low intensity, I can make it work,
but I just can't think of, my immediate thought
went to that one anime show about the girls
camping, and it's really cute.
But they speak that fucking Gooke language.
You just gotta get the dub!
I think they dubbed that show.
I'm not using a fucking dub, I hate fucking dub.
We just gotta ask the people.
What's the best example of tent?
Get a guy saying tent.
That's a good idea.
Oh, I was gonna say get primitive technology,
because I never talks in this video.
What about that guy who was trying to make it
all the way through Ireland or whatever,
does he camp in tents perhaps?
Maybe that guy.
He did not in that series camp in a tent.
Well, maybe he did.
He must have said tent at one point,
because he has a backpack with a bunch of shit.
Maybe he can go watch some episodes of Naked and Afraid
and see if they talk about tents at all.
I don't know, something like that.
It's a meme coming soon.
It's a half-finished meme, we'll get back to you.
You'll see the finished version one of these days.
Anyway, that conversational branched off of Has been Hotel,
which I want to say that I think is alright.
I think the worst part about it is the stuff
that was animated a really long time ago,
the music song, the song where she's dancing
and singing about how she wants to make a hotel.
That has been around for a few years.
You can tell there's some spotty animation in it.
It was done by a team, right?
It wasn't just Vizzy, it was alone.
There are a bunch of people who didn't work on it.
I don't know much about it, aside from that.
Just like Endless War.
There's a lot like Endless War, but overall.
Except not in any way similar at all, since one was a TV show.
No, it's basically the same thing.
Yeah, I mean, Vizzy in fact said that.
In the narrative, it's like the exact same turf war
fucking everybody against everybody.
It's just Endless War, but mostly rowdies.
Everyone's a rowdy.
It's true hell.
No killers in sight, I can't stand it.
Although that one Alistair, whatever,
that guy's definitely a killer.
I don't remember anyone's names.
Doesn't matter.
Radiohead.
The writing, it suffers a little bit from...
The end of the end of review, the writing, it suffers.
I just leave it there.
It's all right, it's just...
I feel like when it comes to a team,
it's mostly a team of animators wanting to make an animation project.
Rather than any team of writers, there may have been one or two scripted editors.
I mean, I don't know about you guys.
I sure wasn't grabbed by the premise.
That's my review.
It was serviceable.
The premise is just a little confusing.
It's pretty cool.
It's just sort of like, what is the purge?
Why should I care for shit about it if the demons can't die?
Can they die or can they not die?
Why a hotel?
Whoever heard of a hotel that you rehabilitate people at...
It was for the pun of passing through, which I thought was not worth...
Wait, what?
She says a hotel is for people who are just passing through, you know?
What's the pun there?
Passing through from hell to heaven.
That was the in-universe explanation.
That's awful.
That's just sort of weird because you don't go from hell to anywhere else.
It was like a limbo hotel.
Like you need help to pass through to the afterlife.
I guess it's becoming purgatory now or something.
I mean, can we think of a pun like the words has been hotel, except for a rehabilitation clinic?
Has been hotel is not a great pun either.
Just call it the smite site.
When would you ever describe someone who is dead as a has been?
Being a has been is something you are before you.
Well, okay, here's the strangest thing.
I don't know, did you guys notice, because it was right at the end,
the whole time she's calling it the happy hotel.
And at the last two seconds of the episode, Alistair just changes the name magically to has been hotel with no explanation.
He thinks everyone...
No, he says like all these has beens, all these people who are shit demons and they suck,
we'll put them in a hotel and I'll laugh at them as they struggle to try and be good.
That seems like an even weaker excuse for that.
I mean, I think that what the show is going to be trying to suggest is that like these people all had a chance when they were alive and they failed that chance.
Like Alistair says at one point, you know, these people, they had their chance to prove themselves when they were alive.
And now that they're dead, this is where they're stuck because of those decisions.
There's no way to rehabilitate them because they already had their chance.
So like to suggest that they are has beens in his mind is like these are people who could have been something,
but now they're in hell and they will never be anything again.
I assume so.
I guess so.
The premise of like generally I feel like it came from has been hotel is like kind of like a nice sounding name of something.
I think the name came before the logic for sure.
And like the princess of hell is just like put in there is like that's an obvious protagonist sort of thing.
So that they clearly, you know, you don't need to think too much about why they can do all these things or why they have this viewpoint.
It's just, you know, if anything, I think a lot of the like the messiness in this probably just comes from the fact that the creator had invented like so many of these characters and concepts so long ago.
Because like, yes, you know, we know that the radio demon was like a character she made up in high school and like it reminds me the overall tone of this thing reminded me a lot of this book that I wrote in 2010 called Tales
from the end of the world, which is similarly just like Chaotic City full of gangsters and violence, whatever, with a bunch of characters who I'd made up.
And even at the time that I wrote that book, I had spent like two years continually like reworking these characters, reworking the narrative, changing all these things.
And in the end, it's like this weird, clumsy, uneven story because of the fact that it's trying to maintain as many of the elements that I loved from the original version into the final version, regardless of how the story has changed.
So it's like the story is not built around what makes like the most sense with these characters are in this setting.
It's built around, you know, how can I justify these characters in this setting, you know, and I think on, I don't know.
That's definitely true.
I don't know that's exactly the case with this show, but it definitely seems like these characters, a lot of them probably existed before the idea of the has been hotel existed.
See, I feel like so much that it has potential to be a really good show, but like you'd need to change quite a lot of like the premise as it is now.
Like the fact that it's in like quote unquote hell is like it could easily just be a place like having hell and that's pretty essential because they're trying to redeem demons.
I know, but like it's not like a made up concept because there's so many different types of hell.
Different religions, different ideas of what it is.
So like what you're saying is you could take everything exactly as is and just not call it hell and nothing would change.
Well, you have to change a few things.
It's just sort of like the pilot doesn't do a very good job of setting up the universe because I think they use the term hell and they assume the audience will understand exactly what that means immediately, even though that's not like I'm a little confused.
Because like, yeah, I'm confused as to whether people can die.
I guess they can't.
They can't die.
I'm not sure.
Like is the normal application.
They definitely die in the purge.
Like in the normal world, is it just a normal human world?
Well, okay, here's the thing.
People die becomes grotesque monsters based on the whole premise of the show.
Or does that have nothing to do with anything?
Well, the whole premise of the show is that they have to die because they have the purge to clear out the population.
If they didn't die, it would do nothing.
Then what's the point of hell?
Is the purge a specific event where people get like removed by like God or Lucifer and other than that, they all can't die?
I don't know.
Hopefully, if more of the show came into existence, we would have these questions.
How many years does this take for more, though?
This feels like one of those.
The second episode will just be a long series of justifications for why all these questions don't need asking.
I mean, I feel like this is one of those situations where the pilot is like an episode that is not part of the actual series when it gets made.
Like episode one will be done again.
It'll be different, but the characters will still be there.
I mean, is this fun enough to watch the characters goof around?
And I don't know.
I don't like love the characters, but I like Charlie.
I don't know.
Like Aleister.
You know, I said in our show, our video that like, I feel like he is her like special snowflake OC.
She's had since high school and she's wanted to like find a vehicle for.
She's finally done it.
She's succeeded, but I'm worried he is going to like drive the plot like a hundred percent and is going to be way too like up in everybody's business.
And it's just going to get tiresome and boring and it's not going to, I don't know.
It's the problem with like having a story from, you know, the first story you ever write is shit, but if you continue to build upon like a shitty foundation,
you will have something that looks kind of good, but like deep down is just sort of flawed inherently and you need to scrap it all and start again.
You don't want to do that because it's like a cherished character, cherished world building.
It's your baby.
You don't want to start again, but like you guys should check this out.
Let me introduce you to this concept that Michelle introduced me to.
Okay.
Look at this.
This is the music video for High School Musical 2.
The song bet on it.
Okay.
I'm going somewhere with this.
This is in the audio links.
This is a famous meme song for being so ridiculous and over the top and sometimes give it a watch and enjoy it.
Okay.
So this has long been like a huge Tumblr meme or something.
Everybody loves this, but it's like a huge part of like Michelle's childhood and like her whole generation.
Okay.
Gib can't see it because it's not available in his country.
But no fear.
No worries.
This episode is brought to you by NordVPN.
Gib, you can watch this video.
No problem.
No.
Don't even talk about that.
The Norse people kill the Vikings all of them.
Yeah.
That's fair.
Okay.
But here's what I'm getting at.
So like in the same way that like these like stories of our youth can be like oddly impressed upon us and oddly big memes.
Look at Take a Gander at this video by Tricia Paytas.
Famous YouTube personality like two or three weeks ago or whatever made a shot for shot remake of this exact music video on the exact same like golf course in like Nevada or something.
Just due to it being like such a gigantic meme and she is like a huge YouTuber who just had the resources now to recreate like this meme.
She's playing the character dressed like him with the same hairstyle as Zach Efron or whatever.
And it's just like there are these there are these I don't know cultural milestones that you just get so attached to.
This this movie is famous for like, I guess it's famous for being bad.
This is awful.
What you're showing me is awful.
It is awful.
It speaks to like everyone in the world like Michelle will just like she we watch these because they're so funny to her or whatever.
But but the fact is why is it funny.
It's funny Ben because it the amount of effort that went into shot for shot recreating a professional Disney Channel music video just because she fucking felt like it on the exact same ground.
Wow.
How dare she stand where he stood.
What's what's the joke.
There is no joke or is it like funny because I mean I'm pretty sure Trisha Paytas is like like a living meme like a famous living meme.
She is in fact absolutely living meme and the fact that she would do this.
I mean just to stand back in awe of this but the point I'm getting I'm sure if I was a big Trisha Paytas fan I would absolutely be living for this bed on it remake.
I would absolutely stand.
You're completely missing the point Ben.
I don't think I am actually.
I really don't think that it doesn't seem that ridiculous.
I mean this doesn't seem like an over like it's just they got to the location there where it was filmed and there's a person holding the camera.
OK you clearly lack all the context of this because I just totally will.
I will.
I mean this this is not like on the level of I mean this is a very simple looking video.
I mean I mean to the end of it.
You know what this is.
This is just John Tron renting a cart but bigger.
This is John Tron cart debate.
Chapter two.
Yeah I mean.
Who cares.
What John Tron was doing was recreating like a giant meme with full like professional production value.
Paying a whole bunch of money to do a thing that isn't funny.
Like it's only funny if you know the meme.
Like it's not impressive to me just to watch this video.
You guys are here.
You guys are.
I'm not impressed by this video.
My point is.
Wow.
She sure liked this video to recreate it.
That's where you need to be to understand my point.
I don't know why you're over at.
I'm so impressed.
What's your point.
That's why I was asking you earlier whether it was funny to laugh at this situation or funny because the meme is really funny.
Whether this is funny or not has anything to do with the point Nate's trying to make.
I think.
No it doesn't.
It was pointing out.
What is the point.
That this happened.
That's why it's confused.
The point is isn't it really funny and weird and silly when people recreate things that they were way into when they were kids.
You got my answer.
The answer is yes.
Is it.
Question mark.
I think isn't it.
No.
It's just it's just it's not funny as in like this is entertaining.
It's just like it's strange about the human condition that we can attach something.
Like that was really confusing because you weren't like selling it as that and you kept arguing with us on our terms which made it like we were on the right track but we were completely on the off the right track.
I understand your point now.
It's funny that humanity has got to the point where people do this.
Kind of.
I mean I look at it as just like I look at it as just really retarded.
Like it's the stupidest idea.
And I fucking.
That's correct.
I mean nothing.
Which was probably looking at this gives me nothing but seething resentment and anger that this person has this money and has chosen to use it for something so bad that I know.
Is going to get fuckloads of views and recoup that cost and people will like it and it will just make me want everybody to die as usual.
All right.
Like even with that context it just to me this this specific video does not elicit that at all.
Like I don't I don't feel like it just makes me it just makes me roll my eyes at the waste of human energy.
It doesn't even seem that budget is just walking around and singing which you can do I mean there's a high you know there's a nice nice camera was used you know a day on the set you know one of the funny things about this is that she is a big fat lady.
He was like a skinny fit boy like he puts so much more energy into it and she is like like walking when he's like running and it's it's funny that she's so much low at whatever I don't have to explain this fucking meme it just is silly take my word for it.
I've looked at crunch the numbers and the verdict is strange and amusing.
So has been hotels animation.
I don't I don't know if I really liked it.
That's what I was trying to figure out was how you were connecting this back to has been hotels.
That's what I was waiting for.
It isn't happening.
I'm bringing it back.
The connection here is weird things that people liked when they were young and then they put a lot of effort.
So you're saying we're going to get a shot the shot remake of has been hotel ten years from now.
Why that is funny.
Is it funny because my god that point is not a joke.
I don't know why you guys put a point in my brain.
I just I just want you.
I just want you.
I just want you to explain like I like this episode what you think about this.
The fact that she has done this.
You say that this is working for what reason like would you have rather she did something else like what is what is not at all my personally would have rather she did something.
Who are you talking about.
Trisha is my opinion.
I don't care about Trisha.
My point is that people do people get really attached to things they liked when they were kids.
That's the point.
Your point.
Your point Nate is that your point is that.
Oh god.
I got to set up the analogy that that that radio demon is to Vivzi as bet on it is to Trisha paytas.
Yes.
That's correct.
Okay.
That's right.
The reason I'm so lost in that.
She made the radio demon.
It's not something she liked when she was a kid.
Why does that matter?
What's the difference?
Well there's a huge fucking difference.
I think that is a pretty salient difference.
I mean like if I invent a character.
It's not something that I'm just going to like.
It's not just that I was attached to it because I was young like it represents a part of me.
It's like it's something that has to do with like fundamentally who I am.
Stop.
So what you're saying is there is no similarity between one thing person made when they were
young and thing person liked.
My point is not to say they're exactly the same.
I'll say this is a thing you could both be right about.
And there you go.
All right.
I'm.
Yeah.
I'm interested in the idea.
But like this.
It's just that this comparison.
I'm so sorry I wasted everyone's time.
I mean it's broadly similar.
We're in a podcast pretzel right now.
Yeah.
And Nate is like responding to like the things that we are.
We have moved past or like we like Nate's ahead of us.
Or like this is we're talking past each other.
We're talking about pretzel.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
Nobody knows.
I feel like I know what's going on here.
I am confused.
I want to make this first.
I don't understand anything.
Nothing is funny.
John Tron sucks.
God damn.
Yeah.
Sucks so much.
Tell it.
I agree.
No.
Tell it like it is.
He has a bit of money and he can buy it like a costume.
I'm none of that.
I'm living for this Gib.
I'm living for this Gibbon take right now.
Gibbon hot take.
Gibbons take.
More hot Gibbon takes.
If you please.
Make a side channel.
I just want to repeat something I said.
Because Gibbon was talking about his.
His reaction to you guys talking about John Tron on the last episode in the chat.
And I said if any of us had the resources that John Tron had, we could make things that
were much better, much faster than we have.
That's why I'm not impressed at all with him.
I mean, we had one percent of the budget.
Absolutely the things.
We're like nine percent of the budget for Radcon.
Would they be more popular?
I don't know.
Well, yeah.
Okay.
The popularity is a is a is a fickle thing.
I can't guarantee.
That I would make videos that would be more widely viewed.
No, no, no.
The key to like popularity is to be shit.
If you are shit, you get the views.
That's all it is.
Okay.
Lowest common denominator.
It's as simple as that.
By that you mean lowest common denominator.
Then I unironically agree.
That's not what he said.
He said shit.
Well, I don't know.
I hate everything popular except PewDiePie.
He's all right.
When I do find out a thing is popular.
I do lower my opinion of it significantly.
I feel that happen inside.
Did you ever imagine back in 2012 that we would arrive in a future
where we thought PewDiePie was pretty good
and John Tron was total dog shit?
No, no, no.
I don't sign off on this notion that PewDiePie is pretty good.
What are you talking about?
I mean, neither do I.
I don't watch PewDiePie.
Yeah, exactly.
He's better than John Tron.
Why is he better than John Tron?
Because John Tron is miserably bad.
I cannot watch a John Tron video.
I don't even think he's miserably bad currently.
I don't know.
No, no.
You know what?
He isn't better as a content creator than John Tron.
His content is fine.
The only reason I've cared about PewDiePie at all
is that his attitude towards things is usually on the money.
He's like, you know what?
I like this guy.
And that's all.
I like the person.
The content I could leave.
Very much.
I watched like one, I don't know, I watched like one video of his in the last year
and I found it mildly entertaining.
I have literally never been entertained by PewDiePie once in my life.
So there we go.
It's a totally different, like John's out here making his like crafted jokes.
PewDiePie is like literally just like vlogging and then the editors, you know,
they spice it up, which is, it's fine.
I've enjoyed it many a time, but you know, totally different.
I guess I just have more respect for what PewDiePie does than John Tron.
See, I have more respect for John Tron
because he's obviously putting more work into it.
Boy.
No, he's not.
He's definitely not.
This motherfucker gets out like one video a month.
PewDiePie has a video out every day.
Like, I can't imagine that John Tron is doing more overall work with PewDiePie.
Okay, okay, Digi.
Let me ask you a question.
Now, I can under, I can understand respecting the hustle,
but is it worth it?
but is it worth respecting someone who is literally nothing but hustle?
Like they have no other value other than their hustle.
Look, I, I don't think that's the case.
Like, I mean, I know people who watch PewDiePie.
I get what's entertaining about his videos.
I don't really find them entertaining, but like I look at it and I think,
okay, I can appreciate why if you think this is funny,
you'd want to watch this every single day, you know, and he, he does,
he mixes things up a lot more, you know, like there's a lot of variety.
I watched a bunch of grumps for a bit a couple years ago.
I watched a lot of grumps.
Is it a similar appeal to that?
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, I don't fucking watch PewDiePie.
Like I'm just saying that like what John Tron does, like to me is completely worthless.
It's just like dumping all this money into a void because the jokes are not funny.
And I understand that other people find it funny.
Yeah, that's the thing.
You know, maybe it's just as good as PewDiePie to those people.
I don't know.
Like I look at these John Tron videos, even the recent ones that people did like,
like the stupid flex tape video.
I thought that was fucking horse shit.
Like not funny at all.
I can't even crack a smile.
I just get mad.
Still haven't seen it.
Like I just, as I watch his videos, I just get madder and madder that I see these,
these high budget things being done.
And granted, I do think he, he scaled back certain elements from like when it was really bad,
when he was like on that weird alien looking set.
Like it's, it's not that unnatural anymore.
I agree.
I haven't watched John Tron in fucking years and I don't know this newest controversy is
about, but it just sounds to me that like, like the problem is that YouTube in general
for like people like us who actually care about the platform and like how we got here
in the first place is that it's supposed to be unprofessional, like kind of like dirty
content, I guess, just like clearly different from mainstream.
And it feels like John Tron's production values and kind of conceptualization and execution
of ideas now feels very studio-esque.
Seeing John Tron sort of limp along in his current state kind of just sort of creatively,
sort of like just sort of aping his past self in a sort of ghoulish imitation.
I acknowledge the problem there.
I see the same fault that you do.
But for me to say that, for me to say that PewDiePie is better for me, I would have to
acknowledge that anything PewDiePie does has any actual value and I don't know if I can
make that leap.
Okay.
That's fair.
I don't know.
You know, I had made a whole video and a whole to-do about the fact that like what John
Tron's problem was was that he was focusing too much on production value.
But more so than that, it's not the production value itself that's the problem.
It's that the production value isn't funny and the way he uses it isn't funny.
And like when you watch old John Tron videos, the main thing is that-
The one where he goes to fucking New England was so baffling.
Do you see this one where he like goes to New England?
No.
Anyway, let me finish my point.
That's the joke is that he's in New England.
The thing that made his older videos funny-
That one's unbelievable.
God damn it!
The thing that made his older videos funny was the facial expressions and the way he
says things.
It's the quick zooms.
The-
You know, the fucking wacky Jackie shit.
You just zoom in really fast on his face.
He says something.
It's funny and ridiculous.
And you know, there's some funny commentary on the things he's talking about.
But like-
And he had a bird.
And it didn't-
It's not a matter of like, oh, he raised the production value.
Therefore, it's bad.
It's that he's not doing the jokes that he's good at.
He's doing his high concept jokes that his delivery doesn't match.
His setup doesn't match.
To go back to the point I was kind of making-
It was all in the delivery.
I think the reason-
From the beginning.
Is that like, you look at like, you know, a bottom of the barrel Hollywood comedy.
And there's no good jokes.
There's no good writing.
And it falls back on that like Hollywood sheen production value to make you think this is
a movie.
And I feel like Jon Tron is kind of doing a similar thing with like, I have this budget.
It looks like a real thing, but there's no substance to it anymore.
And it's because he was always obsessed with like, doing a real production, you know?
Like, it's that mindset that I think a lot of YouTubers have always been stuck in of
like, I want to, you know, like this is just a stepping stone for me to do something bigger.
And it's like, to me, it's like, YouTube is the bigger thing.
It's the new thing that is taking away from the old media.
The old media is flawed because of the fact that they are-
They're concerned about things other than making something good, something unique, something
artistic, you know?
And like the best YouTube channels are ones that are just so unique and so in that, like
my recent favorite, I showed this to Nate, is a guy called Steve 1989 MRE Info.
And all he does is review rations, like military rations from-
It's pretty sick.
Oh my God.
From like all throughout history.
That's amazing.
He, I highly recommend this channel.
It's super relaxing, got an ASMR quality to it.
And the guy is just, he has like textbook knowledge of every fucking MRE that's ever existed.
So he'll get like a-
What is it?
What is the MRE?
Military rations?
Okay, okay.
Yeah, so-
Steve 1989 MRE Info, got it.
So like just yesterday, he put out this-
First autocomplete.
He just recently, the other day, put out an hour and 20 minute long video just about this
like set he got of these World War II rations.
Yeah, the 1945 C ration review preserve vintage 24 hour MRE testing marathon.
And you were the worst talk over person on this fucking podcast, bro.
I just think it's funny and it had to be said aloud for the viewer to get it.
This man, if you want to watch him literally eat 75 year old food, this is the channel for you.
And it's not presented as like a stunt eating thing or anything like that.
He like very carefully goes through every single step of like opening the ration,
showing you all of its contents, explaining it, eating the food, reviewing it in depth.
And he's so excited about it.
Like this dude, particularly that hour and 20 minute video because it's like the last known existing
like set of this particular type of ration.
And he bought like this huge box of them and he eats like six of them in the course of this video.
And like they're all just like crackers because World War II rations are not interesting.
They're all just like six biscuits and like some jelly or something.
But like even the slightest variant between the different ones that he opens is enough to make him like,
oh, this is so cool.
Like this is when they started varying them.
You know, like this is the first era where they started adding jam into the fucking thing.
And he's like so fucking excited.
And there's a part where he goes to try to eat this jelly.
But he's looking at it and he's like, I'm not sure about this because when it's these old ones,
he constantly has to inspect all of it to see if it's, you know, edible.
And so he's looking at the jelly.
He's like, hmm, it looks like there might be.
And then he goes and he puts it on a plate and puts it under a microscope and looks under the microscope.
It shows footage of like, like there's moving, like, you know, micro stuff.
And so he empties out the jelly tin and there's like a little hole in the tin and he's like,
oh, good thing I didn't fucking eat this because I'd be, you know, I'd be fucking with the shit later.
Six feet under.
How much leave?
What is fucking half?
What's what's happening?
What's happening?
Internet? Internet issues?
Yes.
How a Steve guy, how much of the appeal of the channel is that the shit he's eating is like some ancient shit
reclaimed from an Egyptian tomb.
He also makes videos where he'll just eat like new modern rations from all over the world.
Just any, like any ration, basically, if you send it to him, he'll do a review.
And they're all just like filmed on a light box, you know, like a basic setup you could make on your desk in 15 minutes.
He's been doing the same setup in his room the whole time, even though this guy gets millions of views.
Like he is, he has over a million subs doing this.
Who is the audience?
Autism level four.
That's exactly literally what I've been saying since I discovered the channel is autism level four,
but also any military nut because like he goes into a lot of historical shit.
I gotta read this one.
This one is called 1957 rations, small detachment, five persons, five man, 24 hour ration pack,
astoundingly unusual, 24 hour MRE and a cigarette review.
Oh yeah, dude, he refused a cigarette.
It is so good.
The first time that I saw him open one that had cigarettes in it, I like the whole video.
It's like, please tell me he's going to smoke one.
Please tell him.
Sure enough, right there in his room, he smokes that cigarette, gives it a full detailed review,
just like the food, geeking out over how good, like wow.
And he has all these like hilarious like catchphrases that he says as well.
But like let's get this all onto a tray.
Nice.
Or next time I'll bring you, I'll be back soon with something old or something new or old.
That's how he ends all his videos.
Anyways, I love this guy and but yeah, I think the audience for it because there seems to be a big community
of people who who like review and trade these MREs around with each other like sell and trade them
because he's always mentioning like, oh, I got to save that because there's a few people who might want this piece.
The original hashtag post food boys.
Not quite.
You know, the funny thing about it, I mean, MREs, they have like real food in them,
especially the newer ones are like really advanced.
And like you could have a full meal because they come with like little fire starter cubes, you know,
that you can use to like cook in bag and stuff like that.
There's all kinds of interesting technology they've come up with to make so you could cook stuff in an MRE.
But they are like, I mean, if you were to buy a modern MRE because they sell them,
you can just buy like literally what the military is eating.
And it's only like seven bucks for one package.
So it's, you know, a full meal for $7.
Obviously, the older ones probably sell for more.
But like, you know, vintage like I've learned.
1963 was a good year.
I know so much bullshit about MREs now after watching this.
I could probably like I've watched enough of this guy's videos in the last week that I could probably tell you
like the distinctions of different eras of MREs.
I'm ready for the MRE PCP lecture.
Yeah.
Yo, did you show me a couple?
But you should check out this one.
I put this in the links down there.
It's this fucking front from 1899 to 1902.
We're talking 120 years old.
This one is a 2018 MRE.
This is a modern one.
2018 MRE pepperoni pizza.
It's a bag.
Oh dude.
That one.
The pepperoni pizza one is one of the most views because apparently that was like something
that the military had been trying to perfect for like decades.
Like they've been trying to get the perfect pepperoni pizza and they kept having to cancel
the project and like change the technology.
And so like people were like.
This is where my tax dollars go towards.
Yeah.
How can we get our soldiers bags of pepperoni?
Well, the thing about it is that like because all of it is about morale.
It's all empty columns.
Fuck this shit.
They're trying to make the ration something that you will be like excited to eat because
this is all they eat when they're on deployment is these rations, you know.
So it's like they want to create some variety.
Excited is distracted.
I need them to be focused on killing.
This is bullshit.
Yeah.
But the pizza in particular, he's talking about like people are so jazzed that the pizza
is finally there and he's like, you know, people are going to be fucking trading these.
People are going to be obsessed with these pizza ones.
But like when he reviews it, the pizza looks like shit.
Like there's no way I would eat it at all.
Like period.
I would not eat that pizza, but.
Oh, what the.
We've crafted.
Okay.
There's some weird.
There's some weird shit on these crackers.
There's like some weird yellow goop on those crackers.
Okay.
Well, let's let's let the audience tell them to the visuals.
I'm pretty excited about.
I'm pretty into this.
I like this.
They're good.
The 1899 one that Nate linked in particular is like the oldest and like grossest thing
that he eats.
And like the whole video, he's going like, what am I doing?
Like why am I?
Why am I subjecting myself to this?
But like he also, he's very particular that like he can't leave a plate clean because
it's like this is all this is all historical artifacts, basically.
So it's like anything he doesn't eat, he has to save.
So if he doesn't, if he's like cooked it and can't save it, it's like, well, I have
to eat it because like, you know, this is this is ancient history.
You know, he's just so excited throughout the video.
Like he's talking about how disgusting this is.
And he's wearing a clean plate club shirt as your music.
That video, I think that I think all of us have like one thing that we've made that
completely encapsulates us as a human being.
And that is that particular video for that guy of just like watching him try to struggle
to eat this disgusting beef from 120 years ago in a boiled porridge.
Imagine being the cow that yielded that beef.
And this is where your journey ends.
What a legend.
This guy's jacked.
Holy shit.
He's pretty ripped.
I think he probably was in the military.
Unlike all the other cows that have turned to shit a long time ago.
This cow stayed in the forest.
Immortalized for all time.
It's true.
In this YouTube video.
He made it 120 years past his expiration date.
Literally past expiration date because it's food.
Nice.
Yeah.
That's the funny thing about it is even if he's eating something from like the 90s,
you still have to think about like this is 25 year old food.
Even if it's a year old, it's kind of gross.
But oftentimes the stuff is extremely well preserved.
They built this stuff to last as long as possible and some parts of these things will
last fucking, they'll be completely fresh like 50 years later.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
Check it out everybody.
Well, speaking of whatever the fuck this whole thing was, I want to jump into a topic rant.
I have about nofap November.
Yeah.
Okay.
The other one.
Fuck it.
Fuck it indeed.
But like also the idea just doesn't make any sense.
And I know why it's so popular and it makes me annoyed.
So the ultimate premise, like underlying like aside from all the memes and the jokesters,
the idea is that people are quote unquote addicted to pornography and they wacker it,
they jacker it all day every day and it takes hours out of their life and they want to like
curb that addiction by not fapping so much.
Yeah.
I mean it's a reasonable, understandable goal.
There's also a lot of things that they say.
Like if you go to the nofap guys who like really swear by it, there's a lot of different
things they claim it gives them.
I don't know if any benefits are worth becoming one of those guys.
I don't think, well the thing is I think that a lot of it is psychosomatic.
It's like if you do something as difficult as not fapping for a month and then you feel
good about yourself because you're accomplishing this goal and so you're like walking around
with all this confidence and all this like yeah I did it and it's like that's where it's
coming from.
I think it's probably the same thing with Keto.
Like people that do Keto and are really into Keto, like me, talk about how it gives you
like mental clarity and stuff and like I don't feel like I've achieved some like super mental
clarity or anything.
Yeah.
But I think some people probably talk about increase energy, increase mental acuity, increase
such and such and improve this and they're like I'm just.
You know I think it might be that some people need to believe that that stuff will happen
in order to convince themselves to do it.
It's like it can't just be that I'm losing weight.
It has to be that like it somehow is making my whole life better you know.
Yeah.
Their belief in the mental clarity grants them a small measure of it.
So like it's, I get it right.
It's fine.
But the idea of doing it for a month, just one month of the year is not the way to curb
the addiction if you actually have it.
You need to do it all the time and the fact that it's like a month that you can, like
I mean people joke about doing dick destroy December or whatever they say.
Right.
Like as soon as no not November is over, they destroy their dick and fap every day.
Like completely.
You will be no fap November and now it's no not November.
When did it change?
Alliteration man.
You know I think it might have to do with like no fap particularly as a movement having
some kind of weird associations in like political landscape.
You think so?
I think it's just that the term nut has come more into common parlance.
I mean it's also like no not November is you know yeah the better alliteration or.
It's made it all the way to Capitol Hill now infesting our laws.
I mean I never heard nut as a verb before couple years ago.
I don't know.
It's kind of new to me anyway.
But yeah I also know that like the proud boys were all like no fap or whatever.
So maybe that has to do with it.
Yeah that sounds about right.
But yeah like it's a silly like cutting off of an addiction like immediately and like
holding yourself to it for a month straight is sort of like too intensive.
Like it's like an exercise.
You need to like wean yourself off of it slowly and then do it for a very long time.
I mean even if you cut cold turkey like it has to be like you said if it's really an
addiction you have to stop.
You can't just play at stopping for a while.
You have to stop like you can't just say oh I'm going to not smoke for a month and
then go right back to smoking.
Yeah that's the thing.
I guess the idea is that hopefully you'll go a month without doing it and it'll teach
you like something about the benefits of it.
That doesn't happen.
New perspective.
You can see the people on Twitter literally just like like Jax played talking about how
because people keep betting him money to do it so he does it each each year and then
at the end he was like oh yeah you have the biggest come in the whole universe as soon
as the month is over.
It's like okay well then this means nothing to you other than an excuse to make a couple
hundred dollars from some idiot who wanted to bet you couldn't do it.
The only the best reason well Gibbs point about it only being a month is foolish but
like the best reason I ever heard historically was just like it will like if you can't jack
off you will then need to go find women you can have sex with which is an excellent motivating
factor.
Maybe.
Yeah but do that do that all year.
Why November?
Yeah I mean you're right.
Nobody's outside in November.
The one month thing is the fools are in there.
I don't know.
But like it's not just all that.
Oh god I'm getting shot at.
It's not just that it's like because people could argue that it being an event gets people
to start and that's good enough you know that's fine.
It's just that the reason it's so popular and people talk about it every time November
rolls around is because teenagers and young adults love talking about sex and laughing
because it's really funny.
Yeah that's true.
Like to bring up November is the big joke of the day and everyone goes hee hee.
Yeah I mean I think it's definitely people are like chomping at the bit to have a socially
acceptable reason to talk about masturbation.
Like speaking personally of somebody who talks about masturbation out of turn all the time
for no reason.
When it's not warranted or appreciated.
Right.
It's often looked down upon that I do that.
So like I look at this and I'm like what the fuck.
Oh so now it's okay.
It's like your gay pride month basically.
We literally spend all year pretending that we don't masturbate and then this month it's
like everybody's making a big deal out of the fact that they've stopped doing it.
It's like okay so that's like implicitly admitting that everyone masturbates all the time.
So can we please just like accept that as a thing we're all doing.
Can we talk about it more than just in November.
Plus that it's just like all the people who do it like say you know it's like implicitly
we were jacking off the whole time.
But all the people who don't care about no fat November just take it as an excuse to
be even more egregious with their sex talk all the time.
Is there a big cultural smoke screen to be destroyed.
Is there a big cultural smoke screen around the fact that we're all jacking off all the
time.
I mean among what communities.
Among like I don't know old people.
Yeah probably.
In society a lot of sex is bad.
What society says.
I think a lot of people especially women don't want to.
Maybe if you go to a fucking evangelical megachurch or whatever maybe you're a Mormon.
No I think a lot of people like don't want to admit that they masturbate or they don't
want to talk about it or don't want to signal it like they're afraid that it makes them
weird.
I literally don't know those people and I wouldn't want to.
So like to me that's like such a foreign concept.
I'm sure you're right I'm sure they're out there but I don't it's not that I don't
believe they exist.
I don't believe in them in the way that I don't believe and say the teachings of Islam.
Well hey there's a great example here.
There's a great example here which is just that so me and Michelle stayed with Digi
for the last couple of days and we saw that glorious shining tweet from Digi that was
just proud to be the first loser of hashtag no nut November while we were you know at
the house and like me and Michelle gave each other a look.
Are you still there when I do that.
Yeah yeah we were fucking there when you did that.
That was our last day there.
So we were just like OK we are now aware that like just a few short feet from us Digi was
going to town you know whacking off and as God intended but you know you don't like to
think about that particularly much.
So I go up to the water cool and said hey Steve I had a really good nut the other day.
You know if we can if as a society we can have like Brazil or Macadamia we have we have
those like breast milk pumping stations like airports where am I like jacking off boost.
What I think is the funniest part about that analogy is that neither of you even thought
for a moment that I was just telling a joke.
You were absolutely sure.
Well we know you so we felt confident with them on this one if I were a funny joke but
it's a real life joke.
It is.
You know how I know that it wasn't just a joke because I know that to you it would be
so much funnier if it were true.
Yeah.
Well the funny thing about it is that I didn't tweet that until like 12 25 because I just
hadn't realized it was no not November.
And so when I got to the computer and saw that I was like oh I'm pretty sure I was nutting
at midnight.
So like yeah there were a few people who responded to me like oh you weren't first this person
cracked.
Oh shut up everybody who says that I nutted right before I tweeted like am I literally
like busting out and then immediately break out my phone.
No at the fucking neither of you got one hand on the dick and the other hand over the send
ready to send like the only reason I was masturbating was so I could make that tweet.
I'm sure for somebody maybe they were thinking about that so I guess now I understand I understand
the appeal of not fapping or nutting or whatever we're calling it whatever the kids are calling
it these days.
Whackering.
Yeah.
Buggery.
Fuck the no nut November I'm all about the Coomer meme.
You are a big Coomer.
I've never identified with any meme character more than the Coomer.
I get the appeal because it's like it takes time out of your day it's a big it's dumb
it doesn't accomplish anything it's a waste of time that could use them productively.
The thing about that is that for the like since I've been working on slime and punishment
I have been fapping like way less because I just want to fucking filled with purpose
yes because I'm because I'm filled with purpose all the time and I just don't I'm like I'm
like no that's not what I want to do right now.
I mean who is out there like going like oh man I really want to get something done but
I'm going to go fap instead like you fap because you you don't have anything to do yeah I definitely
procrastinate sometimes you know but I am definitely procrastinated we need title
drop by being like no I'll jerk off for a while it needs to change it needs to change
from no fap no not November to find purpose November what a better world what if we imagine
if we had a whole month just dedicated to like helping people find purpose well obviously
because that's better because that's hopefully the end goal that not fapping doing keto you
know other other godly godly practices I don't know I mean I suppose should be find purpose
February I would no no it's funnier when there's no alliteration at all the problem with find
purpose February is that you have to try to find that purpose before the 14th or else
you're going to feel lonely all month oh we need a shirt shirt on the on the procrastinator
shirt store first loser of find purpose the ramifications of that are staggering I actually
want that can we get that on the store on this episode drops please yeah we need a volunteer
to go make the shirt but Ben I think you're the man for the job you you you make the art
we'll slap it on there okay sure okay I can do I can make that happen you know we really
got to capitalize when there's a big laugh there's a big joke that's when the wallets
loosen and everyone thinks themselves who I could participate when we all get the big
laugh we're literally laughing all the way to the bank because we all recognize the money
making opportunity yeah that's the reason we're actually laughing that's why I'm really
laughing yeah I'm rubbing my hands the dollar signs appear in our eyes yeah speaking of
what a high note speaking of classic cartoons I did something a little strange I did something
that I found very speaking of classic cartoons yes when were we talking about when the dollar
signs appear in your eyes that's a cartoon thing okay maybe maybe that was a little bit
of a stretch but that's what I was thinking but but it reminded me of cartoons and I was
like I found myself doing this and I was like this is so not Ben core this is so human core
right now but I'm but I'm reveling in a little bit I watched a bunch of Mickey Mouse cartoons
that were really good I don't know I saw one I saw a Mickey Mouse cartoon from the official
Mickey Mouse YouTube channel in my recommendations and I was like huh that's like a more modern
kind of modernish yeah and I clicked it I was like let's see what this is about and I watched it
and it was really great it was a compilation of like a whole season them was like a 20 something
minute video and they're fucking sick as hell like they're super good and cool and have really
like beautiful gorgeous art and like they're super fast-paced and frantic 2016 this one right now
Mickey and Donald have a farm Disney Junior what looks great Ben what what I will I posted
an epic kids June Disney Junior episode well here I'll find what I can post yeah I've been
finding this and smiling yeah wow I'm finding so much material here the dimensional merges
upon us and Mickey will be joining me we will I'll be on Mickey's farm and it'll I'll be there
how fun here here here's a link you you fools you doubt you doubt me you dare to doubt me
I've I've seen this series I'm assuming you're talking it's basically like the hotel of Mickey
Mouse I clicked one just looks like a cuphead ripoff I clicked one and I noticed that they all
had like they all had like a like a regional kind of like everyone took place in like a distinct
region of the world and that they were really going for like a strong local flavor kind of thing
and the ones that were set in like you know I like that looking places a lot of them were like
silent you know those sometimes they were in other languages and like subtitled and I just noticed
this video has like a fairly large down I mean not that big and I was like oh my god Mickey Mouse
is a real cartoon character features and animations in the modern day shots yeah I mean I'm
just saying there's a sizable ish kind of down vote portion is there something people don't like
about this is it cuz it's Mickey or is it too edgy but to it's so fucking edgy edgy yeah maybe
they thought it was a hard and they were waiting for the shoot a drop and it never did yeah that's
probably it I just cut to a random moment where it's like Mickey and Donald and goofy standing
against this like white picket fence and it looks exactly like a shot from Billy and Mandy and
it's freaking me out look at this fucking look at this look at this incredible look at this
incredible fucking watercolor background alright right right yeah looks pretty good yeah good
looking show I'm not gonna watch it cuz fuck Disney I mean I have 100% agree and yet I watched
like three hours of these I forgive you maybe not three hours they're very tightly made like
this they're not like four kids they're not like new Disney these are made by people who presumably
made by people who actually give a shit about the you know the whole animation thing yeah yeah
like you look at this and compared to what what Nate linked and like the aesthetic is just so
superior it's so much well compared to Disney Junior fucking Winnie the Pooh ass looking at that's
like that's like the default style for these characters as they're drawn for the most part
and rendered in like Disney's promotional material oh yeah they all look like I'm more of a Sean the
Sheep man myself a claymation all day she went downhill Bahasa Bahasa Indonesia you know here's
something I'm interested in cuz I'm thinking about how I just said like fuck Disney I'm not
gonna watch this right and I'm wondering how do you guys feel about the idea of like sacrificing
your ability to watch something potentially good or even made with heart by good people because
you do you truly think the funding behind it is evil I mean this is super relevant because
BlizzCon just happened okay yeah the whole big thing when something like that comes up it's
really my my first thought is well if I don't like the company and I don't want to give them
money I will pirate it if I want to see it or play it good here here's okay I think that I think
that I if there was something I really wanted and the only way I could get it was to buy it from
an evil corporation like probably I would do it I don't think I have the I don't think I have
the willpower to be like to resist something that I genuinely crave and desire so the way to do
that a pound of an ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure so what you got to do is preventative
you got to purge yourself of material desires in the first place so that you never find yourself
in that situation well it's consistent my thought process behind this because I was like thinking
about this in relation to Blizzard and stuff the last couple days because like I've always kind of
liked playing Diablo and the new Diablo is coming out and like you know what's on the trailer it
looked pretty cool it looks pretty cool right and and I'm wrestling with it because like fuck
fuck Activision Blizzard like they're just you know the whole blitz channel there's in general
Activision's like business practices for years now has been fucking terrible like body
prodigy as a nightmare so like the the first like gut reactions like oh fuck them I'm not gonna buy
their shit and like the react like people kind of like instantly forgetting the boycotts they were
talking about just like last week dude like I saw people forget about this it was talked about that
like Dick Masterson pointed out that you know all these people were like oh yeah boycott Blizzard
and like the Blizzard stock went down by like two points for one day immediately recovered and it
made no difference right like but they're completely justified you know in in the eyes of the public
of course and that's the whole problem right because like let's say let's say everyone there's a huge
boycott right and and Overwatch 2 does fucking abysmal uh the the results of that are Activision
and Blizzard are fine they have a ton of money but the team who worked on that game is now their
jobs are at risk well this is this is a this is about the Hong Kong thing right yeah I mean it's
that's part of it that's the most recent example but Activision has been terrible I would I would
imagine that like their biggest market is China so like even if there's a backlash I was watching
a video and the actually right now the US market is still bigger but the problem is like okay China's
growing much faster so in a few years yeah but but here's the thing here's the thing most people
outside of of like Hong Kong are not like this is a political issue and most people are not going
to be motivated to make like a change in their life because they they don't agree with what a company
said about this foreign policy issue I mean that doesn't surprise me at all it's gonna have a
fractional impact on outside of Chinese government and it's and like ever and everyone in China is
going to be on board with them shitting on Hong Kong well that the question I have is how much of
that Chinese audience is outside Hong Kong like Hong Kong is the main place that that has American
cultural import like they Hong Kong is the city like Hong Kong is the only part of China that is in
any way similar to America like China is technologically advanced they have like games and
stuff there you know and that's the whole thing like a lot of things Activision and Blizzard
have been doing they've been like censoring their their games and stuff to appease the Chinese market
which happened before the whole Blitzcrank thing I really hope I'm not talking out of my ass here
but I think that Hong Kong is not under the same Chinese government that it is like you know like
suppressing that is like suppressing a lot of like foreign the issue is that China is
Hong Kong has always had like a certain sovereignty and China is trying to take it away
they're trying to bring Hong Kong under the same rules as everybody else which would which would
really suck it would fucking suck for the people in Hong Kong and it would also suck for everyone
else because again like I mean if you have any like Chinese movies you really love probably Hong
Kong cinema you know like it's the most culturally relevant part of China like that's because again
they have that population market wise it it is insignificant compared to all of mainland China
I don't know how true that is because I don't know how much access just one but that's that's the
whole thing the reason why all these companies are are bending the knee to the Chinese government
is that because even though China's market right now isn't huge it's growing the western market
saturated so the next like billion dollar things are all going to happen in China so by
planting the seeds early they can gain control of that emerging I mean the market's got to be big
because you hear all the time that like western movies are made with the Chinese audience right
now because right there's this I just wonder how much of that of that Chinese audience is just
Hong Kong there's seven million by the way Hong Kong you know yeah but how many people there's
got to be hundreds of millions in China there's like billions and billions in China over a billion
yeah yeah though I mean who knows how many are the actual consumers okay but but question on this
point um on the specifics of the story so the thing that people are mad about right is that they
banned like a winner from after he won what I don't know hearthstone I don't know and uh he
wore a said free Hong Kong or something something that alluded to free Hong Kong supporting Hong Kong
against China okay I'm with you now now if they banned him because that was a political thing they
don't agree with okay that's bad obviously well well what if they just they don't they did it because
they did it because it's it's anti-China and China is a big market like the thing the thing that for
them to for them to platform an anti-China message hurts their market are we sure they didn't just
do it because they have a policy of no political yes Nate because that would be fucking stupid
what they had is like a flimsy is a flimsy uh policy which was like no hate speech uh but it was
very vague uh as to what like don't don't say bad things and it was the actual the actual policy
was saying like you can't bring up controversial messaging in a tournament it can only talk about
the game however yeah I'm sure that's their excuse but if he'd said like fuck north korea nobody
would have banned him for anything right because like I mean active blizzard themselves used their
game for political messaging all the time but that's besides the point the thing is like that was
the read they released the whole big article on their blog talking about this um to the American
like western market about why they made this decision to ban blitzhung I had nothing to do with
china but they released a separate statement for chinese social media where they said we're deeply
offended and will always protect the chinese regime yikes if that's if that's as described that is
pretty revealing I mean that's that's what's been going on I mean it's not just blizzard there's been
all kinds of companies right the nba it's all about the market it's all about the market yeah of
course corporations are gonna companies are that sell shit are gonna side with china over hong kong
because there's more customers there yeah but it's just it's really unfortunate that and my question
is I guess is this a failure of self control or of morals in the west like because wait what they're
still a bigger market for these American companies the same thing not exact self control and morals
no they can be completely different like um what I'm saying I thought you were gonna say is this a
failure of individual self control or is this a failure of systemic capitalist hegemony well
that's not what I'm saying so okay forget about that okay is this a problem of morals or self control
because the okay let's say that I am morally opposed to blizzard's decision to to kato to china
however because I god damn it because I lack self control I want to and I want to play the game
I just keep playing it anyway or is it a problem of people legit don't give a fuck that they did
that you know like is it because that would be the moral depends on the person but I think it's
definitely both you know but like which one is the bigger problem that is an interesting
definitely indifference because I every time I've seen people talk about the blizzard thing
there's always someone responding what's the controversy what's going on yeah I'm gonna
or who cares or this is a smokescreen for for other political ideas or some shit I suspect the
jews are behind all of this it's really interesting if you look particularly at the reaction of the
NBA because like what happened there was one guy uh one coach like came out in support of Hong Kong
and then china like threatened the NBA basically like you have to fire this guy or else we're kicking
you out of the country and the NBA initially was going to you know they were they were just like uh
you know trying to fucking get rid of this guy and sweep it out of the rug but then eventually
they came around they they stood up for it and they got kicked out of china and like Lebron James
got into a ton of hot water and got shit on all over twitter because of the fact that he accused
that guy of like basically not thinking before he spoke and thinking about the effect it would
have on the other people I mean he wasn't wrong he wasn't wrong but it was not very sympathetic to
the plight of the Hong Kong people I mean the problem it's not about that it's about the free
speech thing it's like in america our number one value is our freedom of speech if you tell somebody
they're not allowed to you know speak anti-communist values then uh you know like it's like whoa this is
like the most un-american decision you could possibly make would be like fire a guy for his opinion
on another country because you want to keep your business there you know and there were other NBA
people who came out and spoke for the other side who were like uh I think uh Shaq came out and said
exactly what I just said and so like I'm wondering how many like like I think we as americans we have
to look at these companies and say it is not okay for you to diminish like the core american value
of free speech in order to keep your market in china we will not support you if that's the route
you're going to take well it comes down do you value do you value democracy or do you value
capitalism I mean clearly they value capitalism because they're capitalistic banning because banning
this speech serves capital and allowing it serves uh democracy and freedom I mean for you
what is it uh my businesses can do what they want right so I'm curious what what if for example let's
say you had a small podcast and let's say on that podcast just for example you had some people who
started saying things that you don't like and they were perhaps even alienating your audience and you
were losing customers so you made a business decision to remove that person uh is that censoring them
because that seems a similar kind like is it just the degree I think it depends on your your
justifications I mean in the case of blizzard or or the NBA you have to think of it this way it's
not that it's not that the NBA was offended by what this guy said it's that they didn't want to lose
their business in China and China is offended by what this guy said and so like it's one thing if
you're if you're kicking somebody out because you're like okay let's say somebody said I'm trying not
to say the hard R n word on the show because I know we'll lose monetization but that's nothing
to do with moral quandary it's just this is me doing the same thing right now I'm literally doing
what I'm complaining about um I want to keep the money for all of you because I know it will
fuck all of you out of your money uh from the monetization if I say what I want to say but
you know in this specific instance I'm willing to exert self-control so let's say I say nigger oh
shit oh no I win him but if you one thing if you guys were like I don't like that that guy uses the
hard R n word I'm kicking him out it's another thing if like but we love it we could not be more
excited about it here on the broadcast let's say let's say that like uh there was a listener who's
like uh $15 let's say he's a $40 patron right big roller patron and he's like I'm going to quit
this patreon unless you kick off digi for saying the hard R n word then the question is not a matter
of like what you guys value it's about do we value our money over his ability to say that he
what if a quarter of our patrons were like I can't I won't support this unless you you know if you
if you allow this we would have to come to a decision of like yeah we'd have to decide something
do we care more about being able to say whatever we want or do we care more about making the money
and like it'd be one thing if all of us came to a mutual like let's say that you talked to me
and I agreed like okay I will stop saying the hard R n word because I too care about the money
and make it good for everybody you know but like if I was like no fuck that I'm gonna say whatever
I want then the question becomes like do we cut this guy because he's bad for the money you know
and like we shouldn't we shouldn't give our audience ideas that they can unionize against us
but Ben known anti-union organization yes yes the the thought that like that these companies
are are doing like going against the values that they themselves would purport to have
in order to you know sell more in in this foreign market like selling out the values
and literally the people of their country in order to you know broaden their profit margins I just
have to ask like are we as American people not going to do anything to stop that are we just
gonna say this is fine I mean what I mean I mean Amazon shows that nobody cares right everyone hates
Amazon nobody stops using Amazon Blizzard is an American based company right yes although they
are partially owned by Tencent which is a Chinese company yeah okay why a lot of people think this
happened in the first place yeah um fair enough I'm sure that has something to do with it uh I mean
well what could we possibly do other than boycott them right and and people won't do it that's like
like it but that's why the question I want to know is like is it that people won't boycott because
they don't care or is it that they just can't bring themselves to like care enough to stop playing
the game I'll tell you how I feel there's a huge difference between there's a huge difference between
like I don't care what Blizzard does and this upsets me but I can't stop playing I think I'm
gonna I'm gonna date definitely probably most people are just like that's some politics that
doesn't affect me yeah I don't want I'm not gonna take a stand on that because I just the people
the people who just legitimately want to experience the thing I think will probably just pirate it
and call it a day and be like this is a fair enough I mean it's difficult to do that and I mean
you can't pirate Blizzard games they're all online games yeah you have to be in those servers
so mostly I mean you could go to a private service you can't really pirate world of warcraft yeah I
think it'd be yeah I don't know if that's really I mean you you you could pirate and play only on
private servers which you know like before vanilla wow was created that was what that existed there
was a vanilla wow private server but you know there's always a risk of cease and desist you don't
have all the same you're not going to get updates in real time you're not going to have it's also
just not the same experience if you're mostly by yourself well I don't know I mean I think I think
the vast majority of people don't care I think it's just like they'll be like that sucks I think
they care for like in the moment like they hear it and they're like oh that they hear it and they're
like oh no that's terrible but then they get here's a related question which do you think Matt okay to
a to a mostly disengaged person who is like whether they care at all or not at all and maybe
they're like eh but it's not that big a deal they're still gonna play blizzard games they like
fucking was this overwatch was the game was this this was about what game was it was about
hearthstone hearthstone yeah yeah like they like hearthstone whatever which do you think matters
more to them that like they that blizzard did this thing but like blizzard like banned a guy
over this or that like um wait fuck what was the alternative I guess my question is do you think
people are people bothered about that like like not so much about the political issue but about
this player getting fucking axed because I think it's a mix they definitely care more about the uh
the banning because like they're into the yeah the narrative of competitive play that seems like
even if you don't care all about Hong Kong it's that seems just like a really bad optics at the end
of the day it's just in the in the dopamine addled thrill seeking mind of the kumer kumer is gonna
coom at the end of the day there's no getting in between them you can't I can't support I can't
support no not november because unlike other forms of entertainment there is ethical nutting under
capitalism and therefore it should be encouraged every month of the year but yeah like what got
me thinking about all this is just like I in a very general way hate disney like as a corporation
I hate their their slow overreach of fucking taken over all media and just putting it all into one
goddamn thing and so I like this cartoon that you linked I'm like I like I look at this cartoon and
I think man the people who made this cartoon are clearly like pouring a lot of heart and soul and
talent into it I think these are like talented passionate only it could have been not disney
yes I'm not I know that disney made this possible and granted I don't have to feel that bad about
stealing this because it's not like the people who made this are going to profit off of me watching
it on youtube disney would profit off of that so it's kind of like it's it's nice that disney
caused this thing to exist but I don't want to give them money for that because that's
ultimately what all these companies want to do is like the reason they make these more experimental
more art house things like the reason they're willing to bankroll that stuff is because they'll
give it a small budget and they'll recoup that small budget with very minimal advertising and it
satisfies people who would reject the mainstream stuff of disney and like it's so it's an insidious
way to get people onto your side to be like oh well I may hate disney but at least they did this
you know same with like ubisoft like bankrolling all these you know little indie games and it's
like oh ubisoft may suck but they funded this little indie studio to do this thing and we
wouldn't have got that without them and it's like yeah but that doesn't mean that the system isn't
broken like just because they did that doesn't mean that it should be that we need them to do that
you know we we got to create an alternative way of getting these things made so that we
don't have to rely on these corporations to do it some animation studio somewhere had a choice
and their choice was they could do something else they could they could make what they wanted to
make for some money or they could work they could do something else for however much money or they
could do they could animate this they could animate mickey mouse for probably like 10 times as much
money and i'm sure that like it's um fine like i'm sure to a lot of people it doesn't matter
what they're making like a lot of them probably just like to draw an anime just for the sheer joy
of the craft which is fine and i and i don't have any disrespect for that um but yeah like did disney
did disney did come in and with the power of its of its um of all its resources it did scoop up these
people who would have been making something else probably and gave them a bunch of money and now
we have this instead but like whatever else would have been i mean how do you know that they would
have made something that was better well you don't you don't you don't know they would have made
something that was better but they would have made something that wasn't disney that wasn't owned by
disney we don't know like this this animation studio how much of them have like how much they
have gained in personnel based on this like maybe they got a really good writer or like really good
storyboard guy from disney to work with them to make this like it could have been a boon for them
i was it could have been a boon for them and maybe because they got more funding because
they chose to do this they were able to hire more people and like they got a bigger team
and more people were a are are now able to work in this field because a bunch of jobs were created
by this faustian bargain struck by their ceo's or whatever um and um let's talk about this best
guy ever pcb bingo that nature's posted it's funny you know digi let's do that uh but we
gotta move on to the voicemails uh all right let's just cut it off that's one of the things on
the thing that's one of the things on the bingo oh my god there you go aside from free space and
word which i think is hilarious uh my absolute favorite is no my favorite is i don't know i'm
not an expert you do say i can hear your voice saying it as i read it it was magical yeah it's
it's a good one uh although this one of shitting on my dog i defend yeah why are mostly i don't
know you're you're not you're not like the guy who brings up rfc like you you do bring it up
sometimes slime corp every day i feel like they were a little bit strained veil when he was making
this was a little bit reaching for some of them i think like that one i think that should have been
replaced with like slime corp but in the minecraft server i think that's where that's coming from
which way you can find on patreon.com slash pcb minecraft join five dollars a month for all
the minecraft one of these squares should be no like six of these squares should be like really
excitedly explaining something you just learned about like the bare minimum like 101 level
foundations or something like minecraft or the stock market or something yeah yeah sure sure i
feel like i haven't even done that that much uh but nonetheless you did it on the i did it last
time or whatever it was two times ago whatever no was it was it munchy munchy complained to me like
i can't believe nate is explaining he's like he looks like he's just learned what a stock is
he was like well i never owned one i never looked into it i don't know sure sure i mean i know what
i don't take stock and such things per se you know what i will say this i didn't fully grasp
see that this was my misunderstanding i assumed that the way it worked was like if let's say
own a stock in like apple or whatever oh okay great like apple did really really well so my stock
in apple went up okay great but like i assumed it was like isolated to that one business i wasn't
aware of this amorphous the whole market grows that's how we all hope to get ahead as like an
amorphous blob of businesses that are all part of the trading thing i guess the you mean the market
the market or the like a mutual fund whatever we talked about this last time no i'm just saying
that's what i like is is the farmer's market in the small villages where you see all the weird
kooky things and then sometimes they have video games and i see ah that's a good video game but
it's really cheap yeah fresh fresh grown fresh grown from from the farm well i say farm market
i was i was making i was making like a i meant like not a flea market like a village market like
it's just a bunch of stalls of people usually there's a lot of farming like a bizarre uh like
like a like a community yard sale uh you know just a fucking shop you know one of those fucking
just a hole in the ground where people can throw their crap and you can come get some and toss some
money in oh that reminds me that reminds me uh i'm gonna start no shit november where i'm not gonna
that should be no shit september you missed it by a month everything happens on november this is
the new rule okay listen how okay well after no shit after no shit november i fasted for a week
so maybe i'll do no food december or no food february go for a whole month this february i'm sure
people have gone you know i definitely got a month without eating before yeah ben that does seem like
an interesting idea to like fund a community though to like have everybody just leave like
whatever they don't want just like put it in this shop i guess it's basically like a like a pawn shop
but where the money all just goes to the community itself just like everybody just resell all your
shit that you don't want and this one big thing like all the money just gets piled up and then like
spent on a public works project or something maybe that's already a thing that exists i feel like
i'm just describing reality now there there is a there is a cool thing in my town there is a community
garden and what you can do is you can pay like some small amount of money to rent out a little
like plot of like soil in this fenced off area and you can just go there and like that's your soil
you can just plant whatever you want in it and like come back and you know 10
about that dank kush my dude probably not we i think it's it's legal and well is it legal to
grow like i don't know whatever it might be maybe not to grow yeah i think it's legal to grow you
just can't sell you should yeah there's like there's a little community garden where people can
rent out little plots and they just grow a little they probably just grow like herbs or whatever
just grow a little like vegetables you should grow like well there's all weed you should grow
one of those like super deadly poison plants that if you touch them you die within five minutes
or one of those hentai rape like venus fly trap that's not real sexy i was talking about a real
thing oh that's real in my mind is there a plant that's like so deadly that it'll like kill you in
five minutes if you touch it uh yeah i was i have a feeling it doesn't grow around here
well just get the seeds uh tar oh shit that's right that's what you need system have it
yeah that's a good idea i can use their seeds to get the girl he needs i i saw a tom scott video
that murder he needs i think it was a tom scott video and he went through a poison garden which
had like all of the deadliest plants of all time uh and don't touch them because some of them will
kill you just instantly it was really cool that's pretty funny what how did that man achieve this
position of getting to do cool shit like that uh basically he he did it a few things and then
people come to him to say please come to talk to us for advertising kind of did you guys see his uh
his vpn video i did i did see that one which is very interesting red shirt man british red shirt
man describes things yeah red shirt man describes things i know exactly who you're talking about
on iran yeah that vpn video well we're going to be examining one of the the oldest known things
to mankind like he always says ice ice ice has been with us what is ice really i don't know
uh but yo that that vpn video was enlightening because he basically told me what i already knew
like why do i have a vpn wait a minute it's for torrenting shit that's why i have it and he's like
that is one of the main reasons you would want that video was enlightening because he basically
told me what i already knew well no it's he he reaffirmed what i long suspected that the only
real reason to have a vpn is like if you're literally just trying to do things and not be seen
by people like all this shit yeah you hear the shill say that's what but beth of course that's
what they're for the contrast here ben is with what the advertisers say yeah when they're doing a
pitch nate's doing a bad idea of explaining this but basically i'm doing a bad job of explaining
it i have a great idea of playing it vpn's uh they like everything that they claim in the ad
that they do that they protect you from he like denounces a lot of it he's like dubious at best
like they they they claim that like you know all your passwords and stuff will be like unprotected
if you're on public wi-fi or something and he's like that's just patently false like
like you know and he works in that like he works on developing like cyber security
like that's his background so he's like believe me as a security guy i know these vpn's are not
saving you at all like unless you are just torrenting massive amounts of shit like that's the only
kind of use that like the regular person would have for this thing vpn ads illegal activity
vpn ads are like the equivalent of like smoke shops they say they're for tobacco but you know why
they're really i mean that's what i would absolutely take a vpn sponsorship because i
fucking use this shit all damn day every day and i totally endorse uh fuck the man go off the grid
man do whatever it was funny how like by saying the truth he didn't get the sponsorship deal with
the vpn company because they just didn't want to be associated with the truth the truth yeah well
there's a pitch to everything you know there's um speaking of speaking of smoke shops can we talk
have i talked about the vape ban on massachusetts oh no we talked about it after the show because
we forgot to mention it like two or three weeks ago yeah okay so i live in hell and the way that i
know that is because like at like the end of sometime last month the fucking governor of
massachusetts in response to some bullshit declared like all these the display and sale of all vaping
and e-cigarette related products banned in massachusetts it's not illegal to have them or to use them
only to display them and sell them so my twitter banner that says vaping is not a crime is still
technically accurate um but um i think the most amazing thing about this like decision is that it
is like it is obviously patently retarded but it is like the problem with the vaping thing in the
first place and the reason why they even like wanted it banned is because there are black market
uh uh thc carts that use a certain ingredient that caused lung damage it is all it is all in
response to that you have it is only the thc kind so not the kind i use of vaping but it's all
banned anyway to go use gray market alternatives and increase the problems you've done nothing
but make the problem worse yeah and like damage literally good job i have to go i found i found uh
i found like shut down like possibly the most burgeoning business right exactly five years like
the mouth of vape shops that have sprung up everywhere in the country in the last half decade
is like astonishing and now they're all going to be and and like there's like some sort of lip
service like okay like people are bringing like business owners are bringing suit against the
state of messachusetts for this and like i hope they win but like the law like like the emergency
like declaration or whatever says like emergency this like yeah cuz like 30 people contracted cases of
this um this like mysterious lung disease hey man you gotta break a few eggs to make an omelet
that's what i'm saying man that's what i'm saying um but uh um it doesn't like it does it says that
like the ban like will be like reviewed again in a couple months so like there's no there's no hard
deadline of like this is a temporary ban it will end on such it's like this is gonna last for four
months and then maybe we'll lift it four months from now and i think big tobacco is probably just
gonna lobby for it to stick around so we're just of course i just i just think this i just think
this um this great and valuable product for society okay it's probably it's probably just so
when are you gonna move down to the libertarian south where i hate the south digi i hate the south
i it's bad about the south it's bad and i don't like what's wrong with it i don't like your accent
and i don't like you that's exactly the same um okay cigarettes are really cheap though it's pretty
cool um but i did find i did find a one store you know with an indian guy with a really thick
accent i can barely understand him but if i ask him for jewel pods he'll take some out from under
from under a secret a secret place behind the counter and he'll sell me some and i went back
one day and i was like hey you got any jewel pods and he's like uh and i'm like uh mint and he's
like oh yeah yeah he brings out some grape and i'm like yeah cool i'll take it and i went back
and i was like hey you got any more of those jewel pods he's like yeah he gave me some
rings me up cool they're cheaper now because they don't have to tax them because he's selling me
under the table now they're costing did you a favor they cost way they cost he could be gouging me
he's not yeah yeah so i go back the other day listen i was drunk for like two days straight
before halloween so i don't really remember most of this journey but i went on a big circuitous route
because i had to pop off to one liquor store to buy a certain thing i was looking for and then i
want to stop at this place and i must have been hammered or something i must have made a huge
fool of myself but i guess i must have gone in there because i came back with like 12 boxes of
these of these jewel pods in my backpack and i'm like cool that's that sorted out for a month or
so um and that's my vape story and you know what i heard that you had a supplier going out of state
to uh to acquire them for you you know crack crack did make one trip to across the border to new
hampshire crack cocaine reminds me that i had i had a subscription for like cbd vape cartridges
and the next second one never came in so i guess that's why they just can't ship it to me oh yeah
yeah okay i thought that maybe jewel.com would still like ship and like they would be slow to
respond to this ban no the very day that the ban went into effect they immediately cancelled like
my next order my next it's illegal now i guess so meanwhile but here's the thing if they had sent
if they had sent it the day before it would have been fine because it's still it still could have
come through the mail and that would not have been illegal but selling it to me online think about
the fact that there is there's a website i could that we could all go to right now where you could
buy a sheet of 50 acid tablets legally and not jewels like there's you can buy what are considered
uh research chemicals um which are just legal versions of hard drugs uh namely acid that are
very easy are they expensive as fuck um not really actually it's quite cheap but you have to buy
them in like gigantic sheets like you get a sheet of like 50 tabs for a hundred dollars or something
like that that'll be a stretch goal for radcon four is when uh when i'm looking at when i'm looking
to propose to the little lady one day i'll make sure i have a tab or two i would love to just set
up a camera in a room where all of us are doing acid and just see what happens right that's that
that's a different that's an acid bro packed no that's that's degeneracy uh you know when i when
i got to digi's house did you was like would that be illegal would we be allowed to post that
um we bought it legally and what are they gonna say you did acid like it's not illegal to do
acid it might be illegal to do acid also it again this is a legal it's illegal to do certain
drugs online uh we're talking about the research chemicals it's legal it's legal to to buy it's
legal to do but it's not legal to have so if we have it for like one second well yeah we have to
we have we have we have to buy it from the distributor it has they have to place it directly
into our mouths i mean for for what it's worth technically these these reason like the reason
that they can sell them is that you're supposed to be buying them as research chemicals like
not to use but to to do other things i feel like there might be terms of service that say like no
using drugs what if it falls into my mouth accidentally it's not my fault like like snoop
dog has a talk show on youtube where they just smoke blunts and the whole show like it's definitely
allowed to like do drugs those are blunts though i don't know snoop dog he has he has money coming
and he's got those views so i'm sure well i know that um uh nearly senior citizen yet a gamer my
favorite dwarf fortress streamer on youtube is uh he smokes medical marijuana on uh on on on
it's it's medical yeah he's a disabled veteran you know okay so he's got the hookup we we have
not established if weed is the same as acid in this capacity but fair enough some drugs i mean how
would they even like we would probably do the acid before we started filming so there'd be no evidence
of us doing it we could just claim we were acting i mean that yeah that might be that might work even
if it is anybody in the future is listening it was a joke we're not actually talking about doing this
wing and obviously both of preamble about how guys we're going to do a little performance art piece
called what if we all took ass i mean obviously we should do pcp if we're going to do a hard
pcp pcp scares me a lot more than that's almost worth it for the meme though it would be a good
way to end the podcast permanently when we're all about this i i think pcp might be addictive though
so oh it's fine you guys are well i'll take all of your doses for you i will remain pure i mean
when i went to digi's house did you was like net you really gonna spend your whole time here without
smoking any dank weed with me and i remained pure you didn't smoke even a single bud of the devil's
that's pretty lame that's pretty gay though for what it's worth you were in a
fucking room full of smoke so i'm sure you were definitely hot boxing but you know i didn't
feel much what an absolute dorkus malorkas yeah well that's true you did consume plenty of alcohol
though so it's not until you were straight edge i mean i never got even close to drunk but i did
in fact consume alcohol did i mention that i was like straight up like intoxicated like full on
hammered for like two whole days leading up to hell you mentioned it but i am you are full on
hammock right now no i find i find i have some leftover alcohol in my room and the very side
of it disgusts me was that the then was that the longest you've ever been drunk for no god no
senior year of college i was fucking i was tipsy 24 7 damn for a for a i mean for a period there
okay all right well you say that you were an alcoholic no well that no because i was still
pretty functional i wasn't like fit i wasn't like flunking my classes or anything how do you
define an alcoholic exactly just depended on every day or addicted to alcohol right it's it's um
yeah well like like any like any um debilit or debility or what's the phrase um you know it's
based on how much it impairs your function so like oh okay i'm trying to not have it or whatever
so it might be not a weed addict if i can survive while being high all the time maybe someone would
contest this but i'm pretty sure that if alcohol does not impair if if a if a substance use a habit
does not impair your ability to function or your like happiness or satisfaction or whatever metric
you want to use then it's not technically an abuse problem that can't be i mean if you're smoking
like nobody who smokes is like having their life fucked up by if you're if you're drinking
if you're drinking a lot and it's like not causing you any problems what's the point in calling you
an alcoholic because you're dependent upon a substance well you're still damaging your body
like you are doing yeah i mean isn't the issue being dependent to function yeah addiction is just
i mean like most of us are caffeine addicts you know and like it's not a problem but we are addicted
you know i mean it becomes a problem if you don't have it which is just as bad see this is the
weird thing i don't feel like an addict i don't feel like i need it but i do consume it regularly
well i don't know that you need it until you don't have it and then you feel right i mean i feel like
a day without caffeine would suck i mean that's that's how i would describe addiction is if when
you don't have it anymore you feel worse like you feel like shit that's like like when i've been
you know i've been like on and off full-blown addicted to weed in recent times and i'm saying
the word addicted because uh just recently i think they changed the definition of addiction to include
this stuff because like for instance uh like in the dsm i'm not sure but like okay like well
game addiction did recently enter the dsm and like it was considered a compulsion for a long time
because it was seen that uh something being an addiction meant it had to have like a chemical
influence over you like you it was forcing you to be addicted by the chemicals that are in the
substance now they seem to be changing that because i mean what you're addicted to is whatever chemical
is being released by your brain from partaking yeah so um but like for me like smoking weed i was
just doing it so much that when i would stop i could not eat you know like and that's how i
that's when i consider that an addiction it's like you know that seems like a clear case to me
yeah yeah i mean granted it's only for a couple days but like you know it's a few days of being
like oh i'm miserable i can't eat like i can't bring myself to eat this food that i have you know
the reason why i was drunk for two days is because i went out to a liquor store looking for the
specific ingredients to make my signature beverage the dragon raider and um what's in that uh well
the original i got it from a thai restaurant in new york and the original recipe was a combination
of midori melon liqueur uh bakardi grand melon rum uh lime juice and a pulped kiwi fruit
sounds good it's it's very fruity and it's very it tastes like a jolly rancher and it's very strong
it gets you fucked up and um sick but they but they don't make they don't make bakardi grand
melon anymore they've like changed the flavors that they offer from bakardi so now i had to i
ended up having to settle for a dragon berry which i think is a dragon fruit strawberry blend it was
fine um but so i went i asked them uh like well can you get it for me they were like we can try and
order the grand melon for you and i was like all right fine in the meantime i guess i'll just get
some sea ice my signature vodka brand sea ice 999 a handle can't afford not to drink it so of
course that's what i immediately started doing so i just spent the next so i just spent the next
two days just kind of casually working my way through this handle of sea ice because i thought
it would be fun and it was there and that's my story classic tale it's a classic tale reminds me
of that time i just decided to just drink drunken halloween yeah on your stream right no i did
that's the days before that wasn't i did get really drunk on twitch.tv slash saint comics that
one time and then i fucking and then i this is i this is embarrassing i'll talk about it because
when else am i gonna talk about it yeah i just i i got super hammered on stream uh set a bunch of
shit about chris chan uh-huh that should have completely turned chris off to me forever people
clipped it showed it to chris chris listened to it and then responded to me like hey ben i listened
to your commentary here's my here's what i think about all this every don't worry about it we're
all we're friends i'm like nice it all works it all works out um and then i and then i ended i was
hammered i ended the stream and then somehow i started the stream again and it's fucking embarrassing
because i like stand up and i fucking like take my shirt off and stuff and i'm like getting ready
for bed i'm glad my fucking dick didn't come out or anything because it's a bannable fence
almost like full dsp there but but then i just i take my shirt off i turn the lights off i presumably
get into bed and then what follows is five hours of pitch blackness and five hours of ripping fat
farts constantly while sleeping shaking the room most most likely i got i got several messages
how much money from people did you get nate call ben help him help him help him assist him nate
what did you do i think at least one person donated like a like a hundred bits it was just
while i was asleep so it was worth it i'm asking you boys why not stream while we sleep why not
get the viewers why ever why answers been in front of us all the whole time make money while
you're sleeping of course we just had to do it literally why ever end the stream that's what i'm
saying i mean what there's there's a video where uh where mr beast gave a guy who was sleeping on
stream like 10 grand just to see what he would react when he woke up so that's all need to sleep on
stream all the time when the off chance is anyone else sick of mr beast shit i get it you've got
lots of money you like to give it away i'm bored now are you bore me unless you give me the money
that i'm no longer bored i'm invested in the narrative now by my by my engagement coward
um but uh wait there was oh no okay i did get really drunk on that stream but then on halloween
i got fucking wasted and i puked but i don't think i puked because of the alcohol i think i puked
because i ate too much halloween candy and i puked i puked all over the bathroom and it tasted
like chocolate coming up uh on the second pass i just went to mr beast's channel and i know things
are only gonna get worse because his latest video is i spent a hundred thousand dollars on lottery
tickets and won now he's got even more money he might have won like you can always win like a
five dollars did he ever get did he win more than he more than a hundred thousand dollars and find out
that's the question that would be that would be astounding that would be always tell us the
odds are bad but what if the odds are actually really good when you play the lottery that's
hmm you know you can't prove they're not
okay it's not it doesn't seem as though
he's like the whole thing is him like doing scratches and calculating like how much has
he won versus how much has he spent on the yeah okay that's why i'd be curious there's no way he'd
win more than he spends that would be truly shocking and i and anyway planted 20 million trees
apparently well he's he's trying to that's the i i don't know whether you know about that i
assumed everybody i don't know anything i didn't watch mr beast i'll i'll explain just uh just so
that i can show that i care about the trees uh huh um mr yeah dude that's what i'm saying climate
change we gotta talk about climate change it's not no good mr beast uh did one of his like wouldn't
this be a really good click bait and everyone around him was like yeah that would and uh to the
challenge to plant 20 million trees by the end of the year and there's like this uh this uh
foundation this tree planting thing uh i forget the name of it but he's partnered with them to
actually do this and he made a video where he like got a bunch of people around for like a number of
days planted like a few thousand trees in a huge field and you know that's just youtube vlogger like
jokes and and all that after that do that a couple thousand times yeah i mean even even looking into
this has taught me about a functionality i did not know youtube had yeah it's a very new i think
it's a it's a brand new functionality for this um it's a thing under a certain number of like
there's smarter every day there's mr beast uh captain disillusion was also doing this uh
they have a special little button uh which directly funds this thing of like you give a
dollar you you get a tree planted i've pledged money to it haha i'm so cool i'm so smart and
better than everyone else um and the idea is the idea is on a massive scale one dollar does
plant a tree and they're going to actually do it if uh i assume they're gonna plant as many
you know trees as they get dollars and hopefully they'll get 20 million
by the end of the year why why spend money planting trees when you could spend that money
on andrew yang shirts the the profits of which will go directly to bernie's campaign when you buy
them for my teespring right no no no the trees were made the t-shirts were made from trees that's
why the t-shirt for every tree you plant i will tear down five of them to produce a t-shirt a cotton
v-neck um actually that's pretty cool and uh considering the climate change is terrifying and
i will probably be displaced within my lifetime um yikes possible i mean i'm on the coastal city
so you know that close to the ocean though you're like inland not boston is like on the
it's a port i don't think boston is gonna get fully swallowed in your lifetime by water
i don't know unless things get like accelerate somehow i mean things are gonna accelerate
they okay i you know i'm curious i actually don't know the extent of like how much the water levels
are predicted to rise if like things don't change their trajectory or whatever they say they say
that like climate change and like rising water levels are now irrevert they are they are irreversible
they will happen but hey that's that's business baby but we but we can still like if we reduce
emissions if we start reducing emissions in the next like decade we can like reduce we can significantly
reduce the amount to which they will occur yeah it's not it's not gonna happen because i am praying
well we could do we could we could do something maybe the 20 million we could reduce emissions
perhaps the 20 million trees thing is is like the opposite of reducing emissions because people
just don't like the idea of reducing their emissions they don't want to be like like judged for using
an airplane they don't want to be told to like do all of this bullshit busy work at home i'm just
gonna say this i'm just gonna say this it is not it is not i i totally reject i fully reject the
idea that like we the people ought to do anything to like oh don't waste don't waste water turn the
lights off when you like agree like no it is like we must fucking legislate our fucking corporations
it doesn't allow them to do this then the problem is that even if we do that it's only we will do it
like yes i know i know it's china has to do it too and all the other superpowers yes here the two
big ones right now yeah so like in in terms of the grand scheme of like how difficult this is to do
planting a bunch of trees that will slowly but surely eat up some of that carbon dioxide is it's
something you know yeah and 20 million is not insignificant i'm glad i'm saying if we just put
a tree in the back of every car it would offset it then we'd never i mean if you know what and help
it grow then yes where do i give a fucking tree where do i give a fucking tree i guess on mr beast
yeah go to mr beast channel i will get the link and post it as well please mr beast flexing with
all his money but he doesn't fund 20 million trees what a coward all right well i don't want us to sit
here and promote other people's content yeah no the money needs to be ours please i got the thing
it's teamtrees.org i'll post the link you don't need to go through a youtuber to do it it's just a
button youtube is implemented in order to make it easier for people who don't want to click links
i said that even though i spent 20 minutes promoting steve 1989 mre so i guess i'm completely wrong
yeah that i don't want to support when i when i see mr beast and his unbelievable success i just
sit back and cross my arms and scowl and say fuck that guy we don't hate youtubers we hate we hate
new tubers this new kind of internet celebrity that does mediocre content i have no problem with
mr beast's videos are actually great like why does this guy have so much money i feel like we've
talked about him before he's because he's just sort of like a youtuber who uses his youtube money
to make the videos that are like whoa he's got so much money and then it just perpetuates itself
he does do impressive things i mean he the way he started was just doing like crazy weird stunts
like i'm gonna read an entire dictionary or like i'm gonna livestream myself counting to a million
and like just he was that guy which he did yeah i've never seen a mr beast video so i know nothing
about him all i know is that the philanthropy is uh tainted in my mind because his name is
mr beast and it makes me feel like he's a smug he's a hot beast boys oh he clearly isn't mr beast
tongue he's fine i wish him well he's doing just anyway the pcp endorses team trees dot org
i don't endorse anything i'm i'm gonna donate five trees right now with the custom tree message
hashtag feel the burn yeah you really want to put that on a tree that seems to burn spreading
between all the trees in california not literally don't let's hey hey guys let's be burn let's bern
down the house over here in this man-made tree enclave am i right fellows okay he's right and with
that also about how about voicemails yeah just just want a little snippet okay okay um if you want
to know a bit more about the science of of how to do like tree planting of on such a scale
smarter every day did a video on t the tree thing and he he goes into like how do you do that like
how do you do that and it's how do you plant 20 million trees don't like like there are ways all
day no because there's ways to do it wrong that's the reason this uh charity thing is all like set up
so that the people who are actually going to plant the trees know what they're doing to make
sure that the trees live to be long to to grow tall and all that well this is all well and good
why plant trees when you can smoke trees if you know what i'm saying might you tell you because
like if you plant them too close together they'll like choke each other out and starve each other
for a space yeah stuff like that smoke each other there it is all right there you go let's do the
fucking voicemail singular this week wait really got one because all the others god well okay honestly
let me just give a little so so our voicemail god this motherfucker left like 10 voicemails
but in his defense in his defense so he one of his last ones was like guys am i living too many
voicemails that's a weak defense yes leaving too many voicemails uh at least he's aware of the problem
and we can now diagnose it and cut out the cancer you're leaving too many voicemails and some of
yours i may have been tempted to play but there was just too many and i got annoyed and i didn't
want to play them on the show uh so here's your fickle god you know at work so like just just two
or three guys next time you next time you want to make a voicemail don't go over that if it's
still funny in the morning by all means okay because that's the problem it's quality over quantity
and not the quantity which we said last time which we said we're dealing with the follow-up
i mean we keep saying that but you keep choosing shit ones is that why i'm playing one this very
episode give wow what a coincidence looks like i solved the problem your welcome zero next week
i hope they'll be less than one they'll be minus one you'll have to make your own voice
nate look we got very few this week from anyone except voicemail god and there were too many by
him was like 90 i'm not and i'm not gonna sit here for 45 minutes playing messages from voicemail
god so just pick the cream of the problem let's fucking end this charade i will say i will say
though that one of the messages uh was just that you know we were saying like he said last time
something about like uh oh you guys uh guess who i am and we're not gonna play that fucking game but
he did say that like two of us would know who he is and man he's trying to do this fucking game like
guess who i am i'll leave clues every week no who are you no i'm not doing that voicemails
to pick up all your clues if it's two people that it's not me crumb trail i don't know he probably
if i can hear his voice i'll try and think about if i've heard it before we will never
hear his voice on the show ever again i thought you met the end of it well i was from a different
person well from a different person uh so voicemail god just get it under control chief you just you
just going way too fast and lose uh settle it down settle it down okay but here we go i have
actual one voicemail one and only uh of dubious quality but you know it wasn't i'll tell you all
right here we go after all this okay and this is that yang confirms the dimensional merge is the
name of the voicemail all right let's let's let's let's see what he's got for us go okay bcp the
dimensional merge is literally literally confirmed by fucking andrew yang okay right now right now
go on the fucking instagram site of andrew yang look take a look at the picture from october 28
you can see a giant poster
telling you yang will make yang will make anime that's the one yep this means the dimensional
merge it's literally retarded not funny yeah you were right even that was even you just picked
one that was right i'm i'm i guess i'm just i'm glad you didn't pick anymore i'm really glad that
right right you see i did my best i mean you gotta have one but andrew yang better hope the
dimensional merge isn't real because if it is lisa simpson will be president in 2020 and uh
he's gonna be shit i don't want anime to be real no what about all your wifus for sex first of all
i already have a wife second of all who cares what get more what anime is going to become like
do you want berserk to become real no i don't want to live in the world of berserk yeah dude
dark souls i want the freedom i want the freedom to travel between anime worlds at my ledger and
have as bad or good a time as i'm feeling like at that moment let's just make this what i'll get
devil man real and the world would just end that sounds good that sounds pretty sick i'd like astro
boy to be real it'll end much like this it'll end we can we can make oh very true top cutting down
20 million trees and accelerating climate change you can make devil man real by beheading your
childhood love interest and uh you know be in literally the most heli person who's ever existed
i don't advocate that but you could you gotta go to i'm just saying the options are there devil
man cry baby come from has been hotel does devil man cry devil may cry man he cries devil may cry
baby in the show uh huh well all right uh give leave us better voicemails at speak pipe link down
below we need more voicemails but not too many please don't bore me with your endless fucking
voicemails we don't need a lot of voicemails we just need good ones we're here for a good time
not a long time preferably that's the way to do a show uh what else is going on patreon.com
slash the procrastinators give us money for doing these episodes you're welcome five dollar bonus
episodes one dollar patron discord you know how it is uh we got a new bonus episode out which is uh
i can't remember but i think it was good right questions right oh that's why we were talking
questions that's right we answered your questions as we as we try to do and we tried to find decent
ones uh no luck wait the quest continues wait wait a minute yeah i thought i thought the bonus episode
was like viewer topics that's what it was it morphed it morphed into just questions it just
morphed into a q and a somewhere topics somewhere topics that people said i wasn't there what's the
difference when you get right you know what's my idea the very topic is is more nuanced a question
requires an answer a topic requires thought and and and exploring the idea in more detail and we've
got no make sure to pledge to that patreon indeed all right are we are we fucking done and that's all
there is to say about it folk at tpcrastinators on twitter follow the things we do uh and of course
don't forget to go to patreon.com slash pcb minecraft to play minecraft for all their pcp
minecraft playing buddies mage just ran a halloween special i was away nobody told me about this great
time mage barely told me i mean i was away so i was yeah but she i don't know ask mage go into
the server and look for announcements if you're one of those people who's like i just watch the pcp
for digian nate go listen to cantan our new channel come back i don't know if that's a person who
actually exists but like specifically me and nate but i'm just i don't know i think mage might be
creating seizing fascist dictatorship over the minecraft server she's like she's doing events and
like doing shit without oversight she has no there's no oversight i mean she she does she does call
herself god like if you want an item you have to ask god and ask god chat in the discord god is
fairly generous though so that's different from our shitty god in real life who doesn't do shit when
i killed my sister wouldn't bring her back to life uh well never done anything for me uh that's it go
play minecraft with us everybody and give us money on the patreon very appreciative um ubi is a fantasy
so you might as well just do what you can do here for us by giving us your money that's
just as good right all right we'll see you next week everybody thanks for being here another
episode of the pro crass naters podcast bye alley you