Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, a podcast
comprising the most brilliant intellectual titans on the whole internet, myself best guy
ever being chief among them.
We've also got Mumkey Jones here.
Oh boy, you guys ran for a good episode here.
Yeah, we're really going to bring our wisdom to bear.
We've got Hippocrit, Hippocrit is here.
I'm very scared.
As you should be.
And we've got The Davoo.
Me and my rowdy droogs are out at night in the town to do a little bit of clunge dunking
tonight.
Fantastic.
And he's going to be the star of the show folks.
We already know this.
Alright guys, here's the topic.
You've been waiting for it.
You've been asking for it.
You've already seen the name of this episode so you know that it's time for the long-awaited
PCP fetish cast.
We're diving deep baby.
We're going both hands into that pussy, in and out, making it happen, expansion, ballooning,
a scat.
What else you got?
I don't know.
Seaman drinking, snowballing.
It's all on the table folks.
It's all coming out.
Yeah, that's right.
For all three of the ladies at home, be sure to get your dildos ready now because you're
going to be tickling those clits all night long.
Now just come right out.
I'm going to come right out.
I'm just going to say I'm probably going to disappoint everyone here because it's not
that I'm more weird than normal.
It's just that I pre-planned how I would talk about my weirdness in a properly paced distributed
way.
It's sort of good storytelling.
I've been putting lots of thought into exactly which details to say when.
For example, to know the right time to tell people that when I'm reaching for the lube
I sometimes accidentally grab the baby powder because the bottles are right in the lube.
It's all about delivery, more so than the actual substance of the thing you're fucking.
I'm just here for you to deliver, Davoo.
I don't care how you do it.
Speaking of that, we're into delivery.
Can we get in some baby birth pregnancy kind of shit?
That sounds good.
Brilliant Nate, we thought the same thing.
We did.
Okay, let's read our Urban Dictionary definition of fetish that we can move on.
All right, here we go.
Number one.
Urban Dictionary of every single fetish.
Oh shit.
That's a good idea.
Okay, number one.
We might have to refer to it for some more obscure ones.
Okay, fetish, number one.
An object thought to have magical, especially magical, sexual powers.
So my cock.
Okay, number two.
A sexual fixation or obsession with a usually non-sexual object.
Example, socks, horses, monkeys, pain, bondage.
Who says horses aren't normally sexualized?
Get the fuck out of here, dude.
Come on.
What about the monkeys being on that list?
That's not cool.
We are monkeys.
Yeah, have you guys ever been to blacked.com?
Oh no.
Okay.
Well shit, guys, where do we start this thing?
Where do we launch in order to scat you?
Well, you just said shit, so I think we should start there.
Let's start with scat.
Okay.
I mean, DeVoo, why don't you take us away?
What do you got on?
Well, why are you jumping to DeVoo so quickly?
Because actually, yes.
I want to get to DeVoo.
He's the most interesting one here.
Fine.
And the logical connection there is a taxonomy, I don't know, there's sort of a distinction
between being attracted to the substance of something and being attracted to the concept
of something.
And I am a very concept centric person.
Like I know that there's a lot of porn.
I sometimes, the hentai that I really connect with are the ones that have a lot of details
about how the character is feeling and what they're being put through.
Actually, it's more common in Western drawn porn, right?
Where the character will experience this horrible torture and often they just sort of shrug
it off.
Like they just sort of like, oh, well, I guess this terrible thing just happened to me.
And like every panel will add on more and more details of the terrible, unfair, cruel
suffering that they're going through.
And often they don't really react to it with that much suffering.
And there's something about context that can really get my cock tested.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Yeah, so it's like cruelty, unfairness, like tragedy, like just terrible things happening
to someone for no reason at all.
If it's then coupled up with some sort of other more specific thing I'm into, I'm probably
going to download it even if the art is shit, right?
Sure.
So just if we can dissect this as we go along.
So the first point you're making is if people are suffering and it's connected with something
sectional.
Well, suffering, yeah, suffering is like one of many contexts, right?
So does any of this have like, like, do you have a rationale for it or is it just like
an innate animalistic design?
There's different logics to it, you know.
So regarding shit, I am very much not into the substance of it.
And I can tell it some people.
No, when you see some scat thumbnails out there, it's like those people just like the
feeling of it.
No, but the humiliation of it, the intimacy of it, right, is some is kind of captivating
to me.
I mean, P obviously is a much more is a much more managed is the PG 13 of that kind of
direction.
Sorry.
The thing about P is like, I don't like the smell of feet, right?
But I like the fact that that's so, um, it's so TMI, right?
It's so intimate.
Sure.
So, I mean, you know, me and my girlfriend walking on each other in the bath bathroom
peeing like all the time, right?
It's great sometimes we make out while peeing because it's so intimate, you know, make out
while peeing.
Oh, yeah.
So it's great.
That's great.
At my house, we lock the bathroom door.
Remember that scene in Almost Famous when the kid walks in on the girl peeing in the
bathroom and she's just like, yeah, no, don't worry about it.
Just stay here.
Yeah.
That was always a kind of romantic scene.
That's really hot.
And like, you know, I think also P is really fetishized because, um, hold on, the door is
being opened.
I have to wait until the door is shut again before I continue talking about this stuff.
Normies get out.
And now the door, I mean, it was my girlfriend.
Anyway, so now she shut the door again.
So anyway, Normies get out.
Um, because like, I think another big fixation of P is that guys and girls do it differently,
which I'm assuming is a big part of sexuality.
Like boobs and abs, respectively, can be attractive because that distinguishes the male and female
figure.
So like peeing out the front or down the center, you know, front ish is like different.
And that difference is what is captivating in a heterosexual way.
You know, like that's, it's like, wow, that's not how I am.
Right.
And it's that constant, uh, curiosity of what that must feel like.
Like my girlfriend a number of times, like, what does it feel like to have your dick sucked?
I'm like, it feels like if my clit was several inches long and was being sucked, like, how
do I communicate that to you?
There's never a way to do it.
And it's like constant fascination, that constant mystery that, um, I remember Jesse said that
after the first episode of the plebeian weeb was recorded, that he forgot to mention that
in his, his personal political philosophy is that if a boy and girl ever switch brains,
they are fucking obligated to have sex because it will be your only chance to know what it
feels like on the other side.
And so I think that is, um, yeah, differences in that is, uh, captivating.
So you're talking about, there's kind of an umbrella here of like, um, just sort of
exploring the unknown or, or, or experiencing something that's a very private personal thing.
That's sort of the underlying thing that makes the stuff.
There's a number of umbrellas I'm talking about, like probably two in the pink, one in
the stink, if you know what I mean.
And, uh, I don't know what you mean.
What is that an expression?
I'm just, I'm just like imagining like, like umbrellas going inside the girl.
I'm sure there's a point of that, right?
I'm imagining, I'm imagining it then opening and it's like, oh, no, it's like, oh, no,
people have died doing that.
Really?
Shit.
There was a, like a hundred ways to die.
Somebody, it was like a, um, those circus performers who swallow things all the way
down their throat and the fucking umbrella opened inside of them.
Oh, no.
Oh, that's fucked.
That's fucked.
Yeah.
That's not even like a fun, sexy way.
Like if it's in your pussy, at least that's kind of fun, but I died from an umbrella opening
in my pussy.
That was the sexiest way to die.
There's worse ways.
Okay.
Uh, okay.
So we're talking about some, some, some general themes here.
Um, here, let me say a specific fetish of mine that I, I just thought of, I was trying
to think of one, I was afraid that my tastes are like two vanilla, but I actually did think
of one that I, I recognize in myself, I do actually like a lot.
And you guys can tell what you think of this.
And it's basically, um, you know, cause I'm, I'm more attractive to like when the women
do things like the, like the porn I watch, the guy is just like, you know, he's just
the dick in the situation doing whatever.
So it's like the women doing things that's the interesting part.
I like it when the women are treated just like meat or like flesh lights or like not
even people, like they're just there.
They're like sex toys.
When you like treat a woman like a sex toy, I find that extremely,
It's that context.
Yes.
It's absolutely the context.
Now, obviously I'm not into dehumanizing people in general, but you see this a lot
in hentai with the mind break porn, where you just see a woman get fucked for such a
long time.
And then eventually at the end, like she's just like, she either is now into it and
she's just like, yeah, everybody fuck me.
It's great.
It's a fun time.
Or she's just like her, the, the, you can see in the eyes, the way they draw the eyes.
Yeah.
They always draw the eyes with this vapid expression, this vacant expression, like they have no
mind left.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Like when there's a bunch of porn I've seen where like, uh, there are these, these, these
are interesting to me.
There's like, um, uh, there's, there's a bunch of porn with like high schools, right?
And they're like very high performing high schools.
And so I forget the name of the show, but like what they did is they assign or there's like
a bathroom with female women, like strapped into the wall as flesh toilets.
Oh yeah.
They're just for public use.
Yeah.
Public use.
That's what you'll see on D sometimes.
Uh, yeah.
It's, it's too, yeah.
It's as dehumanizing as possible.
It's to make them just this fucking product in a goddamn wall.
Though to self analyze myself on this, I think the reason I'm into it is because for a long
time I had a great deal of difficulty actually getting sex.
And so I would think about all the, wouldn't it be great if there was just like a toilet
somewhere which had women just strapped down that I could use?
Yeah.
Wouldn't that just be great?
I'm sure that factors in.
So I'm not, I understand that.
Oh, of course.
Oh, absolutely.
It's the, um, I mean, there's a pretty decent reason why there's a correlation between out
there fetishes and shut-ins or otherwise unattractive, unaccepted people.
I don't still self identify as a guy who gets laid ever.
There, I still have all these moments of like, oh yeah, I have like a girlfriend and shit.
Right.
Like, you know, and I feel like especially when I'm like 13 or whatever, the whole idea
of having actual sex is about as foreign to me as the concept of say, uh, like a fantasy
where like everyone in the world except me and like maybe five or so girls like vanished
like the fucking left behind series all of a sudden, right?
Which were some of my earlier fantasies, right?
And I thought like, yeah, like I know logically actual sex is plausible, whereas like a fucking
anthro transformation is not, but, you know, it's still felt that my dick felt that way.
Let's say, you know, the dick has its own fucking train of logic and its own ideas.
Um, and I think that if you, you know, I'm just going to talk about sex in general for
10 seconds.
This is sort of a general like moral thing.
I thought of like my, my, this is like my favorite neck beard of fedora, a statement,
which is that the whole idea of sex before marriage being bad was a rule that was invented
back when people got married at like 13 and now sort of religion and other things in general
societal standards have subjected us to this situation where people go into their twenties
as virgins, which is probably a thousand fucking times more unnatural than fucking a member
of the same sex.
And I think it is probably quite instrumental in getting people to fuck everything that they
see laying around their desk.
I hear what you're saying.
It makes sense to me.
Humans are obviously extremely sexual creatures and we want to do it all the time.
I mean, at least men, I can't speak for women, but they seem pretty similar.
They seem pretty similar.
Yeah.
You can speak for women.
I know some women.
You know, when I was a kid, I really thought that like women just didn't have sex drive.
Turns out I just met a bunch of shitty prudes.
That's not true.
Turns out I was a kid and they weren't revealing that information to me.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's true.
Hippo, what are your fetishes?
Like holding hands, kissing?
No.
Hippo was like, I remember whenever we, whenever.
Mud puddles.
It's mud puddles, obviously.
Ew.
No, no, no.
It sounds like an offset of Davoo.
Hippo's pretty high up there.
Hippo, I think he's the only one like me who was like firmly from the sort of deviant art
school of fetishization, whether or not he's using that website.
Well, like inflation, there, because there's a number of different categories, right?
There are the sort of certain sort of fetishes.
All right.
Hippo speaks for himself.
Let's hang on here.
Move on.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I guess I am kind of up there.
Like Davoo, I have an umbrella of like, I don't know about many umbrellas, but I have
a lot.
Eat your pussy right now.
Is that what you're getting?
Yeah.
Like I keep buying them.
I just keep putting them in because they get lost and I just have to keep adding more.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Like the, I feel, I feel all apprehensive about this.
I'm not as gung-ho as about me.
Dude, no matter what you say, it will not be as fucked up as the shit I already said about
wanting to dehumanize women and treat them like meat.
So don't worry about that.
It's, it's, you know, you shouldn't be hyped up for what I'm about to say.
It's really just that I have, I don't, you know, my umbrella is more about like, growth
and growing.
So inflation is part of that, but it's, it's not like, all right, I'm trying to think of
a way to put it.
Growth in humans in any facet is like something I'm really interested in, a realistic or not,
but usually I prefer the realistic stuff.
Like, like the natural breast growth of girls, just like if they, they just, you know, a
young teenager and then, you know, over the years they get like real big boobs and they're
like, oh yeah, I'm, I'm a sex god and I'm like, yeah, that whole, that whole process
was great.
It's, it's the sequence.
It's the process.
It's the, the going from one to the other doesn't necessarily have to be, yeah, it doesn't
necessarily have to be a thing that I would like otherwise.
Like, you know, it could be a penis.
It could be like a, just a person go like a giant, giantess.
It could be somebody getting really fat, even though I don't like fat people.
I think that's the thing.
Yeah.
Like the flat thing falls into like the humiliation, demeaning, you've become worse, specific fat
women are beautiful.
All right.
The thing is, I'm talking about it.
I'm talking like actual, like fucking round.
Like I'm talking like there are D threads of blue barrification straight out of really
long.
I'm not kidding.
It's really long.
I'm not.
It's not even like, that's not even hyperbola, man.
Willy Wonka that one did in fact in set, like incepted a very specific blueberry based
fetish in the dicks of many young men.
You're right.
Not me.
I mean, I'm pretty flexible.
I can do it sometimes, but, but, but some people are pretty into it because it's like
when you see that girl reduce to this pathetic little blob out of her own misdeeds.
It's like that's some fucking great a context right there.
You know what I mean?
It's just how the, the Disney cartoon Robin Hood got all you guys into my little pony.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I mean, yeah, obviously if you, if you want to talk about correlation and causation with
fetish is Disney and furry is pretty fucking objectionable.
Zootopia baby.
It's a, I was a late bloomer, but I want to go fuck a rabbit.
Yes.
You know, I do want to talk about anthropomorphized stuff, but I want to give to go on first.
Yeah.
But now I've lost my train of thought.
I was talking about, yeah, yeah.
It's not necessarily the thing in question, like the, the being fat, like I don't like
fat people.
I don't like just seeing a fat person, but the idea of somebody just eating like so much
that they become a giant, like even to ridiculous proportions, just becoming a giant blob of
like, you can't even see their face there.
So, you know, it's like, it's like weird.
It's, it's, yeah.
Conflation feels weird because that it's just a sphere and they just go outwards in a, in
a sphere and it's like, that's so far removed from human anatomy that I can't even.
I don't understand what's, what's attractive about that though.
Can you explain to me?
Yeah.
I wanted to ask, but I didn't want to seem rude.
Uh, what, what about the fat thing?
Well, like, yeah.
So like somebody gets blown up and you can't recognize their face and it's all like, it's
it's not, yeah, but that's the thing.
It's not the end result.
It's the fact that it just goes from one to more.
Yeah.
It's like the growth aspect, the, the going.
Like accelerated puberty.
Yeah.
Well, anything, any, any sort of growth thing, that's just really what I'm into any, any
growth thing.
And, and what I'm into like the most is the stuff that could actually happen in real life
like, like breasts enlargement.
Just over time.
Yeah.
Like a girl turning 14.
I'm into that too.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, that's interesting.
But like what I think this is, we're coming from a slightly different perspective, at
least the way I view this stuff, uh, whereas at least how like this specific fetish works.
Cause like what I'm thinking about porn or like what gets me off is like, I think about
how my dick gets involved in this situation.
And like, that's what I'm really focused on.
And I just don't understand how my dick gets involved in like an inflation situation.
That's, that's, yeah, that's, that is the thing is, it's, it's, it brings us back to
the thing I said before.
But how, wait, wait, wait.
I really wasn't sure if he was going to say or not.
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm say, I'm going to say it, it's, it's the concept, it's the idea of something
happening.
Um, I'm trying to think of like exactly like the fat thing.
Cause like sometimes it's, it's nice when they just get put, uh, like chubby, they just
a little bit and they're like, Oh no, I put on weight, but you know, you love them anyway.
Like that's, that's all right.
But then there's the stuff where it goes way over the beyond, beyond what I would consider,
like after I'm finished, I look at it and I'm like, Oh God, that's not the point that
you'll use it.
But beyond the point where once you're done, you're like, yeah, and it's not, it's not
about sex at some point, at some point, like, um, there are things that aren't sexual about
growth that get me feeling weird, but it's not, you know, it's not my dick that's feeling
it.
It's just like anything that, where there's like, uh, like a monster in a thing that
just eats souls and it grows to a gargantuan size.
It's not about sex, but it does make me feel a similar feeling.
So really all it is is to this feeling.
Um, I don't know like, like, I think the last time I remember it like very vividly was when
in one piece, Gekko Moria was like getting loads of shadows and he was going in and he
was just becoming gigantic, but not only that in the anime, he had his voice deepened
like several octaves and it was, it was terrifying.
I was absolutely terrified of it and that, I think that was what it was.
It's the, it's the behemoth like gargantuan size that is uncontrollable.
It's like a Godzilla.
It's like, that's, that's, you know, it's way beyond anything I could even imagine.
It's terrifying.
That's, that's what makes me feel weird.
And then if they have tits, then it's also sexy, I guess.
So the, the, the female pirate from one piece, episode one, do you like her?
Doesn't she get all big and fat?
Alveda, she was just a baddie from the start.
She actually gets, she actually gets way skinnier later and becomes like a sex god as a,
oh shit.
Yep.
Wait, she comes back later on.
They have to bring back even the, the episode one villain for this shit.
She comes back with like a whole new context and is actually a much more interesting character
when she does and is pretty cool.
So, uh.
She does.
She comes back quite well.
She salvaged her well.
Oda doesn't forget, man, but okay, we don't need to get into a lot of these things.
So the whole issue that we were just talking about, once again goes back to the whole,
if you're a fucking virgin, your dick thinks that nothing is going to happen to it, so you
might as well fantasize about anything.
Like you can just keep going further and further down the, the fucking giant fat rabbit hole
there.
And having sex is a good way to stop sexual exploration, you know?
Yeah, yeah, it really is.
You gotta, yeah.
And like, so like inflation, right?
I think a lot of it does, once again talking about the whole context and also tactility
thing, right?
Like, um, I'm looking, I've deviant art search some, uh, and there's a, there's a pretty
decent, uh, focus on panty shots, which is to say this giant white wedge that is vaguely
in between their two feet, right?
And like imagining what that must feel like to have those panties be so stretched out,
which, you know, realistically, the clothes should just rip off, but usually the clothes
manage to stretch out, right?
And it's that feeling of like, hmm, what would have a giant feel like if it was this giant
12 foot ball?
Now I see how my dick can get involved here.
This makes more sense to me.
Nikki's looking at me.
My girlfriend has her name and, uh, just letting you know, like, I'm not particularly into
this one.
Like, I mean, if I had to, I could do it, but not really, but like, but again, also there
is the context of like a fact that a girl could be reduced to something like that is
like, oh man, that is so hot that she could be so like, I'm talking like a ball.
I'm talking like an actual fucking ball.
Nikki's like looking at me like shaking her head.
And that's the thing.
Don't kink shame this man.
Get the fuck out.
You're going to be, you're going to be bottling up my hero to food.
This is a sexual safe space.
Exactly.
That's why pedophilia is okay.
Triple S.
Yeah.
No, we'll get into pedophilia.
I'm looking forward to it.
You got more turns coming up.
That's perfectly natural.
We will, we'll, all right, we'll get to that.
I've got something else to say about, uh, stuff.
There's the, the, the futonari fetish, uh, chicks, chicks with dicks, um, oh, uh, this,
this whole thing is called a trap.
It's called a trap.
No, it's, it's a separate thing.
It's a separate.
I mean, sometimes I see images of, of when it's just a girl and traps or distaste, it's,
it's just a girl with a, you know, not even wearing anything down there.
Just sort of having the dick swing around cause it's like 50 feet long, doesn't make
any sense.
But, um, I, I, over the course of like looking at that sort of stuff, I've come to realize
that I like it, um, not because, because I can disassociate the idea of a male and the
idea of a penis.
I don't know whether it's, it's like the cause, cause as a man, I have a penis and I'm
not repulsed by it because it's not gay to look at your own dick because you have it.
So the idea of someone else's dick, it's just, uh, you know, the dick isn't inherently male
because the, you know, it's like, there's an idea of maleness being, uh, gay, but you
can't be gay if you look at yourself, you know, so the dick isn't inherently gay.
So if a girl has a dick, then it's just, it's just, you know, a girl with a thing.
And, you know, I actually had thought about this point for a long time because my favorite
hentai to this day is still Bible black and Bible black is just full of food.
It's like food is central and, uh, I really had to think about like, okay, so you've
got just a woman here having sex with, well, you've got, uh, Professor Kitami, uh, Kitami,
yeah, Kitami, who is, she's just a woman, but she like uses magic to grow a dick like
above her vagina and then she has sex with women with it.
So like that, that's cool, but like what's, what are the, what are the, uh, the bits of
this equation here?
So you've got two women plus one dick basically.
So like basically when you're watching them having sex, so like, for example, uh, in episode
one they're having doggy style sex, her and this green haired girl.
So like when you, when you're watching from the front angle, you get to see two pairs
of tits bouncing around while they're having sex.
So that totally fulfills my criteria of imagining where my dick would be in the situation and
I get to see two accidentally animated pairs of tits bouncing around.
It's fantastic.
It's really great.
And I love it.
Now I actually do prefer, uh, like one man, one woman just because it's that much easier
for me to project myself into it.
In case you can't tell, like my tastes are extremely basic here.
I just want to be able to imagine how I'm having sex with this person.
That's what I do like every time.
I'm wondering about that because I don't know whether I even think about that when I'm
looking at porn.
I mean, I'm not sure either.
Really?
I think what I do is I've never been into like lesbian porn at all because like I can't
I'm not really into that easily because it's, you know, lesbian porn is boring.
I mean, I legitimately think so.
Did you would argue against that?
But I do think that I think so too.
I wouldn't watch that shit.
I think it's like, I get a grasp of what the character is and then I just imagine how
I would interact with that person instead of just literally taking the place of whoever
is actually having sex with him.
You're using more imagination than I am because like I'm just projecting myself whereas you're
kind of coming up with your own stuff.
I'm coming up with like lore and stories of like potential like what would happen.
He's coming up with cum.
Indeed.
Oh, of course.
But yeah.
Well, that's, yeah, that's interesting.
That's why I like, I like, like characters a lot.
Like I have so many waifus because I just keep thinking about what they would do to me
or what I would do to them.
I've got a couple of waifus myself, so I'm no stranger to that.
But yeah, I hear you.
I hear you.
When it comes to specifically porn though, I do notice this about myself and my viewing
habits.
I'm looking for a guy fucking a woman because that's what I want to do and I want to see
most of the woman.
I don't want to see the guy's face.
Like whenever they put a guy's face in, I mean, I just prefer it if they don't.
Obviously.
You know, you see that in porn all the time.
They try to keep the guy out of the shot.
Oh, you know what?
You know what?
It might be, it might be because I'm not like, like built like the sort of normal, I'm not
either fat or muscular and whenever there's a guy fucking a girl, I'm just, I'm just kind
of small.
I'm small and skinny.
And that's, that's more similar to the shape of a woman that it is the shape of the man
that is usually fucking the girl in the hentai.
So I can't really project myself onto that big muscular man.
So it's easier to project myself into like one of the futonari girls.
Maybe.
Maybe that's how it works.
Girl, I know a girl who like she can't enjoy porn if the girl who is in the porn is like
not white.
Right.
And she feels bad about that.
I'm like, Hey, man, it's how you see yourself.
And like for me, I don't really think of myself racially.
I just think of myself as like having like curly hair and like having sort of my general
kind of face.
Right.
If there's like a guy who's like a big manly man with a beard, I can't project it all.
Or if they've got like straight hair or like short hair, I can't project it all.
But if it's a guy black or white or whatever, but he's got like kind of thick hair and sort
of like just doesn't look like a grown ass man, I can project myself way more easily and
I'm way more into that.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I mean, I do like it when the guy looks as much like me as possible and if he's like super
ripped or anything that will be distracting as if he's like black or something because
I'm not black.
So it's like, okay, well, that's not me.
Um, yeah, but it's never really been like a huge issue for me.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel like usually at the moment of actual like coming, I'm thinking intensely about
the feelings that the female is going through.
I'm, I'm, I'm latching entirely onto that fascination of what it must feel like for them.
I feel like that's the moment where I usually like end up at, uh, because I don't know.
That's just, so that's usually why I can, I can, I can, I don't need a guy to be involved,
although it does often help, but I do plenty of like just two girls just thinking about
what they are feeling, you know, just constantly empathizing with that.
And by the way, to those of you, I, there is a contingent of people out there who argue
that like lesbian porn is the straightest porn for guys to watch because there's no
man there.
Obviously it's less gay than watching a man have sex.
Like what are you gay, bro?
Why do you like looking at dicks, dude?
Uh, just letting you know that's incorrect guys.
It's incorrect.
Yeah, reasonable.
Yeah.
I think they're onto something.
Uh, okay.
They should chop those all their own one off and then they won't be gay anymore because
they won't have a dick.
That makes a lot of sense to me.
Well, did you have more of your diet tribe to go through because we cut you off like
an hour ago?
Well, I mean, no, I'm willing to like just, I mean, I do have more.
I do have some notes.
Yes.
Well, I'm ready for it.
Yeah.
Let's me enter through that again.
So as I was kind of alluding to a little bit ago, like there's sort of like, um, different
cores or different layers of fetishism, you know, based on like how obscure it is.
Like, you know, people might say like, it's, it's a debate as to like what fetish is more
weird than another one.
Like say choking, you could argue, well, that's like bringing about death.
That's like pretty fucking extreme.
And also fairly common.
Yeah.
Tons of women.
There's a thing, right?
Like, you know, all that inflation stuff.
I think DVNR is still primarily the, uh, the home of stuff of that sort of sex sector.
Right.
I'm sure there's plenty on Tumblr, but Tumblr tends to be more of a quality zone, uh, in
terms of what you're going to see.
Uh, DVNR is an absolute dumpster fire of quality, uh, and that is what inflation is.
You know, I'm sure there's probably a number of people drawn to it because of the amount
of quantity of it because inflation is easy to draw because it's a circle.
Anyway.
Oh, true.
That's true.
Does Kirby Count as inflation porn?
Just inherently?
Oh, shit.
Oh, probably.
Oh, there's probably, like, I'm, I wouldn't be surprised if a couple of people who work
at Nintendo were into inflation, there's a couple too many times.
No, man.
Like, you know, Super Mario Galaxy 2, Yoshi has a power up in that, and Mario like doggie
style grabs onto Yoshi's ass and floats up with him.
I'm like, this was animated with a little bit too much, uh, TLC, for me to like not
be entirely unsuspicious.
I hear what you're saying, and it also happens that in, uh, both the Galaxy games, there's
those lumas that you have to force feed tons of bits to, and then they get fat, and then
they explode into a star.
Oh, and let's not even get into fucking Mario and Luigi Bowser's inside story, which is
all about being inside every intimate detail of Bowser's body, and also he grows and shrinks
a number of times, and also he has a weight gain scene.
Yeah.
Someone who works at Nintendo jacks off to Bowser daily is what I'm saying, come on.
Is Shigeru Miyamoto.
I think somebody...
Yeah, it's true.
You think anybody jerks off about playing Dig Dug?
Oh, God.
There's the inflation, and not to mention, of course, it's mentioning Miyamoto, there's
the whole power mushroom thing that makes Mario big, you know?
Oh, yeah.
That's pretty similar.
Yeah.
So anyway, so like, there's a whole DeviantArt section, and like, but the thing is, if you
go to DeviantArt and search fetish, then click newest, you're gonna get bondage, bondage,
bondage, latex, latex, latex, latex, latex, latex, latex, latex, furry, latex, bondage,
bondage, bondage, inflation, bondage, bondage, bondage, uh, and cutoff.
Right.
So the thing is, those fetishes are way more common, right?
Those fetishes are much more in the realm of people who do actually, you know, go out
and meet people, right?
So there's this website called FetLife, which is a dating website for fetishes, and it's
all about the...
Those kinds of fetishes, right?
And this list that I posted on the Discord chat, I might even share it on the internet
somewhere, it's a list of FetLife's top 100 fetishes as picked by its users, like how
many, like, users have identified with a fetish.
So bondage, oral sex, spanking, hair pulling, anal sex, blindfolds, um, then you go down
to the bottom, you get stuff like enemas, daddy girl, bisexuality, teasing, submission,
orgasm denial, cock-sucking, flogging.
These are all things that can be done in real life.
Cock-sucking is at the bottom?
This is basic.
This is basic shit, yeah.
I know, right?
And there are some weird stuff.
I mean, one time I saw...
Getting a blowjob is a fetish?
The thing about that life is you can actually add any fetish you want, and what you'll see
is a lot of profiles, men and women, they'll just start, like, mass adding, like, hundreds,
literal hundreds of fetishes that were submitted to the site while they jack off.
So some of them get really specific, you know, like, laying down while daddy rams his cock
through my left ear socket.
That kind of thing.
Oh, no!
Okay.
Davoo, is this the website you used to meet your current girlfriend?
Uh, no, that was a different one.
This website kind of sucks, because I'm not into these kinds of fetishes enough, you know?
Right.
And whatever.
Anyway, so, like, there's that difference.
So when you go to somewhere like DeviantArt, it's a much more obscure realm of, like, such
that the sex doesn't even have to be involved.
In fact, that's actually another thing I want to talk about in a minute, but I might have
to, like, restrain myself so I don't just go on straight for over two hours.
Oh, please don't.
Um, which is that, like, um, sex isn't even, most of my fetishes, like, the whole diaper
thing, right, the whole ABDL segment.
Yes.
That's the acronym, right?
But what does ABDL stand for?
There's two different subgroups.
There's diaper lover, that's the group for the diaper thing, right?
Then there's adult baby, which is in phantalism, right?
Yeah.
You can't be one without the other.
I mean, I think a lot of people are, but ABDL is the place.
Vote up in phantalism, people.
Yeah.
So, um, so, so, like, that often, if you go to DeviantArt and you look up, like, diaper
art on there, most of it, in fact, the vast, vast, vast, vast, vast majority of it, never
is explicitly sexual if you don't have that fetish.
And if you were somehow unaware as to how fetishes work or you just weren't cottoned
on to the nature of the internet, you might just be generally weirded out and not even
realize that there is anything sexual going on.
And in fact, the comments section and the whole community on DeviantArt is amazingly
chased or chat, roundabout.
It never, there's no one who can just comments, I came to this picture, like you'd find on
certain other websites.
There's other, there's a site called diaperedanime.org where people will say, I came to this picture,
right?
Um, but I'm just like, if you go to DeviantArt, is there a gif of the Rugrats theme song when
Tommy's diaper falls out of the air and lands on his legs perfectly?
Uh, probably, yeah, but you know, there's some good art.
I came to that too.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, no one ever talks about sex there.
No one talks about being turned on by all that shit.
People just sort of say, ah, cute.
Everyone is on DeviantArt, you're saying?
Yeah, yeah, it's almost like a weird, like sort of drug deal.
Like it's like, it's like a drug market where everyone's like, hey, do you have the, uh,
the gashi?
Thank you.
Mmm.
Ah, this one will be quite nice up on my mantelpiece, you know, are you suggesting there's Deviancy
on DeviantArt?
Yeah, well, in the diaper community specifically, but all those like, I don't know what to call
them, like the pure fantasy ones where no sex is involved, like most characters aren't
hardly even drawn in sexually compromising positions half the time, right?
There's never any like genitals involved, almost never, and it's like, but it's still
entirely something you can jack off to.
I can jack off to.
It's entirely something that's like, it's, it's all those things I mentioned before,
context, humiliation, the sensation of like what it must feel like, you know, like what
a diaper feels like tact-highly, you know, maybe some people think, or think it's a really
good feeling.
I don't fucking know.
See, that's, that's interesting because I just fundamentally do not understand anything
that isn't like, like jacking off to anything that isn't just sex, and that's a limiting
thing for me.
That's a, that's a hang up I personally have.
So I'm just very interested to hear all about this.
You're only living half a life, Nate.
I know.
I need to expand my horizons.
And it's right.
Yeah.
I should have got a diaper for this and be crapping in it as well.
This is my favorite episode so far, and we're like half an hour in.
Yeah.
This is good.
I'm actually learning from DeVoo.
I didn't know all these things existed, and he's like educating us on the communities,
and I'm really interested in it.
Me too.
Well, do you have any, any further points to make?
I mean, we've got some other things we can go to if you like, but.
Dude, he has two hours.
He has a whole PCP lecture of points to make.
I'm sure he does.
Oh yeah.
So what you were talking about a little bit ago, Nate, is that like, because you can
go pretty deep dive into de-esque stuff sometimes, right?
What is de-esque?
Like D, four-channel board.
Oh, de-esque.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
makes you look like a little girl.
Yum, yum, yum.
Big difference between that and like writing a, yeah.
Big difference between that and then like extensive
multi-branching stories on cyoc.net
about a girl becoming incontinent and shitting herself
and being changed by every different member of her family
and coming to that for about a week and straight,
maybe something along those lines
where sex never even gets involved.
That's being submerged into the same fetish
that for others is a garnish.
So for you, are you saying it's a garnish or a submerge?
Yeah, that's my dude, that's my guy.
If I can ask, what is the appeal of a girl becoming retarded
and her parents changing her diaper?
Well, doesn't Incontinent just make you
take control of your balance?
Nikki, what's the feeling about a girl becoming retarded
and her parents changing her diaper?
Good question.
She just gives me a sad face.
It's just deep personal trauma.
That's really the root cause.
No, I'd add it back.
Yeah, you wanna answer?
Oh, I'm gonna give her the mic.
She's coming up.
Get in close now.
Any second.
What's the time to get everybody retarded?
Yeah, what's hot about your girl being retarded
and then changing her diaper?
Being retarded?
Her being, okay, I can relate to that.
Yeah, it's not hot for the guy or the girl.
So she just says being powered.
Sorry, I have the headphones on so she can't hear you.
This is a really awkward idea.
I knew having her being in the room would be weird,
but whatever, it's the sheer powerlessness.
The sheer dehumanization of it.
They have no independence now, right?
Well, what about you?
Those are the things I usually whisper
in her ear during sex.
Is it?
You have no brains, no ability to think,
no independence, no ability to make decisions,
no freedom.
You don't have the option for freedom.
You have no ability to choose.
Okay, all of that is true in Trump's America
for a woman anyway.
It is, I mean, in North America.
Now, I know that sounds weird people,
but I'm sure there's a lot of virgins.
Listen to this.
This is normal shit to say during sex.
It is not weird to say the most fucked up shit
to get me out for sex.
They don't even know why you're bringing that up.
I thought it was perfect for fun.
All right, I got a question.
I got a question.
Oh, Nikki wants water.
Remember, I thought she wanted the microphone.
She just wants some water.
She must be sweating a lot.
Okay, all right, okay.
All right, debut.
Yeah?
That would back...
More like Dupu.
There it is.
Nailed it.
I've been holding that one in all night.
Hey, that's what you're gonna say tonight, aren't you?
Oh, hey.
All right, everybody, shut up.
Give, go on.
Would that idea work also with somebody
who was just a vegetable?
Like they had brain damage and they can't move.
Not as good, no, not as good, no.
All right, why is the diaper part of that then?
What...
Why is that?
I don't think they're tart enough
to be needing to wear diapers.
It's just kind of a, I guess, sort of an indicator
of the low level that they're functioning at,
sort of if they need that, you know.
But it's only attractive if you know it's an illusion,
because if it was like an actual person,
you wouldn't want to do, right?
Right.
Maybe.
Yeah, so yeah, I can see that.
Maybe he slips that in.
Well, if there was a real 20-year-old girl
who actually fell off a motorcycle without a helmet
and became retarded and wore diapers,
who would want to have sex with her?
Well, okay, all right, all right,
let's not put this position.
Guys, you gotta listen to me on this, okay?
Because there's nothing wrong with being attracted
to the most fucked up shit.
But it's not like you have to,
even if you admit that you're attracted to something,
that doesn't mean that you're going to like
fuck a person who meets these people.
Yeah, I wasn't, like, it's okay to be attracted to it.
I was asking if you would actually rape this retarded person.
I don't think-
No, because I would feel bad.
If I was brought up in a society
for whatever reason rape was not frowned upon, then yeah,
but that's not the case.
You know, that's all we need.
That's all we need.
Let's keep going.
Because I mean, like, it's not like,
oh, I'm not doing it because I'm not allowed to.
It's like, because people would feel bad about it,
I would feel bad about it, right?
Okay, everybody needs to understand,
if you raise in a culture where like you,
when you get older, like you and your brother
have to fight and you have to kill each other
and the winner gets the inheritance or whatever,
like you would do that.
Like that's, that's what we're talking about.
Like being in an immoral culture,
we understand of course that these things are not good
that you shouldn't do them in real life, but like-
But if society thought it was okay, we would just do it.
Well, if society thought you could do things
that you wanted to do that aren't okay now,
then you would do them too.
Like that's just how humans work.
It is.
Oh no, I'm totally on board.
Why are you so defensive?
I'm on board.
I'm on board of people getting involved, like doing,
like, like, but when it comes to not doing harm,
like, you know, maybe do I Google like medical journals
of parents raising their retarded children
and jack off to that?
Sometimes potentially, you know, I don't know.
Sometimes we've all been there, Nate.
This is fascinating.
Why are you freaking out?
I'm not freaking out.
I'm just making sure people understand.
That's my only goal.
I understand completely.
It's very much not as bad to say out loud,
but the same sort of things sometimes happens
with me with like breast expansion and stuff
where I would look at charts of like the average cup sizes
over certain decades and I would jack off exclusively
to the idea that breasts in general are getting bigger.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, man.
That's kind of funny.
I mean, like, okay, I want to talk about sequences
for a second because like there was some like medium sized
kerfuffle on the internet a few years back
over like some image that was meant for Tumblr alone,
but somehow found its way into the SJW anti SJW sphere
on Twitter and Facebook and such.
Of an image sequence.
It was probably Sargon of Akadu leaked it.
Of like this girl who's like a bimbo, a gyaru,
or however you say it.
Gyaru, yeah.
And she slowly transforms into becoming shorter,
smaller, pail, darker haired, glasses wearing,
book carrying, right?
And you look at it.
Are you sure it wasn't the other way around?
Doesn't she become the bimbo?
No, it's the other way around.
Wait, no, it's the other way around.
I remember specifically.
And like.
Okay, if you say so.
And like for me at first,
because I had heard about it in the context of this SJW fight,
I was like, oh wait, huh?
Is that trying to send this message of fucking,
it's important to not be attractive and be bogus instead?
But then I looked at it more closely.
I'm like, oh, it's a transformation sequence.
And I posted it without context on the PCP chat
and Gib was like, oh hey, it's a transformation sequence.
It's a very classic medium of like,
have point A to point B, you show the steps.
You know, maybe they turn into a pig,
they turn into like twice their age,
two characters merge into one, you know, that kind of thing.
It's the sequence of events
that itself can be attractive.
Yeah.
And I remember people got mad about that
cause, okay, I honestly can't remember
which step came first,
but like she went from like what appears to be like a smart,
I mean, she gets a tan or like she loses her tan,
but people took that to be like a racial thing that like,
she's like becoming like people thought it was that,
which it wasn't at all.
She just like got a tan
and became like a sexy housewife or whatever.
Yeah, I mean, it was a racist thing.
It was a racial thing.
It was a fetishistically racial thing,
not a politically racial one.
I'm not sure I agree with that.
I mean, maybe that's true,
but it looked to me like she just got a tan.
Yeah.
But okay, but putting that aside,
like it doesn't matter either way.
It's about the transformation and that's it.
I was thinking about like why it is that like growth
and like big things getting bigger
and like not getting smaller,
like getting smaller is bad.
I don't like that.
But getting bigger is good.
And I was thinking probably that stems from-
Is it because you want to be bigger?
Is that like a personal thing maybe?
I don't know.
I think it might stem from the fact that I'm just small
and I'm used to people being bigger.
And the idea of a giant woman is pretty good, you know?
Giant woman.
Like that Steven Universe episode.
Yeah.
Oh man.
See, that's the first one I ever saw.
I like that a lot.
And I thought, you know,
this is going to be good jerk off material later on.
We were talking about relating,
connecting empathizing with the guy in the fucking thing.
You know, you also have like the contrast of the fantasy.
I'm sure a lot of people are like,
well I want a guy who's all attractive and muscular
because that's what I want to be.
And of course that's obviously why dicks are so big.
You know, as a potential alleged,
slightly above average dick user myself, right?
That has no appeal to me.
And honestly, I just look at like a 10 inch dick
and I'm like, whatever.
Small penis humiliation, SPH as it's called on D,
is pretty good.
I'm really down for that.
Like when like the anime girl just grabs the dick
and it's like, this is it?
Wait, isn't it going to get, wait, it's already hard?
Huh, I don't think this is meant to go inside a girl.
Because from your perception,
that's such a fantastical situation
that you would never find yourself in.
Yeah, of course.
We got a real Mike Matei over here is, you know.
Yeah, wait, what the fuck does that mean?
Mike Matei has a huge cock.
He does?
That's canon.
Yeah, it's like 11 inches long.
You can see it in a video when he shows it off.
Oh, really?
I haven't seen that, but.
Yeah, he tells James like that his wife loves it.
Well, that's nice.
Yeah, cause James Rolfe is a cuckold.
Well, that's true.
Okay, well let's move on.
I have another one, like a whole separate topic
that I wanted to bring up.
And I know this has been discussed many times
by various members of our organization here,
but I want to talk about anthropomorphization,
specifically when it comes to like animals and shit.
And I just want to make a broad point at first,
at least how I look at this stuff.
I mean, and several of us have made videos about this,
but like when I, like for example, my little pony, right?
Okay, so those, those, those.
What's that?
That's, it's this, you know,
it's this famous Japanese anime you probably have.
But it's.
Oh, don't they have a movie coming out soon
that we're all going to go review together?
I'm pretty.
I'm pretty excited.
On an ABAP channel.
There's going to be some things.
There's going to be some things happening with that movie.
Uh-oh.
I'm very excited for it.
But so like when I jack off to my little pony,
as I do all the time, like what, what I'm jacking off to
is their human characteristics that are attractive to me.
It like, there's no difference to me
between jacking off to like, I don't know, rarity
or like some anime character,
because neither of them are exactly human.
So what you're jacking off to is this sort of representation
of a human female, which I find sexually appealing
because I am a human male and I am programmed
to respond to these things.
Like they've got a pussy.
There it is.
The hood, the mane, the cutie mark.
Yeah, exactly.
All those human things.
Their faces.
To me, like anthropomorphization is so like banal.
It's like.
Exactly.
A lot of the time it's really just surface level features.
As long as they have tits, you know.
But the ponies don't have tits.
Okay, but if you doggy style fuck them,
then you just look at their ass,
but you just look like a human ass.
No, no, no.
Like the anthropomorphize images of ponies
as if they were humans, they're just girls with tits
and what are you talking about?
Well, I'm kind of talking about like.
Are you fucking free?
I'm talking about the ponies themselves
and the way they have human character,
like they aren't just horses.
They're like this cartoonified version of horses
that have a lot of human characteristics.
Come on.
Well, I made a video about that many years ago.
And I think it was great.
I'd love that video.
I think it made a lot of good points.
I think the appeal makes a lot more sense.
It's much more apparently obvious, self-evident
if you check out monster girls.
And I mean, monster moves that made the show
will immediately educate you as to the appeal,
which is you're getting everything that,
usually 75 to 85% of everything
that you like about human girls
with some cool animal features tacked on.
So it's like the idea of like,
man, wouldn't it be cool if you could ride your girls back
and like she's perfectly comfortable
taking you around town like that, you know?
How would it feel to be fucking her from behind
but so far behind that her head's all the way
like fucking over there
because she's a goddamn horse, right?
She's a centaur baby, right?
That's the thing that like.
Spider girls are pretty good.
Rockin' air is great.
Best girl, lover, she's a beauty.
I like Lola Bunny.
You could do her Bunny style
and then play human basketball with her.
Wait, what's Bunny style?
Is that where they fell?
You just jumble, get into that and fetish his part too.
Okay.
Well, I mean, that's pretty much my entire point.
I just want to kind of go over that.
Like, yeah, I will jack off to furries all the time.
I'm not a furry at all,
but I have absolutely no problem
like jacking off to a furry.
But the furry doesn't necessarily.
I mean, like.
Yeah, like that's not what I'm into.
I'm into like the female human aspects.
Oh yeah, there's plenty of furry stuff.
The further furry it gets, the furrier it gets,
the more I have a hard time with it.
Some ears, nothing, right?
Some fur on the skin, as long as the art's good.
Muscles, you better have a really hot context
and some good dialogue that I'm gonna be able to jack off to,
or I can't go any further, right?
And like sometimes I specifically seek out furry art
because it has its own culture, its own style,
and sometimes I'm into some of the things it does.
Furry art is way more just abrupt
with getting to the point of what it wants,
at least like in the whole diaper zone,
like art that is both furry and diaper,
is just way more like, all right, here's what you want.
Boom, crank it up to 11.
Furry art tends to crank things up to 11
and be even more shameless and direct.
What's that, Gib?
Now I've noticed that as well,
like furry art is like always like.
Shameless.
Like, they're huge.
Yeah.
It's huge, every time, every single thing that they could be.
Right, so I was on a pretty big furry kick
for like a week, a month or two ago,
because I was just really into a shamelessness kick.
And the furry community provides that.
You know what's like a good example of that?
For many, many years,
there's been a vast shortage of like Kingdom Hearts porn,
but like Kingdom Hearts furry porn.
Now there's a diverse community out there.
Really? That's it.
To some extent.
I mean, I'm not an expert,
but like I feel like I've seen at least as much,
if not far more.
Is there the Lion King in that?
Is that one?
Well, Sora does become a lion in Kingdom Arts 2,
which you should play and find out yourself,
because it's pretty cool.
Does somebody have sex with the Keyblade?
The Keyblade is not too involved in this situation.
You just gotta be a porn of a woman fucking.
I have a key fetish, so that's my problem.
An actual Keyblade model, right?
It's gotta be somewhere.
Probably.
People who are into like fucking metal things
are probably called Shinies, right?
Oh, they're called by that, maybe.
Well, when it comes to like,
my mind as a porn consumer of my mind,
crows are into shiny porn.
Crows would be into that.
My mind, when it comes to Kingdom Arts 4,
if you wanted to involve the Keyblade,
it would be like some sort of situation
where they're like unlocking this
like ultimate Chastity Belt or something, you know,
where like you, the key is used to access the vagina
in some way, and Chastity Belt comes to mind.
You know, I'd go for something like that.
Or you could fucking with the Keyblade,
though it would be pretty uncomfortable.
It's not really shaped for that.
But you know, you get it.
Like, oh, sorry. Life finds a way.
What if you, yeah, go ahead and give.
What if it's like an anthropomorphized door
with a keyhole vagina?
Oh my God. Hell yeah.
Hell yeah. I've never seen that one, but.
That's a good idea.
Let's get to it, boys.
Let's get drawing.
Let's get writing.
That's the next draw cast.
That's a good idea.
Whichever. If all the artists in the audience
haven't been drawing everything we've been saying,
up to this point, they should be.
If any of you. I need lots of fan art of Davoo
and his girlfriend pooping on each other.
Oh, no, that's just scat zone.
That's just the actual zone of like being
into the tactility of it.
That's too far. Don't do that.
No, no, no. That's really just for people
who want to have the feeling of it,
which I am not into at all.
That's why I'm pretty hesitant to do it.
It's like. Can we draw Davoo in a diaper?
Oh. I don't want to jack off to myself.
I mean, I guess.
I don't know what your girlfriend looks like, dude.
I can't draw her.
No one wants to jack off to like their own situation.
What's fascinating about porn is like the newness of it,
the fantasy of it that you can get involved with personally.
Yeah. Porn yourself.
I don't know.
I mean, there was a little porn
of drawing of my, of keg standard back in the day,
which was fine, but.
Nate, the other day,
somebody drew the art of you as a girl
and you jerked off to that in the PCP chat for like an hour.
But that's because that's.
It's different from your real life, yeah.
Fantasy and sexy and something?
Well, it's still you.
I definitely get turned on by PCP to the
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Monkey. Hold the fuck on.
You tell, like, like rule 63 versions of yourself
are like some of the hottest things to jack off to.
Cause like, to know yourself.
It's not just you though.
It's girl you.
And contrary to popular belief,
there are actual differences between women and men.
Look it up.
Google is a big fan of this theory.
So, you know, like there's differences there
and we could explore them together
while I pound the shit out of her vagina.
I mean, I will say right now on my channel,
I'm doing an art contest to draw me as a girl
doing lesbian shit with Luna Lovegood.
But I, like I don't masturbate to it.
I just appreciate it.
But I guess I'm just not in that head space
of wanting to jerk off to myself.
I mean, if there was like a dogen
of like this female version of character of me
that someone had made, like I would absolutely
jack off to it without a doubt.
But like.
Get to work PCP.
You know, I've never been much of like
a jack off to picture kind of guy though.
That's just not really my.
I actually don't know whether I would
if it was like a girl version of me.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know why that's.
It depends on the situation though.
Like if it's me like editing a video
and like releasing it and I'm like,
yay, that was fun.
Also, I'm a girl.
Also, I'm going to suck this cock now.
Like.
Hell yeah.
Wait, just let her masturbate to yourself,
sucking a cock?
Well, if it's girl version of me,
that's one of the many sexual acts that she could do.
But the thing is, when you watch porn,
you imagine yourself as the dick,
but now you're imagining yourself as the person sucking.
Well, yeah.
No, no, no, no.
I'm still projecting.
You're sucking your own dick.
Exactly what you're sucking somebody else's dick.
I'm projecting myself in the situation
as the guy getting fucked by the gender swapped version
of myself.
Wait, so you're imagining you having sex with yourself.
Oh, come on.
This is basic shit.
I know that you've thought of this a thousand times yourself.
No, I haven't.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
What are you fucking talking about?
I'm thinking of girl version of me
and I'm thinking of me getting fucked by a dude.
I'm thinking, oh my god,
well, how would I feel being fucked with the vagina?
Okay, I am not thinking about it that way.
I'm not thinking about that.
You're thinking about sucking cock.
I'm thinking about like a female version of me
that exists that I could then fuck.
And that's what I'm, you know.
That's what I'm doing.
I mean, that is kind of like funny
because you are the best guy ever.
So of course you'd have enough of an ego
to want to fuck yourself.
Dude, every person in the world,
I don't believe that you don't want to fuck
your own gender swapped version of yourself.
Because everyone knows about it.
The girl version of me is going to be as ugly as me
and I have higher standards.
I'm a golden god.
I'm a fucking beautiful hero, man.
Don't push your beliefs onto me.
I don't want to fuck me.
I'm hideous.
You know what, that's fair.
I think I wear a monkey mask in these fucking videos, dude.
Yeah, all right.
Okay.
I don't want to fuck that.
I've had the thought because everyone has the idea.
Like what would it be like if you met
a female version of yourself?
Yeah.
And I'm just, all I think about is like the conversations
we would have or how awkwardly it would begin
or whether we would even want to hang around each other.
And then it doesn't really ever go further than that.
I don't know why it's so different for you
and for me.
Well, it's like a pair of twins
where one's a boy and one's a girl.
Like do they wanna fuck each other?
Is that masturbation?
Absolutely.
I do enjoy like,
I do kind of enjoy like the idea of me as a girl
just for the cute aspect.
Like seeing like drawings of me just gender bent,
just doing normal things.
Like just being a pretty girl.
Like yeah, that'll be nice.
That's cool.
I like that idea, the idea that I'm the other gender
and I just look better because, you know.
Yeah.
And of course when I play Pokemon,
I always play as the girl.
I'd rather be a girl,
but that doesn't mean I wanna fuck me.
And of course there's like a bit of a fantasy element to it.
Like, you know, you can like in your head
make your female version look like basically
whatever you want.
So like, yeah, of course that's real.
But like when I kind of think of this female version of me,
she's also an anime character.
So, you know, like that's, that's.
It's also my little pony.
Of course.
Yeah, anime.
I already covered that.
D'Voo, have you finished your big story yet?
Big story?
He's got the rolls points I think, right?
You said that he had like a whole thing planned out.
Oh, I've just been like taking down notes occasionally here
and there.
I have another one, which is like,
Hippo talked about like other emotions that get attached.
Because we are an hour in just to let you guys know.
That's true.
I'm looking at the waveform.
I'm paranoid about audio glitches.
So like Hippo was talking about how like things can be scary.
And I believe he was alluding to the idea
that it sort of enhances the emotions.
Like, gets your blood rolling a little bit faster.
And that can like, that can like, you know,
enhance the groin area action if you know what I mean.
It's like some subdom should, right?
Right.
And like, there are lots of things
that I'm just fascinated with in general,
that then also become fetishes.
They were like, hold on.
Wait a second.
Oh, anyway, there are things that I can.
Wait, what?
There are things that I can stick out?
Of course.
Sorry, there's just people walking around.
I haven't been, I haven't had like much of my own room
in the last handful of months.
Anyway, there are things I was fascinated with
for a long time, even like as a child.
And my body did whatever it could manage
to do to turn me on in some way.
It didn't have the resources yet, right?
There's just general fascinations, right?
Gender bending is definitely one of them.
The exploration of the other sex back and forth
is a very interesting concept for me.
So much, I'm just really so obsessed with that concept
that it pisses me off when it shows up
in a piece of media because it's always done
as a joke or for quick fan service
or for like some sort of sitcom-y thing,
although Ranma One Half,
and never really explored as a real theme,
as a real narrative, right?
And I love it when it's really talked about,
when it's really like explored
like in an interesting, intimate way,
but it's almost never done that.
And it always teases me so, it pisses me off so bad,
both for my dick and for my heart,
because I find it a fascinating concept.
And so I feel like I'd never be able to like
watch Ranma One Half.
I'm even really hesitant about watching Your Name
because I know it's gonna have that thing.
And I know they're not gonna really explore that in depth.
They're just gonna have some scenes that tease me
and I'll just be left frustrated, right?
But what I wanna do, and I have done sometimes,
is there are some, there's some ecchi fricking mongas
out there that really explore it.
There's one where this guy gets into the body
of like a seven-year-old girl.
And like, it's great.
For the first, it's called Ichinense Nina Chaturla.
And it's like almost every page is in service
of either your dick or like feeling the concept
of what it would be to suddenly be
in this different body, right?
And so what does he do as the seven-year-old girl?
Oh, he'll go to school, but still secretly study
for his exams in high school,
because that's what he has to do.
Hang on.
How's that sexual?
Yes, I think I may have seen that,
or seen something very similar.
I think I told you about it, yeah.
No, but it was like this idea
that this guy got transformed into the body
of a little girl or a little boy, I forget.
But it was like, he thought it was great
because like, oh, I'm younger now,
and I have all this future knowledge.
But then slowly, his like future knowledge
started to go away as you realize
that he had a child's brain.
You're gonna have to find that and link that to me.
Because then he was like,
oh, I don't know how to count anymore.
What's going on?
Oh my God, I had to read that one.
I don't even know what it was.
It may have been like, it was years ago
that I think I've seen that.
Yeah, that's definitely not the one I'm referring to.
Now, I was gonna talk about age regression.
That's just my outright favorite concept in anything.
Mental thought, hypotheticals, science fiction,
fetishes, anything.
That's my favorite thing ever.
The series movie 10 has a bunch of age regression
of all the characters,
but especially Nami becomes a little baby girl
and Robin goes from like 30 to like 27 or something.
It looks, no, she goes like 16.
She goes exactly the same, but it's amazing.
14.
See, the same problem.
It would just piss me off
because it wouldn't go deep enough.
What about Benjamin Button?
There's a whole movie about that.
I actually didn't finish that movie.
I mean, it's a dude, I'm not like, you know.
Yeah, I didn't finish.
Yeah, I love it.
But anyway, yeah, like so the manga I mentioned before,
Ichi Nensei Nina Chattara.
It's like probably the most complicated Japanese title
I can enunciate.
I know Nichi Nensei means first year.
That's what I know, folks.
There you go.
Right, so he, like in the second,
the book always refers to him as he,
just because he never accepts it, right?
He eventually gets cured at the very end.
But like-
Because as we all know, gender is what you identify as
as opposed to your biology.
This is what it all just did.
Right, so chapter two, he like wakes up and like-
Nate, shut up.
And like starts walking around the room
and like immediately, like it has all this dissonance
with how many steps it takes to get from place to place,
how much he has to reach to grab shit.
And like just, it always explores like
how different things feel for him.
There's a part where like, he has to like jump up
on a pole to like save himself.
And he like-
Oh, he's jumping up on that pole.
How can we tell you about that?
Well, yeah, but what happens is that
as he's holding to the pole really tightly,
he's like, oh man, in my old body,
this would like, I'd be feeling the pressure
against my dick right now and this would be fun.
But in this body, it doesn't do anything for me, right?
Oh, they're going deep.
There's like a multiple part chapter
where he's like tries to figure out whether or not
he can like, you know, masturbate
in that young girl's body or not, right?
So like, it's like, it's just constantly exploring
like what is happening to him.
And that's what I want.
I actually found out about it, I think from D
because someone posted a comment saying,
I really, what I really want out of age regression
and like transgender stories is not so much just going ham
on the fan service as much as explore
what happens to their life.
Like show them hanging out, right?
I remember some people talking about they like it
when like a guy gets turned into a woman
and it just stays like that for years and has kids, right?
That's what I really want to see.
I want to see like Bruce Jenner.
Yeah, exactly.
So that's, and then for me, it's like, I don't know
that exploration of being in a different body
of having that like age taken away from you
is a very fascinating concept
that is definitely my least favorite thing about reality
is it doesn't have that or gender-bending remotes.
I know for months, I mean, I know for months
like gender bender and age regression remote
should be a real thing was a suggested title topic for PCP.
That's true.
Next week.
No, we already did that.
There's not really much to say about it at this point.
We did gender swapping, right?
Yeah, so like the fact that I'm so into it as a concept
gives it so much allure,
even if somewhere were to just cut off my dick.
And like the fact then that it also feeds into it, right?
And it creates this feedback loop
of still having a burning passion for it
even after I'm done.
I'm still thinking about it being like, yeah.
You know what I mean?
Oh, I know what you mean.
Well, all right, there you go.
All right, let's, anybody got some final points to make
on this before we go to questions?
I think it's about that time.
Well, I could talk a little bit more
about the whole like giant woman thing
because I didn't really say anything about that.
Okay, let's do it.
Well, I think I like the idea of like girls
that are taller than me, which is usually,
it's the other way around, like the short girl
is the cute one and you got to be a tall man,
but I'm not tall.
And I've always annoyed that the fact that I'm not tall
because it seems like tall guys get everything.
So it was like-
Don't worry, manlight uprising is coming.
Don't worry.
Yeah, yeah, at some point I just-
You can finish what Allie gets started.
That's right.
Like the idea that a woman could be like bigger than me
and like, you know, put our arms around me
and then cradle me like an idiot,
like a stupid, small little man.
Sure. I don't know.
Do you masturbate to the P-E-T-A sculpture?
The what?
The P-E-T-A where it's the Virgin Mary
and she's like nine feet tall,
cradling a little tiny Jesus.
Oh.
Someone should draw that picture
and replace Jesus with a gift.
You have to do it.
Someone, please.
Please give me hippo in the P-E-T-A.
I guess I didn't really have much to say about it.
I like giant stuff.
I like big things.
It's good.
Big things from a small packages, Gib.
Yeah, that's why my last girlfriend broke up with me.
She liked big things too.
The big things coming small packages argument
wasn't really enough for her when I, you know-
She wasn't buying it.
She didn't give a fuck about the motion of the ocean.
She wanted the wave.
It's sad, but true, folks.
Let's all kill ourselves.
Okay, let me just finish.
I just want to make one final point
just to sum up what I was saying before.
Remember, folks, it's totally normal
to be in all kinds of weird fucked up shit.
A lot of it just stems from the experiences
you have in your life, you know?
Yeah.
I'm sure that's an explanation for most of the reason
why I'm into the stuff that I'm into sexually.
Not that I'm that weird or anything,
but yeah, just, I don't know, don't shame anybody.
This is all totally normal, you know?
I think it's pretty normal.
Don't shame anybody, but if they rape a retarded person,
do arrest them.
I agree.
Yeah, I do endorse that, by the way.
I'm not, I'm saying that should be arrested,
that that wouldn't be allowed, that should be allowed.
As Davoo slyly slides away his proposition
to make rape illegal,
just slide that under my desk here.
All right, well that's it.
That would be the great PCP civil war
is that Davoo wants to make rape legal
and Munchy wants to make sex outline.
Yeah!
He'll have to go to war.
That's a great idea.
It'll just be like in the near future
where probably smoking will be banned
and weed will be legal everywhere.
Everything just gets flip-flopped,
you know what I mean?
See, if there is a war, I can't be on Munchy's side
because people always confuse us for each other
and I'll probably get assassinated
when they're trying to get him.
That's true, that's true.
Wouldn't it be even worse if,
even if you were on the opposite side,
they still assassinate you by mistake?
Now that would be bad.
Somebody on my team.
Exactly.
That would be real, you see.
So actually a war of people who like sex
and people who don't like sex
would instantly, well, not instantly,
but eventually the people who like sex would win
because they would make more soldiers.
Exactly.
But then again, maybe it's a good point.
Maybe our heroic virgins, like Isaac Newton types,
like they would all get together in advanced science
by like a thousand years
because they're not distracted
by disgusting sex havers anymore.
Maybe that would happen, you know?
Those heroic virgins, like Elliot Raj
or the Columbine kids.
Yeah, exactly.
The Columbine kids are heroes.
Elliot Raj would have been a fine warrior
if he had a cause to wave his, you know,
to a banner to wave, you know.
If he had a real card to batter people with.
He had some issues to sort out
beyond just his main thing.
He was pretty good at World of Warcraft.
Hey, no argument there.
And who, what makes a man beyond his Warcraft account,
really, not much.
All right, let's go to our questions here, everybody.
Remember, hashtag askPCP, we do it every Saturday.
There you go.
Hey, can I come out with like a little bit of an announcement,
like to talk about some shit that's happening?
I was just checking my Twitter.
So, okay, here's some YouTube titles for you.
The big change in the anime industry
that has people, I can't read the rest.
Her potential is insane.
He saved this one, dot, dot, dot.
Oh no.
You, five exclamation marks.
Digi has gotten into some Twitter beef
with some guy who doesn't like his thoughts
about this shit, about the whole anime streaming thing.
He's doing it publicly,
so I'm not breaking any boundaries here.
Now, I'm not gonna make any comment myself.
I haven't watched this guy.
His name is Forneverworld,
or as I like to call him, Forlorn Hope
that he'll ever get laid in his life.
He said, I'm not a bad YouTuber.
He said, I'm a bad YouTuber,
responding to Digi calling him a bad YouTuber.
He says, when you don't have to rely on clips and images
to get audience retention, come back to me.
Wait, wait, what?
I think he's referring to how Digi's videos,
like with Unate, like the podcasts,
get less views.
Listen, it's not because they don't have images.
I mean, that's part of it.
The fact that you don't rely on images
to get views of Forlorn Hope that you'll ever get laid
is that all of your videos have clickbait titles
and his do not as often.
So anyway, that's all I have to say about that.
I don't give a fuck about this beef
between Digi and this other guy,
but like, is he making a,
I don't understand the point.
Is he saying that it is bad to add clips
and images to your videos?
I don't understand. I think he was saying
that the only reason people watch your videos
is because you put clips in them.
Yeah, but you're one of those mainstream guys
who dole the senses of your audience
with a bunch of fancy clip keys dangling before their forehead.
That's why I don't understand the point
of what you said about like,
he's like, but that isn't an insult to the videos
of that's just a still image from one anime
that we just leave up and don't animate
because we're not editing anything.
Yeah, I'm looking at it.
It looks like all of his videos are just vlogs
with his big face in the camera, so.
Okay, well, this is a huge waste of time.
It's funny that I'm jumping into like,
putting my, like sticking my dick in this horrendous nest
on the podcast that is literally loaded
with the most material against me
that could possibly be posted.
Hey, fucking whatever.
Well, to be fair, you posted a picture
in this for never world guy.
His own chosen profile picture looks like a retarded person.
So I wouldn't feel too bad about what he has to say.
Yeah.
I don't give a shit about any of this.
Let's get to the question.
I just had to get that off my tongue.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, here's one.
At Aaron underscore fell asks,
why did you all pick your respective names?
Apart from Nate, we all know why.
I'm the best guy ever.
What can I say?
Shut the fuck up.
That's a good question.
Hippocrite was just a-
I've been trying to figure out the meaning behind that.
I can't tell what hippocrite means.
Please explain to me.
What do you mean to me?
It means that puns are awesome.
It means it's, I thought like critical hit
and also gaming critic.
Like critical hits are in games, gaming critic, crit
and hippocrite as in like it's an animal.
And I just thought of that one day out of nowhere
and I thought I gotta have that if that's gonna be,
I gotta keep that name.
So I made a YouTube channel.
Yeah.
So that I could, you know, keep it.
And then that's it.
Good boy.
I was protecting.
I thought it was because you always logically
contradicted yourself and we're acknowledging
that you were a hypocrite,
but also you are very bad at spelling.
Cause you're English.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm surprised there's not like a you in there or something.
At the beginning, my thing was also
on top of all those other parts of the pun,
hippocrite as in I will say things hypocritically
so that in case I actually do be a hypocrite,
I could say, look, well, look at my name.
What are you gonna do?
Nigga, what is the channel called?
What are you fucking talking about?
You've got cover for life.
I haven't really utilized that at all
because the only way I'm a hypocrite
is that my name is hypocrite, but I'm not hypocritical.
That's true.
That's how I use it.
Oh, that makes sense.
Monkey, how'd you come up with this?
The appeal of Hippo's channel for me is that
he is so authentic and genuine with his love
for like the games he played when he was younger.
So I wouldn't like it if he started saying
hypocritical things like for a meme,
I had to take away from some of the magic.
I'm glad you haven't done that.
My name is, it was not chosen as a username.
It was a name thrust upon me in high school
by my so-called friends because they noticed
that I resemble both a human and a monkey.
So they went ahead and threw those words together
and it stuck and I embraced it and now that's me.
Oh, I didn't know that that came from friends or something.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, I could see where they got that idea
from the way you look in videos.
You do kinda look like a monkey.
Yep, I'm very happy with it.
And it helps that I'm five foot seven
because I'm about the height of a monkey too.
Okay, DeVoo.
That's tall in me.
My username means that...
Well, yeah, but you're a gibbit.
You're smaller than a monkey.
That's true.
When I got on the internet,
I didn't really feel like having a username.
My first name was just my name, but condensed a bit.
But then my dad was like,
it just looks too much like your name.
It looks kind of dangerously Google-able.
I'm like, okay.
It's very interesting that your dad was giving you critiques
on your user names for your online activities.
I mean, it was like my name and then my last initials.
And he was like,
I don't know, that seems a little dangerously Google-able.
I'm like, you're right.
And I just had this, I don't know what day, what moment,
what fever dream, just the whole idea of taking my name,
which is David,
just changing the last syllable to an ooo came from.
And I just came up with it when I was 13
and never changed it.
Pretty fortunate,
because it seems to age pretty well.
Like the further I go on in my life,
it just seems to take on new meanings.
Like people, my PCP friends,
you guys tend to describe it as like sounding all mysterious,
like I'm some sort of abstract mythological beast.
Yeah.
Or like it rhymes with the dupu, which is a getup.
And that too.
I always thought of it as soon as I saw it,
I thought davoodoo, like he's a witch dog.
Oh, shit.
It reminds me a little bit of my friend John
that I reference sometimes on here.
He actually, he calls himself-
John Tron.
John Tron, that's right.
Yeah, he's a different John.
He calls himself John-os sometimes.
It's not his name.
He just came up with it
and introduces himself as John-os sometimes.
Nice.
No idea why.
Yeah, no, the part of my name that didn't age too well
is I was calling myself like the great davood,
because that's like internet,
making yourself all grandiose.
Usually because davood is usually taken from most websites,
cause I think it's like a Spanish word name or something.
So it's actually not, up until a couple of years ago,
my name was like very, very bad for Google.
Like, cause there'd just be like some,
I think it was some rapper called davooda producer
or whatever.
So it's not great for Googling.
But usually the davood is never taken.
So it's a perfect middle ground.
That's why the duff stuck around.
How great is it to finally beat Google
and overcome that like search result thing
when like, I remember for like a year
after starting Best Guy Ever,
like when I searched it,
all this other shit comes up that I didn't give a fuck about.
But now finally, I have conquered Google
and now my shit comes up.
But I've been noticing,
hypocrite does not come up initially
when you search hypocrite and it pisses me off.
It's all people misspelling it.
Yeah.
Or it auto-corrects to normal hypocrite.
It's one of the biggest tragedies.
I didn't even think about that.
It will be fixed in time.
You just have to grow more and that just works itself out.
You just have to grow more,
but just like all that art you look at it.
Exactly.
So I can jack off to it.
I was about to say though,
that the poddy curse actually came up
when I typed it in.
I was having that same problem.
That's great.
Do you have to put like the period after the D and shit?
No, I didn't.
Whoa.
Just put a space.
Well, fuck, I gotta try that out.
Uh, okay.
In my house, all the period comes before the D.
Okay, here we go.
At papa mutt dog asks,
is the vape pen Mike?
Shout out, you ruined my flow.
Is the vape pen mightier than the sword?
There's a vape sword?
Could you imagine, could you imagine a vape sword?
Like it's actually the size of a sword
and you blow or you suck on one side
and it comes out of the tip of the sword right at the end.
I imagine it's like just take this potion sword
and just go and hit people with it.
Saying vape sword reminds me of invisible air,
which is the name of saber sword from Fate, Stay Night,
which is actually just, it's actually just Excalibur,
but they pretend that it's invisible air.
I would like Ben to have a vape sword.
Me too.
It would be very, it would be very cool.
That would be his fucking,
that would be a striped sword.
I would like Ben to not be alive.
No, wait, a vape katana, there we go.
That would, that would,
Ben is practiced.
When he's been striped as a specimen,
it would be vape, it happens, right?
Well, Ben is practiced in the art of Kendo
and has maxed out his Bushido stat,
so he's ready for that vape katana.
Okay, here's the greatest comment.
This isn't a question, it's just a comment,
but at Jam Shmain, it's spelled kind of funny,
says, thanks for fat shaming me
into losing 10 pounds, hashtag fit boy.
Oh, shit.
Hell, yes, ya main man, Manny,
is his, like, his main thing.
Oh, well, that guy, I know him.
You, you're welcome, dude,
and I will continue on this quest
to fat shame everyone into getting their shit together,
cause there's no excuse to not, you know, be a fit person.
Excellent, thank God for you, you're a hero.
Oh, here we go, at Swagdude.
I don't know if you want to answer this, Davoo,
but he's asking, how's Davoo's video game going?
Oh, very, very slowly, I just keep, you know,
I'll spend just weeks at a time,
just editing videos and then watching anime.
It's definitely, like, I don't know
exactly what speed it's gonna take,
but I'm having a huge fun time with it.
I am learning the incredible power of, like,
and when you're a teenager, you have unlimited time,
but no purpose in life, so you're depressed,
you're too depressed to make anything and all that good.
Well, at least that's how I was.
As an adult, I have that sense of mission,
but the sense of mission and the needing to make money
can also sort of trap you,
it can keep you trapped in this need for money.
So, basically, I've made enough money to,
well, I have not really a decent amount of money,
but I have my own career now and I have all my spare time,
and so I've bought myself that teenage sort of lifestyle
to work on something because I want to make it
and it doesn't have to make its money back.
I think it might, because, I mean, I don't know,
probably only, like, 108 people are gonna buy it,
that's basically what I'm prepared for,
but it's so great to just have all this time
to make something that I want to make,
but yeah, it's going around very, very, very slowly.
Don't expect it out by the end of the decade.
The decade? Looking forward to it.
Hey, that's only three years, you know, it's not that bad.
Oh, I thought he meant, like, the next 10 years,
I was like, well, four.
Well, this decade's almost over,
so it probably won't be this day.
D'Vu, I want to be alive to play the game,
so please don't take 10 years, I'll be dead.
Yeah, definitely not taking that long, yeah.
Okay, here we go, Hindu, Hindu God of Homoes, as-
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, good, yeah.
Our boat's good, what is the best boat?
No, I love boats.
Boats, the best kind of boat is a boat that can fly.
And her name is Going Mary.
Going Mary is the best boat.
No, no, really, like, the idea of a pirate galleon
that has either magically or scientifically
the ability to fly through the air
is my favorite thing of all time.
Hey, you know what you would like then?
Final Fantasy, specifically Final Fantasy IX,
because it's full of those.
Well, there we go.
It's aesthetic as fuck.
You'd also like the music video Boats and Hose.
You gotta have me, my Boats and Hose,
I think is how it goes.
That's pretty good, that's pretty good.
Yeah.
Okay, okay, here's one.
At the Wolf Heart, hey, what's up, dude?
This guy's a good artist, man.
Between single and multiplayer,
do you think one is superior,
and does the lack of the other-
Single player is superior.
affect your interest in a game?
Single player will make me want to play.
Very singularly focused on single player games
for the most part, yes.
Yeah, multiplayer, as long as it's,
if it's turn-based multiplayer, like a card game,
it's okay, but generally,
the idea of playing online with people,
the internet fucks me over more often than I would like,
and it just annoys me.
I have an idea.
I'm back to having not viable internet,
so it doesn't even matter anyway.
You know what's funny about this?
I almost exclusively play single player games,
but I just so happened,
I got Splatoon 2 recently from my Switch,
which I have been playing more than any other video game,
which is to say, I'll play one or two games a day,
which is 15 minutes, but I'll still do it,
and it's fun, and I'm certainly playing
in more than any other game right now.
Of course, I did just beat Hollow Knight,
and that took 40 hours split out
over many weeks of playing, so.
I guess I should clarify,
competitive multiplayer games, I hate.
Playing on a Minecraft server with people, that's fun.
That is super fun, that is super fun.
I used to play League of Legends a lot,
but I just cut the time out because it's not fun,
and it sucks.
Didn't everybody say Splatoon 2 sucks?
Splatoon 2 is fun as fuck.
I mean, I bought it because-
Splatoon 2 splats.
The biggest complaint was that it's too much
like Splatoon 1, and it certainly is,
but the thing is, I never owned Splatoon 1,
so I just wanted to play this game all the time,
and I don't have a Wii U, so I needed to get Switch,
and I already had a Switch, so I bought Splatoon 2,
and it's exactly what I wanted,
and it delivered, and it's fucking great for me,
maybe not for everybody.
The only thing I know about new video games
is what video game Donkey tells me,
so I just assumed it sucked.
Yeah, he was one of the guys making the criticism,
I think, that's just like, it's not enough,
it's just like the same game again,
with some extra couple of things.
It's like a DLC that you got conned out at 50 bucks for.
For people who played Splatoon 1 and owned it,
and if they were buying this to get an upgrade
or get the new game, I can see why they'd be
a little disappointed, but I-
Like any Call of Duty game ever.
Yes.
Yeah, it's like, this is one of the only times
Nintendo's gonna pull this kind of fast one on people, so.
But like the flavor I loved, and I got to be around,
fuck, it's her name, Callia Marie, it's Marie.
Yeah, Marie is there, and she's cute as fuck,
and the squids are squids.
They're minerals, Marie.
I don't, I don't know.
Jesus Christ.
I don't know what that means, explain that.
That's from Breaking Bad.
Oh, good, excellent.
Good joke, good joke to end on, everybody.
Hippo, you're supposed to get it, Hippo.
I saw that movie on the show.
I, you're goddamn right I got it.
Okay, we're done.
Yeah.
Oh, it's excellent, excellent.
Thank you for saving us, we're done, everybody.
Thanks for listening.
Make sure you pledge to our Patreon.
Go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Get those bonus episodes, of which there are five now.
Last one was Kill, Luck, Kill versus Hey Arnold.
Come the fuck on.
The result was shocked.
Is that the one that Ben released for free?
That is the one that Ben released for free
for a minute accident.
So everybody, you already heard this episode,
so go buy the other ones.
But even if you've already heard that one,
you can't get to any of the others
unless you go to the Patreon and pledge five bucks.
So there you go.
And there it is, folks, we're all done.
You ask us more questions next time
using the hashtag AskPCP on Twitter.
Follow us at tbcrastinators, subscribe, comment,
fuck you, et cetera, et cetera.
All right, we're all done.
Thanks for listening, everybody,
and we will see you next week with another one.
Oh, and I almost forgot, this is episode 69.
This is episode 69.
We did it, motherfuckers.
We did it.
Nailed this.
A convenient coincidence that we didn't bend over
as backwards to ensure happened.
I know it, my dude.
All right, everybody say goodbye.
Bye.
Yeah.
Uh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did come true?