Hello everyone, welcome. It's PCP. You know what it is. You know where you are. Welcome,
one and all. I'm the best guy ever. Join today by my brother Ben Saint.
It's nap time on the PCP. It's time to go to bed.
And you know him. Beloved sisters of Battle, Munchy, and Gibbontake. They're sisters. This is their lore.
We're brothers. They're sisters. This is a shit intro I don't care about. Radcon!
Hey, you're a week late idiot. We already talked about that last week.
Yeah, but the Kickstarter is like out, right? Or you know, gonna be out?
It may well be. It's possible. As a recording, we only God knows.
Did I tell you Ben that I was wrong about the 8-day thing? It's actually like a 1-3-day review period.
I saw the message. That's simply epic.
Is Kickstarter out by now? Is it not out by now? Only unchecked by doing the description.
My Kickstarter got approved in like an hour. So I'm hoping it performs similarly.
I feel it's a little awkward. If we knew it was coming out, I would love to be. Go to it now.
But I can say, if it is out, it's Schrodinger's kick. Go to it now.
Check the description.
Check the description box.
This Kickstarter exists in a state of superposition until examined, upon which time the URL links to the Kickstarter.
So we'll see if that happens.
I want to have a real heart to heart, real father to son moment with the audience right here.
Because I want to hopefully illustrate why exactly I'm back right now at this crucial juncture in the PCP's development.
Because for the past couple months, I've been thinking, you know, recording the PCP, whatever.
Who even fucking cares about that shit?
I hate money also.
What? Democrats? Republicans? I love those guys. And then I wouldn't go on the PCP.
And then, going to the PCP chat to discuss Radcon 4, you know, getting all worked up about this, and spending the many, many late hours at night.
I am so fucking sick of all of you after this week of nothing but nonstop discord calls working out all the bullshit.
I'm at the exact opposite where it's like, oh my god, actually I like everyone. Oh god, the PCP's cool actually.
So let's see if the PCP's cool or just the PC is cool.
On this episode, this will be a tryout run.
What? I hear you.
Oh wait, no I get it. It took me a second.
Very, very hard to understand.
We're going to have a battle against our rival, the MacP, you know?
Make Donald?
You know what I'm saying?
Stop, you're making me hungry.
Tim Cook?
Do you want to go get McDonald's Ben?
Yeah, a little bit. I'll just go get my classic two McDoubles, throw away the bun.
Dude, the other day I ate two McDoubles and it felt like I was a fucking god.
Did you throw away the bun?
No, I didn't.
Well, you were fucking wrong.
I like the bun. I feel like the bun...
Yeah, you like inflammation, you like diabetes.
You like to be a fucking coward.
I like soggy bread and I like ketchup and mustard which gets stained all over the bun.
Loves that sugar rest. Loves that insulin spike in his blood, you know?
Oh wait, I've been counting my calories and I, every single day, every single day has just been constant agony and not even worth it-ness.
Because I'm so fucking hungry. I'm just nodding off my own arm every single second that I get.
I'm literally the hungriest person and I'm starving to death actively as we speak right fucking now.
It's been a nightmare.
It has been challenging.
It's great.
Try to go an entire day without eating.
I did that yesterday until, I guess, Michelle did bring me a bunch of mochi late in the day, but it's not that hard.
Just for fun. And then you'll wake up the next day and you'll be hungry but you won't want to eat that much because you'll get full really fast.
I have done that before in the past, like intentionally, like I've fasted for a couple days.
I mean, I could use it again to refresh my memory.
I mean, because if you're used to eating a lot or more and then you go down to less, you're like, oh no, I'm accustomed to more food than this.
But if you fast for a little bit and then you start eating again, you're accustomed to less.
That's genius moves.
We're going to tell them comments that are just like, um, that's really like a bad view.
You're irresponsible. You're going to kill, you're going to kill a munchie, Ben. What are you doing?
He doesn't know any better.
Dude, if you don't eat food for one day, you fucking keel over and die so you could put a clock strikes mid night.
If there's one man who needs more kidney stones, it's munchie. There's no doubt.
Ben's got you covered on that front.
Speaking of food, I was walking past you.
Highly speculative.
I was in the grocery store the other day and I was walking past the ice cream section.
And I looked inside and you know, gazed at what it could be if I were a different man.
And I was looking and I saw an ice cream that I want to know your guys opinion on because I've been asked, I've been pulling everyone.
It seems nearly unanimous and I don't know why this product exists because it's so obviously reviled.
There's an ice cream where it is vanilla ice cream and then inside of the ice cream pent, there is french fries.
Like just pieces of french fries inside of it.
No, no, no.
Dipping french fries into shakes is delicious.
No, I'm against that as well.
Yeah, I'm against that too.
You're against that too.
No, I don't get it at all.
For sure.
No, okay, okay.
I understand french fries and chocolate a little bit because it's like salted chocolate sort of thing.
I never really understood the milkshake thing.
That's a slightly more socially acceptable version of like melting a slice of American cheese on your apple pie.
It's equivalently disgusting to me.
It doesn't make any sense and I don't see the appeal at all.
The reason why you would dip a french fry into a shake is because you're getting a massive difference in texture and in flavor.
It's like way different things.
Okay, it's hot and it's cold.
It's fluffy and crunchy and it's soft and sweet.
It's way different.
You put them in an explosion of different types of perspective.
Are you trying to say that you're pro this thing, Munchie?
No, I'm not trying to say that.
He's obviously saying that.
Listen to how lovingly he's describing the experience.
But he just said no.
He's lying.
There's a difference here.
Dipping in a shake is not like this ice cream pint at all because the fucking french fries are all soggy and gross and cold and disgusting.
They aren't fluffier crispy and they aren't hot.
They don't balance against the ice cream at all.
They're just fucking potatoes.
I guess I sort of see the path of logic that would convince one to make this product.
These fries have been processed and they have lived in that ice cream for who knows how.
I'm sure they've fucking absorbed their native environment and just become a homogenous mess.
How many fries are we tossing inside this block of ice cream?
It sounds at best dumb and pointless and at worst disgusting.
I'm very against it.
Yep.
I see no justification for allowing this in a civilized society.
Imagine if you could have fucking...
Look at this cross-section.
I don't see it.
While you post that.
What were you saying Gib?
I'm trying to imagine it.
Oh yeah.
Could you like fucking imagine like energy drink ice creams?
Imagine bang ice cream.
I can imagine it.
Oh my god.
Oh my god guys.
I have said it.
I have said it for years.
Yesterday I found a...
I was looking at vapes.
I was looking at vape flavors and I found it.
They made it.
They made caffeinated vape.
Oh.
Whoa.
Really?
Yes.
With like taurine and B vitamins and shit.
It's like energy drink vape.
I want some so bad but they were sold out.
Okay.
I just...
For the sake of argument is through the lungs the correct way to absorb like B12 and you know...
You know it's a reasonable question and I don't know the answer.
Okay.
Maybe.
But I mean the point is...
It's the superior option.
The point is I've been saying...
Like take it in the ass.
I've been saying the caffeinated vape sounds incredible and like something I want for a long time and I saw it.
It's real.
Somebody fucking did it.
Ben I had the exact same fucking altercation.
I found caffeinated water and they're like really fucking expensive for some reason.
Some order this as soon as I get and then I can get hydrated and caffeinated at the exact same thing.
We should be sponsored by waterjoe.com.
It's just water and caffeine.
What more do you need?
Dude look at how fucking like oh my god please think that I'm like really fucking healthy for you.
Please think that I will like make you cool.
They're clearly marketing this as like like to the people who like wake up, have like a cup of coffee, a black coffee and go to the gym.
They're like fuck the coffee man.
You just need the water and the caffeine.
You're a god of sports.
This french fry ice cream and I'm looking at the cross section.
I literally can't see the french fries.
We're talking about small bits of fries at most.
They are totally indistinguishable.
They don't look any different.
Oh look at that.
Aka in quote fast food.
Like on the label.
Stupid.
Yeah I guess so.
I mean I'd give it a try.
Actually you know I almost feel like the fact that it's like enmeshed in there and more and homogenized and just sort of blended into the.
It might make it better than.
It might.
Cause I'm on record.
I don't do the dip fries in milkshake thing.
I don't get it.
It doesn't appeal to me.
So I think maybe this might be better than that.
Just because maybe it would just sort of lend a kind of starchy salty texture to the ice cream itself.
Maybe.
I'd give it a shot.
You know what sounds like a really satisfying job though.
Being the guy who does cross sections of ice cream containers.
Yeah.
Probably gets a paid mad shit.
Cause this is definitely like a fucking shit.
I mean we're talking about a pro photographer.
People who made this ice cream are definitely on the fucking flight logs.
Honestly this doesn't look like that professional shot to me.
Like the resolution is not amazing.
But imagine taking this tub out of the freezer and just put it on the table and just take a knife and just like work it down through and split it in half and then set it out and take a picture.
Yeah I'd love to do that.
Do you think that they are working it down or do you think it's like a clean like samurai katana slice down the middle?
This looks like a fairly clean cut.
You need like a level 2, like a level 3, level 4 samurai to execute a slice of this level.
No.
You would want to get a very clean cross section with like a good down the middle cut.
And I don't think that like a clean like fast stroke would do that.
You would want to like play carefully place the knife on top of the tub and just like push it down slowly.
I'm sure they use like a bandsaw or some sort of like table.
You're probably right.
Thing to go zzz.
Wait dude.
Wait imagine.
Okay this cross section like this pint that's been cut in half.
What happens like after this photo?
Like does it just start like leaking out?
Like just start melting immediately and just spill on the fucking floor?
I mean well yeah.
They just throw it on the trash.
They're not going to eat it?
The cameraman's not going to eat every ice cream?
Are you mourning that somewhere out there a pint of ice cream was thrown away and not consumes?
It's the principle of the matter.
I understand.
People are starving in Africa.
It's true.
Wait okay going back to this caffeinated water thing real quick.
I just want to say that I like every single day have been waking up and I've been drinking energy drinks.
And they're all great and they're literally good for you at any doctor that tells you that they aren't.
It's literally fucking lying to you and it makes no fucking sense and I don't even understand it.
It's literally paid off in every way.
It's paid off by big sport water.
My brain and body hurt all the time now and I'm starting to crumple up into like origami.
And so I'm thinking okay maybe all this extra sodium and stuff that I'm getting from the energy drink is maybe not good.
But I love caffeine and caffeine is actually good for you and any doctor that tells you that it's not is literally lying to you and wrong.
So how can I get caffeine and anything else?
I agree.
I've got a prescription for you and the prescription is get up and do yoga.
Do yoga.
First thing don't drink coffee.
Do yoga for 10 minutes when you wake up.
Are you for real?
I've been doing it.
I've been doing it the last little while.
What?
You could do both.
Those aren't mutually exclusive.
But one is free.
One is free though.
That's a plus for me.
What am I even coughing?
Well yeah.
I mean technically.
Coffee costs nothing.
Ben listen to the awe in Munchie's voice.
She's clearly into it.
Be a yogi guy.
I'm disgusted to the point of surprise.
I can't believe what I just fucking heard.
It was like a brain shock to me.
Nate you do yoga?
Is this the fucking bitch cast right now?
What's going on?
I am a mildly surprised.
But like I don't care either.
Yeah well it's not that interesting.
My fucking tea is dropping at astronomical levels.
What's wrong with yoga?
You're prepetuating.
This is literally toxic masculine.
You're prepetuating unhealthy gender stereotypes.
I think we have to vote fucking Nate on.
I specifically made sure I wasn't gay.
I respected the gender binary by making sure I did yoga for men.
Like all videos are exactly the same.
But I watched one for men.
Thank god.
I mean the way I think of yoga.
Like the first thing I think of is like the Wii balance board.
Dolce from Street Fighter?
No.
The Wii fit.
Like I think of yoga in that.
And I'm like yeah video games.
I like yoga.
That's gay.
There's a male fit.
You can choose a man if you want.
But the default is female.
Improving that it's default female.
God why do they have to make it so political by making the default female?
By choosing a woman.
Yeah yeah.
Oh have I told you guys the most hilarious joke I ever heard from a feminist
that I thought was legitimately great.
It was like it was just a Twitter post.
And it's like you know whatever.
And her post is that like doctor like it says to new father.
It's a girl.
Father replies ooh I just think that that's a little political.
Like why you put your agenda into like.
Why did it have to be a girl though?
Like what does that add to its arc?
Yeah exactly.
Great joke.
A legitimately great joke.
Alright.
I hate women.
Enough misogyny.
Enough of that because now it's time to talk about my Lord of Ghost comic that came out.
Oh of course it's out and it's great.
Yeah it's so good dude.
Oh thank you.
It's delicious.
It's so good.
I read it and I jumped onto Discord and I was like at Hippocrite.
Fuck I love this Lord of Ghost comic.
It's wicked cool.
Thanks for making it bro.
The structure is creative and excellently executed.
I know the only reason you made this comic is because you wanted to jump on the PCP
and say hey guys and then I want to say back to you to fulfill all your hopes and dreams
and your blood and your sweat and your tears.
You're cool.
Oh thanks guys.
The Lord of Ghost is cool.
Hey fuck you.
Can we get the Lord of Ghost on the PCP?
That'd be pretty cool.
Please?
He's called in before Hezney?
I can't remember.
I think he has.
He's been on at least once.
He's been on a bonus episode.
I mean he's a constant present.
He should come back to promote his comic though.
He definitely should leave a voicemail or something.
He's sort of the elephant in the room that no one will acknowledge.
Well it's sort of like the ghost in the room actually.
He has no elephant things about him.
I think you're thinking of terst where they've been?
I am thinking of terst where they've literally been.
All right enough.
Tell us about it.
Tell us the tale.
Oh yeah.
Well how did this come about?
Why are you doing this?
Also I want to know is this like the main comic you're working on?
Because I knew you were working on two.
Is there a big one?
I'm technically working on three.
This is like plan-wise.
This is like a practice comic to try and understand how they're made
and how to plan them and make them and stuff.
And then in the future I'll be working on more original things
that aren't tied to existing things like Endless War and whatever.
Right.
I was going to ask about that.
But yeah this came about because I wanted to...
Ever since the Lord of Ghosts canonically became mayor
I was exiled or like killed and I decided he should be exiled
and I wanted him to be a character in my rotating cast of characters
that I can use for things.
And I was always thinking of making a comic,
depicting what happens outside.
And so the obvious thing...
Outside of the city?
Outside of the city.
Yeah.
The next chapter is him traveling outside the city.
There's going to be a number of chapters, maybe five each of 20 pages in length.
I got to tell you Gib, I'm sick to death of Inside Slime City.
What's going on outside Slime City?
No it's not.
There's nothing interesting going on out there.
It's just a normal ass United States.
It's just desert and then probably towns and it's dumb and don't worry about it.
And like people...
There's not even any slime...
I don't know if you know this.
There's not any slime out there.
It's crazy.
Anyway, hippo continue.
But yeah, I wanted to do that.
I had this idea...
Originally it was going to be like Bale shape I was still working on.
I was going to finish that.
I had written or like sort of planned out some of this comic.
And then I was going to sketch it and hand it over to some RFCK people to like do the drawing.
Or some people I, you know, some art friends who are some RFCK related.
But it like it took me until the end of the year to finish the sketches because I was busy doing other things.
And by that time they had like, they had realized and sort of I had realized as well that if I were to hand these sketches over to them because they were too complete.
They wouldn't be able to like do their own style on top of them.
And so it would sort of be like kind of pointless for them to be involved.
And I decided, nah, I'm just going to do it.
And then I started doing it in January 1st.
I inked and shaded the first 20 pages and I pushed them.
And it was very prolific and it was very good.
I was very happy with a lot of the stuff in there.
The way the pages are like, you know, coming down in the beginning.
How it explains everything you need to know without too much like pointless extra stuff.
And the characterization things I put in there.
My favorite thing about the whole intro is that the entire time Lord of Ghosts is referring to himself as you.
Because he's anticipating as correctly that he will forget who he is and need to read it.
And so he'll he's writing it like an instructional guide, like you are this.
This is what you are thinking.
But on the very last page when he thinks he's going to die, he writes, I it's like I'm scared.
And because he's like thinking that this is the end.
He's like so panicky that he forgot to do that.
He's not he's not writing it to his future self.
Yeah, he's just being scared.
And it's like, oh, yeah, I'm so cool when I thought of that.
And I was like, yeah, I'm fucking smart or something.
The whole the whole thing about how I just I said this in the discord.
But the whole like the whole first part of it that is just like it's the pages that he wrote to himself.
And sometimes as you see the pay like in the background, like between pages,
you can see like the nega slime over the city and stuff.
It's so good.
It's so fucking cool.
Holy shit.
Hey, incidentally, can you tell him where they can read it?
So everybody who's now dying to do it.
You can go to give and take a dot site.
It should be the first comic at the top there.
That's my web comic website.
Bill J. was on there.
All my stuff is on there.
I also have a tapas tick tapas dot IO slash give and take or something and a web toon thing.
I think and you can find it on there.
There will be links and I'm just going to post to those three places every time I update.
Hopefully every single time, every single time.
I'm hoping this is optimistic, but I'm hoping to get the next chapter done in the in the in the next week.
Maybe probably be like 10 11 days from now from from this recording.
Oh my God, that's nothing.
But by the way, I want I want to say that you do not have to be an rf2k whiz kid to understand this.
No, it is very, very, very user friendly.
Like you can basically know nothing about it in this war and you will be able to easily.
I mean, even if you didn't know anything about it, like I don't.
Yeah, you would totally get what's happening.
I mean, there's a little bit explains to you.
I mean, you know, you'll have to use some context clues in some areas.
But for the most part, you're going to be able to basically get every single thing.
I mean, if you have context in the endless war, some some things might be like, oh, I know what that is.
But like, it's not like it's perfectly understandable without that.
Yeah, that was my main thing.
Just like slime and punishment.
Slime and punishment is also that way.
By the way, people just like endless war itself.
By the way, it's not that fucking hard to get into you.
Stupid fucking idiots.
It's literally not that hard.
It's really fucking simple.
You fucking boobs.
I was really thinking of like the digi factor.
Like if I told Digi to read this, would he?
And I think the fact that he knows what endless war is, he would be like, oh, it's not for me.
But like, I will try to convince him because it's the only thing that is RFCK is the setting.
And I like structured it with like Act One, Act Two, Act Three, like a real story with a character that you're following.
It's just a narrative.
You don't need to know any prior knowledge.
You can just read it.
That's like the polar opposite of it's just two frames.
Like you derisively like just two frames, then you like happy looking up towards heaven.
It's a real narrative.
I feel so powerful.
Maybe if we're lucky we play our cards right, we can make enough money to fly Lord of Ghosts out to Radcon for Mappy and I's special guest.
He was at RFCKCon London.
He was hanging out.
I wonder what point in his timeline that occurred.
I wonder when and where that happens.
Or maybe it's an out of canon experience.
Out of body experience.
My wonder.
I wonder what's for dinner.
If we acquire vast sums of cash required to buy one bed sheet and perhaps scissors to cut holes in the eyes,
maybe we could use that as a material vessel to summon forth the Lord of Ghosts from wherever he exists in Canada.
We'll have to get like a pentagram and place those in the middle.
Yeah, I getcha.
Yeah.
That would be great.
We'll have to get some slime.
We'll have to get some anti-slime to tempt him.
You know, quick aside on this out of canon thing.
You know, we had an interesting experience on my Nuzlocke yesterday,
which was the time finally came for Russell to shed his mortal coil.
I was there.
Oh, were you?
When Radifriker's cop killers ended, you were still going, so I...
That's right.
I forgot to say it in the chat, so I said,
I ended the stream and then a minute later I was like,
wait a minute, fuck, I can raid.
Some of the people had left, but I raided with whoever was left.
Please keep doing it.
I mean, I just can't remember to do that ever, but I always mean to.
Try to remember.
I know it's hard.
I did it.
You can do it too, Nate.
I believe in you.
Once I get in the habit, I will do it.
That's true.
I did it the last time.
Honestly, it's good practice.
Just pick a fucking stranger and raid him.
You're right.
As long as your name gets out there, that's probably good for you.
Yeah, like nobody loses anything by it.
It's just a good...
Just end every stream by raiding someone.
Why the fuck not?
That's a good thing.
I'll try to do that.
I'm not gonna say.
But anyway, the point is that I stuck around because I saw the trials of Russell.
Right.
So we were in this horrible battle in the underground in Goldenrod, and there was this boy with
psychic powers who was really fucking me up.
Oh, no.
This is Route 36.
It doesn't matter.
We got into one of those situations where if anything happened, someone was gonna die,
and this is exactly what Russell was made for.
If I remember, it was because you had Doon Koon, the Pidgeot, no, the Pidgeotto, and you
were gonna quick attack there at Kadabra, I think, but he was confused.
So if the quick attack had gone off, you would have won, but if you were stricken with confusion,
you would kill yourself because you were a low HP.
And the way to guarantee the victory would be to switch in.
So it was a total coinflip.
Total coinflip.
Exactly.
So the only thing to do was to put out Russell to take the blow, switch back into Pidgeotto,
and that guarantees success.
The only thing to do was take the coward's way out.
That's exactly what...
Everyone was cheering for we hashtag LetRussellRussell, and he wrestled his fiercest, and actually
he had a little moment of glory earlier in the stream as a Rattata too.
All in all, not much more a little Rattata who believed in himself could do.
That's the guy destined to fucking die, it seems like.
You didn't grind enough, Nate.
You had like a 19 and a 20, and then all your other guys were like level five, level six,
level two.
It's true.
I should spend more time grinding.
But you know what?
Russell was yearning for death anyway, to escape this shell that felt so wrong, whereas he
foolishly donated too much and caught a fucking Rattata.
Aren't we all?
All I'm saying is that I think in the Chronology of the Pokémon series, Pokémon Gold or Silver
takes place so far in any of our Nuzlocks featuring Russell earliest in the timeline.
I'm wondering if perhaps this Rattata is the original incarnation of Russell.
Oh, so you're saying it's the tale's been told out of chronological order.
Exactly.
It may well be.
What a storied history.
I mean, Rattata is a purple boy, becomes a purple ghost, there's connections here.
Who can say?
It's true.
I wanted to say, by the way, I wanted to ask you something about the comic.
I wanted to know what it was like drawing the final line art.
What was that experience like?
Because I know that you have always had a bit of an issue like, oh, my art is bad.
But your art's really good in this.
So how did you reconcile those two contradictory facts?
Well, I think due to just generally drawing a lot at the end, last few months of the last
year, it was good practice, good, good, all that.
I think with the sketches that were very robust and pretty much perfect as they were in terms
of structure, like where the characters were located.
It was just a matter of making it clean.
I think, I don't know, it just sort of worked out.
There were parts where it was like, ah, that's a little sloppy when I zoom real close in.
But if I focus too hard on this.
Never zoom in.
Working drawing digitally, never zoom in.
I zoom in a little bit.
It's always a mistake.
You always regret it.
Because you can see tiny little bits here and there.
Well, I like to zoom in just so that I can see dots that are easily get rid of a bowl.
Dots that are far away that were from an earlier part where I was erasing a big line.
I felt like doing the due diligence to clean it up a little bit before I move on.
But not to redraw everything because the line isn't smooth enough.
I'm sort of becoming more comfortable with just seeing how it goes.
Seeing how I draw the first few times and not redrawing too much unless it's like seriously
bothering me.
I guess my threshold for what seriously bothers me has changed.
Now I'm like, yeah, you know, it's not important for this to be the most beautiful thing ever.
Even though I did design it so that it could be potentially printed at some point as a
book.
I'm not sure how possible that would be, but that would be nice having a lot of ghosts.
That's how I feel with slime and punishment.
Not every panel needs to be a masterpiece.
Just fucking draw it and if it gets the most of the time it's enough just to get the idea
across and not look bad and that's fine.
I think the main thing that was different from compared to just drawings in general
is that I was keeping track of the size of the pen brush when doing certain things like
the boxes are always like 15 point when I was drawing those.
Oh, this is, I can talk about this afterwards, Photoshop tattled on me and told Adobe that
I was using a pirated version.
I don't know, I've seen that on my computer recently and there's a process you can kill
to get rid of it, but it is annoying.
Well, the thing it was like I was getting annoyed with Photoshop generally anyway because
it sort of lags a lot and sometimes it just like lags indefinitely and there's no fix
so I have to turn the computer off and on again for it to be okay.
So I was like, you know what, this is a good reason to just not have Photoshop anymore
and I got one of those many, many, many free alternatives.
What'd you get?
I got Medibang paint.
What the fuck is that?
It's something I heard Tom talk about once and I was like, I'll remember that, I guess.
And it's really good.
This is like the ball-pitted McDonald's version of Photoshop.
It sounds really good.
You can do basically all the same things with all the same shortcut commands, but it has
some improvements and it is sort of designed for writing mangas.
This is like Pintuol Psy 2, that's all there is.
I really like Mango Studio, but it did take me forever to pirate it.
It took me like multiple days of working on it.
Maybe I'm just stupid, but it's really hard.
The future is free shit, I guess.
It's a free program.
You can download it right now and it has this great tool where you can click a grid, like
an assist grid thing and it can be like straight lines or like a crisscross pattern or like
a radial thing or a circle thing and you align it.
If I wanted to draw straight lines going in one direction, such as rain, I can align
it to be a certain thing and then when I draw, it only goes on that specific angle.
So I can't fuck up the angles, which is really nice.
That's pretty convenient.
I mean, with Mango Studio, I can kind of do that by just, I rotate the canvas instead
of the axis and it works, I guess it would accomplish the same thing, but that's pretty
good.
Drawing digitally is so much better than traditional.
It's just better.
I don't understand why people still do traditional.
I think people say it's good to be well versed in both because they'll influence each other,
I guess.
Okay.
Or at least traditional will make you better at drawing digitally.
Traditional can impart a certain aesthetic, like a watercolor painting has a certain
feel to it, and that's cool and all, but that's bullshit and aesthetic is all bullshit
and it's just about getting the idea across and digital, it's just so much less complicated
to do it digitally.
Listen, I'm all for digital, but the aesthetic is part of the idea sometimes.
Sometimes you want to convey a certain feeling.
Not for me.
Oh, jeez.
I wonder, I guess that's why your art looks like that, huh, Ben?
Hell yes.
I think I said last time, but the way I'm working with these comics is this one's going
to be digitally, and then I'm going to try doing one that is traditional, just to see
how much more difficult or easy or better it makes it because it's something I should
try at least.
I initially tried inking vapors one traditionally, and I got two pages in, and I was like, nah,
this isn't going to work.
I'm just not up to it.
To then scan it and do all the shit you have to fix with it anyway, I mean, fuck that.
I tried to use a nib pen because I had just read Bakuman, and I was like, what the fuck
is this thing?
Who made this?
Hey, so this comic is cool and all, but we only know any comic or piece of media is
as good as the memes that are generated out of it, so more importantly, let me just save
this comic from the dustbin of history by posting this, guys, this is literally me when
I'm so fucking scared.
This is literally me, everyone, post how this is literally you when you're so scared of
shit.
Now that we've thoroughly disrespected Hippos comic and everything about his character,
we can finally move on to a new fucking topic.
Yeah, that's fair.
Guys, listen, if the reason, well Hippo, do you have anything else you want to say about
your comic?
Go read it right now.
Go read it, yeah.
Very good.
I think we all vouch for it's quite.
What is the release schedule this going to be?
Not like, when is it going to do do do do do do do, but you're going to do page by page,
batch by batch.
I'm going to do chapters, like originally I didn't have chapters, I just sketched a bunch
of pages, but I'm thinking a 20 page chapter is meaty and cool.
It is, it is.
And to drop that would be like, oh my God, read the thing.
And I was like, yeah, hell yeah.
So yes.
Is there any time we can look forward to that in the future?
Do you know what I promise anything?
I mean, initially, like I was saying, like, optimistically, I could do 20 pages of this
because it's all sketched.
I could line it and shade it in like a week each chapter.
Did you say it's all sketched, like the entire thing?
The entire thing is sketched, like I wanted to have it finished.
So it's already a completed story in your mind.
Damn.
I mean, it was already a completed story when I wrote it and completed it and wrote all
the dialogue and like character actions in a screenplay format.
Well, I don't know about anybody else, but to me, that makes it be like, oh shit, this
thing is real and we'll be completed.
There's no like, I don't know what the ending is going to be, I'll figure it out.
That's great news.
You mind?
Yep.
We'll go read it, people.
Go to give him, take that site and read it.
There you go.
Go read all the shit.
Fuck you.
I haven't been able to do any slime and punishment work lately and because I put that on.
Because I put that on the back burner for the, to finish the vapors to a Kickstarter work.
And then I put that on the back burner because this Redcon 4 shit cropped up, but um.
Have you given Cassie her vaporette yet?
No.
Epic.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Leave me alone.
Hey, listen, audience, if it sounds like I'm tired right now, then there's a very good
reason for that because I was staying up until 4 a.m. last night to work on Lonesome Cactus,
which is a new bot that you can click on and play with in the Quickdraw server.
You remember, you may remember the old PCP drawcasts.
Those are dead and gone and buried, but Quickdraw is the new hotness and Lonesome Cactus is
just the first part of the puzzle that you can go and play with right now.
It is a game sort of kind of more like it's like robust discord reaction enhancements that
make you even more likely to whore out your body and your soul for points that mean nothing
and do nothing, but look cool and you be like, fuck you.
And it's great.
So click on the link in the description to be taken to the Quickdraw discord.
So it's like you post images as it is a drawing art server thing and people react with certain
emotes to indicate how much they like it and you get bounty, you get a thing, you get currency
for how many reactions you get to your art is the idea.
And depending on what reactions they give you and if you have a collab with people,
then they get all reactions, or they get all bounty too.
It's basically a point system to incentivize people to get as much like a high bounty as
they possibly can by creating as much art as they fucking can in this discord server,
which by the way, it's like tied to Quickdraw in the sense that it's tied to Quickdraw,
but this is just an art server.
So if you ever have those art servers, which everyone's in, they joined some fucking posseass
art server and it's always like, yeah, okay, I guess the people in here are cool, I guess
so, but you know in your heart of hearts, you fucking hate all of them because all of
them are lame sauce and all of them are veggies, you don't even fucking matter.
Then click on this one because this one will literally make fun of you and bully you relentlessly
unless you have a high bounty and a roll name and you will get a fire under your ass and
you will be completely obliterated unless you have a high bounty.
You get like a, you get a notification from Lonesome Cactus screaming at you every one
second.
Yeah, literally.
Well, it's great.
Well, it's to keep me from gaming the system hardcore, failure of a draw hack that I am
and just racking up massive pointage to sail by and just survive on surplus labor of others.
The thing is, how would you make that happen?
I enlist a cabal of collaborators and we all cheat the system and vote for each other.
Is this, can I break your game?
Can I ruin everyone's fun?
You have to spend bounty to have.
You already have.
So if you don't have your bounty to give, then you can't, like, they can't get bounty.
So you theoretically, I mean, theoretically, if all of your people were accruing massive
amounts of bounty, you know, from other people, then you would be able to spend on all one
another and inflate your scores.
But everyone fucking hates you and everyone hates all Nate heads, so no one would ever
give you anything.
That's the landscape we're dealing with right now.
Wait, so if I, if someone has a zero bounty and they resonate, they click the resonate
emote with an art piece, does that person not get any bounty?
No, no, they get bounty, but they get the negative bounty, which has massive ramifications
for their social currency.
They are basically like in the complete, like lower rungs of society.
They are in the like the half basements in parasite.
They are that like lower class family.
I don't see how this operates.
Like if somebody joins the server, they have zero bounty and they react to things.
Do people lose bounty?
Yes, you can theoretically go into negative bounty, but that wouldn't happen.
But like, surely if people join the server, then everyone will like, you know, they'll
react to things, not knowing this, and then everyone will just lose bounty until everyone
has negative bounty.
Wait, you lose bounty?
You lose bounty by reacting to stuff?
I don't understand the mathematics.
You spend way less bounty to give more.
So you are spending like a fourth of the bounty that you reward other people.
So people are all a net getting way more bounty than they are losing bounty.
It's merely it's merely like a system to make it so that you are at least somewhat stingy
with what you give out.
And you aren't just reacting to every single thing with the highest tier reaction.
Hmm.
Okay.
So confused.
I'll just react when I like something.
Trust in the cactus.
Exactly.
That's what we should do.
Just don't worry about it.
You know, it kind of seems like it's like a prisoner's dilemma sort of thing.
I feel like even though like the optimal play is to like be very generous with resonations,
and then like other people will probably be generous with them with you, and then everyone
will mutually benefit.
I wonder if it would fall into the trap of like, people, nobody reacts to anyone because
they want to hoard all their bounty to themselves, but then everybody suffers.
Well, here's the thing about bounty.
It literally doesn't matter outside of social currency.
It literally only matters for bragging rights.
And so you're not going to be super hoarding with it.
And I mean, already evidently, everyone is reacting to everything way too much already.
Like literally, like literally every post I'm scrolling up has like the highest tier favorite
reaction, literally all of them.
In fact, let me see how much bounty I have right now.
Um, I got a cool $6,000 going on $7,000.
That's pretty good.
This is why YouTube took away the star rating thing and just replaced it with like and dislike
because people would only vote for five stars and one star.
Yeah, basically.
Nobody was like, hmm, three and a half stars.
Yeah.
Well, none the less.
Well, there you go.
Go investigate and be an outlaw.
Yes.
Come and be an outlaw and roam the territory deserts of Arizona and try to avoid the sheriffs
trying to take you back to Fort Whipple.
It's a great grand adventure.
I am curious.
Right.
That does sound great.
What is the lore of the Lonesome Cactus?
What is his authority in this town?
The Lonesome Cactus is merely a Lonesome Cactus, who, you know, is able to assist in the development
of young independent content creators such as yourself for a small price, which may or
may not be your soul, which may or may not be your dignity or, you know, your mortal coil.
We'll have to wait and see.
We'll have to see what kind of deal this Lonesome Cactus is to us.
It slurps up mortal coils like spaghetti noodles.
Maybe one day, if enough of his new friends move out and start creating art, he won't
be so lonesome after all.
Something tells...
You like it, though.
Well, I imagine that he's, like, recetti, so he can, like, burrow underground and, like,
move wherever he wants.
So if someone tries to come over and talk to him, like, outside of asking for roles,
he'll just, like, burrow underground and then walk away and just, like, go.
He's lonesome because he obliterated all the competition.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, that makes sense.
This guy was the original artist.
He created drawing.
Oh, maybe he did in fact obliterate all the competition, but he learned that, like, no,
no, no, this is no way to live.
I'm lonesome now as a result of my misdeeds.
I was too powerful.
I need to encourage others to also be artists and foster community.
Do you think he dips his needles in ink to write?
Ooh, yes, I do.
Ooh, he can draw so many things at once.
Yeah.
Do you think he's a piotic cactus?
Do you think you could, like, bite into him and then you get, like, super high-yags?
Yeah, exactly.
That'd be awesome.
Yeah, I mean, that lobe on his head, I mean, that's weed, if ever there was weed.
Have you seen, oh God, I don't know if I want to change the topic, but I'm gonna talk about
it.
We're done with this one.
It's over.
I was gonna talk about Pokemon.
Sure.
Just go ahead.
Have you seen it?
Everyone click on the link and go there now because Quick Draw is actually cool now,
and the drawcast is actually cool now because it's not on the PC, it's a real thing.
We're actually doing it again.
It's actually alive again.
It's epic.
It's pretty epic.
It's online.
Episodes aren't being recorded as well.
Episodes and new shows are being conceived of and recorded, so, fucking, Quick Draw has
a crazy future.
So do you guys see the Pokemon news?
No.
I heard some of it.
I missed all the details.
Who fucking cares?
Is it good?
Is it bad?
It's kind of funny.
Wow.
Basically they're really, okay, I might be a little, the general idea is they're releasing
like DLC that has all the fucking Pokemon that they withheld from the first release.
Lemau, who could have possibly, who could have possibly guessed?
It's not all of them, but it's a bunch of them, as I understand it.
Who could have possibly guessed that they didn't need to withhold all those Pokemon?
They were just doing it to make more money.
What an absolute shock.
That is unfortunate.
I mean, it, this, oh god, it's so disgraceful that they did interviews and said like, no,
Only to immediately assume is the game is that it'd be like, huh, no, we were just trying.
It was a lie.
We're just trying to milk more out of you.
And like, honestly, I would respect it so much more if they had just said, yeah, we're
withholding it because we're going to release them as DLC.
They just did fucking admit it.
You fucking cowards.
Even worse though, because like they like had a different excuse after the technical
limitations.
They said, Oh for balance reasons.
You know, it's hard to balance so many Pokemon, but they're putting them in there.
So like, you had to have balanced them.
Yeah.
You did all the work.
Don't get me wrong.
I don't respect how weasely they seem to be.
However, all these things could be part of the decision that like, it takes more effort
to put more Pokemon in.
Okay, true.
Balance.
I mean, okay, sure.
That could be part of the thing.
And ultimately, you know, it takes more work to get more Pokemon in the game.
There's updated textures and it's shit to some degree.
So I mean, is it embarrassing?
Absolutely.
I'm just saying, no, I'm just saying they lied, okay?
I'm just saying, well, maybe I know.
I'm just saying, like, okay, obviously I wouldn't like it if they were gonna like, section
off, cordon off certain Pokemon and only give them with DLC.
I would never like that, but it wouldn't offend me if they hadn't like, lied about it.
I am not seeing a clear lie.
Maybe we just disagree on this.
They said it was for technical limitations and it's just not.
It's just not.
I think not.
It cannot possibly be that.
They kept changing their story.
Yes.
Also, and further evidences that apparently they changed their story.
I think, boy, I mean, I also think it's a terrible thing just generally.
But I think the argument if to play devil's advocate, stop, to play devil's advocate.
The argument is that they couldn't develop it in the time for technical.
It wasn't like it's impossible to port them over.
It's like they need to remake them and that's why it took so long and it took so long.
So that, you know, they have to get a Pokemon game out.
It's not good, but like, I think it's not technically a lie, but you should treat it
like one because it's fucking.
Okay.
Well, all right.
So the Pokemon company is terrible now.
It's bad.
I, you know, you, you know what, okay, I don't, do we like Arlo?
I kind of, I sometimes I like Arlo.
I watched some Arlo videos about Pokemon.
He is Keto Ben.
He is pretty.
He's not full Keto, but he dabbles.
He's fine.
But he's fine.
Arlo will be destroyed by, when I, when I get like, you know, some red felt and I make
red man the puppet and he reviews games, Arlo will be dead within minutes.
That sounds good.
He did a bunch of videos about covering Sword and Shield.
He's fine.
Yeah.
He, but he did a bunch of videos covering Sword and Shield and he said some stuff that
really struck.
I was like, oh my God, he's onto something here.
And it was basically that like, Nintendo is like, I guess I just never thought about
this before.
I mean, every generation, they add like cool new features, but they take old good features
away.
Like they're not, they're obviously not just trying to make the series as good as it can
be.
The strategy is to add features to every generation and then take them away later so that every
generation has like certain things about it that only it has.
They're kind of creating like an illusion of progress by doing that.
No, it's not, it's not that it's, it's sort of the opposite.
It's like, okay, well yeah, Heart, Gold, Soul, Silver, that's the one with the Pokemon
that follow you.
Sword and Shield, that's the one with the Dynamaxing.
It's not, they're not, they're like deliberately not making progress and adding more stuff to
make the game better.
They're deliberately like, they add something and they take it away to make every generation,
such that every generation doesn't like obsolete the previous ones.
In Galar, it has to be side grades.
In other words, in other words, they don't want to make the games too good because it
would make their old games look worse by comparison.
And also it would set the bar too high.
Like I don't, why do they have to worry about depreciating value for stuff that is old?
I mean, it's not like fire red, green, being ugly, overshadow is really going to cause
new problems for them, is it?
Well maybe it's more just about not setting expectations too high or just, yeah, I don't
know.
Do you think, maybe they're not that concerned with sales of old games, I'm sure they make
relatively less money on things like that.
I kind of feel like a lot of this is a feature creep that, like if they had Megas, Anzi moves
and Dynamax, then it's just a lot to do when you make new games.
Well I wouldn't have added all of those things if they had kept the ones from when they started
adding special delinquent.
Like they could have, instead of doing Z moves, they could have just made more Megas.
If that's what they were going to go with.
Sure, sure.
You're right.
There's definitely flaws.
It is definitely a marketing thing.
Like, oh, the new Pokemon game, it's not just the same as the old one.
We got this new thing that makes them different aside from more than new Pokemon.
It's explicitly a native thing, Dynamaxing is only in Galar, can you Dynamax?
So that certainly fits the pattern there.
I don't know, I think they said I was watching the Arlo and he got the game and he was like,
I haven't played a Pokemon game in like eight years.
I didn't play any of the last three generations and he's like, he booted up Sword and Shield
and he was like, oh my God, it's still the same?
It hasn't changed that much?
How disappointing?
And I was like, yep, I'm kind of sick of it.
I'm kind of fucking over it.
It's bad.
I feel like I decided this like 300 episodes ago on this very podcast.
I know, but then someone else said it and I was mad all over again.
Well then why don't you go watch that guy's video?
No, to only watch this channel.
I'm here to do reporting on what he said.
Listen, I'm here to regurgitate content creators' videos for the mass market.
I'm just, I'm only expressing all this because I strongly share the opinion and am upset
about it and it bugs me and I don't like it.
Did you see the new legendary or the new like mystical mythical Pokemon?
I did see that.
The one like the deer with like the giant ball on its head?
Hideous.
I like that one.
I actually like that one a lot.
That's pretty funny.
Okay.
Such as with old Pokemon discussions is like, fuck Pokemon, fuck, they suck, but I kind
of love them though.
That's my thing to talk about.
Yeah.
This is, I think the thing, I mean, most people just buy Pokemon are like, oh good,
the new one.
I like Pokemon generically.
I will buy this.
That's most people.
Anyway, he talks about Pokemon and how much they like or dislike Pokemon are literally
the most fucking caveman brain dead sex of shit corpses on.
Yeah.
Speaking of which.
And yes, I am talking about you.
It just fucking, it just makes me so upset when I realize they're not trying to make
a good game.
That's not what they want to do.
They don't give a shit.
They don't care if it's good.
Ah, it just has to be good enough.
It's just the first gigantic thing that has been around for like decades.
It's a lot of money tied to it.
Like they've got to make, they've got to string it out for as long as possible.
Think about what it means.
If you want a good game, you go to a gamer that likes playing them.
Like what is, what is the perfect Pokemon game?
Like it's, it's probably, like what we'll get the most sales, it's probably not like
kind of what we envision with like, I think these things that like fan hacks or whatever
where they make it like really challenging.
Maybe like a more interesting story.
I'm not, I'm not even talking about challenge.
I'm just talking about like, don't fucking gut your own games and like take out good features.
Like they had a writable Pokemon in, in Pikachu, hey you Pikachu.
They could have had it in Sword and Shield if they wanted to.
They didn't.
Why?
Because it, because it doesn't matter.
Like like including good features that people like, like that's not what it's about.
It's just about like making the new one, making it different enough.
And it doesn't matter if you, if you add or if you take away.
It's all the same.
It all comes out in the wash.
I think we can all agree that does seem to be pushed and how it comes out.
You know, the worst thing, obviously, obviously the worst thing is that they're successful
because of them doing this.
I'm sure this is like a calculate, you know, a calculation that has proved to be true every
single time they do it.
They still make lots of money and from all the games being slightly different, but none
of them being like straight upgrades, except the remakes, because that's an opportunity
to hype up, like selling a really old game that nobody would potentially buy on the old
console.
Although I wonder if your Omega Sapphire and Rubies are actually better than the original
because they're filled with, I mean, I didn't play them, seems like they're filled with
bloat and bullshit.
I don't know if I could be wrong.
I think so.
I haven't played all of it.
I've played it in a little bit because of nostalgia, but it's like.
I mean, Shea Mei's seven hour review of Pokemon Omega Root.
I don't remember if he ends up deciding that the remake is better or worse than the original.
Was it kind of a toss-up though?
Was there even, like, it wasn't clear?
Because Heart Gold is, like, basically straight up better than Gold and Silver.
He definitely had some things that really annoyed him about the remake.
I don't remember if he ever goes so far as to be like, the remake is worse.
I just forget it's been a while.
Fair enough.
Oh, oh, oh, my old bone lake when I think about Pokemon.
Huh?
Oh, I'm just letting the audience know.
There.
No more Pokemon.
You could skip to this part of the video to skip the Pokemon discussion.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry, everybody.
Oh, jeez.
Hey, I've got a tangent to say, which is just out.
Guys, let me tell you about a little guy that everybody loves named Jordan Peterson.
Oh, God.
No, God.
Okay, no, no, no, no.
Okay, all right.
Why?
The story at the point is I cleaned my room, guys, therefore I'm up right now.
I did it.
You know what?
Hey, you guys heard this last name, Mari Kondo?
Yeah, you could live.
Oh, yeah.
That's a queen.
You fucking sex.
You know.
I mean, I want Mari Kondo and Jordan Peterson to, like, have children for the ultimate cleaning
machine.
She seems like she'd be a fun mom.
Too bad she's already...
Imagine this.
She's already spent 99% of her eggs.
I guess that's what become a great meme.
That is a great meme.
It is.
It is a great meme.
I can't remember.
I made a really epic joke.
Okay, whatever.
You just summed it up with that.
Point is, me and Michelle have just been cleaning, and I just got to say, it is certainly
a truism that when your house is dirty and then you spend a while cleaning it, it just
feels better afterward.
So highly recommended.
Do it.
Funny enough.
Live in a clean place.
I also clean my room.
Not entirely, but, like, yeah, I put a lot of my stuff away and I clean up a lot of space.
I was inspired to do this because I made a genius-level purchasing decision.
Let me explain what's the most exciting thing in my life right now.
So my room.
Nate, have you been to my room?
No, but we did see that epic room tour that Zenn Huckstable made for Michelle upon request.
I never retweeted that.
I'm so fucking mad.
What are you doing there, buddy?
I can't believe I wasn't there for Christmas.
It makes me so upset.
There was so much shit going down.
That is too bad.
It was sad because Nate and Michelle had to go, like, right away.
Like, me and Tom and Zenn hung out and had anti-pasto platters.
We were very sad together.
It was a bummer.
It had to be done.
We had a pretty good time.
But anyway.
Next time.
Yeah.
But anyway, my room has, like, you know, it's got, like, a little sort of alcove corner
to it.
It's only, like, maybe three feet wide and it sticks back, like, four or five feet into
the wall and it's got, like, a little angled half ceiling.
It's just, like, a little, like, nook that I just keep, like, shelves over there with
books and stuff on them.
Sure.
And so I purchased a tension rod.
You know what that is?
I don't.
It's, like, a metal rod that's, like, spring-loaded and you can put it.
You basically just wedge it between two walls and you can use it to, like, put up a shower
curtain or something.
Yeah.
So I bought one of those and then I got a bunch of coat hangers and my closet was stuffed
with thing and now I have a rod because, like, my closet is, like, it's, like, a little,
like, low half closet.
It's only, like, a couple feet high.
I have, like, a little, like, a long, horizontal, low closet.
So now I hung up this tension rod.
So now I have all my hangable clothes over on the nook hung up.
And also they form sort of a little makeshift curtain that I have to sort of part to get
into the nook.
It's, like, in the adult section of an old, like, DVD shop.
And also, because I just went to the garment district and I bought a bunch of cool items
from the women's section, Lamal.
And one of them was a sweater that has, like, a cool, like, skeleton ribcage pattern on
the front.
Whoa.
And I hung that on the front of the rack.
So now I have this, like, cool skeleton pattern sweater prominently displayed in my room.
And it makes me feel pretty edgy.
What a life upgrade.
Can we get a picture of this set up, perhaps?
Yeah, please.
You want it right now?
I mean, hey, take your time, but at some point.
Yeah, I know.
I'll take one right now.
Your room is so fucking small, Ben, that I can't even imagine this device, this major
operation taking up any space inside of it.
Is it that small?
Yeah.
I don't know.
It is.
It's pretty small.
It's pretty, you know, okay.
The L-Cove makes it, like, technically, I think, normal size, but, like, it feels much
smaller because the L-Cove is so, like, jetted off to the side that it doesn't really feel
like it's part of anything.
Maybe I missed this part, but, like, what's the gain here?
I'm not quite understanding the benefit of this set up.
Well, I created new storage space to hang my clothes in.
And also, I just like that it's like a little curtain, a little hangable clothes curtain
in front of my book nook.
All right, if anyone wants to know how to visualize Ben's room, here's how you do it.
You get a cheese wheel, you make a slice of cheese from the cheese wheel, then at the
broad base of it, here's this computer at the tiny little sliver a little in, there's
just, like, a mattress on the floor, and that's Ben's room.
That's, oh, and then a bunch of caffeine pills and, like, vape cartridges just scattered
across every single place.
Hell yeah, dude.
That's the life.
Dirt cheap E-Fox.
No, everyone.
Channel Marie Kondo.
You're perfectly politically neutral, cleanliness individual.
Be her.
It brings you joy.
And, you know, Michelle, I said this before, but, like, we've been trying to just get rid
of shit we don't need because only keep things that spark joy.
If you've got a bunch of crap, there's, like, a bunch of boxes that are, like, anime figurine
boxes, I think to myself, oh, I might want those boxes one day to pack up my anime figurines.
You think I will ever use those?
No.
You should get rid of them.
They're a waste of space and a waste of time.
Bigger space to live in will make you happier, so do that.
Wait, you do that to point your anime figurines?
Bigger place to put incense and candles to pray to Jesus.
That's right.
We could have a whole shrine to Saint Jude or whatever.
We could have a tired chapel in your house if you just cleaned up your fucking room,
Nate.
You could literally get a mast.
I posted the room picture.
Where's your tablet, Ben?
The tablet is, it's, okay, I'm actually lying on my bed right now and I have the tablet
on the floor in front of my bed.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, that incredible, look at that, look at that Nuzlocke team poster there.
Yeah, but that's good stuff.
Nat blasphemous, yeah.
But yes, that rack is great.
I'm sure that makes space.
And then there's Nobby's Nalacacum art over small, small prints right next to the rod.
Wait, Nobby?
Yeah.
Um, Ben.
That little postcard.
What?
I drew that.
Is that wrong?
No, you fucking moron.
Not that one.
The other one.
You fucking dipshit.
You piece of shit.
You motherfucker.
Get the fuck out of here.
I don't even see it.
I think I don't know.
Oh, I see it.
Oh, way in the back there.
Way in the back.
Yes, yours is under the picture of Rando from Lisa, indeed.
I mean, you mean can man, right?
Yeah.
That's right.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, can man.
Fuck can man.
Let's talk about, is that pink or is that like green and purple over there?
My original Spike Cosplay that I sewed myself and I revealed fabulously a burning thing.
No, that is, that is, while I was at the fucking garment district, I just bought a green and
a purple handkerchief because I thought they would be cool to add to outfits at, is it
because you like green and purple, green and purple, you know, like weed at RFC KCon.
I was cleaning out my room because that's the way I want to say, that's why I went to
Garment District.
So I went to Garment District to buy one pants that fit because I didn't have any and two
cool outfits to wear to RFC KCon and I got that skeleton sweater and I got a cool like
hood that makes me look like some kind of like cultist and, and it's pretty great.
And I got them all in the women's section, women's clothes are better.
They're more interesting.
Yeah.
True.
When they can fit.
I found, I found so many great plaid shirts in the women's section that were like beautiful
colors and I was like, I love these so much.
I want to wear them, but they were all, even the ones that were large, even like large
size ones were like too small and didn't fit on my body.
They're like cut differently.
And I cried.
Yeah.
I cried.
That's it.
It's the end of the story.
Hey, hey, viewer, listen, hey, audience member, listen the fuck up today.
As you're reading this, as you're listening to this right now, the 17th of January, 2020
is the first day of RFC KCon six and tune over to my channel, like the RFC K channel or something.
Because there's going to be mad live streams.
What is the PCP release?
Like what time?
Friday.
Friday at 2 PM.
2 PM.
Okay.
During this time, literally stop listening to this episode right now and tab over to
real life gang violence, which is happening right now in the RFC K channel.
Go there right now, right now, right now, right now, right fucking now.
Click on the link in the description.
Show notes.
There you go.
It'll be the X.
Oh, by the way, I want to say that I was cleaning my room because a family member is going
to be living in my room while I'm away at college and we're going to switch out.
And so I've been cleaning out my room and I've been trying to make it less, you know,
I'm trying to make it more presentable to the people and more easy to mold in their
own.
So I've been taking down all my posters.
I've just been trying to make it as, you know, as base and stock and diplomatic as humanly
possible.
And I've been shifting through all of my possessions because I had forgotten that I had possessions
because I took like literally nothing to college and my room had just been completely
bare.
Like there's basically no furniture inside of it.
There's literally nothing.
You look at my roommate's side and he has a bunch of posters and he has a bunch of
like knick-knacks and stuff.
And look over at mine and mine's like a bed, a desk, a computer.
And that is literally it.
There's nothing else there.
I'm like, oh my God, I have like books.
I have like a globe.
I have all these things.
I want to take it all back.
Oh, I missed having furniture in my room.
It's cool.
And it's pretty good, right?
You got any shit on your walls at your dorm?
No, I have literally nothing on my, on my wall.
Because that's, that's sad.
That's really sad.
There's a legendary clip you should hear, Munchy, when it's a flashback in Metal Gear
Solid 2, when Ryden is fucking around, he's talking to Rose, and Rose describes the legendary
event where she first entered his bedroom, like he's at an apartment, it's fine, but
then she enters the bedroom.
And he's, by the way, he's a war orphan, a child soldier, and he walks into his room
and he's just, there's nothing there but a bed.
And she takes this as a big yikes, as a big oof, and it makes him very spooky and scary.
So just so you know, this is how you are perceived by the people in your life, whether they say
it or not.
That's really fine.
Yeah, okay, great, great.
Having, okay, listen.
You are a child soldier of the PCP, so it's fitting, frankly.
This is a pretty human core thing to say, and we're gonna kill me if you want.
And I'm not like a su, up until very recently, I've been very anti-possession, very anti-like
buying things that isn't an experience and slash or food.
And that's all been cool and, you know, buying consumables, I guess, is alright, is like
a philosophical outlook.
But there is something to be said, I have this tiny little tiki statue right next to
my computer, and this little tiki statue gives me joy whenever I look at him.
So maybe, maybe kids, when you go out in the town with your friends, don't spend all of
your money on cheeseburgers, maybe buy a tiki statue instead.
I like little things like that.
I still have, I think it was from Radcon 3, oh no, it would have been from the Barone
Con.
One of the times where we met up, I still have that squishy Kirby from, yes, yes, yes, yes.
And he's been on my desk and every so often, I squish him and I'm like, ah, memories.
And also, it just is a nice cute thing.
I am way too into like keeping things.
I really don't need, not in just like a, you know, a whatever sense, but if it has like
a historical value to me, I have like a drawer, like near my desk, that's just full of like
historic artifacts and I can pull it out and there's like plane trips that I like, like
plane tickets to places where I went and I have like little like knickknacks and stuff.
I keep, I keep all my receipts.
I don't know why.
It's not like I need them.
I just like, oh, I remember going to that restaurant and getting that thing and costing
exactly that much.
Yeah.
I have a ton of movie stubs and stuff like that where it's like, oh dude, remember when
I saw the emoji movie?
I remember that.
What a great time.
What a fucking godforsaken night.
It's pretty awesome.
I really, you know, hold on.
I'm going to rustle through.
One second.
Let me, let me pull out the first thing that I see over here.
Oh, oh, oh.
Any day now, chief.
I have a breeze card, which is the Georgia Atlanta, like public transport.
It's the Atlanta shitty version of a Charlie card.
Yeah.
It's the Atlanta.
That was a nightmare.
Dude.
Okay.
Getting from the plane to your house.
Such a pale, such a pale ghost of an imitation of the, of the, of the MBTA.
Yeah.
What a fucking nightmare.
Okay.
One last note about clean your house and we can go to wherever Nate is dying to talk
about.
Cause I know I can hear it in his fucking voice while cleaning out my room.
I found a mysterious artifact, which was not its original location, which means that someone
must have moved it, which means that I'm a ghost now because it was my, you know, like
baby shoes never worn.
It was my fleshlight never used.
And I bought it in a tent spit of shame and dysphoria.
And I decided that it was not the kind of man that I wanted to be, but I already bought
it.
So there's nothing I could do about it.
And so I put it away.
I put it away.
Like, like, like, like, like the Ark of the Covenant sealing it away amongst of my many
artifacts, never to be taken out and used again until I found it and not its real location.
So everyone knows, everyone fucking knows that I was once a coomer and that that side
of me is brazen to the world and to a fully, you know, dismiss myself from it.
I offered to my friend Kyle on New Year's and he did a shot out of my fleshlight and
it was incredible.
Ew.
That's so disgusting.
That's so far.
I saw that.
It was clean.
It was unused, bro.
It was cringed, dude.
It's cringed.
On a conceptual level, that is repulsive.
Listen, I hate absolutely everything about that.
Me too.
No.
Dude, I fucking hate you, man.
Yeah.
Nah, bra.
You gotta get the fuck outta here.
I'm gonna put this in the description.
Hold on.
All right.
Wait, what are you gonna put?
What are you gonna put?
Ew.
No.
Bro.
It's a video of him doing it.
No.
Watch it.
Kyle, shout out.
Shout to you, Kyle.
Oh, it's horrible.
No, it's great.
Oh, it's heinous.
Why?
Why is it heinous?
Ew.
Look into it, Ben.
See, there's a reason I see people around him.
I see people covering his eyes and not acknowledging it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Please stop.
Bruh.
I don't know why.
This really fucking bugs me out.
I hate it so much.
Ben, do you want the flashlight?
Yes, please.
Do you actually?
I'll literally give it to you.
I don't care.
No, I do not want the flashlight.
Why?
Does anyone hate why?
Oh, oh, wait.
To drink out of, of course.
Oh, my God.
The perfect idea.
Guys, an auction, PCP fans, if you want my flashlight, then make the highest bidding
in the comments and then I will follow up with you.
You got to bring it to RAGCon4, dude.
You got to bring it to RAGCon4.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
We got to have the group.
The group fuck.
This is actually happening.
No.
Okay, guys.
Put dollar sign, you know, your bid in the comments and I will follow up after, like,
a week.
I will follow up with the highest bidder.
Here you go.
This is a munchy thing.
Not a me thing.
Just no.
No, this is the same thing.
No, I actually discussed this with Nate previous to the show and he begged me to do it.
This is actually just a cover.
This is actually his flashlight.
Yeah, we're doing a good cop, bad cop routine right now.
Give him the salty and the sweet.
You know, that, you know, there you go.
Just like the french fry milkshakes.
There it is.
Yeah.
Bringing it all the way back around.
Sadly, if you cross section the flashlight, you won't get the delicious ice cream, delicious
french fries.
You'll just get rum and coke and cum and blood and sweat.
If you cross section the flashlight, you won't get the delicious ice cream, delicious french
fries.
You'll just get rum and coke and cum and blood and sweat.
Which is equally delicious, in my opinion.
I was looking in my drawer.
The first thing I picked out was a Chipotle thing.
Oh!
On the back though.
Front rack on three.
Let me try.
I don't think there's like a date on it.
It was 750.
It was a chicken ball and my host was Soraya.
The fuck is a chicken ball?
Chicken ball.
I don't know.
It's a rice ball.
Oh wait.
No, no.
Here's the date.
The eighth.
All right.
It's American, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
Baltimore.
Okay.
So the fourth of October 2019 is the eighth month.
That don't line up.
Wait.
That was when we did the meetup at Digi's Place, right?
No?
Am I wrong?
No, no.
This is August 2019.
This is BronyCon.
This must be BronyCon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When are we going to Chipotle BronyCon?
At 4.30 p.m.
Maybe he went without you, Munchie.
No, we definitely did.
Some people do things without you.
I remember.
No, I remember we went out to BronyCon.
I remember being there with, uh, uh, Cassie was there and I remember we were with the
little bird.
Wait.
I remember Banana was there.
Was I there?
Oh my God.
It's not that deep.
He went to Chipotle Munchie.
There's no analysis required.
No, no, without me?
Without me?
I'm sure you were there.
I think it was a whole big group.
Yeah, we went with a whole big group.
Yeah.
Like, we sat on the table.
This is radically an act that we're really tall.
What were you doing at the time?
I was doing partwheels.
I don't remember what.
Oh, was I printing out Slime Corp stuff?
Yes, that's it.
I think that's it.
You were printing out Slime Corp, but you missed on to Chipotle.
No, no, no.
That was something else because I remember, I remember, we went to Chipotle on the last
day.
We went to Chipotle on the last day right after we closed the ceremonies and then we came
back when we got MAP and we got, we saw MAP and we saw Ice Cold Water Guy and he was
awesome.
Right before that.
I remember now.
It's all coming back to me.
Thank God we solved this.
It's what my cue marks are telling me.
Sounds reasonable.
You see?
You see how cool that is?
Like a stupid fucking receipt brought all those memories back.
That actually is pretty cool.
I suppose that's true.
It's fucking awesome.
It says on the back, if you'd like a chance at free Chipotle, you should take our survey.
Nuff said.
Okay.
You've said enough already.
No need for more.
I can't answer the survey actually.
But I want free.
So anyway guys, about an anime that I saw recently.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is a shitty anime.
All right.
Transition, transition to, let's talk about what a nightmare experience it was just yesterday
and the day before and whatever.
Just grinding out these bureaucratic details about Radcon stuff that's now like done.
I just wanted to spend a few minutes perhaps to just be like, holy shit.
That was like one of the most grueling meetings I've had in my fucking life and it was so
long and it, sure, it was profitable.
It was fruitful in the end, but it was a true nightmare and I had a headache and my body
was in shitty condition and I didn't get to go to the gym and also tensions got raised
and people were mean and it hurt my feelings.
What?
No one was mean.
What the fuck is this shit about?
I may have sounded silly, but I was really low on sleep and cranky and like not holding
back in any, like, I was just sort of like the whole time.
All right.
Now I'm going to get mean, Nate.
I'm going to fucking push you down.
I'm going to pick you up and I'm going to put you down.
Sure.
That was it.
That was the extent of what I was going to do.
Oh, that was it.
Okay.
All right.
Well, fair enough.
No, nothing to get into too much.
Okay.
But let me quickly take a time to shit talk perhaps the worst actor in this whole endeavor,
which is as you, it's did you, bro.
I mean, this motherfucker, right?
We're working for hours on this.
He fucking strolls into the chat.
He's like, ah, just figured out guys and we're like, uh, okay.
And here we go.
Spaying our entire fucking several days working on it.
And he just comes in and this fucking comment in the chat was, yeah, I'm calling you out.
Did you piece of fucking shit?
He was like, wow, you guys are really still meeting after six hours?
Oh, what the fuck guys?
Which by the way, translation that that call it was just, wow, I can't believe you guys
are means to after six hours.
How that's like not even that different than my emphasis.
That's like basically the same meaning.
I just put a silly voice on it.
True.
It's just so fucking disrespectful of the effort we're putting in.
These things matter.
They were important things being discussed.
Okay.
What a fucking asshole.
Jesus Christ.
Am I wrong?
Am I fucking wrong?
And he thinks that we could just do it wherever.
Probably.
Okay.
Not literally wherever, but I'm sure he just trusts us.
Well, I think he thinks it's probably less effort than it is.
And I think that he thinks that, you know, whatever we come up with, we'll be fine for
him.
I think someone has to come up with those things.
No, no, the perception of what I think, you know, Digi, if you're listening to this,
I hope I'm not putting words into your mouth, but the perception I think is happening here.
It's like we are arguing over our ideal houses, not like coming up with houses to then decide
upon.
It's like we are all are coming at this and like he doesn't have to have a stake in
which house specifically we go to.
So anything is fine with him.
Only he actually did have huge preferences for some of the houses over others.
So actually he did have some pretty strong feelings about which ones.
So it's not like that's really totally true.
Oh, well.
Is Digi brah?
Yeah.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
All right.
So Digi cares about all the details less than most of us and he's just by disposition.
It's true.
He's less detailed concerned than somebody like me at least.
It's like I get it.
I get it.
But just shut up and let us do it.
But just to specifically laugh at how fucking long we've been working.
Technically laugh in the comment he wrote.
Like you read that into it, I think.
You were like going insane over this like two like a message long paragraph that he
wrote.
It was like a one message long.
It was like one sentence.
It was one sentence.
He was like, haha.
Wow.
Oh, okay.
Exact quote.
Digi.
Yeah.
Damn.
Have y'all been mean for six hours?
Indeed.
But I mean, this is one day out of several days.
He's just, he's just, you know, surprised, you know, this usually doesn't happen.
And so he's surprised and he's, you know, he's just voicing that, you know, there's
no direction.
Okay.
Here's the difference.
If I was getting paid more than Digi for this work, I wouldn't care.
But I'm not because we're already likely to barely break even.
So I just won't.
So why exactly is this like, why am I doing any of this?
What benefit do I have by putting in more effort than people who aren't literally nothing?
Oh, great.
That seems like a good use of my time.
See what I'm saying?
Yes.
Okay.
But, you know, world peace, you know, love among brothers, kumbaya, yoga, you know, meditate.
Let's just say, let's just say where we all meet up to Red Con.
Where's your yoga skills now?
You're losing your composure.
Control your anger, Nate.
Control your anger.
I feel this is a healthy challenge.
Do a yoga.
Downward dog.
Let's just say that when we finally meet, we'll be six, but we will leave as five.
Oh, no.
That's true.
I need to get more choice Digi images, because the one from Red Con 3 where he's down the
Isle of Toys R Us and he's looking at me menacingly, that is literally the best thing to come out
of an entirety of Red Con 3.
So we have to get more shit like that.
That is a good one.
No doubt about it.
We should do that thing where we build like a Digi Sandman instead of a snowman and kill
him as well.
That's giving him too much respect to even give him that.
I mean, why?
Because he's more important?
No.
Fuck that.
Fuck that guy.
You are.
This bridge is burned.
Fuck that guy.
It's all coming out.
I hate this guy.
He's a real piece of shit, you know, just fuck him, man, just fuck.
If he just hadn't made that one comment, I wouldn't care, but he did.
He didn't respond to it in any way.
You didn't let him know that you were not going to do it until now.
Yeah, I mean, what am I going to put a fucking paragraph after paragraph about how fucking
insensitive and cruel that comment was?
I think that's how you do it.
Well, you did it, but you did it verbally right now.
Which is way easier than typing it out, so there you go.
Listen, dental plan, Lisa needs braces, damn, have y'all been mean for six hours just swirling
around in your head just over and over, you're stewing in and out.
Pretty much.
Yeah.
Yeah, pretty much.
Damn.
Okay, listen, this is going to be the greatest good of all time.
But we got a lot accomplished.
We got, in spite of Digi's meddling, in spite of him putting up roadblock after roadblock,
we accomplished everything.
No, man, that's giving you too much credit.
It was pure indifference.
This is the most fucking totem on our heads thing that's ever been fucking like, like
Digi's is like a nefarious mastermind trying to thwart Radcon at every, not like, you
know, being uninformed, like, active guy.
He hates us, Monty.
He feeds on the chaos and the discord that he ensues in our hearts.
He feeds upon it.
It's his only means of substance.
I mean, the premise behind this whole thing is that like, if you're not present for discussions,
you basically have no say.
So you know, you have no say in what your reputation will be going forward either.
That's right.
After day one.
It's your own fault if we conspire against you.
That's right.
Exactly.
I want every single person, every single comment after day one of Radcon to be, damn, have
y'all been meeting for 24 hours and then so on and so forth.
Damn, have y'all been meeting for 10 days?
Dude, Radcon 4 means to come in early.
Oh yeah, I guess so.
That's true.
It's an early slime or not.
You're present for everyone.
I'm sure you guys know, and people can certainly weaponize this against me, but like, the thing
that makes me the most angry in this world, I definitely mentioned it to degrees before,
is like, not like an insult that like, hey, your stuff's shit, but like, like a disrespect
for the effort being put into something as if it's like it was pointless or didn't matter.
Shows like that are the most angering to me because it just, it shows like no care for
the effort being put into something, you know, it's just the most angering thing someone
can say.
Mm-hmm.
For me personally.
Yeah.
There you go.
Understandable.
I will say like I was saying at the beginning, the Radcon Fiora bureaucracy has been mind-numbing
and terrible and like the actual act of like, you know, searching for things.
So it was profitable, I think, and productive, and it's now like done basically.
We got it.
It is.
And you know what, it was fraternizing, which is good and cool.
I think I can use the word fraternizing in this way.
Well, that means to collaborate or something, right?
Yeah.
I don't know.
It was community building, but for like friends.
I think that's called like a conversation, I don't know, I don't think I've ever heard
of it.
I feel like we've gone through a trial by fire.
Yeah.
We all suffered through a common misery and we're all closer to the experience.
Dude, it's just like the West and Nazis, bro.
It's just like World War II.
It's just like band of fucking gather, dude.
It is like the Band of Brothers.
But like it's like we're the veterans who already fought like the first salvo of the
people and then like the new recruits were like, I can't wait, you guys are having so
much fun at war here, can't wait to join.
And we're like this motherfucking piece.
We are, we are like proud war veterans in the Vietnam War, right?
We've been out there doing good work, burning down villages, napalming preschools and stuff.
And then we get back here and Digi's here with his fucking hippie protest like, uh,
you know, child killer and I'm like, come on, freedom isn't free, fucker.
We are like the admirable Viet Cong going through the jungles, building tunnels underground
and Digi's just trying to blow up our rainforest and do guerrilla warfare tactics against us
every single step of the fucking way.
We're out here setting the Amazon rainforest on fire.
Okay.
This was kind of weird.
I saw an article.
Fucking up our atmosphere.
The great Australia brush fire.
There's like a weird like image, like a CCTV footage of like this like homeless looking
guy with like a joint like walking away and like he threw down the joint on the ground
and it started like a big fire.
That's really like strange.
It's really kind of weird actually.
Also Pam's was playing in the background.
I guess to be fair, the redeeming thing is that at important moments when we needed
Digi's input, he did eventually respond.
It was much harder to reach them than other people, but you know, fucking bad or epic
wall fucking epic.
Yeah.
That's why he did join for some jobs where he was needed.
So it wasn't all bad.
Listen, right.
Okay.
All right.
Here's what, here's what you need to understand guys and cut this out.
Eleazar.
If this is like too much, if this is too real, listen, we're already in the ship, we've spent
hours of our lives, you know, conducting a research, trying, oh my God, the search for
the house of this fucking place was an actual fucking number that went on long into the
night.
That was literally a travesty.
That was a holocaust too, if ever I fucking seen one.
And even on top of that, just all the hours to put it into trying to figure out things,
all the hours I spent making the logo for this, this has been a long endeavor and we
already have the Airbnb.
We already bought for it.
We bought all of our plane tickets.
We're fucking in the ship.
Cut that out.
Don't let them know.
Cut out the entire point then.
I don't want them to know we have financial vulnerability.
Isn't that good though?
Isn't that good?
No, we should tell them, yeah, we've already invested in it, like we've already put the
money where our mouth is and now it's up to them to make sure we don't regret it.
That's the idea, but I was going to be like, now you fucking better donate, bro, at the
wall.
No, don't argue for a position of weakness.
That's gay.
Is that weakness?
I'm just saying that I think it's good.
I think it shows that we are dedicated, that we went right ahead with it.
We got the house.
We already bought all our plane tickets and stuff.
We did.
That is true.
I think it makes us seem like chads where it's like, listen, we don't even fucking care,
bro.
We're out here.
If you want to be out here, then you can be, but if you're too fucking pussy and gay,
then you won't, but we're fucking out here, dog.
We're here.
We're at the level.
We went right at it.
We paid for it all out of our own pocket and now it's just the Kickstarter now is what's
going to make us not have lost all our money.
Yeah.
Fair enough.
Keep it in L.A.S.R.
Flip a coin.
What were you saying, Munchie?
You were making a point there of some kind.
No, the point was that.
So.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I see.
Well, audience, if you've heard this, then you've experienced a very special.
The reason we did that was because plane tickets get more expensive.
We would have paid double for the plane tickets probably if we'd waited until the Kickstarter
succeeded to buy our tickets.
So.
Yep.
That's true.
We're doing our best over here.
Hmm.
Well, I guess it'll be what it may be.
The Kickstarter will be ready today.
Who knows?
I don't know.
Probably not.
But in the next few days, it should be out.
Maybe.
I mean.
Well, I don't know how much is left to go.
Gotta make a video.
Gotta blah, blah, blah.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody's got to make an announcement video.
That's probably like the biggest thing.
Yeah.
That is the biggest thing.
And then maybe a couple little details.
But I guess we'll see.
So look for that.
But I guess that's it.
That's all I wanted to say about that.
More details will be on the Kickstarter when it comes out.
So keep your eyes peeled.
I guess that's it.
Tretch Gold, we get on the flight logs.
We ascend reality and we get to be on the mythical flight logs.
We need to be etched into history in the most admirable way possible.
By being on planes and being on the...
No, no, no.
Not just any flight logs, the flight logs name.
What are the flight logs?
I don't know what you mean.
The Jeffrey Epstein jet flight logs, of course.
What else could I need?
The Lilite Express flight logs.
Yeah.
I think.
Okay.
Now I get it.
We go instead to Epstein Islands to have our confines.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
That would be epic.
Redcon 5 Epstein Islands.
Yes.
We have to.
We have to kill ourselves.
It's just like a hero.
It's like a hero Epstein.
I can't wait to kill myself.
Has anybody got a bed sheet handy?
Anybody got some gravity handy?
I don't actually know that.
We're done.
Let's do voicemails.
Let's go to voicemails now.
Okay.
That sounds good.
How many do we...
Oh wait.
So okay.
Fucking issue with rhythm.
We all got to play them ourselves, but we can do it.
Leave them.
Leave your voicemails at the speak pipe link down below.
It's still working.
I didn't change anything.
Still going just fine.
I forgot about the worst part of this fucking show.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go.
We have eight of them.
Do you guys have them up?
You have them up?
Shit.
Let me...
I got to set it so it's coming out of my headphones.
God.
Oh my fucking god.
Hardware and sound.
Jesus.
Can we talk about the real worst member of the PCP?
Ben Saints?
Yeah.
I mean I have the exact same problem and I've tried to fix it for weeks.
It doesn't fix.
So it will just come out of my speakers and get picked up by my mic.
So I'll just mute myself while I listen, I guess.
Okay.
That works.
I have fixed the issue.
I am ready to go.
Okay.
We got...
First one is live from the Cuck Shed.
Sounds like a winner.
Okay.
So on the count of three, everybody play it.
Here we go.
Three.
So, did anyone in the PCP see little women?
It's okay because you're all men and that you're afraid to watch it.
You got this.
I believe in your fam.
Support women now.
Before it's too late.
Wait, did we see little women?
Have you seen little women?
No.
Every day I see them.
They are diminutive.
They're pretty small.
I mean, relatively.
I'd like to see more of them, frankly.
I'd say looking at my anime figurine collection now.
I can joke about really fast.
Wait, before the show, Ben was going to say something really cool.
Is there something like you met a girl?
You met a girl today, Ben?
Yeah.
Tell that story, please.
That's right.
This is good.
This is funny.
Well, okay.
The meme is that...
It was a miniature woman.
Yeah.
This was the meme on the last quick draw we recorded.
Before we started, I said in the call, hey, guys, I talked to you.
And everyone fucking crucified him and brutalized him.
And laid his corpse on the floor.
Oh, my God.
She had huge tits.
Her tits were so fucking big, by the way.
Wow.
Should I tell?
Should I tell what happened?
The legendary story?
You're already sitting on the quick draw.
It'll be on the quick draw, won't it?
No, I want to fucking hear it, goddamn it.
I haven't heard it.
I don't think you actually...
I don't think you actually told the story.
You started to tell it, and then we made fun of you.
I don't think I did.
Okay.
All right.
It sucks.
It's a bad story.
Good, good.
So strap in.
Well, I was at Garment District, you know, shopping for women's clothes, like I do.
And I don't know.
There was just a girl walking around, and she was really cute, and she had the biggest
tits imaginable.
Incredible.
I was just like, wow, you're gorgeous.
And she was like, is that bad?
No, it's fine.
Ignore the Zoomers.
They don't know how to talk to people.
Yeah, I just said, you're gorgeous.
And she was like, thanks.
I really appreciate it.
And I was like, OK, she doesn't want to be
spoken to by the male in public.
And that's her prerogative.
So I was just like, OK, cool.
That was it.
That's the whole story.
It's almost like the fucking worst method
in the entire world you could have done to get inside her pants
Give me a better method, Zoomer.
You have to work up to that.
You can't fucking just say, hey, you are a fuck right now.
You can't just say that.
OK.
People don't want to talk to you right now.
It was perhaps a slightly coming on a little strong.
But I mean, look, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
At least you talked to someone.
Give us time.
Munchie's talked to another human being ever.
Propose me an alternative strategy
that you would not be making fun of then.
Listen, I'm going to ask her about whatever specific thing
you say.
People will mock.
Whatever the specific thing is.
Like, that's not good enough because people
are so precious about their interaction with girls.
Hey, hey, oh, hi.
Oh, what you buying for?
You out shopping?
Nice weather we're having.
Then you didn't execute your one, two, three incremental nags.
You know, you didn't establish rapport first.
We could always.
Ben, you want to play this game?
OK, we can all just use silly voices to, hey,
you're looking beautiful today, babe.
That's probably more accurate to how it actually went.
To an outside observer.
Listen, I'm not being Ben Shapiro's sister, by the way.
I'm just imagining that the person that you're talking to.
Well, now you know the story.
And you can all go fuck yourselves.
You know what, what have you done today?
Nothing.
I, too, have talked to girls and embarrassed myself
in doing so many.
This wasn't even that embarrassing.
But I have done far worse.
And to anyone, have you ever told a girl
she was gorgeous?
In your fucking life, you cowards.
I just know there's people out there laughing
and I want them dead.
But OK, that's enough.
That's enough on that.
Like, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
If I say, never mind.
I don't have to justify myself.
It's fine to say it.
It's just like in a clothing store, it's a bit weird.
Like, it's just blanket a bit weird to start with.
Oh my god.
Anyone thinks it's weird that you're Ben?
I'm saying is you blew it.
You could have had it and you blew it.
That's the only concern.
OK, but you're right, Munchie.
I fucked up.
He took a shot, man.
I made a critical error.
You cringed, posted in real life,
wait you fucking hard and you blew it.
I mean, it's not like I expected it.
It's not like I was like, oh, if I say this,
she will fucking, she'll be all into it.
She'll be all over me if I say she's gorgeous.
It all comes down to episode three of Fooley Cooley.
I think that's episode three or episode four
about swinging the bat.
So many people just don't swing the bat at all.
That's episode four because I stopped in episode three
and I haven't been there yet.
OK, then maybe it's episode four.
But it's so much more honorable and respectable
to swing the bat even if you fail.
Thank you, you miss 100% of the shots you don't take.
There you go.
Exactly.
OK, all right.
And you know what?
OK, I'm going to justify myself even more.
You know what?
I could tell by her response that she
wasn't super comfortable with it.
And so I was like, OK, well, I'll leave you alone.
And I didn't say anything else to her.
Yes, that's well done.
And I think I did everything right.
So there you go.
There you go.
You're gay.
I'm sickly.
Take a lesson.
Hey, hey, babe, do you dip french fries
and it melt chicks?
Do I have an ice cream flavor for you?
Next time you're a listener, next time
you're going to call into the PCP with some dumb question
and be like, oh, I saw this girl.
And I don't know how to tell her I like her.
Like, how do I ask a girl out?
Just like, just remember, just use the Ben St method.
And get rejected immediately.
And get the Ben St results.
That's right.
If you play the Ben St game, you get the Ben St earnings.
That's what you do.
But you know what I got, though?
You know what I got out of it?
What?
A story?
The moral victory.
Of course, of course.
All right, let's go to that deal still on top.
Don't pretend to like jazz unless you know who Ben St is.
All right, voicemail number two, it's from gayboyjo.
All right, you guys all good?
I am like, yes.
Good?
This is my boo.
On the count of three, click on it.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
I wish our man got a face of the facts.
I'm 25 and my voice still cracks.
I'm a little bitch ain't worth the shit my dick.
But I got my butt fucked a dude, even though he had AIDS
and a bad attitude, because even though I ain't gay,
there ain't no way I'd get in there late.
Even if I had the pegs, ugly as sin,
can even begin to pop the pimples in my face
like the night sky, constellations all over the place.
And I'm sick and tired of running in front of this damn rat race.
I can't keep pace.
That's all I got.
Poetry, poetry.
Pointless.
Thanks, thanks, Joe.
I like how he stumbled.
That was funny.
It was pointless.
We asked for poetry.
Self-deprecating humor is perennial.
We'll never go out of fashion.
Indeed.
By the way, somebody else.
It would have been funnier if he was badly
rapping about how good he can rap.
I suppose that's true.
That is correct.
Yeah.
By the way, there was another guy who left on that.
I think it was like PC poetry.
OK, that guy left one interesting poem
about the Wright brothers.
But it was over two voicemails.
And look, I got to tell you, if you
are expecting me to commit to playing two voicemails
for your voicemail, it's got to be something above and beyond.
And it was not up to quite that caliber, dude.
Pair it down.
Just pair it down to one and submit it again.
Editorialize, remove some of that shit, send it again.
It was good.
But it was just too fucking long.
All right, let's go to the next one.
Here we go.
Tectonic improv, you guys good?
You ready to click?
Yes, this guy, who may I remind you,
this is the guy who did a PCPU style lecture on the canon
of Linkara and the Linkara universe.
Oh, right.
Fascinating.
If you want to check it out, he's got a YouTube channel.
It's called Tectonic Improv.
It's entertaining.
Well, shit.
All right.
He also does other stuff.
But let's see what he has to say today.
All right, start on the count of three.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
So Ben brought up that Matthew Matosis released
a new video in the last podcast.
Yeah, he got cut off.
I don't know if anyone had anything to say about that.
But I'd like to hear you guys' thoughts on it.
Personally, I was really psyched to watch the video.
And I got like 20 minutes in.
And then I realized that I kind of want
to play the game for myself.
And I feel like the commentary will be a lot more
enjoyable that way.
You guys ever really had that sort of thought
where you wanted to watch a video on a game or an anime
or something?
And maybe you got like a little while in.
And then we're like, you know what?
I want to watch the show before I get any further into this.
This is the saddest reflection of modern society
that I've literally ever seen in my entire fucking life.
The fact that this is a quaint idea.
Like, ooh, maybe I should like actually like watch the show
instead of just watching the video essay,
reviewing the show by my favorite internet personality.
Ooh, oh, that's such a weird, like a new kooky idea.
Oh, very strange.
I'm going to defend this other bizarrely idea.
I kind of don't care about spoilers, like almost ever.
I can't remember the last time I was like,
oh, a guy put out a video essay about a thing,
but I haven't seen the thing.
Oh, the biggest example.
I better go check it out before I watch the video.
I watched all of Twin Peaks before ever experiencing
any of the stuff they talked about.
And I absolutely love them.
But at this position, I had gone and watched all of Twin Peaks.
And like all of Silent Hill, blah, blah, blah.
And they just came out with their giant season three
of Twin Peaks like review or whatever.
And for this one, I was like, okay.
That's a while ago.
Yeah, at this point, it was months,
but I still haven't, I just have been doing other stuff.
I watched most, some of it, not all of it.
You haven't seen it yet.
I'm halfway through, give or take.
So like, no.
Wait, the review or through the show?
Through the show.
I put the review on hold to watch the show first.
Even though that's different from how I consumed
all the other material, but since I was so close
and I just had to watch one thing.
But like, you'd seen the old Twin Peaks.
So you were like largely, you were in it already.
Exactly, which is why I felt comfortable doing this.
But I just put it off cause like, you know,
I wanna fucking experience it for, they say,
like it's the spoiler warning of a lifetime right now.
At the very beginning, I'm like, well, okay.
I guess I'll, you know, I'd seen the old,
I'd seen the old Twin Peaks.
I wasn't that interested in watching the new one.
So even though I thought about it,
I decided to just go ahead and watch the video anyway.
And I don't regret it personally.
Well, that's fine.
Even if I did later on decide to watch the new Twin Peaks,
I don't think it would like hugely denigrate
my enjoyment of it.
You're probably right.
It might even improve it, I don't know.
It's not about spoilers or not.
Don't you see what's happening here?
You're all lying to yourselves.
Cause so, so, so often it's not like,
oh, you know, I'm in taking this information
and I will watch the show eventually,
but I'm just getting spoiled for it now.
I don't care about that.
That was a completely separate issue.
So, so often, 99% of the fucking time,
it's not you are just watching the video essay
or, you know, the review of it
and you never get around to the actual thing.
Cause you've just in taken all the information from it.
And you know, that's completely different
from actually watching the show,
but you've satisfied your bloodlust
and, you know, a hunger for content.
So that you're not actually going to get around to it.
This is the exact opposite of what should be happening.
You should be actually watching shows
instead of just watching regurgitation.
That's exactly what I described.
I don't know how many shows I actually want to watch though.
Well, that's a problem.
There's only like two shows per year
that are worth anything.
There's good old ones.
Currently, yeah, there's tons of old ones.
Like, you could, I could easily do someone
making like a great review.
Maybe I'll do this one day.
I mean, like to watch.
I watch two things per year.
Okay, sure.
Yeah, and that's a problem.
And I'm maybe one day I'll do a big video
on like The Sopranos, a show I love
and watch the entire thing.
It's like seven seasons, but it does rule.
But like anyone who I'm like,
hey, go watch it first.
We're talking like seven seasons or whatever
of a fucking show.
So that's a big commitment.
I have a lot of like,
oh, it would be nice if I could get around
to watching Star Trek The Next Generation or something.
Yeah, yeah.
I have lots of like a list, like mind maps of those things.
But like, I feel like in the free time I have
getting that all set up annoys me.
And even if it's easy, I don't like binge watching things.
And so, I don't know.
You don't have to binge watch Star Trek.
It's a different mindset to sit down
and watch some episode of a thing
than it is to like passively intake a YouTube video
while you're doing something else.
Yeah, and it's a massively worse experience.
You can get way less out of it.
You can passively consume.
I will strongly advocate Star Trek is a show.
Most of it I watched, tabbed out,
just listening to people talk, doing other work.
It's absolutely a show you can do that.
But I'm just making my little pitch
because I love Star Trek and I want everyone to watch it.
Neither here nor there.
In any case, the point is fair.
I would like to be in the mindset
where I want to consume thing.
But like, I very rarely get excited for anything.
It's just, it's not even like YouTube.
This has been like all of my life.
Like, I just don't care about stuff.
I have a very, very small pool of things
I'm extremely passionate about.
You're on the same page as me.
I'm just, I just don't care.
I just don't care that much about, oh, a show is out?
How good could it possibly be?
Well, look at the classics though.
I mean, I would find, I'm certainly in what's become a classic.
I mean, it's not even like,
it's not even about like, oh, current things.
It's all, it's all media.
Like I intake not that much media
and I'm pretty happy with the amount of, you know,
that I don't watch, like cause.
Fair enough.
I don't know.
Like it sort of gets overwhelming
if I'm trying to watch one show,
like one episode per week.
Even if it's an old one.
It's just sort of like, ah, who cares?
I think without strong influences in your art
and being an artist and not seeking out other artists' work,
I think is a major detriment to your evolution
as a person, as a human being and as an artist.
I think it's a big problem.
You're probably right.
But just like such a small percentage of the things
that I do consume end up being like meaningful to me.
Sure, but that's what you gotta do.
It's discouraging.
There's a sense, all right, there's that, all right.
But there's also like life experiences.
I'm not saying like YouTube is life experiences.
YouTube is definitely bad and I agree with you on that.
But like when it comes to meaningful experiences,
I know what I like and I seem to like the same things
every time and so like going for a walk is like something,
you know, I mean, I went for a walk today.
I walked the dog and it was cold, but the sun came out
and you know, the sun was like glistening on the lake
and across the grass and it was like incredible.
Like I would much rather had gone on that walk
than watch a few episodes of a show
I've been meaning to get around to.
Okay, fair enough.
Hey, what can you say?
I get you, I mean, I understand that.
But I think that, okay, I think that novelties of virtue,
I think originalities of virtue,
I think that experiencing new things
is almost inherently good.
And I think that people overestimate
how hard it is to get into things
even that are super long,
like let's say for Homestuck for example, for instance,
and this isn't a great example
because this is extremely short show,
but as we were just talking about it,
Fooly Coolie has been on my radar forever, forever.
And I've always wanted to watch it,
but I just haven't gone around to it
because I fucking hate watching things.
I'm on the same page of the sense that it's like,
I tried to watch like a couple of like episodic dramas
or like HBO dramas and it was so fucking hard
to slog through them all.
But once I get into a show and I just say, okay,
today I'm gonna watch like an episode, you know,
if I get the time.
I've just been putting on Fooly Coolie during lunch breaks
where I normally would put YouTube on
because I've blocked YouTube from my computer
literally indefinitely forever.
By the way, link in description to my Tumblr post 2020
where you can read all about why I'm doing what I'm doing.
But anyway, I've been watching Fooly Coolie
and it's not that hard.
Obviously it's only six episodes,
but like I can easily see doing this for a longer show.
It will take some time to realize,
but it'll be so much better for me in the long run
and feel so much better even in the moment
than doing the same sort of stuff
that I've done a thousand times before
and re-watching a Dude's Bro video
and doing all this shit that I could.
Well, that's your mistake.
Did you finish Fooly Coolie?
No, but I'm close.
Oh, it's so good.
When I first like started trying to watch anime in 2014,
I watched like Space Standing, Kill a Kill
because they were out and they were cool
and Ava and Gurren Lagann and Cowboy Bebop.
But then, and Fooly Coolie, I think,
but then there was like Gun Buster and Die Buster,
which was recommended to me by you two, Ben and Nate.
Yeah, yeah.
And I don't know what it was.
I think it was just sort of the wrong mindset.
This thing I'm talking about,
like the wrong mindset to enjoy or view something
because I've watched it to get it off the checklist
and I was like, yeah, yeah, well, yeah, cool, yeah, cool.
Sure.
And I was, my reaction was not,
like my reaction was not cool enough in the chat,
I remember, and you were like,
what the fuck, isn't it the coolest thing ever?
And I was like, I stand by.
Sure, sure.
Oh God, this just proves even more
that society is fucking crumbling before me,
that the West is falling.
This literally proves it.
We truly live in a fallen state.
It's literally, I understand why you have that.
It's not like you're a fault hippo.
That's just what these institutions in our life
has bred us to believe.
Because you wanna check out these,
check off these checks on the list
because you wanna be a part of the conversation
that people are having around us.
We wanna be a part of the YouTube sphere.
We wanna be able to consume all this stuff about it.
We wanna get into the fandom and show that.
But yeah, I mean, that's my whole argument
is that if I'm not in the right mindset
to take something in,
it's going to be at the expense of the thing.
And I kind of don't wanna do that.
Oh, watch a show when I feel like watching it.
And then it'll be way better.
I think we all understand this point now.
Let's go to the next goddamn voicemail.
Okay, I'm ready.
Okay, next one is The Puppet Master.
We all ready?
You guys good?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, count of three.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Does being autistic help you focus on your project, dude?
Does that help?
Shout out.
Oh, Nate, you wound me deeply.
Before I respond to that,
I just need to reiterate the most important part
of my last voicemail,
which was cut off by your autistic screaming.
And that is to profess my undying love and affection
for Hippo and everything that he does.
Although I did once leave a nasty comment
on one of his previous videos.
And I think you know which one it is.
Anyway, yeah, I know Digi is a complete and utter madman
and his whole autism spectrum thing is just a meme.
I threw it in there because I thought it might be funny.
And you know-
Tell us more of your life story, buddy.
I'm really serious.
Oh my god.
So I understand how you thought that I wasn't joking.
Come on, give me some credit for that.
I'm not that fucking autistic.
That aside, I'm really glad you guys
liked the communist hell voicemails
and have to put me in the PCP voicemail.
And I would really like to do a finale
at some point this year.
If I can find the inspiration to conclude it.
It's a nice creative outlet to do fun stuff like this.
And thanks for the advice.
I'll try it out and see how it goes.
And also, Nate, I was not joking in the voicemail
from Comrade Stalin, October of last year.
From one software developer to another,
coding and coder are normie words.
To thick dick master race digital gods,
like us, it's called programming.
Anyways, thanks again, guys.
Xin yen kuala.
Voice, voice, voice, voice, voice, voice, voice, voice.
I mean, what a record.
This man has been previously in voice grail
until this point.
Jail, jail him, jail him.
Okay, before we make that decision.
There's something, okay, there's something going on here.
There is a brand of voicemail lever
who weirdly thinks that we need to know
so much of their personal backstory
with the voicemail, like guys, I left this voicemail,
this voicemail, this voicemail,
but you need to know that.
It's important.
Clearly shows that he is actually that autistic
with the amount of, like, he assumes so much
that we would remember all of these things that he's done.
I mean, I do remember them.
I understand the urge.
But specifically the comment that he assumes I know
that he left and will remember when he mentions it.
I don't know what he's talking about.
That you're gonna make a finale.
Just like, call in with the finale and we'll hear it.
This is so long, so meandering,
such a waste of fucking time.
Just pussy-footing, apologizing and clarifying
to these voicemails.
What a more pointless thing could possibly exist.
You are an autistic, more autistic, more autistic.
You're insane.
You are a psychopath.
You are a unabomber.
You are a fucking,
this is just pure constructive criticism,
no doubt about it, to help the puppet master
and those like him leave higher quality voicemails
in the future.
You're in the fucking voice jail.
This is literally the fucking worst day of my entire life.
I guess the people have spoken.
I guess he's going straight to voicemail.
We are personal inmates.
I am on a first name basis with you and your mom.
We're putting the voice puppeteer in the voice jail.
Okay.
Okay, let's go to the next one.
She pollution from the future.
Oh, this is the person who asked us like our thoughts
on what would be left in the future.
Reporting from the future, it seems.
Okay.
All right, you ready?
Ready to click?
Okay, on the count of three, here we go.
One, two, three.
Hello?
Wow.
Can you guys hear me?
He's receiving you, yeah.
Hello?
Yes, okay, yes, hello.
It's me, she pollution from the future.
I was too curious about if your predictions were correct.
So I built a time machine.
So let's see.
Ben is still in Pito.
He also got his 26th kidney stone.
Hmm.
Oh, and Digipro is a father now.
You guys edit the page material for naming a skate
like you said you would.
And well, let's just say that you guys call him Nick
for short.
The PSP still exists and your channel is doing great.
You got lots of subscribers when a short clip of hippo
making a joke became viral.
Something with apple juice and dogs.
Also, it's in prison for animal abuse.
Okay, so there we go.
Took that my time machine can only go one year
into the future.
Hey.
Well, see you next year.
Bye.
What's at the end?
All right.
There you go.
One year.
Sorry, if you are not, if you don't have a proper American
accent, then you cannot put a voice modulator on.
You can't do it.
It's like the double way of me.
It can make things.
I mean, every word that was modulated,
I understood in that.
I heard my name, but I don't know what you said.
One of you is echoing, by the way.
It's not me.
It's a hypocrite, probably.
It is hypocrite.
When I'm listening to the things only,
it's an unfortunate setup.
I'll cut it out of my ear.
Okay, okay.
Well, hey, there's Sleet Sheepolution.
Thanks for the report.
In a year, we'll look at another year in the future.
Glad to know the future is bleak,
just like I expected.
Called it, hashtag called it.
All right, let's go to the next one.
Looking forward to it.
Okay, oh, here's an interesting one.
No more shit lectures.
Let's hear what he has to say.
All right, on the count of three, here we go.
One, two, three.
Okay, so what made the original PCP lectures good
is that we had each member's esoteric,
autistic perspective on this very weird subject
and how it related to them.
So we had Nate with his devotion to the Kingdom Hearts
and how he understood its weird nonsense plot
across all the games.
About Ben, how he explored Christian as a person
through Christian's work.
And then Munchy, like, loving performance art
through Park or Dude91.
And then the next year, for Adcon 3,
they all deliver utter fucking dog shit.
Nate just poorly remembers parts of the Final Fantasy games
and there's no connection there
and just it was boring and useless.
Ben just tells you the plot to a webcomic
that has Sonic to it.
So I guess, you know, that's the same,
even though there's literally nothing interesting
about what he says.
And then Munchy just watched a YouTube video once
and then repeats it back to the audience.
So congratulations, lad.
You really put in the effort.
You really did the groundwork there.
Don't fuck it up this year for Adcon 4.
Actually put the work in.
If you don't have a lecture to be interesting,
just don't fucking do one then.
Thank God Digi Tom could save Adcon 3.
So please, don't be shit.
Yeah, Digi's gonna save Adcon 4.
No doubt.
I kind of low key agree,
but I don't think-
A little bit.
But did you have to hurt my feelings on the way, sir?
That's my one question.
I think, okay, well, both the lectures
I'm planning on giving, I think are pretty solid.
So I don't think, I mean,
I don't think the Tails Gets Trolled Lecture is shit.
I don't think it's as good as the Sonichu one.
Yeah, yeah.
He's probably pointing to that drop off, I guess,
in some degree. It's good.
And I think I have some interesting points to make
about Jennifer Diane Wrights.
And I think that I have lots to say
about Chris Chan post 2000, whenever it was,
that the-
Right, right.
Whenever the last one ended.
I mean, it's gonna be good.
Fuck you.
Maybe I didn't explain it well enough
in the actual lecture,
but it's not like I had seen that video recently.
Like it had been like a driving force between,
like I had seen it as a kid
and had continuously come back to it over the years.
And it's something that I had ruminated on
various, many different times.
So the human history lecture didn't come out
like the ether like a couple of weeks beforehand.
It was, I mean, maybe I didn't come through the lecture
and therefore it made it worse because of it,
but like it was definitely not like random
or like I watched a YouTube video.
I watched a very important YouTube video
and then I reached out.
Hey, true, true.
Yeah, all right.
These are fair points.
Keep in mind.
All right, anyway, let's go to the next one.
We've got Mass Effect Mouth Noises.
Okay, let's do it.
On the count of three, here we go.
One, two, three.
All right, Mr. Bestman.
I have a complaint from last week's episode.
You claimed that Mass Effect 3 was a bad finale
when really only the very ending was a letdown
and the rest of the game and its multiplayer
were received pretty well.
What's your take on that?
I voiced jail, I hate this person.
I think, isn't Tom the only one of us
who's actually played Mass Effect?
I have not played Mass Effect.
I'm repeating, I played a, look, was I not clear?
Everything I know comes from
Mr. B. Tung's review videos.
Did you play Mass Effect, Jesse played Mass Effect?
That's true, none of them are here
who actually played the game.
Why does this person exist?
Why did he do this?
What did he hope to be?
Yeah, what a strange small complaint.
This is the, you know, I'm sure there were people out there.
These people always exist.
That like when a wave of criticism appears,
there's the people who are like, you know,
and you know, maybe they're literally correct.
They're like, sure guys,
your point about that one specific thing is fair,
but there's all this other good stuff.
Like I could believe that.
It's just, it seems like,
wasn't the entire promise from the beginning of Mass Effect
was a big story where things would,
your decisions would matter in the end and like,
okay, everything else, let's say, was great about the game.
But when that, you could, I think it's fair to say
the most important thing, at least relating to the story,
and it's a story-based fucking game,
turns out to, they actually didn't plan it out
and it made basically no difference.
I mean, at that point, it seems like fair to be like,
can you call it a failure?
I mean, everyone's got their definition, I guess, but.
I don't know, I don't feel comfortable speculating
having not played it.
I mean. Yeah, fair enough.
We shouldn't even talk about it.
We have nothing to say about it.
It's really stupid, it doesn't even fucking matter.
And this guy is stupid.
Fucking Mass Effect mouth noises.
Never call here again.
Yeah.
Voice jail, voice jail, huh?
Yeah, I don't feel that strongly about it.
I'm feeling pretty generous today.
Voice jail, I'm feeling pretty generous.
I'm feeling generous.
No, that's giving him too much credit.
I don't care, whatever, let's move on to the next one.
We can actually shout later.
All right, Zolpher is our last words.
We can have another six hour meeting about it.
Yeah, we'll have that, that'll be good, that'll be good.
All right, Zolpher is our final one for the day.
Let's see how he does.
Okay, one, two, three.
I did it, PCP.
I lost my virginity.
I completed my love quest by listening to your podcast.
Yeah. Thank you.
Here's how I did it.
Step one, I went to Animate Club.
Nice.
Step two, I approached a cute, quiet girl
that was just by herself.
You said you're gorgeous.
This car knocks me for the sake of this story
or just not see for short.
Step three, the most important step,
I didn't talk to her about Animate.
We talked about philosophy, poetry,
love, our dreams for the future.
She wants to be a pediatrician,
but she's failed to cause entrance exams seven times.
I asked her why she can't pass a test.
Biology, she says, I'm really bad at anatomy.
A bell rang in my head.
I knew exactly what to say.
I look into her eyes and I just say,
I'll teach you what I know.
Well done.
Wow, wow, okay.
Unbelievable.
Munchie, I think you think that that's a real story,
but it was clearly a joke story.
Yeah, that actually makes it really good now, actually.
That actually completely changed me.
In that case, I'm very entertained.
Yeah.
Guys, we have to have an intervention here.
What is happening right now?
Nate, why are you like this?
Why does this happen?
Hey, just consider these were the best of the bunch.
I mean, you know.
Just pick better ones.
There are no better ones.
You heard the best ones.
Then pick zero.
Yeah, none.
We could have.
We don't need to have more than one ship.
Guys, guys, guys.
Listen, your complaints are totally worthless
and I don't care.
You just do this unpaid job,
then you'll have nothing to complain about.
You do get paid.
No, not for this, no I don't.
You get the ad?
Okay, fine, fine.
We've been over this many times.
Okay, well, listen,
I'm gonna fucking slap you on the wrist
and say do better.
That's the only thing I have the authority to do.
That's, I suppose that's fair.
And I'm gonna fucking work it to the best of my ability.
All right, that's it.
We're done with this shit.
I'm ready to get the fuck out of here.
Please improve voicemails.
I'm sure you don't have to read Confor.
Wait, wait, wait.
We're not actually done.
Please shut up.
Assuming that it exists yet and nobody knows.
Speak, pipe, link, voicemails,
please leave ones that are improved.
Or don't honestly, don't leave a voicemail, please.
Please fucking joke.
Just leave the cream of the crop.
Do your thing, do your thing.
We don't need your whole life story.
We don't need your whole every, you know,
fucking voicemail you left in your whole fucking life.
What do you say at the beginning?
Just amuse us.
It's still nap time.
It's been nap time this whole time.
It's really a loud nap time.
All right, but as they were saying,
pick your read Confor Kickstarter.
Come in, maybe by this time this is out,
but very soon.
Either out now or out soon.
Soon at the latest.
So keep your eyes fucking peeled on this channel.
It'll be here.
Go to the right, focus copy this channel too
because there's like shit happening there
right now guaranteed, so you can watch that too.
Oh yes, Rowdy Focus Cop Killers, Con is on.
Yes, right now.
As you hear this, holy shit.
Powerful stuff.
And don't forget to look out for the next chapter
of the Lord of Ghosts comic on give and take dot site.
And keep in tune for more updates
to Lonesome Cactus, the best disc robot ever made.
It is, Endless War was a pre-alpha for Lonesome Cactus.
It's literally true.
This is gonna eclipse it completely.
And go to QuickDruck because there's gonna be
a bunch of shit.
It already is shit now.
And there will be more, because yeah.
I'll also say, I guess while we're on this,
more videos from me, go check out my shit.
But more importantly, right now.
Hey guys, Morweaga was on the way guys, yeah.
On the canton channel, we just did our big
seasonal anime wrap up that people always enjoy.
Part two will be out by the time you hear this,
so go check it out.
It's a good time.
Everybody likes it.
Nate, I'm gonna racially profile you.
Hey, I got a little bit of news.
I got a little bit of funny news this week,
just yesterday, or maybe the day before.
You should fuck off.
The Sonichu Lecture hit a million views.
Oh, that's right.
Pretty cool.
Congratulations.
Now nobody can watch it again.
It has to stay there.
I got that nice M under the thumbnail.
You got that nice W in life.
What?
It's a win, Ben.
It's a win.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is what the Urban News say, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know all about them.
They've adopted me.
All right, that's it.
That's what's up.
We're done, everybody.
Hey, patreon.com slash theprocrastinaires,
support the show.
$5, get the bonus episodes, $1, fucking Discord,
and hang out with us, blah, blah, blah,
but give us more money.
And also, PSB Minecraft, I'm sure it'll be back up
by the time you see this.
Hopefully, we'll see about that.
Oh, my God, is it not back up yet?
Oh, no.
We're currently waiting for shock bite to fix it.
It's the problem on their side.
We are convinced of this.
They got to fix some bullshit.
And hopefully they'll give us money,
but they won't because they're clearly cheap motherfuckers.
But we'll see what's up.
It's not our fault, but we'll have it fixed soon.
Play Minecraft.
It's a good time.
All right, we're done.
We're out of here.
We'll see you next week, everybody.
Rack on four.
Pay us money.
We could use it.
Thank you very much.
All right, we're out of here.
Later.
Bye.