If you don't stand with your fellow Canadians, then you are a rat!
Don't call me a rat, buddy!
I'm not your buddy, friend.
He's not your friend, guy.
I'm not your guy, buddy.
He's not your buddy, friend.
I'm not your friend!
Hello!
Everybody, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
The only show on the internet about friends.
I am the best guy ever, and we're joined today by Mumkey Jones.
Oh, look at Donkey Go!
That's funny.
We've got Ben Saint here.
Yeah, the PCP, the only show produced by friends, for friends, and only for friends.
If you're not our friend, get out of here.
If you're not on the Patreon, you're literally a worthless friend.
Oh, wait, Mumkey's calling you out.
Mumkey's calling you out, listener.
That's true.
We've also got the DeVoo with us.
Hey, everybody.
I saw those pictures you posted on Facebook of you guys hanging out.
I guess I didn't get the invite, I guess.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
DeVoo wasn't supposed to know.
And at her glorious return, it's going to be a real frenesance, everybody.
Lethal Aurora Mage is back with us.
Holy shit, here I am, guys.
We're just delighted to have you with us once again.
Yeah, I'm happy to return.
Beautiful.
So let's do the thing that we're doing and let's clarify what the PCP is real quick.
It's a YouTube podcast where a bunch of friends from the internet,
who all are content creators, get together and just talk about a bunch of bullshit.
Any clarifications?
It's also a pyramid scheme, as of very recently.
A hashtag PCP Pyramid Scheme, everybody.
All right, well, today's topic, everybody, is friends.
Worthless friends, specifically.
Those worthless fucking pieces of shit.
Okay, we'll get into the exact definition.
But first, okay, so there's no worthless friends on Urban Dictionary, if you can believe that.
But let's just see what a friend is and we'll go from there.
Nobody knows about friendship better than the people of Urban Dictionary.
That's very true.
Okay, here we go.
Here's the top definition for friends.
People who are aware of how retarded you are and still managed to be seen in public with you.
People who make you laugh till you pee your pants.
People who cry for you once your special items disappear
when you don't have enough money to get an ice cream they chip in
knows all your internet passwords who would never make you cry just to be mean.
I think I have a lot of friends that would fit this perfectly.
What a terrible definition.
If not making me cry just to be mean, it qualifies you as a friend.
Then I think I have an awful lot of friends.
That's true.
Does anybody actually trust their friends with their internet password?
That's like a recipe for disaster.
You know what I remember when I think about that?
You know that scene at the beginning of Full Metal Jacket
where the Sergeant guy calls out a private fat body or whatever his name was, Gomer Pyle.
He's like, there's nothing in this world I hate more than an unlocked footlocker.
If it wasn't for worthless pieces of shit like you, there'd be no thievery in this world.
He's making the larger point there that sometimes it's best not to trust everybody
because everybody's better off that way.
So I'm totally with you.
You shouldn't share all your personal details
even with your closest friends because people don't want to know that shit
and it causes temptation.
You can fuck you over in the long term.
Well, the problem is they do want to know it
so that they can fuck me over by posting I'm gay lol on Facebook.
So that's why you don't want to give them the password.
Was that any different from a usual Facebook post for Monkey?
Like, I don't even...
It's been posted so many times they wouldn't know if I got hacked or not.
You guys use Facebook?
You're such normies.
My Facebook actually got hacked this morning
and my college friends were messaging me being like,
dude, thanks for notifying me about that 90% off sale of sunglasses.
But please keep that to your...
And how ironic is it that it's sunglasses?
Knowing that it's me.
Fucking perfect.
But in any case...
So, okay, we're talking about worthless freks.
Nate, don't pretend you're not taking a little handout under the table
from some unscrupulous foreign bootleg sunglasses corporation.
They supply you and that's how you get your fix.
They keep me in the green with these sunglasses.
Keep me out of the red.
Okay, so let's...
I think we all probably got a different idea of what a worthless friend really is.
I'm sure it'll be around the same...
Same general theme, but...
So who's had some experience with a friend who turned out to just be of no value
to you or anyone else on this earth?
Oh, buddy.
I've got a wacky cavalcade of lovable characters to introduce you all to today.
I have two.
Ooh.
Two.
Well, I think...
I think since Mage is a lady and she's also back after a long summer,
I think we should let her go first.
No.
Agreed.
Don't.
Okay, never mind.
Okay, let's get somebody else to give one and then we'll maybe go back.
Well, we've all heard the tale of Momke's great friend in high school
who fucked his girlfriend and also slashed his sister.
So that's pretty worthless friend, somebody who betrays your trust like that.
Well, hang on, hang on.
There is a right way to fuck your friend's girlfriend and to fuck your friend's sister.
I'm just saying, you know, context matters in these situations, but okay.
Sure.
Yeah, context the fucking his own sister and...
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, great story.
I think I've read that anime before.
But I mean, the thing is though with me is I think my greatest weakness is that I might be too forgiving
because despite how worthless and terrible these friends are and all the bad things they've done to me,
like they don't even fucking say sorry, but I'm just like,
Yeah, well, I guess live and let live, you know.
I think there's a difference between boys and girls is that girls like really hold grudges long term
and the guys are just like, uh, fuck it.
Let's go drink a beer.
So hold on.
So your biggest flaw is that you're too forgiving.
I think I read about that on like page 17 of Humblebrag Compendium 2018.
Oh, that's not a brag.
Is being forgiving something to brag about, DeVoo?
In Jesus fucking did it.
It's a sign of weakness.
It's like quite literally mess-ionic.
In today's, in today's feminized society, I suppose it is a virtue.
I suppose it is.
I think being too forgiving is a sign of weakness.
I think it's a, it's a humble deficit, not a humble brag because it only leads to more pain.
Like, oh, I guess I'll let you walk all over me and treat me like shit all the time.
But the thing is, I don't have any other fucking friends.
So what am I supposed to do about it?
I have no choice but to forgive them for all these terrible things they've done.
But, uh, you know, that's just the one example.
I'll get into one so you guys haven't heard before later on.
Okay, uh, mage, can you give us one of your two?
Okay, but I'm leaving the last one for last because this is super long.
Okay, okay.
So like, um, there was this guy, we go way back.
I think I met him when I was eight at first and like, we have a quite a history, but
like to summarize it, like at first he was like absolutely terrible.
Disgusting.
To summarize it, he raped me.
He was, he was, he was the, he was the brother of my best friend.
So we, he had to be there, I guess, but whenever we went to hang out.
Was he an older, an older guy?
Yeah, by one year.
So he was, yeah.
So he's around.
So, so at first, like we really disliked him, but then like, uh, started to really
get along with him that at one point he became the best friend rather than my best
friend, that'll come up later in the second story, by the way, um, or should do
if I don't forget foreshadowing.
But yeah, so, and then, uh, we were like really, really good friends and stuff.
And he went to, um, study in America for a year as, uh, not an exchange program,
but like he won the privilege of studying in America for a year and was really cool.
And we, um, kept in touch and he actually sent me a manga, like the death note first
volume manga for Christmas as well, because he knew I was really into death note at
that time.
So it was like, it was wonderful.
We were good friends, but then he, he returned and when he returned, he was, he
kind of got set back a year in school because in America, they were learning a
different curriculum than we were learning.
Sure.
So he ended up in my class and I was like, we can sit together during the classes
we are going to have together and like we can hang out and stuff.
It'll be like great.
But then he never did.
And then he kind of started shunning me and it's just like he, he got like too
cool for me or something.
Like because, because I think the thing is like he was always sort of, he had that
American, he had that, he was, he was an American.
No, the, my theory is because he was always sort of like the nerd in his previous
class.
He didn't really have much friends, but, um, then he came back and he was like,
he started getting along with the other people a lot.
And it was like, we were teens at that point.
I think 16 or 17 and you know, everyone kept hanging out and drinking and stuff.
And I'm not about that.
And like we were, we went to like the super special class called like the
baccalaureate program.
So like all the smart kids quote unquote went there.
Right.
And I got in there because I was very good at English.
That's the only reason I got in there.
Um, I suck at everything else other than English class.
So, you know, I wasn't the most popular kid, especially since I was like into
anime and stuff.
So I was like the weird kid.
So I, I was not popular.
So I think he sort of like traded me off for popularity.
And I was like, you know, I, he's been a loser kind of his whole life.
I'm going to let him have this one.
So, you know, mage, that's a, that's an excellent point.
I also want to add to the point that it is a big propagandized myth that nerds
are like actually good people or nice people like the shitest meme of all.
I hate it so much.
Every time you see like the scrappy loser kids, honestly, it's like, it's like an
it, the, the, like all the kids who were like the outcast were like the best
people and everyone else was literally an evil monster.
All the bullies were like fucking, you know, evil freaks, but the loser kids
only hang out with each other because they can't do any better.
That's why they hang out.
And the second you give them a drop of something beyond that, they'll
seize it and they'll betray you at every turn.
You can't trust a nerd as far as you can throw, particularly with the whole
like, oh, he's going to be better to a girl stereotype.
It's like, there is going to be a, they're taking the beta path to get the
pus.
Right, right.
That's what they're doing.
You're going to, you're going to be able to perceive a above average
level of giving a shit because of the desperation.
If they get it, the desperation goes away and then they haven't had the
experience of trial and error and how to treat a woman gentlemanly that a
fucking Chad would have by it.
And I know this game cause I played it for many, many years.
That was my ankle in life.
Oh, I need to go back.
I'm not shitting on them at all.
They're smart.
They're, they know what they're doing.
You know what it makes me think of?
It makes me think of Griffith from Berserk and how, and how
he was, you know, he was, well, you know, I won't not, no need to go into the
details, but you know, once, once he, once he got like, once he had all the
power and once he, once he could do whatever he wanted with no consequences,
he showed his true colors and you know, what's interesting about that, Berserk
really is the story of a friendship and how like, yeah, like, I guess even the
whole thing with Charlotte and like, when he was pursuing, you know, marrying
the princess and becoming king and getting his kingdom and all that, he
never really like, betrayed guts in any serious way until he, you know, like the
eclipse happened.
And like, obviously that's, you know, that pretty much sums up his feelings
right there.
Like these people were his tools, but Berserk, he was nice to them and treated
them well because he needed them.
That's right.
And it's a complicated thing, but yes, it is very interesting.
I think that Griffith did show himself at the very least, not a true friend to
those individuals.
No kidding.
Yes, that's my, uh, that's, that's my deep, that's my deep analysis of that
situation.
Yes.
I'm just like, those guys are okay.
Those people, if they were, if they were like hot 10 out of 10s, you know,
they'd be banging cosplay sluts that wouldn't be hanging out and making this
commercial for Sakura con, like a bunch of bullshit.
That's their angle, man.
That's their angle in life to hang around Vic Minyana, make these terrible
commercials and go to soccer God every year.
My one, the one ambition.
Um, okay.
Let's, let's move on to another one.
Ben, do you have a story for us?
Um, worthless friend of yours.
I remember one that involves you actually.
Wait, give me a hint because I'm thinking of one.
I just, I remember a vague story about when you used to ride the bus with a
kid and he, you seem to be really have fun with him.
But then when the other people were around, he would, he would be mean.
He'd be mean.
He proved that he didn't actually like you.
I, you know, I actually don't remember that story.
I think you might be thinking of someone else.
No, the, the guy, okay.
So I have a guy, he, I don't think he's not worthless.
Like I actually like him in a lot of ways and like I'd still consider him a
friend, but he did prove to be troublesome.
Like not just to me, but to other people.
This was like God, like maybe a year and a half ago before I moved in with
Digi, I was living, I was living in this place in Medford, which is near
Boston.
It was called Monkey House.
And Monk, yeah, we call it Monk.
We were, we were this, yeah, we were this, we were six, six little Monkeys
living in a house and jumping on the bed.
We, we, it won't tell off and call the doctor and the doctor said, no more
Monkeys.
Oh yeah, I've been there.
Actually, I think, I think like to, like the first day at Monkey House, we all
like jumped on a bed together, you know, to seal a rhyme, teach you nothing.
Oh God, we didn't, yeah, we really didn't think that went through, did we?
But, uh,
You could have bonked your head on the floor, dude.
So, so Monkey House was a collaborative effort.
Basically, there was, we knew, we knew this guy.
I'll just say his name.
His name, his name is, uh,
Say his first name.
Vic Mannyana.
I'll hide his name.
Let's say his name's Carl.
Um, so Carl, uh, like he had, he was friends with me and another guy locally.
And then he had a couple of other friends from like these internet forums that
they hung out on and talked about and like it came to pass.
Well, see when I first knew Carl, I thought he was like a real ironic
hipster kind of guy and he'd make all these funny like, ha ha.
Um, um, you know, sure, I'm suspicious of the Jews.
Ha ha.
You know, not, not necessarily criticizing Middle Eastern genocide or anything.
I'm just saying maybe there are good reasons for it, stuff like that.
I thought it was a joke.
It turned out not really, not entirely.
And a bunch of, so a bunch of the, these other guys that he brought in and literally
the experience I had with Paul, I really thought he had the exact same arc.
I feel like Paul was like genetically engineered out of like one of his hair,
lots of hair that created pull out of that guy.
I don't, I don't mean to, I don't mean to diminish this guy or like throw
his, all of everything he thinks under a blanket statement and like make sweeping
generalizations because I talked to him a lot and he had a lot of knowledge and
he had a lot of really complicated opinions that were not just simply, oh,
I hate Muslims or whatever.
But you know, he was a little, him and his friends prove to be, if not alt right,
maybe kind of alt right adjacent.
So, so that was troubling.
So alt tab right.
Yeah.
Um, but I got something bad to tell you, bed.
Well, so bad news, but that wasn't, but that wasn't really the problem.
The problem was that like to get all these guys together, like he basically
just said like, I have a house, I have a bunch of people moving in.
Do you want to split the rent?
And I was like, sure.
And I moved in.
But like after we'd been there for months, it came out and I hadn't realized
this, that Carl had like, Carl had really like fucked the other guys over
because he had told them that the house was there and we had it and we had like
made the down payment only for them to like fly here from across the country
and arrive to find that the payment had not been made and that he needed more
money from them immediately on the spot.
Like, yeah, to pay the down payment on the place to pay first month's rent
or else there'd be no place that they could live.
So they basically had no choice but to lend him money right then and there
or they'd be homeless, uh, which they did.
And then for months, he kept telling them like, oh, I'm going to pay you back.
I'm going to pay you back.
But he didn't work like his, his dad owned a little print shop and his dad
would have let him work in the shop to make money anytime he wanted.
But he frequently didn't.
He would just kind of sit around, say he was doing things when he wasn't.
Um, he would, the final.
Oh, I remember this guy now.
The final fucking straw came when we were like, Carl, this month we cannot
be laid on rent again because we'll be kicked out.
Like, do we'll just, just, just level with us.
Will you have it?
Yes.
Like days before Carl.
Okay.
We're serious.
Like we really need it on the day.
Just, just be straight with us.
We're not going to be mad.
Are you going to have the money on time?
Yes.
And of course the day comes and goes and no, he doesn't have it.
And we're all like, shit, we've got to cover his part.
So we fucking me and some of the other guys went up and who grabbed
all his stuff and gathered it together and put it in the living room.
And he came home that day.
And, and, um, one, this other guy, Matt was like, Carl, Carl walks in
the door and Matt's just like, Carl, welcome home.
Now get the fuck out of here.
And we just turned him around and sent him away.
Um, and it was sad, um, but he richly deserved it.
I think that is sad.
I think that's the exact kind of worthless friend story I was hoping to hear.
That's exactly right.
He, um, yeah, he, he, he, he dragged his feet about paying those guys back.
I think that later he eventually did.
Um, I don't know how, but I think benevolent of him.
Yeah.
I think it came like after much conversation with everyone involved.
My theory was that he was hoping to just get himself in so much debt
and like fuck him, his own situation to such an extent that it would be
so hopeless that some like rich guy that they knew on these forums
that they hung out with would just like throw him a bone and be like,
here, I'll cover your debts for you.
Um, but it didn't happen.
Interesting strategy.
Yeah.
Um, but it didn't happen.
You forgot to be a hot girl portion of that.
Yeah.
You were like, yeah, I think this guy had gotten, I think the guy had like
had like spotted him before.
Like I think he'd this was, yeah.
Carl is the kind of guy who kind of gets by on pity a lot of the time
and will like spin a sad story to get people to like give him stuff
and to like forgive transgressions and forgive deaths and things.
That's just no way to run your life.
You know, it's just no way to run your life.
My question is, why does he have to actually go into debt?
Why can't he just tell the guy online?
Hey, I'm in debt.
Get the, give me the money.
You know, um, I don't know.
Maybe he probably just fucking lie.
It's the internet.
But I guess I don't think he's lying.
Well, maybe I'm thinking maybe because the other guys would be able
to corroborate the story.
Like, yeah, Carl owes me all this money and he can't pay it back.
So more importantly, his conscious mind will be able to corroborate the story.
Like, you know, there's a big difference between like people who lie
and they know they're lying versus the guy that you're describing then.
If you know what I mean, like it seems like a person who lies to
themselves enough that they can sufficiently mental gymnast their way
up to the top of the trapeze, but they can't ascend outside of the entire
fucking circus into the heavens just on mental gymnastics alone.
They just, they just can't break that glass ceiling to get beyond to the,
to the freedom above.
I, I want to say that like this guy never fucked me personally over
like that.
So I don't have any like personal beef with him and like I do like him
and think he's pretty fun to hang out with and he's, he's, he's not worth
always are.
Yeah, but he really did, but he really did, he really did fuck these guys
over in the, under the guise of friendship and it really sucked.
No one, no one is truly worthless, but, but we're here to make sweeping
generalizations about people's character that we know.
So it's understood.
It's understood.
Yeah.
So yeah, that's, that's the tale of Carl.
I have a short one actually.
I realized I actually have two stories.
Okay.
So I actually, I actually don't have any that are actually my friends.
I just have two ones that I experienced adjacently through someone else.
Right.
I have no tolerance for shitty people.
I, I like for me, the definition of liking someone is that they like me.
Uh, that's not, you can't just get me to like you by liking me, but that's
like 80% of it to be completely honest.
Like if you like me, then you're probably the kind of person I want to
hang out with.
If you don't like me, if you don't value me, I don't value you for the most
part, but you like me to do.
How do you explain that?
Hello.
Well, got him.
Oh, I like you to do.
Yeah.
Let's fuck.
So anyway, okay.
So what would you want?
So this one is from childhood, right?
This is my brother.
You know, my brother's a more sociable person.
He's a, he's very much that, um, he's, he's sort of a, uh, chivalrous, uh, outdoorsman
kind of guy or at least he was.
Now the Dora tipper of the highest.
No, well, no, he's never, he used to be into like, you know, tennis and BB guns.
Like the entire bird population of our yard was eliminated within us, within a
summer, which is great.
There was no more poop anywhere.
And now he's into like fucking actually now he's into ballet, which is really
cool because he's the only guy sick.
He's the only guy.
So was I when I was a kid?
Yeah.
He's just having guns to ballet.
It seems like two completely.
Yeah.
You watch, you watch a little anime called princess to hell.
Hell yeah.
You do the pendulum.
The pendulum always swings in the other direction.
Yeah.
Well, it's like the fucking heterosexualist thing you could ever do because
he just goes around grabbing the shit out of girls and touching them.
And that's right.
He's like, yeah, it's pretty cool.
He even got like, so actually he's doing ballet class.
He's like in the class.
It's like this fucking like don't it's like this fucking Christian thing though,
which makes it a lot less dope.
No, but you know, I don't know how he's because like he got into it because our
youngest sister has been into dance since she was like four.
And I guess my brother was just like, I guess I'll try it too.
And now that he's the only guy, let alone like a six foot really strong guy.
He got sent like to a trip to Israel because they were going to do some like
performances there for like a whole month.
And they're like, well, we need someone to pick them up for the whole picky upie
parts of the ballet.
So he got to go to Israel for it.
And he gave me, he came back with a freaking wallet with a really badly done
rendition of the Pink Floyd album with the light coming out of the other side
as the rainbow.
It's really shittling.
Yeah, Dark Side of the Moon.
Now it's my wallet.
Anyway, that's the kind of man this is, right?
So he's the kind of man who will trust you even if I don't know if it's
necessarily worth it.
So we were kids and he was like 11.
My brother's name is Aaron.
This kid's name, I think his name was Josh.
I don't remember.
And he was just a kind of like charming attractive manipulator kind of guy who
would just keep fucking you over and keep lying to you, you know, the stakes
weren't that high because we're all 11 here.
But you know, you know how it is.
And the thing that was, yeah, his whole upbringing is, you know, single mom fucking
will do drugs, someone gets shot or whatever.
We didn't live in a great neighborhood.
We lived a few streets away from where, you know, there was like literally a tree
growing into someone's wall and they never fixed it for some reason.
That part of neighborhood is where Josh was from.
And the thing that was really notable to me, I remember specifically
he fucked over my brother seven times.
I specifically counted the number of times he lied to him and like Aaron, how
long are you going to keep trusting him?
But the most notable thing Aaron's Aaron's got to forgive him until he fucks
him over 70 times, seven times.
Yeah.
And like, and the weirdest thing is that Josh had so many mannerisms that reminded
me not to get political, but reminded me of Bill Clinton like astonishingly.
He had like the same smile, the same demeanor, despite being like,
he fucked a lot of secretaries.
Probably has by now.
He's Sonic the Hedgehog.
Oh, he's probably, oh, he's probably a snap and get a pussy kind of guy at this
point, I imagine.
Right.
Okay.
I believe he went to Julia.
He looks down.
He just looks down his penis.
He snaps.
He's got a pussy.
Oh, yeah.
He's really excellent.
He's like, you know, really charming and attractive and skinny and like got that
like boyish charm.
Is his wife un-electable?
Yes.
So yeah.
Well, that doesn't sound like Bill Clinton at all.
It was just a really interesting thing to me at the time because I was probably
like 13 or 14 or whatever, you know, and like, so I kind of like knew what Bill
Clinton was, you know, I'm not that fucking young.
And yeah, I guess that's really all there is to say about that.
So.
So wait, what were the seven ways that he's fucked?
I don't remember.
It was all a bunch of dumb, you know, preteen bullshit, but it wasn't anything
too big, just like, I actually don't remember at all.
So I'm not even trying.
Okay.
All right.
We throw this man out of the bus.
Fuck that guy.
I condemn him to death.
Oh, I remembered one short one as well.
Oh, actually, but before you say it, I just want to say that, you know, Josh, I never
thought that it'd be so simple, but I found a way.
I found a way.
Oh, there it is.
It's going to take you time to realize.
But if you realize that actually I found out over your shoulder, you're not real
find out.
I'm always picking you up when you're down.
I was, I was really glad to see your brother.
I was really happy.
Your brother, Aaron Drake, Davoo finally made up with Josh recently.
That's my last name.
The is my first name.
It is.
It is for this joke.
Baby boy.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Mage, what do you got for us?
Yeah, it'll be just quick, much like the nerd in the last story.
I don't dislike her at the current state.
It just so happens the way it happened.
Like she, um, we met also when I was very little, even younger than eight.
I think it was a five or six.
Um, and we, we were friends for almost a decade, I think.
And, um, she, maybe the last, uh, she, she kind of was a bit of a liar, but
she didn't do it on, I'd like to see on purpose, but like, I mean, you know,
when you're lying, but it's like, you know, little kids being little kids and
she just wanted to impress.
So she would sometimes make up lies.
And so I can't really hold it against her.
But the thing about her though, um, she would sometimes make really stupid
decisions in her life.
And every time she would come to me and be like, Hey, I want to do this thing
or Hey, I'm going to do this thing.
I would be like, no, that sounds like a bad idea.
You're going to regret this.
And she never listened to me and she got in trouble and then she would come
back to me and be like, I should have listened to you and it would repeat
for many, many years for many, many occasions.
She never listened to me despite, you know, admitting that post fact she
had, she should have listened to me.
The very last thing she didn't listen to me.
A new girl sort of moved in into the neighborhood.
We were sort of neighbors in the same neighborhood.
And I could tell she was trouble.
She was the kind of like, you know, preppy long haired, uh, a bit of a
skanky sort of girl.
And my kind of girl.
I think the words right out of my fucking mouth.
14 at the time.
I Oh, that's really my kind of girl.
Oh, we go.
Skanky 13 year old.
Can I move to what Lithuania?
Where the fuck do you live?
But basically she moved in and she, she was very much like a drama whore.
I think like we've never dealt with the sort of person, but I knew she was
troubled in the moment.
I met her.
I did give her a chance, but just from interacting with her, I knew that,
you know, she's going to lead people down the wrong path.
And, um, my friend sort of got friends with her and I was like, don't
become good friends with her.
She's like, you know, stay cautious, please be mindful because, you
know, she's probably going to get you into like alcohol and smoking and
maybe even drugs.
Who knows?
Like I knew, I knew she was going to be like that because we were living in
a not the best neighborhood.
Let me tell you, uh, a lot, lots of drug people.
Like surprisingly, I kept hearing stories about people using drugs and
like other stuff, like all these spooky stories in our neighborhood.
And I never met any person that actually did that.
I was like, where are these stories come from?
Cause they, cause they, cause they knew that you were beaten up boys with
your Dragon Ball Z moves and they knew to stay away from them.
Did I tell you that story?
Uh, should I not have said that?
Was that told?
No, I'm just, I'm just surprised.
I was beating the people with Dragon Ball Z moves.
Yeah.
Okay.
Are we talking like spirit bomb or like, or like, punch or punching?
We punched each other and it was, it was, that's how we played.
Like when I was little, our games was like, we would punch each other
until it would hurt and that was fun.
But we were playing Dragon Ball Z.
So it was okay.
So is this, is this person, someone who never really became a close friend,
but was like a fake friend or was just a friend of low caliber?
She was like quite a close friend to her.
I was her best.
And sometimes on some occasions, even the only friend she had.
Okay.
So we were really, really close friends.
And yeah, I told her not to get close to her because I knew she
was going to be trouble.
And the same like the nerd guy, you know, she exchanged me for that girl
and we never talked again.
Just kind of like, trade it up.
Yeah.
Trade it up.
Can't, can't say I heard stories about her and not very good ones
about how she, when like she, she, she, the thing is though, like,
I don't want to like, you know, stereotype or whatever, but this is
a story that was quite common in, in Lithuania at that time, considering
the time we lived in, like a lot of broken families and stuff like that.
She, she, she came from a very poor and a broken family and her chances
of like, you know, getting a good life were pretty low in comparison.
And, but everything changed upon the election of Donald Trump.
But yeah, but yeah, she, and yeah, so like, I really, I really wanted
to try and, you know, leave her on, on, on the good path and just, just
like to, to give her a chance to like, not, not fall down.
This is the same rabbit hole her mom fell down as it seemed the history
repeated herself with her.
So I'm sad.
I did, I did the basic, you know, if she doesn't want to be your fault made.
Yeah.
She didn't want to be my friend anymore and she wanted to hang up with
the skanky girl.
So, you know, yeah, for me, it's like, if there's any person
who I'm getting into some sort of affiliation with and I recognize
some major problem and the only, the only way I'm going to have
a long-term affiliation with them is if that problem is rectified or
addressed, this individual has the social equivalent of a five second
span to prove that they are self-aware, self-deprecating about
that issue and are willing on some level to deal with that problem.
And if they do not demonstrate that self-awareness, that, that courage
of the self to challenge themselves, then I'm like, all right, bye.
You know, like I have a very short, very short patience for people
who are not willing to address themselves and a pretty long patience
for people who are like people who will like regularly with absolute
genuineness say sorry and they don't do the same thing a second time.
Like they're really showing a, a, a statistical improvement chart,
you know.
Oh, I just remembered this friend also got me into some pretty deep
shit, but that's a story for another podcast, I guess.
Oh, okay.
If you say so.
Yeah.
For those of you who cast.
I have a story.
This one is actually about, it's about me being a shitty friend.
It's about me being the worthless friend.
The plot twist.
Wait, is that going to be the subject?
Cause I mean, I, that kind of needs its own episode with just me for
about seven hours.
I mean, well, that's fine.
I, I really only have this one story because I really don't have
any experience of a friend, uh, proving to be shitty or worthless.
I've got some that are like minor things.
Like they just started being boring.
So I didn't.
Hey, I'm sure you've got some minor things.
Hell yeah, Nate.
High taste boys.
We got, we're very fucking selective.
That's how, that's how it should be done.
I discard what is worthless to me, which is everyone I've ever known.
Yeah, basically.
And you all will be too in time.
I look forward to it immensely.
But let me tell you about the time where I was a terrible friend.
Um, so, yeah, this is basically worthless, I suppose.
So, um, a friend of mine got married two years ago.
And maybe I've told the story before, but I don't think I have on here.
So two years ago, a friend of mine got married.
So I fly back to Massachusetts for the wedding.
I haven't been there in a while.
And, uh, so I'm at the wedding.
It's a good time.
All my old friends are there from school.
It's, it's absolutely fantastic.
Um, and I, uh, my, my one friend brings a date and this date is like,
I've seen her several times before when we've been hanging out.
They'd known each other for a while and she, uh, was clearly friend zoning
this guy really hard, really hard.
And, uh, she, man, she just turned it on for me, man.
What can I say?
She just turned on all the signals, uh, the, the, the touch and the extended
eye contact, laughing at jokes that I was not even attempting to make.
And what could I do?
Uh, you know, what can a man do in this kind of situation?
So, uh, the extent of it was we, we kissed at the wedding for a while.
Uh, yeah, I, I, I, and I don't want to glorify this.
This was a very bad thing I was doing.
I was simply, this is an excuse, but I had not gotten late in quite a while.
So I was just like, finally, finally an opportunity presents 22 years.
Here we go.
No, no, uh, more recent than that.
But anyway, um, yeah.
So what can I say, man?
I just, I just made out with my friend's date.
Uh, they had, like they were not dating.
I was, I was in my drunken way.
I was like asking her like, so are you guys like an item?
Like, is this okay?
What are we doing right now?
She was like, oh yeah, it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Little did I know, uh, this was, I mean, certainly not in his mind.
You know, I just, my judgment was way fucked up.
I totally was a bad person, uh, regret it deeply.
I don't think you did anything wrong.
I mean, that woman is her own being.
If she's not into that guy and she's into you, like, why would you, like, he'd
be fucking you over if you weren't allowed to make out with that hot shit?
You know what?
I am perfectly willing to say that from a, from a basically like moral
standpoint, like no, no contract has really been violated in this situation,
but simply from the perspective of like being 100, as cool as possible to
your friend, this was not 100% cool to my friend, you know?
So on, on that scale, you know, since we're talking about friendship specifically,
this is not the best way to maintain a friendship, you know?
No, probably not.
Probably a pretty poor way to do that.
Exactly, exactly.
And, uh, I regret it deeply.
If you're listening to this friend, I apologize sincerely.
I regret it all the time.
He's, he's definitely not listening, but in any case, I am very sorry.
I will not do it again.
I've learned my lesson.
That's it.
That's, that's, that's all I got.
Really?
That's all I got.
Well, I'm going to have to one up all of you because I've got the most worthless
friend of all time and you guys are going to, your jobs are going to drop.
Hope you guys are ready.
Hope you're all sitting down because this story is going to
revolutionize the PCB podcast as we know it.
Fuck yeah.
Not too long ago, I had a decently good friend of mine and we decided, you know
what, we're going to start a podcast together.
That'd be real good.
And, uh, you know, let's try to do this consistently.
Let's, let's work together.
No.
And, uh, you know, we decided the podcast would be reviewing each Naruto panel
one at a time.
Oh, that's a good idea.
That's a good idea for a show.
We thought it was a good one.
Yeah.
So we did the first one.
It's a huge shit, probably the most popular channel on video on that channel
at the time, but then the friend just like disappeared.
She like disappeared like to some fucking Middle Eastern, uh, European
country with like no microphone.
And I didn't hear from her for like three or four months.
Like what the fuck goes on a vacation without a microphone.
Hang it.
She left you hanging like that.
What the fuck worthless.
I say how dare she horrible.
I'd be pretty.
I'll never know what happens on our toe page too.
Now.
Max revive the Nauru casket.
You're, you're attacking the wrong source here because like the ultimate
problem is the lack of abundant fucking microphones in all the places.
Like I'm all about.
I'm all about UBB universal basic blue yeti and like everyone should be
entitled to one at all times or else like life cannot function.
We end up with all these fucking, you know, fan dubs and review collaborations
or even interviews with some celebrity who's currently at his house that
always has half shit audio.
This is a big issue that needs to be saved for the everyone is shit.
But if Bernie, if Bernie had just pushed the UBB platform during the
primary, God damn it, everything would have been different.
Fucking Hillary was going with that snowball mic and everybody ate that
shit up.
Yeah, I know, right?
Oh, I used to have a snowball mic and I would take it along for journeys,
but I would get stopped every single time at the airport because of it.
So because of these minor moments of inconvenience, that is worth, uh,
it's worth ruining your, your lucrative.
No, the microphone broke.
So I got a new one, but this one is an XLR and it plugs into, um,
what's it called those mixer thingies audio mixing?
Yeah.
So like I can't take the microphone, the microstand, the mixie thingie
and all the wires all with me with just one little bag thingie where I have
to make excuses.
Yeah.
I mean, this seems irrelevant.
I wasn't talking about you.
I don't know why you're bringing up your way.
We're talking about microphones and I mentioned my microphone problems.
Fair enough.
Unrelated microphone.
I should make it like a public thing.
Maybe, maybe this other mystery person suffered from the same problem.
We should, we should, we should have, we should, we should extend her the
benefit of the doubt wherever she is.
I don't know, Ben.
I'm ready to bury her into the fucking prison.
Yeah.
I'm ready to throw away the key.
You know, Nate, when I needed a microphone help, you sent me like an
Amazon wish list of all the things to get.
Like you should publish that shit publicly.
I was just saying that.
I was just about to say that.
Yeah.
Like we should make that public the like the PCP standard good audio set.
It's like probably like 500 bucks total or something.
Can't anybody get on Amazon and like do an affiliate program thing.
So if people buy things that we link them to, we get some of the money.
You have to have like a partnership with Amazon in order to do that first or
something.
So like you'd have to like talk to those guys.
I think, pretty sure.
Listeners.
My audio set is about 200.
It's a $99 SM58, sure SM58, which is like the AK-47 of microphones.
It's the most famous one.
Then they have an M audio M track, which is $100.
There might be better ones, but it's really simple.
Doesn't have that much extraneous shit.
I don't use.
So if you find my audio quality perfectly fine, then do that.
Mike, you're being really shit friends by derelling this podcast about shit
friends right now.
Wait.
Okay.
Mage, if you want to finish, go ahead and finish your plate.
I'm sorry.
No, I just said my microphone was like 20 bucks.
So if you like this, Ben and I, Ben and I made world famous channel,
YouTube channel, TBAP we using $130 microphone for like years and Ben still
use it on the PCP for a long time and might be using it right now.
Are you still using that?
Mike, Ben?
No, I'm using a blue yeti right now.
Although I still have that one lying around somewhere.
Yeah.
Use champion.
It's a champion.
Yeah.
The thing is like 99% of audience members don't even notice like slight differences
in audio quality.
See, that's true.
The thing is using that using that piece of shit microphone.
I never noticed a problem because I was listening to it.
This was back when I had my laptop.
I was listening to the podcast on my laptop speakers through laptop headphones
and it was only when Digi told pulled me aside and was like,
Ben, this has to stop.
And I was like, what are you talking about?
Dude, it's fine.
And then he brought me up to his fucking room and played it to me on legit
speakers and suddenly I was like, oh my God, I sound so much tinier than everyone else.
Like the difference is palpable and like, what have I done?
What have I done?
I was a real shit friend of the podcast back in those days.
It's true.
It's very true.
The people need to be educated on audio quality so that they'll buy our
fucking affiliate like microphones or something.
Yeah.
But I did.
Why don't you save yourself a week and do it?
Why am I genius weekly on fucking microphone shit?
Like that'd be easiest shit.
Not a terrible idea.
Not I remember I put like into one of my, I think it's like that last day of me
and Mavva, I like just for a second.
I was like, this is why I have to like take all this time to fix the audio
because like, and then I cut to this is what I sound like from the camera
microphone and it's just like an ear raping like, you know, camera mic.
I didn't even edit.
It just sounds like that.
But that'd be fun.
That's not a bad idea.
It would be like super helpful, especially if you showed how to connect
everything because I spent about three hours trying to figure it out.
I could put together the Amazon wish list and make it a whole big thing.
That's not a bad idea.
There you go.
Very interesting.
Okay.
Back on the friendship thing.
Yeah.
Anyone else have a story?
I mean, I have a bigger story actually.
That's like someone who is my friend, but like just it didn't end up being like
quite worth it enough where it's like, it's someone who gives very little
and takes more, you know, it's like someone who is very emotionally
like in need of people, but he's already like, the reason why I didn't feel bad
about going into a, oh, sorry, it's been two weeks since I responded to your
message mode with him is because he has other friends.
So it's like, he doesn't need me necessarily, you know, it's just
and even if he did have friends, does that mean he's entitled to your time?
And it's just ultimately it's because he's like gone to college for like different
art mediums and yet his art medium ability is like, like his drawing ability
is I'd say at least in half order of magnitude worse than me.
And it's like, if you went to college and you're worse than me, then I don't
and you're like four years older than me.
Then it's like, uh, you're just, I don't know how many.
I'm pretty sure most of the PCP have the same standard of me of like,
if the main thing that I connect with you over is art, but you are a really
bad artist, then you're not that valuable as a person.
It's, you know, Davoo, I got to admit it.
Now's a good time to launch into a portion of what I want to discuss with
this, and that is the idea that like you owe your friends something that
your friends are like owed you your time or your energy in some way.
I completely reject that idea.
And I think friends are only valuable to me in the sense that they
continue to be actually valuable to me and are a worthwhile usage of my
time in some way.
And the second that someone isn't, they can still call him your friend.
You can have a history or whatever, but there's no point in staying involved
with their lives or wasting your energy and time on maintaining that kind
of relationship.
Yeah, it's all about whether or not it's worth it or not.
Yeah, like, yeah, and like, there's no reason to like let an old friend
like completely die out from your life.
Like I've got friends from back home that I have almost nothing in common
with at this point, but occasionally I might message them and just be like,
yo, what's up?
Because those people have something of value.
They have my histories in them and my old relationships and there's no
reason to discard them.
But like if I have a shitty friend who I barely knew from back in high
school who messages me as has happened and it's like, yo, dude, what's
going on?
Let's catch up.
I'm like, don't ever speak to me again.
You have nothing of value to offer me.
Stop.
You are, you are, this is an act of violence.
You're perpetuating against me by wasting my time.
You are stealing my time from me by sending you this message and I
raping me, forcing me to read it.
Never do this again.
That's violence.
I'm gonna go your fucking safe.
Your Nate space.
Yes.
That's right.
I need to go to my Nate space.
Is it just like anime posters and a Hillary Clinton cut out and that's the
Nate space and power bars and like cans of beans in a just like
cans of beans.
Do you know how fucking safe spaces on campus like official ones are like
they're filled like videos with like puppies and flowers and like coloring
books and shit.
Yeah.
Mine is just like a streaming girl and log in on like 10 TVs across.
You've got your Hillary cutouts.
You've got your copies of what happened lining a shelf.
Everything you need, everything you need to mentally re-energize yourself.
Trigger you even more.
Wouldn't you rather read it takes a village?
No, it's a brilliant alt reality story from the mind of a genius author.
Hillary Clinton.
Someone else comes into your Nate space and they grab your girl and gone
coloring book and you're like hey, but they grabbed the orange marker for
Oh my God.
We have to delete all orange crayons cannot be allowed.
Send them all to the gulags.
They can't be allowed anymore.
Oh my God.
What a what a journey we've just taken.
We need to decide what everybody's safe space would look like.
I agree.
That should be its own episode.
I mean, Ben's safe space is just your local dumpster up behind you.
You know, just hop in.
Let's do this for a bonus episode someday.
Let's not ruin it.
That's a good idea.
Okay.
We'll get all nine of us in there at the same time and just fucking go him.
But to finish my point from before, he was just when I think about friends,
I honestly, maybe this is a bad sign, but I think about it the same way that
Griffith articulates it in his speech.
It just before he did anything bad or, you know, really bad.
He didn't write about some things.
Griffith was definitely right about some things, which is why there's such a
hot debate about him to this day and his speech that guts over here is about
like how his friends are the ones that keep up with him.
You know, they're his peers.
They're not the people who just like, you know, I mean, he frames us like like
not even parasites, but like his loyal soldiers are not his friends.
His friends are the people with with their own ambition and their own drive
in life because because like this is the thing.
Nobody wants to talk about followers in this world really do drain the energy
of the leaders that guide them through this world.
Like like employ everyone.
The fucking Democrats, for example, just want to like frame workers as like
these these virtuous like, you know, plebeian citizens of this great world
that offer so much value to their leaders, but without those leaders,
those people wouldn't have fucking jobs and wouldn't have fucking shit.
And the whole economy is floated up by these, you know, people at the top
orchestrating it to be so and a rising tide lifts all boats.
I know I'm speaking in some generalities here, but I really do think about
about like friendships that way.
And if someone is not worth my time spent on you, it's no insult to you.
I just don't want to waste my time, which is why I fucking get messages on discord.
People in my fan chat and shit.
Stop wasting my time.
I don't give a fuck about you.
Tweet at me or something that at least wastes less of my time.
But there you go.
Here's a story about why your friends are not.
Yeah, it's about not owing friends things.
And it's also about why working with your friends is not always a great idea.
See, it's not always.
Don't you mean not ever?
Holy shit.
Well, it's up there.
I mean, me and Nate work together on T-Bap and that ended up working out fine.
So it can work.
It was a struggle, but you did work out.
You both proved to be true people, not friends.
You proved to be actual artists in the East.
I'm prepared to frame us as the rare few.
I'm prepared to do that, to be that virtuous.
Well, let me tell you about something, a disappointing tale from my life.
I have a friend, I still have this friend.
And like years ago, this guy, he, well, he wanted to make video games.
And we were really into, we were really into roguelikes.
Who is that you?
Um, we were, we were really into roguelikes at the time.
And like he said, like I'm going to make like a simple roguelike game.
And I was like, you know, okay, like you're serious.
This is a guy who's serious about like computer science and computers and video
gaming and stuff.
And like, I believe in this guy.
I believe that he's going to follow through on this.
So I agreed to help and I did a bunch of work.
I did a bunch of work on this project.
I made like a ton of like really nice sprites and I made like this sick animated
intro screen for it.
Oh, damn.
I remember like on the plane to Poland, I was like on the plane.
I had my laptop open and I was drawing monster sprites and I was really proud of
a lot of them.
I was drawing like floor tiles and stuff.
I was really putting the energy in to like make the floor.
I remember I was drawing vine floor tiles and I had to draw them in such a way
that they could connect and be continuous.
Like if you were walking on like a viney jungle.
Oh, yeah, I've gotten.
Oh, I love.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Fuck.
So long story short, the game never happened.
And so yeah, he didn't.
He didn't make the thing and like I don't hold it against the guy.
Like I don't.
He's not a worthless friend.
I don't hate him or anything for it.
But looking back, I'm like, I kind of wish that I had done less for a friend at
that point because he hadn't like proved.
He hadn't like proved that he was willing to follow through on it in order to make
my investment.
Oh, I feel like if being if being a over promising, under delivering in their art
was a deal breaker for friendship, I would have no friends.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's something that everybody does like something that everybody does
and you like you shouldn't.
Well, I would say it doesn't make them a bad person or a bad friend.
Like it just you have to you have to be responsible.
Yeah, you have to take the responsibility of being like I'm not I'm not going to
commit to this thing.
Yeah, I can I can smell the not that serious coming from people a mile away.
There's always ulterior motives.
There's very few people who want to do art just for art like when my brother
does projects with me, it's because he wants to do something with me, which is
also a motivation for me as well.
But it's like at some point or another, the art becomes we work in separate
different little sections.
We're not like locking arms 24 seven.
And when he realizes that it's like he loses interest.
And it's like, all right, you know, it's you know, it's fascinating about this
to me. I really feel like I mean, we probably all have this story, but I
have taken the journey from that guy to the guy I am now.
And a lot of it really was not to give myself too much credit was just like
figuring out what it is that I actually want to do and what makes me happy to
be working on because, you know, I've talked about this before, like I went
to school for programming and like I got a minor in sort of the game design
equivalent at my school and you know, that's complete.
I have my degree in it and I was in the like the game development club that
I helped start at that school.
You know, my other guy really was the champion.
But I was like the secretary or treasure or something and like we would
get together.
We had a team of people who were like willing to do it.
And I was like the project leader on the we did a game jam.
We made like a demo that it was my idea and it was it was good, but it
didn't get finished.
So like afterward at the the game development, I'm sorry, in the game
club, like I pitch like, Hey guys, let's remake this game as an app like as a
mobile game because I think it really works for it and would be really
great and has a lot of, you know, just would work with that, which I think
it would.
It was game called monochrome.
It's called monochrome.
I remember still get it in some places.
Yeah, I had a version on my phone for a while.
So me and a team like we're working on it and developing on it, but the
problem was like, ultimately, the problem was I had like a team of people
who really were willing to put in time to like make it happen.
And we got pretty far along, but at the end of it, like I just wasn't
willing to invest the time to like finally finish the thing and get it done.
You know, we needed to develop like a ton of levels.
We need to do a lot of UI work and stuff.
And I just really didn't have the the conviction to like lead this this
team to finish it.
You know, a lot of it would be me personally programming and stuff.
Um, and so it just, it never got completely finished, which I deeply
regret to this day because I think it was a real winner.
Yeah.
I mean, I used to be that kind of guy.
It's just that it's just that I, I, I wasn't like on board with that.
Like, uh, one of the reasons that I even was interested in doing videos in
the first place is because the turnaround between deciding to make a video.
I mean, it's ironic that for me, I started making videos that took
me six months to make.
Cause like my, my first thing that I like about it is that a game can take
like years to finish, even like an indie game.
The first game I really made took like a full year to be finished developing.
And, um, like a video can take like a day if it's fast or like a month, you
know, for, for one that takes more work and shit.
And, uh, yeah, like now looking back at myself there, like when I was, when I
was in this mode, man, I used to like be terrified of myself like, oh my God,
I'm so worthless.
I'm never going to have the conviction to like actually get the things done in
my life that I want to do.
And now that I sit here where I am having accomplished the things I have
and you know, with a long way to go, I just like, I finally did it.
I finally figured it the fuck out and to waste your time working with friends
who are, who are like me as I used to be is not only hurting yourself and
your own time, but is hurting them because it does not help to just give
these people more things.
They have to work for it and figure out themselves, what motivates them and
possibly more importantly, what avenues they are interested in pursuing.
Cause the personal drive factor is so essential, at least in my experience
to actually motivating you to do the fucking work and accomplish the things
you want to accomplish.
Yeah.
I was like, there you go.
And that I was just, I think I was almost always doing some stupid
shitty art thing.
I was just flip flopping constantly and never getting anything done.
I always, yeah, exactly what you said.
And then it was just simply a matter of being forced to work a regular job
that like just, I'm sure I've described this a million times across different
podcasts, but there was just some sort of snowball at the top of my head
that needed to be pushed and then it was rolled.
And now I've been great ever since.
I like, I started making a video game very quickly realized I didn't
know what I was doing, but I was like, no, no, I am going to finish this.
I ended up only finishing one half of it.
Like the first half of the game is fully playable.
Glitchy as fuck, not very good.
You barely see what you're doing, but I just pushed through every day.
I had no fun for it, very little passion for it.
I just kept doing it and now I'm fucking reliable and it's great.
And then the whole, no, recently I squared away the whole actually
trying to be good aspect of art, which I think I might be doing.
So, and you know what's essential to this whole process, self-betterment
and the desire to improve your own station, which is why I want to
say to all our antifa listeners out there, and I know they're the vast majority.
Communism guys is not going to work.
It's not going to fucking work.
People have to motivate themselves by their own betterment.
You can't work for a collective good.
It just doesn't fucking work.
Someone should make a video about communism, you know, that's if only
some hero would step forward and it should be like the parody of a really
old, like 15 year old show on Nickelodeon.
That'd be really funny, you know, because it's like, I just don't think that
would work. I just don't think that would be called the truth about communism by
Stefan Malinu. Yeah, that'd be good.
I'd watch that. Let's pray for that.
Let's pray for that.
So fucking I'm satisfied with that.
Should we hear mage's big old story now, her finale?
I'm ready for it.
Oh, I got the lube ready.
Don't commit violence against mage like that, monkey.
That's very not acceptable.
Hey, when I play Yu-Gi-Oh, my favorite card is mage power.
Great.
Nerd.
I wish I knew Yu-Gi-Oh enough to laugh more at that.
Okay.
For every spell and trap card, you gain 500 attack points.
Oh my God.
That's pretty good.
Mage being here makes us all strong.
Sounds like a real top tier threat in the OU meta game.
It fucking is.
That card should have flaming a sprite.
If you like that card would be banned if it isn't already.
No, it's not banned.
Really?
Isn't literally every card in Yu-Gi-Oh banned?
No.
Around that area.
Like quite popular cards that were banned.
You don't remember the names.
Reborn the monster was banned because it was too good.
Yeah, and like the Karebo thing knockoff with three eyes.
I think that was banned as well.
What's it face?
I forgot.
Three-eyed Karebo?
As much as I love to go into Yu-Gi-Oh card lore.
Yeah.
Let's hear your story about your shitty friend.
I'm really eager for it.
Yu-Gi-Oh is all about friends.
Okay.
Yeah.
So just first disclaimer.
We had some good times with this person.
She wasn't awful to me all the time.
Otherwise we wouldn't have been friends for like literally a decade.
And I do mean at least decade.
We met when I think I was five or so and our friendship ended
around 16 so more than a decade.
And I still have sort of nightmares with her.
Well, I wouldn't say nightmares, but bad dreams about her.
Okay.
Just arguing with her screaming at each other is just like
she's affected me quite a lot.
I mean, when you know a person for at least 10 years,
they're not going to leave your subconscious anytime soon.
You know?
Sure.
Okay.
So like she was always such a very petty and stubborn person
and she would be like the only friend I would have such big fights with
that we would, you know, it's kind of like this discontinue our friendship
and we're like, oh, we're not friends anymore.
And then like he would take like a week later for one of us to apologize
and become friends again, mostly because like we lived in the same neighborhood.
So like it was kind of hard to play with our friends and not be there together.
So it was just easier on us to be friends again.
I think and for the most part.
Sounds like a healthy basis for a relationship.
We have to be friends.
And for the most part, we, you know, we didn't have fun.
And then we ended up going into the same class as well.
And that's where we meant our best friend.
Like she was best friend to both of us, the one with the brother
that I mentioned in the first story.
And yeah, it's and it was just this free for the longest of times until,
you know, the whole thing happened.
And just to sort of like the things she would deal with the way,
the how petty she got, there was this one argument we had that was never resolved.
I might have told this to a few people.
I'm not sure.
But okay.
So like back in the day before internet was a thing or at least we didn't have it there.
I saw it came out, I think by Jennifer Lopez, like Jenny from the block.
Okay, keep, keep in mind, like English, not, not her first language.
And the fact that I spoke English at that age was a miracle in itself.
And my friend also could speak English, but not as well as me.
So we argued about the lyrics of the song.
And let me, let me tell you how stupid.
Relatable.
Okay.
So like the lyrics were like Jenny from the block.
And that's what I claimed.
You know, she was saying Jenny from the block and she insisted that she said
Jenny from the back as in back from, you know, the past, that sort of term.
And I was like, that does not make sense.
She means Jenny from the block.
But the thing is, I don't think in the opinion we have the term for block or at
least it's, it wasn't a word us little kids at that age would know.
And I tried to explain to her what block meant, but she would have none of it.
And we, we got in such a big fight over it.
We ended our friendship.
I wouldn't have friendship over something like that.
And then like the thing is she ended it because she would have none of it.
And despite everything, this like the only way, the only way we could become friends
again, if we both agreed that one time she sang Jenny from the block and the
other time she said Jenny from the back, that's how she sang the song.
We had to, I knew it was wrong, but that's the only way we had to keep peace.
And even like years later, when we did have internet and I looked up the lyrics
and I showed it to her and I was like, Hey, remember this argument we had?
And she still was like, Oh, well, you know, that's on the internet.
You don't, you can't trust everything that's on the internet.
Are you telling me someone would just go on the internet and tell lies?
I don't fucking believe it.
And it's like she had none of it.
And we never resolved this issue.
She did not want to be wrong.
I think like the way our three, three, um, the three must be tears of us.
The way our friendship worked was like, she was sort of like, you know,
the baddest homeboy leader sort of character.
And that was a bit of a like the comic relief, I guess.
And, you know, leaders don't take shit from the comic relief, you know?
Of course.
And she, she, she would not let me be right.
She never wanted me to be right.
She kept putting me down.
She was always right.
She knew best.
She also mistreated me in ways that I only really recently realized that holy shit.
She kind of really treated mistreated me because like we were both like art people.
We, we draw a lot dare.
I say it was a slightly better than her.
I don't want to use my own horn.
I am serious though.
You know, she had talent of her own, but I think I was just slightly a little,
a few steps ahead of her.
Like also when talking in English as well.
So like, I think one time I sort of said, oh, hey, you know, you didn't draw the nose.
Are you going to put in or is that going to be your style, you know, without the nose?
And it was like, oh, you know, that's how I draw it.
She told me.
And then ever since then, she never really showed me her drawings.
She would show it to every other friend, not me.
She would never let me touch her things.
Like I couldn't touch her pencil, pencil case, backpack, anything of hers.
She would let other people just touch and borrow sometimes even without asking.
I had to specifically ask him.
Sometimes she wouldn't even let me.
This really reminds me of the situation in Clockwork Orange,
where the droogs start to challenge the leader of the droogs.
You know, what's his name?
And he cannot, she cannot stand for this.
You have to be crushed.
You have to be crushed to remain subservient.
That kind of pettiness is something that sounds in line with myself.
Like, yeah, I would probably do that.
I call that strong leadership, my dude.
That's what I'm impressed.
I'm on her.
I'm letting you know I'm on her side right now.
She's a powerful leader.
But I mean, so now I lost my, but yeah, she was very petty.
Um, she would also like take things very personally.
Whenever like, I would do something.
I was, I was, I was a tall clumsy child, by the way.
Sometimes things would drop from my hands and sometimes I would give her a
flat foot just because when we were three, we can all walk in a line.
I had to go, you know, I would fall behind them.
I would follow and sometimes my, my big steps would be too big.
And if they, you know, slow down, I would end up giving her a flat foot, not out of,
not on purpose, but she would, I think she assumed it was out of malice or
something because, because I think the way she thought, you know, like, because
she had some sort of prejudice against me and she wished ill upon me.
She thought I was reciprocating.
I think that's the word, the ill will, but the thing is I was like stupidly
clueless about her ill will at that age.
I, I didn't realize she was mistreating me.
I was like, oh, we're, we're all friends and okay, she has a short temper.
That's fine.
You know, I'll just try not to cross her path or whatever.
But then we got done with this, this summary because it segues really well
into what the main one I want to get to.
So yeah, it's cool.
Okay.
Yeah.
Also, so fast forward until we're teens.
So I got a little rebellious.
I didn't take her shit anymore so much and I would like, you know, have my own
opinion and I would speak, uh, that didn't go well.
And, um, yeah, we, our, our fights would get more frequent and, uh, our common
friend, the best friend, she kind of had to tolerate being in between us
because we, we both like hanging out with her and we refused to let the other
one have her in a way.
Um, and, uh, like at some point, um, my, the best friend, she sort of realized
that, you know, the other one, she was being a bit toxic and she was like, you
know, we should maybe stop hanging out with her so much because, you know,
she's, uh, a bad influence on me.
I was surprised how self aware my friend was and was like, yeah, I think, you
know, it would be kind of for the best in a way if, if we just, you know, just
kind of, you know, stopped because she, she was this other friend who finally
said something and, and initiated the after all the after not really like
let me, let me finish the story.
That's how she, she, we were planning things, but the thing is though, um,
around the, uh, the time, oh, hold on.
One thing, one other petty thing she did at this time when we were around 16.
Okay.
Let, let me, okay.
Just let, let me tell you, like, so I got a locker.
I got a locker for free.
Otherwise you have to pay for lockers, but I got a locker for free because I
was a really poor child and they give like really poor children used lockers.
And so I got one and was like, you know, oh, cool, a locker.
And, um, my friend, she didn't get a locker because, you know, she wasn't
poor enough, I guess.
Um, but I was like, you know, this locker is big for two people.
I could share it with you and, you know, she, and I let her share my locker
with me for free.
And, um, okay.
So like, I was doing a really nice thing.
I think, you know, because we could like put our coats in there and we could go
home together and stuff like that.
It was, you know, would speed things up rather than going to the, you know,
public place where you put coats in and whatever.
Anywho.
So, um, we also went to this after school activity, like art club.
It didn't teach you art.
You just like kind of hang out there and be friends and you do artsy things.
And the teacher was really cool.
And we each like got our own desks.
Um, and the desks were like really old desks, um, that we're probably going to
be like thrown out if they weren't reused.
And like we could just like have fun with those desks.
We could paint all over those decks, whatever we wanted.
And that was really cool.
Mine was a very edgy red and black one.
Oh, a little Nazi propaganda on there.
No, no, there was no white nose.
The colors of the Nazi flag.
Well, I just fucked it up.
As you can see, clearly I'm not, I wasn't tearing you down.
I was holding her up for knowing it.
Oh yeah.
You're right.
Yeah.
So, um, the thing she did, I, and I know it was her because no one else
disliked me that much at the time.
I would think, uh, and, um, I couldn't hang out at the after school activities
so much at that time.
Um, it was the time I went to the, like the international
vocabulary program again.
So, you know, it's tell lots of homework, whatnot.
Um, so like I would often come back to like trash on my left on my desk,
usually like from snacks or like, uh, like an empty cup from like, um,
those, uh, machines that you get, like coffee or hot chocolate.
Right.
And I knew it was her because I would sometimes see her by these,
uh, these, these specific items that would be left on my table.
So one time I decided to just take all of those things and put it
on her desk and see how she would react because it's her trash.
Um, technically I'm not doing a very bad thing here.
I'm just returning the trash where it belongs.
Um, then the next.
You're committing the worst sin imaginable major, performing
disrespect against your leader.
We'll see how that goes.
And then, then the next day after that, I found my desk dragged
all the way out of the class into like the hallway and almost outside
of the whole school and it was like, this was also in the basement.
So thankfully no one like really saw it other than me, but it was like,
yeah, the comfort it was her because she knew where she left her trash.
So she knew who left the trash on her desk.
So yeah, it was her and like, so.
I sort of like went on non-speaking terms with her and I told her a common
friend, could you tell her please that, you know, if she doesn't knock
this shit off, you know, I would prefer to get like the key.
You'll fuck her up, you'll fuck her up, right?
I would prefer to get the key to the locker bag because I'm not going
to share a locker with person I don't consider my friend.
And yeah, she just sort of like threw the key at me and I guess
I got the key back and we didn't share the locker anymore.
Um, it was also like the whole plan about, you know, not being friends
with her anymore that kind of fell through because I went to the baccalaureate
class while those two got stuck together in the same class because
their last names were literally one letter apart.
So of course they were going to be stuck in the same class unlike me.
So, you know, they kind of ended up being closer friends than before.
And that was around the time I became best friends with the brother
rather than her because she started becoming a bit of a bitch because
of the influence, the very thing she noticed that was going to happen
to her and she let it happen.
I was like, gee, thanks.
Yeah, man.
You can you can judge a lot about a person from the kind of people
they hang out with.
It's true.
Yeah.
That's why you're all scumbags because I'm in here.
It's true.
She was awful.
I think also I have a suspicion that I'm being like paranoid.
I guess like we also started our very first comic together.
My idea, by the way, initially, but she jumped on the on the ship.
Did she quit after the first issue?
That must have really hurt.
No, no, no.
Like we both.
Oh, no.
Let's not drag that up again.
Let's open those old wounds.
And it was like, you know, we both had our own comic that we worked on,
but it was the same idea, which was my idea.
It was a Dragon Ball C fan comic with our self-inserts.
Wait a minute.
We were the perfect foundation for our relationship.
We were eight and like I just remembered.
Yeah, I just remembered.
I have a similar story about someone else who isn't mage who we were doing.
We were doing that.
We were doing that pony comic.
We were doing shelf deprecation about Phantom and Aurora and it never happened.
Oh, interesting, interesting.
Okay.
Let me make another one for the gulags, I guess, whoever this person is.
She's betrayed two of us.
Who knows how long until she gets to the rest.
Okay.
But yeah, so we were both working on our own, our own adventure comics,
with our very first comics and we showed it to the guys in our neighborhood
and we're like, oh, that's so cool.
And we like to both of them equally.
And I was really proud of that and I wish I still have it.
Like I even like made it into like I put paper and I sewed it together
and to make little comic pages.
I didn't just take like a, you know, a notebook and join it.
Like most of my other comics.
I really worked hard on this.
It was like, my magnum opus at my eight year old.
And like I was really happy with it.
I even colored it.
I colored it.
It's like that's something I didn't do since and out of all my comics of all
the two boxes full of comics that I had started and never finished.
And that was, that was the one I think I did sort of finish, but it left on a
cliffhanger.
And so like that one comic was the only one that went missing.
And I have a feeling that she was the reason why because like the actual
like Omega or the alpha version of the comic itself, like just disappeared.
Yeah, I jacked.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
The thing is though, I did lend my comics to my friends a lot to read them
and, you know, let them see what they think and stuff.
And all the comics would return to me and I knew, I knew who, you know,
who would get their hands on who and you, you know, who to ask her to return
them.
But like that one comic, it just, just, I don't remember lending it to anyone
and it just disappeared, but she was the only one of the few friends that
had access to the comics as easily as she did.
So I have a feeling she might have had a hand in it.
I mean, I could be just, you know, seeing Malice where there wasn't,
it could have just gotten lost and it just so happened to be that one
comic that we started to sort of together.
Um, they say you should never assume Malice where mere incompetence
would explain, uh, what, uh, yeah.
Okay.
I'm talking nevermind.
I'm just, I know, I know the saying and I do try to live by that
saying personally right, right now.
But it's just like how petty and malicious she was.
I wouldn't put past her to do that to me.
Um, so yeah, and we just, and she went off to college, I think she
went to the first off to college at 16 years old and I stayed in
school for two more years to finish.
Um, never saw her again up until like a few years ago back when I
was returning to Lafiania and I saw her and I was like, you know,
it's been like, I don't know, like five years.
It's more than five years since we last actually saw each other
in smoke and I was like, you know, I don't want to be friends
with her anymore, especially how, you know, we treated each other.
But I sort of want to, you know, just ended on a common old be like,
Hey, yeah, that was, you know, we were stupid kids.
That was silly.
Haha.
We're, we're on good sort of terms and leave it on good terms.
And I saw her and I was so ready to be like, hi, you know, it's been a while.
But then she looked up at me and she gave me the stinkiest high.
After all these years, after all these years, yeah, like, I was like, dude,
it's been over a half a decade and you're still like holding this
They had more malice for you than you'd for them.
Hashtag confirmed.
Yeah.
And just like, I didn't, I ended up not saying hello to her
because I was like, well, if you're going to glare at me and just
seeing me after so many years, I'm not, I'm not going to even
bother anymore.
If that's the kind of person you want to be, he's fine.
So mage, is it possible in this situation where you made this eye
contact that she was, that was her normal, you know, you know, a lot
of women have resting bitch face when they're in public just so that
people, so that, you know, people approach them and like talk to them.
It changed.
Okay.
Yeah.
I see.
Well,
very run to the prison.
Another one for the gulag.
There you go.
They're all.
Hey, I'm kind of, I'm kind of eager.
I'm kind of eager to get to questions.
Yo, I got my biggest one yet though.
I'm saving one the whole fucking time.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm only times people are going to undercut the questions before I
get to my main thesis.
You just got to, you just got to get to it.
Right.
You guys stick it in there.
I see a trend in mages stories, a childhood friends, like elementary
school friendships that go on one decade too long.
And I, my thesis, my theory on this obviously is that when you get to
know someone as a kid, you know, kids get along pretty well.
It's, you know, as Louis CK has said before, it's typically because
you're the same size there for your friends.
If you get attached, you get emotionally invested in one another
and you feel obligated, you're just, you're connected now.
You know, if it ends up getting broken apart at some point, it's going
to be painful.
So you stick around and as you age, your actual like characteristics
start to emerge in more like meaningful ways.
Like you start becoming people and that's when conflicts happen.
And so yeah, like a five, like you're five years old and you become
a friend and you stay there friend, you're going to end up with a
friendship that nine times out of 10 wouldn't have gotten started in
your adolescence, but it's now in your adolescence.
And like, it's not like being siblings where because you have
genetic similarities, you have a lot to be united over and relate
with and like living together.
You have to get along.
You have to reconcile.
But when it's just a friend, someone who you can like get pissed
off at for 20 minutes, go home and then like think about how pissed
off you are proud of them.
And like, there's no like need to rectify the situation.
Then things can get shitty.
And like, this is what happened with my girlfriend's friend who it
was like a friend of like, I think 13 years and just recently sort
of like came to this annoying fight that had to end the friendship.
Right.
And they had been fighting since before I met my girlfriend because
like, they just get mad at each other over over random shit.
And like, it was very obvious to me.
This friendship would not have gotten started if they had met each
other today.
Right.
It's just because they knew each other since they were kids.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
This is on the part of this girl.
Uh, I'm not going to name her, but like, they like give a hint.
There's a certain Dr.
Seuss character whose name ends with I am.
So not going to like anything specific, but so.
Oh, the laurel.
So this girl, um, she would definitely would fit into a very
specific, uh, instance of worthless friend.
And like, she definitely is bitchy and annoying, but it's definitely
not a, um, an unprovocated act of social violence on her part
because Nikki, my girlfriend is someone who will like be confrontational
if she feels that there's a problem with something.
And sometimes I'm like, you could be less confrontational, but
whatever.
And I am someone who can be just a dick, you know, and it was our
relationship, me and Nikki being a unit that basically set, uh, a
ticking time bomb on their friendship, right?
Because Nikki just kind of started falling away from her friends
in general by spending so much time and calls with me.
And so you can see how that goes, right?
So, you know, and, and so, uh, the I am girl here is, uh, is, uh,
was, was the most incensed about it from what I can gather.
And eventually Nikki moved away from Oregon to come live with me instead.
So yeah, she basically leaves her friends in the dust by and large.
So you can see that, that issue.
And I did visit Nikki's hometown for like a couple of days and I
was hanging out with all of her friends because she really wanted
to introduce me to all of them.
And it's like, like, okay, you know, but obviously I don't make good
first or millions of impressions on people by and large.
So a lot of them were weirded out and wondering why she was into me.
You know, whatever.
Um, she literally Nikki could literally grabbed my phone at one
point and just started adding some of her friends without introducing
them to who I am.
And I'm like, uh, okay.
So yeah, you can see how this is sort of a powder keg to piss people off.
Right.
So I don't want to be too accusatory here, but basically, um, we were
in the car, me and Nikki sitting in the back and this, you know, the girl
in question, I'll call her acorn head because that's where her hairstyle
reminds me of sick.
She's driving.
I don't even think she was driving, but I think it was her car.
It was her CD, right?
Or she was playing like, yeah, it was her CD and, uh, drive by by train
was on the CD and I was just like muttering about how, oh, yeah.
I remember watching like a, I was just muttering to Nikki like, oh, yeah.
I remember watching a video by Todd in the shadows about how like the song
has like some of the worst lyrics possible.
Like if you really analyze it, lol.
And then like she put on this like rock cover of somebody I used to know
and I just muttered to Nikki like, Oh yeah.
You know, man, when this song is sort of isolated from its interesting
instrumentality, the lyrics are pretty, you know, average.
And so this was phrased to Nikki in the form of a Facebook chat message
as your boyfriend is belittling my musical tastes.
And I was like, I had this like this, this disconnect moment of, oh, right.
Not everyone is on the internet constantly talking opinions all the time.
I like had to really brain search to remember what the fuck I said
because I consider myself to, if I'm not on the internet,
reading random strangers, especially friends of someone important to me,
I'm going to keep myself pretty tight-lipped.
And indeed, I did just subconsciously.
She also put on a mixed tape of like early 2000s Disney pop songs.
And I didn't say shit because I never really thought about this as a policy
until I until I until I was faced with this issue with Acornhead.
But that that I was the result of this situation that I can fuck.
Okay, fine.
I'll we'll talk about musical taste insulting policies in another episode.
The point is, she was like, what the fuck is wrong with your boyfriend?
Right?
Because she was like blowing off Nikki like through texts and Nikki was like,
I'm so mad at Acornhead.
I want to like tell her to f off and like Nikki, calm down.
Let's just say, hey, you know, you're here.
You're there for her, right?
And just just be nice.
And she wants to tell her to f off.
That's some pretty strong language right there.
Yeah, I don't know why I censored that anyway.
So, um, so she just was like, hey, what's up?
You know, I don't know what's going on, but you know, let me know.
And then Acornhead was all like, oh, your boyfriend's such a dick.
You know, he always corrects people.
And I was like, wait, what?
And so apparently an instance of me correcting people is one of her friends
was like, I was playing this game on my phone and it was like one of those
things where like the camera was like out and it was like at an angle.
And I'm like, isometric.
And she was like, well, well, like it was like things were at an angle
and I'm like, isometric.
That was apparently really offensive.
You know, like I was trying to throttle my dickishness so hard,
but it's still enough of a came through.
Well, you know, a lot of that is just if they have a certain impression
of you already, you know, like it's a straw that breaks the game.
I already fucking represent like a tension, a new tension with their friends.
So I get it, right?
Exactly.
Um, but so yeah, you guys ever see that episode of Big Bang Theory
when Sheldon goes to the dinner party?
Unrelated question.
Just asking.
But yeah, so like their friendship was over for like a couple of weeks,
even though like I went back to, you know, back to my zone and Nikki was left,
you know, IRL friends with Acornhead and everyone else.
And so I was like, well, how are you going to like not be friends with someone
when you're in a densely connected web of friendship?
But cut to a few months later, now Nikki lives with me.
So now it's all online friends with her, right?
And what happens?
Oh man, we do something that really offends or really disappoints Acornhead.
So Nikki says we're going to get a hamster because like me and David
are going to live up in this room.
We're going to get a hamster and it's going to be so cool.
Who's David?
Yeah, I know, right?
Who the fuck is David?
I actually hear my real name more often than a username once now.
David's the hamster obviously.
Right, it's the hamster.
David the hamster.
So, so fucking, she even had the idea like I'm going to name the hamster Donut.
That's specifically what I'm going to call it.
She had like, she basically had visualized exactly what this hamster
is going to be before we even had it.
And Acornhead was like great hamster idea.
All you got to do is we like once you get a job, you save up some money.
You buy all that hamster equipment.
You buy yourself a hamster and Nikki was like, yeah, Acornhead.
I'm totally going to do that.
But then, you know, Nikki's laying around like before I think, yeah,
she was about to get a job actually.
It was just like a couple of weeks before she got called in, I think.
Um, she was about to get a job.
Uh, but like a few weeks before that, whoops, I'm fucked it up a bit.
It's a few weeks before.
Right.
Oh my God.
We're going back weeks.
Sorry, it's no big deal.
It was just seriously.
It was just one little clarification, right?
Okay.
She fucking, she was like, I want to get the hamster stuff now.
I'm like, okay, fine.
So I spent like a fair bit of money to get like a hamster cage and all the stuff.
And Nikki said, hey, she take my money.
So she said, Hey, Acornhead.
I got all this hamster equipment, snap a picture.
And Acornhead was like, Oh, dot, dot, dot.
And Nikki is like, what's going on?
Huh?
What's up?
And she's like, Oh, nothing.
I'm like, what?
And she's like, are you mad at me?
Acorn's like, no, not mad.
Just dot, dot, dot.
Disappointed.
Turns out, of course, the classic believe that she got dramatic ellipses
that your boyfriend is getting you a hamster before you got a job.
Right.
Oh man.
Your boyfriend is like spoiling you in the humanity.
Right.
Sounds like sounds like she's in need of a hamster.
Dude, now that we got the hamster hamsters are great.
I finally realized that there is a pet that is great because you know,
even cats are kind of, you know, they're not zero maintenance.
Hamsters are basically zero maintenance.
It's just like watching my every day.
Now every day is Hamtaro time.
And it's wonderful.
Hell yeah.
Finally, I have an animal I really like.
Tomorrow will be great too.
Hell yeah, Ben.
Hell yeah.
So it was definitely worth it.
But like Acorn had this frame.
This is like, Acorn had this framing this as like me like spoiling Nikki,
you know, like giving her too much stuff and like, you know,
again, Nikki wouldn't like let it go.
She'd be like, Hey, no, you shouldn't.
But, but Acorn had to be just like so offended that her life advice wasn't being
taken.
So here's where we get to the worthless part of the friendship here.
Is that Acorn had is was so like, it's just a couple of years older,
right?
And she sees herself as very mature and like independent and was just
in sense that Nikki was not quote listening to her life advice by virtue
of not just following all of it, you know, and, and she was just like,
and I even told Acorn had like, I gave her my own message like, Hey,
I mean, I decided to give Nikki the hamster because it would be a
responsibility.
Like, you know, she has to like feed it every day and she just needs
something to do while she looks for a job.
She's really bored, really depressed, waiting for a job to show up.
I'm giving her some more stuff to do, right?
And what she did was the classic internet technique of like pretending
to agree with that point so that they can then proceed to like completely
contradict you.
She was like, Oh, I totally get that.
But just wait.
She said, just wait until five years from now when she's still not doing
anything with her life and see if you still want to be with her.
And I was like, Jesus.
That's I see where she's going with that.
Sounds pretty zero to 60.
Yeah, yeah.
This person's got an agenda.
Yeah, I fucking know, right?
And so Nikki was so mad and then like, you know, like she was just browsing
Facebook a few days later and she saw a comic that reminded her of Acornhead
where it was like some it was like a little Facebook, you know, comic
strip thing of like, you know, certain guys went this out of a relationship
and like all the responses were like, oh, yeah, fuck those guys and fuck
those relationships.
Nikki was like, all these goddamn people telling me how to have my
relationship, you know, like, yeah.
And so she so she posted a reply to that thing saying, or you could just,
you know, let people have their own fucking relationships and live
their own goddamn lives by their own terms.
The problem is that she did not like, like nest the actual original image
because it was also like a fetish thing.
So she didn't want that to be on her post.
So she just out of context responded to something that wasn't there,
which was like the weirdest shit ever.
But it made Acornhead think it was directed completely at her because,
you know, she knows that there you go.
So Acornhead, this is fascinating.
This is like the tale of the snarky Facebook post.
Like the origin story.
This is like, uh, uh, yeah, Facebook post redemption.
Yeah.
So like he was all like, yeah, that that Facebook post wasn't directed
at her.
It wasn't about her.
Although emotionally it was about her, you know, but it wasn't directed
at her.
She didn't at message Acornhead, you know, at acornhead.twitter.com.
She did not message her, but Acornhead was like incensed about it and
wasn't talking to Nikki for a couple of days.
And she was like, why is she like blowing me off?
And she was like getting mad.
Like, I'm going to say F you Acornhead.
And I was like, Nikki, Nikki, Nikki, Nikki, Nikki calm down.
Just be there for her.
Just send her a message saying what's up.
Right.
And she was like, okay, fine.
So she wrote a message hit send message could not be sent.
Oh shit.
So after about 30 attempts to call her because I don't know.
Maybe Nikki is a little bit clingy.
Uh, she finds out through the grapevine that she has been Facebook
blocked by Acornhead Esquire.
The worst sin you can commit in today's age.
What a fucking shit.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, so now Nikki kind of goes like, no, cause Nikki has this sort of
this really difficult relationship of not being able to not respect Acornhead
for being, you know, an older girl who's gotten more accomplishments
and done more things with her life and acts like a know it all and
therefore like attain some authority.
You know, someone who Nikki has looked up to for a long period of time.
So it's hard to like reconcile the fact that she's actually kind of a bitch dick.
So it's, you know, kind of tears her up.
You're right.
And it was just like, eventually Acornhead responded with, yeah, fuck you
and your stupid messages.
Um, you're not, you're a terrible friend.
Um, I'm not going to be your friend anymore.
I don't want to see any more of you.
Oh, you're dumb.
And I thought it was pretty interesting to see, uh, to see Acornhead after
all of her like posturing of like how mature she is, like taking
her ball and going home, just the amount of spite that was like spread
onto me indirectly through Nikki is palpable in my soul.
This is a very recent thing.
That's why I'm going in through too many like unnecessary details
is because it's hard and I haven't had as much time to filter it out.
But, uh, but, uh, yeah, and, and eventually like her last message to
Nikki was, yeah, you know, um, you think you can live without me,
but when it all comes crashing down, you'll be sorry.
And I'm like, Jesus.
And, uh, yeah, that was that.
So that was a friend, you know, when you talk specifically
about worthlessness, it's a friend who felt that they were more
worthful than they are and couldn't deal with the fact that they're
fucking life advice and you know, this whole like hamster thing
was at the tip of the iceberg.
Sounds like someone who's willing to, who's willing to write
you off completely when you don't need them.
And like, like if you, if you're no longer dependent on them.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
It was, it was very, yeah, it was pretty manipulative and controlling
in that kind of way.
And she was just, yeah, she was just getting herself into this,
the cycle of like acting more immature because she wasn't being
treated like the adult in the room, you know, and, uh, we see.
Yeah.
There's a lot of ways that you can be a worthless friend and a
lot of ways you can approach this from.
So, uh, yeah, that's interesting here for that perspective.
All right.
Well, we encourage you all to go out and try and experiment with
your own ways of being a worthless friend and let us know how it goes.
All right.
What's up, mate?
Yeah.
Just quickly while I was talking, I remember like the friend from my
last, uh, story, she, um, told her family, like, like, uh, she was
really good friends with her, like, um, cousins and stuff.
Uh, she, she told her cousins about me and during like one time while
we were friends, like we, you know, we had the on and off thing.
Uh, while we were friends, like her cousin came to visit and like in
the middle of like the neighborhood, I was just walking home.
The cousin just kind of like pointed to me and shouted across
the neighborhood, like, you can't like my cousin says, like, you're,
you're a terrible person.
And I was stunned.
I was stunned.
I was like, I never, I never talked to you.
You don't know anything about me.
She must have said really terrible things about me for you to go out
of your way to bully me in public like that.
And she was older as well.
She, we weren't like, we weren't like, and like the same age.
She was much older than me.
She was like, did you say sorry?
Yeah.
She was, did you say you cunt in Lithuanian in Lithuania?
She said something of equivalent.
Uh, I don't remember the exact words, but I knew it was like a swear word.
It was like approximately say something like that in major major.
Can't believe you remember the English translation better than what
was actually said in your native tongue.
She's living in the first things first, like Lithuanians don't
have swear words all their swear words that we use our Polish or Russian
or even English.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
So we don't, we don't have swear just in our, that's, that's what I like.
A good clean language.
If we wanted to insult people, we would use animal words like, you
know, pig, uh, kurwa, rooster.
That, that's Polish.
And that's a swear word.
I know, I know.
That was fascinating.
I heard kurwa all the time.
Kurwa was the only, was like, was like, was the most, was the big thing over
there.
Um, I'm medical never, never at me.
Um, never from me because I'm a good boy.
Of course.
You didn't do nothing.
Never.
But yeah, just like my point is like, she should talk so badly about me to
her like close relatives where I, while we were friends, I never should
talked about her behind her back.
Like only time I would complain about her to our common friend who knew
how she was.
I wouldn't like, you know, poison new people to her like by, by, you know,
just, you know,
that was like, that was such a shocker.
And I just remembered it.
And like, there was also other ways how she mistreated me, but like this
podcast is a long enough for me to tell all the stories.
But yeah, she was, she was terrible.
Hey, what can you do, man?
Uh, sounds like she really was after control.
Friends are scary.
They can become enemies.
It's, it's true.
It's a role in life.
I like how like every, never have friends.
Everybody has a message.
Yeah.
All the friends I had, like in real life, just sort of like pissed off from my
life all at the same time.
When I was 16, 17, so they all left and you were the common element here.
Wonder if there's a.
Come on.
I don't know.
Fuck you.
I like, I like to believe I was meant for greater things.
Interesting.
That's what all sociopaths say.
Okay.
So this is the part of the show where we take questions from fans at home
on Twitter and on the private PCP discord for patrons only.
Hooray.
That's right.
And if you patron, uh, you're more likely to get your question seen because we
got a whole bunch of Twitter ones.
It's a more exclusive club.
And for the first time ever, the entire, the entire PCP patron lounge came
together with one big question that they want us to debate.
Oh, God.
They've been having a debate about this all day and they wanted to get our
take on it.
What's the best kind of chocolate, dark chocolate, normal chocolate?
Oh, I have a very specific answer.
I like how it's called normal chocolate, not milk chocolate.
Well, sure.
That's true.
Of course it's not dark chocolate.
Of course it's dark.
Milk.
Does anyone not think it's dark chocolate?
It's not dark chocolate.
It's dark chocolate.
Milk chocolate.
No.
Okay.
So look, hang on.
So, uh, who, how many people in favor of dark chocolate?
I.
What?
Only two?
Is it genetic?
Is it a genetic disposition that we shared?
Who's, who's, who's for milk chocolate now?
Uh, I like white chocolate.
What?
And a white, what about DeVue?
And what does DeVue say?
Are we limited only to dark white and milk?
No.
No, you got another.
You can suggest it.
Yeah.
That was the question.
The kind that you get that are chocolate chips out of the bag that are meant for baking.
Those for some reason.
So baking.
That's not, that's not milk chocolate.
No, that's not sweet.
And it's dark chocolate.
Dude, I can't.
Are they sweetened?
I don't know what to fucking tell you.
You can buy any kind of fucking Hershey's.
It's not going to taste quite like, uh, chocolate chips that you get out of a bag that are meant for cooking.
It's like, it's like this weird civilization where like everyone is doing the wrong thing
and I'm the main character who like looked to the side of the shelf and like found this other different path.
It leaves the secret society where there's the fucking completely way superior in every fucking way chocolate that people put in chocolate chips.
No, you don't need to buy it in chip form.
You can get it just normal.
Well, DeVue is making the case that it's not the same.
The taste is like like a Hershey's part.
Hershey's favorite flavor is a shape.
I'm going to tell you what, it's, it's dark.
It's semi, it's semi sweet and it's dark chocolate.
I'm sure.
You erased all memories of chocolate from me and you blindfolded me and had me eat a regular Hershey's bar.
I would be like, hmm, kind of tastes like I'm eating like a candle or something.
It kind of like, it almost tastes like some sort of like weird, like maybe chocolate that was like inside a can that was like sitting there for two weeks mixed with like a red candle or something.
Maybe some bugs flew into it.
That's what I think when I eat like Hershey's bars or Hershey's kisses, every kind of Hershey's thing.
But even Hershey's, the same exact fucking brand.
If you just buy the bags of chocolate chips that I'd see in my mom's jelly cupboard, I open it up, pour that into like just a little cup and just eat those like a snack while I'm 14 and don't have to worry about getting a fat belly of beer belly yet.
That was the only kind of chocolate that was really worth having.
And I'm just like, why, why, why is the world not like understanding this weird mistake we've all made?
We've all made this collective mistake.
Fair enough.
If we can pick random shit as our favorite chocolate, then peanut M&M's are the best chocolate ever made.
Okay, now we're just poisoning the well here, bringing in these candy coated shit.
What is the word?
You let the food do it, you fuck!
He's talking about a specific type of pure chocolate.
So much!
No, but the peanut M&M's got damn it.
The question is, the question is white milk, the question is white milk or dark.
Well, in white milk or dark, dark all the way.
Like I would rather like fucking eat like a celery stick than any kind of dark, any kind of chocolate other than dark.
People who prefer dark chocolate are also like wearing a fedora and like smoking a pipe.
Well, I'm literally doing one of those things right now and I'm gonna do the other later today.
Like I've been dark chocolate fans also like watch Rick and Morty every week and like do a podcast about it.
Disgust.
Rick and Morty?
You're not wrong.
My, I'll always have a place in my heart for cookies and cream Hershey bars.
Yeah, one of my chocolate.
That's not white chocolate.
I know that's not pure white chocolate.
That's a meme candy bar.
It's not, it's not in the running gear.
It doesn't taste good.
My mom will occasionally get this like hot pepper like dark chocolate, which just has like spiciness to it, which is kind of good.
But I gotta go with dark chocolate.
The answer is clear.
The consensus here is dark chocolate.
No.
There you go.
I disagree.
Facts are facts.
You disagree with the consensus.
This is math mage.
In general, I like fake chocolate like Atkins chocolate more than real chocolate.
Like even more than like fucking chocolate chip chocolate.
Because it doesn't make me feel like I just ate a bunch of sugar because I didn't.
It's a faker, but it's actually actually like a taste better.
That's why I like diet soda.
Like it might be just psychosomatic, but I just feel better about myself after drinking a diet soda.
I recently got super into zero water.
It's all the taste of fucking soda without feeling like I just, I'm about to fucking pass out, right?
But yeah, like fake chocolate.
I even like the taste.
It's not just the feeling afterwards.
It's got this like powdery texture to it that is just so much more even and smooth.
Then like, cause like chocolate chips.
Yes, they have an amazing taste, but they're so fucking intense that they kind of command my attention and I become numb to it.
You know?
So like, cause like, like chocolate chip cookies, for instance, I would say are not actually enjoyable to eat in the long run because they're so good.
What the fuck are you talking about?
How is there so no one ever let me finish my fucking sentence?
They always boo me before I can completely beat it.
Yeah, there's so many people here who boo.
When you eat one, you like, it's like so good that like now that you're done eating it, life sucks now.
So the only logical conclusion is to never stop eating them, which will become a thing you can never eat.
God damn it, are you stop gaslighting us on the definition of good brother fucker?
Are you actually here to argue that because the chocolate chip cookies are so good that it's so sad to stop eating them?
That it's not worth eating them in the first place, man.
But he loves eating dark chocolate, so it must taste like shit.
I don't know what to fucking tell you.
There are things I think taste even better than chocolate chip cookies, but they're just a certain kind of good that aren't the same problem.
I guess Davoo's making like the heroin arguments.
Like is heroin good?
I mean, kind of, it's kind of good, but when your whole life is wrecked because you've reached to by a peak of euphoria.
I don't know, hold on.
It's not just simply the level.
It's not a fucking DBZ power level here.
It's more of a complicated thing, right?
Because like for example, like-
My P-brain can understand this.
Yes, yes, fucking tortilla chips.
I have the same issue with them.
Because it's all about the fucking salt.
The beginning of every tortilla chip is great.
The end of every tortilla chip is all right.
And so the only way to continue the feedback loop is to keep doing more chips, right?
It's a clear science.
Like potato chips even fucking advertise themselves, can't put them down.
Like that's kind of like weird abusive marketing right there, abusive products.
It's that skinner box.
Right, yeah.
Every time you get the fucking shiny thing.
Like obviously with chips, the logic in science is very clear.
It's salt and then the salt gets absorbed and now you're dealing with a bunch of tasteless darts.
I don't know how the science works with chocolate chip cookies.
I don't understand why, but I can have something like say brownies with ice cream,
which I think I would write above chocolate chip cookies as in terms of taste.
But I feel more satisfied about that.
Please stop, I'm so hungry.
Okay, well you know what?
You know what?
I'd say dark chocolate chip cookies are better anyway.
So the question is settled.
Actually guys, I just realized I made a mistake.
The question actually said dark people, milk people.
Oh no, we've been racist this whole time.
What are the milk people?
Wait, is that like gay people?
Like the guy named the milk people?
It's the carthine.
It's the carthine are the milk people.
Wouldn't a milk person be a woman?
Oh shit, you're right.
They're the cows of people.
You're not wrong.
I guess I'm going to maintain my same answer from before,
which is that my favorite of the kinds,
the really small ones, you get in a bag.
Davoo sent me to have some jungle fever over here.
Yeah, I guess we do.
Yes, we do.
Should we move on to the next question?
I've got it right here lined up.
Okay, all right, there you go.
All right, here we go.
New question at Faye88son says or asks,
are you with or with not?
This is how they say it.
Are you with or with not designer babies?
Designer babies.
What does that mean?
What do you think, everybody?
So a designer baby is the idea of being able to genetically
engineer the type of baby you want,
and then you just, you know.
I think I've got to be against,
because lately I've been thinking about dog breeds
and about how fucked up it is that we've like fucked up
dogs so much with genetic engineering
and like turned them into mutants.
And I'm pretty sure it would be a bad idea
to start down that route with humans as well.
Well, Ben, let me just play devil's advocate
on the obvious points here,
but like wouldn't it be great though, Ben,
if we just engineered everyone to like
not have any chance of cancer and like have, you know,
I don't know, be tall and strong and muscly.
You know what, I was thinking,
I was thinking designer as in like purely aesthetic.
If we're talking about like disease resistance,
then I'm going to say.
Yeah, but like having a foreign amendment against aesthetics
is just, here's like talking about ideology, sure,
but let's go one layer down towards a little bit
more of practicality as to like what platforms,
no matter how noble, cannot possibly win.
Here's the thing, like because when Ben said it would be
difficult to go to start down that direction,
keyword I want to emphasize is start.
Similarly to like say cyber augmentation
and how some people say that it's kind of a stupid argument
because we already augment ourselves with things
that we wear or like put on our wrists.
It's like the same thing.
You are already putting into consideration
the design of your children if you make any decisions
about who you're going to mate with
based on what you want your children to be.
And if you choose to not drink alcohol during pregnancy,
you are making an effect.
It's just a very simple one.
It's a very simple, obvious, not complicated,
not morally gray yet series of decisions that you are making.
And if the decisions become really complicated,
every fucking forum argument is just going to go back down
to like, well, you already weren't drinking alcohol.
So like the people who are against this are hypocritical.
And I just don't think people are going to be able to like,
yeah, people, the people who are going to stand against it
just aren't going to be able to win.
Probably because all the people who are for it
are going to be like a lot stronger than them
and just kick their ass.
I agree, Davoo, that the, to say it's just bad on its face
is overly simplistic for a lot of reasons.
But like, I see that the biggest concern that I would have
is through the, like how good is the actual process?
Like are we saying in this example that we magically
have the ability to just, you know,
wizardly control whatever kind of way we want our kids
to come out and there won't be any side effects?
I'm thinking like that the real issue will be
the actual like tangible effects of monkeying around
with like a zygote's DNA and like trying to control it.
But yeah, I'm sorry, that's your word.
I know that's your people's word.
You fucker.
First PewDiePie and now you.
How can't you do this to me?
What I did want to say was that, so Star Trek,
totally sidestepped this question in what I would consider
a fairly cowardly way and it's that,
so the way that Star Trek addressed the question
of genetic engineering is, so even in the original Star Trek,
everyone knows Khan, you know, the famous Khan guy.
So he is a genetically engineered like super Ubermensch
and that's like, and it just made him like think that
like, okay, I am superior to everyone.
So I have carte blanche to just like rule the human race.
And there were a lot of guys like him and you know,
it caused a lot of bad things to happen
because he had that mentality.
But like, and so basically, and in Deep Space Nine,
there is another character who's also genetically enhanced,
but basically the whole thing is like, he's okay.
He happened to turn out okay.
But there's a bunch of other genetically enhanced people
who like got kind of fucked up during the process,
which I think is interesting and probably more realistic
to what will happen because, but the reason they got fucked up
is because the practice has been completely outlawed
to genetically engineered children throughout the galaxy.
Exactly.
And so like these people were fucked up because like,
they had like back room geneticists, like are the ones,
like it's really similar to like a back room abortion
that like can fuck up the mom and stuff.
Like that's the idea here.
And so like, of course in that process,
things get messed up.
A much better conceit would simply be that like,
well, we try, but it turns out we can't make people
that much better than we already can
because DNA is more complicated than we thought,
you know, like fucking, you know.
Yes.
They're trying to avoid the question of like,
okay, but what if we really do just start making every baby
like pretty much perfect as a campaign?
You see the Ubermensch.
They're not answering that question.
They're still getting fucking,
I'm actually like editing a fucking Hunter, Hunter thing.
I'm watching the Merrim versus Netero fight right now.
That fucking Ubermensch.
Well, that didn't work out too well for him.
But it probably would have worked out okay.
I mean, okay.
So like he was not a bad person.
He just had a big ego because everyone, you know,
fed it a lot and he had to kind of sort through it.
But like he did develop human emotions
and an appreciation for life.
He probably wouldn't have lost if he was like more than
like 15 days old and had like more life experience.
Yeah.
Like the only reason he lost is because the, you know,
people assumed he was going to be a huge problem for the world,
which he may or may not have eventually been.
You know, the ants did kill a lot of people,
but you know, he didn't really have control of that
from the start.
He was brought into this system.
So he himself, you know, maybe he would have fixed things
and like, you know, they basically just assassinated him
without finding out what he would eventually become.
He was only like a couple days or like a couple months old
at that point, you know?
Yeah.
God, I love this fucking discussion we just had like 20,
like 2% of people are gonna be like, yeah, that's good points.
20% of people would be like, you fucking spoilers.
And then the other people are like, they're fucking talking about it.
That's okay.
We don't need to get into that anymore.
So does anyone have like a strong stance against it
on any kind of moral level or is it all practical?
No.
Yeah.
Human life is there to be toyed with in my mind.
Okay.
I see a good question here, pretty heady one.
It's on the Twitter?
Yeah, it's on Twitter.
Okay.
PoraSailingGod asks, what does humanity deserve more?
Alien friendship by solving global warming for us
or punishing us with death for causing it?
Oh, wow.
Well, okay.
By killing us because we caused global warming that only hurts us?
What's...
I think what she's asking is, does humanity deserve to be,
should aliens step in and help us solve the issue
or should they destroy us?
Because we've caused this issue and we're too dangerous.
I think the destroy thing is a silly point.
I would not be on board with that.
I would be surprised if I personally was ever a huge fan of a sci-fi thing
where aliens did anything other than not give a single shit.
You guys are still relying on the atmosphere of the rock you grew out of?
Plebs?
Yeah.
Why would they even give a shit?
They're interdimensional travels.
I hope people realize the moment that we have faster than light travel,
fucking no one's gonna care about climates of planets.
Well, you know, we'll need to fix it.
Still gotta live on them.
Yeah, you gotta...
Sorry, you could live in a ship, I guess, but whatever.
People do better on planets.
Yeah, no.
I mean, I wouldn't really...
I mean, it'd be nice if the aliens fixed it
and then just like gave us the answers to these questions,
but I think humans will sort it out eventually.
I think we deserve the benefit of the doubt.
I agree.
What's her face from horror, he said?
Yeah, I could influence the weather,
but if you influence it just slightly in an artificial way,
it will basically cause apocalypse for hundreds of years.
Wait, Haruhi said that?
Oh, right.
The alien girl from it.
Oh, Yui.
No, not Yui.
Yuki, that's right.
Okay, the question of like, should we be wiped out for it?
I feel like that attitude is coming from this like,
because we have committed this sin against the planets.
Guys, the planet is a fucking rock.
It's not alive.
It has no personhood.
It is not like...
It is not deserving of moral concern outside of...
It is a habitat for...
And I don't even care about animals.
My standard of caring about something is
if it has like an intelligence that is worth preserving.
Some animals might qualify for that,
and definitely humans do.
But like, I don't feel bad for the fucking planets
or like wiping out bacteria.
Every day you're fucking alive.
You are murdering bacteria in your fucking gut.
That's no different from like,
burning down a fucking rainforest
and just like letting all the trees die.
All I care about is our environment.
That's all I care about.
Yeah, for our own sake.
Yeah, I mean, not to like pile on and be too much of a dick,
but hearing that question,
it reminds you of like my parents and their friends being like,
do you think that like America deserves to be destroyed by Satan
for all of its sins at this point?
I'm just like...
Okay.
Gotcha.
Oh, is this it done?
I mean, yes, but, you know...
All right.
How about this one?
Jade Murrow asks,
how much do you value being a jack of all trades
versus specializing in one craft?
Immensely.
So, because I feel that the two,
that the one field I have proven successful in videos
would not have been able to be,
if not for having a very specific mixture of skills.
Let me finish the question.
She goes on to say,
I mean, most crafts take more than one skill to do.
Right, yeah, exactly.
But like, it's all about the very specific mixture.
Like, you can have people with like,
mediocre to pretty good skills in certain things,
but if combined just right, they make something great.
And I would consider James Rolfe to be kind of in that camp.
Like, he's pretty good at writing,
he's pretty good at directing,
he's pretty good at editing,
he's pretty good at analysis,
and he's pretty good at filmmaking.
I think he's kind of like a mediocre to decent filmmaker,
but he would just happen to have the idea
to combine filmmaking and narrative with video game review
and created an all new like genre
that like revolutionized everything
and happens to still do it better than most people.
So it's like, you know.
The single most important invention of the last hundred years
was the induction of the video game nerd.
Yeah. The angry video game nerd.
Yeah, yeah, oh, absolutely.
The greatest creation of the last hundred years,
I would say, of course.
You know, we're like, you know, Andrew Hussey
taking pretty good art skills, great writing skills,
great work ethic skills,
and creating something that's spec'd perfectly to his abilities
and he made something amazing with it, right?
So, yeah, like to do videos,
to do videos like all around well,
you got to be pretty good at analysis,
you got to like understand writing,
you got to understand like visual flow,
you got to understand how to talk at least decently,
you got to have the privilege to afford all the equipment,
and yeah, you got to have like a thin array
of like a little bit of skills in many different fields
and if you don't have all of them, you're fucked.
That's true, that's true.
Yeah, this question,
this question highlights to me why it's important
not to like spend time like practicing to do a thing
by doing other things
and why the best practice for a thing is just to do it
because like, yeah, whether it's videos or comics
or anything you're wanting to do,
like yeah, it takes a set of skills to do a task well
and the only way you're going to like practice all of them
in the proportions that you need to know them
to get good at the particular thing
is to do that thing
because anything else is going to be imbalanced, you know?
Like if you're trying to draw a comic
and you just do like figure drawing,
like maybe you'll get good at drawing figures,
but like drawing comics, it involves more than that.
It's all about framing, about dialogue and pacing.
Like you're never going to be the best artist
because there's a thousand best artists.
So like if you want to be the best of something,
come up with an all new combination
that no one's even heard of.
So I would say the best thing to do is specialize.
Well, hey, is anyone?
I can hear it, I can hear it.
Okay, Davoo, cut out.
The best thing that you should specialize in one thing
and you should be, and thereby become good
at all the things needed to do that one thing.
But yeah, I think overall,
like specializing in one thing is the most important
because like you're only,
that's what makes you stand out.
You know, they say like do one thing and be the best at it.
If you're doing all kinds of different things,
you will never be the best at any of them.
And being the best is what it takes, you know?
Being the best at what you specifically are doing
is what it takes to, you know, stand out.
Agreed, agreed.
If you're doing, if you're mediocre
at a bunch of different things, it's normal in case.
And when you say the best of a thing,
a thing doesn't mean a whole medium.
It can mean a whole genre.
It can mean a very specific thing, you know?
Like if you are, if you have the same amount
of writing skills as a bunch of other people,
but you happen to know a whole lot about fucking hepatitis B,
then you could make the biggest, best hepatitis B novella series
that anyone, that all the preteens
are gonna go crazy for, right?
That's exactly what I mean.
Being the best at specifically the thing you're doing,
like even if it's like something real narrow.
You go on the internet, like here's my hepatitis B fucking OC.
Do not steal.
It's hepatitis B DC5.
Yeah, and you know, like the small but dedicated
hepatitis B fan base will go wild for it.
And that's what you want.
And your mascot, the hepatitis B,
Buzz Buzz will, you know, be on the internet
and take it by storm.
It'll be great.
Yeah.
You'll be like, oh man, you sure are lame.
What are you, a hepatitis C fan?
Well, we're better than those people.
Hey, here's a question that's totally relevant
to our podcast here from the Twitter at
M-I Cool Man, or Me Cool Man, says,
how do I make cool internet friends like you guys?
And the great thing I like about this
is it's not a question of like, how do I become your friend?
This man is looking to cultivate his own circle
of internet friends.
And I have advice for that.
I would say the best thing to do is just
find a community and get engaged with it
and identify the people who, you know,
are investing their own energy
and providing value to that group
and, you know, contribute to it in whatever way you can,
be it like a content creator or otherwise.
And identify the people who are worth your time.
Hang out with them.
Just talk with them.
It's inevitable that you get to know them
because you're both there investing your time
in the thing that you're doing.
And yeah.
The PCP, the procrastinators,
could not have been formed in any other environment
but broneism.
The MLP fandom like specifically facilitated
a sort of like, you know, hypothetical social structure
of like people running around like sort of an ecosystem
and there was this one little, one little like area
where a very specific type of cream
rose to a very specific type of top
where it was the brone analysis scene
where it was like there's just enough autism
flying around, just enough creativity
and just enough people who are lazy
to create this giant like, this giant field of people
who are idiots and bad, but like there was just enough
people who were actually good
that they were definitely going to find one another
and hit it off really well through this highly relatable
place that they're both in.
Yeah, agreed.
Yeah, that's the only way that the PCP could have been formed.
Like everything with like the kind of art that we do
all sort of being synchronized.
We were sort of all on the same page for a period.
I mean, I wasn't in it at the time, but I was following it
during the pony era and doing some pony stuff myself.
Like we sort of all got synchronized.
We all sort of like understood one another and sort of like,
yeah, we started similar projects in similar ways
for similar reasons and all imbued in ourselves
the extremely categorical elitism
over like the people around us because that was
what the brone analysis community was
where there was this just giant swath of people
who were utter shit to make you feel better
and superior about yourself.
And that's the attitude that we still have basically.
It's such a stigma against feeling superior to people.
But when you look at the landscape and you see that
you really just are superior.
Well, if that's not the right time to feel superior when it is.
Oh yeah, believe me.
If you're doing an art specifically something that you're like
it's like a new project, something you've never done before
and you might be really insecure about it.
You don't know if you're going to do good.
You know, obviously you need to like look up to those people
who have done it better than you're ever going to do
as like inspiration and like motivation
and like showing what you have to do to be successful.
But when you're actually in the trenches working on it
chipping away at the project, it's perfectly fine
to spend 90% of your time like dwelling over and over again
about all the people who are worse than you'll ever be.
To tell yourself no matter how much you fuck it up
you're not going to be as bad as them.
It's a beautiful thing.
I see another question I want to answer.
Sure.
From at underscore swagdude underscore
favorite black fictional character.
And I just was excited to see this question
because I definitely have an answer
and it is the guy with the afro in chromarty high.
Oh, he's like...
I guess he's black.
He's totally black.
I mean, there's a lot of indicators but he's not like that dark skin.
You know, he's really not.
He's just fucking looking at him.
He's definitely a black guy.
That's definitely what they're going for.
Well, yeah, exactly.
And he's great and the fact that he's great
doesn't have anything to do with him being black
but he happens to be.
And I fucking love chromarty high
and he is my favorite dude from that show.
I might be forgetting someone else right now
but the one that I really think of is princess tiata
from princess and the frog.
I legitimately love that character.
I think she's fantastic and she's also hot as hell.
So there you go.
My favorite is Nino.
I think the best black character is
Bobobo Bobobo from this anime
called...
If Bobobo is black, then this guy from
Chromarty High is definitely...
Because they basically look like the same...
Bobobo has a giant blonde afro.
This guy's got a giant regular afro.
If he has an afro, he's fucking black.
What is Nino talking about?
I cannot believe you have not seen Chromarty High.
You should absolutely watch it.
It's one of my favorite shows of all time.
Okay.
What about you, Mage?
I was thinking...
I haven't watched much of videos lately.
Uh-oh.
We've got...
No, no, wait.
Is it Jamal from black.com?
No.
I never finished, but I should probably get on that.
What's it called again?
The show...
Young Justice. There we go.
Aqualad or whatever.
Yeah, he was cool. I like that.
Wait, he can swim?
I never liked him.
He was shitty and not cool.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to undercut your choice.
Okay, other questions?
No, no more fucking questions.
I don't pay two hours.
Fair enough.
I want more.
Now we're done.
We don't get paid more if we make the episode longer.
Davoo?
If you want more, talk less during the episode.
Okay, so thanks for listening, everybody.
Remember, send us more questions.
Hashtag AskPCP.
Those are the questions that we just answered on the Twitter.
Or become a patron.
Ask questions there.
We're there all the time.
All the PCB guys hang out there.
And if you're a $5 patron, you get access to all the bonus PCP episodes.
We have got six already done, I think.
And we've already got the next one recorded.
It'll be out in like a day after this comes out, I think.
So it'll be right around the corner.
Which one was that one?
What's the new bonus?
Shit, what was it?
Oh, it's our one on ASMR.
We go deep on ASMR, everybody.
I really want everyone to experience that one.
Your bones will experience their fucking reverberations
of the deep tingles you experienced from that episode.
It's gonna be fucking intense.
And hey, there's merch as well.
Go click the links below.
Go to our red bubble page and go buy a fucking some PCB merch.
There you go.
Those are all our revenue streams.
Please support them as best you can.
Alright, thanks for listening, everybody.
And we'll see you next time.
Bye!
When I was a young boy