The Pro Crastinators Podcast
Hello everyone! Welcome to a PCP episode. That's the Pro Crastinators Podcast for the layman out there.
I am the best guy ever. And uh...
Boom! Gotcha!
Layman? More like layman. Wow.
That's Ben Saint, always before hurtful feelings.
I've just brought a hot take to the table, and it is a sizzlin' on the griddle.
We've got, uh, hopefully to win Hippocrit.
Let me tell you the story of me old bones.
It all started in... I forget. Now you've distracted me. Now I can't remember my story.
Shit. Well, sorry about that.
Little Aurora Mage is here.
Am I a demon, or am I a mediton ex?
Are we human, or are we dancers?
Um, uh, and we've got Munchy.
Layman, more like low main, I say, preparing my dish to serve.
Well, happy Halloween season, everybody!
It's not keto!
I forget who said it, but we have a commenter who said last episode,
can there be a single episode where Ben doesn't mention his diet?
Why would you want that, idiot?
Yeah, Ben's a man of and for, exclusively.
His diet, commenters, fuck, fight me.
That's censoring that you're trying to censor my very being.
That's true. We should talk about our costumes that we're all wearing.
Yes, it's a Halloween close enough episode.
Yeah, we're all wearing them, as you can see, on screen in front of you right now.
Oh my god!
I have a cream sickle colored onesie.
It is a footed pajama onesie.
It is cream sickle covered, it's a very pleasant yellow.
And then I have moose antlers, and I am moose.
He is moose!
Okay, most moose aren't cream sickle colored.
What's going on there?
I think you better stop saying things like that before I encase you in the stone again,
and you won't be able to get out, because it will be so thick,
and you won't have any tools with you.
That's true. I might be able to get out in my dreams,
because I'm Freddy Krueger, guys!
Haha! Look at my fingers!
I'll cut you in the dream world, where you are right now.
Freddy escapes to New York, too, the other day, for the first time,
and he was like, I'm gonna fuck you, and it was exactly like Rick and Morty.
Like me?
I haven't seen a single 80's movie, let alone 80's.
Dude, I've been on a big horror movie bender,
because I just got into, finally, some tiny bit,
I was saying this the other day, of cinemastical shit,
I was watching all this monster movie shit,
and like I watched, just yesterday I watched The Exorcist,
I didn't finish, but I was watching fucking Freddy Krueger, Nightmare on Elm Street,
I was having a great time, I absolutely love it,
and Freddy is Kino, is all I have to say about that.
Ben, what are you wearing today?
Shit, damn, I guess the world's my oyster,
I guess I can just say anything I want,
and just whoever's editing this episode is just gonna have to go with it, aren't they?
Just put you in a cardboard box.
I am...
Oh no, I was about to say that I'm Kirito from Sorted Online,
because that would be really funny, but then I thought about it,
and they realized that people of my age and stature actually go,
actually do things like that, and unironically...
Ben, I met a Kirito cosplayer not too long ago,
just living his life as a Kirito cosplayer.
No, on Halloween, there was a Kirito cosplayer three years ago,
and he was walking around the library, and I walked up to him and said,
hey, is that Sorted Online?
And he said, yeah, and I was like, huh, okay, and then I walked away.
We were like, do you know Ditch Bro? I love him!
I went to a comic expo yesterday, it was called MICE, Massachusetts Independent Comics Expo,
and did not check who was going to be there.
I met Casey Green and Abby Howard, who it was like...
You met Casey Green?
Yeah, Casey Green was there, I shook his hand.
Shit, I forget what he made, I remember the name.
He made the anime club in the gun show.
The anime club!
Oh, dude, that's...
And he makes fucking, what's it called?
He had a portfolio there with originals from Anime Club.
He was selling the original pages of Anime Club.
Did you get any?
You could see the blue pencil sketches and the ink layer over them.
No, I didn't get any.
He makes Fat Boy comic, right?
That's the one he's doing now?
I'm not sure.
I know he did, he's a good boy, and nut, and...
What?
I like it.
I don't know about Fat Boy, I haven't heard of that one.
God damn it, he's the guy who makes the comic about...
Isn't it just about him as a character who's the most reprehensible, fat little...
No, that's Womp.
That's Womp.
I'm sorry, Casey Green.
I'm sorry.
Ronnie Filmyaw from Womp, I think, isn't it?
Ronnie Filmyaw?
Yeah, that's the one.
Well, I love gun show anyway, so no insult intended here.
Yeah.
What was I talking about?
Oh, I think the only reason I was bringing up Mice, which is the acronym, was that I actually
saw a guy in some kind of cosplay.
There was like...
I think as I was walking in, there was a guy and a girl, I think, sitting on a bench.
Human Centipede cosplay?
And like, the girl was kind of cute, but they were both too fucking old for this shit.
And the girl was in Wonder Woman cosplay, and the guy was in...
I couldn't identify what it was, but it looked like some kind of anime shit.
And I was like, shut it as I walked by.
Oh, no.
And I gotta say, the whole experience was not...
I didn't like it.
I did not like going in there as a customer.
It felt bad.
It felt predatory.
It felt like I was a sheep walking into a den of lions.
How so?
I did not want to buy anything.
And even if I had wanted to buy anything, it wouldn't have been enough.
Because it was like every one that I made eye contact with...
Obviously, some of them were more aggressive than others.
But even the softest among them were still pitching in a sort of attempt to get me to buy something.
Oh, that was like at the county fair.
It was just...
It's like I was just inherently at odds with them, and they were like...
I was immediately like...
Even Casey Green, he didn't put the heat on or anything.
He didn't try and hard sell me his shit.
But even he was clearly wanted me to buy something.
Because that's why they're there.
And I was mad.
Because I had wanted to sign up to be a tableer at this convention.
And I think I could have probably done it if I had applied.
It's just that I didn't move...
I didn't live here in time.
And when I moved back to Massachusetts, it was too late.
The deadline was already over.
And I was there, and I was like...
Man, I would like this so much more being on the opposite side of this.
I would much rather be the lion.
I think I might enjoy that in this scenario.
I do not like being the sheep.
That's cool.
I understand what you mean.
I felt that way a lot about the county fair.
I think I talked about it in the PCB before.
It's just a whole cabal of weird, bizarre conspiracy theory wallets
that prevent radio waves from accessing your credit cards.
And overpriced hot tubs to install on your mansions.
It was just a whole range of shit that people are trying to force on you
over and over and over again.
Really aggressively.
Just constantly.
I felt socially.
I felt like I was just...
The people tabling were in charge.
They had all the social power.
They were the artists, and everyone else was the public.
And I felt inherently denigrated by the scenario.
I was like, I should be...
This is such a humble event that I don't even know why I felt this way.
But I was like, I should be on the other side of the table.
I should be the one with the power.
People should respect me.
I should not respect anyone.
I think most people there kind of wouldn't have that problem
because you actually are a comic person.
So you probably feel like that's just where you belong.
I did.
I felt like nature had twisted around.
Why are you spooked?
I'm spooked by the idea of being on the other side of the table.
Oh, fair enough.
It's spooky.
You have to stand there and smile and get people to buy things.
I do not have the confidence to get people to buy things.
Here's the thing.
I would enjoy it because I would not care if anyone bought anything.
I would not care at all whether someone bought...
I mean, obviously I would like it if they bought my shit.
But I would not be there to be like, ooh, I hope I make some money by selling my wares.
I don't care.
It would be good to just be fun.
I would be there so that people like Abby Howard and Casey Greene would be like,
ah, yes, this is my peer.
That's my only goal.
And you know what?
I'd have accomplished it just by getting there.
I wouldn't care about feeding his family.
He cares about chasing that class.
I would just have a good time and meet people and it would be great.
It's a romantic rung on the indie comic Cursus Honorum to be able to not only publish your stuff in a real store like Ben has done as well,
but also attend some sort of a small time convention.
I feel like that's just a ride of passage and a romantic ideal.
You know what?
I've never tabled a convention.
That's just what people do, but I've never done it.
And it's weird.
I don't think it's weird.
And being on what I consider to be the wrong side of the equation.
And history.
Made me really want to do it and also made me really want to get back to work and get my shit done so that I could go to events like this and have more stuff to show and be like, yes, this is my stuff, idiot.
Put down the dwarf fortress, Ben, and pick up the pen already.
Get back to it.
Yeah, you know me.
Ever since I've been like a comic guy now.
You know me, Ben, a dwarf.
Yeah.
I've had thoughts of like, oh, wouldn't it be fucking sick if I made a little book of Bel-J for whatever.
And I had little plushes of punk.
And I was standing there like, hey, you want it?
It's yours, my friend.
Like, you know, just like goading people over to it.
Which you'll have to find it first.
Dude, I think clump.
I think clump.
I think punk pushes fucking help.
Pump.
Plushes would sell pretty well.
They'd be cues.
The thing about that is that, I mean, you'd like, they'd have to be all handmade.
Like, like, like getting a, like getting like a fucking setup to like mass produce plushes is like super hard and impossible or make sense.
Speaking of plushes, I have something.
Wait, mate.
It's for the love of God.
I want to hear all about that.
But we have not finished our goddamn Halloween costume introductions.
Can we please just do...
Ben, what the fuck are you wearing right now?
Just tell me.
Fine.
I'm dressed as a...
Casey Green.
Look at you.
Yeah, I'm Casey Green.
I can see it.
That's right.
It's just Ben with the name tag.
Hey, kids.
This is Casey Green.
I hope you all got your faces ready to sing a little tune here.
Let's go!
Good.
Having a baby and the baby is you.
Okay, anyway.
Gib, what are you wearing?
What's your costume?
Oh, me.
I'm a pirate skeleton.
I was from Pirates of the Caribbean, number movie one, and I was a dead guy.
I still have my little piece of gold.
Good.
Well, that's great.
I'm dead.
Ah, shit.
Who else has left?
Munchy?
No, no, we never did Munchy.
Mage.
Mage, right?
Mage is...
Mage is Mage.
Yeah, Mage is Mage.
I just put on an extra pair of wings, like little bat wings to complete my evil demon
look and also opened my second pair of eyes just for you guys.
We appreciate that.
Well, okay.
Thank God we've got those inter...
Wait a minute.
Oh my God.
She's open, not just...
What's happening?
The earth's rumbling, people.
Do you feel that?
Nothing.
What's happening?
Not another calamity.
There's a zombie.
What the hell is that thing?
Oh, here he is.
What the fuck is that thing right there?
Oh God, help us all.
Could it be?
I don't...
Is it him risen from the grave?
I see an empty Max Revive on the ground.
What's that next to it?
Oh God, he got into it.
He got into the Max Revives.
Oh no.
It's all drains.
It's the PCP guy.
There it...
No, that's not the PCP guy.
That's the legally distinct PCP guy.
Legally distinct PCP guy.
And he's legal.
Oh, he really is after three years.
That's really scary.
Get him off the screen.
All right.
He's back, everybody.
He makes Halloween.
He's so legally...
He's so legally distinct that he's...
Yeah.
He's bulletproof.
We are.
We're all bulletproof now.
It was drawn by Mage because she's like...
She's a necromancer, I guess.
She made him come out of the ground.
I'm a demon.
Demon and necromancer, same thing.
You just have powers.
Whatever.
Get over it.
Yeah, whatever, dude.
Does that make a big deal of it or anything?
Yeah.
Well, you wanted him.
I wanted him.
Yeah.
And he's back now.
He's legally distinct.
You can stop bulletproof.
Oh no, he's scared of us.
He's running and he's hiding in the background there.
Yeah, don't worry, guys.
Okay, he's more scared of us than we are of him.
I mean, we are horrible beasts right now.
If you encounter him in the wild, just spread your coat out.
Try and make yourself look as big as possible.
Do not run.
Face him down.
Just look at his face.
Make loud noises like you're a crazy person.
Yes.
That's how we've kept him in check.
Throw sticks and rocks.
Do not run.
Okay, that's out of the way.
Moving on.
Mage, what the hell are you saying about plushes?
I want to hear it.
Yeah, today was a very exciting day.
It was related to the Pokemon community today,
but I'll skip all the details, I guess.
Oh my god, it's Belldom Day.
Shiny Metagrosses people, they're out there waiting for you.
Dude, where's my phone?
I gotta pull my phone out.
It's a weekly night, so...
I'll be doing it.
I'm going out to get them.
I'm switching to headset.
I'm going out.
I'll do the rest of the PCP remotely.
Actually, Ben, it doesn't actually start for us.
Wait, no, it does start in 10 minutes.
Five minutes, yeah.
Well, plenty of time.
E.
Well, it was a big journey, a big, big day for me.
I'm not sure how many details I want to go into,
but however, one highlight of this whole thing
was that I discovered a Build-A-Bear thing,
and they had Pokemon in it,
and I had my very first Build-A-Bear,
which is a low on Vulpix, and I love it.
And I named it Tyga, and it's on my desk right now,
and it's life-size.
I love it so much.
Can we get a picture of that?
Hell yeah.
Or show notes.
A low on Vulpix is very hoggable.
That's a good one.
That is true.
Fucking Build-A-Bear is really sick.
I love Build-A-Bear.
I have very, very fond memories of the game.
I prefer a low on Ninetales.
Much more competitively viable.
Look at them there.
Okay, question about this, though.
Isn't kind of the point of Build-A-Bear
that you're supposed to customize it,
but this just looks like a generic low on Vulpix.
I didn't want to dress it up.
Oh, so you had the option to dress it up,
but you chose not to.
Oh, okay.
You could have given it thigh highs.
Oh, God.
Jesus Christ.
And like a choker.
And like a choker, lace collar.
I didn't like any of the clothes options.
You could have given him, you know,
crotchless panties, you know.
Stop.
Stop doing this to my pure baby.
Don't start a bell.
Yeah.
Stop that.
You're all banned.
Yeah, that's true.
You're not allowed to speak to me or my son ever again.
I just have him like, he's got like,
what if you come out and you've built your bear
and you just go, hey, I made this bear
and then one, he's got a big old fat cigar
in the one hand and the other one,
he's got a big old stack of pornography.
Tiny little like knitted pornography,
but you can still read it kind of.
Oh my God.
There's a, there's a baniere.
Where's that baniere?
I want it.
Do you like baniere a lot?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I like low-punny because it's fuckable, you know.
What if you went into a builder bear
and you said, make all the homestuck characters.
Would they do it?
They don't have the template.
You go in, you pick up a head.
They don't have the courage for that.
Useful.
Yeah, like when you go in,
they have already pre-made heads and empty bodies
and they fill up the bodies.
I've got an empty body.
I've got an empty skeleton.
No, no, no.
I was meaning like I have no soul, like I'm depressed
because they couldn't make homestuck figurines.
The interaction with the lady that was like filling it up
was quite awkward.
Really?
How so?
Yeah, she had a Pikachu on her bag,
on her back in a bag.
And so I thought maybe, maybe she likes Pokemon
so it won't be as awkward,
but she kind of seemed like a bit of a,
bit of a normie.
Such a normie.
Yeah, there it is.
I wish I had that sound bite ready to go.
I do have that.
Gib actually prepared that sound clip though.
So, one day.
Prepare for what?
For what?
For what are you preparing?
I don't know.
Don't worry about it.
Once the bombs drop Mage,
we're not going to be able to hear you say things like that anymore.
So we're just going to play it down.
The only currency that's going to have any value
is going to be, you know, Mage audio clips.
MP35.
It's going to be the new currency.
Listen, listen.
The Petrodollar is cratching our over-extended oil needles
and octopus tentacles
are retracting from the world.
We're not going to be able to sustain our currency anymore.
And what do we turn to?
Some people say crypto.
Some people say nuclear waste.
And I say Mage audio clips.
Yeah, funny audio clips.
I'm literally printing money right now
with every single word I'm speaking.
Oh, yeah.
Belden Community Day.
Halloween episode.
Let's talk about Pokemon Go again.
Fucking, I got so many Belden.
I caught, I looked at the Pokedex.
I caught 150 of those fuckers.
Damn, that's like all the Pokemon there are.
Yes.
I caught 150 and I traded one of them with my brother
right at the end and I evolved it.
And it's like a 98% lucky Metagross
with like almost maxed out CP.
And then I finished him off
and he's like the biggest, strongest lad.
That's crazy.
There he goes.
Right.
Gen 4 came out guys.
I sure did.
My absolute favorite generation.
I caught two Banearies.
I still can't get my Mamas one.
I know, you have to wait for another wave for that.
But yeah, I'm super excited.
Gen 4 has been my favorite gen ever since I was a kid
because it was the first one that I did, obviously.
And I've always had a soft place in my heart
for like Starling and all the stars and stuff like that.
I'm walking my Chimchar right now.
I am really excited because I don't know anything
about the past gen 3.
So like this is all going to be new and fun and cool.
Like when I saw Baneary, I was like,
what the fuck is that?
It's got like weird brains coming out of its head.
But it's just fluff.
It's so cool.
He's like a zombie Pokemon.
Woo, Halloween.
I can't wait for Munchlax to come.
I'm so excited.
He's coming dude.
He's coming.
I don't know if you're going to get him.
I don't know how they're going to replicate.
I just assume eggs maybe.
He's really, really hard to get in the games.
I was watching a video.
Here's how you get Munchlax in the game.
Can I explain?
I'm the Munchlax guy.
Please do.
All right.
When you start a copy,
when you start a new game of Pokemon,
Diamond, Pearl or Platinum,
there is an item called the trainer card
and it lists a number there.
But what isn't listed there
is your secret trainer ID.
And your secret trainer ID
is calculated whenever you press new game
and you start a new character.
And this secret ID calculates
the placement for Pokemon
within the Gen 4 gameplay mechanic
which is slathering honey on trees.
In Gen 4, you can slather honey on the trees.
And if you come back in five hours real world time,
keep in mind you can't manipulate your DS time
like you can for literally every other game.
I don't even know how they fucking calculate it.
But once five hours actually pass in the real world
and you've slathered honey on some bark,
you can come back to that specially marked tree
and pick up the Pokemon.
And these Pokemon are mostly shit.
Like they're almost always terrible.
You've got fucking combi
and it's probably gonna be a male combi
so you can't even get a vetspequin
or you're gonna fucking get a fucking bee doofen.
There's no reason for you to fucking do it.
But based, calculated on your trainer ID,
there are four trees
that could possibly contain a munchlax.
Keep in mind, possibly.
This is not like these are the munchlax trees.
Go here for munchlax.
Munchlax has a 1% chance
to be in a tree calculated by a number
that you can't fucking see.
So you're going to have to go to every tree in Sinnoh.
Do it a hundred times.
Like, and just slather honey on there a hundred times
to make sure that tree doesn't contain a munchlax
and then move on to the next tree.
And there's something like 27 trees or something.
So just randomly, these four trees are calculated
and you have no way of knowing which one is a munchlax or not.
I mean, breed it how?
Like, trade a Snorlax from another game or something?
Yeah, you can, but you would have to have a Snorlax
and you would also have to have a full incense.
Those games don't have a Snorlax?
No.
No, they don't.
You would also have to, if you don't have two Snorlaxes,
you would have to get the National Pokedex in Platinum
because then you can get a ditto in National Park.
In my current Nuzlocke I'm doing right now,
I saw that munchlax is a Pokemon I could possibly get
and I'm like, dude, I'ma get a fucking Snorlax
for my Elite Four team.
By the way, just beat the eighth gym on my Twitch.
Twitch.tv slash definitely best guy ever.
Check it out every Saturday at 7.30 p.m.
Oh boy.
I'm getting ready for the Elite Four right now,
eighth badges, here we go.
Anyway, I wanted to get that fucking munchlax,
but when I see this shit, it is impossible.
There's a zero chance I'm gonna get this fucking munchlax.
You'd just be throwing away your random encounter for the area.
Yep, yep.
Supressing.
Oh god.
Hey, something cool happened in Pokemon Go.
Tell me if anything like this has happened for any of you.
So, there was, so I have my house.
My house does not have any stops in range of it.
There's one kind of down in the corner.
Like it's like around the corner from me,
there's one at a church.
And then a little ways down a side street,
I pass this church like on the way to and from like the convenience store a bunch.
And then a little ways down, like one block down the side street,
there was a stop, a gym actually.
A weirdly located gym in the middle of,
in like this nothing little corner.
I think it's with the new update that they've switched,
and now the gym is the one that I pass on my way to and from the convenience store.
And now that what was for me, the gym is now just a stop,
which is great.
That's very strange.
That is weird, but that's also cool.
It definitely happened.
That place was absolutely a gym.
I have walked there and like stood on their,
Do you have the gym badge still?
In people's corners and like probably wears them out by just walking down the street,
standing on their corner for 10 minutes and looking at my phone and then walking away.
I used to do it all the time.
I do that all the time, dude.
Guys, get a fucking electric skateboard, increase your efficiency.
I'm just telling you, it's such an upgrade for Pokemon Go specifically.
I like the walking.
Hey, it's what fucking...
I don't want anything to add noise to my walk.
I walk through the park and it's really peaceful.
I also don't want to go fast for any reason.
I like that it takes a long time to get from point to point.
But you can be more efficient at getting more Pokestops and stuff.
Because it's more pleasant and I enjoy it more.
I can walk around the park nearby my house.
It takes about an hour to go all the way around it.
We want to shred hardcore on the pavement and make old ladies jump and fucking splash them as you go by.
I'm with you, Nate.
I'm all about that efficiency.
The walk I have is like an aesthetic thing.
You go down the path alongside the river and then you get to one end of the park.
You turn around and you start going up this hill and then right at the top of the hill there's like a gym.
You can just sit on the hill, on the grass and just look out over the whole park.
You sit there, you spin the Pokestop a few times, you beat the gym and you just sit there for a while.
And then you go home when you feel like.
That's what I do.
Having a skateboard would be completely useless for me.
I have a lot of stops in my vicinity so the skateboard really helps me hit them all real fast.
Because otherwise I definitely would not walk.
I don't have a lot of stops where I live so I have to kind of walk.
Yeah, I've noticed your trainer ID says you've walked over 10,000 kilometers.
No, over 1,000 kilometers, not 10,000.
I just want to let you guys know.
The clock just turned over in Pokemon Go.
I have it open and all the Belldoms appeared.
God, fuck this podcast.
I want to be catching Belldoms.
Can we call it here?
No.
Quick other life update.
I just want everyone to know that I've got like, when I record this, I usually sit with like a blanket wrapped around my legs.
And currently my dog has entered that blanket and is sitting on my feet.
And it's the most comfortable and adorable thing in the world.
I'm happy that you have a dog name.
That's such the most positive character development that possibly could have happened to you.
I'm so ambivalent.
I'm going to harvest him for his meat one of these days.
I could not be more ambivalent about your dog.
This is a stepping stone and practicing responsibility to be a fucking dad like how I know you want to be.
I agree.
It's a fun aesthetic thing that is like the platonic ideal is you're a human who eats bread and has a dog.
And it's just great.
How are you so heinous, Munchy?
How are your values so...
I'm the only sentimental person left on this podcast and the only person who cares about the good things in life which are on the way out.
Munchy, we were having a talk before this episode and I want to now grill you.
It's time to get deep into it.
Okay, this isn't...
Okay, we've all talked about how we hate college and we'd only do it if necessary.
You're like currently working on going to college right now.
I feel like it's been a big, weird elephant in the room and I just want to know why.
Like what is your plan to justify the cost of going to college?
Well, my plan to justify the cost is first of all that my mother's been saving up all of her life for me to go to college.
So it won't be...
You could use that money on anything else, but okay, go on.
Okay, well, she doesn't want to and she wants to use it on me.
And the reason I want to go to college is for a lot of reasons.
First of all, obviously, I like art and I want to continue doing art and I want to do art for the rest of my life.
Do that for free or perhaps for profit as you do now.
Can you let me finish any statement whatsoever?
Okay, I want to get better at art and I want to be taught by a trained professional who has been in the art industry for any amount of time and who I trust their opinion on.
I have been trying, or not trying, but I have been learning things online.
I've been self teaching myself my entire life, but I don't feel like that is a sustainable thing to do.
As it is hard to self teach yourself.
It is not easy to find the right tutorials and to try and mix and match all these different YouTube videos and try and create a through line.
And all YouTube videos are just a standardized formula for the masses.
I want to be able to have a teacher that is able to respond to me personally and is able to give me accurate and in-depth information and good education.
In order to further my art career in ways that I can't fully predict.
There are going to be ways that the teacher could teach me things that I wouldn't think to look up, that I wouldn't know that I am missing, that I wouldn't know that I need to know in order to be a good artist.
So I want to do it for purely academic reasons.
I want to do it so that I can be a better artist and I genuinely believe that I think being in a college or any school type scenario, but I am past high school now and my high school didn't have an art program.
But any sort of classical training and sort of classical teacher helping me in any sort of tutors or something like that.
I think that will be extremely beneficial to me as I think I learn better that way and I'm more proactive in learning anyway.
And that's the academic reason.
Social reason.
It's so weird to hear Munchie talk seriously.
What?
It's so weird to hear you talk like seriously just in a calm voice.
It's not bad, it's just weird.
I want to hear the rest.
The second reason is the sort of social reason.
I have been cooped up in my room for a long time.
I have been cooped up in my room doing internet stuff for a long time.
And as such, I have let my life run me by completely and utterly.
My friends who I cherish with all my heart, my offline friends who honestly I like way more than a lot of my offline friends.
I have not seen them in so long because I've been so single-mindedly dedicated to achieving internet e-fame.
What does this have to do with college though?
I don't get the connection there.
I'm getting to that.
Hold on.
They have gone and now they're in college and I can't see them anymore.
All of my social interaction is nil.
And if there's one thing that I think you can't knock college for in any way is that it's a positive social experience right down to the fact that you are living with someone who you don't know.
Aside from all of the classmates you will meet, especially in art college where everyone will be of a similar mind to you.
Everyone will be of a similar predisposition to be an artist, to be creative.
Aside from all of that and how you're going to be able to network with other people, young, up-and-coming artists, artists of my age, people who I relate to more than random people on the internet.
People who I will be able to maybe even collaborate with or resonate with.
Aside from that, the fact that I just simply will be in a room with another person and I will be able to maybe not fully agree with this person and everything.
Maybe I will have differences with this person.
Maybe I'll be able to have arguments and people have-
I mean, you can just get a roommate.
What?
You talking about just a dorm mate?
Yeah.
That's weird.
That's kind of a weird thing to be excited about.
You can just get a roommate.
Living with someone else is not special.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
That's what I'm doing is I'm getting a roommate.
I would say that's a terrible reason right there.
Throw that one right out.
I don't want to hear it.
Well, I just said other social reasons as well.
I'm saying that this is an emblematic thing that I will have to interact with more people in my life and that's what I want to do.
The only question behind all of this is, is this worth the debt that will be accrued or the monetary expense?
Because I feel like a lot of this can be done for less money than a college education.
I've already done the entire financial system.
Obviously, I'm not going into this blind.
I have been on the podcast and I've said that I don't think that college is cool.
And I understand the financial risk.
I've calculated it at all.
I know how long it will take to pay it off.
And I know how much money I'll be going in, like you'll be able to pay like down.
I know the risks.
And I think that the positives outweigh the negatives.
And everyone in my family is supportive of me.
My mom is more than happy to help pay because she's wanted me to go to college all of her life.
I think that the financial risks, while they are risks, I think they are worth it in the end.
I want to be able to get an industry job.
I want to be able to be an illustrator out in the industry, creating, I don't know, the future lays in store for me.
But to something to the effect of maybe working at Disney.
Maybe that's a pipe dream, but I would like to be able to do it.
I like Disney.
I think it's a great company.
I would like to be there.
I would like to be able to work on logos freelance.
I would like to be able to do industry stuff like that.
I'm not saying that I would abandon the internet or anything, but I think...
I don't care if you do.
I'm just wondering about that.
I think having this outlet is a good idea economically.
I think it's a good, or having the diploma that is, you know, with our colleges.
There's obviously risks and balance, and you know, it's going to be a large investment upfront.
I think ultimately it will pay off.
And even if it was like, you know, like I can't use the art degree for the things that I wanted to,
and it would have been fine if I didn't have it.
I still think that the positive social experiences...
There's one other thing that I didn't get to mention, by the way.
It's that I will be able to live in Boston far, far sooner than I would be otherwise.
And I love the city of Boston.
It's my favorite city on earth.
I've been traveling a lot recently to really great places.
I've been fortunate enough to travel to very old cities like Rome and see the sights.
But nothing has captured my attention more than Boston.
Boston is everything that I like about cities and everything that I want in cities.
And I want to be able to be there as soon as possible.
Then just move there and pay rent. Just do that.
I have no idea when I would be able to do that.
I have no idea when I would be able to do that in any sort of reasonable timeframe.
Of course, guys, I know that there are other ways to achieve what I want.
But don't you understand that these are all of these things in one package?
These are all of these things in one thing.
All it is, this all strikes me as these are the reasons that the millennial generation went to college
and the vast majority of them regret it immensely.
And so I'm just wondering, what's the difference here?
Alright, I'll jump in here.
By the way, you owe me nothing and don't have to defend anything to me.
I went to uni for similar reasons.
I wanted to know what it was I wanted to do.
And I thought animation might be something that I was interested in.
But I came away with a degree that I think is kind of pointless for me
because nobody is going to care about whether or not I have a degree.
They just want to see my animation and how good it is.
So art degrees, they're just like a formality really.
But the teaching I learned, the things I learned that were important
and very much so, the social aspect, the fact that I was living alone for the first time
made me grow a lot as a person.
In many ways, I would have just stayed like a weird baby if I stayed at home.
Some of my friends, or one of my friends, he commuted every day to uni.
And now he looks like the guy at the end of Aunt Boley.
Yeah, he stayed with his parents and commuted to uni.
And the rest of us in the friend group were living in the town.
And by the end of the three years, it was quite obvious that we had become more mature and he hadn't.
And we just sort of stopped talking to him.
And it was kind of brutal, but it really crystallized for me how important it was that I was doing this.
Even though it's a lot of money and I'll probably never pay it off.
See, that's the important part for me right there, at the end there.
I don't know how it works in Britain, but you can't shake that.
I don't have to start paying it back immediately.
I only start paying it back once I reach a certain income threshold.
So I'm more okay than someone in America.
So I don't know exactly how it works over there.
But from what I understand, as soon as you stop, you have to start paying back interest or something.
I think a lot of the reason why...
I'm going to use Tom as a sort of case example here.
Tom, please listen to this episode and correct me if I'm wrong or anything.
But if you recall, he talked about this on the PCP before, that his father just said,
Don't think about the debt. Don't think about it. Everyone has debt.
There's no reason to do it. Just go to art college because it will be a good opportunity.
And I feel like the distinction here is that I'm not in the dark about any of the faults of college.
And I've accurately prepared for them.
I have all of my finances in order.
I'm not going to be able to pay literally 100% of it off immediately,
like my first time that I get a debt notice.
But I have calculated the amount of time that it will take.
And it's not a big deal. It's like 10 years. It's not a huge deal.
How is that not a big deal?
I'm sorry, but how is that not a big deal?
A lot of the time, it's like 30 years or something.
I understand that 10 years sounds like a long time. It's a decade.
But in the grand scheme of things, if I'm going to be able to get these four years of the experiences,
which I think I'm in tail for, 10 years does not sound like a bad deal.
So you mean 10 years after you're done, right?
Yeah.
So you'll be 32 when that's done?
And then whole time, you'll be paying...
Okay, all right.
Well, I mean, if you think it's worth it...
I'm not your fucking dad. I'm not trying to dissuade you.
I'm simply trying to... We've all recognized it.
We have talked a lot of shit about college here.
And it would be weird to not bring it up when Bunchie is going to college soon.
I don't know.
I mean, you say that that's not a big deal, but suddenly it's like, oh my god.
What exactly are you spending 10 years in debt for to move to Boston and have a roommate?
And to further my career?
You can do that for like $500 a month.
You could split a room with someone in Boston.
To further my career, to have academic credentials, to become more proficient in art,
to do the things that I love in the city that I love,
and be able to meet new people and network and have more opportunities in my life.
That's what I'm paying for people.
See, those reasons make perfect sense. They make perfect sense.
But, you know, people have regretted it.
Well, there is no but.
I'm not trying to tell you not to.
When it comes to art specifically, it is kind of important to have somebody over your shoulder
like if you have a specific question to have somebody who can give you a specific answer.
Because everyone on the internet has a different idea of how you're supposed to get good at some sort of art
and you'll never really understand how to improve fast enough.
There is no answer.
There is no right way to do it.
I know that, but there are some fundamental things that just increase your ability to do whatever you want more and quicker.
Me, right? I went to college, but my professors did not teach me anything that I could not have read in a book, you know?
Did you go to an art college?
Yeah, I had the books, I had the textbooks, and the professors told me the same stuff.
I thought you got a calculus degree or something. I thought you got like a physics degree.
Yeah, you didn't go to art college. You went to liberal arts.
I have some experience with college as well.
First year college, something, art and design, I think.
And all they taught us was like the color theory and some other basic stuff that I already knew.
So it was a little underwhelming.
I don't feel like I learned anything in that year, but I might have learned something in following the year.
The thing is with, I mean, it's not good that they do this, but they have to do it, because they have a wide amount of skills.
The point of the first year is to get everybody on the same page so that they teach all the basics to people who don't know.
For those who don't know, let's go over this.
So expensive.
I know, but like...
The thing is though, I'm pretty sure I was put in the slightly above average course of art and design, because they were like levels, I think.
So I was put in the advanced ones. You think we know color theory by that point?
Well, okay. I mean, I agree with Mage. Here's where I come from.
I totally accept the value of an art education. Absolutely.
I went to college. It was a STEM, and it worked out well financially. It's not like a passion project or anything, but it worked out well.
So yeah, college totally makes sense.
But I contrast the two realities in my mind.
Okay, there's one reality where one goes to art school, works on it, and then applies for a job later, has to deal with debt for an amount of time.
Okay, fair enough, and they'll have more credentials, maybe they'll have significantly more skills who knows.
There's another path in my mind of where the same person, I don't know, gets like some meaningless job, but they're earning money as opposed to losing money.
So okay, that's cool. What about the art?
Well, what if this person in their off time, which is exactly how my YouTube career has been, has been like offline, they like work on a webcomic for four years.
And in four years, that's a pretty good amount of time to develop something cool, or maybe not even one thing, but like lots of stuff.
Like they invest their creative energies independently, and they work in that way.
So they're not taking on any debt. And in four years, you can probably make some pretty good stuff.
And I totally accept that you won't get the kind of professor one-on-one exchange thing there, but comparing those two futures, I don't know.
I think that's the ideal situation, in the sense that I don't think that that can apply to not just me, but like the general public.
A person who just tries to draw a lot, while obviously practice is the best way to practice, you still are not going to be able to get the same sort of success
or the same sort of understanding that you would have if you teach yourself.
You could teach yourself on the internet, or you could teach yourself with a professor and you pay for it.
I mean, if you've seen like a lot of certain DeviantArt accounts, where they just draw the same thing over and over,
they are drawing a lot of stuff, but they are not getting better at drawing.
They are getting better at drawing the one thing that they think they know how to draw.
It's important to get advice from lots of different people.
And one of the more direct and powerful...
I mean, it depends on the college, obviously.
I had a good college and it had a good track record, and the lecturers and the people there were really cool
and well connected to important people, like the new people from Aardman and stuff.
It depends on the professors, but it is invaluable if you want that.
It's worth the debt.
Will you be saying that in five years, though, when it's still there, looming?
That's the horror show. That's the true Halloween spook.
The horror of debt is what I live and feel.
I'm out of it, man. Thank God.
But only because I was in the STEM field that pays really well.
I want to ask, because I don't really know how the debt works in America.
How did it work for you? What did it do that made your life bad?
Well, it is a financial burden for some out of time.
In America, I believe the way it works when you take a federal student loan is...
If you want to, you can call them up and be like,
hey guys, can't pay, please just delay me paying entirely.
You get three years of that total that you can split up.
If you lose a job, you get another job.
After that point, you do have to pay it, and if you don't, I don't know what happens, but something bad.
But when you are paying, they work with you and they budget, I think, based on your income,
how much you're going to pay.
But you are continually racking up interest, so you might not even touch the premium or the base or whatever.
It's going to take a long time. The less you earn, the less you're paying into it, the longer it's going to stretch out.
Possibly, probably not forever, but I don't know, a really long time.
So there is an expectation that you will start paying after some amount of time.
I don't think it matters if you make literally zero money.
There's a time when the time runs out and you have to start paying in some amount that they decide with you.
I've refinanced a bunch when I still had the debt and I'm no hero.
Why don't I hear anything?
I don't know.
How are you responding if you can't hear this?
Headphones issues? He's probably just talking to himself.
Yeah, it's funny.
Well, whatever. That was the point. You do have to pay eventually, even if you don't earn enough.
I don't know what happens if you just literally can't.
I know that they'll garnish your wages or something, they'll directly just take the money after a while if you get any job.
So that's the basic gist, I think.
I don't know why that is like...
I mean, maybe they can, but they can't just take all of your money so that you just starve to death.
I mean, I don't know.
Presumably, that's the worst case scenario.
If you get some shitty minimum wage job and your degree counts for nothing, as is the case for a lot of people.
Does the money just keep getting drained and then they get beaten by the police and then they die in the streets?
Does that actually happen? Or is that just what they scare you with?
Maybe to some people. Here's the actual thing to be scared of.
This is the actual thing to scare you on this Halloween night, ladies and gentlemen.
It is pretty scary.
It is pretty scary, but more realistic is it's years later, whatever, you've got your debt, you have a job.
The real terror is that you're not able to get the job you want.
And so you're forced to take some other job doing, you know, like so many baristas working at Starbucks, paying off their thing.
Well, will people turn you away if you have debt?
Sorry, what?
No.
Will a job turn you away if you have student loan debt?
No, I mean, they don't care if you have debt or not, they'll employ you.
But like, what's scary is just that your education didn't really give you like a guarantee of a job.
And then you aren't able to get the great job that you want.
Yeah, but this is alright.
And so you have to take a shittier one.
Yeah, but this is different.
That's not the problem with having debt.
The problem with having debt is that your credit will be bad and you won't be able to get a loan.
I'm painting a picture. There's that.
And then on top of that, you aren't able to live a great life because your wages are getting garnished
because you have to pay off a certain amount of your debt so that your total take-home income is like pennies.
And you have to live in a shitty place.
You can't have the kind of life you want.
Your wages are getting garnished.
Your wages are getting garnished, but that's just you paying what you were supposed to be paying in the first place, right?
In this case, yeah, that's what I'm framing it as.
For your debt.
But they will literally garnish your wages after a certain amount of time though and just take it off the top.
The reason I bring up all of this is because I just want the best future for you much because I care about you and I like you.
Thank you. I appreciate it, Nate.
And that's why I bring all this up.
I'm not mad. Obviously, I'm defending myself.
I'm kind of challenging your life decisions, which I understand is a sensitive kind of topic here.
Well, I mean, it's fine. I just haven't heard anything that's made me change my mind, you know?
Do you fear being naive because I fear that all the time about myself?
Sure, sure. I fear that maybe I won't be able to get an industry job.
And I don't think that will be the case, but I'm prepared and sure that will suck.
But I feel like there's a distinction here that, wow, things might not go my way when I'm out of school.
And, you know, sure, I will have debt and that's not good.
And you don't need to have debt. That's not a natural part of life. It's bad.
Yeah, yeah.
And I might not be able to get an industry job.
But the lessons that I will learn in college can't be taken away from me.
I can't ever lose the academic or the skills that I learned there.
I won't be, no one will be able to take away the social interactions that I have.
No one will be able to take away the experiences that I accrue.
And no one will be able to take away the friends that I meet.
That's technically true of anything, though.
Yeah, when you're gathered around the fire in the dumpster with the other homeless people
scraping the last bean out of the can, no one can take that experience away from you guys.
Yeah, that's yours forever.
I mean, yes. That's not an experience I would want.
So these are experiences that I want.
Yeah, it's technically true that I can have fun without college.
Do you see my reasoning?
It's not even about having fun.
It's about any experience you have is something that can never be taken away from you.
Okay, I wasn't speaking literally.
I don't think they can reach to my brain and take my memories.
Okay, well, here's a more relevant example.
What don't you have as college days?
You don't have to just resign like, okay, Munchy, you know, you're making a bad choice, but don't do it.
No, I'm not resigning. I'm just saying, we've been talking about this for like how many, 20 minutes, 25 minutes.
This is an interesting goddamn topic in my humble opinion.
Well, you're not going to change Munchy's mind.
Well, I don't want to phrase it like that.
I mean, I can listen to reason.
Mage, debates, if this even counts as a debate, are an attempt to convince the audience.
No, we just got to let the baby have his bottle, Mage.
It just, okay, last thing I'll say is it just reminds me of, especially that last stuff you were saying,
on Kanye's album, I think it's late registration.
There's a bunch of skits, or it might be college dropout or whatever, where he's just like,
my dad got so many degrees.
Well, me and mom were starving in the street.
My Christ, he had so many fucking degrees, and he kept going back for more degrees,
and he loved those degrees.
And when I have his degrees now, and I'm going to pass those degrees on to my children,
and when they had burned them from worth, we're going to think, wow, our dad was so educated.
It was so great.
All right, that's a joke, but that's a hyperbolic example of the story here.
Am I okay?
America's fucking scary.
I agree.
I don't really know how that relates to me, in a way.
Because you were talking about how the inherent worth of the degree, which I would argue is objectively false.
I think the value comes within the four years that I'm in college.
I think that's where the true worth of it will lie.
I think the only value in a college education is what it gives you afterward.
That is my humble opinion.
Yeah, the skills increased faster than they would have otherwise been increased.
For the cost of a huge amount of debt, or maybe a little if you go to like community college.
I mean, I don't know.
Oh, lay an egg.
That's important, goddamn it.
It's important, Nate.
I don't disagree with you at all.
I don't know if you guys are trading, Nate.
Like, he's just being a big old scrooge over here.
I know.
He's sensible, but it's just like, clearly, Munchie is going to get more out of college than most,
because he very much wants that.
Why do you assume that?
To get a lot out of it.
Yeah, why do you assume that?
Well, compared to people I've seen in college who just go because their parents told them
to, and they don't really know what they're doing, they rack up debt, they go to college,
and they don't really try very hard because they think of it as just school, and then
they leave college with big debt, and they're like, oh no, I don't have any skills because
they didn't try very hard.
Munchie clearly wants to do this.
So, he's going to get a lot of skill, art skills out of this, regardless of whether he gets
like a job in the industry or not.
He can apply that to like anything he wants to do.
I think that that drive that is like, yeah, he will do good in school and get a lot out
of it because of his attitude.
I think that attitude would serve him well in any, like whatever path he chose, right?
I don't understand...
It would serve him...
Sorry, I'm sorry.
I can finish.
I'm sorry.
It would serve him just as well if he decided not to go to college and just work on his own
stuff, like that attitude would still be there, and that's what it's about, right?
It's about your fucking attitude more so than whether you go to college or not.
In my humble opinion...
Sure.
You guys don't have to walk on eggshells as much.
I'm not going to get mad.
I mean, I fully expect in your minds thinking that I'm retarded, like I don't...
Like it's obvious, but...
All I care about is that it's worth the investment.
That's the only thing I care about at the end of the day.
I don't claim to have...
I don't claim to know the right answer for everyone, but I wouldn't do it.
Hold on.
HELL, on.
paying the money like I'm just doing the work I was doing it's also worth it to
mention that I have a man on the inside and I'm not oh shit I'm not going into
this line not only have I researched extensively the college I'm planning to
apply for and I vetted it with all my little toes and hands with my
grippy little hands but also uh Kazi goes there now and everything she tells
me is good and it sounds great all the hard homework all of the fucking like
like weird out there stuff that they teach you would normally think to do it
all sounds like you know good stuff like stuff that I want to learn learn
stuff that I want to be able to know that you can't find like a YouTube how-to
to do so what you tell me munchie is you're going there for a girl all right
throw it in the trash wasting time there goes the money everybody I'm Ben wait
before I'm sorry Nate Nate do you think that actually literally no okay
you know what it probably is part of the equation well okay I'll try like this
Kazi being in Boston is one of the reasons I want to be in Boston but not
one of the reasons I want to go to college I'll phrase it like that okay also
by the way one of the reason I want to go to college is so that I can fucking
form PCPHQ more by the way that's one of the reasons I value your financial
future more than the formation of PCPHQ at least where you are concerned yeah so
yeah everything I say stands it would sure be convenient for me to encourage
you and to go into massive debt so that you'd be around to work with me and yet
I don't so I appreciate me I don't have I'm glad that you've been willing to
challenge me in such a way well good I'm the dad just to be hard but fair to
lay the truth's on the line as I see them maybe I'm wrong in fact I appreciate
research and you looked into things and you know what the curriculum is that's
very encourage I mean I'm obviously like not as aware of like the the money
ramifications because for me the debt is not really an issue yet and it won't be
a big issue ever yeah well no no no no I can just say Britain adults pass on to
their children at their debt is it sure nice no I'm kidding I assume low I can
just I could just you know just throw it in the trash you also just like throw
taxes in the trash if I recall correctly there's like ladies debts that you have
to pay and just don't do this you weren't thinking of Jesse with that sounds
like a Jesse thing I'm sure Jesse as well I'm sure Jesse as well when what
there's some sort of payment that we were that you were talking about unlike I
think it was a shekels for heckles that like you just don't pay some money thing
I forget what it is damn sounds like what a great like a ticket what a promised
land like a what a ticket or something Nate you remember right yeah give there
was something you were talking about some fee to be like on some like housing
thing that you had to pay but you hadn't been paying oh well no I didn't had to
pay it was the government that mixed up the forms and they said I had to pay and
I was really mad it was it was it was it was council tax yeah that sounds right
but I didn't have to pay council tax because I was a student living in the
house but the they they mixed they mixed it up like something went wrong and I
thought I wasn't a student and then angry letters and I threw them in the trash
and then they sent me a court summons and I threw that in the trash and they
never did anything and that all worked out because they can't they don't have
the money to look for me right and I'm long gone I'm fucking long I'm out of
there okay what I'm about to say is not to de-legitimize this conversation
because this conversation has been fruitful and productive but I will say
that like I have been in the PCP for a while now I've listened to the school
sucks podcast I really want to emphasize that I'm not going into this blind or
with way crazy expectations of what I will accomplish I'm talking a lot about
experiences and and industry jobs and stuff like that but I realize that the
future is not as smooth as I would like to think about it and I realize that
there will be trials and tribulations both in school and out but I am taking
what I believe to be an educated decision maybe not the best decision but an
educated decision nonetheless and I have weighed the pros and cons more than I
feel my contemporary ill cap not you guys but I mean like you know like
like millennials at large I feel like I have done more research and am more
confident in that this is a sustainable idea more so than might be normal and I
not trying to say that guys like I know what I'm doing don't talk to me that's
not what I mean I just mean to remind everyone that there might it's
specifically in the comments there might be some offshoot that was talked about
in school sucks that we haven't addressed but I know I know feel free to
comment but like I know I know I always said that college is definitely right
for some people and that could certainly be the case here so you know yeah not I
mean I'm definitely not gonna sit here and say don't do it cuz I like I I went
to college and never used my degree and I'm still in debt over it and I don't
even really care that much I don't even necessarily think it was bad because it
was just like some good years of my life and I like the person that I ended up
being so I guess it all worked out I don't know
yeah my gripes was the first year I had in college it was a pretty good year I
met one of my bestest friends ever there and it was it was funny it was a fun
year yeah see this is why I was supportive of what when she came to me
and told me he was doing it and like he seemed very serious about it like
clearly like there is gonna be good that comes of it even if like the debt is
one thing obviously there's gonna be that to deal with but like everyone who has
debt seems to be okay this whole distance break I think it's gonna be a
bad I know I said I won't be that long of time relatively but that doesn't mean
that it won't be that that it is like fine I totally accept that I am more
financially kind of concerned than your average person my age I'm not gonna say
that I'm great it's just I do worry about it a lot and care about it a lot
being having my future secure financially so you know fair enough fair
enough I get it but I'm not when I fucking leave my job and go full-time
YouTube which is all I think about and you know okay okay this is sort of
tangentially related Nate why do you want to become a youtuber like because
it is the most rewarding experience I've ever had that's why it's scary and I
completely agree because when I when I go to work it's fine when I come home and
work on my projects I feel alive and I love it okay I mean I mean I mean I yeah
I mean and this is in no way me saying don't become a youtuber or that's
negative whatsoever feel free to challenge it you know it just sounds like
like YouTube is just constantly getting fucked so I just I really all I want to
know is what's the experience like like how do you feel as someone who has a
sustainable job that wants to enter at not an unsustainable job but a
fluctuating job does that concern you has that entered your thoughts at all
absolutely there's a major difference with me versus other people which is me
I'm coming into this thing like my whole last couple years has been paying off my
debt building up my financial reserves so then I can make an honest to goodness
serious long-term attempt to make it on YouTube and if that fails have a
contingency to go back which is that that is what I've been building towards so
right I don't think the risks are very high for me at all and like YouTube might
it I might not even fail it just will turn out that YouTube is not as look at it
not as fun anymore you know yeah or not as fun in which case I will be you know
prepared I have a degree in a in a in a good field I've had a job I've got a
resume of work that I can fall back on and use and and find another job if
necessary and like my YouTube career has been honestly going fine with it as a
part-time job and I could continue to do that it's just that I know I would be so
much more like productive and you know and successful like even if I don't even
if I fail like to make it big time as a YouTuber like I could do better than I'm
doing right now because all my time is you know taken up by you know normal job
so like do I worry about YouTube in general failing absolutely I do think
that I am more willing to adapt and change like like for example all this
copyright shit's going on right now I'm gonna I will I will adapt to what's
necessary we Agua itself was a big adaptation to try to figure out how to
survive on YouTube doing we Agua consistently was by far the most
lucrative period for my channel so I know what to do and that's what I would do
instantly when I go full-time doing it like maybe YouTube will just find my
content objectionable and fail and you know I'll have to like stop doing it
entirely because everything will close down except for like Jimmy Kimmel and
shit it's possible it's possible and at that point I will I will just always like
if I if I go full-time YouTube I'm just gonna always try to make sure after I've
got this idea of like I'll do it for a year if it's going well I'll keep doing
it after that point I will switch plans to make sure I have enough money that if
things go belly-up I can survive long enough to you know switch out and get
back to a normal job and survive on that and then I'll you know that that's what
I'll do let me ask you this would you consider yourself to be that you want
to be a YouTube creator or like an internet creator would you be fine
moving to different platforms or is this platform specifically something that
you are invested in you want to become a video content creator on YouTube I have
found the most joy specifically making video content and so I would like to
stay in that that medium it's kind of my field of expertise but I feel no
particular allegiance to YouTube itself it's just that YouTube does create a
specific kind of ecosystem that you know like my kind of content does fairly
well on and I hope to you know expand and keep trying it so I wouldn't say I'm
inherently like I like if Vimeo took over I wouldn't really care I just keep
doing what I'm doing and just hope that you know people are still able to find
my shit and I can spread it around so you know hopefully that answers the
question yeah okay and this really is a scary episode I'm thinking of my future
now yeah what a dude what am I doing it's like I got a cool like I got a cool
comic and that'll be that and I like I have patreon people who like that and
that's nice and the progress news podcast yeah hippo beyond that I don't
really have anything hippo I think you have a way brighter future ahead of you
than you may industry kind of connections and career you're working on well
there's that yes I mean I'm pretty good at that so I'm sure that I will continue
to have work in the field of writing hippo whether or not you want to do it I
just want to say how like unbelievably aesthetic and like proud of you and like
just how giddy it makes me you just giving us even cursory information about
the industry job that you're working in I think it's so cool it's such it's so
romantic it's just everything that I would want to be in my life it is
romantic here we are being like um sorted online sucks guys meanwhile Gib is
making sorted online yeah wait wait hippo can you sell us exclusive rights for
the first slam negative review of your work oh yeah the so-and-so project
exposed yeah I want that I want the rights yeah I'll have to shop around a
little bit first okay yeah get the highest bed but like like when you say
romantic it is very much like cuz like a few months ago well earlier this year
I was asked to come to an animation festival in France yeah I think I may
have mentioned this somewhere I definitely mentioned it on my patreon
podcast patreon.com slash hypocrite well tell them the name the money
spenders by the money spenders podcast can I get a link to those and not yeah
thank you sure I am a patron but I have not listened to the last
couple I should I should catch up yeah so I mentioned that like I was just last
minute my my the director of the show we were pitching said just just come to
to France to Anisee and do this animation festival I'm doing a talk or like no
we're gonna meet the producer I want you to meet the producer of the thing I'm
like oh shit fine I've never like this is like last minute fly the first time
I've not had a flight booked in advance so I just quickly got a flight it wasn't
that expensive I flew down there and I was you know I think I told the story
about how I got lost in Sweden or something yeah yeah but like when I
was there like for the couple days I was there it was just so it was such a
really tiny picturesque like French city next to the Alps there's a huge lake
and there was an animation festival and those people and we like we were just
walking around these old cobbled streets and like I met the producer we had dinner
with him and then later during the night we had like pizza and like a Italian
French restaurant like weird thing and it was just McDonald's sorry and it was
like like nice pizza it was like yeah this is this is like I'm on holiday but
this is a work thing this is the first time I felt this cool in my life it is
really cool thing to do and if I were you I would lean into that but I don't know
your employer looking for someone to do the same job you do but better and for
free no no no free yes and recommend me do they looking for more are they
looking for more use can I be another you please if you live in London then
yeah that's where we have we have meetings every barf my right hello
Marifat I don't know if I've talked about this all and there's no reason for me
to because it's not gonna be like a big deal but I'm just excited about it a
lot and I just like thinking about it and I like talking about it because it's
gonna be cool I'm going to see about this summer is a thing that's happening
like yeah and like not a joke or like oh yeah like why why why would you ever do
that because I like him a lot he's my favorite I like him so much have you
ever left the country before wait oh god you went to Italy yeah that's right I'm
stupid yeah okay I fucking don't laugh at me I'm saving up I'm saving up my own
gosh dang money I've got I've got a whole plan I know how much I have to save
each month so you are you are personally financing a trip to the UK
specifically to see hippo um yes for the most part well specific to see London
and stuff dude hippo I'm gonna drag you to so much gay historical stuff you're
not even gonna you're gonna hate you're gonna know yeah much she's gonna
get there and be like hey hippo you don't appreciate your own culture as much
as I do let me appreciate it for you I'm gonna show you the real the real the real
London yeah this is where James Cromwell pissed his pants I just want to
lick it right up yeah well that's all very good episode no now on to onto the
topic at hand Halloween yeah yeah I have I have some scary joke from last time
where I breathe we briefly had a little spat a little fight about like Jack
O'Lanterns shaved or cut right right I've solidified my my problems with
shaved Jack O'Lanterns good okay they are they are technically impressive but
more often than not they are just a copy of a photograph or a piece of other
yeah draw that's true that's true that's strike one strike two is that they're so
often not Halloween themed like if it was a spooky skull etched into a pumpkin
then it'll be like oh cool you know Halloween themed it's a spooky scary
month you put spooky scary things on pumpkins pumpkins themselves are not
spooky if you draw a tiger on they are festive the pumpkin aspect I suppose the
pumpkin is like a timely of the year but like it's not spooky you got to make it
spooky that's the whole point is like the tree during Christmas but you have
to decorate it's it's it's a bunch of pumpkins on your Christmas tree it's
gonna be like what the fog like like if you like shave like a photograph of a
tiger or like a legend of Zelda image skyward sword or whatever the fucking
breath the wild yeah but like oh I'm a epic gamer you put that dude on a pumpkin
the equivalent is to like decorate your Christmas tree with like legend of Zelda
gamer Mario I hate that though it makes me sad dude that'd be so fucking or even
funnier just to have a tiger themed Christmas just have to brief aside
brief aside when I worked at Astor Camp there was a slightly older guy working
there and that I say slightly older he was like in his 30 he was slightly older
than me okay and he it like had used to be a teacher whatever but he had changed
jobs but that's not the point the point is that like you know we we had like a
pool area there was like a lifeguard zone so you know we there was a locker
room and we were changing in there one time and he can't behind you and start
touching things he shouldn't do that's not right and he was like I learned this
in the public school he had he had two tattoos on his back one of them was on
his shoulder blade and it was a small kind of crude profile drawing of a tiger
and the other was like a bigger sort of maybe like maybe six or eight inches it
was kind of like a big thing of like like it was a like a tiger's face and claw
like tearing a hole you know what I mean yeah I hate those so stupid those
are reprehensible yeah he was it was a tiger to and I was like why do you have
these two tiger tattoos and he was just like I just really like tigers he had
gotten the smaller one when he was like a teenager and then later on he had like
treated himself to like the bigger like superior like really cool one or
whatever treated himself wait what he just treated himself like that's like
his little oh no cake for me tonight I'll just get this big man he was like
when he turned 30 or something or some milestone he was like you know what it's
time for me to get a new tiger tattoo to upgrade can you imagine what you're gonna
get it for what's he gonna get at 40 that's gonna be at 40 he's gonna get a
tuger which is a two-headed tiger oh god that's anyway what I don't even
remember what story did I interrupt with that so wait wait wait wait at three
headed tiger would be a trigger that that that that that that that that that that
that that be a trigon yeah I don't know what we were oh I just like the pumpkins
and stuff yeah you guys like those those pictures of my mom's pumpkins from last
week oh let me let me see let me see I'm talking to the audience because they
saw it but they were cool they were cool um I want I want I want anime themed
pumpkins this year as I always do maybe like a maybe like soul eater that's I
can keep it relevant I can do it it's a good show for Halloween boys um hey um so
I was talking to a Kazi actually about Halloween and she somewhat convinced me
about Halloween and her argument was pretty good she was like she said it's
a hot because you know I've said that I don't care for Halloween very much but
she said like Ben Halloween is a holiday where you don't have to do any like dumb
family shit it's just about like hanging out with your friends and having it's
just about having fun and nothing else and I was like well that's uh huh what as
an adult I suppose that's true and I was like you know that's fair that is good
about it and I do like that but it's not the only holiday like that like I would
say that St. Patrick's Day is pretty much the same like you don't digi likes
New Year's cuz New Year's is kind of like that yeah I don't really I don't
really like any of the specific like details that come with Halloween I don't
like spooky shit I don't like horror movies I don't I don't love these the
Halloween aesthetic it's fine I don't watch the extra I don't hate the
like I don't love it either and watch the exorcist you will you will love it I
think you will love it legitimately it's like not scary and it's all Christ II
and shit wait really your aesthetic yeah huh it's really good I watched it
last night and I love okay all right you would enjoy it very much it's like a
horror movie that there's no jump scares it just is occasionally there's creepy
shit and there is some absolutely disgusting moments but they're good and
I like them and most importantly is that there's a there's a sensation that this
movie is from the 70s and they throw out like fuck and cunt and in tasteful
ways that to us are totally tame but to those people it's like the actual words
of the devil and I love that aesthetic it feels great it's awesome it's the one
with the spinning head girl that's the one yeah it sucks cocks and hell yeah
yeah I should watch The Shining I've never seen The Shining the Shining is my
literal favorite scary movie it is absolutely ball dropping terrifying
wait I'm a zoomer right yeah you are okay as a zoomer as a proud zoomer who is
proud of my heritage I cannot wait for your shitty old people movies to fucking
die and for creepyposses to take over as the rightful Halloween material the
true creepypasta munchie munchie well when he's old crack open like like a
coconut water like zero yeah whatever he'll sip it gingerly at age 35 and
say crack open Jane activity 10 now there was a movie I can't fucking wait for
like and like a real movie of a creepypasta where a guy buys an n64 game
and there's something wrong with it okay because because nostalgia nostalgia
like plundering dictates that somebody will think that's a good idea Nate the
paranormal activity thing like yeah you what are we on what paranormal
activity or maybe or something okay well how likely do you think it is
because people do this for fast and furious and maybe it's true I don't
know because I haven't seen them but what if like five or six fat of paranormal
activities from now zoomers on YouTube are making the case like here's the case
for paranormal activity and how after number 10 they became a like metatextual
commentary on their own John we'll achieve the and achieve the pinnacle of
what hard the horror genre is capable of that will definitely happen I mean
that's not even that unlikely to happen because after a while you're almost more
likely to try something different and like do okay then just do the same thing
over and over by the way there there have been six official ones and there's
one unofficial film called a paranormal activity to Tokyo night one of my
you mean Tokyo night with the K right unfortunately not one of my favorite
experiences of being alive like one of the best times I like like like like
intervals of time that I've ever breathed in my entire life was I went to
see the slender man movie recently in theaters with my friend Kyle my friend
and as all diehard diehard bobble horn its fans it was so good to see slender
man and just know that life will never be the same and that I shouldn't feel
myself really upon leaving the theater it was great and okay okay aside from that
and something the legendary experience of slingy scene slender man completely
messed misrepresented and interpreted and literally they just saw the fucking
character designs like I'm gonna make a movie about this aside from all that
for the next fucking like hour and a half it was just one after another it was
us making a joke that there would be a creepy pasta cinema universe and it was
us coming up with after-credits scenes for different creepy pasta so it's like
the main characters to drive the slender man movie she would walk into a bar all
wistfully and like there would be no music and she would go over a guy with a
hood over his head and she'd be like I hear you're good at killing and then
and then he would turn slightly and he would say well I am Jeff the killer and
then the credits would roll there was a fucking Freddy versus Jason movie so
it's inevitable there's inevitably a fucking slender man versus that black
Pokemon cartridge the girl gets on playing like I'm so glad to be rid of
slender man I'm so ready to have that chapter my life be over oh time to get
on a vacation hmm that that or like kind of have a vacation goes to Orlando
Florida you know I like Disney World but what's this abandoned river country hmm
I sure hope I don't get abandoned by Disney credits roll
I don't know what that one is actually I watched I watched this as Fuki sort of
kind of anime like that's the one did you like recommended to me forever ago
angels of death I think yeah I finally finished watching it and like I kind of
liked it at the beginning I really like it gave me sort of a bit of a dangin
rope I feels but then I hated it by the end it fuck did you your predictions are
all shit guess you guys should watch you guys should watch Ultimate Survivor
Kaiji because it's the scariest of all because what it says about capitalism in
our financial system hey Ben we're watching as cry it for Jimmy Bacchus
soon oh you want to do that on Tuesday uh to hang on wait the bonus PCP is
recording on Tuesday we would have to do it before before the bonus PCP which
yeah that's fine before that I could do six p.m. it's on Tuesday yeah sure I can
do that hey guys quick quick question have you have you started watching
zombie lens did you just did you just spoil the next thing you just spoil the
next Chibi Bacchus it'll come out after much it'd be recorded it might not be
released yet but we'll I don't care I don't think it's like a spoiler I think
we said that on the last episode anyway I think we announce the next I don't think
on earth gives a shit about s cry yeah except me except I said yeah you and me
Nate you and me I remember yeah I already disperposed to hate it because
it's called s cried and there's no way it has the worst name of any really bad
name it doesn't I like I haven't read the mind I and I thought and I thought the
procrastinators was a bad name for a whole new level a major major
mention zombie land saga relevant to to current Halloween anime what do you
think mage I like it I really liked it I mean I never liked idle enemies but I
really love this one looks legitimately good kind of it also has me in it for
those who aren't aware there's a big meme literally means in this anime and I
guess you meant IDOL but I was thinking like idle anime is like an idle game
like one that you just let run in the background yeah yeah you don't even have
to listen to it or watch they're gonna make the cookie clicker anime that's what
I want you or teal listen or teal license cookie clicker right now oh my god
I'm playing cookie clicker right now I forgot there's a legit are you really is
that true yeah I started up today no reason I had cookie clicker open for a
couple of weeks there like maybe as of a month ago I it was just open on my
desktop for weeks and weeks I had a bunch of add-ons that basically played the
game for me right pretty much the only thing I had to do was the gardening
minigame I've never played that I don't know what the fuck that is yeah it's
it's one of the later additions there is you can you you have well you have to
grow sugar lumps and you spend your sugar lumps to upgrade your farms and
once you spend them on your farms you have plots of dirt and you have to you
have to like find seeds and plant seeds and hope they cross pollinate into new
seeds in order to get more seeds in order to get more sugar lumps in order to
grow more cookies you see because it all comes back to the cookie cookie clicker
is a great game and it is it is on a on ironically no lean it is a great game and
the lore is honestly pretty damn good I could honestly see some kind of like
lore product being made based off of cookie clicker it is fucking great on the
on the one hand it's like I get it it's a elder tar the grandma's but on the
other hand it's like fucking sick dude like fucking yes I love it yeah I don't
know perhaps a little thin but whatever I still like it I don't know I do love it
it's it's it's it's it's the effort was just the way that he boldly that he boldly
filled his uh his fucking idle his idle clicker game with this this like huge
he vast array of like dumb cliches this like it has this big fucking weird yeah like story
going on it's sort of in the background uh and it just fucking spirals uh I love love cookie
clicker man guys I love thinking about it I love that it exists I should probably do a youtube
analysis video of it do not steal that from me I that's that's the best idea I've ever had um yeah
we uh uh we we gotta wrap this up guys the pokemon event is only two more hours and I
have to get out there oh my god yeah this is a juicy ass episode that I'm loving but I think we
should just yeah we've been going an hour and a half I just want to say that I had a topic
and it was like I like I went on a trip to Denver recently not like a fun trip to idly but like a
like oh it's like a family like okay I'm sure yeah yeah I have come uh I have a lot to say
about that but I wish I had to do that next time on the pro yeah that's how it goes sometimes I mean
I want to hear about it only an hour well well I guess we have questions we yeah we got quite
that'll take a half an hour probably oh oh have we decided to not do text questions are we doing
text questions or we have weeded out I am adamantly anti text questions that yeah that's
where we're that's where we're at right now yeah I haven't heard a good argument to really bring
him back so uh yep yeah that's okay cool all right well uh let's let's get right the fuck into it
um here we go people uh uh uh uh by the way I want to hear some voicemails about the huge
cataclysm earth shattering event that is the max revival of the pcp guy so uh you know let let us
know oh god he's still there he's oh my god he's still alive pcp guy what do you think about me
going to college I never I can't hear you piece piece wow he just speaks and all pcp guy does is
just speak in swarms of flies he he he he talks like the adults in Charlie Brown yeah yeah he's
procrastinating on forming actual words with his sounds you know whenever he opens his mouth to like
like have air exit his lungs he just has flies and said they just swarm they're like lotus is they
just he's an avatar of procrastination yeah yeah uh all right let's let's get our first one he's a good
boy in a word indeed here's our first one we got 12 I prepared 12 this time a little bit more but
whatever uh first one like final fantasy 12 oh my god my favorite game not a bad here we go AFY
and why pony uh I wish we were only dealing with a ladder is just and why wait I want to
talk about wait before we go on I want to talk remember the remember the me too video yeah of
course by who okay I was talking about the other day wait really don't say it don't say who it is
because last time oh yes yep yep yep okay yeah but okay I went back and listened to it again
because something about it creeped me out right I found I found the video I think I know exactly
and I went back and I yeah yeah okay it is halloween I'm spooked the thing okay so ostensibly the
video is about how what she was quote unquote abused or harassed by this guy she tells the story
and it's not what happened like just that is just not the story that she tells even though she claims
that it is yeah um but there's there's more right because like the setup to the story like what she
says happened is that she got on a call with you know the the the the villain the supposed
villain of the story um and she quote showed off for it right oh no but you go back and you listen
to the context that sets up this and what she says is that she was in a call with with an y pony
right and um it was his birthday it was his birthday yeah it was a birthday call for an y pony
and she says this with like a little giggle she's like tee he you know yeah you know how it is guys
she says we were on a call and me and the girl me and the other girls were giggle showing off yeah
what does that mean okay what kind of a fucking birthday is this so all these bronies get together
and have their girlfriends show their tits to yeah all right they might have done it to to the
birthday they might all just be sluts that's definitely possible I don't think it's okay I think
it's probably likely for bronies just to think that that's okay to do it's is that I mean yeah I
I listened to this I listened to this and it was like I was gobsmacked right like I went on a long
walk and like a sad song played like I looked out a window into the rainy night and I just thought
about my life and I was like it was who's who's crazy someone's crazy here and I and I and I think
maybe it's me maybe maybe I'm some kind of weird puritanical weirdo to like hear this story and
be creeped out by it like maybe I need to check my privilege and fucking realize that I live in 2018
and everybody's trans and poly now and there are no and they're and God is dead and there is no
objective morality and nothing is not true and nothing is good no no no no no I was I was jealous
I wanted to be a and wise birthday on my birthday this is why I hate having left the fandom you
guys I could get all that bronies we gotta go back we have to go back there's so many no they're doing
over there finally a good reason to go back there's so many girlfriends in that community and as you
know dating a bronie like the contract of dating one of these bronies that all on on your on your
boyfriend's friend's birthday you gotta fucking you gotta fucking show up you gotta fucking show
up and show out like the piece of meat that you are that's you will you sign the contract your
communism it's pure everyone gets a piece of everyone yeah you introduce yourself into a big
communal marriage of everyone with everyone and I mean I mean yeah yeah effectively like like
if you're dating if you're dating one bronie you're basically dating all yeah which basically means
that that what what this the me too girl did was fine because that was just part of the contract
makes they're all they're all public use I self-identify as a liberal and I would say that
I'm I'm probably liberal on a lot of social things but what I can't ever get my head around
or like appreciate is polyamory and open relationships like I can't do it it's the
one thing where I just am a fuddy duddy about it you know some people I'm sure it like I don't
want to be overly judgmental like I'm sure yeah okay there's some people who tell themselves that
it works when really they don't they'd rather they don't but I'm sure there's probably another
subset of people that like actually are fine yeah I'm sure that it's real it just feel like with
my own personal baggage it feels strange not in an open relationship obviously but you know
having maybe one it feels like what you described Nate is a real thing that is worth looking into
the idea of being an open relationship when you don't want to be in one I think that's
fucking terrifying whoa whoa whoa whoa when you when you don't want to be in one then that's
that's just cheating I'm not some people will they like rationalize to themselves that like I'm
totally okay with this honey that you go and fuck you know down the road yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
sure um here okay here's the thing here's the thing and I don't know this might be a hot take
we'll see tell me tell me if this is too hot to handle um I think I think okay I think being I think
being poly or whatever is an umbrella term but within that term there's probably like as many
ways to be poly as there are people that do kind of like kind of like being trans or being like
gender like a gender and like here there's trans people but every individual trans person like
they're not all this they're not all doing it the same way right like they don't all see they don't
all see it the same way or do it the same way and it doesn't mean the same thing to everyone at the
very least there's the trans movement that like believes in like I was born female in a male body
like I'm switching now I'm like I'm just just and then there's people who are more like fluid so
you know sure sure like the point is just that I think there's like probably a rainbow there's
probably a rainbow of different situations and attitudes that would all be that would all fall
broadly under the head of being in a quote poly relationship you know there's probably people
in there there's probably people in there who just are who just are like who don't feel you know
there's probably people in there for whom it is like a passion that they're like I like this is
what I want to do I want to I want to fuck and my partner wants to fuck and we like to fuck but
there's probably other people who are like maybe in an unhappy marriage in there but they can't
but they they don't feel they can leave it for whatever reason and so the compromise they have
reached like well let's just say we're poly now and then it's like whatever um you know I mean I
guess that's fair you know and probably there's many others that I I wouldn't I wouldn't like for
example though I wouldn't describe like let's say you got like uh like uh like in house of cards
you had like power politician couple and like they don't get divorced for one of the reasons is
they actually do love each other but they don't get divorced uh because like it'd be bad politically
so like yeah even if those people like let's say they fuck other people I wouldn't call that really
polyamory though you know I guess kind of literally is because okay if they didn't love each other
anymore just kind of a show right well kind of yeah I don't know I don't know I I haven't seen I
haven't seen how's it something that I don't like to talk about for obvious reasons but but I feel
kind of is an important distinction nay I feel very kinship with you I was also a migtau incel
yet you never want to admit that you feel so yeah yeah yeah that way lies madness
yeah I was also like like oh like I had a lot of a tortured history with with small women this
and stuff like that oh and uh and and this is the one thing from that era that I've never been
into shake is that's really weird and I don't and it makes me feel weird just thinking about what
what's the one probably amory no that's not you're not you're not weird for not being down with
with polyamory that's I think that's the vanilla okay okay I know it's the vanilla position but I
am like a cuck so like it would make sense okay I think polyamory is good but like that's the one
thing you're saying it doesn't match your progressive values what does that mean I mean
I mean that I'm like an sjw libtard and it's weird that I'm not down oh I think what you're I mean
you would never stop anyone else it's not that you're not it's not that you're not down with it
it's that you don't want it for yourself yeah yeah yeah you're right I mean I've never stopped anyone
but it just makes me feel uncomfortable when people talk like if a friend of mine okay this is
probably where we agree if a friend of mine came to me and is like hey man like like that's how I
feel whenever there's a black person okay right there you go it's it's like a friend of your
comes I was like hey dude you know hey do you want to talk listen so my girlfriend's been saying that
like she doesn't want to break up with me but like she's polyamorous and I'm like wondering if
like I should do it like maybe I'm polyamorous too dude like what I would tell them to break up right
then yeah yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah 100% uh yeah to all the to all the p the poly fans sorry I guess
look yeah like it's totally fine if you want to do it I am suspicious that you're fooling yourself
if you come into me yeah tell me that you love it but I think there is probably a lot of that
I'm not I think there's not everyone maybe not everyone but I think that there is a lot of that
is my is my impression people really want to be down you know they want to be down do you think the
majority of polyamorous relationships are of Caucasians poly want a cracker oh my god I hate you so much
he fucking got me that's like the most stretch for a pun ever you're stretching cock Asian to be the
cock of a parrot and poly to be a parrot I got it got it that's the most stretch of all there was layers
you know hey oh I'm a pirate I'm a pirate skeleton I have a parrot here the whole time this is not
even a point this is not even a point this is just a fact or a feeling or something I don't know
just fuck I'm gonna throw it out there and see if anyone cares there's a thing that I have like
read about or seen talked about the idea like like there's like real poly people right okay and that
like lifestyles or whatever and then there's like this other thing this like light version this like
this like dipping your toe into it and like thinking like tee he I'm I'm progressive or I'm different
like I'm I'm poly now sure and it's and like the real poly people hate it and it's the like
the girl right like a couple like a guy and a girl couple like getting a getting the quote
unquote unicorn to be their third or whatever and this is like this is like okay specifically I'm
thinking there's a there's a hello not not not uh what's that fucking comic with the comic uh
ojoy sex toy there's an ojoy there's a guest ojoy sex toy that is about like like here's my experience
with polyamory I fucking was best friends with these two people who dated each other and then I
dated them both two and we had sex with each other and blue sure and it's like and now I'm poly
and everything is great and I love my life and people and the response to this was like you are
just you are just a unicorn this is like this is like some fake trans shit you've been like coerced
into a threesome by like these two people like they've this is like this is bullshit this is
this is the bullshit version of our lifestyle this is like yeah yeah yeah this is this is just
some garbage that's so weird that's like bizarre and I don't understand the distinction I think I
think what it is is that I think in this situation I think this is a pretty common like a relatively
common way to be you know poly or whatever this is a relatively common way to do it but it's like
I think that the power balance is off I think the power balance is that there is two like this person
is writing like now I'm now I'm you know I'm I've found my two soulmates you know I'm in love with
my two best friends haha and and they're in love with each other but like but really there's the
couple and the other one and she's like even if she likes to tell herself other I think I think
that generally the way the way that the reason this is looked at as negative and this is not
seen as great is that the way this usually plays out is that there is the couple and the other and
this person might see herself as a part of this but really she's the other one okay and she's
and she's less that's kind of a compassionate thing like they kind of want this person to not
like trick themselves don't get her heartbroken or whatever like this is this is kind of maybe
subtly manipulative or emotionally abusive and or deceptive or something you know I don't know
people don't like that hard the hardcore lifers they read they read a story like this and they roll
their eyes and they go oh another fucking unicorn who gives a shit that's how I feel about people
who say they're gay wait no uh not me just kidding uh sorry we gotta move on quick
oh we suck guys dick oh yeah real gay just what a fucking what a poser you call that gay come on
let me show you kid this guy doesn't know about being about the hard gay you know
do just suck each other's dicks and that's that it's like a gay life without even being gay that's
lowercase g gay unless you fucking the ass that that's you're not gay your buddy let your
buddy let him fuck your ass a couple of times oh big deal like I got some stories for you
wait wait wait wait wait wait your body let him fuck your ass your butt my buddy like he let you
get all discombobulated yeah real gay dude yeah he allowed you to to fuck you well that's how
good guys I'm sure glad I'm not gay haha all right I'm glad you're not gay too I'd say like
brandishing lip brass knuckles and like uh all right here we go shall we go on to the questions
now yeah it's it's time by the way what do you think about polyamory uh yeah hopefully the question
is about that mage mage what do you think oh yeah okay weigh in it exists I I don't care to think
about it yay go ahead makes it we did it we did it we got it uh hey we got the main hot take now I'm
happy okay well good first voicemail is from from from african afy this guy is this guy I know
and he actually had his channel deleted with like 75 000 subs recently for uh well he so he made these
meme videos about um there was an elf there was like an elf character who was named stated to be 14
years old afy what what his name was afy oh yeah afy or afykun it's anime for you I think it's his
channel something like that so he got his channel like instantly removed zero strikes just gone uh
after really releasing this video about an elf character and the point of the video is that the
character is stated to be 14 but then he he humorously looks up how like elf years to human
years and she's actually like 140 or something and then he has a bunch of crabs dance and it's
funny that is the joke also she has huge tits and they're portrayed prominently in the anime so you
know whatever okay um uh uh he eventually got his channel back just congrats afy glad to hear it good
good job good job and uh let's let's hear what he asked for us today he's a great editor by the way
this guy's real good at shit so uh well let's see if he's got a good question for us go
no stop one two one two okay i thought i was gonna be christian for a second
okay did i get your attention right now i need you use the pcp so listen very carefully this
will all be done in one take and if any fuck ups will happen to occur i will get
the sounds like the hay kids ai so i need you guys to say super smash bros ultimate pcp
in a me me japanese accent all right no no wrong all right okay here we go
one super smash bros ultimate super basma oh and again i forget what i have okay it's an
undercover meme mission you'll snitch me to fucking you oh fuck
this message will self-destruct in 10 seconds
the fucking okay the eu meme band is here for him is it still going are we in 10 seconds
i'm gonna see it explode what's happened in a few seconds is it still oh there we go okay
yep just had to wait for it there it is um and we're all dead good night everybody good night
everypony well i hope that works for you afi uh wish you're best of luck i i i i wonder about
like he was using the the neon genesis a vangillian opening theme yeah like if we get content id for
that we're gonna have to mute him and then and then we get our channel then and it's a virus it's
it's an infection that spreads that is definitely possible you might be muted you might be muted
guy yeah we might have to mute you if that gets fucked up uh we'll see what we can do we'll see
what we can do um all right well good uh we gave him his thing all right next up another regular
one spar let's see what one spar has for us today the boy go he's not wolf hey pcp it's me and
got no gimmick this time just a basic hypothetical question for you which temporary video game do
you think could benefit most from a pcp themed mod pack like uh one good one that i can think of
would be a grand theft auto five story mod where you replace the three main characters with munchie
digi and nate and then you know you can have like some uh some podcast voice clips thrown in their
forum for comedic effect i think that would be great uh we'll be some other good ones uh you guys
do the work for me undertale uh uh uh uh we talked about imagine imagine undertale bonus bosses
like like bonus like like we're like someone makes us okay okay i was thinking about this
extensively earlier i don't know why ben and this is real this is true i was imagining you
was an undertale boss but it wouldn't be like you were drawn it would be like it's an fmv video
of you just like maximum black and photoshop and would just be a voice clip of you like pointing
the camera and saying stop that over and over again when you got hit and for some reason i thought
about this like for like 30 minutes i was just thinking about like yeah like how can i program this
like a little fmv like like um threshold like black and white only yeah and there would be and
since you couldn't get a perfect like wall in the background there would be a little bit of pixels
that wouldn't be able to render right and so it would be like there's like an oar of white around
yeah we should build that in minecraft as well uh minecraft it's not it's not a very new game at
this point but uh what about binding of isaac what if we there was a patch for binding of isaac
we're like with each of us and we can talk about that yeah yeah yeah pcs we gotta get we gotta get
forward and back home i want i want a mod of smash a nate would be cat and falcon i would be getting
a door sure uh then would be like some like like projectile character i don't know who though
greninja i don't know pit i hope so i hope i'd be greninja um i don't know hippo would be like
villager yeah he would be he would be rosalina and the luma would be ah oh that's a good one
that's a good one uh i'll be floating around for some reason we see who else have we got
that i can't think of any other characters yeah that's about i think that's about it for the roster
mutu uh once you would be mutu i'd play mutu i love mutu he would just be blasting psychic
energies i would be constantly transferring myself over nowhere again i could i could be
be annetta am i am i on the right game yeah yeah it's not me annetta's in there now okay she
has glasses i have glasses and that's all right oh yeah is there any other with glasses i don't
think there is i can't think of any uh yeah no i don't know only one representation for glasses
that's very discriminatory how embarrassing there might be more i can't more more i would just
wait wait i would just be pokemon trainer and i would just be oh wait wait do they is that even
a thing anymore uh yes yeah it's it is i would just be pokemon trainer and you could just change
my sprite in the background and everything else would be exactly the same yeah that's
all the pokemon have like lace chokers and like emo goth stuff on yeah i like christ tattoos
i they're all malnourished and they're covered i would fucking love um a tf2 oh my god model of
pcp of us and and then and then a special one of munchie going like um you know christ consciousness
activated like a sx oh my god yes oh my god make me a sacks and hail boss that would be
the best thing to ever happen in the ground you fucking nigga is the thing you say over and over
again yeah sacks and hail sacks and hail is a game mode where it's like one person is super
overpowered and you have to in the entire team has to take them down and really hard because you can
get one shot activated christ people have like made mods for like pinky pie being yeah yeah
running around oh dude people have made so many fucking models for like the pyro to have huge tits
and and and for all the ponies to be different uh classes dude okay okay here's the seals the fate
of this nine classes nine pcp members do the math who's who i think one oh isn't our ninth
wait no that you're right yeah you're right um um question uh i'm sniper how many i'm a sniper
how many dragons are there in skyrim have you seen the randy set or the uh the macho man
mod for the dragons in skyrim no i want to be pyro it just turns all the dragons into macho man
randy savage but like you know i was about to say skyrim dragon yeah yeah just make each of us
give me different dragons the dragons being thomas the tank engine and then they just fly around
but but i don't i don't know if there are i don't know how many dragons are in skyrim i'm assuming
more than nine probably yeah the very first dragon mod of skyrim i saw was a giant fluttershot
huh uh excellent first row yeah all right this question is getting burned into the ground let's
move on uh okay next question this is from enraged but chilling chocolate our old boy chilling
huh hey munchy hey hippo i i really love your content i really love chibi bakas is what i would
be saying if you i don't just commit a grave crime against all of the anime fandom you see
here i'm getting my papers out i i'm here to litigate you when did you brony mlp himself
challenged you to the most important thing anime rap cipher 2018 oh we're supposed to follow up on
that you're supposed to give us a sick raps but you didn't okay he's right and so it's time it's
time for you to face your proper punishment all right so munchy here's what's gonna happen
that's a good idea if you don't if if within a week of this pcp episode coming out he's making it
up there is no rap i will be forced i will absolutely have to make an account called at the
real munchy enlist as a killer and vaguely insult rowdy's hypocrite i can't do anything
unrelated to rfck but when munchies credibility is destroyed like this you're gonna be
missing out on those sweet sweet chibi baka add dollars you know you're right
we'll be down to mere sense do it you have one week hippo give me a beat integrity is everything
oh well right now right now okay i'll lay down a beat okay then you do it no no you're not part
chibi box fucking idiot hippo okay so i don't have to rap cool correct
yo i watch anime sure it may be gay but i'll do it every day hey listen i need my antidepressants
i need my well butrin sure i might be depressed but if you mess with me i'll be shooting and i'll
knock you down call me isik newton because of gravity and the force that i will use to push
you down to the fucking ground and kill you boom boom boom boom boom yeah anime raps yeah there you
go you did it now we can use the n word box it did the trick just just increase the gain massively
and make it really fast okay uh just speed it up chipmunk style there it is
i'll it lasts like three seconds it was long enough all right here we go next one's from help
help we're sending in a message all right where's your brother kelp i have this friend
she's basically the definition of a pcp fan she's bi she watches anime she draws uh and knows about
internet shit but introduce me the only thing that's not right is that she doesn't work in pcp
how do i convince her to watch the pcp this is a good question well okay okay did she not like the
pcp she does not know about it he says that she doesn't watch we also like an i okay and there
there are people who draw in the pcp really relate really yeah yeah this is actually a pretty good
question because there might be people out there who love us and love our stuff and want to introduce
us to other people but don't know how i feel like this might be fairly common i agree like a fairly
common problem uh okay just throwing this out there let me know what you think i mean i think you
should the way to introduce the pcp would probably be through one of the not one of the other things
one of us have done right like show them like i don't know show them like uh fucking you know
best uh best anime ever take a good top of gurnlog and if that's their jam or if that's their jam
or show them you know the ben's ben ben's ain't nuzlocke conquest if that's if that's what they're
into or you know or or punk or something or just or like the ghibli curse that's quite yeah yeah yeah
or the ghibli cast you know or maybe some of the radcon stuff any of the lectures the point of
the entry oh yeah the lecture they need an entry point the p the pcp is not an entry point the pcp
is the end point the pcp is the end of all things once you're you want you you've only you only
arrive here once you've circled the drain and finally been pulled down he's right uh so you
have to start the process you have to get that penny wobbling as it spins on that uh you know
tourist thing where you put a penny in and it goes around the circle many many times you got to get
that penny put in there before it goes down there so find some some video yeah don't think about like
uh i need them listening to the pcp right now you've got to you've got to hook them
so start with a video of any of the pcp related stuff that they'd be into that you think hook them
with something by one of us yeah that is their thing and you think they would like like what
what did you what did you like about from us that got you into maybe show them that i don't know
yeah good idea yeah that's a good question that now that that's actually useful uh yeah good excellent
okay and everyone should do that everyone should be thinking all the time about how to get all
their friends into the pcp and us mostly me uh all right here we go next one this is from
furniture is a scam by tar buck transom is the full name okay go furniture is a scam and i don't
mean that in the ben saint way where your home decor should be chinese takeout cartons you've
scavenged from other people's trash think back to the sturdiest comfiest couch you've ever had
on the inside that was made of the cheapest garbage wood they can find and then badly
stapled together and i mean that is literally as possible that shelving unit against your wall
right now it's made of particle board which if you didn't know is literally just sawdust and glue
i literally have a particle board so here you say well look at the underside it's particle board
with a wood textured sticker on it it's all fake and flimsy and way too expensive a few
episodes back you were talking about wanting to make stuff with your hands well i'm a real crafty
boy and i made two six foot tall bookcases for my games a set of shelves for my consoles and a
little end table and it was all for 15 bucks i'm a rat 35 dollars if you include the cost of the
tools which are reusable and all of it was solid wood and sturdy as fuck and will last for a century
minimum because it's fucking immortal it's probably true if you any of you procrastinators out there
and only the procrastinators fuck the rest of you want to learn to be crafty like me hit me up on
twitter i'm fast talking megastar an indestructible super god tar buck transom spelling is in the
title i like him too i'm i'm really i like this guy yeah wait no was that an ad uh did we
kind of we just use as a vessel for advertising no no no i don't think it was an ad it was that
just just for us he did just simply say he doesn't want to hear from anyone except us
okay acceptable it could be deceptive but yeah i don't know i trust this man with my life i have
i literally have a piece of shit particle board shelf right over here um my shit is on it it is
not it does not have a wood panel sticker on it is painted white interesting thing about it i'm
looking at it and there is appears to be a whiteout or some kind of like like cover up paint
painted over but if i look at it at the right angle in the right light i can kind of see what
this whiteout is covering and it seems to say it says i love came possible a lot blade or blade
or blame i love some i love lake so much with a heart i'm glad that was painted over that's
quite a it was painted over with something but the the the remnants are still there fascinating
it's a metaphor for life uh well that's cool i hope those two have a happy future together
doubt it otherwise it would have been would have been one to wish them a happy wedding
don't do it don't waste your ones people okay guys the first pcp fan to get married is the first
pcp fan to get married get on it do it do it now yeah that's true that's quite a distinction uh uh did
i mention on my live stream i think it was it was it was reverse spectrum i think oh yes dude he uh uh
on my stream he was telling us like hey guys i'm about to go proposed to my fucking girlfriend
here i go and then he did and he was like she said yes and so wait on stream yeah this was on my
pokemon stream uh fucking oh it's pretty sick so cool yeah congrats pretty dope dude uh also he's my
knock dowel which is pretty all right guys can we fucking wrap this up because i gotta go all right
we got we we got like six more let's let's burn through them all right here we go here's mission
response let's get to it boom you know what annoys me people who talk about ketosis but they also
don't work out and they don't actually take care of nutrients in the body yeah these these people
are just using the whole ketosis meme as just an excuse for not buying food because they're poor
also this goes out to mr bones i think you got the wrong podcast the best debate in the universe
is to block down i forget what that end part is about the best debate in the universe oh yeah
bone said something to him last time i think i think he's a bitch or something i don't remember
i don't remember mr bones his message i'm sure it was wonderful
the time is spreading amongst the people you know is a fucking hope that ketosis is
a kind of a meme it is kind of a meme yeah yeah okay well great i should i should work i should
work out more but that's a separate issue that's a separate that's a separate
failing of mine i like his idea that people people just say they're in ketosis when really they're
just too lazy to buy food that's their real problem you know food is more expensive because
i'm on keto i spend more on food because i buy like brazil nuts and like meat and poison yourself
i can't just i can't get by on ramen whatever yeah well fair enough all right next one here we go
tazzle spur tazzle spur go
mirror mirror on the wall who is the gayest one of all i'm terribly sorry my lord but you're not
on top there is still one guy who's holding that spot the true king a mighty foe no one says gay
as digi bro
i don't know i don't know if digi's the gayest i mean he says i'm gay more so that that is what
makes it no i don't agree i think this magic mirrors aim is off i would say that uh i would say it's
i would say it's uh tom
means he is gay he is actually over gay he is currently digi adjacent so yeah yeah
okay next one next one next one next one next one next one next one next one next one next one next one
this is this is uh this is from someone called tom worst guy ever oliver or maybe maybe i don't
know i don't know we'll we'll see what this is about i hope it's the real tom oliver being the first
result on google images when you search for worst guy ever is tom grasping at straws and some kind of
astroturfing campaign to get as much attention as he's human he can without looking like a
fucking idiot what the fuck was that it's like auto tuned roba why did he auto tune this random
to the to the point where we couldn't understand him yeah well he was just saying that like tom's
like he he is like editing google search results so that he is the top result on worst guy ever
as some sort of campaign for attention or something um why would anyone do that uh
he is a bizarre coincidence he must not believe that it's genuine i i guess that's what he's saying
i guess that's what he says he's he's he's this is a conspiracy theory worst guy ever it's the
funny that comes up tom that is bizarre um okay let's let's get to our next one small world small
okay here's one from sands apparently oh oh is this my is this my old son
and let's let's find out he's here at last all right gay darts time to sing along
oh
i figured out your secret
wow
makes us real low please mr. edit boy uh that was uh i mean i think it was terrible i like that
because he was just actually playing piano live on the thing which is pretty dope yeah yeah that's
pretty dope nape nape nape nape nape nape is this is what this is this why is this why you were
having this maybe that might be relevant to why i was humming it earlier uh all right one more
from tri zeno 10 apparently okay i might have spelled that wrong whatever it's close enough
huge fan and i just wanted to point out that ben saint is the personification of the doomer meme
he is the meme made flesh discuss just i said discussed for a second i've discussed that
ben said just discussed as well um kind of uh what's a doomer what's what is i wasn't on that
episode okay what specifically is a doomer a doomer is uh a type of millennial who is nihilistic
kind of given up on life uh just like smoke cigarettes and doesn't place much value in his
life or plan for his future and is just kind of content to watch the world burn basically and
just hates everything well i mean can you be a happy doomer i'm kind of like that but like i'm
i'm fine with it i'm not i'm not bummed out about any of it that's the thing you don't actually fit
the profile of a doomer in attitude because you don't like beat the world that much all of those
behaviors right i do all of those behaviors right so my attitude is not is not doom it's a yeah a
doomlet bed's kind of a doomlet that's i'm do i'm doomer lights yeah i'm doomer adjacent i mean
yeah you're no one would say that you're a bloomer or anything like me uh uh you know for various
reasons because you're not are you wait what's a bloomer again uh one who wants to secure a future
for the white race oh yeah that yeah i'm not that cool like an like an optimistic uh like
kind of that it's kind of that uh like positive negative uh thing about like nothing means anything
the the bloomers that nothing means anything i can decide my own my own destiny yeah exactly
just somebody i feel like i feel like i embody all the behaviors of a doomer but my attitude is
more like a bloomer yeah i am i'm a more pretty positive person i think and i i share a lot of
the doomer conclusions about i don't i i sure i don't believe in like an objective it's almost as
if labels are stupid yeah it's almost it's almost as if people can't be like broadly slotted into
white categories like haha oh all right well all right all right no sorry there's one more from
the lord of ghosts the lord of ghosts himself has has a message let's let's hear what he's got for us
um sorry i'm behind on the typing there we go go
if a friend with a lord of ghosts has claimed your soul where am i people people is that you
no no no does that is so anyone could anyone understand that in i i i i i i think i did i
understood it hippo the lord of ghosts has claimed your soul and then are you and then he
larped as me saying hippo where are you well okay hang on i think what happened was you were
saying before that you don't have a soul you you jumped the gun then because i think what
just happened is he separated the soul from your body during that call the lord of ghosts
and that was your soul crying out which is now separate from you uh that's my yeah how tedious
how very it all comes together hey it's halloween though i don't make videos anymore
except we just made one which i enjoyed quite a bit oh yeah forget about it it's all fine
except for that one i'm glad we had the lord of ghosts on our halloween episode everybody
and with that it's time to bring this bad boy straight to hell we gotta get access the sun's
coming up we're all gonna get burnt to a crisp we gotta hide patreon.com slash the pro crastinators
yeah that's right twitter people at tpcrastinators follow us there i just want to say one more
thing yeah just one more quick thing okay hey ben i challenge you to a duel it's not a game but
rather a simple coin toss heads i win tails you lose do you accept um oh my god oh god uh it's too
much i can't i can't uh i'll do it yeah sorry sorry it's it's heads sorry it's heads you lose
oh no how could this have happened well i thought i had this one last uh i thought you were finally
looking up by the time you're listening to this in a few days there will be a real hardcore halloween
bonus episode out the day after halloween i don't know maybe we should release it on the
day or something just to give everyone a treat i don't know whatever it's it's gonna be spooky as
shit my dude so you're gonna want to get in on that uh that's all i can say but give us your money
five dollars patreon.com slash the pro crastinators there's like 18 bonus episodes you owe us this
people you owe it to us soon to be 19 soon to be 19 that's right all right well thanks for listening
everybody happy halloween have a great time and remember if you are here if you're listening to
the pcp you have arrived at the end of history that's true uh you are on the right side of it
so take heart all right as opposed to the left side of it we wouldn't want that no i don't like
thanks for being here everybody we'll see you next week