What's up, PCP Nation. Coming back right at you again with a new video and new podcast.
This one is going to be crazy. But before you watch, remember to like, subscribe, ring
that bell, put on all notifications so you don't miss a single upload. And remember
to watch the entire video, preferably multiple times so we get that sweet watch time. Alright
guys, we'll see you next time. Just watch this video from now. Very cool. Yeah. Can't
believe it. Can't believe it. It's a Friday once again.
Hello. Jumping right in. Episode 299 of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's me, Ben Saint,
and Oblivionfall is with me today. This week. Hey. I almost had to do another solo Bencast.
Everyone's favorite. But Oblivion jumped in to save me from that. I'm always hovering.
I'm always the specter. The specter of the solo Bencast is always hovering, floating,
just out of reach, haunting me. It's just a matter of staving it off. Yeah. How's it
going? What's up? What is up, dog? I'm here. The people have spoken. I read the comments.
They said, Oblivion, come back. And I did. Yeah. Put the baby in a blimba. Yeah, everybody
liked that. I was shocked to click on that episode and just hear my voice and I'm like,
what the fuck? Why am I at this? I wasn't on this episode and then I remembered. I had
some leftover voicemails I sent last week. Old ones that never got used. I was like,
oh, yeah. It was shocking. Shocking. What could this be doing here? Oh, I put it here. Yeah,
I said it was clean. Yeah, I said it was. Yeah, I kicked the habit. Well, how's your week been?
My week's been pretty productive. Because I haven't been productive enough, I did other
productive things. I was supposed to have my animation project done this month. I thought
for sure I could get it by January 15th. And so I realized shit, it's not going to be done. I
got to put something on Patreon. I guess I'll do another sketch dump because it's been about six
months. I want to do a sketch dump at least every six months. So I had to clean up a bunch of old
sketches. And I don't know if I can really share them because they're pornographic. So
of course. Just trust that at patreon.com slash oblivion. I did some good boob and penis and it's
good. I believe you. I believe you. I think I owe my patrons a Q&A. I haven't done a Q&A in a
couple of months because for a few months I've been like, well, I don't want to do a Q&A until
after the game is out. Because that's what I think people are going to want to talk about.
So I would put that off for a little while. Well, I was going to say I thought the game
would be done this month, but it is done this month. I was talking about this last week. I've
been drawing more of slime punishment because I need to have the comic done because the game and
the end of the comic are intertwined. They are one and the same. So I've been drawing that.
And then I realized I was like, okay, maybe I got like 30 pages. That's not so bad. So I started
cranking them out. I think I've done like 17. It'll probably be more than 30. It'll probably
be like 35 or 40. But then I realized, shit, I know what I have to draw up until the game.
And then I know what I have to draw is what happens immediately after the game.
And then that's the end of the comic. Slime and punishment is over. So I have to draw an ending
and I have no idea what the ending is. I know the climax. I don't know like, okay,
but what's the ending ending like? And they lived happily ever after. I don't know what I want to do
for that. So I have to think of that, I guess. I'm surprised. I'm surprised that wasn't like
planned way ahead. Well, I mean,
well, I mean, slime and punishment was an evolving thing because I kept changing it in
response to, you know, Chris Chan making up weird shit at me.
Waking up weird shit. They would never. They did. I did incorporate some things that she
told me in DMs. She would occasionally send me some weird DMs about like what she thinks should
happen. And I did incorporate some of that. I guess I don't mind spoiling a little bit.
For instance, you know, in S. Revert, Laka Kam falls in the alpha timeline and crushes Chris
Chan, Sonichu. But she mentioned in a DM that like an alternate version of herself would become
quote unquote corrupted by slime. So I have a little narrator's note from Discord,
the draconiquus, that there's an alternate version of Chris that is still in Laka Kam.
It's just like a slime junkie, just like sleeping in between dumpsters or whatever. It's great.
You know how it is. So I'm getting further on that. I will surely have it done this
in February, probably early February. I hope it won't even take. I hope it won't take most of the
month. Yeah. Damn. And then, I don't know, maybe I can like make some money selling,
doing a Kickstarter for a book of that in the not too distant future. That would be cool.
That wouldn't be. I need to buy me one of those plebeian that we blew rays, but my
PayPal is sadly drained. As I had one of, okay, so you know how I do those,
those Milo Pony Vector Commissions, I still do them.
Yeah. Especially now that I don't have a job, it's an easy way to get and come on the side.
There was one that I offered a refund to like back in December, because very design
was just a little too much. It didn't work. It wasn't like some like super like,
OC do not steal like a million like wings and stripes or whatever. It wasn't that sort of
issue. It was just with the hair. Just looked like it would be a pain to do with how my roots work.
Yeah. It was like really wavy and had stripes in it. And I was just like,
that's difficult to handle with my templates. So I just said, hey, offer a refund, you know,
I'll even give you 10 bucks extra because you waited, you know, about a year or more since,
because I accepted a big bachelor way back and took on way too many. So this person had been
waiting like a year. So I said, I'll give you 10 bucks extra. And then I don't hear anything for
like a month and a half. Yeah. And I'm just sitting there. I'm like, okay. And my PayPal is
getting a little smaller, my balance, but I still had like just enough in there to pay them back.
And then then I get an invoice from them. And it's like, they're like, in the invoice, it's like,
hey, sorry, I asked for 10 bucks extra. And I'm like, what do you mean? And I'm sitting here thinking
I already offered to give them 10 extra. What are we talking about? You were gonna give them
10 extra as like a sorry, can't take your commission. Here's $10 to cheer you up about it.
And then they were like, sorry, I'm putting 10 bucks extra on the invoice. And the invoice was
30 extra. So I was like, well, no, no, your math is not good. And then I was just annoyed. And I'm
like, you know, I actually only like received like $124 because PayPal like charged a $6 fee at
my end. So the 10 bucks extra is technically only going to be four bucks extra for you.
Because I never actually received the full 130 that was agreed on way back.
So that was a thing that happened. And then PayPal charged me like another $5 just to send
them the money back because of course it did. Yeah, wherever I receive or send money,
the charges only come out of my end and never the other person's end. It's weird.
Yeah, I saw you're, I don't know why you have like weird PayPal issues.
Yeah, someone thought maybe they switched me to like a business account or something,
like against my knowledge. I don't know. But like when I send like 20 bucks and it charges
me like almost five bucks worth of fees. And I'm like, that's not how it's not how it's supposed
to work. Yeah, definitely not how it's supposed to work. Yeah, the fees are really high for me.
And it might be because my account is like based in New Zealand, but they don't let me change it.
They say it's against policy to change the region. And I've been trying to like,
What if you move? I did. I mean, exactly. I move like almost six years ago,
I moved to America and I still am so confused. New Zealand PayPal account that tries to convert
everything to New Zealand dollars and I keep going to be like, no, keep it in America dollars.
I don't want even more conversion fees. And I tried setting up a new one and they're like,
oh yeah, you can't set up a new one unless you send us a picture of your driver's license or
if you have a bill that has your name on it, I can't get either of those things. My apartment
complex, we don't get bills. Like everything is like handled in the rent. There are no bills.
Like they're just none. And I don't have a driver's license and because I don't
fucking want to drive. At least not at the moment. My husband takes me everywhere I need to go if
I need to go somewhere. So I've had a PayPal account for like your housewife.
Yeah, totally. No, no, I'm just for cool. I'm just a cool cackling at your expense.
I'm the cool artist man and my husband is my chauffeur. Okay. But yeah, that PayPal account,
I tried setting up three or four years ago. And there's I when I first set it up, I like
accepted a few commissions. So there's a couple hundred bucks just sitting in there. And I can't
access it. I can look at it, but I can't touch it. In your PayPal? Yeah, in my American PayPal
that I set up. It's the same one I use for the PCP dating sim OST, which made about $80, which is
alright. I'm sure the work on that was worth more than $80, but it was definitely worth more.
Yeah, just the fucking, the fucking like little music video I made that went on the PCP channel
like a week to do. Yeah, it looked great. I don't know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. But that's, you know,
I'm actually really bothered by I, for some reason, after effects, if you have a wave file,
and of course, wave is like the best sound quality, like it's the most losses format.
If you have a wave file and after effects, I found this out when I was editing the PCP way back,
is there will be little popping and clicking sounds that'll start appearing in the audio. If it's,
if the audio is really long, like say an hour long, more than an hour long, around 30 to 40
minutes, and you'll start hearing little clicks and pops, and they get louder and more frequent.
And by the end of the video, it's like,
like, and it's like really like harsh sounds that it really, that's just okay. So what you're
saying is after effects like just simply doesn't process audio, correct? Yeah, like really long
lossless audio formats just kind of sound fucked up towards the end. And you have to either use an
mp free, or, which I guess I could have just done that. Or what I usually do is I use X media
recode to remix the audio afterwards. It basically just lets you like, you just swap out the audio
file for a different one and the video information is untouched. So you don't lose any quality.
And also it's really fast. It takes like two seconds. So that's what I did for the PCP episodes.
I forgot to do that for a dating sim because I wanted it, the soundtrack to come out exactly one
week after. And I was already like, running late on that day. And I guess I just forgot to so
the video went up with shitty audio and it's just been like that. And I've been mad about it.
Silently for like two years almost. Two years. Who would hold a grudge? Who would hold a grudge for
years of Libyan fall? Who would hold on to anger for that long? You know? I only anger against
myself. I don't, I can't hold grudges against other people. I'm incapable. It's like the Buddha
said grudges are like holding on to a hot coal thinking I'll throw it at, one day I'll throw it
at my enemy. Unironically, that's how I feel. Your enemy is yourself. Well, yeah, it's just
sitting up my ass, keeping it warm, I guess. I don't know. I've never been able to stay mad at
people. And there've been people who have like completely fucked me over who I've just forgiven
and like let back into my life. And that's happened a lot. And usually how does that work out?
It doesn't usually work out great. Granted, like it's not usually people who are like
really like fucking annoying. Like it's usually people who work close to me about it.
Like family or stuff like that where I've been like oof.
Yeah. But man, I'm mad. That's that's personal poopiness. I don't know where I'm going. It's
seems he's saying you might jump in. That'd be cool.
It seems like he's gonna. I'm glad you thank I'm glad you mentioned the the blue rays though.
Link in the description.
stcomics.com slash store.html for the store. $20, $20 cent fee $5. Unbelievable.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. It's not for me when I get
I have I have orders for the blue rays have continued to trickle in. I have sold
about twice as many as I expected. Hey, Simsie. Hey, how's it going? Whoa. It's
Hey, leave the episode. Yo, well, that's three three man three man tag team today.
It's better than nothing.
You are recording, right? Yeah, I just started recording.
We'll do a sync at the end there.
Wait, let's do let's do a sync right now. On the on the count of three, say sync. One,
two, three, sync. One, two, three, sync. So I was just gonna say
I have sold about twice as many as I expected to sell my first batch of 50.
I have basically I think I have literally one more left of my second batch of 50.
So if I if two more people order blue rays, I will have to I will have to buy another set of
blank DVDs and cases for them, which is fine. When when people order it through when they order
it through when they when they just DM me and ask like where do I send the money and I give them
my my email address. Sometimes they choose, you know, buy as a buy it as a, you know, by a service
or item, which charges I think it's about 5% of a fee, which is not very much. So I don't mind
it that much. The best outcome is that they choose like buy through friends and family.
And then there's no fee at all, which is which is great. So I like that, although I don't blame
anyone for not wanting to do that, because like, you know, they are, if I were to rip them off,
they would they would have no way to like file a complaint and request their money back through
PayPal. So fair enough. And then the button that I made for the store page,
stcomics.com slash store.html is that one also charges a fee, but it charges like
ever so slightly more like instead of charging $1.50 for a $35 transaction, it charges like $1.65.
And I don't know why that is, but it's an insignificant difference. So I have not interrogated
it. But I did notice it and I thought it was odd. Yeah, fuck you. It's crazy. Evil PayPal's feeling
little man's money again. Elon Musk. Elon Musk. He's got he needs that $1.65 to build his big fucking
rocket ship that you can jerk off on his way to the moon in. Does he still does he still like run
PayPal or has he like sold it? I don't know. He was one of the guys who made it. I don't know like
if he's still involved in it. Yeah, but it's funny to blame everything on him because he's
dick face weirdo. Absolutely. And of course. How's your week, Simsie? How have you been?
Not too bad. I felt really sick last night. So I called in sick for work and I was like,
I ain't coming in. And then I got a text from work today saying, ha ha, even though you work
overnight and there's no customers there, you can't wear headphones anymore. So it's like, oh,
fuck. What the fuck? I'm going to be stacking shelves for eight hours without headphones on.
I'm going to go insane. I don't know. I think they said something about like people who come in
closer to when like the store opens. They leave their headphones in when the customers come in,
you're not allowed to do that. So they've just banned the whole thing. It was really annoying
for someone like me who only works when the store's closed. That's so awesome. That's so awesome.
I can't listen to the PCP while I'm stacking shelves. This is like how they insist that
like cashiers stand, like cashiers are not allowed to sit. Yeah, it's one of those type of things.
One of those is just like, I the boss just think that work should just be worse for me.
I just feel like it should be worse. So it is now. And that's good.
I'm really annoyed. I'm not looking forward to it. There's literally no reason they couldn't just
cashiers couldn't just sit. Luckily, my contract ends in March. So it's not going to be too bad
because it's going to be like a month of fucking pain. And then I'm going to say like,
please don't bother extending me. I don't want to work here anymore.
That's why I shop at Aldi. Aldi lets their cashiers sit.
Also, they're cheaper. Actually, I don't even shop at Aldi anymore because they don't have the
brand of ice cream that I like. Amazing. They don't have Knicks. Hey, Gib, what's up?
Hey. Hello. Hello. There we go. Now I hear you. Nothing's up, really.
It was a slow week. I had a slow week because, wait, I already explained the whole thing about
how I'm drawing the pages, right? I already said that. You did mention that last time. Yeah.
Well, I mentioned it again this week. I'm just doing that. So that's my week.
What have you been, Gib? I've been okay. I've been like fucking...
I don't know. There's been the secret project and that's going along.
And then there's been a lot of ghost mailing stuff. And I've packaged some envelopes up
in tomorrow. They're going to come around, pick them up. And I got to buy a bunch more
for sending to all over the globe. There's one in Japan. There's a few in Chile.
And Greece and France and Belgium and fucking everywhere.
Is the guy... I have a suspicion about who the guy in Japan is. I think it might be the same
guy I talked to this week who is the same guy who does a lot of the like PCP, like the music
voicemails. It could be. There's one guy in Japan. He ordered a road to Radcon. He was a
Kickstarter backer. He ordered a Blu-ray. And he's in the comments too. He's the guy who...
Fuck. I forget what his handle is, but he's a...
It's the Pink Floyd guy.
Amazing. Anyway, I just like... It was a mastermind.
Dark horse.
But yeah, it's mostly just been like... My thing for this pickup is mostly to America.
They can come to my house and pick it up and put the labels on at their warehouse,
which is epic and nice. But for basically every other place that isn't America,
I need to go through Royal Mail, which is the cheapest option, but it requires
that I go to one of... I bring everything to a post office and I have to print the labels and
stick them on myself, which is like, yeah, it's a hassle. I got to do that.
You heard it here first, people. If you bought one of Gibbs Comics and live outside of America,
fuck you. How dare you?
No, no. It's just that I've yet to do that. And I don't know. I could barely believe a week has
passed. I didn't even notice. Yeah. I mean, same. I feel like that a lot. I feel like that a lot,
but I got to say something. I got to get in here and I got to convert my lived experience
into content somehow. I feel time just slipping away a lot. I don't notice the weeks anymore.
Maybe it's because of my horrendous scheduled sleep and work, but I just don't fucking realize
when one day it ends and the other one begins. I know this is... Oh, this is where everyone's
quarantine started, but fuck me. It's just been awful. I don't know what's happening. I don't
know where I am in the world. I don't know what's going on. We had a blizzard here yesterday,
so it was like a foot or two of snow outside, which has compounded the issue. Since New
Year, since everyone here got COVID, I have not been working out. I have gotten off of the
schedule wherein I used to go over to Munchie and Kazi's house and lift three times a week,
and I have not been doing that this month. And it's bad. That was a ritual, I guess,
that I had that got me out of the house, but not anymore. I'm hoping that starts up again soon.
Munchie's school schedule is like, I guess he's like, I don't know what my good schedule is.
Figure it out, bro. Compounds the like, I don't know. I don't do anything. I don't
leave my house. I have no reference point for when one week starts and another ends.
I mean, I've, working on The Secret Project has been really fun, and I really enjoy that,
which is why I can't wait to release it and then tell people, so I can talk about it in public.
Yeah. I know what you mean. So the days feel the same, but they're good days. It's not like I'm
like, despairing about everything. It's just sort of like, what the fuck, time passes?
Yeah. I can measure time passed in pages of slime and punishment drawn.
And you can get back to drawing comics as well.
That's really how it feels. I think I got, this week I have like 17 panels drawn,
which is not as many as I should have for a whole week, but that's what I got.
So that's like, if a day goes by and I don't do any, it's like, well, today might as well not
have even happened. What am I doing? I get that feeling a lot, where if I haven't drawn anything
that day, I would just be like, oh, I didn't exist. I didn't, it didn't happen. Nothing,
nothing happened today. Yeah. Before that, it was, when I was making the game, it was,
I would have like a to-do list. I would have like my items on the to-do list, like bugs
that needed fixing or like assets I needed to make. And it would be like, how many items
did I cross off the to-do list? That was how I used to measure it. Yeah.
My criteria has been like, unless something has gone up on my Twitter or my Patreon,
the day has not counted. It's not been a thing. It's, it's unreal.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
But I've been pretty good about that recently. I was in a big art slump for like all of fucking
December. And then over the last month, I've slowly built up the steam again. And I'm putting
down a lot more than I used to. And I've actually started using my Patreon for the fucking first
time in like six months. Yeah, I've seen, I've seen you've been drawing a lot of, of one piece
girls. Yeah. Yeah. It's mostly because my, my friend has gotten into one piece recently. So
we've been talking about it a lot. And it's just like, cool rules. It's the best thing ever.
Yeah. It, I mean, it is. It's perfect. I've been seeing you, I've been seeing you draw that maid
girl. Oh yeah. The milkmaid. That's fun. I don't know if she has a name. Amelia. I mean,
it doesn't really matter, but yeah. She looks similar to I smell. Yeah. I have two characters
that wear the exact same thing. And I realize they need to redesign the horse to get rid of
or something, which is unfortunate because we used her for a drawcast episode recently,
but I just put a trash bag on her head, literally. Yeah. There we go. That work. I'm gonna give her
just like a generic Alma helmet or something to make it look funny. I don't know.
Whatever. Speaking of, speaking of the drawcast, I, I, uh, how many more people does the, uh,
does the, uh, the, the telephone episode have to go through?
Not that many people. We've just had a couple of people who just sat in it for weeks.
Yeah. Yeah. When did it start? I can't remember.
It's 12 months ago. Probably four months ago.
Maybe five. I just, uh, I don't know. Look, look, look at forward to that. I guess the list must
have grown because when I looked at the list, there weren't that many more people. There's like
20 people on the list, which is pretty long for a telephone, but I think that'll make it way
better when it's done. Cause the character will have evolved a lot more, I assume. I haven't seen
any of you yet. I can't look at it because I'm still waiting for my spot. I haven't looked at it
in a while. I looked at it. I looked at what was done after I did mine. I had assumed it was like
canceled because I hadn't seen it be updated for so long. I was like, are you, are you in that
Simsie? Yes, I think so. Oh, sick. Yeah, I had been waiting for a while. I had kind of been like,
that must be canceled if it's been this long. Okay. Well, that's good.
You got to hound people who love you and fool. You got to hound them. You got to say,
get this shit done like all my commissioners did. And I finally, I had commissions from
fucking four months ago that I hadn't done. I am the worst at this shit. I should not do it as a
shit, dude. That's pretty bad. That's pretty bad. It's like my record.
Jesus Christ. What was that though? Was that like a full vector model?
Well, yeah, that was one of those vector packs. Well, here's the thing, the vector packs,
most of the time I can do them in like a single day. The problem is it was really hard for me
to keep on top of them with pencilmation. I was always behind on things and those things had like
strict deadlines that like had to be done and everything was always like down for the wire.
And it was like that for like a couple years at a certain point. This is very hard for me to
actually make progress on my commissions. Now that I am not working at pencilmation anymore,
I can, what I'll do is I won't accept batches of commissions anymore. I'll accept one commission
at a time and I'll do it that day. And then I'll accept another one and do it that day.
That's what I decided on. So no one waits. The way I'm doing it going forward is if I'm in the mood
to do a commission, I think I can do one. I will put up on Twitter. Hey, I'm going to do a commission.
I'm not having multiple slots open because it will just get past me. And I know how my brain
works and it doesn't work properly. Speaking of, this reminds me of the most annoying comment
ever got on the last episode. I'm going to complain about this one commenter.
This one made me feel like I was losing my mind because this is like, I anticipated,
I imagined someone complaining that like me talking about the artist, you know,
bailing on the dojin and ghosting me. I imagined someone finding it objectionable
that I would complain about that. And then I was like, no, Ben, you're being ridiculous.
It's just so foolish. Well, some commenter was like, Ben, you're bullying this guy.
It's evil. It's cruel. You're a monster. It's not really true, I'm paraphrasing,
but someone was complaining that like, this guy thinks it's wrong. This guy thinks it's wrong
for me to complain about the guy who basically like scam. I didn't even do like a full scam.
It wasn't like a deliberate scam, but he did like, he took, he took money for a service and
he didn't deliver on the service and then he, then he ghosted. And I, I just can't believe this
guy thinks I'm the bad guy for just for saying that, for saying that that happened. Fuck you,
commenter. It's the ghosting part that makes it like, like a bad thing that you can complain about.
Because like if somebody is saying, oh, I'm taking a while, at least they're in contact with you.
Yeah, absolutely. And you can talk to them about it. You can, you can, you can like arrange
something and you don't have to say anything publicly because you're talking to them.
This fucking pussy. But if you have no way to, to talk to them, what are you gonna do?
This pussy, this pussy commenter was like, oh, you're probably just making them anxious. You're
probably giving them anxiety. Fuck you. Fuck you. We live in a society. I don't care. It's your
problem. When you do, you're, I guess we shouldn't, I guess we shouldn't have trials for criminal.
I guess when people do crimes, we probably shouldn't have trials for them because that would
be bullying them and it would probably give them anxiety. They'd probably be like, bothered by
that. You fucking, this sick fuck, sick fucking mentality this guy has. I hate it. I hate it.
Yeah, with my incredibly late stuff, at least like tried to contact and say, hey, sorry,
I haven't been able to work on it. Or when I went back to do those, I would not have been mad at
all. I would not have even been mad if the guy had been like, sorry, I'm three months late.
I'm working on it. I'd be like, you know what? No big deal. You know what? These things happen.
Three months is the cutoff point. Wouldn't even, wouldn't even about it.
Where I offered like a refund or the, or to just do it and then say, sorry. You know what I mean?
Yeah. Like half the people who's commissions were really late recently. I offered them refunds and
half of them took them. So it just seems fair. I mean, I'm not saying like that guy should give
you a refund, but he should give you a refund. He should give me, he should refund me at least
part of it because he didn't do, right. Cause I paid him half and he didn't quite do half.
He probably did like a third. So is that going to be used anywhere? What's been done?
Yeah. Yeah. I think I'm going to keep what's done. And, and, uh, uh, yeah, I'm going to keep what he
did. And, uh, Kaiju is just going to just do the rest. Yeah. The, the dodging is like a few like
short stories, isn't it? Yeah. So they can be like different art styles and not be too jarring.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't think he, I don't think he like finished. I think he did quit mid story.
So one story will be split. I don't, you know, I mean, not that they, they look the same,
but I feel like Kaiju and this guy have close enough style. They, they both do, you know,
sort of manga style, like, you know, black on white, uh, uh, line art, kind of sort of a
traditional manga look. It's not exactly the same, but I feel like they are, they are compatible
enough in a way that it's not like going to be a weird, like doesn't, doesn't look like the same
comic. Uh, I don't know, whatever. It'll just be a funny, like, oh, huh. This, this page was by,
you can see, you can tell when the art is shifted because the art style changes a little bit here
and here. Yeah. Yeah. Like, uh, when that voice actor from Avis Alastair Vendor died and they
got another white boy guy and it sounded like exactly the same and you can only barely tell.
Which, which, um, that's Iro. Iro, um, was voiced by Mako, I think. Yeah. I don't know.
Yeah. So it's sort of a, he was like a prestigious Japanese like actor who worked in a lot of stuff
and, um, very old guy, sort of had a, like a, like a, like, oh, voice.
But you mean in the English stuff? You mean in the, you mean the original?
So I was going to say, I didn't say it. I was, I meant the, but you, but you mean the English
voice actors? Yeah. Yeah. I didn't, I didn't know that. Okay. I never noticed the voice change. So
I mean, on the first watch, I didn't, but I think I've definitely noticed it every time
since the first watch. So I'm like, oh, that's when. If I ever watched it again, I'm sure I'd
be listening for it. Yeah. Uh, yeah. Oh, well, maybe I'm just kind of deaf.
I'm pretty, I'm pretty bad at noticing and noticing things like that. I have a tall,
kind of good, kind of like one of the best. Yeah. That's what they say. That's what they tell me.
Is it as good as they say though? Yes. Pretty much. Yes.
As far as the last airbender is really that good. Dude.
YouTube thumbnail, red text. Distilled critic watched every episode with his brother and they
talked about it and he said, show good. Hmm. I agree. Thumb up. I'm not sure if it's good.
I have a bunch of, um, I have a bunch of gripes. I have a bunch of life gripes that are bugging me.
I'm just going to go, I'm just going to go down. Hashtag Ben Sains life gripes.
Here we go. Top number 10. I'm just going to go down a list and list off things that annoy me.
The life grapes and the wine corner. You turn gripes into wines.
Yeah. Yeah. This is the wine corner and these are all the individual grapes that I'm about to smush.
Number one. My glasses broke, uh, sort of. I dropped them a little while ago and one of the
frames cracked and it's just a small crack in the side of the, of the, one of the, the frames and
the lens is fine. Like the lens didn't crack, but now like there's a little gap and I,
if I move my head a lot or like I, I, I, I hold them the wrong way, the lens will fall out.
So I need to like glue the frames. I should get new lens, new frames because I got these
like eight fucking years ago. Oh, let's try and come up with solutions for all of Ben's life
gripes. Uh, number one, get new frames or tape. Uh, uh, I, I'm going to order some gorilla glue.
I'm going to order some gorilla glue, but I, it's only like $6. So I had to buy some other stuff
to get free shipping on Amazon. So I'm waiting for it. Like I said, if I sell like two more
copies of the Blu-ray, I will have to buy more discs. So I'm waiting until like two more Blu-ray
copies sell so that I can order another batch of discs, which will get me over the $25 limit
to pay no shipping on an Amazon order. So so I get my gorilla glue free shipping charges.
You see, it's all, it's all connected. Would you like glue your glasses with like a glue gun
pointed towards, uh, like while you're wearing them, just right into your eye?
Cassie said they had a glue gun that I, I was going to, I was going to glue gun them
temporarily together, but I just forgot to, uh, and now I don't want to walk over there
because it's too cold out and there's too much snow. So I'm just, I'm just fucked.
All right, life gripe number two. Let's go. Let's go. Uh, my toilet is clogged.
Plunger, Amazon, uh, put you over the limit for the things.
I have to buy a new toilet.
Dude, you mentioned my plunger.
Destroy it. Plunger.
Dude, plunger, plungers are so cool.
When I was a kid, I loved when I run into the store and I would grab a bunch of plungers and
stick them to the walls. I have, I have been, I have a plunger and I have tried to plunge it
and it doesn't work. Okay. This, since I moved in, this, this toilet, this toilet in my apartment
is, I guess it sucks because it clogs quite often. It has clogged a bunch of times. However,
if, if I just like have like, let it, if I just have ignored it, because there's two
toilets in my apartment, I can just use the upstairs toilet, right? I can just, if I have
just let it sit for a day or two, eventually the clog like dissolves or whatever. And it,
and it has like cleared up and it's like fine. This time it has been clogged for like a week.
It has in fact only gotten worse. The clog has only gotten more severe. I don't know what's up with
that. Um, but so, and plunging has not fixed it. So God, I might actually have to like call my
superintendent or my landlord or something and be like, uh, fix it. Or I guess I could just go buy
some like Drano or something. I've never, I've never like, gotta get that, that like duct, toilet,
blast pipe, chemical dissolving, get like an air cannon and fire it into the toilet.
So I mean, whatever, I just been using the upstairs toilet. Like it doesn't even matter,
but it just makes me annoyed. It just makes me feel like I live in a, in a dump, which I do live
in a dump. So I guess that's fine. Uh, third problem is I don't have a, uh, uh, I don't have a,
I miss, I need another blanket. It's too cold. I need a third blanket. I have another blanket,
but it like, I think I spilled something on it like a while ago and I've been meaning to do my
laundry. I've been meaning to put it in the laundry, but it requires like a load unto itself
because it's a big blanket and I just don't want to put you over the limit of the spending thing.
And I just don't want to spay the $2. I don't want to pay the $2 to do a whole load of fucking
laundry just for one, actually $4 because I have to dry it afterwards. So I've just been,
so whatever, I just have a bathrobe. I just put it, I just put a bathrobe on top of my bed and
now that's my third blanket. Watch your fucking clothes Ben. Jesus. I don't, it's, it would take
a whole separate load just for the, just for a blanket. I don't want to. You can put some socks
and pants in there with it. No, it's too big. Oh, fuck you. And I don't, you're telling, oh,
what am I, what am I going to do, Simsie? Just, just lift myself, pick myself up
in my bootstraps and spend the $4 to do a whole load of laundry. Yes. Don't be ridiculous.
Self-care is important, my friend. I was thinking of like getting a blanket and buying like a brooch
and making a cloak because like, because that's basically what a cloak is. It's just like a long
big piece of cloth that you wrap around yourself. That's a problem with walking around your house
dressed like that. Well, not just like outside, like, but the only problem is like,
it's getting warmer, it's going to be spring and it'll be very weird to have a like cloak.
It's good for like when it's really cold. I mean, why not? And you can like wrap it around and it's
like, it's like a fashion thing that is completely gone for no reason. They're trying to sell you
coats. Coats aren't as cool. It's a, coats are a racket. Coats are a new agenda. Coats are a jacket.
They make fucking people. They, they, they sell, they sell us poison and then they suppress our
cures. Well, no, they, and they, to sell us cures while we suppress our medicine. Selling,
give us poison is cold. Sell us cures is coats. Suppress our medicine is cloaks clasped with a
brooch. Anyway, it's just, it's just such a, such a base cloak life, a base and easy solution.
All I need is a brooch. I don't know where to get one. I guess I can Amazon or look around.
A brooch is just like a pin, right? Like a pin in the class.
A big, a big hefty pin that you can go through and can withstand pulling forces of a big,
heavy blanket. Big, heavy person pulling it real hard. Yeah, like give. Yeah. Yeah. Give you like
400 pounds, right? I cost a lot more than that. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. Life grapes go. We
need another one. Yeah. I had one, one more, which is a dental insurance. I've been trying
to look into dental insurance and like it doesn't make any sense and it sucks so much and it doesn't
even work. Like it doesn't, it doesn't, it's not even good. It doesn't even like actually pay for
shit. Amazon.com, cheap dental insurance. Amazon Prime Dental, the new services they're rolling
it up. Because I got, because I got to go to the dentist because I'm sure I need a couple of
fillings at least. And so I'm like, okay, time to actually do that. So I tried to do it. I tried
to like be good and get my shit taken care of and I went and I tried to look into it. And I guess
the most popular dental insurance in Massachusetts is something called Delta Dental, but everyone
hates it and apparently it sucks. And I was looking at their policies and like you could get,
they'll give you, they'll give you like, they won't even pay for shit. They'll give you like 50%
off at best. That's the best, that's the best you can get for, for, yeah. It's 30% on some things.
And then like, I don't know, like they're, I was looking at their plans and then they have like a
regular plan. It's like, oh yeah, this is a plan that like, if you have this plan, you'll have no
waiting period. It'll cover all this stuff. It's not available anymore. That one's, you just can't
get that one anymore. I'm like, okay, cool. So I don't know. It's just, it's so like inscrutable
and like they don't even tell you what a plan costs. They don't list the price anywhere. They just
will say, yeah, this plan exists and this is what it covers. What does it cost? I don't know.
Depends on how big your teeth are. Don't even worry about it. Well, how am I supposed to
fucking choose a plan? You freaks. You sick fucks.
I called my, called my parents and I asked my dad like, what should I do? And I forgot like, well,
they have like Medicare. So like, they don't have to worry about this shit. Okay, great.
My dad, because my dad gets all of us kids, my dad gets all of us offspring, a AAA membership.
Every year. So he recommended that I get some insurance offered through AAA. There are some,
there are some companies that are like, affiliated with AAA. I was like, okay.
So I was going to look through those, but like, I didn't because it's like,
they have names like choosy, like they sound like fucking apps.
Jeez.
That's horrifying.
They sound like fucking Twitter artists.
C-H-E-W-S-I. I don't know, man. That sounds weird for an insurance company.
Choosy Manfredo.
Yeah. So, so, uh, I just, just, um, I don't know. I haven't done it.
That's a life gripe that you've got to solve on your own, my friend.
Yeah. I'm afraid Amazon free shipping isn't going to solve this one for me.
As it does so many things.
Yeah. So that was it. That's the end of my, uh, that's everything on my list of stuff that's
bugging me.
That will be a recurring segment every week where we go through all the little things that
have ruined Ben's existence and life.
I mean, I mean, it pretty much is already. It's just we've never put a name to it.
We need a jingle for it.
Ben's life gripes.
I think, is it, I'm going to get that guy, I'm going to find that guy's name.
Came to make a life gripes jingle.
Oh, yeah, please. Somebody has to do it.
Genius.
That's all I got. That's all I got.
And we're only 45 minutes in.
Um, well, I guess I can talk a little bit about maps. I said last time.
Mutu Sandu. Mutu Sandu is the guy in the comments. He's the guy who does the music.
And I think he's probably the guy in Japan that you got to ship to, perhaps, perhaps, maybe.
He's a real Tokyo boy. He's got a Tokyo address. He gave me his, his shipping address to send
them some stuff, but he gave it to me like in like fucking kanji.
I'm like, what the, what the fuck am I supposed to do with this?
Oh, speaking of Japan, I got my first, he gave it to me in English too.
I got my first embarrassing sexy one piece figure.
Hooray.
When it arrived at the house, my dad looked at the package and he was like, Fukuoka City.
What the hell's that? I was like, never mind.
I want to see you, Simsie.
Uh, it's on my Twitter. It's not.
Is it Robin?
Yeah, it's Robin. Of course it's Robin. What the fuck do you think I am? So I'm going to plebeian?
Or I'm going to buy a fucking.
Like Batman and Robin?
Yeah. From one piece.
From one piece.
He's got his, he's got his like little short, short.
Hang on.
But out.
Here's a picture.
I bought it with leftover Amazon money that I had from.
That's not embarrassing.
No, but it's like, fuck yeah, there it is.
Dude, I didn't know she was that much taller than Bulma.
What the fuck?
I know. I was very surprised.
It's the same brand as well. It's Canon. That's the Canon height.
Wow, she's tiny.
Yeah.
Oh, I like it.
Oh, I found her. I found her.
And I immediately bought another one because I was like, that's cool.
I want to know. I need an Ami now.
These sorts of figures are like cool as a photograph.
When I see them in, in like real life,
like the time I went to Digi's or Trixie's older house
for Redcon one and two and stuff.
I saw all those figurines and I was like, oh, that's what they look like
in person because I'd never bought one.
And they're like, this just annoys me because of like,
it not not because of what it is.
I don't care about anime or whatever or like whatever it is.
Like, oh, it's it's embarrassing. It's not. It's just a figure.
But like, yeah, having figures that with with like, oh, you got to dust them.
You got to put the fine shelf space for them.
Yeah.
I'm like, that's a whole that's like a full time job is keeping a display looking nice.
I do hate owning things.
Just minimize ownership and everything's fine.
Yeah.
Well, that's that's the attitude that got me in a fucking shithole apartment
with a clogged toilet and so, you know, who's who's not enough.
I have I have a plunger.
I have a plunger.
I guess I need to plunger.
I need to do one.
You got to you got to you got to do a dual system.
Yes, that's the phrase I was looking for.
You're using the right bed.
You're not sticking a thin bit down the toilet.
Oh, it's just just jam the.
Well, yeah, you jam the wooden end down.
You just wash it around to try and break up the clog.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, well, it doesn't fucking work.
So what you fix a clog door is you keep flushing it until the water comes out.
And then it's done.
And it's everything's fine.
It used to work.
It used to just it used to just unclog itself.
But not anymore.
Now, well, not that not this time.
Yeah, I like toys.
I like buying embarrassing toys to have my desk and it makes me smile.
That's all I wanted to say, really.
I have like more like a collection of of plush toys instead.
And those at least you can squish together and like and throw on the bed or on the floor.
Yeah, you can have the you can have convenient storage of plushies.
Yeah, you don't have to worry about all that fell off the shelf.
Yeah.
Oh, or or anything.
Because along the top shelf.
Along the top shelf, which is next to me.
Yeah.
Along the top of the bookshelf, which is next to my desk,
I've got all my like Gundam models and action figures and shit set up
because I'm an embarrassing 22 year old fucking freak.
But I own I own nothing.
I own nothing.
You own you have digital ownership of things, but it's fine.
I have a little my friend.
My friend Chelsea gave me a little a little Homer Simpson Buddha,
who's like holding a donut.
That's the right kind of thing to own a little a little.
I'm not I'm not sure if it's plastic or rubber,
but it's a little a little figurine of a little Buddha Homer Simpson.
And that's that's my Nika Robin.
You look at him longingly every day.
And that's culturally insensitive to someone, probably.
He's up on my he's up on my shelf next to my Sonic the Hedgehog and Shrek glasses.
Very nice.
I collect collectible glasses.
Shrek glasses.
Do they have I have do they give you a little Shrek here?
Let me put them on.
They just have a little screened on.
They're like promotional glasses from like Shrek three, I think.
Oh, the one with the best one.
You mean the one with the babies.
You mean drinking glass or eyeglass is they're not shot not shot glasses.
They're just I don't know what you call them.
Tumblers.
Tumbler glasses.
They're you know, they're like not like tall glasses.
They're like, you know, medium height glasses of normal width.
Yeah.
Chugging down your Shrek flavor, Jack Daniels.
Shrek coming green green.
Yeah.
Green St. Patrick's Day Shrek themed whiskey.
They do green versions of basically every food like I know around Halloween,
Jaffa cakes, they do like green versions of those and I've always been scared to try them
because I don't know why we don't have we don't have Jaffa cakes over here.
But I mean, they do green.
They do green beer.
Yeah, they do some green.
I've never had green beer.
That sounds terrible.
That might be that might be a thing that they just do like at bars.
Like how do you tell it's green because you're drinking it, you know, looking at it.
I don't know if they sell like I don't know if they if many brands like sell green beer
like in bottles.
No, of course not.
It's funny.
I used to think beer was green because they were in the glass bottles.
I didn't really put it together that it's not that color.
Yeah.
This is like way before I started drinking.
There's just like, oh, I see that beer bottles are green or wine bottles are like a weird color.
Yeah.
I think my parents drank like mostly like clear bowl stuff all the time.
And then they straight vodka.
Yeah.
I was like, that's cool.
That footage just makes you act real strange.
My dad, one time at Olive Garden, my dad gave me a sip of his firewater whiskey.
And when I was like a kid and I was like, oh god, he like laughed.
He thought it was funny that I was like, disgusted by it.
Honestly, it probably was funny.
Honestly, I think I get it.
Yeah.
That happened with me, but with like a normal beer.
Like, you know that warm throat feeling you get from alcohol?
Like too much of it.
Yeah.
I had that.
I had like a sip of my dad's desperado.
So when I was like eight and I was like, my throat's burnt.
It's on fire.
What's going on?
I smell.
I smelled beer as a kid and I thought it smelled because I would because we would have
to like sort our recycling into, you know, you know, returnables and non-returnables.
And then, you know, my parents would let, we, okay, we didn't have like, like trash pickup.
We had to take our trash to the dump and we would sort recyclables and we could bring
the recyclables to a local, to a liquor store, actually, or to a returnery or whatever you
call it.
And they would accept, you know, cans and they would give you return money for it.
A nickel per can or whatever.
And so parents, when we were little kids, parents would let us sort it and then we
could take it and return it and we could get the return money.
And, you know, I would do that and I would sort out my dad's beer cans and I'd be like,
oh, this is gross.
It's so fucking disgusting.
It smells nasty.
So I never wanted to try tasting beer as a kid.
I thought it was the grossest shit ever.
And I was right.
You were correct.
I should go, I should go back.
I should go back to that.
Yeah.
If only it was possible.
My dad, my dad, by which I mean my bare father, who's a piece of shit.
Let me try beer and it was fucking gross.
It was the worst shit.
And later, like over a decade later, I got my first job and the boss from America
randomly showed up at our tiny office.
He just walked in unannounced to check up on me.
Was this in New Zealand?
Yeah, it was in New Zealand.
He puts a beer on my desk.
It was like, yeah, I bought you this.
Haha.
It's brand is really good.
And I'm like, oh, thank you.
I don't really drink alcohol, but sure.
I'll give it a try.
And I tried it when I got home and it was not good.
Yeah.
Do you still not like beer?
Well, that was only a few years ago.
Most alcohol I don't like the taste of.
Well, sure.
The alcohol itself is just kind of nasty.
And there's only been a couple where the flavor has been good enough to
mask it or work with it.
Like I like Baileys.
That's why mixed drinks exist.
The point of them is that you mixed stuff together so you don't taste the alcohol.
I think there was a few beers I've liked.
I like Hobgoblin, which is like a.
That's funny.
I've never heard of that.
It's like, I don't know what it is, like ale or pale ale or whatever.
It's a beer.
It's got a hobgoblin on the front, like a fancy creature.
Let me see.
Those taste all right.
I think it's a gold beer.
I remember really liking, yeah, I remember really liking this Icelandic beer
because it was like a lot of beer is quite bitter and like
yeasty or fermenty flavor.
And it's like whatever who cares.
But this was sort of sweet and smooth, but not super strong either.
It was it was really good.
And I don't know what it was called.
One time at in Atlanta with econ, I went to we went a couple times to this ramen restaurant.
And this place had a couple of Japanese beers and one beer that they had was this.
I guess it was sort of a novelty beer.
It was blue, but like it was light blue was pale like sky blue.
The beat the liquid was and it was supposed it was supposedly like
supposedly it was like it was naturally that color.
Like it was brewed with like glacier water or something.
And it was like, I don't think it was died.
And it was really good.
I really liked it.
It was very light and a little bit sweet.
And I was like, this is great.
It was like it was like 12 fucking dollars a bottle though.
So, you know, that's the way.
But it was neat.
I'm not sorry.
I tried it.
I like I like sours.
I like I like beers that are like.
Yeah, that are not that are very.
I mean, I don't exactly know what a sour is like how it's made.
But it's it's very like light and it's not very hoppy and it's very tart.
And sometimes it has a fruity taste.
I like sours a lot other than I like I don't really like dark beers.
I don't really like loggers.
I kind of just like drinking like some fucking like Miller light,
like piss water bullshit, because it's like whatever.
It's basically just water.
Ah, what we.
Like I barely even taste.
I mean, it's a good word for it.
Oh, because it's because it's just like drinking water.
You barely even taste it.
It's like fuck it.
Yeah.
Yes.
It was Einstok Icelandic pale ale.
I like that one.
And the hobgoblin is a dark English ale.
Yeah.
I guess I like ales.
Ales are good.
Have you ever had doomba?
Doomba is pretty good.
Corned.
Doomba is very good.
I love.
Well, I wouldn't say very good.
Most beer is like that's that's all right.
And hobgoblin and Icelandic pale ale go a little further.
I think they're not like my favorite thing to drink.
I'm just like if I'm in the mood to get drunk, I'd rather be this.
I think it's the seeds of the bloke in me that has come out in the last few years.
I just I just love the.
Seeds of the bloke.
There are aspects to my personality and the things that I like that I'm like,
oh fuck, I'm kind of am like a typical English fat guy bloke sometimes.
Dude, I take one drink of ale and I am king in the north.
I am Jon Snow.
I am all of that.
I'm glued to the footy.
I'm arguing about the rugby.
I'm kicking the cricket ball right in my son's head.
I'm doing all the stuff.
Hmm.
Well, I mean, you just lean into it, I guess.
I guess I could do.
You're going to be you're going to be wearing like an like a newsy cap and.
But what's what's a bloke?
What's a blokely thing to do?
Opening a newspaper to look at the boobies on page three.
Getting a tattoo of your favorite football team on your shoulder.
And then you're you're then you get really fat.
So the tattoo gets stretched out and it looks really terrible.
Seen that before.
That's pretty good.
It's a it's a it's a tradition.
It's a tradition.
It runs in the family.
Alcohol, cigarettes.
It's all garbage.
It's all shit.
It all tastes like crap.
It all smells terrible.
Just to have sex.
That's the only thing.
Just have sex.
Just just have sex, a virgin.
Yeah.
Especially to get a beer though.
You can only have one.
If you can't get it, draw it.
That's mine.
If you get drunk enough.
Draws beer.
Just damn.
Damn, I'm thirsty.
Draws a draw.
Draws a pint.
Beer or booba.
You could only draw one.
The answer is clear.
And it's not beer.
I'm slave to your edges, oblivion, full of your slight.
Most most most like guys, a lot of guys that I know and I'm friends with are very
they're very like into beer.
They're like they like they like to buy like micro brews and like oh locally brewed like oh
an IPA or like a pale stout or whatever.
It's like you know buying a fancy whatever.
Pick a new brand every week and it's and I'm like that's fine.
That's cool and all.
I like trying new things as much as the next guy.
But at the end of the day most of these most like of those beers are like they're strong.
They're like they're brewed to have a strong flavor.
Yeah.
And I'm like I don't kind of I kind of don't like the flavor.
I don't really drink it for the flavor like it's fine.
Like I kind of get how you can kind of enjoy like you sip like a dark lager
again or whatever and you're like ready.
It's like it's fine.
But like I kind of don't really care about that.
So you know just the piss water.
Piss water is fine.
And it's like a dollar fifty you can.
So who's the who's the real genius.
Who's the real real beer official.
I've only ever dipped into like fancy beers like once.
And it was when me and my friends went to a micro brewery in Lincoln.
And we had like a chocolate hazelnut stout.
And it was so fucking fulfilling.
It was like jam packed with fucking stomach space.
It feels like a couple years ago.
This was right when I moved back from Atlanta.
I moved back into my old place monkey house as we called it.
And I think like shortly after that I guess I wasn't invited.
Because I guess they had I guess they had had to schedule this in advance.
And I had not been back at the time.
So I couldn't go.
But a bunch of those guys went for one of their birthdays.
They went to some brewery.
And as part of this brewery trip they got to like.
They got to like mix their own a batch of their own beer or whatever.
Like they mixed it in like a keg or something.
And they you know then like later they would bottle this entire batch.
And they gave them like the whole batch and bottle.
So this guy got like yeah he got like like several dozen bottles of some like beer
that he had like technically brewed himself or whatever.
And I never tried it.
I never got to try it.
That's a cool gimmick.
It's a cool gimmick.
Wonder if it was good.
Yeah apparently brewed beer is actually really hard in terms of like stirring
it and shit.
So they might fuck that up and made some shitty beer.
I like to pretend that.
One one Christmas.
One Christmas I went to my uncle's house and my cousin was there.
And he and we didn't have anything to talk about.
So he kind of told me he was getting into like brewing his own beer or whatever.
I think he eventually like quit his his normie job and became like a.
He worked for some like micro brewery that he had like part ownership of or whatever.
They became a brew only.
They started a beer co-op or something like that.
And he showed me some of his like he showed me his like active.
I don't know what you call it.
He's like he showed me his active cultures.
He showed me some like tank that he was brewing in.
And like if you looked inside of it you could see that it was moving
because like the yeast inside was like alive and it was like swimming around in there fermenting.
And I was like weird man.
That's crazy man.
Seems cool I guess.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Not not a hobby I would probably pick up.
Yeah.
It's one of those things that's so like it's such a bad thing where like he gets.
Yeah it is.
He gets to like 60 and then he's not 60.
Like he gets like let's say 48.
I would say he's the perfect age for a dad to get really really into brewing.
And he clears out his garage and he puts fucking three vats in there.
It's like what are you doing?
It is a dadly thing.
I don't know.
You need a hobby I guess.
Yeah.
You do your thing.
Do your thing on the side.
Whatever if it's sparks joy in you.
Yeah.
More power to you.
It's you know it's equivalent to like making keto gummies.
It's just like what if I was in charge of what I consumed.
What if I was the means of production.
It probably yeah basically basically is.
And that's why I draw.
Yeah yeah.
Man sad again.
Sad again.
Crack found a link to a site that's that purported to offer isomaltoligosaccharides.
And it asked me to like enter my info and they would send me like a quote.
They would send me a quote for like how much will a certain quantity cost.
And I did it and they didn't send me anything.
I think the site is like is like soft to defunct.
It just doesn't work.
I was like damn it.
They were like this chump doesn't need enough
saccharide.
Maybe it maybe it was maybe like they saw the numbers I was asking for.
And they were just like this guy's not worth our time.
This guy's working in change.
We're dealing with this guy.
I'm sorry I only I'm sorry I only need like 10 to 20 pounds of the stuff.
I don't need like metric tons at a time.
Where would I even store it.
Where would I even store metric.
Wait.
I just thought of another gripe.
This is really important.
Can't get it's not a gripe.
No.
There's mice.
Oh no.
Mice in my kitchen.
Mice.
Ratatouille.
There were mice.
There were mice months ago.
I saw mice months ago and then I put down traps.
And I haven't seen any mice.
But then I was walking out my I was walking out my fucking bedroom door.
To my fucking clog toilet bathroom to not use it I guess.
And I heard and I heard a little rustling.
I heard something like twitch.
I heard a little paper bag rustling sound under the kitchen table.
Where we keep a bunch a bunch of people have bags of stuff.
And I went and I looked and I was like and I stopped and I listened.
And then I heard it again.
I heard a little rustle.
And I was like I think there's something.
I think there's something in one of these bags some creature.
So I like I walked towards it and I tried to like.
I wondered like what if I just picked up the bag that it's in.
And I just like threw it out into the parking lot.
Just throw the mice out of the house.
Right.
But I but I walked up towards it and as I got closer I stopped hearing it.
And then I couldn't I couldn't hear it anymore.
So I didn't know where it was.
And so I tried like I tried like nudging it.
I tried like kicking the little box that like the bags were in to try and see if I could make it move.
And I didn't hear anything.
And I was like and I was too scared.
I was too scared to like pick up the bag that I thought it was in.
Because I was like what if it like jumps out?
What if it like runs up my arms?
You're gonna fit five nights at Freddy's jump scares me right in the face.
Yeah.
So I couldn't do it.
I was like I'm just gonna I'm just gonna pretend I didn't hear anything.
I'm just gonna pretend it's not real.
And maybe it won't be.
But then why do I keep things under the table in bags?
You never keep like a bag of like rice or something?
I put it in a cupboard on the floor.
It's like asking for like little little creatures to come and get it.
Well, it's in like a rubber.
Yeah.
I mean in this I mean you're right.
And that's and that's what happened.
My stuff is at least it's in like a box.
It's not just like on the floor.
It's in like it's on the floor under the table, but it's in like a box.
But anyway, so I ignored it.
And then long story short, two days later I go again.
And this time I hear it again.
And this time I see two mice at the same time run out from under the table and run under the refrigerator.
And I'm like I think I think that my door closes tightly enough that the my that mice could not
come into my room as long as the the door was closed.
I think they could not get into my room unless they were to like burrow through the walls or
something. I don't know that for sure.
I would be very upset if there was like a mouse in my room like living in like a pile of my dirty
laundry or something that would that would ruin my my day.
There's not a chance there's not a mouse in your room.
There's one that poops in your mouth every night.
I'm sorry it's true.
So that's my other that's my other gripe.
Just pretend they're pets and then everything's fine.
Can we pretend that airplanes in the night sky are like shooting stars?
Can we pretend that mice that live under our table are really nice?
No they are nice. They seem nice. They're just gross.
You seem chill.
Mice are so small they're like cockroaches.
No they're not. They're cute no matter what.
They are a little cute.
They're cute but like if they're around on the floor and like you step on one and you kill it
that's terrible.
A corpse of any kind is not very cute.
I don't like knowing that like at any moment I could tread on an animal.
They are a little cute like up close but like from a distance like you turn on the light and one
of them scurries across the floor it's not it's it's like disgusting it's like it's a
cockroach it might as well be a cockroach.
I run over and try and give it a high five as quick as possible.
Ends up like slamming into the wall.
Just smushing it with my hand and killing the poor thing.
I would love have I ever I've probably mentioned the time that one time in my
old in monkey house I dropped a frying pan on a mouse on purpose.
There was a mouse and I saw it was on the floor and I was like how do we get it and I just dropped
a frying pan and it crushed it.
That's horrible.
I know but that's life.
That's not the life that's death.
That's mouse life ladies and gentlemen.
Son it's not disgusting it's just reality.
Take a deep breath and kill some mice.
Kill some mice.
Yeah.
I have to go to the bathroom.
I'll be back in one second.
I gotta pee.
Oh no we gotta entertain ourselves.
He's gonna go to the bathroom.
And he's gonna go and he's gonna go be like oh no that's blocked still.
It's clogged and there's mice in my toilet.
Then he's gonna walk over to the next the the other toilet and he's gonna
encounter a mouse or two and he's gonna come back and say guys there was a mouse's.
Oh my god.
That's my prediction.
Yeah you go oblivion for what you gotta say.
Um what do I have to say?
Um mouse cute.
What's better than a mouse?
A mouse woman.
No no here we go.
It's true.
There's a guy on youtube who draws for mouse and she has an ass and it's good.
Right is it?
I can imagine such a thing.
Is it the guy who's using the name of something like J-A-O.
J-I-O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O That's his name.
J-I-O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O He follows me.
It's great.
Yeah that's cool.
Legend moment.
Uh I wanted to think, I designed a mof uh a big tittie mof character.
Oh yeah I saw that that was cute.
On the draw cast.
I like that.
Yeah um she's cute and I and I thought of a really funny idea.
I'm back.
Hello.
What's not.
Part of a funny idea with my mof character.
I'll post a picture over if it doesn't show her pussy.
So that way you'll be safe.
Impossible.
I don't believe you've drawn such a thing.
It's cropped.
I mean, it's cropped.
Yeah, I cropped it.
Um, okay.
The uncropped is on my Patreon at the moment.
There's also a version where she lifts her shirt.
But, um, so, so the idea I had, if I want to, I want to have a NOC that's like a
masochist, uh, cause I think that's funny.
I think it's funny if you have a character who just wants to get beat up and
they think it's good, actually.
Um, I thought, what if, what if I do that with a character who's a bug?
She's just a little bug and she wants, she wants you to like pull her fucking
legs off and shit.
Oh my God.
Yikes.
Cause I drew it with two arms and I'm like, people like, oh, don't usually like,
if you're drawing like a bug girl, you give her four arms.
And I'm like, oh, I fought about it.
I'm like, no, she had the other arms pulled off because, um, she enjoys it.
And then they just grow back.
They grow back and pull them off again.
You know, you can't pull off too many, you can't pull off too many at a time.
You can't put a whole, yeah.
Like she, she, she's got to keep at least two so she can go for her daily
functions, but, uh, she, she likes bug zappers, you know, you know, people in
the BDSM sometimes I like getting electric shocks.
She likes the bug zapper.
She likes to fly swatter.
She likes newspapers.
She likes getting hit by cars.
Um, I, I, I was like, what?
Like splatting on the windshield, just splatting on the windshield.
Yeah.
Oh, I was thinking about size cars.
Yeah, like human, human cars.
She's in the human world.
She's just this, she's like one foot tall or something.
She's, she's got to be at least big enough to put a penis in.
Um, and it's too big and that's also good.
And I thought of a funny like music video.
I just want to montage of her just getting squashed and electrocuted, but enjoying
it and then go into a bug hospital and just, I've been thinking of all these
funny ideas in my head and I want to do like a simple, I want to do in like a
simplified, like almost like barely more of a storyboard style animation similar
to that, uh, that one guy who draws the mouse for joy.
Oh, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you.
Um, anything that'd be fun.
Yeah, the only thing is that after drawing this character, I stared at it
and I stared at it for a while and I'm like, looks, looks a little familiar.
Looks.
Oh, no.
I, I, I hope.
Wait, I think I see it.
I see it.
Yeah.
And I'm like, huh, maybe I should change the hair a bit because it's a little too
similar to someone we know.
She doesn't have a copyright on that hair style.
I think it's just like the mitt.
Yeah.
It's Marge Simpson.
Oh, yeah, Marge Simpson, she starts with an M.
Exactly.
You're right.
I don't know.
I couldn't tell, so I don't know.
You know, I actually think Marge Simpson might not even be real.
That's a controversial opinion, but if she's not, if she's a fictional character,
she can't copyright anything.
True.
Mickey Mouse can't even copyright themselves.
So really, um, it's all fair game.
True.
True question.
Only his, his, uh, his master, his, his, his wrangler can, can copyright Mickey Mouse.
John Mickey, what's his name?
John Doon.
No, he can't because he's dead.
It's true.
No, it's Walter Mouse.
Because he's fucking dead.
Walter J.
Is that from, is that from Mr.
Boop?
Walter Mouse.
Yeah.
No, it's doing like Walt Disney, but his last name is Mouse.
Okay.
And he named his Mickey after it.
But in Mr.
Boop, he goes to, no, it's, no, it's Mr.
Boop, but Mr, doesn't Mr.
Boop also own Mickey or just, or did they just mention Mickey?
Because Mickey has copyright issues also in that.
That's part of the story.
Oh, it's been so long since I read it.
I have no idea.
You can't have been that long.
It was only last year.
Yeah, but I'm a fucking idiot.
But I, I, yeah, well, I forget to.
So who am I?
Who, who am I judge?
Uh, no, I got, no, I don't think so.
Cause I, cause I remembered there was like, oh, big copyright man.
But I was thinking of Mr.
Boop, like the, the dad.
But then I also remember that Mickey is like, oh, oh, my, my master
wouldn't be happy if he knew that I was having orgies with other cartoon
characters.
Oh, and, uh, and I conflated, I conflated them.
No way.
Hmm.
Mickey Mouse did that.
It's true.
He did.
Master would be happy.
Clearly.
You see his dick.
You see Mickey's dick in that.
My main memory from Mr.
Boop was a, a very move Goku coming downstairs with a bath towel around his
cock saying, Hey, get back here with continuing the orgy or something like
that.
And I was like, that's awesome.
I think that happened.
Yeah.
That was, that was pretty good.
That's pretty good.
Mid, mid, mid, mid, mid run.
That's stuck with me.
There's a, just the, the, the, the, the, in the orgy era.
There's something about sticking Goku in things that makes it funny.
I don't know why.
Yeah.
Is it his like ridiculously like carved angular muscles.
Yes.
That clash with every other art style.
It exists.
It's true.
And then it's also the, the eyebrows.
It's the fact that he's, he's, he's wacky silly as well.
Goku is a wacky silly character.
So putting him like in anything is just odd.
I don't know why he does, he does act.
He is silly enough that his, his, his personality is like cartoonish, goofy,
Mickey Mouse, Donald Duck, goofy style, I guess, but he just looks like that.
Yeah.
This is beefcake muscle, man.
What a hero.
Yeah.
A true shonen hero.
Speaking of which, I've been reading Full Metal Alchemist recently
because I watched it like years ago and I remember literally nothing about it.
So it's.
Did you watch Brotherhood?
I think I watched Brotherhood.
Yes.
Okay.
I believe so.
I've only seen the original.
I've never seen Brotherhood.
I know the original gets pretty crazy and it sounds funny and cool, but.
I, it's pretty weird.
The original, the original ending and the movie that they made about it is
pretty, is pretty fucking weird.
I liked it.
I liked it a lot.
It sounds very unique for it.
And I, yeah, there were like little bits in the manga that I
referenced that I was reading that were like, you know, how like the beginning
of a manga chapter, sometimes the author will have like a comment.
And it was, it was, she was talking about how the anime was ending.
And I was like, oh, Jesus, that makes, that puts it in timeline really
weirdly in my head.
Yeah.
But, um, and like how she, she, she gave them a few ideas and was just like, yeah,
go wild.
And she loved the way that it went.
And I was like, ah, that's cool.
Maybe I'll have to give the anime a chance someday.
This is very, it's like George, it's like George RR Martin.
It's like Game of Thrones.
They're just like, well, I'm still right in the book.
They're, they're finishing the, the show.
Uh, I guess I'll just tell them like, uh, what if you did this?
What if you, what if you ended like that?
Fuck it.
Um, is that how, is that something that happened?
I thought he was like largely like disconnected from the show running by
that, the point they were going beyond the books.
I remember hearing that he gave them the outlines for the end.
And he like barely understood what was going on.
It's just like, well, you know, that's, that's their thing now.
So I, I don't think so because I don't, I mean, he might have been less involved
by that point than he was originally, but I think he did have input because I
remember they talked about like the, the, the hold the door thing was like
direction him.
Like, like he told them about that.
That's, that's, they didn't come up with that.
Right.
The, yeah.
He, I'm sure he gave them like a general gist of like where characters end up.
Um, but like the, I mean, a lot of the reason the show is so like shit right at
the end is that they have the ending in mind and they don't like,
they don't properly build to it.
They just sort of have the characters as they've evolved through the show as opposed
to the books and then, you know, changed a few character arcs and like dropped a
bunch of them and just say, okay, well, you wouldn't do this, but because your
ending is coming up, you will now do this.
And it's completely out of character for you in the show.
And who cares six episodes in the last season, just get, get it done.
Well, and that's why that was like different.
So I know he, he had, he had some like say in like, what would the ending be?
Yeah.
That he has for his book thing.
I remember hearing that he gave an outline of who ends up where, like in terms
of throne things like that.
Yeah.
I don't know if I should just say it.
I think he may have changed his plan since though.
Like he's, he's, he's mentioned that his, his books will not be the same as the show.
Yeah.
I think that's a given.
Which is a.
Yeah.
So I'm wondering if he like just said, here's my like first draft ideas for how
the show ends or how the books end and use that.
I kind of like that.
I know the second My Hero Academia movie does that where the author of the
manga had come up with what he wanted the final action scene to be.
And he changed his mind.
So he just gave them that to do in the movie.
And it's just fucking ridiculous.
And it's like, oh, it's in a non-canon movie.
So it's nice that we got to see it.
It's that that's fun.
I like that.
It's not the ending of the TV show that everyone loved and ruining it though.
They didn't actually love it, right?
No.
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh, I don't, I don't, I haven't seen, I haven't, I've read a little bit of, I like,
I read the beginning of My Hero Academia.
It is fine.
It's completely the most like white bread.
Like, yeah, this is quality, but there's nothing, there's really nothing special
about it, aside from the art style.
I think I liked, I did like the art impression.
Yeah, I like how the faces look, like how the eyes look on the, I like that the
mouths, the mouths and the teeth.
The mouths are always really like rounded and cute looking and fun.
And the teeth are very detailed and weird.
Ben, into Vor once again, clearly.
I, I, it was, it was all over like the internet, like everyone was talking about,
it felt like everyone was talking about My Hero Academia for a while.
I had checked it out a little bit before that.
I think maybe Nate had talked about it or someone had talked about it.
And I had checked it out and I read a bit and I was like, yeah, that's cool.
I think I liked the gimmick of like, I think I was, I think I liked, uh, All Might.
I think that like, that he was like, that he was, I liked that he was like weak.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I thought that was reminds me of myself.
I think I checked it.
Yeah.
It's, it's, but, but, but then now late, everyone, it seemed like everyone was
really, really excited about it on the internet for a while.
But now, whenever I see anyone talk about it, it's like they were, it seems
like everyone was disappointed in it.
Or it seems like generally the opinion has somewhat turned.
Yeah.
I think not like hugely against it, but somewhat.
I think part of it is what I like to call the legend of core effect where
something is okay, but then everyone like turns on it because it's so popular
and loved.
Um, yeah, that, that has happened to some extent of it.
There are definitely parts of the series that I think kind of smell and a boring,
but like the last like year or so of it have been pretty like solid.
I don't know.
But, um, seems, seems kind of like what happened to attack on Titan.
Yes.
This is my hero academia, a, a, a manga story about a young man with a super
power and all these people who have superpowers, but they also have to go to
school and they're superpowers at school.
Is that what it's about?
Yes.
That's right.
Basically.
Damn.
So basic.
I know.
So fringe.
Exactly.
I assume that's what it was from what I saw.
And I'm like, there's a little twistiness of it.
One punch man just come out and it's like a parody of that and it's so much funnier.
One punch man doesn't go to school.
Yeah.
No, but like it's like.
Also, that was like 10 years ago of one punch man is like 100 years old now.
Go with the times.
I feel like the thing that sets my hero academia apart is the fact that the
they explained that the, that it's 90% of the planet or something like,
or 99% of the planet that have some super power.
So it isn't just like a certain people have it.
It's everybody has something and some people are really good.
But like, what does that change about it?
It's cool.
Like it's all right.
Shonen, generally, they are a vehicle by which combat can be, you know,
experienced.
Exactly.
My hero academia.
What if this was like a fight and instead of punching, there was some weird wacky thing instead.
Bulk of what the Shonen genre is about.
Takes place in an alternate timeline of the Incredibles universe where syndrome
one, yes, and everybody got a, got a super power.
That's true.
Dude, that's correct.
And so Madagascar.
Huh?
That's true.
Madagascar ending.
I look, I got this, I saw like a video talking about this, but if you see a
world map and attack on Titan after everything gets expanded and they,
they leave the walls and they leave Ireland and everything.
And the world map is just Earth, just flipped upside down and everything
takes place on Madagascar.
Crazy.
Like the movie Madagascar?
No, like the, the play like, is Madagascar the movie canon to attack on Titan?
The movie Madagascar isn't a fictional place that Dreamworks invented.
It's real, it's a real place.
Yeah, but, yeah, but I want to know if the events of the film Madagascar and
sequels are canon to attack on Titan.
Did Chantelle Dubois happen in the, in the attack on Titan universe?
Did that villain from Madagascar three Europe's most wanted, the best
film ever made?
Did she canon to attack on Titan?
That is, she is an acrimon.
She is a descendant.
Oh, cool.
Very nice.
Attack on Titan is another movie Madagascar free.
It's a game of fucking psychotic.
I kind of think she's great.
I would say Attack on Titan is a game of thrones level blunder for me.
I know some people really like the ending, but I fucking get it.
Oh, I never, I never got to the ending.
I'm very excited because the, the last season is coming out now, I think.
So people are going to see the ending.
I'm very excited to see the discourse come around about it and see what people think.
I think, I think the ending is weird.
I, I liked when like the world opened up and we got to see, see like all like.
Yeah, I love that.
The world has like more modern technology that like to me made the show
finally like actually interesting because I didn't, I didn't care about that.
It was just a big mystery box fest for a long time.
I didn't give a shit about that really.
And then when I said it's like a game of thrones, I mean, like
the very last second it throws the bucket in like the last five chapters,
I think Attack on Titan just falls off a cliff.
Do the fucking weird.
The bigger they are, the harder they fall BS.
We can't, we can't talk about it because it's going on right now.
And I don't want to ruin it for people, but for my own opinions, it sucks.
The Titans are actually not as big as we thought.
They were actually bigger Titans and those they just
one of the biggest Titans in the universe came and he put his foot down,
smashed the earth, everyone's dead.
It's you've seen, you've seen the end of Gerr, of Gerr and Lagann when,
when, when the guys in their mechs get their mechs into bigger mechs
and then they get those mechs into even bigger mechs.
Well, Attack on Titan, same thing.
The Titans get form even bigger Titans around themselves.
It's alarming how on point you guys are.
Oh, no, you're kind of like unironically correct.
Yeah, it's been addressed.
It's been addressed in the anime at this point.
So we can't kind of talk about it, but there's this concept called the rumbling
where like a fuckload of colossal.
You remember the colossal Titan, the really, really big guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there's like hundreds of them and a character.
It's millions at the word that they specifically say that there's millions.
Is it millions? Jesus.
That's that's at least the translation I read of the is millions of them said that
and they're going to use them to wipe out the rest of the planet as revenge for being fucked over.
It's just big.
All right. How tall is a colossus Titan?
I think the colossal one is the one that is like taller than the walls of the like 60.
They're like so like hundreds and hundreds.
Yeah, they're like.
Yeah, hmm.
I'm trying to think of like like the biggest dinosaurs and how like the potentially
largest way bigger, way bigger, way bigger.
OK, no, a regular, a regular Titan is like a regular Titan is like dinosaur size.
The colossal Titan is like.
I mean, even I mean, it's like it's like a hundred blue whales or bigger, bigger than that even.
Should I post all of the manga panels?
No, no, it's Godzilla.
It's Godzilla sized or even bigger than Godzilla sized.
Should I post one of the manga panels to give some idea?
I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll provide.
I'll provide.
So there's this funny flash game called Age of War, right?
Mm hmm.
Do you remember this as cool?
I remember I had Halo music as I've ever played this one.
Well, anyway, there's these funny YouTube videos.
Why is there like a Jesus meter in the top right?
It's like a guy being crucified.
You can use your smite ability or something.
OK. Well, anyway, there's a funny YouTube video.
There's a whole bunch of videos like doing size comparisons for all the Titans
and some of the really wacky crazy ones that come out in every end
that are like 400 meters tall or some bullshit.
And the videos look like this game.
They have these little funny walking animations that are really janky
and they're just walking in place and it's really funny.
But but the size comparison is useful, I guess.
But it's spoilery.
I don't know if I could share if people care about spoilers.
I don't care when the Colossus Titan from Attack on Titan
or the behelit like like what's his face?
The many faced big guy.
Ganesha from Berserk.
Ganesha a man from Berserk.
I think Ganesha would win because he's fucking like a god man by the end, isn't he?
He turns into a tree, though, and he has no brain.
He's like so he's so he did the thing twice.
I mean, all the Colossus Titans do is walk forward and kill people basically.
They just stomp.
Oh, my gosh, dude.
This is the size comparison video.
Me, me, me cast a acrimon, the smallest Titan of them all.
It's true.
It's canon.
Oh, God, these fucking flash puppets.
Why did they even bother?
Why don't they animate it like this?
Why wouldn't you just have you could just have a static image?
It would be fine.
It's terrifying.
It's because it's an animated show, Ben.
You've got to have animated in your YouTube.
Literally like skipped like to the five minute mark to start seeing the big ones,
I guess. Yeah.
They're pretty big.
This is a terrible video.
They start out pretty small.
Really funny.
They're only oh, hmm.
Hmm.
How do they hold up their own way?
A cartoon logic, because, you know,
attack is a wacky silly cartoon found founding Titan.
Oh, my God.
What the?
Yeah, it gets pretty crazy.
That's stuff I like.
It's just like.
I've never seen this like fucking fish skeleton one.
Yeah.
Oh, well, that's that's a spoiler.
OK, that's a huge.
That's what happens when you tell Aaron Yeager that he smells like a barker
and he turns into a giant fish monster and kills the entire planet.
Yeah. Jesus.
It's pretty cool. OK, there.
Well, like, technically,
technically, I've watched the whole show now.
That's true.
That's all that's all that runs in the rib cage.
I see the most creepy monsters.
These things are disgusting.
Then these are like, then it's genuinely invested in the designs.
I am. No, I always was.
I always really liked how like how just how viscerally gross
and like I hate these things so much.
The Titans are like, they're so vile.
It's one of the strongest aspects of it, I think.
Yeah, I like the founding Titan.
Yeah, wherever the.
And I know the manga artist has like another artist
who does like the really nice panels that show up every so often.
Oh, really? The founding Titan is pretty cool.
I they have to because the art style is like suddenly like really good on some
yeah, and then it looks janky elsewhere.
I will say because the guy panels.
The guy's like not a very good artist.
Like his original manga is like, it looks pretty shit.
Yeah, the first few volumes are pretty rough looking,
but I feel he really does improve throughout the course of it.
And it does look great unless like oblivion for said the other guy was doing the whole thing.
He he he doesn't improve.
He probably also had assistance to do like, you know, cleaner,
cleaner line work and stuff like this.
It's fucking cool. I'm sorry.
This one's pretty spoilery.
I shouldn't have posted that. Oh, God.
It's horrible. It's OK. I didn't mind.
I'm pretty sure I like this image where the where the skeleton
like is just screaming.
You look at his jaw and it's just wide open.
I'm pretty sure the show's reached this point.
I haven't watched the last two episodes,
but I'm pretty sure it's reached. Yeah, I think it's I've got gearing up.
I've heard big stuff.
I've heard that the.
Oh, you know what?
I remember at the end of the part of the show I watched,
you see the wall crumble and you see what's inside the wall.
So OK, this is kind of like I kind of get what's going on all the millions of
Titans that stomp on that stomp on everyone are the ones from the walls, basically.
Yeah, I did.
I did always want to finish the show because I did like what I read.
Everyone said the ending was was bad and it gets really stupid.
And that was like that a chilling effect on me.
I guess I wasn't enjoying the show for a while.
I read after like because we were waiting a million years for season two
and then eventually I'm like, fuck it, I'll read a bit of the manga.
And I did. I would I would rather watch.
I would rather read almost any manga than watch the show version.
Yeah, basically unilaterally.
I don't know if there's any exception to that.
I mean, in terms of a show,
I would say it's only worth watching up until the end of season three,
because that's when they still had their really good animator on board,
the one who is basically who basically fucking carried the whole show.
By doing like every fucking action scene by being a god tiered piece of shit,
who I love.
And then in season four, they changed studios
and that guy no longer works in the show.
We also did all the best like fighting like moments
and one punch man as well.
Yeah.
Right, right, right.
He's a really good animator.
So it's worth seeing at least his scenes because they are really well done.
But beyond that, just read the manga, probably.
The Mr. Boop guy, Alec Robbins, a little while back,
I think he finally got around to watching Mob Psycho
and he said he loved Mob Psycho.
So he was gushing about it.
It made me want to check it out.
Oh, you haven't seen Mob Psycho?
No, I have not seen Mob Psycho.
Oh, it's really good.
I only I only hear really good things about it.
Yeah, it's what I did.
I did like one punch man, although I never finished one punch man.
Yeah, but it's in the anime season or the manga.
I I think I read up to the point in the manga
that had been drawn at the time.
I don't know if it if it finished, I assume it did.
No, the manga is still going, I believe.
Really? Oh, wow. OK.
Because the web comics still going as well, I think,
because you know how it's as he needed to use two punches at this point.
With the web, that's the web comic.
Like the originally drawn web comic is still going. Yes, I think so.
What? Yeah, no way.
They're still building up to crazy shit, apparently.
I haven't kept up with it, but I see stuff every now and again
when talking to people and it seems like it's going strong.
I didn't watch.
I didn't watch the anime because I had read the manga.
I know it looked great.
Everyone praised the animation and it did look pretty good,
but like I don't really care that the manga is also one of the best looking
manga of all time. It does.
It does. Yeah, it really does.
Although I still like the idea of reading the original
web comic comic that drawn by one, even though even though the art is bad.
Like, I just think that's cool.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, I need to read that.
That's what makes Mob Psycho work so well is because it's directly
it's directly adapted from his comic as opposed to like a re adaptation
in the manga, like where it's drawn better.
So it's like, yeah, it's these sketchy, simplistic character designs
that are like focused entirely on expression, basically, and not aesthetic
quality and they're animated by the gods at Studio Bones.
And it just makes Mob Psycho one of the best looking things ever.
So they can they can go very simple with the faces and stuff
and then go crazy with like effects and things like that and motion.
Yeah. So it was it was a manga first.
Yeah, Mob Psycho was a manga, which was like OK.
I think it was pretty short.
I think it was like 10 or 11 volumes, so it wasn't crazy long.
But yeah. Yeah.
I should I should watch it's great.
Season three coming at some point this year, which I think will be the end.
Oh, it's still going. Yeah, I thought it was I thought it was done.
I thought it was just a one season one and then season two came out in like
twenty seventeen, so it's been like years.
Yeah, because I didn't want to read the man because the anime is too good.
It's one of those things where I got caught. Yeah, that's fair.
My friend's been he's been watching one piece of the anime, all of it.
And he's on nice.
He's on Dressroser at the moment and he's starting to feel it.
He's starting to feel that the slow.
I think that's Dressroser in specific is like terrible.
I think most people stopped at that point and switched to reading the manga.
Yeah, I think I switched to reading the manga a few arcs earlier.
It was I got frustrated.
I got frustrated with the pace even reading the manga in in I think it was
Fishman Island. Yeah, I was like, this is this is going on a really long time.
It was at the time the biggest arc, Fishman Island.
Yeah, you can say that about every arc at this point.
I got I can't imagine watching longer.
I can't imagine watching all of the show at this point.
I know, I don't know how he did it.
It's got to be like it's it's got to be over a thousand episodes, right?
There's something I've noticed where where people seem to have
like a like a like a charge in them of how much
anime they can watch in their lifetime.
And then like after you've watched a certain amount,
you'd switch to like way shorter stuff or you'd stop watching.
Yeah, because like he's realized that it's just more efficient.
Yeah, it's just the better you see your time.
My friend, his only watched Naruto and Fulmer Alchemist, I think, before One Piece.
He was really not like a big anime guy and it's like, wow, yeah.
How is he doing?
I think it would take one piece as a as like an like if you haven't seen a lot
of anime is very good mostly because of like the really good music that sells
a lot of the epic moments and gets you hyped to watch the next episode every time.
It's very easy to binge.
I remember watching, I think like the anime was like a thriller bark or something beyond that.
I actually can't remember, but like I remember binging all of One Piece and I
got like like a couple of hundred episodes in a week.
Yeah, that's maybe more than that.
And it was like, it was great.
I can't remember.
I like it's it's kind of upsetting though, because it's like the music and some
of the scenes that are depicted in the anime of One Piece are like so like emotional.
Yeah.
And like it being animated and with the sound effects and the voice acting and
then the music, yeah, it adds so much to those moments.
But like, I can't recommend people watch One Piece.
That's so fucking long.
Yeah, they'd never do it.
Completely agree.
That's it's it's big.
Binks sake is so much better in in the in the anime.
Yeah, you can hear it when there's a whole musical sequence to it.
But yeah, but you'd have to but you'd have to watch 981 episodes a few years ago.
Do it when I got into One Piece.
It was like I watched the podcast like live thingy.
I think it was and like where you talk about how to get into it.
I think briefly and it's like, I'll read the manga and watch all the
bit the moments that you liked the most from the manga on YouTube.
And I did that and that was pretty much perfect.
Yeah.
And I did some I did some listening to the soundtrack while I read it
because I'm one of those weirdos.
The the OK.
So it's 981 episodes, which OK.
I guess you you could watch all of the all of that in less time
than I have spent playing Noida in my life.
So yeah, that's you know.
So I guess I guess I I guess you could do it.
I swear it's more than that.
But I could have sworn they got past episode 1000.
I thought it would be for the bankers gone past that.
Yeah, apparently the way the anime is on episode 1008.
Apparently, according to this totally legal anime watching website.
Oh, well, I well,
Google says 981.
Well, they're bloody maybe they're maybe they're wrong.
OK, OK, OK, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, oh, here's another interesting detail.
I think he's watching the dub, which is.
I don't think I've ever heard a whole show.
Yeah, they've gotten up to Zoe, I think.
So he's going to have to switch soon.
They they they Zoe is the elephant.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just before Holkig Island.
So I don't think I've ever heard anyone speak about the one piece stuff.
So people don't know that I remember back in the day that the dub was done
by four kids and it was like laughable and that's terrible adaptation.
That's how I found it.
That's how I that's how I got into one piece was through the four kids dub.
But then there was another dub.
Was it the Funimation?
Yeah, it's Funimation.
Yeah, and they should be doing the entire show.
Yes, I did.
Did they I thought they just kind of picked up where four kids left off?
No, they went back and did it later for DVD releases, apparently.
OK, well, that's probably good.
The whole thing exists.
And I listened to some clips of it.
It's surprisingly pretty good.
Something about Shodan works in dubs for me.
I don't love Luffy's voice, though.
It's kind of not great, which is kind of a problem.
What does it sound like?
It's the big character.
Did you ever watch Dragon Ball Kai Gip?
Nope.
OK, it's the voice actress for Gohan from that.
And it's Hello and Luffy.
It's a little too scrimmy.
Luffy is scrimmy, but there's lots of deadpan moments.
Yeah. Oh, what do you what do you mean, Zoro?
Yeah, it's a bit like that.
It's a bit full on all the time and just a tiny bit too feminine.
I'm a pirate. Believe it.
Yeah. Yeah, it's a it's a little Naruto dub kind of.
No, that's a shame.
That's a shame.
But everyone else is pretty solid.
I like I like what I saw.
Usopp is just Krillin, because, of course, he is.
Yeah, I heard they got him.
No, it sounds that makes sense.
I think the thing is in the Japanese dub is is that like
the voice actress plays Luffy.
In a way that he sometimes just sounds like a monkey.
Yeah, like he laughs like a monkey.
He also has a lot of deadpan deliveries, I think, I feel like.
In the anime, which people don't talk about a lot,
but the her voice performance is him.
There's a lot of moments where she's like, oh, OK, like that.
And I'm like, that works pretty well.
And there's none of that in the dub, which is a problem, in my opinion.
Because Luffy saying things flat because he's a fucking moron is
one of my favorite things about him.
Next episode of Talking Pirates will talk more.
I haven't watched Pease.
I haven't. What am I?
What am I? I'm still I'm still at.
I'm still at in one piece, the place where I was
when I almost caught up at Radcon 4, which is I'm past Whole Cake.
Oh, hey, I had just gotten to Wano.
Yeah. So you went through the the reverie stuff,
which is like a few chapters in between.
Wait, that's when all the kings and queens come together and chat.
Yes, Rebecca and VV together, and they look exactly the same.
Hmm, because they have the default female character of Ark model.
They're Nami types.
Have I shown you my one piece girl types chart that I made?
I know, maybe. Let me see this.
This might be funny to post.
I mean, when you say chart, you mean like two?
Like they're either Nami.
No, they're ridiculously exaggerated.
There's Nami types, there's Robin types, and there's aberrants.
And here is it. Here is the fact that I made.
Of these, and then there's subtypes within them.
Almost all Robin are in the lip subtype.
Interesting fact, almost all Robin subtypes are in the lip subtype.
I can't remember why I made this.
I think I was just very tired and thinking about it.
And I was like, yeah, why not?
Ugly subtype.
OK, OK.
My criticism is the only difference
between Nami types and Robin types is the hair color.
Yeah, looking at it now.
There's a there's a difference with the eyes as well.
The eyes are a lot rounder on Nami types, I feel like.
In my opinion, maybe on some of these.
They usually like Robin and Hancock have like slanted
downwards eyes on the outside.
It's like they I'll be honest.
I didn't know that Robin and Hancock were different characters.
I know. I know what you mean.
Until I see the names, like I forget.
I really don't.
OK, I can tell I'm only three minutes in to Nate's lecture.
Wait.
I OK, I'm trying to identify.
OK, there's some.
There's two that you won't know because of one, three.
OK, several of these I genuinely can't tell aren't just Robin and Nami.
OK, OK, I see Shira Hoshi.
I don't know the girl with the horns.
I know the bunny girl.
Who I don't know who that chef is.
I guess she's just some rando from a whole cake.
Is that that's pudding?
Yeah, that's pudding.
Why is she dressed like a chef?
Because it's when they make the wedding cake.
Oh, because she goes crazy.
Is that a is that a mermaid that last
is an unusual outfit for her?
That's camey the mermaid.
Yeah. OK.
And then they're OK.
I see in the Robin types,
I see there's the the smokers assistant lady.
Tashige. Yeah.
Tashige, Boa Hancock.
I don't know the next two.
And those are those different characters, Ben, those two there.
Yeah, are they? OK.
And then the one with the mask is one of the
Oh, fuck, what are they called?
The ones that they fight in the dress.
Rosa in Alibaba.
No, in alabaster. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Not to press Rosa, Ben.
Really? She's like she baby five.
Is that her name?
That's baby five.
She's the one that turns her body into guns.
And she's she has a devil fruit turns her body into weapons.
Yeah, OK. What was I what am I thinking of?
What's the what's Crocodile's organization called?
But the Baroque works.
Yeah, I thought she was a Baroque works girl.
But no, OK.
She's yeah, you're right.
And then the last one.
Oh, the last one is that one that
Sanji like falls in love with in dress Rosa.
What's your name?
Violet. Yes.
Yeah.
Best, best, best one.
Best one piece girl is Perona.
There's no.
I would have thought Perona would be yours.
Yeah, well, it's true.
It's true. She's one of the funny eyeballs.
But the round the really round.
Yeah, that's that's Perona with the big hat.
That's Perona. Yeah, pink hair.
The one the one to her right is my favorite.
Sanderson. Oh, Sandersonia.
Yeah, I drew her.
I just really like her wide face.
Yeah, that makes that makes sense.
That makes total sense.
Sandersonia.
I really, I really like this.
This this Ukiyo a like side view Japanese looking one.
She's one of my favorite designs.
She's awesome.
Actually, I really I also really like
Shirahoshi's mom.
What's what's her name?
Otohime. Yeah, I think she's one of my favorite signs.
Otohime is is one of the best ones.
Yeah. Yeah.
So Yoda can do it sometimes.
He just likes to default to the simple ones.
He just he just likes drawing
like this a circle head with facial features that are the same.
These ones that are different are actually they're actually good.
Who's this one with the blonde hair in the glasses?
Is that a CP nine?
Yeah, no, that's yeah.
That's Khalifa.
Yeah, I think the name's not sheep.
The the the the bubble, the soap one.
Yes, what not me?
Yes, yes, I remember.
I don't recognize this like snake looking one,
even with the chopsticks.
Is she a wano girl?
No, she's from Fishman Island.
She's the prophecy lady.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm Shirley.
Yeah, yeah, Charlie.
Yeah, OK, I remember.
OK, well, I kind of know that stuff.
You know most of them, Ben.
Fine, I know most of them.
That's pretty good.
Rebecca right there looks like so non-distinct,
even amongst the nami types.
Yeah, Otohime would be played by Helena Bonham Carter.
Yes, true.
Yeah.
Actually, you know what?
That makes me like her less.
No, Charlie would be.
Charlie would be.
Oh, is it because like Otohime has like mascara or like eyeshadow?
I think it's it's like kind of kind of her like rectangular head.
And big lips and big lips and Otohime.
Well, it's not rectangular, but she's like a wide set head and wide jaw.
I don't know.
What a good design.
Cute, cute, so cute.
I love God bless.
God bless.
Oblivion for read one piece.
You'll like it.
God bless everyone.
Never have something else to do first.
No, Bummer.
You're missing out on some very funny character designs.
Very funny character designs.
I still gotta finish watching Detective Conan
and then that's like a number of five hundred episodes
and I've already watched five hundred episodes.
How could you not get tired of Detective Conan?
I like it.
That's the it's it's detected.
And I guess it's like if you like detective little mini stories
of one after the other.
The mystery is a lot of them are really, really, really, really fucking clever.
And I'm like, damn, I want to commit a murder now.
I read like a bunch of like a hundred or so a bunch of chapters.
I don't know how many chapters I read, but I was like,
OK, you you grabbed me with this initial mystery
and I enjoy these side mysteries that are just sort of like Detective Conan
solving a mystery, but I don't like that you've decided to pretend
to string me along with an answer to this bigger mystery about
who's behind turning him into a small child,
because I know you're never going to do it.
You just fucking lied to me and I got a mad.
No, this this this being this being some like big ass fucking things
that have happened that just really spread out.
And there's wait, like recently, well, no, like around episode
five hundred of the show, at least, and I think around episode 128.
There's been a few points where like they've revealed some big stuff
and there's been big plot things.
There is a lot of filler and a lot of the filler is good,
but some of it is kind of boring.
I feel like like Detective Conan would be more enjoyable
if it was just this is a young kid who's really good at detective work.
And here's like a serial of him doing detectives things.
And every week, there's a new every episode, there's a new mystery.
Oh, and it's fun.
Simsie, who is this?
It's Charlotte Amanda from One Piece, one of Big Mom's daughters
who doesn't really do anything, but she's great.
She. Yeah, she's got the best.
Like I got a huge part giraffe.
You is that you're drawing Simsie?
Yes.
She drew her hat way too small.
That hat is like, I know.
The next one is not long enough.
What's her name?
Amanda, like Amanda, not the best design.
Yeah.
She literal T pose woman.
Charlotte Amanda, Amanda, I see face.
Oh, my God.
It's such a funny image.
She looks way better in your drawing in real life.
No, she's a lamp face.
Oh, you know what?
Actually, she's got like a bowling pin head.
Actually, when you see her, her like full body.
OK, this is this.
She looks cool here.
Oh, you already are.
You already posted it.
OK, yeah, she looks.
OK, I get it.
I get it. She's sick.
Shut up.
What's this? OK.
All right. All right.
This is awesome.
All right. One piece kind of good.
Does she really?
She doesn't like fight or anything?
No, she she makes sticky and then steal something out of her tits.
I remember that.
There was like a there's so many good character designs.
There's not time for them all to do some cool.
Yeah. And in whole cake, I remember, there was like, here's.
Well, here's a big mom's crew.
There's so many people in it, and it's an unwinnable situation.
We have to get the fuck out of here.
So they couldn't.
It wasn't really like a let's defeat all of these people in turn.
It's here's too many people.
We got it. We can't defeat them.
So they didn't actually get to do much.
And they're all perfect.
They just got to stand there and look cool.
And it's scary.
They're just flexing a whole room of like any one of these could be
look could have like a whole like side arc devoted to them
if I felt like it, but I don't fuck it.
Let's move on.
It's such wrong.
What a good design.
There's just too many.
That's just like how he draws like fat ladies.
I don't know why they're really funny.
They are funny.
That's funny.
These are this makes me this this makes me happy.
This brings us this brings a smile to my face.
This whole.
Oh, it's like about one face.
A smoothie.
Smoothies pretty good. Yeah.
I tried drawing once it was pretty bad.
Oh, in the anime, she.
All right, this image is funny.
But I remember in the.
In the manga, those are like when she was introduced.
There was like a picture of her sitting down.
I remember her and like the angle of it was like really cool.
But when she stands up, her legs are a little little ridiculous looking.
Hang on.
I found the panel, I think.
Oh, I'm such a good.
Where are her knees?
Are they like in the little bulby part or the?
Yeah, they're just like right at the.
Yeah, look at them legs and look at that that wine glass.
That's what I love.
That's a big wine.
Swishin, it's swishin.
Oh, yeah.
You were earlier with your assumption that like any one of the
the Charlotte family could be the main villain of another one piece arc.
Like, in terms of how well designed they are, they're great.
They're so good.
Yeah, they're awesome.
Fuck yeah, they better come back in spades.
There's just not time.
But I think there's time for at least like smoothie to do something.
At least two of them have come back.
She's like third or fourth in command or something.
Quite high up there.
She's the I.
I feel like at some point we tipped over into like a critical.
Zone like a tipping point was reached where in like new like awesome characters
or just like every chapter, there's like a big splash page of like,
oh, here's a new guy with the coolest character design you've ever seen.
Yeah, it's it's it's it has to happen because like the idea that a new crew
that you've heard about and that is like unparalleled power in the seas
would not have a wacky large crew like other smaller crews that you like
the one the store have parts have defeated before.
They've got to have a big crazy crew with the kooky characters.
Just they can't have just jobbers.
Yeah, you're you're right.
Think think back to like what like the pirate crew has looked like
with like back when like Alveda and buggy and like East Blue,
like the very like guys with like striped shirts and glasses.
Like they had like maybe maybe five named characters
that had their abilities and they were like in command.
And then there was the the crewmates,
just the people who would roll barrels and yell.
Yeah, just some dudes, just some dudes.
They even had to do that to the Marines,
because like Marines in the New World, they can't just be like
skinny twinks with a with a rifle.
They've got to be like meaty gorilla brutes with with all of these
like like bazookas and like double bazookas in each hand.
It's like they've got to they've got to wear like big fur collars
and like, you know, have like big, I don't know,
gold boots or whatever and like crazy facial hair.
We've got to have something.
We've gone from like buggy, second in command,
being just a guy who tames lions to like an entire family
of crazy devil fruit piracy is that all themed around sweets
and very sizes. Oh, my God.
It's inspiring.
And I is.
Is that that guy in the far right?
Is he is he in one of the crews?
Well, the egg man Tom ago, that's Tom ago from from a
he's in like the Beast Pirates, right?
No, I don't think so.
No, he's a big mum pirate guy.
OK, but who am I thinking of?
There's there's another egg guy named Tom ago who's in the Beast Pirates.
Is there? Yeah.
Are you sure you're not confusing him?
Because you meet we meet him before we go to Whole Cake is
we meet him in Fishman Island.
He and Peckons are just hanging out.
And they're thinking of an egg shaped man from one
local queen. No.
OK, this is no, this is the guy.
This is Tom ago.
Oh, I guess he is part of the big mom.
Oh, I thought I thought he was in the Beast Men.
No. Oh, well, well, well, you misunderstood.
I guess I misunderstood.
Bomber. Well, actually, it's fine.
It's fine either way.
This is wacky.
What's wrong with living full?
That's why it's wacky.
There is an unlimited wank.
Yeah, no, but it's wacky, but also it'll make you cry your fucking little nuts off.
This is good.
It's it's it's the my favorite thing.
It's like he he has these ideas for these designs.
They're so simplistic in in aspects of like,
what if there was a guy who was just a circle?
You know, like that that's the the character design.
But then on top of that, he has details.
He gives them personality quirks.
And then, you know, someone like
Waltz's face in Dressroser, famous example.
For baby boy. Oh, yeah.
The baby boy.
He's a boy. He's a man who's like a cool macho man.
I don't remember his name.
And he yeah, Senor Pink. Oh, Senor Pink.
Yeah. Yes.
Senor Pink, he dresses up as a big baby with a bonnet guy.
He's like a cool guy, like mafia boss with like a
cadre, he's like a harem of like hot girls that are just like
following around everywhere.
Rips girls bras off and wipes his face with them when he gets sweaty.
And then just throwing away.
Yeah, he's like it's like a complete insane parody of like,
what the fuck's kind of guy is this?
And then because of that, it's the most funny thing to do would be
to give him a heart wrenching backstory to explain why he dresses up in a diaper.
And it's like, it's his, it's because his wife,
I can't remember the exact details, but his wife was like dying
and their their child had died and he dressed up as a baby
to pretend to be their dead child to cheer her up in her final days.
Yeah, his wife went crazy and couldn't like emote anymore
unless he dressed up as a big baby and reminded them of the kid.
Yeah, and so she she she she managed to smile again
because he dressed like a baby, but then eventually she died as well.
And so to honor her memory, he still dresses as a baby.
And it's like it's so heartfelt.
Everyone cries. It's great.
I literally like I was talking about one piece of my friend the other day
and he was like, oh, this in your pink guy seems kind of lame.
And I said to him, I was like, that's legit.
One of the best characters in one piece.
And then two weeks later, when he'd seen his backstory, he came back to
like, you're completely right.
It's just that's that's the vibe.
It's like, what's the most ridiculous thing we could do
and do it as seriously as possible?
Do it seriously and just good as possible. Yeah.
Well, I'm feeling overwhelmed by my feel
and by my by good one piece feelings.
I'm just staring at the size
comparison chart and thinking about attack on Titan.
Yeah.
I'm thinking of them in their little puppet walking animations.
Yes. Why is that fat woman so big?
Why is she big?
That's big mom.
She's just big.
She's that big because she's big mom.
You idiot.
Why else?
Don't call her that fat woman.
That's big mom.
That's a young girl, big mom.
You big mom.
Don't you know what that means?
You're full.
I'm a fool.
I mean, Katakuri is so fucking big.
Katakuri is that big.
Yeah. Katakuri is that big.
You don't realize it when you're like reading it.
But when I know, like, I thought he was like, you know, tall.
I thought he was maybe like twice as tall as Luffy.
No, I don't realize he's like 40 feet tall.
It's because Luffy gets really big when he's in that form that he uses.
If he gets at least twice as big when he's in Snake Man, I think it's called.
But Katakuri is a big boy.
All right, that kind of that kind of makes up that kind of explains it.
Yeah. Oh, and there's the panel.
It's hard to tell in some of the the manga panels, because like in the big
mom parts, there are quite a lot of people who are just very big.
It's like sometimes it doesn't you can't really get a sense of how big he is
in comparison to like the generic human actual size.
It's almost where Luffy is.
It almost feels like Oda just wanted to like cram so much personality
into all of his side characters that you just had to keep making them bigger
and bigger because it just wouldn't fit otherwise.
So true. Yeah.
It's because because they have to they wouldn't fit on the screen.
They wouldn't fit in the panel because they have to stand up behind
the other guys so you can see them all.
Yeah, they said he needs to get progressively bigger.
Yeah, depending on how important they are.
I almost think that like that might be it.
Like he just wants to like have like big people so you can see them all in a crowd
shot. I don't know.
That's why Franky got big.
Yeah. Yeah, pretty sure that's why you did it is just so that you could
add Frankie in the background of Straw Hat panels and still see him.
Oh, you mean after you mean after the timescale?
Yeah, because you know, you got like four times bigger.
I'm pretty sure you did that intentionally so that Franky could be the background one.
Well, good. It was the right move.
It works, but he's still he's still good.
He's he's all right.
I still prefer the Popeye arms to what he has now.
Yeah, I can see both.
It's a little busy right now.
It's it's the only thing he keeps getting busy and busier.
I mean, I mean, yeah, they all do.
Like Brooks outfits and stuff.
Yeah, that's true.
They did like it's not so bad.
He's he wore that feather boa and that crown for a while,
but he hasn't done it in Wano, I don't think.
No, in Wano, he was in the ghost disguise most of the time.
It's good.
God, one piece kind of cool.
No, I can't know what I know.
I want to catch up.
Yeah, so I'm suddenly feeling inspired to catch up.
No, I can't know.
I know I got to draw.
I got to draw my fucking comic.
You got to draw my stupid ass comic and then read and then maybe read.
Four times a night before bed.
No, I want to read it all at once.
OK, there's no point.
But then you can talk about it weekly in a segment on maybe on
twitch.tv or on this podcast, I guess I could do that.
I don't know. I'll do it.
I'll do it. I'll I'll do it.
It worked. I finally we finally convinced them.
We finally did it.
Maybe as soon as you catch up, you'll fall off right again.
Well, probably, yeah, conversing pirates.
Yeah, we'll call it one piece of my mind.
I can't remember who said that.
I think it was crack.
I think it was crack is one piece of my mind.
Terrible, terrible title.
I hate it. No, that's perfect.
We've got to use it. I don't like it.
Well, I have I have nothing else to say about one piece other than that.
It's good and I like it.
Oh, OK.
Now I see this final panel of Katakuri on the holy shit.
He's a big boy.
That's fucked.
He's a big gentleman.
So you can you can live in his shoe than many of the Titans.
He genuinely is.
Yeah, OK.
You have a band.
It makes him look strong.
I it sure does.
It sure does.
And it makes it funny when you find that he likes doughnuts.
I'll give you a toilet.
They just use the ocean.
They've got all of these different sized people.
And when they go to the bathroom, we never see that.
Everybody has like six or seven different rooms.
That's why the Seekings are so pissed off
is because they're constantly eating people shit.
And they're not happy about it.
People just keep getting bigger and bigger.
And the poo just just keeps being more and more poo in the ocean.
And they can't damn.
They can't fucking take it anymore.
So they eat people.
Yeah, yeah.
People have to decide them, though.
It doesn't really solve the problem, does it?
All right, you got to you got to cut it off at the source.
It's worth eating a little bit of poo now to avoid eating more.
It's a it's a simple cost-benefit analysis
that the Seekings has performed to decide that eating people
poo and all is the is the best solution.
Yeah, yeah.
Imagine imagine being an animal
and killing and eating another animal and you're eating them
and you take a big bite of their large intestine
and just poo just starts flowing out just into your mouth.
Delicious, my favorite.
Do do they just not I do they just not eat that part?
I think they mostly don't care or they eat around it.
I mean, dogs eat shit sometimes because they're really idiots.
Yeah, they just see shit and they're like, oh, look, that's something.
It's something. I got to eat it.
I feel like maybe do you do like lie like a lion kills a gazelle?
I can't imagine that like one like like all the lion pack
like jump on the gazelle and they're all tearing bits off of it.
And then one lion is like, oh, well,
I guess my part is the large intestine.
Oh, it's got poo in it, though.
But I just got to eat it while you shit yourself when you die as a courtesy.
Get it out of there.
I hope that's that's literally what happens.
It's a nature solution.
I don't do, dude.
Now I believe Jesus absolutely is correct.
Why? Why?
Because he's a lion.
And he eats people.
From now, I can't think of an evolutionary benefit to shitting
when you die other than to make other animals happy,
which means it had just like this.
I am is correct.
That's for proof.
That's what Jesus said of the Sermon on the Mount.
He said, blessed are the meek.
And also, you know, it's kind of good that when you shit yourself in the back.
They left that pile because everyone was like, that was a weird.
I don't know what I'm going to write that one down.
Lost the time, but it did happen.
It got it got everyone on his side, but they all agreed like,
you know, future generations probably don't need to hear that.
They hated him for he spoke the truth.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you Jesus.
Thanks. Thank you. Thank you.
That's all for me.
That's all for that's all for me, too.
I don't know anything else.
We could we could start voicemails now.
We have a lot of voicemails, actually.
Like we should probably get through them
because I don't think I can stick around too much longer.
OK, sure. Well, let's let's let's start that out.
We'll try and I don't know why we got so many.
It's crazy.
Was it the big stuff?
People want to talk about that, I guess.
Uh, it doesn't really look like it.
Maybe maybe we wanted to the stuff happened that I didn't hear about.
A little bit, a little bit.
Nothing interesting, nothing.
Because it's big stuff.
Yeah, I mean, true.
OK, OK, so here we got one.
This is called this is called Red Five Rainbow.
Put it in the general.
There we go. OK, three, two, one, go.
One of my classes this semester requires me to use Proctorio
whenever I take an exam.
And what that is is basically a software
that records me through my webcam and records my computer screen
the whole time I'm taking the exam.
And it has an AI to analyze
whenever I'm doing suspicious behavior to make sure that I don't cheat.
Can we talk about how that's fucked?
Suspicious behavior.
That's literally 1984.
Probably like looking.
Probably like looking, looking like off your desk or something,
looking at your phone.
Dude, yeah, that's fucked.
I had to use someone.
I forget who they are, but they worked from home
and they had to have a software installed.
They had to like basically have like OBS or something
like recording their entire screen like one of my old one of my old roommates
had he would have to take tests online.
And yeah, there would be a Proctorio that would be like watching him
through a webcam to make sure he wasn't doing any weird shit.
You know, this wasn't even test.
This was like a worker like at a company who was working from home
and they recorded their screen out eight hours a day
just to make sure that they weren't slacking off.
Jesus, my friend had that where
but they would also check his like internet history on the laptop
because he had to work from this laptop from home
and then turn it in every now and then.
Because I think he did like online programming and stuff.
And he specifically, I specifically know this
because he was watching Gundam and he could only watch the ones that were on YouTube
because he couldn't go on any piracy websites or anything.
So we have to wait fucking months for it to come out
on some weird streaming service here.
And it was very strange.
I saw that I use VPN.
I saw that the SATs are going like all online or something.
That's weird.
I guess they're probably going to do the same thing.
Use some weird software.
I bet I bet it'll still be possible to cheat.
I mean, I guess you could cheat the in-person version as well.
They won't in England.
Ha, ha, why not?
Because they're giving up on all COVID restrictions, aren't they?
Oh, yeah, they're going back in.
Yeah, I don't I'm not paying attention to that.
It's just like a yes or no to everything possible
that you could or could not be doing.
Please do or do not do everything.
It's like, I don't know.
I'll just wear a mask.
Yeah, I'll just wear a mask and I'll just go outside.
If there's no legal requirement to wear a mask anymore,
there's no legal requirement to work from home or any of that shit.
There's nothing, basically.
There's no restrictions anymore.
Damn, I think it's just the NHS are going to start firing people
who aren't vaccinated or something like that.
That's the only one that's sticking around.
Something, something, I guess.
Yeah, take what I can get.
I guess Boris, my the lawsuit against the New Zealand government
that my mum is involved with.
As there was a little thing written about it recently.
It's a COVID restriction thing, right?
Yeah, but churches.
Why do I why do I have to? Oh, yeah, that whole thing.
All right, I think the next one might be the same one again,
because there's another one called Red Five.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, my gosh, I already left this as a comment on the last episode.
No, different, OK, probably two episodes ago once you hear this.
But for wordle, it's based off of your system time.
So if you just like set your date to a different date,
it will give you a wordle for that day.
So you can play the past wordles.
You can play some future wordles, too.
Hmm, really? Wacky.
You could go you could go and just play future ones
that no one has seen before.
You could go and spoil all future wordles.
That's interesting, because the timer when it reset
seems to be based off like UK time, because it like it resets like
at like nine p.m. for me, which would be for me.
It resets at midnight.
Yeah, I thought it was like midnight wherever you are.
It's not midnight for me.
Like it seems to if I check.
If I check wordle, when's the next one?
Every everybody else.
Everybody else seems to reset at midnight.
Oh, wait, no, now it's now it's set to midnight.
That's weird. The other day, like I was able to like access a new one
like like five or six hours before midnight,
which would have lined up with the UK. That's pretty weird.
Never. Maybe they recently changed the system time
because of the popularity.
Maybe or or I'm stupid.
Nakes. OK, next one is please tell me this is in the Blu-rays.
And then there's a YouTube link.
That is not a YouTube link.
This is not a YouTube link.
That is not a note.
Yeah, this video isn't of it.
Yeah, yeah. No, here's what fucking happened.
They pasted the link and didn't notice that their their voicemail title
was too long and it only put part of the link there.
I feel like I feel like this happens all the time.
I feel like this happens very often.
I am going to I'm going to assume this is a Jesse video
and I'm going to look at the URL that has 69 Q in it.
I have I have a I have a guess for what this might be.
Is it is it that one Jesse video that went viral recently?
Wait, one went viral recently.
Yeah, there was one going the the Windows updates one was like
it went viral on TikTok recently.
It went viral. You made me a racist, Obama, you made me a racist.
As long as I kept that part in and good, I guess,
because when it went viral on Facebook, if I cut that part off.
So just ended with the N word without the the dawning horror
that they have become a racist now.
That would that's the punchline.
Yeah, that's pretty much ruin the whole point of the of the bit.
Yeah.
It's like I hate Windows update so much that I became racist about it.
But there's a way it doesn't work if it doesn't work
if if you if you omit the self-awareness of I guess.
I guess it would be funny in a different way
if you just cut it off after the N word.
But like it's like then it becomes like a crazy person yelling.
Yeah, that's all shock value, which is funny in its own way.
But like, yeah, then you just think it's just a person who's.
Yes, that's why it went viral.
Well, well, no, yeah, that's that sucks.
All right, next next one is a is a vocabru.
Is a vocabru link, I guess.
So let's let's check. Let's check it out.
Wait, oblivion fall. What are you?
What are you?
I am I am doing some I'm doing some detective work detective work.
Yeah, so with YouTube videos.
You I learned this from Vsauce.
You can search for videos based on what the URL is.
So I can search for a YouTube URL that has that in it.
And hopefully.
Oh, wow.
OK, I'm getting a few videos with this.
Oh, no, it's not case sensitive.
This is just a Minecraft video.
I know there's only three letters that's not enough if we had four, maybe.
Well, well, we'll never know.
You done fucked up, voicemailer.
You done fucked it up.
All right, next next one is this vocabru link.
All right, I'm looking on it.
I got it. Three, two, three, two, one, go.
I couldn't understand it.
No, I don't know what I said.
I couldn't understand a single word.
I have no idea what they said.
Sorry. Good try.
Good try.
Sounded cool.
Sounded nice.
And credits of Red Dead Redemption 2 or something,
but I did no idea what that said.
It's too bad.
Next one is.
It's OK, parentheses.
It's a cover.
It's called It's a Cover of a Song Called Nightfall at Runescape is Fucking
based, whatever, whatever.
OK.
Next one is Shraft, Shraft 3.0.
OK, there it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PZP, two questions.
Well, really one question, but in the form of two,
because I'm that much of an asshole.
So the internet, it's constantly changing.
It's, you know, the internet of 10 years ago is gone
and the internet of 10 years from now is what I'm about to ask you about.
So what do you think the internet is going to look like in 10 years from now?
What are going to be the hot trends?
What's what's everyone going to be chasing for cloud?
What kind of rat race are we going to be stuck in?
And secondarily, what type of internet would you like to see in 10 years?
What would be a good internet?
And don't fucking.
OK, this is an obvious like trash web 3.0 shit.
But like, let's say let's say fucking
the crypto bros don't get their way.
What what what do you think would happen maybe outside of that?
So be more creative, you fucks.
Well, that's too that's too broad a question.
Oh, I have no I have no idea.
I mean, 10 years ago, the internet was like
slowly becoming exactly what it is now,
which is just sort of whatever.
Content, content for the viewing public, the masses, social media.
I feel like it's going to be the same for the next 10 years.
I feel like it was leading up to this and I can't see it like changing anymore.
Well, what I want is a gallery.
A few years anyway, all I want is a proper gallery mode on Twitter.
That's all I need.
It goes month or maybe every media post.
That's all OK.
So the last like 10 years has seen like consolidation of content into like
what's the word, agglomerating platforms, aggregating.
Yes, aggregating platforms.
I'm going to say that maybe that trend will continue.
But I don't know, maybe optimistically,
a sort of like maybe like a more like underground
sort of trend will emerge and become stronger.
Maybe there will be like a strong like a stronger like counterculture
sort of like not like something that will maybe some
maybe some kind of opposition to that will coagulate because there really is,
I don't know, I think it's a vague prediction, but it's something.
Yeah, I think for that to happen, crypto would need to completely die
because at the moment, the whole counterculture like desire
is in the minds of those crypto bros who are like fighting the system
and everyone else is just sort of laughing at them because they're stupid.
And everything they're doing is idiotic.
I don't know if there's like a counterculture to the internet as exists.
Everybody seems to hate Twitter and nobody seems to be trying to go anywhere else.
So like, I don't know, I see it staying about the same.
I mean, it's like Torrance.
Stuff like Torrance seem good.
Stuff that is like, you know, free freeware and just just distributed,
really distributed.
Yeah, I guess if there's like a what would you like the internet to be more?
I'd like it to be more independent individual websites
and that somehow people like going to in the same way that there's like the big city
where you have social media and then you can go on a country road
and explore the towns and the villages outside.
And there are cool websites everywhere.
And there's like a wonderful hamlet of Gibb and take dot site.
We need we need to bring back web rings.
I don't know what that is.
I think I think a web ring was basically just like back when there were
when everybody had a website, you would just like like like websites
would just like ally with each other and they would put links to each other
in their in their in their descriptions.
And then like just a bunch of websites that all linked to each other
would be called a web ring, right?
I think that's what they were.
Yeah, yeah, that's cool.
So maybe I don't know.
I could I could kind of see like a sort of retro movement coming back,
like a kind of like we sort of sort of recreate the old internet
with web, web rings and stuff sort of underneath the, you know,
the fucking the top level web 2.0.
Everything's accumulated on platforms.
Yeah, I think I'm.
I think server hosting costs.
Like you have to buy, you have to pay a server to host your website
or use your own computer.
And I think a technology that would be nice in the future
is like more peer to peer stuff.
So like making it more like what's that thing
that people use, those chat rooms that are like pre forums
that are basically proto forums that I know the ones to peer.
I know the one you're talking about sex hotlines.
I don't know what's going on. Yes, we need sex hotlines.
More sex hotlines.
That's what the internet is going to be.
I think the metaverse is going to completely fail.
I don't know. Oh, of course.
It's it's like it's it's.
Zuckerberg like discovering Second Life and thinking he's invented it.
Like, yeah.
Are you talking about like CompuServe?
I don't really know what I'm talking about.
I think I've heard of like a peer to peer messaging system.
I know the one you're talking about.
Early internet stuff.
I see IRC IRC IRC IRC.
I think you're talking about IRC internet relay chat.
Yeah. So like more peer to peer stuff to like lower the costs of
manage like having a server that has a lot of traffic.
If it's like spread out across, I don't know how stuff like that could work.
But like, all I know is that if you want a website,
you'll need to pay for however many people come to see it.
And you want people to see it, so you'll need to make a lot of money.
And if you need to make a lot of money,
it's in your best interest to maybe put advertising on the website.
And then when it comes to that, it's like,
well, what about all of these free services that have wider reach
and require no monetary input on your part?
And it's like, dang, I guess I should just post on these sites.
These these conglomerate everyone's here sort of things.
So like technology would need to make it really cheap for people
to have their own websites before people would actually be able to do it.
I mean, I mean, I have a website and it cost me like ten dollars a month.
Sure, like if you have if you had a lot of people coming to that website,
it would cost more, maybe would it?
Well, I guess not for a comic website.
I'm not entirely sure.
I don't really know how it works.
Larger traffic makes it slower to maybe maybe like if it needed to handle
like a bigger traffic load, I would have to upgrade like a subscription
to like a higher traffic version or something. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, it's probably I mean, when a Homestuck update came out
and everybody was clicking on it, the website would crash.
So clearly, there's something that can go wrong if too many people
are reading your stuff.
So it's fine if like you're you're relatively obscure,
but as soon as it scales up, you need to scale up the money as well.
And so at that point, it becomes more of an of an annoyance.
The future sucks.
The future hasn't happened yet. We don't know.
It's true. Sad but true.
All right. Next next one.
Next one is called VTuber Revolution.
I don't know. Yeah.
Three, three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, I think I'm going to stop watching
unless you literally all become VTubers.
I want to see avatars moving around, bopping and bopping.
I want to see Ben St.
is the cop killer. I want to see Gibb moving around.
I want to see everyone's mouths flapping.
We have the mouth flaps animations on the podcast.
I think I'm just about done with this show.
Good. Thank you both for that.
They make a compelling point.
I tried to make that phantom horn VTuber rig one time and it was weird.
It didn't act right.
Its eyes were like jittery and I couldn't get them to stay still.
Yeah. Ben, your eyes are just jittery.
Some sort of a crazy setup to get at the tracking.
I think I've seen these clips of this one VTuber girl,
DM, who has like a three dimensional VTuber avatar.
Yeah. And her tracking is like, I think she uses like an iPhone.
And the face tracking on that is like perfect.
The expressions are like immediately picked up.
And it's like girl DM.
Oh, yeah. I just want to see what she looks like.
She's one of those people who has a really nice model.
Yeah, she's got a real nice model.
She's funny, which is nice.
I haven't bothered to like look at her streams.
But the clips I've seen are like, dang, that's really good tracking.
That really good face tracking shit.
It helps out the it was the models by the art gun.
They do a lot of really, really, really high quality ones.
Oh, a lot of the a lot of the face stuff can be done
so that it is mode shifting as opposed to trying to emulate every single expression.
So it will only like subtly change.
And then you press a button and it will switch to like different expressions.
But when you're playing a game,
pressing buttons to change your expression is too hard.
That's why you get a little off this controller and bind it to different things on that.
You have a little foot. I've seen people do that.
Yeah, this is I'm not an organ player.
Good guitar.
Sorry, clone hero players have foot pedals to activate certain things in game.
They're crazy.
I'm not a car driver.
What if I was playing a car game and I had a pedal
and I had my twitch like reaction pedal and I would switch over to it.
And like, oh, shit, I'm going to crash.
Click and I'm screaming.
It goes.
VTubers cringe.
Then I need to be like, I need to be a VTuber
and like have a nice freedy model and it's German.
I'm just like a cartoon German.
No, just a real German.
It's like German's face cut up and like, wait, yeah, just a realistic German.
I think I think I complained.
I think I complained about whenever I see VTubers that are all just like
VTubers on low level VTubers on Twitter,
all like evincing this weird like fake solidarity, this like fake friendly thing.
It's like, we all got to follow each other to support each other.
We're all going to make it.
No, it's a pyramid scheme.
It's a pyramid scheme.
That's not true, but it's annoying.
Red Man was a pretty good VR VTuber, not VR.
The best.
He was wobbly and he had one frame for his mouth opening.
The only problem was the eyes were would would not track at all
and it would completely lose track of my face.
Yeah, it was Phantom's eyes were the problem.
Just the pupils just would not stay still and it just didn't look right.
It didn't like it might have been where like big googly eyes.
It was probably just that my setup was not good enough.
The lighting was not good and it couldn't track it well.
OK, next next voicemail is called D and balls.
There it is three, two, one, go.
Ha, hey, what do you think about drum and bass music?
I don't fucking care.
I think it's pretty good.
I haven't heard much.
I think I listened to like a something on YouTube
that had a pig on the front cover.
Nice. Nice.
When I was in school, people listened to music
that they called drum and bass.
But I don't know if it counts as drum and bass anymore.
It sucked. So I don't know what drum and bass is.
I don't even know what drum and bass is.
The fucking Powerpuff Girls theme song,
that bit where the the drums are playing, that's drum and bass.
It sounds sounds fine.
See, when I was in secondary school,
people basically referred to drum and bass as like,
it's like soft the dubstep it was.
And it's like, this doesn't this is shit.
And also, I don't think that's what that should have been called.
That that that drum sample is like from like the 70s or 80s or some shit.
Yes, yes.
It's it's just being like reused and repurposed like a million times.
It has a name. I forgot what it's called.
It was from like some jazz called the stolen drum beat.
And the drummer is sad.
They didn't get royalties.
Yeah.
Anyway, this is voicemail.
Next voicemail is called one of us doesn't understand boxes.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, just put it all in a fucking box.
No, like you take a box, you put the blu-ray in it,
then you put the book in it, then you close the box and seal it.
And you mail that customer.
It would be why the fuck do you need it?
Like, it would be more expensive, stupid, more expensive to ship.
Yes, it is so much more expensive.
He doesn't understand like, I don't know.
I don't deal with with a whole lot of ship.
Well, like clearly, you don't know, see, seems pretty simple.
Hmm. Ben, why don't you do this thing?
Hmm, could it be could it be for this reason?
I don't know. I don't know anything.
So why don't you do it?
Well, clearly, Ben doesn't understand boxes.
This guy doesn't understand shipping.
Dude, fucking. All right, all right.
I was selling all like me and my partner when we were moving to America.
We had to we had to sell a bunch of shit
because we couldn't take it all on the plane.
And we had a whole bunch of my little pony merch
that they had accrued over the years.
And we were like sort of falling out with the show.
So we're like, we'll just sell a bunch of his shit.
It was like eight hundred dollars worth of like various things.
And we advertised it on a Facebook group
and some person said they wanted it and we put it all in a box
and they were willing to pay like four hundred for it.
And the shipping was like three hundred seventy
because it was in a fucking box.
That's cold. Fucked.
Yes, really made like 30 bucks to this guy.
Yes, it is just it is simply much cheaper
to put the book in an envelope and send it as a letter
than it is to put it in a box and ship it as a package.
I got a CD on discogs from New Zealand recently.
And they said, hey, if I put it in a jewel case,
it'll literally cost like 10 bucks, like 15 bucks extra to ship.
If I put it, if I put the CD in an envelope, it'll be like two bucks.
And it's that all right.
And I'm like, sure.
And I got the CD in a very nice.
I have I have a big box.
So I think I have like 40.
I think I have like 40 more that I need to take to the post office,
which I will do as soon as the snow melts a little bit.
I think I'll give that.
Just bring a friend.
Maybe I'm like, yeah, if I if I could get one.
Next, the voicemail is called Terry Walker.
I'm putting it in chat right now.
There it is. Terry Walker, three, two, one, go.
All right. The setting is December 2019.
I'm making New Year's resolution to stop watching YouTube.
Believe me, I had a problem.
I'm not going to pretend I need to be caught up, though.
I do have a Twitter.
Then it was December, 2021.
I rewatch and get caught up on all the PCP's content.
Like I said, I have a problem.
There was a hot week there that I was confused about
because y'all were talking about the Brony lecture, but no matter how many times
I scrolled through the lecture playlist, I couldn't find it.
Yeah.
Well, where are you now?
See what you've done, Trixie?
What is it? Because this could have all been prevented.
This person.
I'm not sure what the point of this.
I'm not sure what the point of this is.
Isn't it interesting that if you haven't gotten to the point?
Oh, does he not?
Does he not know? Does he not know? Oh, yeah.
Well, there's no Brony lecture.
It was thrown in the trash. Trixie.
Trixie destroyed it.
Trixie destroyed it in a fit of fury of rage and from.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, you asked me for the lecture.
Will you? Well, I'll punish you for it.
You fools.
It was only, but this is only a character I'm playing.
Next.
Next voicemail is, yeah, it was destroyed, was destroyed, is the answer.
Next one is called, wait.
Well, okay.
Next one is called insanely transphobic procrastinators.
Part one, three, two, one, go.
So the reason I called in was I wanted to express
my confusion of Trixie critics that feel the need to shoot the arguments
in the foot by including the transphobia.
Like Trixie was clearly going through an asshole arc
long before transitioning ever came up or completely independent of being trans.
Who's saying that?
The first time I think people noticed anything was when Trixie got a girlfriend.
I wasn't one of the people that thought May was the problem.
She didn't reveal her politics at that point.
But the being high 24 seven and acting like they were the first person
that had discovered drugs, if she's not still in that arc,
that is the most cringe arc they've ever been on.
And then Trixie trying to shame the PCP for not paying May's way to Radcon.
Weirdly yelling at Manji for going to college and belittling everyone
that did go to college on a recorded episode for some reason.
That was fucking weird.
Convincing people to move to Boston or Virginia Beach for PCPHQ.
Like didn't Nate and Michelle actually move for the cantant reasons?
And then hating Boston because it was like cold or having to take a bus.
What the fuck?
Like people moved across country and then dropping projects
that other people were dependent on like cantant or I am games.
By 2020 comes around.
Everyone should have been rolling their eyes at Trixie coming in
with a new paradigm shift or abandoning projects long before the Brony lecture.
Like the how the marketed thing or those rants.
Well, yeah, I mean the signs for all that's all true.
I think I think for my part, it was like I didn't care too much
because I wasn't really involved and I had no stake in Trixie's career.
Yeah, I had no stake in it.
It wasn't like personally affecting me.
There's another part, by the way, there's one.
There's another part, too.
So let's just listen to that three, two, three, two, one go.
So yeah, feels like a full Kiwi Farms article without gender needing to come up.
Even with that, I'm one of the fans that found the PCP through the Digi Bro channel.
Do you all think this was an arc of selfishness and instability?
Or was she always an asshole? Always an asshole. Always an asshole.
It was always an asshole.
It just took she had she had to she had to get on top.
She had to have like everything handed to her.
And then once she had it, I would say as much I can be as much of an asshole
as I want, nothing bad will happen.
Well, I would say always an asshole through selfishness and self importance.
Yeah, she just doesn't.
She just doesn't care.
She just doesn't care about other people is the is the is the problem.
In my opinion, that's my diagnosis lack of empathy.
You're going to work for you once you get there.
Stupid golden witch, bitch, whatever it's called.
OK, where's Kusa, mega, you fuck?
Next next voicemail.
OK, OK, we're getting a bit into it.
I don't know if there's that many of these, but there's the next one is called
Yig commenters. No, no.
So three, two, one, go.
I've been I see you floored about
the Yig commenters being all positive on Trixie's video.
You know, she's just deleting all the rest.
That's all that's all that's going on.
That is true. That is true.
It's true.
But like, it's still insane that people aren't even saying those things.
Yeah, nevertheless, there's like hundreds of a few hundred people being like,
thank you so much for enlightening me, illuminating for me the truth.
Yes, I understand. It all makes sense now.
I'll do anything for you, my queen.
Bless.
Anyway, anyway, it is hope.
Yeah, some people are just beyond help.
Next voicemail is called Otaku Twilight.
Three, two, one, go.
Macross, do you remember? Love is an important classic.
I hope you actually watch the film.
Remembering love is based regardless of dumb internet beef.
I've never I've never seen Macross.
Cool. I had forgotten.
Is that what Jesus said?
That's some.
Yeah, because I guess because Trixie got that phrase remembering love from
what's what's his name, a ghost lightning who, I guess, got it from Macross.
But I've never seen Macross.
Is that the voice of Jesus on that voicemail?
It was a voice of Jesus.
It's quite like that.
Millions of sparkle.
Probably sparkle was Jesus, you know.
I said Jesus because Macross, like he's like, oh, Macross.
OK.
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Twilight is in the pony character.
Oh, you don't even know.
Yeah, it's Twilight Sparkle Sparkle.
There was like two.
You think I was that then.
Twilight must have been thinking Twilight like Edward.
Yeah, that's why I said Ed McMillan, but that's the.
Oh, you mean, you know, Jesus, like Edward Macmillan,
like, like, like Gish and and Meat Boy.
Yeah.
From Five Nights at Freddy's.
I don't know.
Next voicemail.
Yeah, next voicemail is called Question three, two, one, go.
All right, this one's for the Doritos English muffin guy.
That shit sucked.
You must have lost your mind.
Oh, fuck you.
Do you make your bed?
Piece of shit.
He's Doritos and English muffins are fucking tasty.
This guy's no taste.
From in the trash, you're talking about you're talking about
your your cluster punk kitchen recipe.
Yeah, good thing I'm here this week to defend myself, eat a, eat a dick.
I haven't tried it and I'm on a very strict diet as of like a week
and as of like two weeks ago, so I'm not going to try it anytime soon.
But I would try it and I'm not going to knock it until I it sounds weird.
It doesn't sound like it's any good at all.
Sound stupid as fuck.
You fucking imbecile.
However, however, I won't knock it until I try it.
So like maybe it only works if I make it because every time I've
given it to someone, I prepared it.
I put it together and I handed it to them.
Well, what did you do to it?
Do you wash his hands?
It's cold as grease.
You think you English toast English muffin butter it and then
what you sprinkle crushed up Doritos on toast, right?
Well, like you put like like three or four or five or six
however many Doritos you think is appropriate.
And you just kind of, you know, pushed the two halves of the muffin together
and you crunch it a little, crunch it down a little bit like, you know,
you know, like you eat it like a sandwich.
You eat it like a sandwich.
Yeah. And I've done that.
And I loved it and I've made it for like six or seven other people.
And everyone who I've given one to when they they were like a bit skeptical
and then they took a bite and they were like, oh, that's actually really good.
Damn, like all of them had that reaction.
So I've had a pretty good success.
Obviously, obviously someone's going to not like it because taste is like
it's fucking subjective, like like what I want to say, like food tastes.
Obviously, some people are going to hate it.
But I don't know.
I think it's good.
I would try. I would try.
I myself prefer what sits on a bagel.
What's a what's it?
It's a good. What is it?
It's a good, a good crisp.
It's a cheesy puff.
Crisp.
It's like a cheese puff.
You would just call it a cheese puff.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like, like a cheeto.
Oh, like, like, like, like Jax, maybe.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, those things that are like.
Yeah, those, those, those, those chips that are like, yeah.
Cheetos, Cheetos puffed and or Jax or cheese balls or whatever.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like we had we have a different name for them in New Zealand as well.
I mean, those on a bagel.
Yeah, I can see that being good.
Jax coming up. Jax coming up barrel.
I used to put a barrel.
Well, I used to put what sits on my sandwiches at school
because they they have a lot of flavor to them.
So they work really well as a sandwich.
Crisp.
Yeah, I guess.
I guess I could see it.
And they can't.
Should they melt in your mouth without the wishes?
And I say.
And I said, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Next one is called.
Next one is called.
It's Janess three, two, one.
Ah, what's this?
Sorry. Sorry.
Ew, is this real?
I don't think so.
That's not real.
Look at that.
Hold on, hold on.
We can't continue.
I have to set.
You just remind me, Simsie, this is important.
I'd try it. Oh, no.
Where's my phone?
I saw something fucking horrendous, and this is real.
I took I took this fucking photo myself.
Oh, I'm pulling up my phone.
It was dark chocolate.
Yeah, maybe.
I'd try it.
You ever eat like cheese and onion crisps
and then had some chocolate right afterwards?
It's surprisingly good.
I've sometimes had like like some dark chocolate
and then like some salty snack.
Yeah, inside it and the same time or like just bread.
Bread, tiger bread and dark chocolate is like a great combo.
Tiger bread.
It's it's like bread with like burn melted cheese on the top.
Yeah.
That kind of cheese.
Is it? Oh, I thought it was just like a funny
something or other.
No, I'm pretty sure it's just like over cheese.
I've probably said this before,
but the pattern on this bread is much more reminiscent
of a giraffe than a tiger.
So the tiger.
All right, all right, look at this bullshit
if it'll actually copy the case.
Yeah.
Well, briefcase my fucking there,
fucking spicy Cheetos flaming hot ice cream.
Why?
They were just sweet.
It can't just taste like hot cheese.
Oh, I went to the fucking marble slab at the mall
and they had this poster and they replaced
Kai's banana flavor that he loves with this.
How dare they?
Did you try it?
No, I got chocolate with marshmallow and I want to I want to try it.
You know, and cream are both derived from milk.
OK, but it's like spicy.
It's like burning the space.
The idea. OK, here's what I think.
I think it's probably not like actually tastes like hot Cheetos.
I think it's probably some other flavor.
Like it looks like it's strawberry or something,
but maybe it has a little bit of spiciness in it.
Yeah, I think it's just spicy vanilla.
I bet you that's what it is.
He's he's staring at you.
I miss I can't I can't find rain, rain,
thermo, strawberry jalapeno anymore.
That was my favorite rain flavor.
I like the spicy strawberry.
You drink rain. What the hell?
Yeah, R.E.R.E.I.G.N.
It is a it is a bang like it is a bang like produced by the monster company.
I thought Boston was so polluted that you could taste different flavors
of rain depending on how heavy it was raining.
And you were outside and opening your mouth.
Well, since it snowed yesterday,
Munchie was saying that he was going to make snow cones out of the snow.
But then someone was saying like, no, no.
If it if it if it snows in the city,
it absorbs all the pollution from the air, like from the atmosphere,
like it have all the pollution in it.
Don't eat the snow.
Even carbon monoxide in your belly.
Even the clean surface snow is toxic.
Well, I mean, I would recommend about toxic,
but it would definitely be a bit grimy.
It would be a bit unclean as I was just sitting outside.
I don't know. I'm entrusted.
That's everything. No, that's so dumb.
OK, I don't know about all this absorb from the from the air.
That does happen with rain.
OK, like if you but it's not.
But but if it's like, OK, if the air was clean,
then if it was just like snow, like on the ground,
like if it was like a foot deep, you could grab some off the top of the surface
and it wouldn't have it wouldn't be grimy.
There wouldn't be any dirt on it.
It would just be it would be clean from the top of the snow pile.
It wouldn't be dirt.
But the as it falls through the air, it picks up tiny particulates.
OK, I'm sorry.
If you grab if you grab fruit off off a tree, you wash it.
But if you wash snow, it'll melt.
So what can you do?
You can't clean it, spin outdoors, a bug sat on it.
Probably if it's if it's really cold outside,
you left some ice cream out there all all night and it didn't melt
because it's really cold. Would you eat it?
No, same thing.
What? Why not?
Well, you mean like ice cream?
You're not what bugs get on it, Ben.
What bugs have gotten on my snow?
Oh, like wait, like just out.
Yeah, I can't believe what I'm hearing.
You guys are like weirded out by the thought of like eating snow off the ground.
No, no, I'm not.
I eat snow, but I just think it's funny that I eat snow, but I wouldn't eat another thing.
OK, well, I think about like like pollution in the air
getting into the snow as it falls is a true thing.
I don't know how bad it would be.
Ice cream is full of sugar, so I'm sure it would attract pests.
Yeah, I probably would if it just left a bear ice cream cone outside.
No, I would need it.
But like if I left it out in like a pint in like a closed pint, sure.
Yeah. OK, OK, whatever. OK, whatever.
I don't know. I'd never heard this thing.
I'd never heard this thing about absorbing toxins from the air before, but but maybe.
OK, I think it would kill you.
But I'm sure. No, whatever.
All right. Next voicemail is an image of Emmanuel Macron.
I don't know. We missed one because I posted the What's It's Oreo image.
Oh, you're right. You're right.
Janice, right. Janice. OK, three, two, one, go.
If you haven't heard the news yet,
Scott Pilgrim is getting an anime editor.
You asked this last week and the author is going to be the executive producer
on the project. Nice.
This made me wonder, since your comic's art style was mainly influenced by Scott.
The exact same question last week.
How would you feel if your comics were adapted into anime?
And how would you feel about Japanese dubbing of your own creative character?
No, I answered this last week.
Next voicemail is a next voicemail is a an image of Emmanuel Macron.
Oh, my God. I don't know.
Oh, my God.
Posted in the first two of them and then not reaching for.
Oh, this is OK.
This is just a bunch of stuff.
Emmanuel Macron said I saw I saw a good one of these
political compasses about I think it was JFK.
No, it wasn't JFK. It was FDR.
No, was it FDR? Was it Eisenhower? I don't know.
Whatever. Thanks for the fucking meme.
I don't care. No, not reading it.
Next voicemail is a Tumblr link.
Here it is.
Tumblr.
I don't know those words in here.
So there's nothing here.
There's nothing here. It's a broken link.
All right, cool.
We're moving right along.
Use a link shortener.
Use a URL shortener next time voicemail.
Yeah, next voicemail is another image.
It's called Improved the podcast logo.
This is from the freaking epic artist at the artist.
Freaking the freaking.
Fixed your logo and finally made it make good good and make sense.
Please use it from now on.
Oh, OK.
Why the fuck not?
I guess. Yeah, Ben said more like Ben Tate.
Given Tate more like Given Snake.
Tom Oliver more like who?
Hey, that's my joke.
They stole it. Why?
Why did you say about me?
There's the text at the bottom.
Given Snake.
They called you Given Snake.
Given Snake. That's fair.
Because I got a really long neck.
Yeah, like Charlotte.
And I am entirely neck.
This is objectively better than our current logo.
That's true.
I remember Ben's Tate.
You could put you could set that as the YouTube thing
and nobody would notice how screwed up it is.
Honestly, maybe I just fucking will.
Maybe if I'm in the mood later, I will do exactly that.
Well, it's about on April Fool's, but then never change it back.
A February Fool's next next voicemail is called.
What's it called?
It's called Improving Your Intros 5000
percent with this one weird trick.
Three, two, one, go.
All right, PCP, here's the deal.
No intro, right?
I'm a Zoomer.
I grew up watching YouTubers.
And while I do enjoy the PCP, you know,
there's one thing that just really piss me off about podcasts.
And it's the fact that you're not YouTuber enough.
Every time I watch, you know, a new podcast, a new video,
I don't know what to do.
You don't give me fricking instructions.
And any viewer like me will not know what to do.
So from now on, I want you to have a similar intro to this,
what I'm about to do right now.
What's up, PCP Nation coming back right at you again
with a new video, a new podcast.
And guys, this one is going to be crazy.
But before you watch, remember to like, subscribe,
bring that bell, put on all notifications
so you don't miss a single upload.
And remember to watch the entire video
preferably multiple times.
So we get that sweet watch.
I want. All right, guys, we'll see you next time.
Just watch this video from now.
Very cool. Yeah.
I want people to know that sort of intro.
So the viewers will know what's what's up, what to do.
I want people to miss our uploads and people like.
Can we get Eliza to put that at the beginning of the episode?
Just like just some guy saying, what's up, guys?
Welcome to a new video.
Some guy.
Sure. Why not?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, in fact, put it at the beginning of every episode
from now on, so we don't have to do it.
I don't like.
I don't like the YouTube thing that has become normal.
It was it was like hilariously bad.
We the entire time and it still is.
But people are just used to it now.
Dude, I fucking hate like terminal YouTube of voice.
I see it when I when I if I find like an obscure Minecraft video,
I guarantee they'll be like, oh, what's up, guys?
We'll go back to another Minecraft video and they just just fucking it's awful.
I can't understand what they're saying.
It's a roller coaster of of like like literally like.
Welcome to the one of German craft.
The the I don't want you to I don't want you to subscribe.
Here's what I want you to go to the Patreon pledge to the Patreon.
And then I want you to go unsubscribe and unring that bell.
So just forget that we exist and forget that you're pledged.
It's what happened to David Lynch to give and take instead.
Patreon.com slash give and take.
Uh, it's what is this?
It's it's David Lynch at like a weekly podcast thing where he had a funny fucking
YouTuber intro and he just started like every time he said it,
he just like made the vow.
He drew out the vowel sounds even longer and someone compiled it.
And it's just like the second half of the video is just him going.
Ooh, like just like over various videos like half a year.
I'm reeling a little bit from the fact that like David Lynch uploads YouTube like vlogs.
What the hell?
In circle David Lynch saying what January one.
Ali's are the intro of the podcast should just be him going.
That's the intro.
Very nice.
What is it?
What word is he saying?
Is he saying you to?
I like to believe that he just sat there for an entire year straight doing this.
OK, I can't I can't listen to any more of this.
I can't stand it.
Thank you David Lynch.
Next voicemail I posted it up above is called Banana.
Three, two, one, go.
Does your life have a principle or a set of principles?
No.
The principle crop from Captain Underpants.
Fuck, how are dying?
I like probably do, but I couldn't explain it because I don't know how to speak.
I would say I like to not have a boss.
I like to own my work.
I like to own.
I like to own my work, I think is one of my guiding principles.
I guess that's a pretty good one.
Be nice and smiley to everybody.
If I have a ridiculous idea, no one's going to make it unless I do it.
So I have to. That's a good one.
Yeah, that's where all the voicemails came from, by the way, I'm sorry.
Yeah, where? Where else?
No one else is going to do it.
I had to know nobody else was going to be snakes.
It's true, sad, but true.
All right, next next one is called.
Next one is called Stonks.
OK, three, two, one, go.
Then it's it's happening.
It's happening.
AOC is down. It's down a whole bunch and you can buy in.
You can buy in with all the AOC is down and you can buy in and then it's going to moon
and then we're going to be fucking rich. We're all going to be rich.
You know, like unless it's a week later, so maybe it's down even more
or maybe it's already mooned and it would be too late.
Who the fuck knows?
Bitcoin, how did how did how did Bitcoin do today?
Yeah, it's kind of just plateauing.
It went big, big.
It went big down.
It went big down when Trixie premiered that new video because of that new video
announcing that she hates did you broke Crater?
No, Crater, it cratered the value of Ethereum and Bitcoin.
The market will never recover.
It has it has bumped up a little bit since then.
It's recovered a bit.
It's kind of plateauing around 38 Le Mans.
Damn, man, Bitcoin's fucked.
The coins really fucked up.
I really don't like it.
Did you watch the did you watch that line go up video?
Oh, yeah, I've watched that.
But even before that, I found these this info on the energy consumption
of Bitcoin, like if you're in the second worst, Bitcoin is the worst by far.
Yeah, I think it's something like one point five million visa
transactions is the equivalent energy cost of a single Bitcoin transaction.
Bitcoin is like specifically designed to be inefficient.
Like it's it's supposed to it's supposed to be slow and unwieldy
in a way that is designed to mimic gold.
Yeah, but worse and all the energy comes from everyone doing repeat work.
Yeah, everyone trying to mine the same
like hundreds of people mining the same coin, but only one person actually gets it.
And then all the other 99 people or more who are mining that coin.
The energy goes in the trash.
It was worthless.
But man, this this this technology is so amazing.
Isn't it so isn't it so good?
It's it's it's great.
If it's great, if what you think technology is supposed to do is like
partition things away from the public so that someone can charge money for them.
Yeah, but if you think if you think if you think that's a technological
announcement, it's public, though, right?
Like it's all a public.
You can look you sure you can look at it.
Yeah, it's publicly.
But then it's decentralized by which I mean it's it's it's not
decentralized, actually.
It's dude, it's dude.
I love how decentralized NFTs are.
I mean, I can't wait to get my NFT show on Amazon.
It's it's decentralized.
It's decentralized right up until anyone has a dispute and then a fucking
coven of witches get together to decide the fate of everyone.
Did that stupid fucking NFT
cartoon ever actually come out?
Was it just a little 10 second clip I saw?
No, no, no.
It's like a six minute family is free NFT cartoons.
And Reddit family had an episode and it's like on Amazon Prime or on
some service or some garbage or where it's going.
I don't know. It's it's it's a six minutes long.
I didn't actually watch it.
I I didn't watch it.
I watched someone else watch it.
I watched I watched the dire gentleman recap it.
And they they didn't watch it real time.
So I had no idea how long it was.
I got the feeling that it was like 15 minutes, but maybe it's shorter than that.
Looks great.
Looks amazing.
I might go watch this episode.
Just see. I'm curious.
It's unless it gives the money in which case I won't.
It's pretty. It's pretty good.
It's pretty great, actually.
It's it's maybe slightly better than you might expect from a.
No, that's not even true.
That's not it.
It's going to say what?
Wait, what?
I was going to I was going to say, yeah, no, no,
because like just so much NFT art looks like shit.
And like, at least it is a card.
I guess it is a cartoon.
I mean, it's not.
It doesn't look good or anything.
But they look like I guess I guess they did make it.
It's it's pretty dog.
It's no smiling friends.
I'll tell you that.
I still I still haven't watched smiling.
Smiling friends is just a joy.
It's good. I should.
I should watch it.
It seems good.
All right. Next one, which was that?
Seventy one next voicemail is there it is.
And it is called.
Fuck, I can't print.
Annihilation Road to Radcon three, two, one, go.
Hello, Ben and Gibb. Hello, PCP.
I've just finished finally the copy of Road to Radcon
that I bought recently.
And from it, I come away with a lesson and a question.
The lesson being that Ben St.
is a significantly better writer than Trixie is.
The other thing, the question is,
since I'm a bit of a new fan and listener of the podcast,
who really only started listening to the episodes
after the great exodus, shall we call it, happened.
Yeah. What or whom is cold corona?
Is there any short form answer to this or any
piece of content that I can be pointed to to explain what the
fuck amazing because I am a bit confused.
Otherwise, a good wrap up on the story, Ben.
I've got to be honest.
I'm not really sure either.
What? Really?
I've never really gotten this because you haven't.
You haven't watched Jesse's videos.
So that's why. No, that's true.
I haven't watched the single.
Yeah, he's a corona is a real.
His videos.
If you don't know, if you don't know,
Road to Radcon, the ending of Road to Radcon,
basically, the entire conclusion is about is centered on cold corona.
It's like about him. OK.
Because I wrote the road to Radcon, but I haven't opened it at all.
OK.
The corona is like like Jesse's video game reviews
were like half like sincere video game stuff
and also parodies of like that guy with the glasses as content.
And Colt Corona was supposed to be like the stupid idiot character
that like reviewers often have.
And like things would happen like, well, I'm in this video.
What's going on, Jesse?
He had like that sort of a relationship.
And he's like grown beyond that.
He's he was like the front, like the the main character of like the horseshoe saga.
And he's like, yeah, he's he's in bodies.
All of the worst traits of the Brony Frandom.
It's it's he's a complex guy, but he's also like really stupid.
He's just got a horse head.
He has the innocence of a child.
He has like a child's mind, but he's like a violent like
rapist, I think.
Now, that's Michelangelo Michelangelo.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Donatello. That's not a tello.
That's not a tello.
He sang that funny vapor wave song, I don't know.
Yeah, he's he's a Jesse.
He's he's Jesse wearing a horse mask, but he's a whole character unto himself.
OK. So yeah, that's hard to like explain
because I haven't really tried to explain him.
But yeah, I won't I won't I won't explain
what his role is in the ending of Road to Radcon
available at stcomics.com slash store dot html.
I won't explain his role because it would be a spoiler.
But it's just really funny.
It's just really funny to imagine like a new
a new PCP fan who is not familiar with all that stuff.
Just being like, what what is this?
What does this mean?
Good, good question, though.
Yeah, it is great. It makes makes me smile.
A life history lesson for me. Awesome.
I'm trying to think if I wonder if there's other
like stuff in the ending that like you wouldn't understand.
That's that's probably the big one.
It's still out of like.
Yeah, I don't know. That's probably the big one.
Yeah, I'm glad I'm glad you liked my ending.
I was not very confident in my prose writing ability.
So I'm glad you liked it.
Thanks. OK, next one is called.
It's just called OOH. OOH post.
OK, three, two, one, go.
OOH podcast, OOH me likey make longer.
Well, we got so many voicemails.
We're going to have a really long one this time.
It's an epic podcast.
You know, wait, I'm like going
heading to the store in like 20 minutes, by the way.
Really? OK, we might.
Well, we'll try to we'll try to be done.
But I want to say about the retro radical.
I did. I did try.
I actually tried to like sort of mimic
Trixie's like writing style a bit.
I don't know how successful I was,
but I tried to keep the like the tone consistent.
It was very respect, I'm sure.
It felt well like a good continuation.
I didn't feel like, all right, I'm taking over the show now.
And it's me, Ben saying, completely different.
Like you actually finished the story.
It was gone.
No, there were there was a tone.
There was a tone I tried to keep the tone consistent.
And I tried to keep like like like she would make
like the way that she would sort of like make a joke that was basically just a
sentence like she would just make like a long alliterative sentence or something
or just just attack like a bunch of weird adjective.
I tried to like sort of duplicate that and like and copy it a bit to
I thought it came up pretty good.
OK, next one is moving right along here.
Next one is a trans zone from Chip Wiseman.
Three, two, one, go.
Ni hao, Ben and Gib.
So actually, this is just a question for Gib.
So, Ben, if you want to go and draw your comic or something, feel free to do that.
So, Gib, I have a panel working on you.
We're talking about Davoo's new video and how her voice is like amazing.
And yeah, so as a trans femoid, who is, shall we say,
vocally challenged myself, I was wondering if you ever got back to her
and found out like what she does.
Does she have a personal vocal trainer?
What exercise does she do?
Stuff like that.
Second thing in the spirit of sharing the knowledge,
I'd like to put this out there for anybody who is on their own trans voice journey.
And that is, check out the YouTube channel called Trans Voice Lessons.
She does a bunch of videos, mostly going into like the theory of vocal feminization,
like, you know, physically what's happening with your different muscles
and voice folds and stuff.
It's really interesting stuff, great for understanding what's going on.
But she doesn't really go into the practical element of it much,
like actually what to do to practice.
So it's not a one stop shop.
Anyway, thank you and have a happy Chinese New Year.
Trans Voice Lessons.
Do they help trans males as well?
I wonder.
They they definitely would live.
It's about theory.
Yeah, I mean, well, I don't know about that YouTube channel.
But yeah, the people try to change their voice
in either direction.
Yeah, I never talked to Davoo about that.
I guess I should or could.
But I imagine the answer is just going to be like,
oh, yeah, I watched some YouTube videos about it.
And Chip, why not?
Chip, why not simply ask Davoo?
Why ask Gib?
Did you ask Davoo and what did Davoo say?
Why not simply ask Davoo?
I don't know.
She's hard to get in contact with.
It sounded like she had better voice than Davoo might have, anyway.
Yeah, probably. Yeah, whatever.
I just listened to a bit of this person's voice,
this trans voice lessons.
Yeah, they got a good voice.
All right, next.
The knowledge is all there.
It's just like, all right, time to commit to learning.
I'm like, oh, it's a whole skill.
I don't want to do that.
Absolutely. That's true.
Next one is X minus one.
Three. Did you miss one?
Did I miss one?
Yeah, there's a five second.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Yeah, go go back to the five second one is X minus one.
OK, three, two, one, go.
Next.
Oh, God.
Oh, no, it's going to be the time it's three.
It's three hundred.
I don't I don't know what I don't know what we're going to do for three.
We're going to we're going to yell this is Sparta really loudly.
I hope it's not a disappointment
if we don't do anything super cool because I have nothing.
I have nothing in mind.
Sorry. Sorry.
Don't get your hopes up.
OK, all guests to confirm.
Everybody's favorite monsters for
next one is next one is called Otaku Twilight two lovers again.
Three, two, one, go.
Your say it's your movie three.
Remember, my love is a fine movie and the series is a beloved classic
and doesn't deserve slander.
Check out Discotheque's Blurry.
They do good preservation of classics.
What is this makes me like in a submarine?
Otaku Twilight just makes me think about friendship is witchcraft
and how funny Otaku Twilight was in that and how I'll never make anything
as even half as good in my entire life as friendship is witchcraft.
It is good and it holds up and I need to rewatch it for the fifth time.
I should I should just give up.
I should just give up.
Yeah, sit in a hole. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I know. No, no, no, you're not supposed to agree.
No, I love my little pony.
So do I love sitting in a hole.
Friendship is bitchcraft.
Friendship is cringe.
Next one is called episode 300 predictions.
Wait, I already uploaded this one twice.
OK, whatever. Three, two, one, go.
Episode 300 starts with the original procrastinator's podcast theme.
Trixie has an autistic meltdown with endless jets.
And then they talk about it on the podcast.
Monkey Jones makes a grand return.
Cyber shell and cheesy Manfredo become full time members.
Tom dies comes out as transgender.
Known as the best girl ever.
Ben finally calls me back.
What was that last one?
I feel like I've heard that before.
Which one?
The whole voicemail, I feel like I've heard it before.
Am I crazy?
Did you send it?
I didn't send it. That's not me.
If we go back to the old days, we can have we can have Nate and Trixie
having another boring conversation about like the YouTube algorithm.
That those those were the good old days.
Bring that back, return to tradition for episode 300.
All right, next one is called Kyle and Funny Man.
Episode four, it's dark now.
Critical acclaim, please.
Three, two, one, go.
The show is dark now, but that's what makes it good.
No more funny times for Kyle and Funny Man.
It's dark and depressing, but that's what makes it good.
It's Kyle and Funny Man in space.
That's right. We have crossed the threshold.
This is what the show is now.
It's dark filled with pathos, deep characters,
and that's what the show is now. No more fucking nonsense.
All right, let's go.
Hey, hey, Funny Man.
How about we go on a sweet, fricking adventure?
I know I know the last episode was a bit dark,
but maybe we can be more lighthearted this episode.
No, I cannot.
I'm going to go to a therapist and it's going to be one
entire episode where I just talked to this.
My wife couldn't remember and I had to wear a diaper
to make her happy one last time.
And that's going to be an episode.
Well, I guess I can go do an episode
where I realized that my life has no meaning
because I try to have fun on my own, but I can't.
And I'm like, what's the deal? What is life?
Oh, my God. Oh, yeah.
And to do that, we must argue now, so I hate you.
Well, I hate you too, Funny Man.
Let's go do that.
And that's right, people.
This show is now we're going to have a huge critical claim
to show so fucking good. Yes, yes.
Okay.
I love how like that was almost entirely the show is talking
about what the show is.
That's just podcasting.
That wasn't as dark as I expected.
It wasn't as dark as I thought it was going to be.
Where's the murder? Where's the tragedy?
Funny Man didn't even tell a joke.
Get out.
Well, the show is dark now.
The show is dark.
Funny Man.
It's like, no.
My, yeah, it should have been like,
my name isn't Funny Man anymore.
I can't see the joy in the world.
My name is Ma.
I have, I have sadness.
Cancer. I have depression, cancer.
And boy, howdy is it taking a hold in my brain.
And I'm getting divorced as well from you, Kyle.
No.
And here's a dagger that I'm going to throw,
throw into your torso.
Here I go.
No, Funny Man.
And I lost my wallet on the bus home.
Next voicemail.
What's the next one?
The next one is called Ben St.
gets destroyed in the marketplace of ideas.
Three, two, one, go.
What's up?
It's me, Dusty Dumps.
And I'm basically just here to do a victory lap
all over Ben St's corpse.
Because yes, Ben St may have done a sweet ass
lecture about Tails gets trolled.
He may have been the first people,
one of the first people in the world
to interview Laserbot of Tails gets trolled.
That video is critically under viewed.
And also CC as well.
And you might have voiced some characters
in the official dub, but has he named a character
in the comic?
No.
But I have now the character that is a troll,
which is a corner that appears for two pages
in chapter 14 has been officially named by me
as now a rigor mortis.
And you can see it on the wiki.
Rigor Morphis is his official name now.
And it's credited to me.
So get fucked, Ben St.
How do you retroactively name a character?
We just claim it.
You put a flag in it.
The mint is mint him on the blockchain.
Yeah.
How does I wonder?
What if you made an NFT of the United States of America?
Wonder what would be the ramifications
of minting, say, the entire United States of America
on the blockchain?
Dude, I don't even try that.
You should try it then.
No, think of the impact on the environment.
No, no, I couldn't.
But it would make a lot of money.
No, that's just something anti-NFT bro says.
If America gets packaged up as an NFT,
then I can't like pollute anymore.
Think about it.
Yeah, yeah.
OK.
Next voicemail is, it's called something.
Come on, load.
Thanks.
It's called YouTube swearing arc four.
OK, actually final this time.
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
Dusty dumps back again with an update
on the exciting YouTube censorship storyline
story arc that everybody loves.
So last episode, we said something about maybe my account
was too new to be able to swear on it.
But I was like, that surely can't be the case
because my account was made in like 2009 or something.
But you saying that made me click on my account settings
and I could see my location, which is Japan
because I live in Japan.
What's this guy?
And so I said, well, maybe if I try changing this,
I don't know, just on a whim.
So I changed it to the United States
and tried leaving a comment.
And lo and behold, if your location is set to United States,
you can't swear in comments.
What?
Why are they banning us living in Japan?
All Japanese people are fucking banned from commenting.
But like any English?
Saying fuck in the comments or shit
or any sort of swear word.
But if you're from the United States,
I guess you have the God given rights to say a fuck.
So that's Jeff Dates.
If anybody wants to swear in the comments,
I guess you got to make your location America or something.
Not true because I have a ring.
There's a new wrinkle to this.
And this is bizarre.
I tried to reply to a comment on the PCP channel,
like as the PCP account, into our own comments.
Some guy, some freak in the comments was like,
when I told the story about a Trixie defending May
saying that George Floyd deserved it,
some freak in the comments was like,
George Floyd did deserve it, actually.
And I tried to respond to them with profanity,
with well-deserved profanity that was completely justified
and would have been good.
And I couldn't.
I could not comment on my own YouTube channel.
It deleted the comment from myself.
And we're definitely set to,
I think we're set to Nate's old address,
which is Cincinnati.
So it definitely thinks we're in America.
It deleted our own comment on our own podcast
because it had the F word in it.
And then I re-typed it with no swearing.
And I felt like I wasn't being strongly worded enough,
but whatever.
And it worked.
So I don't know, it's just super fun.
Every time I'm in my after dark account
and I just comment on a video
and I say something about come,
my comment doesn't show up when I refresh.
Yeah, that's what happened.
That's the same thing that happened
with me replying to this guy.
So I don't know if it's, for us,
being located in the United States
does not have any, has not done anything for it.
I don't know.
It's fucked up.
Criminal, what's next?
Swear in the comments, everybody.
Swear like a sailor.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Actually, do like YouTube shorts as comments
because then if it's in a video,
it might be harder for them to delete it.
Next voicemail is called Google Gobble.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, you are absolutely right.
The Reddit search is fucking dog shit.
And you wanna know why?
It simply doesn't work.
Because they made their own search.
It's not powered by Google.
They tried to do their own shit
and it doesn't fucking work.
Just like all searches not powered by Google.
You know what the answer is?
More monopolization.
Individuals and companies
that are not part of a giant conglomerate.
Finally.
Google, Apple, Disney, Amazon,
Google, Apple, Disney, Amazon.
That was catchy.
That was a catchy tune.
I wanna make a song out of that.
Now I like corporations.
Interest on Google, Apple, Amazon, Disney,
Google, Apple, Amazon, Disney, Google, Apple.
Bass, bass, bass, bass.
Microsoft Activision Bethesda.
Bass, bass, tap, tap, tap, bass, bass, bass,
tap, tap, tap, tap.
Tap, tap, tap, tap, bass.
Um, there.
Fucking old.
I have to say, though, I've noticed
that if you use old.reddit.com,
you can actually still access
like an older version of the Reddit website.
And the search on that version
is 100 times more functional.
You'll actually get results.
If you don't do that, the results, shit.
I use the old, wait, do I?
I'm not sure.
In the URL, it'll say old.reddit.com.
Maybe I, I'm not sure.
I'll have to check.
Okay, that's a good tip.
Yeah, I found that because I use it
for like an NSFW Reddit page.
It's like the one I wanted.
You should use it for an NSFT.
Ah, shit.
Mint that shit, dog.
Okay, next one is.
Nice, saggy fucking titties.
Next one is called, did I already,
did I already upload the next one?
Yeah, I did.
Next one is called New Pokemon Game Spoilers.
Three, two, one, go.
It's an isekai.
Been stanked.
Give and take.
It's an isekai.
No, it's not.
It's a time isekai.
Uh, okay.
Did it go through a time?
Did it go through a time portal?
Did the character you play as
has been trying to.
Is it good though?
That's an important problem.
Yeah, that's cute.
That's cute, I guess.
Did you see that they retconned how
Pokeballs work?
What do they do?
All Pokemon have the ability to shrink naturally.
That's just something they can do.
And the Pokeball just traps them in there.
Like they shrink.
It doesn't turn them into energy or anything.
They could just drink and do that.
That's insane.
Okay, that's fine.
Whatever.
It's okay.
I mean, how else did they get them
into apricorn balls?
You know?
Oh, simple.
You turn them into atoms.
You record the atoms and then you recreate them every time.
Oh, magic.
It's like a teleporter.
That would do it, I suppose.
Yeah.
Just say it's magic because they're magical creatures
that shoot lightning at each other.
I mean, when I first...
Well, I think I had this idea years ago
and I can't remember when.
But the idea is that they're...
Pokemon are actually also digital monsters.
But they're not called Digimon.
They're just like, you know, because it's a video game.
But are they the champions?
But they don't present themselves as fake digital monsters
in the canon of the story, so whatever.
I mean, in the canon, you literally store them in a computer.
Yeah.
So it's meant in that way to parallel people
playing the game on their Game Boy Color in real life
because you go around and trade,
just like the people in the game in the Pokemon Center.
They trade Pokemon.
Exactly.
Yeah, whatever.
Pokemon smells.
Diageesis.
It's ARG.
It's not ARG, augmented reality.
So then the next question, I think this person's confused
because the question is called
the question on everyone's mind next week when Gibbon visits.
I don't think you're visiting anywhere next week.
So...
No.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
So, like, you're going to fuck?
You're going to fuck.
This guy must be a bit behind because, like,
you canceled your trip, like, several weeks ago.
I mean, I didn't talk about my trip until it was canceled.
Exactly.
You brought it up to sales.
Maybe they assumed that it was just, like, delayed a week.
And when you, like,
No, no.
When your COVID test came back and you were fine,
they just assumed you were going.
No, no, no.
I'm going to go in the summer.
I have the cost of the ticket.
Totally refunded, completely.
And I can use that cost to buy a new ticket at a different time
in the year.
So...
Clearly this person hasn't played the PCP dating sound.
Clearly.
Also, we have about 10 more.
So we're getting down there, in voicemails.
My dinner's ready.
I want to go and eat.
Okay, okay.
We're almost there.
Speed run.
Next one is called Let's Talk About Race You Lib Tards.
This is at beatmyassatlike.drum.
Three, two, one, go.
Lib Tards like Ben keeps saying it like there is only one race.
The human race.
Bah, bitch.
What about NASCAR?
What about what?
NASCAR.
What about NASCAR?
What?
Oh, that is what's going on.
Yeah, well, they drive around and they...
Yeah, well, what about Formula One, huh?
The better race, the master race.
What about Formula One?
Well, I got a race gone out of here.
It's time for me to leave.
Vroom, vroom, goodbye.
You guys have a good podcast.
Will you actually leave it?
I'm literally leaving now.
Okay.
Okay, goodbye.
See you, beautiful.
All right, well.
See ya.
But...
What a cringe.
Cringe.
Couldn't he...
Couldn't hang it out for the last nine voicemails.
Yeah, fuck.
Okay.
Good riddance.
Okay, next one is...
Next one is called May Lover At Trad.Wife.
Oh, no.
Also called rampantatmisoginous.ben.
So, you know, take your pick.
Three, two, one, go.
So, that was pretty funny timing with Trixie's
I Hate Digit Broke video, huh?
One week she's explaining how she likes Riley
because he's a pathetic bottom feeder.
Willing, May, begging to gravel at her feet,
licking her soles in parentheses and wash.
Nodding.
For the meager crumbs of clouds she made grand.
I'm nodding.
Next week it goes bust.
That's what I'd call an epically my moment.
Also, Ben, on the last episode you kept insisting
that Trixie must remember all of the things
that caused you two to fall out.
Not all of them.
And she must be lying when she's saying
that she doesn't know why you hate her.
But have you considered that she simply suffered
too much cognitive decline from smoking way too much?
Epic 420.
Your motherfucking boba-booy gang,
we do remember.
You hear that?
Or your brain is just working overtime
bending reality into something that allows her
to sleep that night?
Got aloof of pissing everything and everyone away
for what amounted to a couple of unwatchable vlogs
after all.
Front aloof?
More like frontal cope?
Ha ha ha.
Anyways, the Ig Arc seems to be nearing its end,
but we never learned where the fuck Bird came from.
How did they meet in what kind of black male
does Trixie have on him to make him stay with her?
I know it's the answer to some of these.
I know that Bird is just a big dick show lover.
Bird is just an obsessed dick show fan
and they met at a dick show thing.
That's that's it.
Cool.
Yeah, the cognitive decline weed.
Yeah, that's all probably somewhat true,
but she must remember some of it.
She must remember some of it.
There I feel like there was one other thing.
Okay, the Yig thing.
I saw something Trixie says.
I don't I don't think in Trixie's mind
that Riley quitting means that Yig is over.
She just thinks like Yig is just what she calls the channel now.
Yeah, it's a studio of two people.
Well, one I mean, Bird doesn't do anything.
So it's one person now.
Yeah.
So yeah, I think she would not say,
okay, well, just because Riley's gone,
it's not Yig anymore.
Like it's still Yig.
Although it is funny that in that video,
in the I Hate Didgeridoo video,
she did talk about like how important Riley was
and how they were like doing stuff together
and then he quit like three days later.
This is pretty good.
It's pretty good.
Next one is called...
Oh, by the way, I just want to say
that that AI voice was really good.
It's good.
It was pretty good.
That's great.
It reminded me of Mandy from Billion Mandy.
I don't know actually what it is though.
I'm not, hmm, maybe.
Next one is called...
Wait, what number was that?
We need 86.
Okay, this one is called For Your Cons...
No, stop, stop.
It started playing for me.
Okay, For Your Consideration.
Three, two, one, go.
Long tick stall.
LDS in short is a method of intercourse
where the rhythm is slow but deep in thorough.
It is most effective with a long penis,
preferably inches or more.
The penis is inserted into the vagina
all the way in using a slow, smooth stroke.
You pull out slowly as well,
right until the head of the penis
is about to fall out and then you sink back in slow.
Rinse, repeat.
This is a slow stroke.
You pull out and then you sink back in slow.
Rinse, repeat.
This allows the female to feel
every inch of your long dick.
It also increases effectiveness
by rotating your hips
and doing a stir the coffee motion with your stroke.
Long dicking is only possible
when the man is in a dominant position
where he can control the stroke missionary,
to argue, or lasebone sideways,
playing on and be in matching your stroke
to the bass line of the song
also increases effectiveness.
Be aware of the side effects though.
While long dicking a woman
can greatly increase your chances
of getting breakfast in the morning,
it can also take your relationship
to a whole other level
that you may not want to take.
Unfortunately, that is not a concern for a week.
Limp-wristed be de-mails like Benjamin H.
Say who haven't worked out in over a month.
No.
It's true.
What a wild voice.
Is that meant to be Ben Shapiro's voice?
I think definitely, definitely Ben Shapiro calling me out
for not lifting for a month.
Ben is Ben.
It has been, I think, yeah,
it has been now over a month now.
It's a perfect punchline.
Because I got COVID at the end of December,
so that's pathetic.
Pathetic, Ben.
Next one is called Am I a Pet?
Three, two, one, go.
My cat's litter box is across from my desk
and every time he takes a shit, he looks at me.
Yes, yes, your cat owes you.
Ha, ha, ha.
Who's really in charge?
He commands me for food when it's his time to eat.
And in the mornings, he tells me when my turn
with the bed is over.
Am I a pet?
Just get rid of your cat.
Just throw it out.
Just throw it out the window.
Just drop a frying pan in your cat and see what happens.
Just, just, it's simple as that.
Simple as that.
You ever try it?
Don't knock it, don't knock it till you try it.
Okay.
Next one is called Keggs Therapy Session.
Three, two, one, go.
So Keggs Standard, what brings you here today?
It's about my character, Dr. Wolfe.
People around here call me Keggs Standard,
but Keggs is just the character I'm playing.
What exactly are you talking about?
It's like a Stephen Colbert situation,
where Colbert played a right wing dipshit
when he was really a left wing dipshit.
It's the same for me and Keggs.
Even though Keggs is eerily similar to me,
he's an entirely fictionalized character.
I wonder, who am I talking to in this therapy session?
Is it Nate or am I talking to Keggs Standard?
You're talking to Best Guy ever.
Who is Best Guy ever?
Is that also a character you're playing?
Yeah, Best Guy ever is a character.
He's almost entirely identical to me,
right down to the laboratory in worldview.
A lot.
I see, perhaps people are confused
because Best Guy ever and Nate are so similar.
I get where you're coming from.
I don't know if you know this,
but Dr. Wolfe is a character I play.
In real life, I'm a certified accountant.
I'm not a therapist.
But still, people look up to me
because I have years of wisdom that they don't have.
That's a really good point.
I guess I have a ways to go.
I'm out of here.
I have a hot date with Abley Jack.
It's good to be back.
That was very good.
It's so eerie.
It's so eerie that it sounds like
the voice.
Yeah, I mean, it's obviously not.
But then there's like a few brief little bits
where it's like, oh yeah, that's Nate.
Of course.
Yeah, I'm the best guy ever.
That one's a good one.
No.
Like in some words,
some words just sound like he said them,
like kegs sound like he said it.
But like, kegstund.
Kegstund.
It's just characters within characters.
Nothing is real anymore.
You could make fake weagwis with a nice AI voice.
Make a hole.
Nate should just, you should use that bot
and he should just like feed all his past script
weagwis scripts through like an AI thing
and just generate new ones.
OK, next one we're getting down there
is called PCP TPC logo.
I guess this is a hot topic this week.
Three, two, one, go.
In episode 282, Ben wondered why the PCP logo
had a scribbled over page of the vapors in the background.
And I believe that's because the vape is fucking sucks.
No, no, come on.
OK, next one is called.
Trixie explains a very intellectual joke,
parentheses, she's brain dead.
Three, three, two, one, go.
So the first lyrics here,
you're playing Minecraft in a cave looking for diamonds.
That's funny.
I'm in the same cave looking for minors
because my sexual attraction to minors is major.
Can't even play hopscotch without popping a rager.
Now these lyrics in particular,
I think are obviously meant to be funny.
Oh, this is the Mr. Girl album, the referential.
They have word play, you know, he's looking for minors.
You could imply that he's talking about minors, people who mine,
you know, but because it's Minecraft in particular,
which is known to have a very young fan base,
it's like, OK, that seems to be the implication.
And then, you know, saying my sexual attraction
to minors is major is like.
Why is she just explaining the joke?
Don't have a comparison to majors, you know, if we're talking about.
Oh, my God.
So it only makes sense if he's talking about children.
So that's where you start to go.
Oh, and then can't even play hopscotch
without popping a rager is obviously a joke.
So it's humorous, but any very in your face
and, you know, calling yourself a fucking pedophile kind of way.
No kidding.
I can't believe that's real.
What?
You have that?
What was the context of that?
Why was she explaining an obvious joke?
It's I can't believe she had to explain that.
It is.
It's like it's like, OK, well, the chicken,
when you ask why it crossed the road,
but then the answer is you say cross the road.
And it's like, oh, I wasn't expecting that because it was obvious.
Like it's that level.
That's from the reviewed.
Mr. Girl is some guy who thinks it's really funny
to just say he's a pedophile.
And that's his whole thing.
And also he hates trans people, but never mind that.
And they did a review of his album.
Yeeg reviewed his album and loved it, like gushed over it.
They can't get enough of this fucking freak.
Yeah.
So this is the review of that album.
So great review content.
Guys, it's funny because when he says I'm a minor,
when he says I'm a minor, he's looking for minors,
but not in the way that you might think where it's mining,
like minecraft, he means it.
It's a homonym, you see, for another word,
M-I-N-O-R, meaning a person of underage.
It is not legal to have sexual intercourse with them.
Nevertheless, he implies that that is what he wants to do.
The humor you see comes from the suggestion that he is a pedophile.
Very, very droll, very droll.
I have one.
All right, this is great.
I have one comment to say.
She made a video, she released a video about Diddy Kong racing.
It got like 3,000 views.
Nobody watched it.
It was obviously meant, it was very obviously
like her trying to do a Hazel video.
It was very clear.
Someone in the chat said, this is just like Hazel.
And she said, no, this is not like Hazel.
This is me attempting to do Civvie, Civvie 11.
And I don't know if you've ever seen Civvie 11,
but Civvie 11, he's like a comedy guy.
He does, he does game, let's play.
He does like commentary, plays through a game and comments on it,
but he like lampoons it.
He's a comedy guy.
Her video is like obviously not.
There was no comedy and no jokes at all.
And it was, and it's like, it was really weird.
Like you could just admit you're doing Hazel.
Why, why pretend?
No, I'm this, no, actually, I'm pretending.
I'm trying to rip off this other guy, but like it's not.
I don't know.
It was, if you don't, I don't know.
The con, you maybe have to know, if you're familiar with Civvie.
And if you're familiar with Civvie and you heard her say,
no, this, this is my attempt at a Civvie style video.
You would just be like, it's obviously not.
Like if there's no, there's no similarity other than the fact
that you're talking about a game.
It reminded me of, it reminded me of when somebody asked,
people said, people accused Chris Chan of,
they were saying, Sonichu is a rip-off.
It's a rip-off because you, here, you just,
you just mashed together Sonic and Pikachu.
Even the name, the name is just Sonic and Pikachu
mashed together into Sonichu.
And Chris Chan said, no, no, no, you fool.
You see actually the name Sonichu comes from the,
the Japanese name for Sonic, Sonichu, you see.
So, aha, I gotcha.
And it's like, shut up.
What are you talking about?
Why?
Why are you lying?
Literally, why lie?
I don't know, whatever.
Anyway, great voicemail.
I loved it.
Pretty good.
Yeah.
Next one is Baby in a Blender Emotional.
Oh, this is a, this is a Vokeru link.
Here it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Baby in a Blender Emotional.
It really, it really liked that little
Carlos Santana riff in the middle there.
Holy moly.
Good one.
Next one is called Rod Serling, coming of 300.
Three, two, one, go.
Imagine if you will, the Procrastinator's podcast,
episode three, double O.
I don't want to.
Everyone is here.
Davoo, Tom, Simsie, Cybershell, Oblivionfall.
It's like a goddamn multiverse fighting game,
except without the concerning community presence of minors.
Gave us excited to record.
Which kind of minors do you mean, though?
Any of his many guests yet.
But wait, was there not a prophecy?
A wording that implied that he was coming?
Joining the call to the horror of everyone
is Nate the Body Saint Himself.
The Body.
The video goes live the next week,
and what they all feared was true.
No, Nate.
Yes, watch.
Zero likes and zero views.
No.
Horrifying.
Worst fate I cannot imagine.
Yeah, not gonna happen, bro.
Twilight Zone episode where a YouTuber
enters the Twilight Zone,
but the only difference is all their videos
just get zero views.
And they go, ah.
They keep gaining subscribers,
getting less views every day.
It doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like everyone's talking about their videos.
Everyone's like talking about them on 4chan and stuff.
They got a Kiwi Farms thread.
Everyone's talking about them,
but no views.
Nobody's watching.
No views.
How does anyone know about it?
They're talking about it,
and it's like, if they're talking about it,
like it's a completely different video.
They're just saying things that weren't in there,
and you're just like, no.
No, that's not what my video was.
And their Patreon starts draining money
from them instead of giving it to them.
Yeah.
Next one is called, is this today?
Okay, next one is called I Did It.
We've got three more.
I Did It.
Three, two, one, go.
What is it?
Hello, comrades.
Nikolai found vodka.
Now, Nikolai, okay.
You just want,
Nikolai just wanted to let you know
that Nikolai considered you all comrades.
Oh, cool.
Thanks, com.
Even if you are a dirty capitalist.
Thanks, comrade.
Thanks, comrade Nikolai.
Thank you.
I love you.
That's the worst Russian action I've ever heard in my life.
Don't invade Ukraine, please.
Yeah, don't.
Okay.
I don't think you should do that.
I think that would be bad.
In my opinion.
The Ukraine has UK in it,
and that reminds me of my country where I live,
and that's scary.
And how would you like it if Russia invaded your country?
Oh, I would be so sad.
Yeah, you better, you better watch it.
Next, next one is called
Wong-Chan is back.
Three, two, one, go.
Flo, it is Wong-Chan.
I'm doing good.
Thank you.
How are you?
What the fuck was the point of that?
Yeah.
It's just the point is to be a racist caricature,
and then say hello.
All right, yeah.
And then say hi.
I'm doing good.
Thanks, Wong-Chan.
How are you?
Yeah, Wong-Chan, you know, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry that God made you like this
as such a racist caricature of your own race.
You know, it's not your fault.
You didn't, you didn't choose to be like this.
And why would I judge, and how can I judge you for that?
God bless.
Next voicemail.
Happy Chinese New Year,
Mahal, Ni Hao, Happy Chinese New Year, Wong-Chan.
Last voicemail.
This is breaking news.
It's called breaking news.
Three, two, one, go.
Guys, guys, breaking news.
No, fucking Riley said that.
Fucking void gazers is canceled.
What?
That's true.
Also episode 300.
Have Trixie.
No, have Riley on.
Yeah, yeah.
This guy's brain's going a mile a minute.
He sounded like ABGN at the last we go, yeah.
Riley on the procrastinator's podcast.
Can we get him?
Can we, can we afford him?
I don't know if we can afford him.
He listened to the last episode, he was mad.
He was, he was, he was mauled tweeting about it on Twitter.
He gets to produce the next episode.
That's good enough.
We can let him produce the next episode.
I guess that's it.
That was the last voicemail.
We're done.
That'll do.
We did it.
That will do.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to call it.
I'm ready to fucking eat because I'm a fat boy.
I gotta go pee.
I gotta go pee to stuff my tummy.
I peed once during and I got to do it again.
Wow.
Because I'm drinking lots of delicious sparkling water.
Stay hydrated.
It's good for your kidneys.
Perfect.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, good.
StComics.com.
StComics.com slash stores.html, Blu-rays, Byroad to Radcon, patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Get bonus episodes.
We will make another bonus episode one of these days.
I promise.
No, you fucking won't.
Don't lie.
We gotta.
We will.
We must.
I don't know.
Anything else?
Twitter.com forward slash simsipatreon.com.
No.
simsipatreon.com forward slash slimsy.
You can see tits being milked.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Give and take dot site and check me out on Twitter and whatever.
I have announcements to make, but not yet.
Not yet.
I will hopefully have some soon as well.
Post it.
Keep yourself posted.
I'll keep you posted.
All right, shut up.
That's it.
That's the end.
And goodbye.
See you next week.
Bye-bye.