I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Okay, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's another week. We had a bi-week two weeks ago.
A channel got in trouble for, well...
A salacious link.
Yeah, YouTube considered the link to Vinny's drawings, adult content nudity, breaking terms of service.
So we got a temporary, one week temporary strike or ban or hold or whatever on uploading, not on uploading but on publishing videos.
Yes, so...
So that was stupid.
Uh, we're back.
Not Vinny's fault.
No.
Uh, just like YouTube being, and then I appealed and then they just have still not, I appealed immediately and they still have not answered my appeal.
But we're back to having the ability to post, right?
Yeah, all our privileges should be restored now.
But we still have a warning on the channel from two years ago because I or someone else put the link to the Shadbase in the description.
Lol.
Yeah, I should appeal that again.
No.
And that one's not for nudity. That one's not for nudity or adult content. That one's for external link slash advertising.
I thought that wasn't a problem.
Because it's Shadbase that it was like they caught, oh, this is one of those websites that are bad.
I don't, I don't know.
Truly, I don't know. You would think that would expire, especially since I removed the link and appealed.
Uh, well, you gotta appeal more. You gotta be more appealing.
Yeah, I, damn, damn if that ain't the truth.
Uh, remember how I said that?
Did I talk about how when I filmed that video, which is almost edited by the way, I have, I had 14 hours of footage and I have edited almost 13 hours of it.
So it is truly, it is truly getting down.
Might be out this week, honestly. I don't know, unless something unforeseen happens.
I went and I bought a light. Did I talk about buying a shop light to light the seat, the shot?
You did, yeah.
Well, I wanted to combine it with the sunlight.
Yes. And it more or less worked. I use that light as my like room light now, but it's too bright on its own.
So I used, um, I think I probably described how like I constructed a like cardboard and aluminum foil like light funnel for it to try and concentrate the light in one direction.
Well, well, I did. And now I use it and I put that like light funnel on it and I pointed it at the ceiling and you know, the white ceiling diffuses the light throughout the room.
So now I use it as my room light and it's great. I mean, I have all light in my, I have a ceiling light, but it's not very bright.
So, you know.
Hmm.
So it all comes together.
I was about to say, like, we'll be careful about if it's a more powerful light, you're using more electricity, but you don't have the current issue that we have over here with gas prices and electricity bills going apeshit.
Because of the Ukraine war.
Oh, yeah. Well, I mean, I mean, I mean, how, how much electricity can it be? I mean, it's a bright, it's a bright light, but like, you know, it just sufficiently lights my room.
I don't know. It's one of those things that like, you look at the voltages and the amperages and the wattages and I'm like, this just, it's just electric. I don't get it.
But I feel like there's like,
Amperage, I hardly know her.
You could, you could probably min max.
Wait, wait, sorry. I fucked it up. Amperage. I hardly know her age. There we go. Got it.
Amperage.
Cross the bridge. That's all I've got.
Sounds like a city in, in England. Amperage.
Or New England.
Or New England. Yeah. You know what? You know what?
Saw a great tweet. This must have been two weeks ago now. It was a, in, in Massachusetts, they call, they call the booster shot.
The booster, the booster shot, but it was spelled like, like Worcester, W-O-R-C-E-S-T.
So the boar sister.
The boar sister, the boar sister shot.
B-O-R-C-E-S-T.
E-R.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's boar, boar sister.
Boar sister.
Um, anyway, I'm using that light and it looks, it looks pretty bizarre.
It looks pretty bizarre with the light funnel on it because it's like four pieces of cardboard and aluminum foil taped together.
Uh, but like, it's, they're taped together imperfectly, so the light kind of seeps out at the corners, so, I don't know.
It's pretty, it's pretty bizarre looking.
But it works.
Lights in my room doesn't get too hot. What more can you ask for?
Uh, I don't know. Nothing.
Nothing. Nothing. That's right. Nothing. Not a damn thing.
You may never ask for anything ever again.
I won't.
Not even one subscriber.
No, please. In fact, I want less subscribers.
Hey, Ben.
The video's almost edited. It's almost edited, Gib.
13 hours out of 14.
That's great.
I know. Maybe this, it should be out this week.
You never know. You never know what's going to happen, but this week seems reasonable.
Okay, what were you saying?
Ben, did you know that the Queen of England, Queen Elizabeth II is dead?
I choose to believe that it's not true.
I can't stand a world without her.
I'm going to call it fake news. Yeah, and I, they can't prove it.
They got her coffin. They got her corpse on display right now.
That's what they said about Elvis. They said Elvis was dead.
They said the moon landing happened, you know?
They said Elvis died on the moon, taking a shit by taking his space astronaut suit off,
and you say, no, you can't do that. And they shit.
That's exactly what they said.
It exploded on the moon.
And it turned out to be false. So what did we learn?
Don't trust the mainstream media. Don't trust anyone.
That's right.
It's actually tomorrow that the funeral, like they're going to put her in the ground on live on TV.
Can't miss it.
Oh, good for her.
She loves the ground.
That's the day that they're going to get that like food banks are closed and like all like funerals are canceled and food banks.
Yeah, people are not allowed to have their own canals.
Cancer wards are forced.
In forced honor of the Queen, you cannot do anything on Monday.
And if you do, you will be slapped.
You will be shunned.
You'll be grabbed out of the crowd by monarchist simps.
You know, we wrestle to the ground and then police will be called and they will charge you for something for saying, you know, fuck you.
You know what that is?
That's idolatry.
You're allowed to work on Sunday on the Sabbath.
The day that God that you're supposed to take off to honor God, but you can't work on Monday to honor the Queen.
That's the false idol idolatry right there.
Yes.
I'm probably going to watch a bit of the-
We should sing more hymns on this show.
I don't even know hymns.
I know-
You don't know-
Wait.
All things wide and wonderful.
All creatures great and small.
All things-
That's not a hymn.
That's just a song.
That's the hymn they sang in church.
It's not a-
Open your hymn book.
It's not a hymn unless it sounds bad.
They all sound bad.
Not a hymn unless it's not catchy.
He's got the whole world in his hands, got the whole wide world.
That one's definitely not a hymn.
That's a damn pop-
That one's probably newer than Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer.
God, it's taken me back.
This is the sort of thing-
Because I went to primary school that had a church,
and so it was just sort of a normal thing.
We had assembly every morning,
and you would sing hymns.
And that was normal.
Oh, zana, hey, zana, zana, zana, ho, zana-
Now there's-
Zana, hey, zana, ho, zana-
Now there's a-
Now there's a good ol-
A good ol-
praise song.
It's a good ol hymn.
What was the one with the-
It's a fucking harvest festival one.
Wait, did you know that one I was just singing?
No, I didn't recognize it.
That's from Jesus Christ Superstar.
Oh.
That's the joke.
Harvest festival?
There's one about a harvest festival.
I'm just like-
Sounds like some pagan shit to me.
Yeah, probably.
Sounds like some people that celebrate Halloween
who I won't associate with.
The fucking-
If I had a hammer song was in there.
I think this is like crossing over with just sort of like-
Is that a Jesus song?
It is, isn't it?
I think so.
If I had a hammer-
Oh.
Oh, I'd hammer in the morning.
I'd hammer in the evening.
All over this land.
And then it goes to like-
If Jesus had a gun,
he'd shoot everyone.
Wait a minute.
The hammer song.
I never sang that song in church,
but there's a Garfield strip where John is singing it.
And I didn't recognize the tune and I was like,
Mom, what is the song John is singing?
And she was like,
Oh, there's a church song.
I'd hammer in the morning.
It's like, I've never actually heard it sung.
I've just heard that song described.
Yeah.
She tried to describe the song.
I mean, some of the songs are kind of fun to sing along with.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, that's why they make songs,
so that they're more fun to sing than to just say.
Yeah.
Pop songs, they changed it.
They made it so you can't tell what they're saying,
but it doesn't matter because it's so fucking cool.
Because it's so fucking epic.
Because you can bump and grind to it.
Because you can get out there
and have premarital sex on the dance floor
and do the sinful, secular pop music.
If you forest it, you can bump and grind
to if I had a hammer.
You can bump and grind to all those hands.
Yeah.
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
And I have been humiliated.
You've been thoroughly pooned this day.
To be a fool.
That's right.
Um, why are we talking about God?
Because, oh, because I love him so much, yes.
Yes, yes.
And we should make more,
we should talk more about his glory.
That's his with a capital H.
No, okay.
You know what?
Fuck God.
You know what God did?
God chose the queen and the queen sucks.
Fuck the queen.
He chose to kill the queen.
He chose to kill the queen
and I can never forgive him for that.
He chose to give the queen the powers.
He chose to take her away
at the young age of 97.
And like, she had so much more,
she had so much more good left to do in this world.
It's only 96, man.
Get it right.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
If I'm just wishful thinking,
just wishful thinking,
she could have made it just one more year.
70 more years, 70 more years.
You know, I see people that are like,
fuck the queen.
Honestly, I don't know enough about Elizabeth
to have a particularly strong opinion
about her one way or the other.
Was she a good queen?
Was she a bad queen?
Was she just carrying on the legacy of colonialism?
Did she do anything to improve it in her own small way?
I don't know.
So I haven't been queen posting
because I don't have a position that I can defend.
I mean, the position I have
is regardless of how nice she was
and how good of a queen she was,
she didn't abolish the monarchy.
Yeah, the monarchy is bad.
She kept the status quo of the monarchy
being in charge technically.
And any argument you say,
well, they don't have real power.
They have a huge amount of money.
They cost the country money at all.
Well, they do make like proclamations, right?
They have some degree of policymaking.
No, on the technical level,
laws only exist when the queen or king now
will look over them and say yes.
But they always say yes.
So it's not real power.
But it is technically the case
that they have the final say.
Theoretically, they could veto a law
that passed through parliament?
Yeah, and I think the House of Lords as well.
If even the Lord say,
the monarch gets to say no or yes.
Yeah.
And people argue that the queen
always goes with whatever parliament goes with,
so she doesn't have real power.
And it's like in practice, sure.
But I don't think that is a good argument
for keeping her and the monarchy system around at all.
That's a little bit like how theoretically,
the electors in the American Electoral College
could not vote according to the way
that their state told them to.
Theoretically, they could,
and they have done it,
but it's never swung an election.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
I think so.
Anyway, I'm glad she's dead.
And then watch this video get flagged
by the British government
and take them down.
The monarchy is bad.
We can all agree on that.
It's just a weird, dumb thing to have
in the year of our Lord, 2020.
Could she have abolished it?
Could she have just said,
as queen, there's no more monarchy?
We're private citizens now.
I think if she by herself said,
no more monarchies, it wouldn't work.
I think she could abdicate.
And then next in line would become the king
and everyone would just do that.
And she would still be alive.
I don't actually know by what means
she would try to abolish the monarchy
because it's like, I don't know.
Even if you kill,
even if every single person
who is recognized as a royal family person
was killed in a catastrophic tornado
and there's no one left,
they could go up the family tree
and then go back down and find an heir.
And so there will always be a monarch.
I don't know how you would abolish it
without, I don't know,
how any other country do it?
This is where my history is lacking.
It would be a pretty base move.
Yeah, I don't know if she,
maybe she lacks any sort of formal power
to decree that the monarchy is abolished.
That's probably not in any books anywhere.
It would be,
I'm sure the books all refer to
the existence of a monarch
under the assumption that there will continue to be one.
But it would be a pretty base move
if she were to be like,
okay, I am stepping down as monarch
because I do have the authority to do that.
And I am personally
coming out with the,
I personally proclaim that I think the monarchy
should be abolished.
So I'm stepping down.
I'm just going to continue to live over here
as the resigned queen.
My successor can become king
if he wants to,
but I don't acknowledge him
as a real monarch
because I don't believe in such things anymore.
I mean, if that was the best
she could do formally,
then that would still be,
that would be cool,
and that would probably-
That would be cool of her,
and I wouldn't be celebrating her death right now.
But the fact is,
she lived her whole life to uphold
the systems that were in place
that led to her having
such wealth and opulence.
It's like, of course,
she wouldn't say,
let's tear this down.
She just likes it.
She likes it.
Right.
Nobody would ever say-
She's good for her.
Nobody would ever say
that she likes being rich,
but of course she did.
She didn't do anything about it.
Right, yeah.
What was that one post
on a Facebook post
that's like the idiot queen
and her idiot hat or something?
Oh, that's Christopher Eccleston.
That's the Doctor Who actor
who, with the resurgence of Doctor Who
in 2009 or something.
That's the first,
that's the hymn
before David Tennant.
He's cool.
He hates the monarchy.
Seems like there's a not
insignificant amount of British people
that are just like,
hey, the monarchy's bad, actually.
Why do we still have this?
Yeah.
All the punks hate the monarchy.
Would you say most people like that,
or would you say that's like,
would you say the average person
is like mildly pro-monarchy?
I mean, as far as like,
tallies go like,
what do you call it when you ask people
what they think,
60% are like pro-monarchy.
That's funny.
And it's probably,
it's not exactly a political thing,
but I think it's obvious
that if you're a right-leaning person,
you're pro-monarchy,
because that's like what you aspire to
is having power and whatever.
I feel like even like a middle
of the road liberal,
someone like CGP Grey is like,
hmm, yeah.
I mean, CGP Grey has that whole video.
The monarchy is actually good for the economy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's a sort of thing
where if you don't think about it,
it seems nice.
It's like, look at all that cool stuff.
Isn't that cool?
Yeah, it's a culture.
I can be proud to be associated somehow
to that culture.
Right.
Yeah, but it's one thing to have like,
oh, it's our culture,
but like the culture of colonialism,
the culture of like having vast wealth
and then the serfs who don't,
that sucks.
That's a shitty culture.
Why would you be proud of such a thing?
It's like,
there's an artist called,
oh, shit.
Well, they're called a red and black salamander.
They're called like nine millimeter something.
I follow them on Twitter.
They have a cartoon that's really good.
It's like,
yeah, it's like a big rich capitalist
and then a bunch of like farmers around him
and it's like,
look at,
it's like, look at everything.
The capitalist is like,
look at everything I've got
and all the farmers are like,
hey, what, hey,
what the, he's got like piles of gold or whatever.
And then he's like,
hmm, and then he draws a circle around
the land that they're standing on
and then he,
like he's still got it,
but he's like,
look at everything we've got
and all the farmers are like,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, it's like that.
I get you.
Shit, what was I talking about?
You're just asking if the average person,
Oh, the average person.
Yeah, I mean,
when like,
I don't know,
I think I,
there's a few people who,
if I asked them,
they'd probably be pro monarchy.
Yeah.
Like friends of parents and stuff
that I've met before,
but
the majority of people I know,
as like associates or friends,
they're either ambivalent
or would be like, yeah, fuck them.
Yeah.
So I haven't really grown up
in a pro monarchy thing,
even though I think there was a part
of my teenage years where,
as a rebellious move,
because I'm such a rebel
and such a contrarian rebel.
Did you become pro monarchy
for a while?
I became pro monarchy for a little while
because, you know,
I get you.
And it's so like,
yeah, but like,
whatever, it's cool.
It looked like cool stuff.
Look at the castles
and the cannons.
Damn it.
I had this, you know,
I've probably talked about
how I kind of had the same thing
or like for a little bit
in high school there,
I was sort of like,
I wouldn't,
I would never call myself a conservative,
but I would like,
I would dabble and like,
hmm, but what if,
but what if,
what if George W. Bush
is actually like,
right to like not respond
to Hurricane Katrina?
What if,
what if,
shit, what was the other one?
What if
the Iraq war was good actually?
Like, what if,
what if same sex parents
shouldn't be able to adopt kids?
You know,
just being, just being,
because everyone around me was liberal,
because I was in Massachusetts.
It's like,
my stupid teachers think that like,
gay people should have rights.
Well, I'll show them.
I'll stick it to the man.
Right.
Because in my,
in my limited,
in my limited field of view,
all the authority figures were like,
hmm, good things are good actually.
And I was like, I'm going to,
I'll show you.
You are going to give me homework
and then you're going to have a political opinions.
Let me see that.
Let me, let me change that.
We're going to do something about this.
We're going to set,
set this record straight.
I guess it's a good sign then that
like,
grew up in a pretty,
not a,
not left necessarily.
Liberal,
like left leaning,
I guess it's,
it's,
it's definitely got more left leaning over the years,
very recently.
Yeah.
My dad is like,
pro-socialism,
which is a strange thing.
That's pretty cool.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah.
I mean, my dad is a,
I think my dad is,
is a,
is a Bidenite.
So,
you know,
that makes basically communist.
Yeah.
He's basically revolutionary.
Biden has been
so popular these days.
Everybody loves dark Brandon.
He's sky,
he's skyrocketing in the pool.
I'm not even kidding.
I wish I was kidding.
I mean,
it's,
it is kind of funny.
And it's,
it's so easy because like,
the,
the Republicans are like,
oh,
we've overturned Roe v. Wade.
Everybody disliked that.
Like liberals,
even conservatives,
even some conservatives were like,
okay,
that's weird,
because it's like the more fringe right-wing
opinions are getting like,
the main attention.
So it's like,
obviously,
you'd rather Biden over anything of that.
Do you,
do you think that's why his,
I mean,
it's that combined with a few things lately
that Biden has said that have like,
cemented his opposition to that kind of right-wing
in the,
in the Republican Party.
So I'm like, yeah.
I'm not sure.
I think,
I think there's,
why,
what do you think?
I'm honestly not even sure
that I can opine on like how the like,
normal,
like fucking Joe six pack mind
thinks about things like politics.
I mean,
gas prices kind of went down a bit.
So, I mean,
I feel like that's big.
They're still up from where they were before,
but they are not as bad.
And like,
presidential approval ratings are like,
extremely tightly correlated with gas prices.
Yeah.
I suppose there's this other things like,
yeah,
Biden's siding against pressure.
In the,
in the whole Ukraine thing.
It's like,
I mean,
Russia's easy to hate.
I think every,
yeah,
like every fucking western politician has,
is against Russia.
Aren't they?
Yeah.
So that's,
that's a slam dunk.
There's,
there's no,
this is like,
the bad guys are so evil right now.
It's like,
he doesn't need to do that much to seem,
Biden for life,
Biden for life.
No,
no more elections.
Biden for life when he was very long.
No,
that's true.
He's almost the queen's age.
Is he?
How old is he?
He's like,
in his 70s.
He might,
he might be 80.
How old is
Biden?
He's definitely not as 90s.
He's 70,
he's 79.
He's 79.
Yeah.
That's actually,
I thought he was in his 80s.
He's actually a little,
a little bit younger than I thought.
Um,
no,
that's right.
It's like,
isn't Trump like the same age?
Like,
like Trump,
Hillary and Biden are all like 75 plus.
It's just going to be a rotation of those three.
Trump is 76.
It's her turn next.
I mean,
if they live as long as the queen did.
Sure.
They've got so many more terms left in them.
There's spry.
No.
Spring chickens.
Yeah.
Um,
what,
what are you talking about?
The only thing that's interesting,
the only thing that's,
I'm finding a little interesting about the funeral
that's coming up is that like,
an incredibly large gathering of world leaders,
politicians,
royals from other kingdoms
are coming to see the queen's funeral.
They're all going to be in the same place.
It's going to be like a river.
It's going to be in one piece.
And then Sabo is going to come in
and he's going to kill someone.
He's going to assassinate someone.
You talking about like from one piece?
Oh no, did I spoil it?
I don't know.
I mean, yeah,
but like,
I'll forget by the time I catch up.
Yeah.
Hey, Alias are bleep that for any audience members
who are not caught up on one piece.
Sabo will come in and he's going to bleep somebody.
He's going to bleep somebody.
Uh, let me see.
Dude, one piece is so fucking epic.
Yeah.
I've been reading the most recent chapters
and you're going to love it.
I should.
I'm sure I will love it.
I have no doubt that I will love it
when I finally get around to it.
I'm asking Oblivionfall if he has any more
of those,
any more voicemails from that side voicemail channel
that he made.
In other news,
I guess I've got some Clarissa stuff down.
I counted up.
Hell yeah.
I saw you tweeting.
I saw you tweeting about that.
Or you made it.
I mean, I forgot the number,
but I think,
what was it?
Let me,
let me check my Twitter.
Find out the knowledge.
Indeed.
Why do I tweet anything other than one thing?
Okay.
One must always find the knowledge.
So currently 54 pages are sketched.
I've made 50 pages already.
Those are ones that are done and published.
Okay.
Yeah.
So it was 50 for the Tezuko Award
and that's where I stopped.
54 pages are now sketched
because I did like 11 the other day
and it may take another 30 pages beyond that.
So it could be like 134.
Have you been sketching pages
or is this just your count of the ones you already had?
I've been sketching pages like recently.
It wasn't 54.
It was more like 34.
Okay.
Cool.
So I'm making progress
and it's difficult like laying out a page
and being like,
okay, well,
do I want this panel to fill up the page
or do I want it to be small?
I don't know.
Where do I put the speechful?
I mean, the speechful was not so difficult
because if I know what I want to be said,
it's just a case of like arranging
the bubble in the panel where the person's speaking.
Yeah, I got you.
But there's a few ones that are like,
this could be a smaller panel
but it's cool as a full page spread.
But I worry that maybe I'm like zooming out too much
and when it's a full thing, it's like the image is too big
and I could fit more onto less pages
because I'm like,
I don't know.
How do you do that?
I think it's probably,
well, my problem is usually zooming in too far.
So if it were me, I would say,
hmm, if I sometimes think I'm zooming out too far,
that probably means I'm doing it right
because like my tendency is to go too far
in the opposite direction.
I don't know if you're the same way though.
I mean, I've got,
I keep the A4 page on my monitor
so I can see the whole thing.
So I can say, okay,
from the last page that she does this motion,
so we need a reaction shot.
I just randomly draw a rectangle
and then see if I can fit something in it that looks right
and if it doesn't, I change the rectangle.
And then, okay, what else,
what space left do I have on the page?
Most of the time doing it this way,
I make a page layout and I'm like, yeah, that works.
I don't think too much more beyond it and it's fine.
But I feel like there's a lot of artistry
that I'm not going into.
Like I could be panel laying out a beautiful panel
or just being good at it.
But I just want it down.
I just want to sketch it all down so I have all these pages.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, you could always do the rough sketch
and then mix up the paneling later.
That does become a little finicky
where it's like, oh, this panel on this other page
would work better on the previous page.
I got to move it over
and then go to shrink some of the other panels.
Sometimes I just drag a lasso around it
and squish it so that it fits.
Yeah.
And it's like, yeah, it works fairly well.
I think I'll need to go over them all again
and be like, just to think about
how good that would be to read
before I sketch it all down.
But it's happening.
It's happening.
I'm making it.
That's awesome.
Yeah, that's good.
That's good news.
Did you finish those commissions?
No.
Give.
There's only a single commission left
that I have not started
and then another one which I need to finish the coloring on.
So I'm basically done.
So don't worry about it.
Right.
And I have edited 13 out of 14 hours of my video,
so I'm basically done.
You are basically...
So you know what?
I should just...
Oh, dang.
So I should just stop here, actually.
It's basically done, so I should just leave it.
Yeah, and delete it as well.
And also...
You know, because if I actually post it,
then I'll lose motivation to work on it.
So like...
I...
Shit, that reminded me of something.
Oh, no.
Fuck, what was it?
Oh, I actually did get distracted.
Okay, I'm sure...
I already complained about how I got ghosted in Alibaba, right?
That printer won't talk to me anymore?
Yeah.
Is that still happening?
Well, she has not contacted me,
so I have two options.
I was doing the price calculations
and it was so irritating because,
like, according to the figures they gave me,
including shipping,
it was gonna be a whole, like,
three or four dollars less
for a, like, per copy.
If...
With that printer.
It's a significant difference
and it's really upsetting.
I genuinely think,
and this sounds so stupid,
I genuinely think I'm gonna, like,
make a new account
and contact them again
and, like, pretend I'm a different person
and, like, fucking catfish them.
Catfish them and try to get me to, like,
print my stupid fucking book anyway.
Uh, I don't know,
just because they're just being cons about it.
Have you...
Have you not...
They have other prices.
They have...
Message?
Have you not left a second message?
You fool.
Yes, I've left messages.
I've left several messages being, like,
Hey, why have you not contacted me back?
Like, why did you stop me?
And they're all red.
It's...
It's, like, they're all on red.
She's seen them all
and has chosen not to respond.
Okay, well...
So it's, like, a deliberate attack.
Then, yeah, I guess you could try.
Yeah.
Do they know what the project is already?
Would they recognize you?
They...
No, they would not recognize...
I never sent, like, the page files
or told them what the book was, so...
They might recognize if I, like,
am asking for a book that's the same...
Like, same page count
and size and stuff.
It's possible.
I don't know.
But they haven't seen the files,
so they might also not recognize.
I don't know.
I'm gonna, like, finish the layout,
because I never, like, quite finished
doing the layout and doing the final cover.
So I'm gonna finish that,
and then I'm gonna fucking catfish this stupid bitch.
And then I'm gonna do that.
And if it doesn't work,
then I'll just have to go with one of the other companies.
But it's seriously, like, this company,
if I printed, like, at 100 copies,
it was gonna save me, like, $4 per copy,
which is significant.
If I printed 500 copies,
it was gonna be, like, less than half the price.
Or maybe not less.
It was gonna be, like, almost a 50% savings.
Let's say 30%.
It was gonna be, like, a 30% savings
to print, like, a large number with this company,
as opposed to the other ones.
And, like, the paper types were all the same.
I don't know.
I don't, I think it would have been a similar product,
just cheaper.
And I'm, like, I can't, I'm gonna,
it's gonna kill me.
It's gonna eat away at me if I do the Kickstarter,
and, like, the book has to cost, like, $35
when I know it could cost $30.
If only fucking stupid cunt Mei Zhang
or whatever her name is,
just didn't ghost me, right?
Just because, like, out of spite one day,
she decided I'm bored of this guy.
I don't want to print,
I don't want to print his sample copies.
You got lord of ghosted.
I wish she was dead.
I want to kill her.
Oh, then you'll be ghosting her.
Yeah, I want, yeah, that's right.
I'm gonna make her a ghost.
How could you do this to me?
It's generally upsetting,
and I'm getting upset thinking about it.
Like, why have I been attacked like this?
Why have I been persecuted like this?
And that sounds like a joke when I say it,
but I'm absolutely 100% not joking.
Ugh.
I have to get those savings.
I have to get those precious savings
and pass them on to the consumer at any cost.
Yeah, it sucks.
Yeah.
You know, I was considering,
like, for the Clarissa,
like, going through Amazon
to have it be like, oh, you can
like, print on demand.
Buy and print on demand.
Yeah.
I feel like that might be,
if that's doable,
or high enough quality,
that would be a lot safer,
a lot less strenuous way
of getting that physical out there.
It's true.
It's safer.
It's less strenuous,
but the margins are worse.
It's just, it's cheaper.
Definitely, yeah.
It's cheaper to print them yourself.
But it is less of a headache.
It's so much more like,
I feel like it's well worth the cost
based on my experience
sending the Lord of Ghost book out.
Yeah.
Like, it's just, there's so much.
It's mostly customs.
It's mostly the fact that customs
in various countries
can just randomly decide,
even though it's all labeled properly,
that they can just rip it open
and say, oh, this looks stupid
and throw it back.
And say, it sucks.
And it appears, like,
seven months later,
my door, like, destroyed.
And I have to, like,
package it and send it again.
Oh, I find-
I hope, but it doesn't happen again.
I finally went
and I opened a new PO box
at my new address
so I can finally tell
my stupid landlord
what my mailing address is
so that I can finally,
maybe even get her
to give me some of my
old security deposit back.
That's exciting.
Yeah.
Yeah, I have a new PO box,
which is good.
The PO box is going to be, like,
it's too- it's tiny.
It's too small to hold, like, anything.
But it doesn't matter because
I don't know why people buy
the bigger PO-
the bigger boxes,
because if a thing is too big
for your PO box,
they just hold it for you.
They just hold it for you
and they put-
give you a slip
and then you give them the slip
and they're, like, here.
We had it in the back room for you.
So, like, I'm just going to abuse that.
Yeah.
Like, big enough for envelopes.
They have to keep the envelopes in the back.
It's big enough for envelopes,
but if I- if I do
slime and punishment,
I'm going to be sending them in, like,
boxes.
Like, little- like,
not large boxes,
but, like,
boxes that will not fit
in this box.
In this PO box is what I mean.
Um...
Uh...
What else is that?
Shit, I was going to say something else about-
Oh, yeah.
Um...
The book.
What I need to do,
I- I distracted myself from finishing
editing the video,
because I was contacting
some of the other printers
to, like, get other price quotes
just to compare
to, like, find out,
okay, like,
what is the price difference
I'm looking at here.
And I pulled out my paper samples
and I'm, like,
hmm,
looking at them.
And I might just-
I think-
I meant to do this before
and I should have gone through it.
I should have finished this.
I need to just, like,
get a sample copy from...
Honestly,
doesn't need to be the same company.
I should just get a-
I should get sample copies
from anyone...
whatever.
And I can use those sample copies
as, like, a,
this is what the book
is going to look like
when I do the Kickstarter.
It doesn't-
it doesn't matter
if it's from the same company
or not,
as long as, like,
the final-
whoever I end up getting
the final copies from,
you know,
makes something that looks
very similar.
So...
I'm probably just going to
maybe buy samples
off of, like,
this other guy
whose prices are not as good
and,
meanwhile,
sneakily try and catfish
the lady into-
into giving me her-
her deal.
Uh,
that's my-
that's my plan going forward.
But I pulled out all these
paper copies
and I'm comparing,
like,
ooh,
16-point,
uh,
glossy,
laminated
versus, like,
um,
this is a 250 GSM,
uh,
UV-
coated.
I pulled out my copy of-
I once again have pulled out
my copy of, uh,
problem sleuth
to, like,
compare page weights.
Somehow,
even when a-
even when a paper type
is, like,
just as thick,
just as sturdy,
just as glossy,
laminated,
whatever,
it just feels like
a piece of shit
when I'm holding
the paper sample
in my hand.
It feels like garbage,
like it belongs in the trash,
versus, like,
in the- in the book form,
it feels good,
and it feels right,
and it's like,
yes,
this is how a book should feel,
even when it's, like,
very similar paper consistency.
I think it's just the fact
that it's a single sheet
and not, like,
many together.
Yeah.
You gotta get the real sense
of, like,
how a book
with paper like this
would feel.
Yeah.
It's-
it's-
it's a psychological
barrier.
Um...
You gotta trust the paper.
But I-
I gotta-
I gotta send-
I gotta send some other guy
the same mess-
requests to-
as I sent to this other lady
and be like,
hey, I want a bunch of
different samples,
and I want them arranged
this, that,
and the other way.
I want different types
of paper on each one
so I can compare them.
And hopefully this person
doesn't ghost me
for the same-
for the same request.
Um...
Yeah.
Anyway, I was-
I feel like I was-
I was getting bored
of editing.
So even though it's, like,
almost done,
I was like,
I don't want to look at this anymore.
I will pull out my paper samples
and I will do it
a different thing
right when I'm near the finish line.
Oh, by the way,
uh,
speaking of-
speaking of feeling bad
while editing.
Remember?
Do you recall
that we recorded
a bonus episode last week, Gib?
Yes, I remember.
It was-
Do you remember-
for the bonus episodes
of the Progress Natives podcast,
Patreon.
Patreon.com
slash the Progress Natives
to find this
and so many other
bonus episodes.
50-
I think this is 57th
bonus episode.
Uh,
we did a three-hour-long
episode where we-
because we needed to clear
the voicemails out,
we went back through
all the old voicemails
and we listened to
all the ones
that had never been listened to.
Uh,
yeah,
and then I did go
and clear them out.
So the voicemail box
is empty again.
It should be able to receive
voicemails
as it used to be.
I think-
I-
remember how-
well,
I think that we eventually
went too far
and I think we eventually
ended up listening to some-
that we had already listened to.
I didn't remember
any of those
if we did.
Uh,
I think-
I'm thinking
some of the samurai ones
might have been ones
that actually we had
listened to
because
we were- it was definitely-
we definitely went past
the era of like
back when Nate used to
screen the voicemails.
Yeah,
that was like a-
I mean,
there was a bunch of pages
missing. It was like,
oh, this one was from
four years ago
and then suddenly
it was from one year ago.
Yeah,
well, that's because I-
that was because
I cleared those out
because those were ones
that I knew
we had definitely-
those were ones
that I knew had been-
had been-
not screened
but had been,
like,
listened to on the show.
So, yeah,
I think we went past that.
Um,
but we accomplished the goal
of listening to all the
un-listened-to
uh,
voicemails
from
four or five years ago,
Lamal.
Anyway,
the point is
do you recall
how when we were recording
that episode
I was having a crisis
about my hair?
Yeah.
Well,
um,
I shaved my head.
Uh,
I didn't-
Oh my god.
Yeah,
I didn't.
Um,
I was editing-
editing the video,
editing the-
the new video.
I just think
my hair looked so bad
and it-
and I-
it was stressing me out
and so I went to
my
bathroom
and I was like,
I'm gonna give myself a haircut.
I think it would look better
short-
shorter.
I was thinking,
like,
I'm gonna give myself
just like a more
shorter haircut.
I think it will
look better.
And I started trimming
my hair
and it looked
worse
instead of better.
And I was like,
no, this isn't working.
No, this isn't working.
No, fuck it.
Fuck it.
Shaving it all.
So,
so I'm bald now
and that's-
and that's life.
You know,
that's just-
you know,
the root of all suffering
is attachment,
Gib.
Hair.
What?
Like the root,
you know, the-
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
The root of all suffering
is the same as the
the hair root.
Right.
It's the root.
It's the where it grows
out of.
No, I'm gonna be-
Delete all that.
Sucked.
No, I'm gonna be
bald guy for a while.
I ordered a-
I ordered a,
like, head trimmer.
I ordered,
like, a specific,
like,
a head trimmer
for, like,
the head.
And-
The tip of the tip is
the beard trimmers are not
very efficient
for shaving one's head.
No.
So we got, like,
an adjustable one.
Well, yeah.
Uh, so,
um, this is-
this is me now.
This is me now.
But I-
I trimmed my beard too short.
I should've kept my beard longer.
Yeah, that's-
My beard is, like,
stubble now.
That's often how,
like, it feels,
like, balanced.
If you've got no hair
on your head,
you just have a big
dwarf beard
and it looks fine.
You got hair on your head?
That's good.
You got hair anywhere else.
That's way bad.
Get rid of them eyebrows.
Yeah.
So, uh,
I don't know.
So that's-
that's my-
that's my latest development.
Uh,
I will-
I'm just imagining,
like,
a style where you
shave one side of your head
and then the opposite side's
eyebrow.
So you have
one eyebrow.
And-
You would have-
Bold on one side,
but then hair on the other
without an eyebrow.
You think-
You think that could work?
I think you would look more
normal on the side
where you still have the eyebrow
and no hair
because that's a more
normal way
to look.
I-
It's not as-
It's not as bad as I thought.
My-
I think my head shape is-
is normal.
So,
whatever.
I just think it looks normal.
So,
it's fine.
Not as bad as I was afraid it would be.
It is one of those weird things, though, isn't it?
Like,
if you've never had
no hair,
you have no idea
really what your skull
head shape
looks like.
I did-
I did shave my head in college
one time
and I didn't really like it.
I decided-
I mean, I decided not to stick with it,
obviously.
Uh,
but like,
whatever.
Uh,
it was fine.
It was fine then and it's fine now.
I'm um-
Oh, shit.
I was gonna say,
uh,
what else was I gonna say?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no.
Uh,
duh.
I can't remember.
Okay, it's gone.
Cover for me.
Uh,
uh,
I don't know.
I swear,
I swear I had-
No!
I have like one more
note
to say about it.
Oh, well.
It'll-
It'll come back to me.
Yeah.
I don't really have much.
Something about my head shape?
Um,
Oh, I was gonna say,
I was gonna say
I talked a little bit
on that bonus episode
about,
uh,
like,
hair therapy methods
that I was dabbling with.
Like,
I'll continue to do those
and like,
just see what happens.
But for the moment,
I'm just like,
eh,
fuck it.
No,
no more hair.
It's-
it's stressing me out,
so fuck it.
And that's-
and that's where I'm at with it.
Well,
it's like,
it's like in the Bible,
you know,
if your right hand
causes you to sin,
you know,
cut it off and throw it away.
Chop it.
And if your hair-
and if your hair
causes you
to-
No, I have nothing I could use as a makeshift musical instrument.
I could go get a musical instrument, but I don't want to.
Run, escape, it's RuneScape.
No, I wasn't even trying to make it a bit.
I just said RuneScape Muse.
I think it should have a jingle.
I think it deserves a jingle.
Go to Google, download Trumpet Sound and then use that.
Trumpet Sound, OK.
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
I got all the iron ore I need.
I have in the bank 102,000 iron ore.
Hey, remind me what the connection is between iron ore and Runeite.
They're both ores that you can mine.
Iron obviously becomes iron and Runeite becomes Rune,
like a Rune bar that you can spit into like a Rune dagger.
Because I saw you posting that like you had overflowed your Runeite into like 100k
and it was like no longer showing you the number anymore.
Yeah, that happens with money as well.
If you get the stack large enough, I didn't realize it happened to things that weren't money.
But if you get a stack high enough, it no longer shows individual the number.
It shows 100 and something k.
So I knew I needed a little over 102k.
Actually a little under 102k.
So I got 102k and that was just that's plenty.
So now I have all the iron ore I need and I need to now mine 200,000 or so coal
so that I can turn, I can combine the iron and coal together.
One part iron, two parts coal to make steel.
Yeah, yeah, steel ingot, a steel bar in which I can smith into stuff for experience.
Okay, yes.
So you've got all the iron you were looking for.
So your plan is to smith it into stuff.
Is that the final goal?
What's the final goal?
The final goal is to get to level 99 Fletching having only prepared in free to play RuneScape.
Do you need iron for Fletching?
To make iron arrows.
But I need the steel specifically as like the the the fastest available method of raising
my smithing level because if I can't smith certain things, I can't do the Fletching
because I got to turn like I got to make arrowheads.
So you need the smithing skill that's required to make arrowheads so that you can Fletch
with them so that you can raise your Fletching skill.
Yeah, so the 102,000 iron or turns into 102,000 steel bars, which should be enough experience
to get me to the required smithing level.
And that is my current goal.
It's a lot of mining, but it's fun.
It's just just every so often when I feel like playing it for an hour or two and I listen
to a video.
You know, I tried to boot up Noida the other day just because I had not played it in a
long time and I was like, I'll just play a quick Noida and I opened it up and it turned
out that yeah, I had forgotten it is it is like auto saved on like a very like late game
save file.
Like I'm very near the end of the run and I have a really powerful wand and I was like,
oh, shit, and I remembered.
Oh, yeah, I have this run where every time I beat the run and when it like crashes and
doesn't remember that I wanted it, it auto loads back at that same thing.
I have like a bugged auto save file.
And I was like, you know what?
Good, you know what?
It's good that I can't play Noida.
This is this is better actually.
Yeah, you were you were a big Noida head.
I was pretty I was pretty noided.
Yeah, I was noided.
I was too noided.
I mean, I almost spent a thousand hours on it.
So that's cringe.
There are YouTubers.
There are YouTubers that have made like maybe a career is putting it strongly, but there
are YouTubers that have made like a lot of content.
They've even made it their whole brand almost just centered around playing Noida and like
they've played like a comparable amount to how much I played.
Uh, so just what I'm saying is like I played enough Noida that I could have made that I
could have been a Noida content creator if I had put my mind to it, but I didn't.
Is that why it's cringe that you didn't turn your enjoyment of a video game into something
that something someone else can consume?
That's not no, that's not exactly why it's cringe.
Although it if I were if I were monetizing it somehow, it might mitigate the cringe a
bit, but that's not just why it's just it's cringe because I in hindsight, I don't really
think there were a thousand hours of content there to be rung out of it.
I don't think I don't know if I got, you know, not all of those a thousand hours were
necessary for me to have, you know, been done with Noida, I think.
It's not a thousand nine nine hundred.
It's like nine hundred and something hours.
I could have put I could have put a lot less in and gotten the same amount out is what
I'm saying.
I mean, but I would you say it's because of like having to getting a little far in and
being like, ah, this sucks, reroll, go reroll.
No, no, it was just it was because it's because I just I don't know.
I think I was just kind of addicted to it for a while.
I was just like, I would just start it up and just do it and it would just be what I
was doing, even when like I didn't I don't know how to I don't know how to describe
it.
I just I just would do it compulsively.
I was playing Noida and I think it was bad.
Does that does that adequately explain my feelings?
That sometimes happens.
Yeah.
I definitely got into a habitual lugging on to World of Warcraft back in the day.
Yeah, it wasn't even necessarily that I enjoyed things.
It's just like I'm resuming my playtime from before.
It's not like I'm starting again.
I'm I'm I've got all these many quests, these many things to grind on.
So let's just grind on something.
I mean, an MMO is an MMO is kind of designed to get you to engage with it that
way, though, right?
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
Yeah.
I think it's a little I think it's a little weird to look back and be like,
why did I why did I put 900 hours into Noida?
What was the point?
I mean, you liked it, right?
I did like it.
Yeah, yeah, I just liked it.
Sometimes there's a boy in his game.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, some people like play like chess every day.
They just love chess.
It's not like chess is worse or better than a video game.
It's just an older thing.
I guess you're right.
Yeah, I guess there's any number of things people do just for fun.
And that's just you could see it as a waste of time if you wanted to.
Yeah, I would never say it's a waste of time.
It's definitely a it starts to become a problem where it eats into time that
you need to use.
Like if it's a sort of game that hooks you in and keeps you there for like 12
hours, well, you need to eat.
You need to go to the bathroom.
You need to like do other things.
You need to get fresh air.
Like a game that keeps you in locked in for extremely long periods of time isn't
healthy, but playing a game for a large amount of hours just like an aggregate.
It's not nothing wrong with that.
I mean, there were definitely times when I would just play Noida all day.
And that's probably that's probably not always good.
Yeah, you got a few of those.
But like it's life needs to continue going on.
Yeah.
And there's always things to do.
And I mean, a lot of the a lot of those were pandemic.
A lot of that was pandemic time.
Oh, well, don't worry about it.
I did.
Well, you know, it wasn't exclusively limited to then.
But like, I mean, I do think I racked up the bulk of my Noida hours in pandemic
times, lockdown times.
So that's my excuse.
Man, I remember what I did in lockdown.
I played Noida and I and I made gummies.
Yeah, I made the Lord of Ghosts early in the year.
Oh, and I worked on Phantom's Revenge, of course, we did.
Oh, you know, I did Lord of Ghosts from January to March.
And then we did Radcon 4 and then I came back and then we're in lockdown.
I think the Lord of Ghosts had already been finished.
And then later I did Clarissa and I don't even know what I did in the months
that I didn't do that.
Clarissa was like August.
What the hell happened?
Did I just play games?
I don't even know.
I often find myself being like, what did I do for this certain period?
Actually, yesterday was a micro.
I genuinely don't remember what I did yet.
I was going to sleep yesterday and I was like, what did I do all day?
What did I do?
Like I didn't.
I guess I fucked around with like paper samples for a little bit.
I messaged that guy from the other printing company a little bit.
I did reorganize my room a little bit.
And those all seem like such small things and yet they added up to, oh, my day's gone.
I didn't even get any editing done.
And sometimes I feel that way about like a whole month or a whole year.
But usually if I think about it, I can recall like, oh, no, no, I was...
No, I was making the game or no, I was making the comic or...
Yeah.
It's a bad feeling though.
It is a bad feeling.
It's a bad feeling that usually I can dissuade myself.
I can remember, no, no, I did this and that and the other thing.
There's usually something.
It's always looking back though.
Like in the moment, I know I'm enjoying myself.
I'm just relaxing, chilling out, doing things I want to do.
Maybe they're not like life affirming.
Like the most incredible thing ever happened to me today and I'll remember this memory forever.
Some days are just nice and comfortable and then I forget what happened during them
when I try to recall them because they were similar to other days.
I think it's only sad looking back and being like, oh, I don't have any memory.
Yeah.
That's why you gotta vlog it all.
You gotta contentize it.
Yeah, when you don't remember it, it's like it never happened.
And that's kind of when you're like, when you're not doing new stuff,
when you fall into your routine of doing the same thing every day,
then you're like, it gets harder to remember it because every day is sort of the same.
And so you can't really distinguish one day from another.
So it kind of just feels like one day that you repeat it over and over again.
Like the more, the more of a routine you have, the less distinct memory you have of the
like the whole long period that occurred over.
Yeah.
And that's, I don't know.
It's not, I guess it's not good.
I guess it's why you gotta do stuff.
I don't know.
I feel like there's an argument that it's not good.
But when I really think about it, it really is only like a future problem.
Like I'll be sitting around being like, what happened that year?
Man, I don't think anything happened.
And that's, that's what will happen is that if I did the same stuff for a while,
I won't remember it individually or just I'll have a vague sense of stuff maybe.
And it's like, is that, that's, that's a thing.
But is that necessarily a bad thing?
Should I feel bad about like having a routine or should I not?
I think I, yeah.
Well, I mean, I think you should.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess it just depends how it's, how it's working for you.
I mean, everyone likes having like significant memories.
I feel like I just want to avoid stressing out about not leading the most amazing life
because then I'd be stressed out all the time.
Well, I guess it would depend on if your routine is working for you.
If it's getting, if it's getting you the results you want.
Currently is.
I mean, it's, it's getting me more results than earlier, which was big depression mode.
Yeah.
I'm just, I'm just chugging away doing a little bit here and there,
playing a game in the, in the, in the time off.
And I'm like, I don't know what happened.
But eventually I'll have a comic and I can be like, oh, well, what do you know?
Yeah.
And that's a, and that's a.
Don't that beat all.
Is that from something?
Won't that beat all?
I thought it was just a.
Don't that beat all?
Isn't that just a phrase, like a saying?
Yeah, maybe.
I've heard.
Don't that beat all of the other things that it could possibly have been?
Whatever.
Don't that just beat all?
I feel it might just be a saying.
Just jack off.
Doesn't that just, yeah.
I don't know.
It reminds me of something, but I can't, I can't think of what it is at the moment.
One second.
I need, I need to crack another sparkling water.
If you've got a crack head, is it an ice cube?
Going for, going for the rare and elusive Cran raspberry this week.
By this week, I mean today.
Hmm.
What was I saying?
Man, my new room is so much less.
It's not even that it's good.
It's just so much less depressing than my old room.
It makes me so happy.
That's great.
It is great.
Boy, that shit was a nightmare.
That's all I have to say about that.
Yes.
It is good when Ben Saint is not depressed by his living situation.
True though.
Although I tried him.
Man, I tried a gummy thing that didn't work out and it was sad.
I, I tried.
Okay.
I try.
I think I mentioned, or maybe I mentioned at my Patreon podcast, which I made one of the other day.
Uh, that like I tried.
I switched to a powdered gelatin.
I tried switching back from sheet gelatin to powdered gelatin and it was pretty successful.
I was like, there was this result is pretty good.
So I tried making.
I thought it was going to be fancy and I was like, okay, why don't I mix up since, since all the ingredients are powdered now?
Why don't I just mix up all the ingredients in like a big batch?
And then I can just, I can keep instead of having to combine the ingredients when I want to make a new batch,
I can just have a tub full of the already combined ingredients and I can just scoop them and combine them with water and make it that way.
Just add water.
Yeah, literally like a just add water version.
Um, well, I tried it and I made, they came out very uneven.
Maybe, maybe I just didn't mix it enough because like I made four batches and like out of this, like, you know, this big sort of pre combined amount of powder that I made.
And one came out very kind of soft and, and kind of particle II.
Another came out decent.
Another one came out like gritty.
And then the last one came out like the texture was okay, but I didn't like the flavor.
That's not really the mix's fault.
So, but I use the sounds like a mix problem.
I think it was a mix problem.
I guess the, I could try, I should try it again and try mixing it more thoroughly.
But I guess the one concern I have is, oh, what if it like, what if there's no amount of mixing that I can do that will cause it like it'll still like naturally separate or something.
If like, if it naturally, if it will naturally separate once it's mixed, then there's no point premixing it because I'll just have to like mix it again before I use it every time.
And then what was the point?
Could you, could you do an experiment to figure out if that happens?
Yeah.
Small samples and mix them together and see if they separate over time.
I should, I should try making like a smaller amount.
Yeah.
Saving it in like a jar or something.
These are like powdery things you're adding together.
Yes.
That's the reason why I decided, I explained this in the Patreon.
I didn't go that much into it.
You know what?
I'll just, I'll say the same thing I said.
This is, that doesn't have to be exclusive content.
I had been using the sheet gelatin because it's fancier and it's more pure.
And that's true and whatever.
But I realized like, wait, if I use the powder, then like all the ingredients are powder and
I can just pre-combine them because it's like, yeah, powdered citric acid, powdered, not,
or yeah, sugar, regular granulated sugar, corn fiber, which is a powder and gelatin powder,
literally just mix it up.
And then in theory, if I got it to work, I would just, you know, be able to scoop that
and add, you know, some amount of water and color and, you know, some sort of fruit flavoring.
Are the particles different sizes?
Can you tell?
Yes.
What they, I mean, the citric acid and the sugar have a very similar like particle size
and consistency.
The corn fiber has a very, the corn fiber and the gelatin have a more similar different
like smaller, drier, powdery consistency to them.
Whereas the other two are sort of like little crystals.
So it's possible that it might separate over time.
I feel like that if you jostle it around that the bigger crystals will be at the top over time.
And so a scoop would need to go all the way down to the bottom to be a full, like a proper scoop.
So yeah, you probably have to mix it in every time anyway.
Because you can't rely on like it being uniform throughout whatever container it's in.
If you move the container at all.
It would be okay as if like I just have to like pick up the jar that I store it in and just give it a shake.
Like if that would do it, that would be fine.
You think that would make it worse?
When you get like different things and you shake it, the smaller things will find gaps in between the bigger things
and the bigger things would rise to the top.
So if you shake it, the bigger things would be at the top.
You'd need to mix it instead of shake it.
Like fold it in over itself and all that.
Yeah.
I mean, if I have to like mix it together with like a spatula or a spoon, then it's kind of like what was the point?
I will try it.
I will try it again and try to be more thorough about it and just convince myself like okay, no, I mix this as well as possible.
This is definitely not a time saving measure.
I bought a bunch of like glass jars to store different ingredients and I have a jar for sugar and a jar for acid and a jar for fiber.
And I was just like, why did I even bother?
I could just keep them in bags that they come in.
It's not that much more convenient.
Maybe I should just use these jars to store the premixed powdered combo.
I was thinking to myself, I think it would be nice.
It would be nice and convenient if I could just get, I could have one.
I could have one for the fiber formula and I could have another jar for the non-fiber like sugar formula.
Hey.
You have little labels on them.
Yeah.
What if, what if I just became a drug lord and started selling weed gummies?
What if I did that?
What if I sold them through the mail, which is completely illegal, but I would never get caught?
Well, they may listen to the podcast.
No, they aren't allowed.
If you're a cop, turn this podcast off right now.
Civilians only.
What if I left?
What is the legality situation on selling weed?
It's illegal substance now, but you probably have to get a permit or something, right?
Yeah, to be a vendor, you need a permit.
But I think a lot of people get around that with like a sort of like it's technically a gift.
Like you're technically making a donation to me and I'm giving you the weed as a gift, right?
I think it's a little bit like, eh, it's probably a little bit illegal,
but you can sort of technically get through a loophole.
Yeah, I think technically you need some sort of permit or license to sell marijuana products for a profit.
It's definitely illegal to put them in the mail, but you know, I was just thinking,
I've sent so many other things that are not, I've sent pins in the mail and I've sent them as letters.
I've sent them as envelopes for the cost of a stamp, even though they contain, you know, non-paper goods and it works.
And it would be so easy to do that with gummies.
It would be so easy and I wouldn't even, I wouldn't have to go to the post office, I wouldn't incur any risk,
I would have no return address, I could just drop it in a mailbox and 99% of the time it would arrive at its destination.
No delivery fee. You know, every weed vendor around here, they don't send them through the mail, they're a delivery service.
You contact them and you order what you want and then they come and they deliver it to you, because it's not legal to send stuff through the mail.
But there's like a, I was looking up, it's like $50 delivery fee, like it costs a lot.
I guess if you're buying in bulk, that's fine.
But it's like, you know how it's really expensive to buy to get food delivered with DoorDash?
Like the fees just pile up.
Yeah, yeah.
I think weed is like that, but like even worse.
So, I don't know.
Here's what I'm saying, is that I definitely would break the law for personal gain, I definitely would do that.
You could just have like a little, you could buy a bike and you could cycle around with like a hamper on the front and it'd be the weed gummy hamper.
Cringe.
You could sell.
Cringe, that's work, that's work.
No, but it would be really funny to see like the bicyclist weed seller.
You could have a little horn on the side.
You can honk the horns.
You can get your weed gummies.
You have a little straw hat.
Yeah, yeah.
Extra, extra.
Read all about it.
Read all about it, you're high.
POV, you're buying my product.
What if I just left, what if I just left flyers?
What if I just left like, what if I left, how would I advertise it?
How do I advertise my weed by mail service?
I want to do it.
With like an insane like picture of you with like your science experiments, sort of like gummy stuff.
No.
And it's like crazy bends, evil illegal weed stuff.
Yeah, that's, you know what, that's a real, that's, you're right.
I should put out pictures of, I should put out literal pictures of myself with my home address on them advertising my illegal services.
Yeah, you know what?
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
It would be so cool.
Everyone would want to buy a crazy bends, crazy illegal weed gummies.
I'd have so many, I'd have so many like, like undercover cops, like in my emails, like, hey, I was interested in your product, actually.
I don't know, I just, I just.
And then you tell them to come to this specific tile on your, in your floor.
They stand there and then you've trapped door and they fall down the chute.
I could do it.
I could do it discreetly.
I could just leave flyers around that were like, I don't know, maybe they just have a logo on them.
Nothing, nothing fancy, nothing too attention grabbing, but they're like, you know, hey, just saying, if you send $20 to this PayPal, you know.
Something good will happen.
You will, you will receive, you know, a certain milligrammage of, you know, edibles in your mailbox within the week, you know.
Maybe, maybe, I don't know.
To feel like that's a service.
Feel like that's a service people might be interested in.
And I just want money.
I don't like weed, but I like money.
You know, I never get high on my own supply is what I'm saying.
I liked that one time that I was high.
Okay.
And it was like, whoa.
Yeah.
That's my experience.
I'm not a, I'm not a super big, not a super big fan of it myself personally.
That's okay.
You know, different strokes for different folks.
I still prefer getting drunk because I feel I have not drank.
No, wait, that's not true.
I drank with my friends a few weeks ago and because then on the unique name of Sora's episode, I was hungover.
That was my first time drinking alcohol in like quite a while, like a month or two, which is fine.
You know, it's bad.
No, it's bad that you are not an alcoholic band.
That's cringe.
That's cringe that you didn't drink every day.
It's pretty, I gotta say, it's pretty cool of me that I only drink socially and I only ever smoke when I drink.
So yeah, there was the further while there, the only time I would drink by myself was during the height of the pandemic
is when I would go and I would get two bottles of champagne from the local liquor store and I would just drink them in my room.
Oh, no.
I was pretty, I mean, those are dark times.
Those are dark times.
The word felt the need to like drink heavily.
I didn't do it all the time, but I did it.
I did it a few times.
Like I've only drunk socially.
There's been a few times where I'm like, man, I think I need a beer to relax.
But one beer wasn't enough and I couldn't be bothered to get another one.
So I just drank it and it was like, well, whatever.
Well, it doesn't feel the same when there's not like a party atmosphere or some sort of event happening.
Yeah.
It's when you're just by yourself, it's like, it's sort of like, when do I stop?
At some point you like you're you get a little buzzed, you get a little drunk and then you're like, I guess on the one hand, it makes me like more like I want to go to sleep.
So it's like, whereas if I'm sober, which is most of the time, I have a tendency to tell myself like, no, I don't want to go to sleep yet.
Like, no, I want to do something else before versus if I'm drunk, I'm like, I'm a little tired.
Oh, I'll go lie down and go to sleep.
So it's kind of good.
I had a recipe for disaster, though, if you go to sleep while drunk before you drink water.
Yeah, it can be.
Because that's where you get a whole hungover.
That's that's true.
So, you know, it's a mixed, it's a mixed blessing.
Alcohol truly is a mixed blessing.
It's a double-edged broken bottle.
Let me see here.
When they say double-edged sword, what do they really mean?
Because a sword has an edge and some swords only have one side of it.
That's sharp.
Other swords like a broad sword has both sides.
Yeah.
Does a double-edged sword mean that the handle is also a blade because that doesn't even exist.
They don't have those.
Yeah, the thing about the, yeah, you know, the thing about the saying, oh, it's a double-edged sword is that like lots of real swords are double-edged.
And they're they're perfectly fine.
I think I think the implication must be that you are holding a handle that is also cutting you like a blade, which is maybe the saying is like.
Like it's referencing a sword that is a stupid idea that wouldn't exist.
But that doesn't make sense.
No, double-edged swords.
I mean, most European broad swords were all double-edged.
You didn't didn't cut yourself.
You just swing it.
You just swing it away from you instead of towards you and it's fine.
That's the trick.
That's the trick that no one, no, they don't teach you in solid school.
You got to swing it at the other guy.
Like a double-edged sword, meaning like you swing it forwards, killing the enemy, and then you swing it backwards, stab yourself.
Well, if it wasn't a double-edged sword, you couldn't stab yourself.
Although you could because every sort has a point.
It's a double-edged sword.
Boy, I wish this conversation had a point.
Even one, not let alone two.
A quadruple-edged board.
In Dungeon Crawlstone's soup, there's triple swords, which is just like three sword blades next to each other on one hill.
So if you stabbed, it would make a little like a-
It would be three times.
Three times.
The thing about that that's funny about that is that it literally is barely-
It would be so much less effective than just one sword.
Yeah, because if you managed to slice, you couldn't go very far because the other two blades would stop it from entering the skin.
Yes, it would distribute the pressure that makes the cut.
It would cut it in three and you would not cut as deep.
It's like so fucking stupid.
I know why they do maces like that just to make it a little easier to hold but still have a lot of weight to it and smaller surface area of contact.
Yeah, yeah.
An iron ball on a stick would be harder to swing.
It would hit more but it's so soft and round so that they make them like many little tiny flanges of a mace.
Yes, yes, flanges.
To make a triple sword like that, it's going to blunt its own impact.
You might as well use a blunt weapon at that point.
If you really want to distribute the impact.
I love my mace.
I love Leopold, my flanged mace that I got from King Richard's Fair.
I forgot I had a name.
It does have a name.
Does it make any appearances in the dogen?
I don't know if it does.
I don't recall.
My character reference had the mace so a bit stupid if it never got drawn into any of those pages but it might not have because it was never relevant to any of the scripts.
It definitely does appear in the OVA at least once.
I made sure to have the mace in the OVA whenever that gets done so it will make an appearance I'm sure.
Speaking of the dogen, you saw there's only like six pages left I think before it's done.
It's like getting pretty close to me.
How many are completed?
I forgot the total number.
I think the total is like 24 or something.
So it's mostly done.
I don't want to release it.
I want to release it alongside the OVA so I hope Nate has reassured us again recently that he will start working on it very soon.
Yes, we've got more of a system to check in on progress.
We all agree that we need to be checking up on the progress on this, which is good.
I really hope he fucking does it.
I'm sure he will eventually but I hope that eventually is now is what I'm saying.
Yes.
Speaking of weapons, I've had a gun and I shot.
No, did you kill the queen?
No.
No, they found out.
Ellie is our cut it out.
Cut out which prominent British political figure who recently died, Gib is directly responsible for the murder of.
It's Prince Philip.
Okay.
We can't let him know.
I was thinking of like Dungeons and Dragons.
I'm just sort of feeling it right now and I'm like, how do I, I kind of want to DM a game.
I kind of want to be the person who comes up with a thing and see what those little rascals, those player characters, what they get up to.
That's interesting.
Have you played before?
I played, I've only ever played like statless like role play mini game adventure things with a few people, a few groups of people.
Honestly based, honestly better than D&D in my opinion.
Yeah.
And it was fun.
I had this one with a group that had a Munchie in it and I had this character.
Yeah.
Which was like, it was a crippled boy who had unearthed an ancient technology.
It was the Atlas, the Boston Dynamics Robot.
And he, and in using the Boston Dynamics Robot Atlas.
Like the dog?
No, no, the walking one, the humanoid.
Okay, yeah.
Atlas is the one who can do backflips and stuff.
Yeah.
Crippled boy, this crippled urchin farmer boy and his legs.
Was this like a post-apocalypse?
Yeah, some sort of a thing.
It sounds very fallout.
It's not a post-apocalypse.
It was some sort of like Norse thing, but I just said this and everyone thought it was a cool idea.
Okay.
And so I was this little boy and he needed to go on an adventure to find batteries.
You need to find batteries for the Boston Dynamics Robot because in their primitive culture, they didn't have batteries anymore.
They don't know what that is.
And the Boston Dynamics Robot is like, I need fuel.
I need energy.
So he only has a limited amount of power before he powers down and it's an adventure.
And it's all the other characters there.
And I thought that was fun, but it sort of peated out because it was difficult to get everyone together.
That's how it always goes.
That's how it always goes with D&D, almost always.
Yeah.
I'm thinking if I make the world.
Honestly, yeah.
That's the hard part, right?
Finding someone who's willing to DM is the hardest part.
So if you're willing to DM, that is the biggest hurdle removed.
Yeah.
True.
I think it would be nicer and more smooth, less stressful for me if I just made a world and people could come and have fun in it.
Which is kind of what I already do with world building for my comics.
So that game that you played, was that the statless one?
That was a statless one.
Okay, so you haven't played with a character sheet and rolling dice and stuff.
I think we rolled dice for do you do it or do you not do it successfully?
There was no additions and subtractions for character class things.
It was just sort of like, I'm going to do this crazy thing.
Alright, roll a dice if it's even you win.
It was very simple, but yeah.
So there was failure.
I haven't played D&D in a long time.
I think last time I played D&D would have been that time I had that Aztec campaign,
which would have been in 2018 or something.
Do you have campaign ideas?
Do you have a concept for a campaign you would DM now?
Okay.
I have no ideas.
It's just sort of like a feeling.
It would be kind of fun, wouldn't it, to be watching everybody.
Like, oh, here's the gnome king and he's got a question for you.
Somebody says, I beat him to death with a mace and it's like, oh, he's quicker than you thought.
Roll them dice.
Just like rattle them bones.
Rattle his bones.
Have you seen that picture?
This is a really funny joke on Twitter where like, you know how you can spoiler an image on Twitter
and you have to click it to unspoiler it to see.
There's a really, sometimes I'll see one that's like, oh, like this image contains sensitive content
and you click unspoiler and it's a picture of a bunch of like skeleton gangsters with Tommy guns
and it says like, they unspoiled it.
Rattle them boys.
I love it every time.
I like that.
Yeah, I've seen that.
I guess one thing I would say is it might, it would be a challenge if you wanted to run like a rules D&D system with character sheets.
Like the DM, the DM should really know the rules, you know?
Yeah.
So if you're, so that's, that's a challenge.
There's like books I need to read and stuff if I want to do like an official thing.
But then I would require like the players to also read the books, which is another thing.
It's like, it's really annoying.
It's really annoying when there's like one player that doesn't know the rules and they're all like, how do I, how do I attack again?
Like every time it's their turn, it's like, I mean, perhaps you know, but I hate D&D because literally nobody in the world understands how to play it right.
Everyone is fucking stupid.
Everyone, everyone plays it wrong.
Every, there's always, there's always, just give me, just let me rant for one second.
There's always one guy who like every time it's their turn, they're like, how do I attack?
Wait, what's, what does my armor class mean?
Like, oh, which saving throw do I use for that?
What do I add to whatever check?
And it's like, bro, you got your attack bonus.
And you roll a d20 and you add your attack bonus.
We've done this a hundred fucking times and you still don't know.
There's always one.
Usually there's more than one.
Huh?
It seems complicated though.
It can be complicated, but like 90% of the time it's, it's not like 90% of the time it's, it's, it's like just like the.
When it, when it's simple stuff, simple stuff like attacking or simple stuff like making a check to, to accomplish something.
Okay.
I mean, there's that.
And then there's my other thing of like, everybody always plays wrong because everyone always rolls.
Everyone's always like, hmm, okay, dungeon master.
Can I make a, can I make a, an acrobatics check to, to, you know, to do whatever?
Oh yeah.
The player tries to tell the DM what skill they want to use to do something.
When it should really be the DM being like, okay, it should really be the player saying, I want to do this.
And then the DM saying, okay, to do that.
Here's what you need to do.
And I mean, sometimes it might be okay for a player to be like, oh, uh, hmm, is it okay if I use my athletic skill instead of my acrobatics skill?
Like I'm not saying that should never come up, but like in, in general.
I feel like it would be easier.
Most people just play wrong.
Most people just play wrong in a way that like makes the game worse and I'm sick of it.
I feel like it might be easier if I just invent my own Dungeons and Dragons rule set.
Oh God.
You think that's, you, you might think that would be easy, wouldn't you?
You would think that would be.
Yeah.
It'd be have like your stats like, oh, flumptuousness and that affects, you know, your, your, your bolus picking skill.
You, you are opening up a rabbit hole.
You are opening up a rabbit hole there.
No, no, I know it can get extremely in depth because I knew a guy in uni who had an, a system for magic and they would talk about how it worked, how it was like based in physics and, and, and all of these things.
And I'm like, huh, these conversations would go on for extremely long time.
I had never really understood what on earth it was, but he was really into this, this, this system he'd invented.
I have a.
It's like, I wish you well.
You know, that's the sort of.
Yeah.
I have a friend.
I couldn't get my head around it, but.
One of the guys.
It seemed fun.
Like I kind of wanted to do it myself, but I felt like it was a little beyond me.
One of the guys I was, I hung out with the other week is a guy who, yeah, he, he, he has come up with many different like pen and paper systems.
I guess it's sort of a hobby of his.
I think he actually told me that he had like recently published one.
He had like, he had put one out and like, I think he had maybe crowdfunded it and it had made like a few thousand dollars, which was like really impressive.
Like that's like most of those projects don't get anything.
Right.
Like there's so many, there's so many that receive no traction at all.
I should have asked him for details because I don't remember like what the game was called or, or what the campaign was, but he mentioned that.
But anyway, the point is that like, yeah, he spends like years, he spent like years doing, doing all these sorts of things.
And there is a very, it's really easy for a system to get way too complicated.
And it's, and it's on the other side, it's like, it's easy for a system to be way too simple.
And then you find it's yourself, you're like, well, how does this rule system handle such and such?
Oh, well, it doesn't, or I can't, or whatever.
Or I never considered that eventuality.
There was that game, that game RISIS that I found or RISIS or R-I-S-U-S.
I always, that's like the one stat RPG.
RISIS pieces?
Your stat, yeah, your stat is your class.
And, but your class is just like a descriptor.
And it's something like a runaway tomboy princess or something, right?
Like you're like a level one runaway tomboy princess and like a level two, I don't know.
What's a...
Crocheter or something, right?
Like, so you have these descriptors of things and anytime you want to do something,
you're not rolling like a particular stat.
You don't have like a value in athletics or acrobatics or search or intimidate or whatever.
You just have like, okay, well how good would a runaway tomboy princess theoretically be at this one activity?
Is that something that one of them would do?
And if it is, then you can use that class, that quote unquote class as like your modifier to accomplish the check.
And I always thought that was really cool and I never played RISIS with anyone.
I kind of meant to.
I kind of wanted to do a game like that at like a Radcon, but it just didn't happen.
Yeah, Radcons were always so weirdly hectic.
Four was like really hectic, right?
Four was like, honestly, I probably could have organized one at three if I had really like put my mind to it.
But then four was like every day we were doing stuff, so didn't have time.
Yeah, the idea of an RPG system, I would want it to be like very simple if I were to make a rule set.
Like something like, oh, Problem Sleuth, it has Vim and...
Yeah.
Oh, just a simple game system, you know, like the one in Problem Sleuth.
Yeah, well, you know.
Yeah.
I mean, honestly, if you're interested, you should download yourself a PDF copy of like the fifth edition player's handbook
and just like read through it and see like what's normal.
Get some ideas.
Yeah, that, honestly, fifth edition is good.
Fifth edition is like way simpler than fourth.
Fourth edition was a nightmare.
Third edition was also a nightmare, but in its own way.
Fifth edition, they really kind of made it a lot more approachable and I think it's good.
And you should read it just to get an idea of like what the baseline, right?
Because that's kind of like the entry point for most people getting into tabletop stuff is D&D.
And we're still on fifth edition, right?
They haven't made a new one.
I have no idea.
I've heard terms like fifth edition, first edition, and I guess like, oh, it's a rulebook and they update it, whoever they are.
Yeah.
Well, I never...
No, no, I did play second edition once.
The first time I ever played D&D was like right at the end of second edition.
The second edition was coming out.
Second edition had Thacko, which was a basically...
They had a very counterintuitive system where to hit an enemy with an attack, you would roll with this number called the Thacko.
But Thacko was like, you wanted your Thacko to be low.
You wanted your Thacko to be low and the enemy's armor class to be also low, I think?
What does Thacko mean?
Is it an acronym?
Yes, it stood for two hit armor class zero.
And so if your enemy's armor class was zero and your Thacko was a three, you would roll a 20-sided die and you would have to roll a three or under.
No, a three or over to hit armor class zero.
And so if their armor class was higher, you would have to roll higher to hit.
And that's why it was...
Yeah, like that.
Then third edition, they changed it and now it's like you have an attack bonus and they have an armor class.
And now you just roll a d20 and add your attack bonus and you compare the number to their armor class and not to be determined if they hit.
But third edition had a hugely expanded roster of skills.
I think the skill system was the thing that they sort of exploded in third edition.
And they kept adding on more and more rules erratic to it.
They kept adding an infinite number of prestige classes that you needed to meet certain requirements in order to multi-class into.
And basically anyone could make their own fucking prestige class and the expanded rule set became incomprehensibly complicated.
Fourth edition, they tried to make it simpler by like...
Instead of having all these sort of uncategorized things that different character classes could do,
every character class would have a set of things that were very comparable to each other.
A wizard had a basic attack they could do and they had a once per battle effect they could do and they had a once per day effect they could do.
And a fighter would similarly have all those things.
And it felt very...
It was very World of Warcraft, it was very MMO.
And it kind of didn't feel like D&D.
And then fifth edition is basically it's more like third edition, but I think they pared it down and they made it more approachable.
And they think they were like...
I don't know, I've only played a little bit of fifth edition.
I think there are prestige classes, but there's like the rules around them are a little bit more like basic and like you can't just fucking do any stupid thing you want with them.
I don't know, I'm not an expert.
So it's the player's handbook I would need to read.
The player's handbook is the basic thing that is like how do you play the game?
If you wanted to DM, you would also want to get the Dungeon Masters guide.
And then the third core rulebook is the monster manual, which is like...
You don't really need that if you're a player, but if you're a DM and you want to make encounters,
you would generally want to have the monster manual as like the thing to populate combat encounters with.
I see.
I would probably want to make my own things.
It would be like a Gip Core version of Dungeons & Dragons, but I will maybe read.
You can do that.
The monster manual has rules for creatures that are like appropriate challenge levels to like the character class levels with the players you're playing with, you know?
You could...
The monster manual exists to give you like a...
Okay, I have a party of sixth level adventurers.
All right, what is an appropriate thing to have them face off against?
You could re-skin a monster in the monster manual if you wanted to.
You wouldn't have to describe it the way it's described in the book.
I'm trying to imagine, damn, I think it would be basically impossible to like design...
The monster manual, it explains like how challenge ratings are calculated and like how a monster is constructed in order to be an appropriate challenge for a party.
So, I don't know.
Trying to make like combat encounters without something like that would be...
You would be shooting completely blind.
Sure.
I just feel like the general theme of Dungeons & Dragons with fantasy like elves and magician people and gold and caverns.
It's like a very, we know what that is thing, but the player dungeon master like dynamic can be applied to different types of things.
I mean, I know that that has already happened, but like it doesn't need to be a combat heavy adventure.
Oh, I mean, yeah.
And the adventures do not have combat.
It could just be like wild and wacky and you meet weirdos, evil gremlins.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Combat is like the cornerstone of many video games and games in general.
D&D doesn't have to be.
The D&D ruleset, yeah, the D&D ruleset is mostly designed to facilitate combat.
Like it's sort of built under the assumption that that's like sort of the main gameplay loop.
But I mean, it does have like skill systems and things that are...
It can accommodate non-combat scenarios.
Is it necessarily the best and most robust system for non-combat scenarios?
Maybe not, but I mean the...
I just like the dynamic, like I build a world and like, hey, come play in my world.
It's kind of like building a map in a video game.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Making a Minecraft challenge run map or a puzzle map and then watching people play it.
I guess just making a game of watching people play it in general is the sort of feeling.
How would you feel if you made a campaign or you made an adventure and then your players just started to play it
and then they just like ignored the main objective.
They just started fucking around.
If I was unprepared, then I would feel a little silly, a little stupid,
because like they're doing these things and I'm like, I have to make stuff up.
Classic scenario, the DM has like an adventure bit made where they're like,
okay, in this adventure, the adventurers will have to rescue the barmaid's daughter from a local kobold den that has kidnapped her.
And then they say, we don't care, let's join the kobolds or whatever.
You start it and it's like, you start in the tavern, are there any wenches in the tavern?
I'm going to go hit on the wenches.
I'm going to get into a drinking contest with this orc over here.
Oh, I'm going to just light the place on fire because I'm chaotic evil black guard and I just do evil things just to fuck things up.
Well, yeah, I mean, I'm sure when you do that, you don't tell the players, here's the adventure.
You say like you enter a tavern and there's these things described and so you put things in there that they might be interested in.
Maybe if you want to force it, like somebody smashes down the door and starts shooting and then there's like a combat encounter that forces them into it.
It's the same way you would construct the inciting incident for a character in a fiction of any kind.
It's like if you just let the character exist and nothing interrupts their normal life, then they're not going to have an inciting incident.
You have to introduce it.
You know what?
So you would introduce it the same way.
That scenario I just described, the DM has failed by counting on like, oh, yeah, I just got a hope that my players will start a conversation with him and ask him like, hey, are there any adventures to go on?
And he'll say, yeah, my daughter's got kidnapped, actually.
It's such a weird thing that that's in so many...
I mean, I know it's ingrained in like, we know that games do that and that's like a thing.
It's a trope.
But like, why would you go to the barkeeper and ask if there's some adventure to happen?
Yeah.
I need a quest.
Who talks like that?
Who would need a quest?
What sort of a weirdo do you need to be to like actually want to go questing?
I mean, maybe the party paladin.
Unless you know you're playing a video game.
Yeah.
And in a video game, like it's like, okay, there's only one thing I can do.
Like the ultimate situation is that you build a world and then the players are actors and they act how they would act or whatever the player would act.
And it doesn't necessarily mean matter that they're...
I don't know.
I mean, it would require like good faith responses on the part of all the players.
Even in a video game.
That would be the ideal.
Even in a video game, if you give the player too much freedom, they'll ignore your quest.
Like that's why like instead of like doing the campaign and like Grand Theft Auto, you know, people would just grab a rocket launch.
I close.
Yeah.
I close car pile ups.
That's the game.
That can be the game.
All right.
All I'm saying, all I'm saying is that the world DMing a campaign is a cruel mistress.
It's a deep rabbit hole that will chew you up and spit you out and ruin your life.
Well, I can start small.
But you got to do it.
Nevertheless, you must do it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Interesting.
But I mean, hey, I'm here to advise if you want, if you want, I don't know, input on anything to do with that.
Because I've done, I've done a lot of it before.
I'll read those books and I'll get back to you.
Definitely.
Definitely read those books in particular.
The player's handbook just just to just to get an idea of like what the game is and what the like baseline concept of like a tabletop role playing RPG looks like.
They should have called it bloodins and daggers.
That's way cooler.
That's like a that's like the no role playing like combat only like tabletop mini.
Yeah, version of it.
Yeah.
You're in the blood pits.
You got to fight your way out.
Bloodins and daggers.
Shit.
What's up?
Goldrums and black guards.
There's too many.
There's too many you could make.
Black guard.
I think I said black guard before, but I meant black guard.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Is it spelled black guard?
Yes.
It's in the opposite of a paladin is a black guard and I grew up thinking it was said black guard because it's spelled black guard.
But no, it's actually pronounced blaggard, but you would you would never know that from reading it.
Never.
Yeah, I've never I guess I'd never read it before.
I've only heard it.
Have you heard it as black guard or blaggard?
Blaggard.
I didn't know it was like a guard.
Yes.
It's spelled B-L-A-C-K-G-U-A-R-D.
It's like it's like I've heard it in like scenarios like where it's like used as an insult.
Oh, black guard, like waste rule.
I mean, I ruffian.
I've never seen it used that way.
The only context I've ever read it in is in the context of reading up on the prestige class called black guard in or blaggard in the dungeon master's guide in third edition.
So like, why would I know how it's pronounced?
A scoundrel.
A man who uses foul language in front of a woman, scoundrel, unprincipled, contemptible.
I guess it makes sense that it would be like the opposite of a paladin.
It's funny.
Yeah, it means like villain or ruffian or something.
In D&D, it's more like it's like a dark knight.
It sort of has a more like, yeah.
It has a more sort of noble connotation in D&D.
Yeah, it's like a sort of a high status thing.
But the word is like the word where it comes from.
It's like it's like a lowly sort of despicable thing.
Whereas, you know, dark knight is more like, oh, he's, oh, he's, oh, he's dark.
He might be dark, but he's still a knight though.
Somebody knighted him.
Someone, some king, some, some dark king somewhere.
Some shit king.
Conferred some honor upon him.
Do you want to jump to voicemails?
Yes.
Let's, okay.
Well, let's, you want to look at these ones that Oblivionfall generously agreed to.
So let's start with an ultimatum from Joshua Moon.
I assume it goes on to say owner of Kiwi Farms.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
I bet you my ass is fatter and more people are going to look at me if I show my ass in public than you.
Thoughts.
I would say.
Do you agree?
I got it.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
I don't, I don't know what his ass is like.
I've never seen it.
No.
So.
Never seen him.
I don't even know.
I'm flying blind here.
But I'm going to say no way.
I got the fatter ass.
Everyone's going to look at me and nobody's going to look at you.
So don't even bother showing your ass.
Idiot.
All right.
Next one is called fiveheadbensaint.mull.mp3.
There's also an imager above it.
Yeah.
Let's look at the.
That's from Bronycon.
The last Bronycon, I believe.
I mean.
Yeah.
You didn't have, yeah.
You had the.
That's when I had the pink hair.
The pink hair.
I mean.
That's all right.
That's fine.
The fucking, that, that convention center is a liminal space for sure.
Oh, that room, that big room.
That huge endless carpet.
That, that, that, that big room is a liminal space for sure.
Yeah.
That place is in the back rooms.
That's what it's called, right?
The like.
Yeah.
The back rooms.
Um, when I say that, I think of the backyard from Guilty Gear.
I wonder if, damn, I wonder if my video will be out by the time this episode releases.
It's not impossible, but I don't want to guarantee it either.
Never make any promises ever.
True.
Okay.
Uh, so.
Uh, the voicemail.
Yeah.
F-bensaint fivehead.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
It's so beautiful.
Damn.
Look at my fucking show here.
Fuck.
Well, now I'm, well now I'm, now I'm all head.
I shaved and now I'm all head.
So get, get owned.
Your forehead, your back head.
Side head.
Side head, top head, bottom head.
What's bottom head?
Is it like the, the right of the back at the, like, what do you, what do you call it, the cranium?
The bat, the bottom head is secret hidden head that you only get.
Oh, it's, it's inside the skull.
Yeah.
It's precious.
Rare and precious.
Next one is called.
Oh, Mentos trio who three, two, one, go.
Oh, man.
It's been so many years.
Please.
Who the fuck was the Mentos trio?
Please repeat it.
Do it.
I've explained this before.
I've explained the Mentos trio before, haven't I?
I don't remember.
Well, okay.
I've never, I don't think I've ever heard Mentos trio before.
I've definitely mentioned it.
Okay.
Well, I don't remember.
Yeah.
Why wouldn't I, why would I mention it and then not explain it?
Did I say I was going to make it like a patreon thing?
I don't remember.
No.
Okay.
Um, it was, well, when I was in like middle school, when I was, you know, a young teen,
uh, 12 or 13 or so, I would, there was this summer program that my parents would send
me to, it was called college academy.
And this is where I learned to play D&D because one of, it was sort of like, it was sort of
like a mock college thing for like younger kids where you would, you would sign up for
quote unquote classes.
I mean, they were classes, but some of them were.
You know, they were fun.
They were things like rocketry where like you would make a little model rocket.
There was one, um, there was one where you would just play D&D.
And that's, and that was where I played second edition D&D the first time.
Uh, so there was, uh, anyway, on the bus ride to college academy, there were these slightly
older kids.
I've definitely explained this, but I'll explain it again.
There were these kids that were like slightly older than me and they had this thing that
they would do and they would buy Mentos before every, uh, bus ride and then they would wait
until the bus came to a stop and then they would, they had this piece of paper that they
would write Mentos the Freshmaker on and they would like slam it against the window in the
back of the bus and they would hold their Mentos out and they would give thumbs up like,
like someone freeze framing in a Mentos commercial and they would just pose with the sign that
says Mentos the Freshmaker.
They'd be like thumbs up like, yeah, holding their Mentos.
And they would just see what the, what the person in the car behind the bus would do
in response to this.
Oh, I see.
I thought they were doing it to the rest of the bus.
No, no, to the, to the, to the person in the car behind us.
And that was it.
It was just these three kids that would do this thing on the bus to college academy.
And, uh, I, I joined, I joined them one year because like one of them graduated and so
they needed a new member and I, there, there must always be a Mentos trio.
There must always be a Mentos trio.
Like when one, yeah, basically one graduates and someone else has to step up and take their
place.
And it got to be me for a little bit there.
I wonder if I took it very seriously.
Hmm.
You wonder if I said, I wonder, uh, yeah, I wonder if it survives.
Like if, if, if somebody replaced you.
I doubt it because it was, I think, I think it was the brainchild of like one particular
guy who had a very particular, uh, sense of humor.
And I think that probably with him gone, maybe I carried on the legacy for a little bit, but
I sincerely doubt that it discontinued.
I don't know if college academy even exists anymore.
Let me find out.
I thought you were going to Google like Mentos trio.
They got a website now.
They're a multi-billion dollar franchise.
Um, oh my God, it's been going for 43 years.
Um, well, the website still exists.
So yeah.
Yeah, there's, there's, there's a, there's a version for younger kids called college gate
and there's a version for slightly older kids called college academy.
I didn't do college gate.
I just started the college academy.
Man, those are good times.
Those are some of my like, the funnest memories from being a kid or from college academy.
That shit ruled.
It was only for like three weeks out of the summer.
I wanted it to go all summer.
Ugh, good times.
Good times, uh, back in the day.
Okay.
Anyway, that's, that's your explanation, voicemailer.
Uh, next one is called who, when, why three, two, one, go.
What am I fighting for?
The real question is where?
Where am I fighting for?
Well, he was fighting for earth because it was, well, I guess he was fighting against
uh, Repliforce, which was on a, had retreated to like a space station, I guess.
So, yeah.
No, it doesn't really work.
Sorry.
You know, he's a, he's a, he's a global fellow.
He's a globalist.
He's a, he's not fighting for any particular place.
He's fighting for all of humanity.
All of humanity was put in risk by the, by the, by the coup that Repliforce was trying
to pull off.
It wasn't about like the nations or locations.
Yeah.
The answer to the question of where is everywhere, anywhere, anytime.
I'll fight.
I'll fight anyone.
That's, that's right.
That's right.
Um, next one is called Requiem for a Meme.
Three, two, one, go.
Actually didn't realize there was a 90 second rule before I decided to send this little
voicemail.
Otherwise, this would have been a much, much, much, much, much, much, much, much, much,
much, much, much, much longer and in detailed story about my ex-girlfriend.
Okay.
But I'll just get to the important part, which is my ex-girlfriend is fucking.
I don't know why.
You know, Jesus.
This is creepy.
It's, it's quite a bit of drama.
So tell me procrastinators because, you know, you guys seem to be geniuses when it comes
to women clear on a year.
Undisputed kings of dealing with femininity.
So I didn't catch that.
I don't know.
I didn't catch the question.
I don't know what to say, but thanks, thanks for the voicemail anyway.
Was that somebody else's voicemail that this guy just chopped and, chopped and screwed?
No, it seems like it was part, like part of the, the bit was that it was like, oh, it's
a generic thing, but it's fucked up audibly.
Pretty fucked up.
All right.
The next one.
Okay.
We got from Prince isolation.
We've got another slime times weekend update parts one and two.
So let's do part one, three, two, one, go.
Are we back?
We're back baby weeks.
Okay.
We're back with the slime times weekend update.
A lot has happened.
Where shall we begin?
All right.
Rowdy elections were concluded and the new rowdy ring leaders are mischief night and anthropomorphic
bunny.
Demodunk, a janitor made of crystal and yours truly, a demon prince with dashing looks and
no grain to speak of.
He's made of crystal.
I shall thus be serving a second term through no political maneuvering or dig riding whatsoever.
Good.
In other news, love to hear it.
Shoko held a slime or tournament for the whole community of which rowdy olive was the final
winner.
And the second one is happening within an hour of this recording.
The reward one receives a snazzy looking metal.
Some updates to the city include a natural disasters, including media showers, firestorms
and tornadoes and a new update, which has some missile launches as weapons and free
apples at the candy store.
They kill you because Demodunk is a green witch apparently.
All right.
See you in part two.
Well, I don't know how I feel about the only newspaper about the talks about the slime
in Nalakakam being elected.
It sort of feels like you could abuse that position.
Well, I mean, Prince was doing slime times before the elections.
I mean, no, I think there is a rowdy bias in the reporting.
There's potential here for major scandals to be covered up.
The way that you counter that is with the free market.
There's a demand for the other side of the aisle.
There's a demand for killer reporting, a killer slant on the news to oppose this mainstream
media.
Cuck shit.
That's cool that they're having slime oil tournaments.
Remember when I made slime oil?
Remember when I crafted them out of numbers and my brain?
I do.
Yeah, me too.
They're still going.
How cool is that?
Anyway, part two, three, two, one, go.
Then finally, the terrible news I must bring you all today.
Several weeks ago by now, janitor and rowdy ringleader Demodunk used a new fun command,
beat killer Ebola spread in gang violence.
With it, he was able to turn the normal commands into fun commands, which Ebola was unable
to use for lack of understanding of fun.
Demodunk, having had prior knowledge of fun, thus gained an unfair advantage in the eyes
of many and was ultimately arrested of his own volition.
Still, this arrest could not quell the bloodlust of the disgruntled masses.
Fun was ultimately removed from the game.
That's right, dear listeners.
Fun is officially known as a part of endless war.
Strangely, no one has seemingly noticed any significant difference.
No fun allowed.
Well, that's it for this week.
And remember, the slime time is the best time.
But most certainly not a fun time.
I can't believe they banned fun from endless war.
And it's so cringe.
It's the image.
No.
Yeah, no.
Are those guys from like Battlestar Galactica?
No, I think this is from the Sonic comic comic book.
Oh, yeah.
They're like, we're evil and Dr. Eggman robots.
No fun allowed.
Oh, what the fuck?
I'm sorry.
Did I mention that I the killer kingpin, the cop killer himself died in endless war
because I tried to I tried to have fun without having a fun pizza.
You were tricked into it as far as I remember.
I was I was duped.
I think it was Demedunk that duped me.
Fucking dead.
The economies and shambles.
Well, you know what?
Honestly, after that, I got to say I'm glad fun was banned.
I think it was it's probably best for the game to not have not allow it honestly.
So good.
Good job, everyone.
The system works.
Base.
Okay, those are the those are all the messages that were sent to oblivion's temporary side voicemail.
Again, the regular voicemail box is in theory operational again.
So let me just see what we got.
Let's see what we got over there.
Speak pipe.
Okay.
Well, there's yeah, I think the first one is Ben's weekly reminder play delta room chapter two.
Then Ben's weekly reminder catch up on one piece.
Okay.
Then no voicemail, no watch.
The first real one is new voicemail contest.
So three, two, one, go.
Hey, I've got a fun new event.
It's the PCP typing competition.
He's winning.
Oh, my God, he's typed so much.
Dude, what are your what are your what are your WPMs on that shit, bro?
It's like NaNoWriMo.
Bro.
He's going for it.
He's going to break the world record.
That's it.
All right.
If you can clickity click further down the track, you win.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think anyone's going to beat that.
I'm just I'm just going to post.
This is this is the one we just listened to.
The next one is.
Two immature links.
It's two imager links.
I was from Prince Annihilation at finallyback.com.
The first one doesn't work.
Yeah, it looks like it's cut off.
I think it doesn't have enough letters.
Oh, well.
Sorry about that.
But the second one.
Let's try the second one.
Second one works.
Fun.
Gun.
Why does no one fun?
So true.
Let me post the.
Yeah.
Damn.
It really it really do be like that is all I can say.
The next one is.
Oh, I think this is more Vinny stuff.
Right.
Vinny stuff killed the podcast last.
Killed the podcast.
So we literally killed the podcast.
Is there a way to tell whether this will do the same thing?
Well, you know what?
We just won't.
We just won't post the link.
We just won't just don't link it in the description.
Okay.
Put on the screen though.
Yeah.
Unless it's too much.
The last one was it was like.
Oh my God.
Yeah, it's too much.
Oh, the last one was marked like mature content.
Like you had to like click like.
Yes.
To see it.
If you're like, are you 18 plus?
I see.
That was probably what caught the thing.
There's a.
Yeah.
I think it was like auto.
Oh my God.
Okay.
There's a lot of these.
I'm afraid to stand pie in your eye.
No reference pic.
Is this just what he assumes cheesy looks like?
Yeah.
Why is he got like Zorro hair?
He doesn't have like Zorro hair.
He has a gap in his teeth.
It's hard to make it.
Look good in.
Wait, is this the stand or is this the or is this cheesy?
Cheesy.
Cheesy has images of themselves.
Yeah.
You could you could find it quite easily.
I'm so maybe.
Okay.
Pie in your eye pie in your eye activates on contact with flesh or most effectively when in contact with your eyes when the car is affected.
The perception is warped into a hallucinated reality.
The affected reality differs from person to person.
The hallucinations can be manipulated or controlled by cheesy and his stand pie in your eye.
There was no reference pic for the first dude.
I drew but the rest of their favorite based on the guy and his music album covers who.
Okay.
Next one is.
I believe in Ben the continuation of the FLCL thing.
I think this is.
Oh, this is Nate as a Camon.
Hey, Ben gasp.
Uh-huh.
Sorry guys.
I got carried away with the Fully Cooley episode five scene.
I came to proposition give and take for.
I love this face.
I don't know why but this panel is reminding me of Rugrats for some reason.
Rugrats, huh?
Don't know why.
I look so miserable.
Conclusion to the Fully Cooley episode five scene.
Hey, Eleazar, maybe just put a sense of our overgives thick clappers in that first panel.
Don't call them that.
Sorry for giving you so much work to do.
Oh, and then.
Okay.
So this is not the conclusion because then it continues.
Ben, we will duel for give and takes honor.
The winner will have a podcast.
With her.
I'm game.
Game.
That's why I sell for it.
Fully.
It's Hariko.
Oh, yeah.
Give and takes on.
Here's my podcast.
It's all for you.
Never in a million years will you ever get anything for me for the but full of lead.
That's not in here.
But I mean, yeah, this is the scene.
Wait, look at the top right.
This is drawn on like some.
Yeah, it's like a like a schedule of something.
It's got old steps.
So let's go parameter.
Critical parameter.
I thought this was like some astronomy stuff or something.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, Lamal, it ends there.
I'm not drawing out the rest.
No.
You don't have to draw the entire episode.
The rest of the episode where in Haruku.
Haraku.
Why does he spell it like that?
Flies around in a bunny outfit and kills a big guy in a trench coat.
Imagine Given taking a bunny outfit being all sexy, but no, but not for me.
My formerly innocent hands shall not be partaking in the making sexy images of Given.
No matter how.
I really saw it as a Tee hee.
Ha ha to have behind closed discord groups.
But Ben had to have Given take sexy butt cheeks drawn as his favorite anime and also be shown to his impressionable YouTube audience.
Tisk, Tisk, I say to you.
Ben saying.
Wait, is he saying that you asked him to draw this?
He's not.
I don't know if he's saying that I asked him, but he's he's saying that it was because I demanded it.
And nearly saw it as a Tee hee.
Ha ha.
I mean, yeah, it's unlike Ben, who took it very seriously to me.
This was just Tee hee.
Ha ha.
This was just laughing matters.
But Ben had to ban it was serious business.
Okay.
Is this me as Beetlejuice?
Yeah.
Say my name three.
Say my name and say, then say it.
Ha ha.
Thanks.
I like my risk a coat.
Am I exuding like green vape out all my my bodily pores?
No, it's called stink lines.
I'm holding the vape.
I'm have my vape cartridge in my hand there.
Oh, it's been saying as Beetlejuice and give a sake as Friska.
Halloween costume get this is the last thing I had drawn for the podcast.
The nest things are of my own imaginations.
Okay, it's a fair.
It's a fair.
It's a caterpillar cat.
His name is Taffy.
He's a magic little guy and generates magic paws to defend himself or hunt how like cats
do.
It's a creature concept I have for my personal comic.
I'm trying to produce.
Cool.
Like a Rayman cat.
A caterpillar, you know, like a ferret.
That's just a ferret.
But with Rayman hands.
This is something that my wife has kicked to gear and this guy has a wife.
You learn something new every day.
And yet he doodles Ben St. at work.
What a what a what a paradox.
And these things can't do these things completely completely exclusive for me.
So they and then this something that my wife has kicked to gear in my mind a comic about
her and I being a pirate and a mermaid that fall in love.
That is so disgusting.
That's sickening.
That's too fucking cute.
And and I mean that with like the most negative connotation I can possibly muster.
My wifey Aurora and then her two aquatic sidekicks.
It's a small spiny dogfish shark and a Hawaiian monk seal.
The shark.
Wait, wait, I just skipped it.
I'll read the whole thing.
It takes place on this pumpkin island.
This pumpkin mountain in the background is actually a volcano.
This volcano where in the natives tried discarding this cursed pumpkin into but the thing blew
up to shape of a pumpkin so they stopped because it freaked him out.
Oh, I feel like yeah, we shouldn't have done that.
The guy who brought all the cursed pumpkin to the island was isolated from the native society
and made his home on top of the volcano.
That's why there's a castle on top of it.
Yep.
Yeah, checks out.
That makes sense.
My wifey Aurora and her two aquatic sidekicks is a small spiny dogfish shark and a Hawaiian monk
seal.
This shark is too small and weak to bite through the seal stick layer of body fat, but he do
try.
He do try.
Look at that shark's little grin there.
He do try though.
He do try.
The seal.
Oh, if he could, he would rend your body fat asunder.
He would sink like in dwarf fortress.
He would sink his teeth into your body, tearing the fat.
This shark is too small and weak.
The seal is one of three subspecies of earless seal foces that are native to warm water environments.
Unlike otarids, foces do not communicate by barking.
Instead, they communicate by slapping the water and grunting.
You probably didn't know that seals get all the water they need from their food.
Their bodies are very efficient at removing and recycling water from their food.
They avoid drinking seawater.
If a seal drinks too much seawater, it can be seriously.
Why is this all of the seal knowledge?
Animal facts.
The Hawaiian monk seal is one of two remaining monk seal species.
The other is the Mediterranean monk seal.
The extinct species, the Caribbean monk seal is extinct.
The story takes place in a fictional island, but I'm getting lightheaded.
I'm going to faint.
But I had done a little research to find if there were any warm water manals and had some fun learning.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Hey, thanks for the seal facts.
I really like the shark.
The shark little sideways look with the big teeth sticking out.
He's doing that thing that dogs do when they look backwards and they show the white of their eye.
Yeah.
I guess this is him as a pirate in the first one.
He looks like Larry Butts from Phoenix Wright.
Larry Butts?
Is he in the first game?
He is.
He's Phoenix's childhood friend or one of them.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I kind of see it.
Abid, what could I say?
Thanks for the voice manals.
Thanks for your creative output.
Thank you for...
I have no more to add.
You've been completely flabbergasted.
I've been dumbfounded, stymied, dumbfucked.
Dumbfucked.
I've been dumbfucked at these posts.
If you know what I mean.
I know, I don't.
Well, I mean, that's the last of the voice spells for this week.
Yeah.
Oh, that's one more.
Is there?
Yeah.
No, that's not.
This is Happy Birthday Ben.
Well, oh, yeah.
Last one is Happy Birthday Ben.
Hey, thanks.
Hey, I appreciate it.
Reminder to everyone that the voice mails are back
and you can send us a voice mail at speakprep.com.
PCP Voice Mail, is that it?
Yes.
I think that's it.
It's linked in the description.
There is, we did the bonus episode where we went through all the old,
never before listened to, we opened up the vault
and we brought the old voice mails out from the vault from years and years ago.
Hear us respond to people asking like,
hey guys, why did Monkey join the podcast or something?
Were there any really funny old questions?
We didn't come over like any controversial things.
Well, there are questions about like DigiNay,
who was still on the podcast at the time.
We got a couple like responding directly to things she said.
There were some about, you know, this was back in the, back in the day.
Okay, so anyway, that's on Patreon.com.
Stuff for a new bonus episode, along with 56 other bonus episodes,
along with a classic Bencast, Ben commentary.
Hear me respond to myself.
Just genius.
How am I such a genius?
Anything else?
I may start streaming Elden Ring soon.
That's just a back in my mind thought.
But no plans yet.
I kind of want to get back into it.
I could, yeah.
I could try a stream sometime.
I could try streaming again.
My internet, sometimes it works fine.
There are times when it's not so good,
but like most of the time it works.
So it might be worth attempting another Minecraft
or something stream at some point, just to see what happens.
Yeah.
I'm a little bit disappointed with the internet at my new place,
but I don't know.
Maybe it would have,
maybe it wouldn't have the issues that my old place had, I'm not sure.
I have to talk to Maren and get all the Minecraft server stuff sorted out.
But anyway, I think that's everything.
I think that's all the stuff I wanted to talk about this week.
So, thanks for listening.
Watch out for my new video, which might be coming out really soon.
Might even be out by now.
But it might not.
Ha ha.
Okay, bye.
See you next week. Thank you.
Thank you very much.