Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever and we're joined by Gibbontake. I'm so medium, I'm the medium guy ever. You've
never seen anybody quite as normal as me. Except of course for Ben Saint. Dab. I did it. An intro.
Have you guys heard about the little game called Minecraft? Minecraft. There's been some rumblings
in the ether mod available for version 1.12 but not higher than that.
Welcome. I tried. It doesn't work. It doesn't work with the latest mods. They're fucking up over
there. What about, what's that one? Is it Technic? Is Technic the one that has like all this weird
technology stuff? Technic is the launcher. Technic is like an umbrella for a lot of mods. It used to
be one mod. I think a thing of Minecraft industrial or something like that. That's got like nuclear
reactors. No, I might be thinking because I'm just remembering the old the old Yogscast
series where they built like the the the Jaffa cake factory and they used the they used Technic
and maybe some other mods I don't remember. Mate, do you think we should like bring this up? Because I
am kind of curious what the audience of the actual podcast thinks. We should definitely bring it up.
Yeah. Okay, well let's just launch into it. We're changing the podcast to be a Minecraft
Let's play show. Minecraft only lads. What if the podcast was just us playing Minecraft
while talking? Duable. Literally doable. No video. Not really. Not really. So we've been
thinking, Meiji and I, it was a major proposal about setting up a PCP Minecraft server for
access for like patrons or something and there's been a great deal of discussion about basically
everyone thinks it'd be potentially a good idea. But the the hot debate has been how to roll it out
so as to not make it seem like weirdly expensive and then also to make it accessible to people
relatively easily. And oh boy, has there been some some I don't know struggles about what's the
appropriate plan? Do we make like a separate Patreon just for that? Well, that doesn't really feel
PCPS. Do we make it like a $7 tier? Well, now it seems like weirdly expensive and more price than
the bonus episodes, which are probably more value. I don't know. It's complicated. No, actually all
of those sounds like great, great values and whichever one we decide on you the viewer should be
excited to participate. If you haven't checked out the heckles for shackles live streams where we've
been playing Minecraft, it'll be like that except in real life. I love the idea of having our own
server may just been all the heavy work of like trying to experiment three days and nothing nothing
but Minecraft Minecraft on the brain. I've been doing nothing but sleeping eating bathroom and
Minecraft making server. So you know tragically, I tried to extend on Twitter. I put out a poll on
the PCP thing saying like, are you interested? I tried to make it as long as possible. It's going
to end like the day before this episode goes out. So it's not quite open. So people could hear it.
We could theoretically do another one, but I'd be very curious to hear people in the comments
if you're interested at all what you after that. Maybe I'll just literally do a second poll and be
like, Hey guys, what do you think? Yeah, like after this episode releases, we can make a poll
with the options we have discussed in this episode. Yeah, you know, why not? Literally why not? Let's,
we should do that. It's an ongoing discussion about what's the best plan. Because I mean,
yeah, go on. Go on. No, I'm just like, how people pay is like, I don't really mind. I'm sure they
think like, you know, okay, they care about like, not paying too much, obviously. I think
the simplest one is just have it part of the $5 tier. So you get bonus episodes, you also get
Minecraft. I just think, I just think that if we do that, we will probably end up making very
little money because probably most, most of the people that we are going to sign up are going to
be the people that already maybe have the $5 subscription. And the thing about that makes a
lot. Yeah, I agree. That's most of the people that there'd be some and like it probably would help
with like longer term people would stay pledged that. So it's a little hard to judge exactly how
that would affect things long term. Munchy for one thinks that's a good idea. But I think what
should be incorporated here is we'll get into some inside baseball because I find this stuff
fascinating. The semi-issue with that is like, for, Mage has been the one doing all the heavy
lifting. She's going to be the one running it if we, you know, get it off the ground and whatnot.
Until I lead the workers revolution. Of course. It's only fair that as someone doing a bunch of
work on it, Mage gets like some cut of the earnings from it. If we just lump it into the $5 tier,
I think it's only fair. I mean, really, no matter what we do, some amount of money that this thing's
earning really should go to Mage. So that means at a minimum, let's say we make it part of the $5
tier, we absolutely should carve out some amount of payment per month. Yeah, I mean, we should do
the same thing we do with you. Like you get like an ad, you get like an, a regular admin fee for
like administrating the, the, you know, the PayPal account or whatever and like doing all the, the
like fucking, all the charting money, all the charting stuff. We just, we'll do that. And like
how Tom gets the fee for doing the iTunes stuff. Right. But here's the thing about that. Because
like we were saying, if we make it part of the $5 tier, I don't particularly expect things to rise
that much. I'm sure we'd go up some. I think that's definitely true. But would that even be enough
to cover whatever potential fee that Mage is making for now doing the job? I mean, I don't know,
probably, but like that sounds like a pretty slim margin. I mean, it would, it would depend on,
it would just depend, I don't know. And, and think of like, it's going to take Mage up on time. Also,
how much does it cost to run the server? We're right now at $15 a month to, for it to be feasible.
Okay. So, so it'll be that plus whatever we pay Mage for it. So if, so we would need
seven more people to sign up for the $5 tier to cover that?
Uh, seven? Wouldn't it just be three? Oh, wait, you, right. You mean,
because I was sorry, I was assuming, I was assuming we were going to pay Mage like 20 a month to
administer the thing. I don't know if that's accurate or not. Whatever. I don't know. I mean,
I mean, something like that. But I don't, but think about like, here's the other thing about it.
What's my incentive? Let's just say, for example, let's say, or, I don't know, anyone who doesn't
play Minecraft that much who might want to do it. What's my incentive to spend time, dedicate time
to this community? If we don't already have like, like when you're on a PCP episode, you get a payment
for that episode. There's an incentive there. If you're on a heckles for shekels, there's donations.
There's an incentive to do that. What's the incentive to do this if we don't have like a
separate thing carved out? Well, I thought the idea was that we would be in, we would play in the
server on shekels for heckles. That does make sense. And I think we should and could like we
would stream ourselves playing in it. I could say that being kind of the way most of us play.
Yeah, like, yeah, I mean, that does make sense. I mean, I thought that was like the entire basis
for the idea in the first place was we should do heckles for shekels on our own server.
Yeah, that is a decent idea. I mean, I stand by. Okay, the only one that doesn't think that's how
we're going to do it. Well, I mean, look at mage is the one who expects to play a decent amount.
And I mean, like, there's, there's other things like managing the server regularly,
managing like the community, she'll have to whitelist people who join because, you know,
it's a private server and all that. I don't know, like working with the people on the game,
organizing private, like, I don't really know what it would entail. I guess it could just be
the heckles for shekels. And that's all that matters. But but just consider the alternative,
which is like, this is the idea that I currently think is the best one. Yes, there's downsides,
but it's still my favorite overall, which is a theoretical, totally separate Patreon,
because this is all new value being added. You know, we could say it's like the PCP one,
that's all fine, we could link to it in various places. And it's called like this is the PCP
Minecraft Patreon, it's just a separate thing. And you pledge $3 or whatever, and you get access
to the server. And you don't have to, you don't have to worry about it at all. If you don't want
to, all the costs now come out of the income from that. So nobody on the normal PCP loses any money.
And in order not to fuck over anybody who's pledging like $10, I saw that like Culek 64 or
whatever, whatever their name is. Pizza Chan. Yeah, Pizza Chan. They're like, Hey, I already pledged
$10. Like I want in like, I don't want to fuck over that guy or anybody pledging more. So we could
maybe just lump in for 10 or up people on the normal Patreon, they just get access to because
they're already, you know, doing good stuff. But like ideally, for everybody who wants a lower thing,
it's just a separate thing, which I think is clean. And I feel like that guarantees more. We already
have a $10 tier, right? Yeah. What do you get? What do you get at $10? What's the bonus? Literally
nothing extra. Okay, cool. Yeah. Yeah, just nice people who want to support. Why? I don't know. I
mean, let's let's examine the downsides of that. Why not make it the $10 tier? Like, because like
there's already the $5 tier to get to the bonus episode. So it's not like we're just, it's not
like we're just saying, Hey, $10 to get into the server, because that's not all you're getting for 10.
Right? Okay, okay. But then consider this, like there might be some people who aren't particularly
interested in the bonus episode, PCP in general, like on my side, at least there are a few people
that would like to play Minecraft with me, but they're not particularly into the PCP. So then
asking them to pay $10 a month just for the server is not fair. I don't think. Or I mean,
you're not, you're not wrong. You're not wrong. But I mean, it's a fifth question.
How many of those people are there? That is a reasonable question to ask. I think that the
people who would want to play in a PCP Minecraft server probably overlaps fairly heavily with people
who would want to listen to the bonus episodes. I agree. I agree. The question is how many people
don't fit in that is my biggest question because I don't know. I don't know. Well, I would imagine
it's in my mind. I mean, there might be people who maybe have not pledged the five dollars to
listen to it. Maybe like they would listen to the bonus episodes, but they don't feel like pledging
the five. And I mean, that's fair and all. Okay, just for those who are listening, me and Nate,
we're planning to make like, you know, if we're going to make a separate Patreon, the fee for the
Minecraft server a month, a month is just three dollars. That's how we were planning it. Yeah,
we like, we thought about some ideas. It seems like a three dollar pledge. So like, yeah, let's do
polls. We'll put some together. Are people with people? Okay, here's the other thing. We can ask
people what they think. And this is this is true of me. This is true of every person on the planet.
The consumer doesn't necessarily think in the same terms of like, what would work best for the
business? Yeah, you've got to be like, you know, I feel like making a second Patreon is really
multiplying entities beyond necessity, split kind of splitting people's attention between two things
in a way that I don't think is going to be optimal. I really don't like that. I already made a few
points. Like from a purely logical perspective, like in terms of like, perfect efficiency,
yeah, I think it makes the most sense. But in terms of like, how it'll actually work and how
like people will actually engage with it, I don't think that's the right way to do it.
Well, let's just examine one other possibility. Because you were saying make a $10 tier or
limited that that makes some sense. We were thinking, yeah, we were thinking even going lower for like
a $7 tier, theoretically, for doing that for and we actually said 750 or something. So if we did
that, that's actually you're paying less additional cost for that over. This is like the first
proposal that we do like a $7 thing or whatever. That's that was what I asked people in like the
Discord server. So you're you're still getting the bonus episodes and you're getting additional
value that technically is cheaper than what you'd be paying for like the $3 on a theoretical new
Patreon. But there's now the hurdle of this $750 mark, which is a psychologically sort of different
thing that could because when I asked people about this, again, this was fairly anecdotal. I only
asked a couple of people. By the way, I hope this is interesting to people. I find it legitimately
fascinating. I find it interesting. I was going to say that like,
inside baseball can be fun. But I feel like we're so inside this baseball that people can't really
relate. Okay, but listen, listen, like I was in a practice with Digi and Tom and then talking about
printing shirts for like half an hour, if not an hour. Some people really enjoy that others might
find out. Yeah, but I feel like Minecraft is slightly catching more people than shirt printing.
People like Digi quite a bit and they get caught up in his site. Not me. Actually,
that's not true. I felt I felt the warm and fuzzies yesterday. Did you did you made a pretty glowing
tweet about about my shit, which I don't want to I don't want to get on the subject of that
shit yet. We can talk about that after Minecraft. Sure, sure. I made a I made a warm tweet.
You also did. And I was very happy. So here, last thing I want to say because I'm
people when I when I propose like the I like talking. Okay, yeah, I enjoy this kind of inside
baseball. Like how much do we charge for stuff? How should we structure this? Because I think about
this kind of thing all the time. Right. Me too. I think about like, I stress about like, what is
what is a what what is a good and ethical and effective business model? I fucking sweat this
stuff. I find this not funny at all. Just purely fascinating. Yeah, the okay. But my last point just
I just for people's consideration for whatever they want to think of the like that $750 model or
whatever, a new tier, essentially, that's a Minecraft thing. Like when we propose that a lot
of people like in the patron server, I specifically when asked people what they thought, they were
like, ooh, it feels weird that we're paying more for a Minecraft thing than the bonus episodes.
It's like there's a weird incentive to like that, like you're saying it's valued more than the bonus
episodes. And like, ideally, if we were making a new patron from scratch, we might make this like
the $3 tier that currently doesn't exist. But the fact like we're trying to work with a model that
already exists. So, you know, there's not really much of a charge. We're not charging the more for
the PCP server than for the bonus that we're charging more for both put together, which just
seems like yeah, obviously. Yeah, exactly. But like people people feel and people say the thing.
I mean, not everybody does the thing. I don't want to shit on any of the commenters or anything.
But I mean, you know, obviously, they're going to be skewed in favor of, you know,
the consumer, right? They're going to want the greatest value for the consumer. And we,
owning the means of production and being petty bourgeois that we are, we want to extract the
most value from the proletariat, i.e. them, right? So, you know, the class struggle continues.
You know, there's another fascinating aspect to this that I think about that's
consider the perspective of those who are the most into this idea and who
likely will do the most work on it and stuff who would want to benefit from the most versus
someone like, I mean, just for example, Digi says, don't care, go for it guys, do whatever you want.
So like, I mean, frankly, Digi doesn't really deserve to benefit, particularly outside of the
outside of the reality. If I think it's fair that if this is a PCP branded Minecraft thing,
I don't think it's crazy for some of that income to go toward like the overall PCP earnings.
It's it's like part of the network or whatever. And I think it gets some benefit from that.
Some. Yeah. Some. Yeah. I mean, I put a pay a model out to like the guys in the Collier that I won't
go into now. But it's like, if it's if it's obviously made, just the main one, she's doing
the hard work, I plan on playing too. If those guys are like developing a community,
they're playing with people there, I don't know, organizing games, they're doing fun things.
They're the one like driving the incentive to play the game. That is a very different thing
from someone like, I mean, Digi or maybe Munchie or other people who are too busy,
not that interested or whatever, who are suggesting things like attaching it to the $5 one,
as opposed to making it like a $7 50 or a separate Patreon, because those guys,
they just want to not have to change anything, which I totally get. And they just want additional
value being provided to what's already there because they benefit from that. Whereas like we
want a separate thing where we can, you know, have the profits there in a place where those who
are working on it can receive that share, you know, being sent to them in a clean way. No,
it would be in a separate when you say it like that. Yeah. Suddenly, I'm suddenly I'm thinking
that maybe the the separate model makes sense from a from a business from a business perspective
in some ways, in some ways, kind of. Okay, I'm a little I'm coming around a little bit.
I mean, maybe for fun, we'll put out that poll. I'm coming around a little bit. It's just that I
feel like the numbers like I like I feel like it's not going to get I don't know. I mean, it depends.
I think that maybe a Patreon is not the right way to do it. And maybe there could just maybe
there's just a subscription service like that. I mean, I would do a subscription. There are like
PayPal, you can do like a monthly PayPal subscription. It's just that Patreon makes it really easy to
manage all that, which is kind of what it's for. But like I did the calculations. If they're doing
a if we're doing a $3 pledges, we lose about 9% off like that's basically what we're paying them.
9% is not a huge amount. Wait, they're paid through Patreon. Yeah, if we use Patreon,
because that's the way they break it up. Yeah. Patreon sucks. So like theoretically,
if we made it to our current Patreon, and we just made it like instead of $5,
now you pledged 750 or whatever, like now that additional loss is lessened.
So no, it's still it's still it's still 9% off of whatever additional money is made. There's a
couple reasons why that's not true. But the biggest one is because our PCP was our piece of Patreon
was made before the rates changed. So it's getting grandfathered in to the lower rates that are like
5% or something. Really? Yeah, that's true. That's true. Secret. Really? It's really true, you guys.
I am shocked. So that's something. That's something. But I mean, if at the end of the day,
if we can't agree, I think it's kind of funny, we all agree more or less that this would be a
benefit. There's there's some disagreement about what's the optimal way to do it. And those
disagreements could lead to an impasse. If that theoretically happened, me and Major just gonna
make it on our own as a separate Patreon, and then we'll make it like effectively the same thing
anyway. And you know, we'll as a person who like delves in and out of like caring about Minecraft,
I'm sure I'll play for a bit and then stop for months and months and months. So I'm probably
not gonna be like making a community there. Well, okay, I mean, for me, like I like playing it on
Shekels for Heckels. I'm not I'm not just gonna be playing it by myself. I'm gonna be playing it when
you guys are playing and probably when we stream it. That's that's what I'm interested in doing.
I do like that. And that's my primary goal too. Definitely. Definitely. So, you know, it's on
experiments. And it'd be nice if we could figure out just some model to try. And then like if it
works, great. You viewer can make a name for yourself. You can be a star. You can be in the
streams, right? You can be on our screens in front of the like 100 people. Just imagine the vision,
Ben. Imagine you open your capitalist heart and just imagine the vision. We're playing Shekels
for Heckels. We're playing it right now. Let's say in this particular model, it's a separate
Patreon or whatever. We're like, Hey, guys, we're having so much fun. We're doing our like weekly,
bi-weekly, monthly stream or whatever. We've got this community going. You could join us right now
and literally be on the stream. If only you cough up those sweet three dollars. You could be griefing
us right now. Only for and three dollars is a is a is a ledge. I think most people are willing to
hop. Honestly, that's a real sweet spot. You know, I kind of think three dollars is I kind of think
that's low ball on it. Yeah, some people said three to five and said like I think I think five is
fair. Um, maybe I don't know. Okay, at the at the risk of sounding egotism, right? I know we're,
you know, we're not like, we're not fucking, I don't know, we're not gonna fucking. We're not,
we're not the Yogs cast or we're not like a big like fucking network. We're not, we know, we're
just the PCP, right? We're not some grow though. But yeah, but what I'm saying is so I know it's
not like, Oh, you need to play with the prestigious members of the procrastiners podcast. That's
the value of at least five dollars. But at the same time, I mean, how much would the entry into
like any old fucking, like private server costs? I don't know. I mean, yeah, you'd have to run your
own. I feel like three is like so little. And like, I feel like for what it is, you get a considerable
amount of value. I don't know. I mean, that's not unsure. And we're talking five dollars a month.
This is a pretty cheap, you know, that's not a huge expenditure. And I feel like most people who
would be willing to part with three dollars would probably be willing to part with five,
like, like how much difference does that $2 make? Because when we did the first poll, I said like
$7 on the Patreon for it. And people were like, that seems like too much. But but really like
psychologically, if you just make a separate payment of $5, a lot of people will think that's
less, even though theoretically, there might be paying more for less value than that $7 pledge
if they patronize the bonus episode. I mean, I kind of think rolling it into the $10 tier makes sense.
I mean, I get the idea. Like for business reasons, I really like the idea of like a clean,
separate way to manage how much money is coming for that specifically. But yeah, I mean, I mean,
theoretically, the idea of doing both so that, well, what appeals to me about that is just that
it makes it really clear on our end, like what value is being added by this particular aspect
versus everything else. What I want is I desperately want the ability for people to be able to choose.
If they want both $10 on our Patreon, if they just care about Minecraft or whatever,
just five dollars somewhere separately, they don't have to fuck around with both.
That would be a pretty swell deal. Wait a minute, brain blast. Is it possible to have two alternate
$5 tiers? Okay, that sounds like we're getting crazy.
I had that brain blast and everyone said it was stupid.
I don't think you can do that on Patreon, but I don't know.
Well, you can have a five dollar and one cent.
It's just that like practically speaking, if you're pledging five dollars for one,
I think you can go in and like change what your pledge thing is at some point. And we all know
axing the bonus episodes is not as hard as we would like if you're heavily motivated to do so,
especially if you're pledging that already. No, that's plain to lose. That's plain to lose.
We can't acknowledge that. Fair. Edit that. Edit that.
Oblivionfall edit. Oh, wait, shit. Oblivionfall is dead.
Oh, by the way, were people confused, Oblivionfall has retired in good spirits and it's all the same?
I think we just haven't said it out loud. We haven't literally went into it last episode.
Was it because the school year started? No, no, no, no.
It was super busy the whole time with other work. He has an animation work thing.
Yeah. Okay, apparently he was putting in like 16 hours of work on each episode,
which is like so much more than any of us ever did.
I'm curious, Ben, on your edits. Yeah, I'm really embarrassed for you, Oblivion,
that really sucks to be here. No, that's not what I meant. I meant for us.
When you were doing your like edits with like the art stuff, like how many hours would you say that
was? Okay, okay, okay, okay. Oh, like on the ones with the moving mouths?
Yeah, yeah. Okay, that did, well, okay. Yeah, that did take a lot of time, but I think that was
mostly just hassle. It wasn't that I was like doing like 16 hours of solid like creative work,
generating that. I was spending like, there would, it would be a days long process of like
getting it to render, like having something fail during the render, like having to try it again,
like, you know, waiting for processing to finish and stuff like dealing with errors,
having to redo stuff. Okay, so yeah, on those, I probably did put in like maybe
a similar amount of time, but not, but just because of like fucking
faulty hardware and not knowing what the fuck I was doing with like- Which I presume Oblivion
did not have the issues. Adobe Premiere and yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, well fair enough,
God, I'm gonna fucking miss him, but we're gonna get an editor. At some point, Oblivion, I love
you, you two make work. He was so good. Nah, nah, he's so good. He gay. Yeah, that's fair.
Well, whatever, I don't know. We'll put out some polls in the description, vote on Minecraft
things. I don't know if we do them. We'll figure something out. Don't worry, have no fear, have
no fear. And just voice off if you're interested in general, because I want to know, I want to know
how many people are into it. Anything else to say on the subject? I'm, I'm spent. I'm excited for
the glorious future of Bufalantopia. Indeed. Indeed. Well, we might need to make a new,
a new land with, I mean, are there going to be Bufalants in our new location or wherever
that happens to be? I don't know. I don't know. We'll have to find out. All right, we can, we can
send our old Bufalant to the glue factory and get some new ones. Indeed. Indeed. Oh, the new one
will be called Bufalantopia. Bufalantopia. I love Bufalantopia. I do too. It's just, it organically
grew. The people there are helpful and cool. I was like, next stream, we got to burn it all down.
I had such, I had such, I had such, I was filled with such pride. I was filled with pride as I,
as I was getting up there on the scaffold and making the sign, I was like, yes, this is going to be
the start, the mark of a new civilization. People from miles around will see the Bufalantopia sign
lit up in the night sky and say, huh, I wonder what the fuck is going on over there. When we,
whenever this happens and we migrate to our new server, we should burn the whole place down.
Oh, absolutely. With our Bufalant, trap our Bufalant inside. They have to, they have to go down with
the ship. That's, it's the right thing to do. Okay, let's move on. What else is going on in your
lives, everybody? Um, well, I got my, oh yeah, talk about your stuff. Oh wait, Ben was going to fight
me about Minecraft something. Oh, I kind of already, well, yeah, I just, well, you know, you're going
to be the motto and whatever, right? Cause you're, you're creating the thing and I just, that's fine
for now, but like once that's all established, um, you know, it's not going to be acceptable
anymore for you to own the means of production. Um, we're going to have to have mutual ownership. So
we are going to fucking, uh, we are going to fucking workers revolution.
Could we get a mod to, uh, to create guillotines in Minecraft? That's gotta be in there somewhere,
right? Yeah. And then when he crafts that soon, he himself will be on the gallows as,
you know, the new guy in charge. This is what happened to what's his face?
That's to happen to all of us eventually. Uh, Ben, talk about vapors. Yes. The Vapors 2 kick
starter is going right now. And that's what I was talking about before. Digi and Nate and,
and hippo. And I think everyone, everyone's retweeting my shit and making nice tweets saying
it's a great value, which it is incredible value on offer at kickstarter.com slash project slash
Ben St slash vapors to, um, Lincoln, the doobly dude in the down there part. Um,
it's, it's going good. It's surpassed. It's we're on the third day and we're past, uh,
4,000 or $4,100 right now, which is, it's pretty good. Yeah. It's out. It's outpacing the last
year. The initial target was $2,586. So you win. You already I did. I passed it like
early into the second day. Um, yeah. And the stretch goal, uh, was 4,000. So you already
got that as well. Yeah. The stretch, the stretch goal was to pay for, um, the extra pages and
paying all the guest artists, which are, I will list them off right now. The people doing guest
art for the vapor arts are hypocrite, munchy wears tiny hats. Who's that? I don't know.
Nobody. Munchy wears tiny hats. Um, uh, nexus mania, cheesy manfredo, jade morrow,
and I'm forgetting someone. Who am I forgetting? You're forgetting fucking, uh,
God damn it. Cassey. Cassey. That's right. That's right. Yes. Yes. Cassey snap. Um, it's going to
be fucking cool. More like Cassey snapper fucking neck when she does it. I realized that chapter
two is actually a lot shorter than, um, chapter one, but I still wanted to make it its own book.
So I thought I would just write a whole bunch of scripts and, and like pay a bunch of, um,
good artists who like, you know, make like more, because like the first one had a couple of,
it had maybe like, actually it had, it probably had almost, it's probably like 16, 17 pages of
bonus content because munchies was like 11 pages long. This one, I kind of was expecting maybe
each vaporette to be like three to five to maybe seven tops. So six of those might be, might, there
might be like 20 or 30 bonus pages in there that are not on the internet. They're not even made
yet. No one will have seen them. Um, but I wanted to fill it out. I want to fill that page count
out. So it's not like half the size of the first one, you know, you know, I want that consumer
advocacy is what I'm doing. I, Ben, you know, you know, I hate you and you know, I don't respect
you, but I think if I can, okay, I've, there's no, I have to have this infinite jest pin to go with
my poobop. There's no, there's no question. So I think, God, I don't know. I, I'm looking at the,
at these amazing reward tiers with these incredible benefits. I think I have to go
tell me about it for the $150 tier. Maybe Michelle wants to split it because I mean,
I have to have a pin. I know Michelle's going to want to pin two and we get three pins from that.
And then I have some spare poobas. If I lose them someday, I want to have that. So maybe me
and Michelle can split the $150 one and you'll have a books, you know, the hundred, the $150
one is like, it's pretty, it's pretty good. It's pretty, it's a pretty good value. What do you
get? Like, you get like a sign. You get the signed copy, which I'll like, you know, I'll do a drawing
for you in there. Just write you a message and stuff. It's personalized. And then you get three
copies of vapor one, three copies of vapor two, three poobop pins, three infinite jest pins. That's
it's epic. And so I don't know. I'm thinking about, so yeah, we passed the the reward tier
that's or the stretch goal for how to afford, you know, the guest art and stuff, paying for the
extra page. By the way, that's not just, it's not a flat amount. I'm going to give, I'm going to give
the, all the guest artists are going to get like, they're going to get like a cut of each copy of
vapors. I decided that like 50 cents per issue of vapors to per person with the six, so that means
$3 total, but like 50 cents to each guest artist per copy of it was to last time there was like a
little over 200. So that would, if we do the same numbers, that would be like $100 to each of them.
But if we go higher than that, it'll be more. That's the plan. Also, I want to say, everyone's,
everyone agreed to do it for free. And then I was like, actually, I want to pay you.
That's the right thing to do. So here's, because I don't want to be a real doctor.
I don't want to be a doctor. I'm looking forward to seeing the script. I haven't seen it yet.
Okay. I have like four of them done. I gave one, one to-
Did you write them with people in mind, Ben, thinking of their particular artistic senses or-
Kind of a little bit. Not exactly. But I did kind of think like, oh, what would be a good one for
like so and so. So I did write one that I thought Cheezy would be the most suited for. So I gave,
I gave him that. But all the other ones, all the other ones, I just, I'm just going to let people
choose. And I, but there's like two of them that I keep like thinking, like, should I rewrite that?
Should I rewrite that? And I don't know. So just, I got to do that. And then I can be like, here,
pick, pick, pick, pick. Are you a Tarantino with these? Do you accept creative changes if they
think that something would be better in- To an extent, I probably would, yeah.
The drawings are going to be like creative changes just inherently.
I mean, Munchies was in high school and it was not supposed to be right. So there was a change
right there. That's fine though. That's fine. That was good. That was good stuff. I like that lore
expansion. Um, yeah, no, whatever. I want everyone to get, get creative like that one video. I'm
just curious, like the, yes, like, like those guys, uh, have you in any way incorporated things that
people have produced in the, um, in the vaporettes? Like, like, I'm thinking of like the background
characters that like Munchie put into some of them. Have those in any way become canon or you want
to do more with? I'm just curious if the lore is expanded due to the vaporettes in any meaningful
way or a small way. I don't know. Uh, that's a very specific question and the answer is no.
Okay, great. But then, but the new vaporettes do expand the lore. Hey, you want to know,
you want to know something? You want to know something you'll learn about in the vaporettes
to this, to this in this issue? Yes. Magda and Vincent's parents. Oh no. Oh my god. Silver
screen. Silver tongue. Silver platter. I can't wait to meet all the siblings. It's going to be great.
Exactly. Exactly. Wait, what's the other one? There was another one. Silver lining.
Oh yeah. Silver line is the good. Oh yeah. Silver spoon is the other one. Yeah, yeah. That's the
family. Wait, no, silver. Yeah, yeah. Silver. Silver screen. Silver tongue. Yeah, tongue was the dad.
Yeah. That's right. That's right. By the way, for anyone who doesn't know, these are our fan
characters of the extended family of Silver spoon. Literally the greatest OCs in the game. They were.
Silver lining. So good. Silver lining and the Silver family. He deserves his own comic series.
I absolutely love those. I'm so fucking proud of these. I'm so fucking proud of these. Silver
lining. Like they're all evil. Silver tongue. Back up. Back up. So we start with Silver spoon,
the character, of course, for my little pony. She's the bully. She's like the lackey to Diamond
Tiara. Clearly a rich kid with a Silver spoon, obviously. Yeah. Her whole family's evil. Her
dad is like a slick lawyer named Silver tongue. Her mom is like an old screen actress or something,
a retired actress named Silver screen. Her brother is a spoiled snotty little bastard named Silver
platter, but she's got one good brother, the one good egg in the bunch, who's called Silver
lining, who always sees the bright side. Incredible. It's so good. He is the Silver lining of the
family. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, it's great. Oh, that's true. Damn. That's deep lore. And also horse fister.
Who could forget horse fister? And his cutie mark is a cloud, but there's just a little bit of sun
poking out the behind it. I know. It's beautiful. I'm a genius. Max revive T-Bap immediately.
As you can see in the famous video, thank you, KP. Check it out now on tbap.com. Or whatever.
I need to, so I've been spamming, so I've been spamming Magi Chan Sonichu on Twitter,
trying to get him to retweet the vapor's link. I think he's my best shot at an endorsement.
I'm just, I don't know. I need, I want to. Oh, you should have got him while he was possessing
Chris's body and that would have been easier to retweet, right? Well, well, he's, no, he's,
he's in, in the real world physically now. Didn't that, oh, oh, that's right. Yeah. He's, he, he,
he, like, just yesterday, he made the full physical transition to dimension 12, 18. Finally.
I know. And he says in his tweets, like, if you see that, if you see like a weird purple
somewhere, that's me. Like, that's, I'm watching you. That could be made just,
just a weird purple, like anything.
Um, I, okay. Okay. You know what I'm going to do? I had this idea. And I don't know when I'll do
this, but I am going to do this as a, as a, oh wait, sorry, I want to talk about stretch goals.
Last time for the stretch goals, one of the stretch goals was the card stock cover. I was
looking at the copies and the card stock cover, I don't know if I can really, I don't know how
much of a difference it makes. So what I did was I ordered two more test copies of Vapors II
with different covers, the glossy covers, just to see if they're better or worse. So I'm just going
to, I don't know, I'm not sure if I'm going to do that stretch goal or not, because I want to
compare the other options and see if it's actually worth like the extra cost. But what I am going
to do is one of my stretch goals, I'm going to implement communism. Okay. I'm going to make
communism real. What does that mean? What does that mean? You ask at whatever, at whatever
level I decide to do it. It's going to be, if we hit this goal, I'm going to redistribute the wealth
and everyone who play, everyone who's getting a package of any kind, I'm just going to give you
a dollar. I'm just going to put a fucking dollar bill in your envelope. It's like yang, but a
slightly more modest. It's like yang, but better because you get it in a cool black envelope.
I do want that envelope. You know, you know what it's like, it's like, you know, from each
according to their ability to each according to their need. Everyone's ability is to buy whatever
shit they can afford on my Vapors to Kickstart it. And what do they need? They all need the dollar,
dollar, dollar, that's what they need. And that's what they're all going to get.
What about people who are pledging with currencies from outside the US?
They will receive a one United States dollar. Okay, I'll put it on my wall. Epic.
And I'll probably write like burning on it or something.
Yeah, if you sign the dollar, then I'll keep it. Yeah, I probably will.
Maybe. Or maybe maybe you just want to spend it. Maybe you just want to treat it as a rebate. I
don't know how to spend American money. The first one, I was tempted to get it because I always
did want a copy of this. I think that because you just gave me a pin, because that was nice of you
and you just had extras and I wanted one, I probably would have pledged it wasn't for that,
but I'll definitely pledge it. God damn it. I know, I know. Don't do that again. In fact,
if you could just like send me an infinite jest pin. In fact, okay, so what you're saying, Nate,
is that I should never do you any favors ever again. I mean, it disincentivizes me to use money
to achieve those same goals. Absolutely. Yeah. This is why capitalism doesn't work, but go on.
This is just worth the value, I think. I want the books. I want the thing. If I get them for
free, great. This is my personal life. I have to pay for them, then I will, then I will.
Dab, dab, dab. Cool. Cool, cool. I was thinking, you know what I could do as like another, maybe
if the thing goes really well, like maybe if we went like really high, like I don't know, like
$10,000 or something. Yeah. What I could maybe do, and like this is possible, I could do basically
the communism thing, but instead of with money, I could just make another pin and just everyone
gets an extra pin. I want those damn pins. I was thinking maybe like the Saint Heart pin,
which I've had, I've been kind of meaning to make for a while, and it would just, it would be like,
it would be a black pin with a silver border, but like the white heart logo with like the rays
coming out of it, it would just be that in silver. That would be, I could make that, and like if,
I mean, if we hit a tier like that, it would not be out of the realm. It would not be unaffordable
for me to just like make a run of like 200 or however many, and just everyone gets one for free.
Yo, that would be great. And sick undertale reference, dude, like totally. Sick undertale
reference. I just, I just, I just think that would look really cool in silver. I, I want to,
I don't know. I was thinking of making those pins, but then I was like, when would I, when would I
ever sell them? I don't know. Maybe not. Maybe now's the time. What am I waiting for? The thing,
the thing, like it does sound really cool. The thing that annoys me about pins though is I don't
have like things I can put them on and that I could like, you need like a rucksack and I don't
really have a rucksack for that. I've said this before. Actually, they're not there right. I think
I put them on the floor just now, but right next to my desk, I have my printer on my printer. I keep
my Radcon three pin and my Puba pin and they're always pointed at me and I get so much joy just
looking over at those because they really are tangible, little physical. It's the same reason
people buy like trinkets probably when they go on vacation, but these are so much more because
these are like, this is what me and my friends have accomplished. These little physical things
remind me that like, when you really put your effort into something, when you really try,
you can do great things and this is just a little reminder and those give me
a disproportionate amount of pleasure. You know, I think my name's Marie Kondo,
that lady who wrote the book about wanting to be clean and wanting everything to be nice and tidy.
The simple joy of tidying up, whatever that is, she says. You never read it, obviously.
Okay, people will know what I'm talking about. She's the cute little Japanese lady who loves tidying
up and Michelle's been reading her books and looking into her stuff and she's been getting me
into it too and Marie Kondo or whatever her name is, if I'm fucking it up, my bad, she says,
like, what's the point in owning things if they don't, this is the quote,
it's everything you own should spark joy. If you own things that don't spark joy,
literally why do you own them? Throw them in the trash. Those pins and in fact, I have my little
slime core pins that I made sitting next to me too from BronyCon and stuff. They spark so much
joy in me. Just to look over at them. Mine disintegrated. You know, mine are breaking down,
but they still are alive. Mine is pretty fucked up, but it's hanging in there. There you go.
I would love metal pins of those one day. At some point, no, at some point, we are going to do,
it might be its own thing or it might be as part of another campaign, but we are going to do a
RFCK pin kickstand. We're going to have a cop killer pin. We're going to have a rowdy fucking
pin. We're going to have a slime core pin. We're going to have a podre... Excellent.
Have you seen the podren pin that I designed?
No. Does it look like a Max Revive? No, no, it looks like... It's cool looking.
I spent a lot of time... Look at the show notes or something, so we are in the description.
All right, yeah, I can find it in a minute, but like, we're going to do, here's the thing,
and like, this is not insurmountable, right? We can get, but for some reason, and it's not just
enamel pin factory. It seems like every company is like this. Companies have such a hard time
printing green. Like, green is like just, yeah, so like, I mean, it's not, it doesn't...
That's rough for slippers, all the slimes. We could still do it, but like,
the options are limited. Like, they don't, they don't have like a really like bright neon green,
like I would really like to see. They just, like, just, they just don't come, like so many companies,
they just don't have that, which is really a shame, because that's like the most important one.
Yeah, yeah, there can, and there are, these are pins that exist in the universe already,
and of course, people want them, especially me, who's the prime example.
That's true, that's true. I don't know, but whatever, I worked around it. I managed to make
some pin design, like the podron pin, I managed to make it look good in spite of that.
Excellent. Anyway, but yeah, that's it, that's the thing. Okay, sorry, I'm trying to find it right
now. Yeah, no, no, no rush, no rush. Well, so that's, so that's what's up, that's what's up with that.
Dope, 28 days to go. 28, 23 from when you're hearing this, I think.
We, 101 backers right now. If we could, if we could, if we could quintuple that,
but between, between when, between when you hear this and, and next week, right? Go, go, go for
between, from when you hear this to when the next, for one week from today, listeners, 200, or bust.
Let's make communism real, everybody. Seems doable, and it's had a great success record in the past.
I'm looking forward to it. Debunked. All right. Well, lads, okay, what's next? What else we got?
I, well, I have been feeling very musical lately. I have been, I've been deep into
jazz fusion and, and cool, cool bands online. And I'm just going to link, I'm going to put this
here. Snarky Puppy is a, is a great, is a great band I've, I've heard. I don't really have much
to say. I just, I just love instrumentation. I just love musicians who are good with instruments,
and I, and I hate lyrics, lyrics bad. Instruments really funny. You know, and my favorite thing.
Most people know you as the dad rock guy when it comes to music. I mean, at least I do. I don't
know how, how pervasive that is. There's the podium. Oh, there's the podium. It's pretty neat,
huh? It's pretty neat. Yeah. But it was funny. I mean, my main exposure to jazz, I've listened
to some, my dad listened to smooth jazz, whatever, but like watching, watching whiplash is just very
funny. Watching these jazz musicians just roast. They're like, um, yeah, you could be a real musician
or you could go be in a rock band, lol. I mean, okay, I guess you could call that music. And I mean,
it's true. Now that's what I call music. I mean, it's not even, it's not even that like rock music
is worse. Like, um, it's just that a lot of the point of all this jazz stuff is that musicians
being like, so into like, all the cool things you can possibly do with an instrument and then
grooving and jiving and jibbing and jabbing. Yeah. And, uh, it's all about the groove. It's all about
the, the, the sort of like sweet solo that makes your face scrunch up like you bit into a lemon.
And it's just sort of like, oh yeah. Ooh, like crazy sort of stuff. Um, and rock is more about,
well, I mean, it's very like, like rock is a huge genre of spanning so many things, but like
a lot of music that has lyrics and is like less music like instrumenty. Oh yeah. Yeah. It's still
like good. It's just, there's a certain level of like bliss and like euphoria you get from hearing
a, like a brilliant musician at nay, a huge band of brilliant musicians all performing incredibly
well together. And it's just so tight. You just can't get that feeling anywhere else. This should
tell you, uh, evidence that like even I can play some guitar and I, I pluck my six string every
once in a while. But like when the idea comes up of like just jamming, no, no, no, I've memorized
my songs. I've memorized the specific chords. Do not ask me to go outside or to improvise.
Can't do it. We'll cry. Yes. I've really, I mean, here's another song, Wolfpick, really great band,
very funny, very funny guys. Yeah. Um, they do a lot of funky stuff. This Dean town is very popular
and the bass line to this is like overly complex and I'm not like a really good. Is it as good as
Monsters Inc opening bass line though? Oh, you know, that, that's a pretty good one. I kind of like
that one as well. I'll learn that one too. Um, but, uh, if you listen to this, like the bass line is
like 18 bars long or something, like the, before it loops, it's just really complex and I've, I've
really enjoyed the past few days just learning it, um, and trying to, to, to match the speed at
which the Joe Dart, the bassist plays it because he's really good. And, um, I'm so wrapped up in
like getting that right that like, I can't, I'm not like a jam musician. I know a bit. I know a
few chords. I know some scales, but I don't, I couldn't probably do much more than like a very
simple like rock solo in E. Um, just like, just go up there like, and then go back to normal chords
because I'm, it's, it's, it's a world that I can't possibly reach at the moment with the amount of
practice I put in, but I appreciate it so much knowing how much more practice I would need to do
to get there. It's just so fucking good. You know, I saw an interview once with, um, what's the guy,
the drummer from Nirvana who, who started Foo Fighters, um, Dave Grohl. Dave Grohl, yes. I saw
an interview with him and Kyle Gass of Tenacious D, you know, Jack Black's buddy. And he was, um,
like, there was, it was like the most eye-opening experience I had about like the levels of
musician because obviously Dave Grohl, seasoned veteran, he, he's a, he's a true pro, but he,
he does like big, you know, rock and stuff. And then Kyle Gass, total hack, total amateur.
He's like a, he's like a professionally, classically trained guitarist, I think, who then
went on to do, yeah. But, um, he, he like, allegedly, he was the one who, what was, I think,
him and Jack Black, when they met, Jack Black taught Kyle Gass, quote, how to act. Kyle taught Jack,
quote, how to play guitar or like something like that. And they, they were formed that thing.
In this interview, though, it was, um, Dave Grohl, I'll see if I can find it because it's
popular. It's a well-known one. Like Dave Grohl's just breaking down. He's like, yeah, like I,
I only write hits. This is what I do. I only write hits because like I just understand what my
audience wants. They want, uh, and he's like, he's just like most white people, they dance to the
lyrics. Like this is, and this is my, like this is what people sell. They dance to the lyrics. What
does that mean? White people dance to the lyrics. And this is the main market. What does that mean?
He's saying that like they don't, like the demographic that most, that consume his music,
they are looking for like catchy, repetitive lyrics that they can get into because this group
does not like vibe with the music the way like, I don't know, probably incongruous to like black
communities or whatever, get into like deep jam, jazzy shit. I don't know, this is the point he was
making. That is so weird. But think about it though. But I kind of get it, but that is such a strange
thought. When he framed it that way, I found that an extremely eye-opening quote. And I was like, I
mean, thinking about like, what, what do I like? I don't know. I went to a concert of fucking, um,
Incubus way back in the day and they're playing like Anna Molly. That song is like
fucking brain blast or heart hitting. It's what I mosh and got punched in the face
while I was dancing to that song. And like, yeah, I mean, I love the rock souls and stuff,
but I definitely see the point he was making. So, so all this is to say, like different people
have different appreciations for like what layers of music and rock songs are like repetitive,
on purpose. They're designed to be that way. So they're kind of like addictive and you want that
big, that big coom, which is a different appreciation from like appreciating a really
well put together like solo that's just instrumental. And I don't know. I mean,
a lot of rock songs have that like the different like the non repetitive and the intricate solo
stuff. Like it's not, it's not like rock can be defined as like one thing. I mean, like prog rock
is getting progressively more jazzy. Like I love Pink Floyd's solos and like crazy diamond and stuff.
So yeah, I get it. But like just for example, for Foo Fighters, those guys, some souls mostly,
you know, what would you describe them? I'm not like, I'm not savvy on all the genre names.
And I might even say, I'm sure people in the comments would know, but like, what would that
I mean, did you could give you a fucking paragraph about it? I'm sure pop grunge or something grunge.
Yeah, pop rock, hard rock, like some no band is any one thing. They're all like a mix and a fusion.
So something in there, but they're not Pink Floyd. They're not snarky puppy, you know, they're
a particular thing they're going for. And it's by design. Dave Grohl's like, yeah, like I'm trying
to be popular and appeal to this demographic. So I construct my songs in this particular way.
And like watching Whiplash, I mean, or anything about jazz, it's funny because like it's,
you know, what it's kind of like, okay, now guys, you're going to understand the point I'm
making. It's like video games. Okay, now my ears, my ears perked up now.
It's like, like jazz music is for basically just like the refined palette. So for guys like me,
I mean, people might like shit on a game like, I don't know, Shantae and the Pirate's Curse
for, I don't know, being too waifu bait, being too blah, blah, blah, whatever. But that game
has incredibly refined and beautiful movement mechanics that like a connoisseur of Metroid
Vanias such as myself finds to be basically the pinnacle. Now other people can prefer exploration,
and there are like specific things that you want to get at different games. Like for example,
I just did a rant on my stream yesterday about how Metal Gear Solid 5 was a catastrophic failure
in many ways, story wise, but the mechanics of that game are so satisfying. And I love just
physically playing it that, you know, there's things to appreciate. So like your jazz is a
more complicated intricate, you have to commit more to it and kind of study it a little bit
to get more out of it. Whereas I don't know, I mean, maybe I'm wrong. Maybe yeah, maybe less so,
I'm sure. But there's definitely jazz I've heard that is like really, really funny and how stupid
it is. And how like people, people like that they're improvising and they're going into weird
keys. They're so weird that it can't possibly be, I can't jive to this, to this noise, you know,
that. Trout Mask replica. That's one of the famous ones by what's his face? She can't remember his
name. Mr. Meat Man. Dizzy Gillespie. Mr. Meat Man. Be Meat. What's that fucking guy's name? It's
Captain Beefheart. Captain Beefheart aka Mr. Meat Man. Same guy.
But like, I feel like there's this, it's like with a lot of things, like the more like, quote
unquote, intricate and difficult and like skilled you need to be to play a certain thing, or to
like the, you know, the more brain cells you need to appreciate Rick and Morty, like the more
elitist people get about it being gooder than the things that they used to like, which were less
good. And I just want to say that jazz is fucking sick. But that doesn't mean that pop music isn't
and rock music isn't. It's just all good if you like it. Indeed. It's good if you like it. It's
good if you like it, but please listen to Wolfpac. If you, if you'll know if you like it once you
listen to Dean Town, you're like, you know, if you're bopping your head and you're twitching your
toes, then you should probably see a doctor. How do you, how do you feel about like songs that I
would consider like earworms? Like you hate them, but like, ah, you can't stop listening to them or
like, you know, you like them and you can't stop listening to them to the point where you hate them.
Eh, it is what it is. There have been those. Well, you know, I, well, you know, I love Avril Lavigne.
Who doesn't? There have been those like. There was this song recently that I was, that was earworms
back into my brain from like a few years ago by Alicia Dixon or something, which is like,
uh, does he brush up? No, he doesn't brush up. Does he clean up? No, he doesn't clean up.
Does he wash up? Does he wash up? He does nothing. The boy does nothing. It's just like a really
annoying song about her complaining about her, how her boyfriend is stinky. And it was really,
it was really popular for a little bit there. And I, I just remembered it. I was like, oh god,
not her, not that, not that stupid song. That sucks. It fucking sucks.
Doesn't gaslight her. He just body gas, you know, with like his odor.
He just, he just regular gas aside. Oh god, Holocaust joke. I'm not going to make it.
Somebody else's making sleeping gas, but okay, fair enough. I don't think a laughing gas, because
it's funny. Yeah, yeah. But like that got in my head and it was annoying for a bit, but it doesn't,
it didn't really stay because I don't know. I had the music in my, in my periphery to listen to.
I was talking to a, I was talking to a friend yesterday and I'm not going to say who,
but they might be listening, they might be listening to this right now.
Hello, this unnamed friend.
I'm sure they'll be mortified, so I apologize for that, but your secret's safe. And this person was,
this person was telling me about some of their, some of their, some of their personal problems,
about some of their, some of their life. And I said, you know, I think this is literally the plot
of an Avril Lavigne song. So now I understand it and Ken Relay. It was, it was, it was, it was,
it was, they were literally describing what is being described in the lyrics of complicated.
I was just listening to that song the other day for personal reasons.
It's a good, it's a good fucking song. I'll stand by it. I will stand by complicated.
I was hoping you were going to say Skater Voight. Now that's, no, I wish.
No, they were literally, this is literally the plot of that kakakakawaii song.
It's just about loving Hello Kitty, which we all relate to, of course.
Speaking of Hello Kitty.
Yeah, speaking of Hello Kitty.
Oh, Maja's cat, the star of the show.
He likes to announce when he arrives. What can I do?
I'm home, Luigi, I'm home, he says.
Big dick is back in town.
Is there a name, his name Lulu?
Lullaby, but Lulu for short.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
That was close. I got it. I got it.
I got it.
Didn't Digi have a cat called Lala?
After Lala from Inuyasha. Yeah.
Lala was, okay.
So I think I famously railed against Lala in the Sonichu lecture, right?
There were a lot of comments for a while being like, why is he yelling at the cat?
Answer, because I mean, answer, because I need my fucking personal space.
But Lala is like, Lala is the best cat that I've ever lived with.
And the reason why, I wouldn't want a cat.
But if I got one, I would want it to be like Lala.
I could, I could deal with it because Lala just fucked off.
Lala didn't, you didn't need to feed Lala.
She just like, she just like hung out outside, climbed on the roof, hunted her own food,
didn't eat you for anything.
Hunted her own food too? Wow. Okay.
Yes. Yes. She, there was a, she like, she caught a flying squirrel out of the air.
And then, and then ripped it in half and left it on the back porch.
Wait, did you see this happen?
I did not see it happen, but did you said that he had seen it happen?
I think, and I definitely, and I saw the corpse.
I saw the corpse that she had left.
Right out of the air. She jumped from the ground.
First I saw it in trade-off.
Then I came back later and saw the same corpse torn in half to him.
Lala was great, except for when she wouldn't fucking leave me alone in the lecture.
She liked you.
Do you not like, do you not like cats, like coming close?
I don't mind it particularly.
I mean, during the lecture, we need to walk around.
You're trying to do something, you know?
You don't want your, your, I mean, I remember the cat was on my future.
I mean, I mean, I'm trying to pace around.
I'm trying to pace around the space and Lala was in the way.
So I had to say, get that cat out of here.
That's perfectly-
Otherwise you're going to crunch on its tail.
Yeah. And who wants that?
Uh, Luna, my cat is extremely, like, uh, right up in your, in your face.
And no matter who you are, no matter if they're, if you're a stranger,
Sixton was over at my house just today.
He was visiting UK and he was like, hey, can I come over for an afternoon?
I was like, yeah, stay the night.
And, uh, like the, the cat, like, instantly was like, oh, yeah, cool.
There's a person, like I'm not in any way scared.
And I'm like, you're going to be in trouble if you ever meet like a nasty person outside.
Cause you just, you're just too trusting.
You're too pure, you're too innocent.
You go up to them, you, you per immediately, you're too nice.
And she doesn't even like struggle if you pick her up.
You know, if I, if I was a supervillain, I could pick her up
and put her in a vat of boiling lava and she wouldn't even realize what was going on.
You know, we, um, so we got some new downstairs neighbors
cause I live in a duplex and, um, the bottom half of the duplex was empty for a little while
cause the old, the old people moved out.
But, um, uh, we got some, we got some new ones, like maybe a month and a half ago.
And it is, it's three, it's three people.
There's like a husband and a wife and another guy who I guess is their friend or something.
And, uh, they have a cat.
The cat's name is queen.
I saw the cat one time.
She seemed fine.
Yes, queen.
And like the, the wife and the friend seem like perfectly fine.
They're perfectly friendly.
They don't see him that much.
But when we do, it's like, Hey, the husband seems like the biggest fucking dick.
The husband is an asshole.
Like the husband will complain about noise at like when we're not even doing anything weird
and at a time that is not even like late and not, and like not even disruptive or anything.
Like we were working out in the basement.
We were working out in the basement at like six or seven PM, right?
So like, you know, yeah, the way, the way it's hitting the ground and like he comes down and is
like, Hey, I've really, you know, you guys need to keep it down down here.
And he like, he came up another time on like a Saturday night at like maybe like 10 30 PM.
And was like, some of us, some of us have work in the morning or something.
I mean, I get it, but what are the, I mean, you live in a shared space.
I mean, and then, and then another time I was coming out the door.
I was coming out the door like 10 PM on a Saturday.
Come on. That's not, that's not crazy.
And like I'm coming out the door and he's there.
I think he's like taking the garbage out or something and he's coming in and I give him,
I give him like a very friendly, I'm like, Hey, what's going, how are you doing?
And he like does not make no eye contact, like deliberately avoids looking at me.
Maybe this is a one time thing.
And he was just at that moment occupied in his brain or something possibly maybe.
None of us, none of us have any, no, but none of us that live here
have had any good experiences with that guy.
Fair enough.
He's bad news.
He's a troublemaker.
We have to, we have to roll him up in a blank and then throw him off the bridge is what I'm saying.
That's the right move.
At least he's in a blank.
At least we know, we know, we know what we have to do.
Ben, that's it.
That's my story.
Okay. Well, Ben, I have something I wanted to share with you, Ben.
I think you'll appreciate it and everyone else will too.
You know, I mentioned Metroidvanias earlier.
There was a new kid on the block when it comes to Metroidvanias.
I've only dabbled a little bit.
I played a little bit this morning, but I've been very interested for a long time.
Okay.
Cast your gaze on a couple of these images that I'm posting here.
This is from a game called blasphemous.
And basically the Orthodox boys.
Oh my God.
It's time to assemble.
Our time has come.
It's time to praise God and lash ourselves.
Okay.
So this game.
This looks wicked cool.
It is incredibly cool.
Look like a big boy.
Okay.
Just, just look at it.
Look at it.
I'm posting an image right here.
This is after you beat the first boss, the beginning of the game.
So here's what you do.
Is he a big boy?
He looks like a big boy.
He's, he's a normally sized human.
He's not particularly large.
But he fights boys that are real big.
Wait, is this from the, is this the new from software?
No.
It's by these guys, I want to say 17th street studios.
This is their first game, I believe.
So they're, they're new kids on the block with a lot to prove.
You're getting some press and I've been liking it so far.
Funny note.
Like I've seen this before, but only once on my Twitter timeline when someone was calling him daddy.
Okay.
I mean, he's pretty daddy.
He's authoritative.
I could see him, you know, be in my new dad, pleasing my mom the way she has been pleased.
And since dad died, I look forward to that.
But this is so, so here's the scoop lads.
So you start off this game.
You're in a pile of these guys, whatever you get up and you keep going.
You've got this cool cone head.
Never fear everybody.
It's not a KKK thing.
This is like a Spanish church thing.
Don't freak out.
Let me put your mind in the use about the whole about the KKK question.
The KKKQ.
Oh, that's the one.
So this guy, he's going, he does swordsman things, whatever.
Okay.
This is like the most Orthodox Catholic shit.
It's he's called the penitent one.
And it's all about experiencing pain for your sins.
So the first thing you do is you go and you fight a boss.
Yeah.
You strike him down as like a big giant guy.
You cut him open.
Okay.
You see how he's got this big bucket helmet on like he's got a normal head under that.
He takes it off.
He can't see his face.
He fills it up with the blood of the boss that he just like he fills the whole thing up.
And then he goes, he puts it on over his head and he just filled with blood.
He just thought this was the right move to make.
I don't know why.
I assume it's like beneficial in some way.
Is this you haven't you haven't told me anything about the game.
Is it a 2D sidescrolling metroidvania?
It's a metroidvania a la like by way of Dark Souls.
It's it's got like estus flask shit.
It's got it's very much like Hollow Knight or Dark Souls.
Hollow Knight is pretty embarrassing.
This blood thing is a very red man-esque thing.
I think red man might review this game.
Him and red man they should and him and red man would be best friends.
Is it out or is it just it's out?
It's out everywhere.
It's yeah.
I was playing it this morning.
There was a demo.
It's it's out.
I mean it's a metroidvania.
I've only played maybe like an hour or two maybe.
It's super duper fun.
I love it so far.
I can't speak that it's great.
Apparently it's reasonably short, but it's just so orthodox.
So like everything you do is about how like your sinners need to harm yourself and lash
yourself and bleed the blood to praise.
I mean it's not specifically like Catholic.
It's like kind of pseudo non-shit and I'm not actually religious.
But the aesthetic is sick.
So this looks so fucking cool.
It is.
I'm watching the trailer right now.
Yeah.
It's it's dope as hell.
So I've been loving it.
I think everybody how much how much on steam.
Shit.
You know I don't know.
I think I paid 20 bucks.
Let me see.
Blast 20.
I bought it on Switch.
But fuck it.
I'll wait till it goes on sale.
Good plan.
I'm just curious how much fucking was this thing.
I don't even know.
I just knew I wanted it.
It might have been like 30 40 bucks.
And so I can't I can't remember.
Okay.
It doesn't matter.
Point is I felt it was worth it and I've been very much enjoying it.
And I knew you'd be into it based on the scene based on the visuals.
But I mean yeah.
Feel free to wait for it to go on sale or whatever.
That's it.
That's my game recommendation for the day.
Looks dope.
This is not a full review people.
Just letting you know.
I played like an hour but it looks dope.
All right.
That's me.
Excellent.
Blast on this.
We could go to voice.
Shit.
I'm just throwing it out there.
We could do it if we wanted to.
I mean I guess.
I got one more thing to talk about.
Sure.
Let me find the image.
I have been drawing like on stream draw streams.
Those are still going well.
Every every weekday on on twitch.tv slash give and take.
If you if you want to see me draw something.
I've split it up now.
Now I'm doing a rendering study on Fridays.
And this is the first one.
Turns out turned out pretty good.
I think it's quite a big image.
Oh yeah.
I saw that before.
You literally cut out for me.
I didn't hear what you said.
Oh.
Oh did you draw that?
I drew it.
That's so good.
Yeah.
I was I was really proud of it.
From scratch.
Anything like that before.
Look at the lighting on the hand.
From scratch.
No.
I mean I was copying images but I was trying to get the.
Yeah.
From scratch.
Oh that's so cool.
The hand was actually like one layer.
I forgot to have layers on the hand.
I just kept like adding like like low opacity like airbrush.
I like the depth of field as well for the hand.
That's how you like the finger furthest away is so blurred.
You can see that like the light is kind of coming through the skin.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh that's amazing.
It's advanced.
These are advanced techniques.
You suddenly I didn't expect when you got here.
Yeah I mean I didn't expect to be like I'd never really
sat down and tried this.
I've done paintings before.
I've done like stuff like this in school.
But like it's really just it's you know you look at it and you're like what does it look like.
It doesn't look like that.
Let's change it here and change it there.
And yeah.
Yeah.
No layers are for pussy.
Draw a close up in this style of pump's face.
I want to see those pumpkin seeds.
I want to see that candle in there.
I want to see it all.
Her seed she's she doesn't have seeds.
She's she's a pure maiden.
Or maybe just do it next time.
Whoa.
I made a slime mead version.
Oh that's so good.
That feel and touch slime.
I choked on my spit a little bit.
This is like Earth of a Slime Boy.
This image literally Adam touching God you know zero BC or whatever.
Yeah this is a this is a branching timeline actually.
There's like two things that could happen.
He could have had an apple or he could have had slime.
This man went for slime.
That's the difference between Dimension 1218 and Dimension C197.
There it is.
Magichan does not take the threat of slime seriously.
No.
Okay but it will be to his ruin right because when the dimensions merge right
the slime boys are gonna they're gonna be out in the forest right.
I don't know.
I don't know if they can stuff you know Chris is so confident that all the
soniches and him and and and all the her and all the deities and whatever all the
fucking superheroes that are gonna like they think they think they can stop the slime but
I mean I don't know I guess we'll see.
Did you see I mean that big I for one am terrified about you know coming back from the
the there was a there was a big I believe it was like a four page like Twitter story.
It might have been on Chris's it might have been on Magichan's I'm looking right now to see
if I can find yeah I was I was just okay that's where that Magichan announced that he has physically
come to dimension 1218.
Right right okay okay I'm with you.
And that the purple blurs him.
I mean in that it was described that the I mean maybe this is already known but that
they are I believe the word omniscient was used and so I mean I assume that they're there
seems pretty confident that slime is not going to be a hassle but I mean I don't know.
Yeah well better better men than the Magichan soniches have fallen to the slime.
Indeed indeed don't underestimate it.
Also here here's a red man image just to show you the the breadth of my artistic abilities
I can do it I can do this guy I can do this hand and I can do that hand.
He's pointing at himself the little red man at the top I love it.
Yeah this is another one you could do oh yes point oh you could have another one of this
this Adam hand reaching out to touch red man's finger.
Oh my god.
Pokey poke finger on finger action.
That's uh you know red man's looking pretty kawai right here.
Yeah he's he's a cute boy.
I was I was thinking of having him be like like the the the bottom right like character on screen
for like I don't know a review show but I but I wouldn't make the review show I just wanted
to draw a red man as if he were.
Yeah do do a like you know one minute long review of Blasphemous by red man and just have to be
like this is the most bloody game ever I love it it's like fuck Bloodborne.
Oh I was going to say fuck Bloodborne that's pussy blood shit Blasphemous.
Now now we're talking real blood amounts and uh it's great it's great.
And he's pointing at it and he said there it is.
There's blood.
I love it.
There's the blood.
I can see some.
He's his famous catchphrase there's blood.
There's blood.
Everybody loves him.
I will get blood.
Fuck yeah.
All right let's go to Boys Nails.
Let's yeah.
I mean great art everybody take a look.
Look at all those look at Blasphemous look at Kickstarter.
I'm still watching this slime.
I'm just watching it flow.
It's a peaceful image.
It fills me with joy.
Makes me hungry.
I just want to put my mouth at the bottom of this stream of slime.
It's just like right below the cutoff of the image is me with my mouth open.
All right well you know what I did and that's canon.
I prepared like 10 voicemails.
They were of decent quality.
They're all they're all something to appreciate.
So let's just jump into those and we can we can take our time.
Uh yeah all right so let's go.
Speak pipe link people down below.
Leave us voicemails.
Good stuff.
And let's start off with um eat my entire ass with a voicemail.
Let's jump into it.
Here we go.
Go.
So I've been doing some thinking.
What is the autism power level of the PCP?
We have the obvious choice being Davoo who we all know as like a
thing he's said himself that is autistic or people have said so.
But do um like what is the ranking?
Who is the most autistic?
I think a lot of people might want to put themselves at the top.
But as a person who not me autistic people or autistic people
are constantly around autistic people I feel like I'm a bit of an expert myself.
And I just want to point out one thing bigger than any other thing that the
most autistic person in the PCP is Nate.
Yeah that's it.
That's it.
I mean what good is that without an explanation of why?
He did not give an I guess we're supposed to fill in the blank.
He says he's an expert but then he provides no no that's lame.
That's lame dude call back and tell me why.
Yeah I do want to know why.
I do want an explanation.
Give me a point by point.
I'm not going to assume it's because Ha Ha Nate likes numbers and being
correct and making sure the facts are straight all the time.
No no no no you don't he doesn't deserve he doesn't deserve to have you go and attribute
all these like facts and logic to what he said.
No failure.
That's fair that's fair.
As for as for who has the most autism it's clearly DigiD.
I mean I was thinking I thought he was going to go straight.
It's clearly DigiD bro.
I mean Digi identifies as autistic.
Diboo is more autistic than Digi.
I don't think I don't this might be a hot take.
I don't think Digi is as autistic as he thinks he is.
I mean he's made it kind of an identity at this point.
So you know it's just a it's just a meme.
Yeah it's a meme.
All right whatever let us know details if you can provide that sir.
Well I mean he did eat that shit.
Sorry.
You know he ate that that non autistic person's shit and he became less autistic remember that.
Oh the whole yeah the whole you know even though even though that study was maybe
found to be like it was not like substantiated enough.
Who's who's shitted he it's a it's a it doesn't matter it doesn't matter it doesn't move on.
I really don't want to know.
Okay great because we got Clyde Caliber here with another voicemail actually his first
voicemail probably okay go Clyde take it away.
So PCP I was just trying to think a good question.
I didn't come up with one.
I was wondering what's like canonically on that disc you know the TPC logo.
There's a disc there.
What the hell's on it.
I don't know you have Digi's secret hentai stash or some shit.
Maybe it's the theme song.
Wait what the theme song.
Yeah one mp3 of yes no I I always thought of it as like
um like whatever is on that disc is like I forgot to burn this disc it's empty.
I procrastinated on it.
Oh I like that an empty disc uh yeah that needs to be filled with data and information.
That sounds good which represents you the audience need to be filled with our
information are useless worth this trash.
Yes it represents you even though it is literally representing us.
That's correct that's correct.
Sounds like as good an explanation as any.
Perhaps DaVoo could provide more insight but uh it's open to interpretation.
Okay we got Smyrg now this was it was specified this is for Munchy but Munchy who knows and
Munchy's gonna be back because he's a busy boy with school and all that stuff.
Yes he did say about school taking up all his time.
Figured we might as well you know play it now because who knows when that'll happen so
okay here we go Smyrg go.
Howdy Smyrg here with a basic ask question welcome so tell me about keeping motivation
on long-term creative projects.
In my experience I'll have an idea for a project I'll dive way into it and burn
pretty much all of my free time for next two weeks maybe a month at most fully devoted to
the project at which point I seem to always hit a wall where I either become more interested
in pursuing a new project idea or just burn myself out completely and need a break.
So how do you avoid this?
Does it happen to you?
You feeling me on it?
Okay see ya.
Okay I was thinking about this I mean first of all I'm terrible at this I'm terrible at
maintaining motivation over a long term um literally literally the thing to do the thing
the way to do it is to make it as not long term as possible.
Yes true and to get it done as fast as you possibly can at any cost.
Just do what I'm currently doing with the Minecraft server right now do nothing else
with your life absolutely nothing that that sometimes works depending on what you got.
No I agree like when I um yeah because then it gets done that's how you get it done the fastest
right well what about I mean sometimes sometimes I wish sometimes I wish that like I didn't do
anything else sometimes I kind of I'm like oh god I wish I didn't have to like have friends in real
life or do like twitch streams or do or record the pcp or do anything else and then I could just
turn off the internet and have literally nothing to do except like work on something for like
how many weeks it took. Strike while there and talk, do what you can, do what you want to.
Like everything else in my life would suffer but like I could I could I would be faster at
achieving like the one thing that like I'm focused that I want to get done next you know.
I don't know I disagree generally with with all that like I mean the idea of burnout is that
you're forcing yourself to do a certain amount in your mind you're like oh I've got to do this
and if you slip up and don't feel like doing it one day then you crumble and die and then it
becomes difficult to get back on the horse. I think um I mean I'm not like an expert either
but like I haven't lost motivation for the things I'm doing even though they're just coming along
very slowly because I'm not like forcing myself to get so much of it done um every day like I have
a reasonable expectation of myself. I have a lot of things planned but like the thing that makes me
like die the most is when I have a lot of free time and I have a like a choice of things to do
and I just don't know how to choose. That's rough yeah yeah yeah that that gets me more more so than
like um you know having trouble starting is like having trouble choosing so make the choices ahead
of time yeah and if you don't do them then doesn't matter you know you had your allocated time to
draw a page of this uh you failed but at least you know when you're supposed to next to do it
and it's like at least you know what you failed at yeah instead of just feeling like this vague
like sense of like you are gonna die one day and you haven't drawn a million things and you're not
Hayao Miyazaki and I'm like ah shut up you know not everybody can be Mozart it's too hard.
We should uh we should remember probably that I don't know exactly what Smirks working on
necessarily obviously I know Smirks are great art boy but um the uh like Smirks sent me a bunch of
um art rfck stickers. Give me one I want one so bad. She designed um have you seen them it's just
it's like a cute little graphic of like endless yeah endless war endless war in the middle.
It's so cool. And then you can see Rowdy Rowdy Rough House in Cobb Kilt Town. I want to see it.
I've been I've been going around I've been sticking them on. Yo put a picture up for the
links. People need to see this shit. Oh they're great. I don't shit. I have to find the digital
image. Um yeah um I stuck I stuck them around like Medford and I stuck them on like Tufts and
stuff but I was gonna stick them in downtown because we were downtown yesterday for Munchie's
birthday but I forgot to bring them but whatever. I'll um I'll um I'll get them um and yeah she
sent me like hundreds of them and I mean I cut a bunch of them out and I've been I was gonna
I want I want okay I want to sell them but not for a profit just so just to like cover the costs
of production because I just I want people to have like extremely easy because I want people
I want these in the hands of like everybody yeah yeah I want everybody who likes this shit
to have just to have like really easy and cheap access so they can stick them fucking everywhere
and I'll say again there's there's one thing because we've already had just from like the
couple ones that we've already had people join the server just from seeing these stickers around
that's great that that's perfect and the one thing you guys should definitely fix I believe on
these stickers it has the discord URL at the bottom right uh in the yeah like across the middle
you guys gotta get a fucking address that's easy to type in just so that people don't get scared
off by letters and numbers and stuff I think that would do a lot personally well we I mean
there's like slime.com or whatever that that takes you to the discord like you buy the url
like slime okay well slime.com is we look into custom urls and what if though
instead of that you get a qr code you get a qr code for that link I have a qr code for um yeah
that's good to server it's good to uh I mean the the sticker would have to be redesigned
there's a shirt actually you can buy a shirt with literally just the qr code it's like a black shirt
in like a lime green like fluorescent just like the qr code for the server is just the entire shirt
damn I like I kind of want one of those that's pretty sick it's pretty sick actually I think it
looks it actually looks good yeah sure sure um uh what was I gonna say oh oh and so I was gonna say
just to just to get back on uh Smirks question here um sorry I'm just writing this down so we
don't forget I was I was gonna say so Smirks question about motivation whatnot was originally
was directed at Munchy so I think the implication was like Munchy with his like doing rfck stuff
seems like the target thing so like and that experience is kind of different from what we
were talking about up to this point because the nature of endless war and stuff is like
like it's an it's intended to be like a long-term ongoing thing that like even if you like do all
the work and make your primary focus just buy the nature of that project you don't really want it to
like be all done now you want it to take a while to like you know be rolled out and blah blah blah
do stuff you want to you want to have like events that people can participate in and
all that stuff so with something like that I've really like never done something like that
but I would say like that that uses a skill that I'm terrible at I want to do what these guys were
saying my instinct I want to forget everything just do one project as I said a million times
yeah that's like that would be like the the ideal like just eat raw sugar just eat raw salt like
pleasure nodes in my brain activating not best way to operate in life but really it's a nice it's
a nice idea I feel like though I'm not the idea of like a bad way to live but I'm just saying to
work on exactly exclusively one thing it's like a very childish idea because you think it like
binary like you're doing this and then you're doing that one or the other life is really
complicated and there's always things that come up there's like there's like there's the bills to pay
there's the dentist appointment there's the there's there's all sorts of things that get in the way
of stuff but what is it bad and so it's you have to you have to like plan like make a plan but then
put like areas in that plan where things can go wrong but it's still okay yeah because like you
know have days where you you don't have anything to do um like weekends are a good time where you're
like uh it's clear on the weekend and then during the weekday you have very regimented clear cut
what you're supposed to do at the time I mean it doesn't have to be like this hour you need to do this
but like a general like goal for the day is easy to get you started and then you can you can juggle
multiple projects at once like like alternating which day you're doing it on and you can still have
time for like oh in the like a like a flight of fancy sort of idea hits you and you have time on the
weekend to work on that if you want to you know you're not you're not like the the the thing that
really gets me sometimes is when I'm working on a project and this idea comes into my head like I
watch a video and now I want to make videos or something and I'm like damn it this is ruined
everything I'm trying to focus on this thing I'm trying to do and all these great ideas are coming
to me and I got to ignore them I got to throw them away I got to like jot them down for later maybe
but like your brain doesn't work like that sometimes you just want to just want to go all
loopy loo and like explore these cool ideas you have and you got to have you got to have time for that
it's true it's true yep I was just freaking out because I was looking for smirks uh sticker art
and I found this I had not seen this one before but she made a bunch you made a bunch of these
too the the cards you know like the redesigned um cards for slime poker oh yeah and I saw the
ace and I saw the ace of killers I think is the the ace of shields and it's so beautiful oh yeah
I'm gonna fucking cry it's so good can you link to them in some ways so we can look at like a bunch
if they exist uh collection yeah yeah well here's a here's a there a bunch of them are tagged on the
rfck wiki as rfck arts like rfc oh yeah cards um I don't like I don't know if all of them are here
but okay well that's pretty good yeah uh okay these look like uh the ones smirk made mine
some of these are yours some of some of mine are there yeah are our name missing
uh doesn't look like it no it looks like all of them okay I'm talking about this link I'm scrolling
okay there's a bunch all right dope check those out let's go to our next voicemail though uh let me
see this one's from where the heck did this go all right here we go this is from craters with
pancakes uh short and sweet okay go quick a gun to your head what's your favorite
that's the correct response to when you ask that question instantly instantly deceased
no fully cool the last time I tried to answer this and I said I couldn't think of one and someone in
the comp fuck I was someone I know in the comments might have been marron pan I don't know it was
someone I recognized in the comments it was like dude ben I know your favorite anime is fully cool
you said it a million times I was like oh my god he's right I forgot my own favorite anime
maybe it was I'm sorry it's stupid I know but Karakano Karakano is really Karikul
curry kano that's I'm not hungry thanks for asking uh all right let's go to the next
did you did you see yeah you guys watch um Brian David Gilbert on polygon I don't think so no
he's done some pretty good videos for polygon I like his I like his shit um he did a video
recently I don't think it's as good as his old ones but it's like I made all 78 recipes you can make
in um sky not skyward sword um oh yeah yeah I saw that floating around what do you think was it
interesting it's all right uh it's pretty good it's not his best I think his best one is here's my
best one is probably the one about like the mega man robot masters that one's pretty excellent did the
did the cooking one reveal no no the one about the the one about the kingdom hearts the one about
the kingdom hearts like story structure is really funny okay fair enough did this by any chance I'm
curious about the cooking did that reveal that the mechanic is relatively shallow and that there's only
so much point in doing it I'm just curious if that was the conclusion no not really it's basically
just it's just goofy and like it's like man the recipe for the recipe for this like pink like
healing drink is like watermelon radish and a dragon fruit and milk so let's just like put those
four things in a blender and blend them and just drink it and like see if it's any good or whatever
oh I see I see but the thing that stood out to me most about the video is that he grew a mustache
and he needs to not have a mustache anymore he needs to get his old swoopy hair back he had
really cool hair for a while there see if you can grab the link to that for the show no sure but
okay let's let's move on to our next voicemail this one's calling out bge rot row okay go calling out
Nate vestman can you please never make a weyagawa promise on the pcp
ever again thank you also starting those lock next month well uh maybe i'll do that uh we
i constantly fail these it's true and i have loosened my schedule i've i've determined that
weagawa's being strictly weekly is not the best you gotta you gotta under promise and over
delivery that's exactly that's exactly right even if you deliver a ton if you promise more it's a
mistake it's a mistake okay duly noted you got a chief gonna do my best all right moving on thick
spanish accent boy okay go hello pcp first of thanks tom and thanks mate for your contribution
with the university paper i passed it on as you welcome so now to my actual voicemail
personal drama but it pays off i saw around six years ago i was in a very dark place in my life
and at that time i decided hey going to japan we will surely solve all of my problems in life you
know so flash forward to nowadays and i sorted my entire life i got a university degree i got a
wonderful girlfriend tons of friends a job it came to the point that i applied just for the
lowest to a university scholarship to go to japan for four months but here is the problem i actually
got the fucking money i got the scholarship they are they are sending me to japan for four months
but i already sorted my life so why should i go there i am not quite sure what i even
applied for this scholarship even more so i i don't even know japanese the only japanese i know
it's from the fucking hentai i have watched in my life so i don't know i might be tired for doing
this i i am going to die i'm going to die right i'm going to die so wait so he applied for this
scholarship and then like years later they get back to him like hey we're sending you to that thing
but like no i think i think it was i think it was like he he he didn't get it the first time
or then or something but then he after he sorted his life out he just sort of like as a joke applied
again and he got it possibly and everyone knows the only reason to go to japan is to have a character
arc development and to progress because you're at the end it's a complete waste of time uh i i don't
see what the problem is like it's only four months you can go have a cool experience and then you'll
have that to add to your repertoire of things you can say you did we all know going to japan if
it's covered i mean it's gonna be fun it's gonna be dope well i mean i i think so but like i mean
i think he would probably have to like quit his job to go away for four months uh huh wait he said
university did he say he has a job he said he said job yeah he said he's got a job well shit
stuff like i mean he would have to like he would have to like put his life on hold i mean he'll
probably be away from his girlfriend for the four months if nothing else i mean that's that you
know kind of a downside well i mean if if everything will go to shit if you leave for four months and
just don't leave is that yeah not possible if that's the issue then that's an understandable reason
to to bail but now do you have to do it are you like committed to it no no but i think he's like
you know he'd like to do it but yeah now it would fuck up everything else four months is a long time
but i i you can go so you can you can make if you've got like if you've got your shit sorted
out you can fucking go to japan another time i was there for shit what was it i want to say
and it sounds like he doesn't even care about japan itself right sounds like he's not even like
it's not like he's like oh i've always wanted to go to japan he just like signed up for this
thing like pretty much at random it basically well is the impression that i get did i forget
how i want to say i was there for two months am i wrong about that i feel like it was two months
and it was a great time and i mean for me like me that's when i had my character arc development
so you're a little past that but there's always room to grow and seeing a new place is always a
good idea if it doesn't totally fuck up your life 100 go you will not regret it it doesn't matter
if you know zero japanese because everything there is designed there's english everywhere
people will help they all speak a tiny bit of english they're not great at it but you'll be fine
you'll be fine go fucking go unless it ruins your life that's this is the one island the cat island
the deer like exactly yeah go to all the animal life oh incredible go to neat uh what's the word
weeb uh uh valhalla uh akihabara go see everything go to the shops and go to that go to that fucking
thing i always talk about those little off the beaten path curry restaurants where you put your
quarters in your fucking yen tokens your hundred yen coins in outside you go beep boop boop on the
thing outside then walk in and the single guy who's running the thing brings you the best curry in the
world that's that's i dream of it every day go live it for me street ramen that's that's good you
to get yaki street takoyaki i would get so often if i went to japan i would actually be pretty excited
to try like street ramen hell yeah dude it's fucking great i would i would break kito just for that
oh wow damn i know that's that's heavy all right let's move on to our next one we've got
che givara's ghost calling in thank god another boy had a commie hell this guy doesn't like let's see
what he has to say for us go hola americones yo soy che givara yama desde el inferno comunista
i just want to say us in communist hell are very big fans of uh the pcp but whatever you do
do not let those melcones the castor melcones onto your fucking podcast
other than that i just like to say then say it uh you're a big hero in let's see communist hell
yeah much kudos to you yes yes i'd also like to say we definitely need to get those t-shirts down
here we would all wear them we would all hang out with satan once he gets verified he can wipe the
t-shirt too uh it'll be it'll be glorious in communist hell yes uh i can't wait for everybody
the next christian that actually should be interesting when we hear about that and i really
hope that magichan does not take over the world that would be most unfortunate for all the communist
anyways uh fuck all of you uh go die so you can come join us in communist hell this is che givara
all right thanks che good to hear from you buddy um um i wait which which shirt is he talking about
uh shit i think it's the i'm just being cool and the um it wasn't the main no wasn't wasn't there
a specific one that we joked about making last oh shit i can't remember i think you're right uh
i can't remember it was probably i am a commune yeah that's probably it uh uh uh che givara's
ghost you're gonna be really we should have a shirt that says ask me about my 20 million murdered
or you know some shit like that wait are you 20 million what murdered or you know 20 million
starved whatever it's all good no no don't um don't make that it's i'm it's it's i'm just throwing
the means of production i'm just season the means of production okay i like that um um
che givara's ghost you're gonna be are you excited for when i for the stretch goal for the vapor's
to kick starter where i make communism real and redistribute the well he's gotta be are you
fucking excited do you think i'm fucking excited if the dimensional merge happens does that include
hell merging with the rest of you know everything else does is that i don't think i doubt it because
i gotta imagine that hell is not is it in our dimension hell and heaven must be their own
dimensions okay yeah it's the dimensional merge is only between dimension c197 dimension
128 it's just these two particular ones that are do you know why these particular two of all of
them is there a what's uh what's the that's a group that's a good question and no i i don't know
i don't know why chris we don't i don't know what's causing this could use your buddy uh
chris call in to the voicemail please leave a link in the description that would then explain why
why are these two dimensions merging i know that they are merging but i do not understand why this
is happening why am i seeing these weird purple blurs everywhere that i know in my heart of hearts
our magic chan sonichu what if it's just mage who's developed super speed and she's just dashing
about everywhere uh you know there's the blue blur i mean i pray that that's what it is
okay let's move on we got uh okay this one's weird it's like they use some weird fonts it's like
dania dianaya it's got like umlats and shit dania i don't know whatever okay go i want to see how
hey did anybody else notice how before when you used to write pcp and youtube the actual pcp showed
up now when you do that just because joe rogan became kind of more relevant every time you see
joe fucking rogan talk to joe rogan go eat a banana dick or something did he did he did he take our
spot on the youtube algorithm i gotta do a search right now i'm gonna go now i have a little i always
search like the procrastinators podcast to find pcb stuff because when you just search pcp which i'm
doing right now my first you get this bike slam thing i mean okay i'm logged in as me so i get like
the pcb lectures on my channel and stuff but a couple down i get the yellow episode which is our
most popular episode of the pcb the virginity cast ben's lectures up there the other lecture
steven universe for some reason is pretty high weird fetishes oh but oh i scroll down and then i
see everlast tells a pcp story uh joe rogan clip or whatever maybe that's the one he's talking about
but then there's a gallon of pcp from the whitest kids you know that's a good one that's a classic
and then they were actually talking about that's been there for a lot or for a while this one always
pops up it's pcb fenciladine whatever it's called what you need to know by the drug classroom i always
see that one up top i don't know okay whatever yeah so feel free to google so vice lands beating us
right now i see the lectures doing pretty well but we do need to seize the means of search results
so let's let's do that immediately uh okay moving on we got two more we got two more this is um okay
now this is called get me out of here but i can tell it's the teen cp calling in the individual
known as oh not only has teen cp and also the manager and runner of teen cp uh calling let's
see what he has to say good go day to log in the voice jail day fuck i don't know at this point
it's been so long i was trying to scratch the days into that wall but they took my knife away after
the whole epstein ordeal yeah nine eleven breakout efforts have been futile my monty plan's been
thwarted he hasn't been on either of the last two teen cp episodes he must have found me out somehow
i can't even get help from my own teen listeners has without munchie they've been tricked into not
watching three thousand people could easily overpower some boom of chair walls sure but not three i need
something anything please pcp has joined the teen cp ranks and get me the hell out of here
oh how the mighty have fallen teen cp locked away in the deepest darkest dungeon of the jail
yep there's no coming back for you your your munchie god has abandoned you your your zoomer
audience turns out they were as flighty as i predicted and they're not in for the long haul
i think you better you're gonna be in there until you are a boomer until you've aged up out of
zoom oh no the worst we'll let you out when you're one of us exactly ha ha suffer died teen cp
now we play the waiting game see you in uh i think they're like 13 or something so we'll see you in
like what what's boomer age like 20 25 i don't know i think 20 yeah you turn 20 or you're a boomer
we'll let you out in seven months munchie's only got one year left he just turned 19 that's right
he's almost over the hill it's he's gonna have that uh you know uh uh kids next door thing where he
either decides to be a secret agent for the kids when he goes for the zoomers when he hits that
codename kids next door yeah yeah or man that's some zoomer core i fucking love codename kids next
door although isn't that more boomery because it was when we were kids you watched it right it was my
channel no i mean like like the idea is that like being young is it's like so much better than even
like slightly being old so true so true the worst of all are the teenagers you know the just past
the age they're the ones who really need to burn uh but that is the zoomer so well i don't know i
guess there's infighting and what are the zoomers feel about the codename kids next door once you're
13 at least the adults have like a purpose right the teenagers are just they're just they believe
in nothing they're just agents of chaos they're probably voting biden because it's the safe middle
option they're the worst yeah you ever think about how like potentially like generations quote on
quote of people are gonna be like colloquially like shorter and shorter like if if you're a boomer when
you're 20 then a zoomers are gonna start dying out pretty quick and then the new generation is
gonna replace them what what are they gonna be called and there's only gonna be like a few years
difference between them there's i mean i'm hearing uh talk about kumers right now you know the porn
addicted people don't like them i don't know i don't think they're an age demographic so much as a
way of life but uh they need to be eviscerated uh yeah i don't know i don't know we'll have to
just deal with it as as the history marches on and let what was that wasn't we looked it up and like
the zoomers are all sometimes called the new lost generation or something is that true god no the
new silent generation which like doesn't make any sense because they're really loud you could only
you could only make that claim in hindsight when you saw the oh yeah these people didn't say anything
yeah they're just kids right now yeah i don't understand it at all whoever made that is i hate
them all right we got one last voicemail an ominously titled not even cluster punk can save
me now so let's hear what that has to say and here we go
it's a night like any other i'm driving home for my weekend a meeting anarcho fascist
anonymous when i see the flashing lights behind me and hear the shul call of misfortune the sound
of a police siren fear is injected into my bones i pull over to the shoulder of the road my heart
beating in my throat i knew i was done i knew i had shit in my car that could end me the police
officer looms over my window and shines his light in my face and as he does he notices my dilemma
out of the cop boy he says and at the booming voice i comply and he throws me to the ground
my head hitting harder than Nate's high dive what is that he yelps dancing his flashlight on the
connected bluetooth device on my dash it's pcp i cry tears running down my baby face his knee on
my back he looks down at me a wicked look in his eyes listening to the pcp huh boy you don't look
like a rowdy he says bringing his face closer you look like a killer a cop my penis shrinks to the
size of a raisin in my soil my pants no sir it's not like that i whimper almost inaudibly
ah and what's this he asks taking out a bottle of fuel and a receipt from my car
looks like a recent donation to big patreon.com slash ben saint oh and you're drinking and driving
huh a fuel oh no he cuffs me and hauls me to the back of his car that's 10 years right the street
lights briefly and it will illuminate the side of his car and as he throws me in it says pc police
before i can begin to beg he he cuts in he cuts in it says you're going for all degenerates belong
boy you're gonna wish you were in voice jail rather than this jail please help me
wow oh man sad and yeah that's a bad yeah fight the power fight the power dude what jail is he in
did he say what jail it was real jail i supposed to jail just regular jail you know well he's that
well he's the pc police so maybe he's taking him to the pc jail penitentiary the pc prison the pc
penitentiary yeah we're all true criminals go oh there's no coming back i i like to think that
this policeman he like he's not like working for the pcp this man's on patrol four pcp heads of
all stripes they have to be locked away because we're the reason people are dying so they have
to make a new division just like the undead asylum and dark souls the same logic they're all
infected it's it's i i really like how you know he says what's that it's it's pcp and he immediately
assumes the podcast yeah i'm thinking that bluetooth device he's drinking okay he's first of all
listen to the pcp that's a five-year minimum right there drinking hule that's a 10-year minimum
right drinking while driving that's transhuman shit we don't abide he's uh don't a receipt for
a donation to patreon.com slash pensate that's 20 years minimum right there we can't comm use them
failed and we are not going to try it again that's all there is to it he's he's he's he's he's he's
driving under the influence under the influence of digital influencers like the pcp
no there's no there's no coming back from this but you know what in the end he was just being
cool and that's all the reason they need to fucking cuff him indeed and if this if you want this to
be you lads and ladies why not head over onto patreon.com slash the procrastinators one dollar
you're in the discord five dollars you get 29 bonus episodes another one coming soon at the
beginning of the next month what a deal or more and maybe one day some kind of minecraft bonus as
well look at those fucking vote things that we're gonna have down below let us know what you think
about them and follow us at tpcrastinators on twitter for updates and stuff to polls and what
not so you can see what we're up to and of course the speak pipe link down below be like not even
cluster punk can save me now and leave quality voice messages to enhance the quality of the show
and that's it thanks for being here everybody we'll see you next week i had a beer time and i
hope you did good talk everybody no doubt chat bye
myself i'm sucking