Can you believe all the money we're making from these ridiculous pony videos?
Stocks, bonds, drugs, blood diamonds, nothing's made dividends like this before.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever and also here's Hippocrit.
Cash money and such.
And that's it. We're the only guys here, that's it.
So let's move ahead here.
Oh, that's the party fucker to the party cash.
IT'S ME!
Oh, what do you know?
PURSING IN THROUGH THE SEALING!
I was parachuting and I just figured I should get out now before the instructor got too mad at me.
And here I am.
Well alright, just in time.
Why was he getting mad at you?
I figured if I waited too long he'd be like, why aren't you jumping out so I better go early so he wouldn't get mad.
What was that voice that I heard from under the door that we locked to keep him out?
Oh, it's Ben St.
Hey, let me just roll on in here and say that I'll probably be leaving a little early because Nate's technical issues have forced a scheduling conflict.
Because around 7 today I'm going to be over fucking streaming video games streaming you, me, Nicky on twitch.tv.
So if you're in the future, go back to watch me.
Yeah, I'll join stream.
Yeah, you should all join the stream by the way.
Oh hey guys.
Sorry I'm late, my dad was taking me in the city to see a marching band.
He said son, when you grow up would you be the leader of the broken.
It's beaten in the damn, he said will you defeat them, your demons and all the non-believers, the plans that they have made because one day I'll leave you a phantom to lead you in the summer to join the black raid.
And that's why he appeared, he tellturnism is bad.
Busted, Nate, busted.
I just, I just, I don't associate that song with anything except Gern Lagen.
Is that, I mean-
I associate that with the freshman year of high school.
Munchy, have you not seen this girl, I gotta link it to you, it's like the greatest thing ever made.
It's just, it so perfectly fits with the, with like the Simone common relationship.
Okay, let's move on.
The Simone.
Can we, can we-
From Moana.
Can we have a peek behind the curtain real quick and say this is not the first PCP episode we've recorded today?
Very true, everybody.
I had technical issues, my computer died.
We recorded a grand episode about Nate's weird utilitarian principles.
So grand.
Yeah, it was actually really great and when we're all real fucking bummed that it's lost forever and no one will ever hear it.
I, I, I object to even mentioning it because then we might not make it in the future, but we'll try again.
I'm gonna upload my audio and I'm gonna let the audience try to piece together.
Really?
Piece together what was going on.
Why would you all upload our audio separately?
I made some really great points.
Yeah, everyone upload their separately on their channels.
It's a good idea.
I'll try to recover mine too and upload mine separately.
Nate, don't even try to recover it because I-
It'll be like an ARG.
Yeah.
Whoa, that's a good idea.
But we spoiled it for everybody.
Okay, well too bad.
Maybe within the week until this goes live, people will be wondering what the fuck these audio's are.
Excellent.
Okay, everybody, but we're not talking about that today.
Instead we're gonna talk about money.
Money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
Insert cash register sound effect.
Is that, is that ruffling?
What's that?
Is that the ruffling of the cash?
Yeah, what's that ruffling of the cash?
Yep, that's, that was my money.
That's Ben rubbing all the IOU's together that he has.
Ben who Ben who hates
Dollars and loves coins would never
Yeah, yeah, I wish I just had a big sack of like weird like ring coins and just things all the time to carry
I never want to see you fail as long as I live
That is it does make more impressive sounds that you do things with it like that. Yeah, there we go
Oh, yeah, it's like a pirate sound you put a sack of gold on the table
Parts knew what was up. They were smart. So okay, here we go. So here's the the Urban Dictionary definition of money everybody
Okay, money that which allows lazy people to do stupid things without painful consequences thus keeping them forever stupid
Here's the example. It's not the love of money. That is the root of all evil, but rather the lack of it
It's not wrong to have money. It's wrong for money to have you
Hey money is the root of all evil is a misquote and I can't remember what the actual quote is
But I know it's love of all money is the root of all it makes sense said Jesus to me right now
Yeah, money is I like it
So as you can guess we did not have much time to think about this ahead of time. So let's just jump into it
Let's talk about my accounts. I have a big bank account. Go go fund my bank account
Here's my account info paid for the PCP last month. Let's see. Yeah
Share our detailed financials. That's what this episode. Yeah, I got one hundred seventy five dollars
Link in the description to our bank account, which you can feel free to just have at withdraw from what's your favorite?
password the ease for your bank
Top ten my bank password
My top ten account passwords and that's a good one. That's a good video. I should do that before I die
That's actually a great idea. Okay, so let's talk. So is money the root of all evil? No, it's great
I hate money money
Causes me more stress than anything else in my whole life. I don't know whatever I hear anybody be like guys
Wouldn't it be great if we eliminated money? I just think you're an idiot. You don't know share life
The fact that I that I need money is what causes me the stress not the fact that it exists. Okay, okay?
Yeah, I feel that way
I would like I would like a nice comfortable sort of amount of money where I'm like well
I'm not gonna die tomorrow. So that's good
I'm you know me and me and DeVoo talked about this a bunch when I was living at Digi house when both of us were living at Digi house
DeVoo would sometimes get on this tub subject of a what's like universal minimum income
We're like just basic income. Yeah universal basic income where everyone it's just like, you know like like
Social programs are are less social programs are cut
But just everyone gets like you know a small but livable income maybe like
$20,000 something a year and
Like you if you make up for it else and like God, I wish that was the world we lived in no
I don't know
Set he'd be perfect. That'd be a big race
I wouldn't have to worry about anything I could just do my art and be happy a lot of the time
I think of like like people who are on hard times
But they never seem to be like suddenly homeless like actually completely homeless with no money and no way to make any
I know I like about Ben though
It's just I like that Ben is a Ben is realistic and is willing to downscale his life
With you know like having made less money
What I what I hate is what or what I think is is wrong or silly of people to do is to like expect
Everything and then also like not realize that like oh well
I'm not generating enough value to deserve these things like Ben is willing to eat trash and live
You know on the streets. Yeah, it's like I only make zero dollars. This is what I prefer it
Yeah, exactly, you know that's like he's he's correctly scaling his expectations to reality, which is good
I think so I like to think so
It seems that way anyway, I think poor people, you know, I I think poor people should be eliminated
Because here's what poor people do they will walk into a
I didn't
Even able to make half my point now. I can't remember what it was. I'm just really mad
You just
Something about like homeless I don't know if you suddenly if you suddenly if there are people on the on the on the on the streets
And I've been like there for years suddenly giving them a paycheck. I don't know what they would do with it
Oh, so you're saying that like even if we gave, you know, even if even if suddenly there was a there was a not
There was like a livable wage for everybody
I don't know whether that much would change like people would no not a bit more not that much
Yeah, but it would just but I just wanted to be good for people like me
So that's why I want like I don't care about anything else. Obviously. I mean, I know Tavu has some weird like
Things that are like that. I mean, I only say weird because I don't understand them
I don't know if they're actually like incorrect or not
But like he's got some justification for universal basic income based on like it would free up people to work on the things
They really want to do
Because that's what it would do to me. Yeah, I mean, you know, it makes sense
But the only thing is
Like so universal basic income definitely makes sense in a situation just where there's like mass unemployment due to like
Technological evolution or whatever. It's just you know, like we don't need like a thousand billion McDonald's employees anymore
We've got robots. They they've got it under control. So like that's you know
And that puts like a million people out of work or whatever
But but like up until that point where like things are covered by robots
If you give people universal basic income like there's not going to be value generated
So it's like the society will suffer and could get weighed down by that shit. It's like there needs to be
Is they were already spending like a million fucking dollars on like, you know, I don't know a stuff
Stuff that the government does that like that like this would be like this would be paid for by cutting those other programs
You know what I like about this though
This puts the responsibility on people to manage their shit properly and then I don't have to feel bad for them anymore
Yeah, you know, I feel like it should at least be something you have to sign up for like just fill in some paperwork
If you can't read if you can't write
No school. No, no, wait wait
Here's what it is. Here's what it is
If you can't read or write you get free school until you can and then from there
Okay, you get you get like a little bit of money and then you can just you're supposed to like you'd be incentivized to do stuff
You go to because like okay, if you get money some people some people will definitely just live and do nothing forever
What if you're just retarded though like literally you're actually mentally challenged about those people?
Well, you get some of that money and you spend it on
Yeah, but they won't know how to do any of that shit. They'll need they'll need care
Guys, let me clear this up with what I think is a far more intelligent solution instead of just giving people
$20,000 a year retarded because the thing about money is you can buy whatever the fuck you want with that
If we're gonna give people handouts, it should be a universal housing and universal like food and water
Don't give them just straight up money so they can go buy fucking anime books and I'll say I disagree with that
I disagree then you're fucking retarded
No, I want I'd be fine with just being housing and food allowances
I I want those people to die who can't who can't make that shit happen
I want them to die and be and remove themselves from the gene pool
Why yeah, why is that crazy why?
What category of people are you right?
These people who squander their universe. Yeah, sorry
I was trying to explain what you were going, but you've seen it says fine
Yeah, I was just saying people who cannot manage their life
They're like 30 grand basic minimum income with the ability to go out and earn more if they want to those people if they can't handle that
They should die. I mean I agree that everybody who gets a gender studies degree should die
But I don't I think that's a little too extreme though. No, see here's the thing
I don't like about universal basic income. What like we've kind of structured society in a way that everybody just gets to live
Like we will take care of everybody. I don't like that. Some people should die
Some people should be weeded out fucking crazy. No, but they're weeded out by their own decision-making
No, they're not like we're killing them. No, they fucking aren't there
Well, they're weeded out because they because they don't have a family support network or because they just happen to get sick
Or because they're mentally ill things like that. Well, free will isn't real either. So, you know, none of this
We have control
Totally
This is why we needed that podcast because it's just gonna keep coming up
Of course. Do you want to actually go back now? I think the mood is set again. We have to go back
Here's my thing about money
I
like coins
And I'm with you so far
Did any of you as kids have like a big thing of pennies? Did you just have a load of pennies?
Sure
Yeah, they have pennies. Yeah, oh, it's called the same thing. It is called the same thing
You have sense we have pennies and everything is also called pennies. It's just like five pennies five pennies
Is Abraham Lincoln your pennies too?
No, it's the Queen the Queen's all about money. Is a pens the same thing as a penny?
One pence one penny. Yeah
But you call it sense you just change the P to a C
Yeah, you know what they say in for a penny in for a pence. That's the expression
All right, I wasn't gonna talk about not know this
All right now I like I like I forgot what I was gonna say, but I like coins
I'll just go back to that that classic
That's that classic tried-and-true tested debate topic. I love coins. Uh, they're good
I like oh, yeah, the pennies thing
Did any of you have like like I had like a treasure chest full of pennies and I and I
Cashed it into the bank one day and it wasn't even that much and I really I really I really am upset
Treasure chest it was a little little wooden treasure chest with a lock and I had a padlock and it was just full of pennies
And it just felt so dude. You know I felt so wealthy. I did yeah
I felt so wealthy having that chest, but my parents told me you know
That's worth money and you can have it and I'm like whoa
So I did and it was like I don't know a couple a couple quid a couple pounds like not even five pounds
Maybe and now I'm sad that I don't have a pirate chest
I do have a related question for everybody if we want to go around the horn based off what hippo just said
And hopefully this is relevant for most of you if you got like for your birthday you get money
Like at the edge of like 10 to 12. What did you spend that money on?
Saved in one time. I went to I went to a hallmark and I spent literally
$100 on webcams
Just webcams. What are those a webkin you mother fuck is that a stone?
Webkins are
All right
Here I'm gonna red pillion webkins
All right, please
You would be a little lad a little boy or a girl or maybe even both and you would walk into it
You would walk into a store and there you would see them the webkin and he would
And they would smile upon you gleefully and with it with the with the tint in their eyes where you know
They mean fucking business basically there's these they're there these little like stuffed animals
And they look fucked up and like fucking like battered like like crazy housewives fucking Los Angeles and and they like
They're all like tie-dyed and shit
They're like mystical and magical and frivolous and you would buy these you would buy them and and and there'd be like like
Like fucking like 15 or $20 like like a lot for like a teddy bear or something or like a cat
And then you would buy them and then they would have a special code and you would go online to webkins
www.webkins.gov and
And you would enter in the this is a government program. Yeah, you would enter in webkins would be cut to pay for a universal
No, we have to abandon that
Yeah, that motherfucker that guy and he would get him and he would put the code in and then he would be like hello
I'm alive inside the computer. I will I will transmit my code into your soul now
And and impressive it's like a soul augmentation program, right? Okay, is it is it like beanie babies for the modern age?
Is that yes? Yeah, and you like put them in rooms and you could like make their rooms look cool
And you could like it was like Animal Crossing
But you had to like get like a fucking like thing in real life. So they're kind of like amiibo
So yeah, yeah trainer amiibo, and yeah
They live inside of a virtual world and you can like see them growing you can play games with them
I would always play this one game where it was like I would go into the fucking like King Solomon's minds
And I would like work my little baby hands until I would fucking cried myself
All over your web was doing slave labor. Yeah, yeah, exactly and I liked it. I liked it like that. I liked being a slave
I was a slave to my own desires, and you know what it worked down the end like what's that?
There was like like that that minigame
It was like an old like asshole like southern like fucking like a big it like fucking confederate sold your dog there
It was like working my minds and maybe you'll fucking not be a slave one day
Wow, and and I did it ever feels like
Yeah, that's what it means to be a slave
And then I always work and I was trying to get like fucking like like heart scales basically I can never get any
I only got like fucking like shoes and like fucking like three dollars, and it was well wait you made money
There's a return on investment here. No, well first of all money like super much like webkins money, okay?
So like Bitcoin
I got I got payment and dogecoin
That's worth 20 times Bitcoin as I understand like when you win the sled game on Club Penguin. Yeah, exactly
Yeah, yeah, and a base. Yeah, it's like web. It's like Club Penguin, but like better because it's webkins
And like it's I know a certain hippo who would probably argue against you on that one sucker
I don't know whether hippo's played
Fiona the hippo world's famous hippo yesterday at the Cincinnati Zoo. Oh, yeah
It was cool. She was a little rambunctious dude. She was hanging out with her mom and papa
That's nothing to do with what we're talking about. Yeah, but then again now that is webkins, so
Let's
What did you waste your money on?
Right without question. It was always video games every single time I would buy mostly like I could afford
I would spend my money on like GBA games because they were generally cheap
Yeah, like every every birthday or like Christmas. I could usually cash in for exactly one video game no matter what it cost
I mean, they were generally like 60 bucks, but nonetheless, I would use my money
Really that much back then. They're like 40 bucks shit 40 bucks
Yeah, you know, but I would scrape together my money and I would buy fucking Mario and Luigi Superstar saga the greatest game ever made or
Fuck what else? I don't know Castlevania. I would always buy the new Castlevania's on GBA. It was the greatest games of all time
Shit like that. So it was always video games. So that's my answer. That's a complete long and short of it
I
Shout out to Castlevania circle of the moon
I would um always save any money I got from birthdays because I
Ever since ever since my parents said oh, we can't afford that at anything
I was like wait, you can't you can't get this thing that I would like you to get for me
And then it was disturbing and then I learned that things can cost a hundred pounds
And I was like no no one is ever gonna spend any of this money. I'm getting I have to keep all of it
So I just kept putting it in my bank account and I have thousands upon thousands
Well, not that many but like what was your what was your goal with this just to have it to save it
I mean as a kid. I just thought well my parents buy things for me
Anyway, so if I get money from my other relatives, I don't need to spend it
I just need to you know, just sort of sort of wait wait around and then parents
So your answer to what did I buy as a kid is I didn't buy I didn't buy anything. I just got shit
I'm I'm a I'm a I was a clever Jew as I wish I was as smart as hippo because regretfully
I spent all of my childhood money buying yugioh tins
Which were never worth it
And now every single card I own is worthless and I I couldn't sell it if I found the biggest fan of the world
It it was the worst investment a young boy could ever make
Oh my god about magic dude should have invested in magic the gathering that would have paid I bought I bought magic the gathering
I just remembered like the most wasteful thing that I spent my money on I did I did spend some money on it
But mostly it was something that I would use my like, you know Christmas and birthday gifts
Like like credits as or such as they are for
Um fucking fucking dungeons and dragons
Uh like splat books and rule books. I always wanted more of them. I ate that shit up
Um god, it's embarrassing. Cool. Huh. Do you still have them?
Yeah, there's a huge fucking pile of them in my parents house
Some of those were e fucking sensual the manual of the planes is a is a wonderful book just to read
Some of them are just fun to read like some like they have rules in them
And it's like that's fine
But some of them are just like lore and it like goes into like each one of the each one of the planes and like talks about
What monsters and what gods live there? There's a lot of creativity there and I really think those are fun as fuck
Some of them
I want to get into but I don't know how and I don't know how to
To get into dungeons and dragons. Well, here's the free get all those rule books like the free on the
Disclaimer disclaimer. Don't get into dungeons and dragons. It's actually a shit game that sucks
Um, yeah, and like any any any any any suggestion to the contrary is the product of memes and stock homes
It's what I mean by that is that I I would like to be able to say
You know, I kind of get what the whole lore of dungeons and dragons is if there is like a consistent law
I know there are like different books. Well, there's a saying this is this is this is like the book of this
And then another book will reference that book a bit so they're sort of connected, but not really
There are a few there are a few like worlds that like certain books are specifically made for and or in
but like
I mean
They all conflict with each other
I feel like if I want to be get it be good at world building. I might have to read a few of those
Forgive me if I wrong. Yes
A dungeon and dragons to like make your own story. It's like you make your own thing
Oh people need not always need a bit of guidance
I guess is the point and some people just want to buy these like pre-made stories and just play along with them
Like remember that one about that that drow elf guy drizz it or whatever who was so popular
Yeah, I know people would just buy lore books to read. I always wanted I always wanted
Like to be in a game like like a professionally made campaign like a professionally made adventure with like
Because like the professionally made ones are better like they're just better
But nobody wants to buy them because someone wants to DM and people want to tell their own shitty stories around your fucking
a basement dining room table
and
like
I feel like I missed out because
Like one time I played a pre-made adventure that like came in a box and I was like this thing is so robust
There's like there's just so much more to do like it's so much more engaging than just the shitty nothing
Whatever that my that my jerk-off friend here has has prepared for my enjoyment. Fuck that guy. Say my name. Say my name
Munchy munchy. It's me. I DM you already said webkins
Uh, no, no, no, I'm telling Ben to name that guy by name so we can make one of them
All of them. Oh, yes, just like everyone. It's just everyone. Just nobody makes good d&d campaign
I nobody makes them. I didn't even know there was
Like lore to dragons dragons. I thought I was just like a rule dragons and dragons. Yeah
Well, that's what we're talking about, right?
Some dungeons and dragons you clawed you colossal weight some of the books describe like a specific setting
But not but like you don't have to play it in that setting if you don't want to
Yeah, I thought I didn't I thought it was just like a rule set for like anything
I thought I thought the mother
There's a whole pantheon of gods and shit and like
The way spoonie
Explained it in his uh series about dungeons and dragons makes it seem like it's really cool. Well, he's wrong
I promise you he's wrong
Well, yeah, I mean, I'm sure it's it's not cool, but it's like cool to have a story to say and then this happened
Although I kind of want to go watch those that video now
Uh, all right, let's move on to the next one. No, no, no, no, just really just really just really just really quick
Wait, all right, what is it? I I wanted I want to be in a spur
Dungeons and dragons thing. Oh god only only I got to never
My dammit, Nate
I yeah, I was thinking about spurred the other day and I was thinking I am such a genius
That was good. Remember how like early on some of the like role playing sessions
We did over text to simulate uh pester logs. Yep. Yeah, I am the greatest. Yeah, those are great
If we ever
And the pcp of course is the thing we have to do that. I will force you to do it
Then I will not you will not have to say in it. You know what? Yeah, I'm not gonna say that I would never do
Like a spur with the pcp
I would if I could find an excuse to do it
So yeah, I mean that one's was actually fun because we didn't give a fuck about although. No, wait. D&D actually has
Yeah, well, I mean there's already horse stuck
Well, yeah, but I don't get to play as my guy. Yeah, horse stuck is just Gibbs thing basically, you know
Well, no, no
I could like have a bit where you I I could have like a like a you skip ahead and then there's like a big area
Where you could have a gorgeous. Let's talk about this another time
I don't care about money. This is way more fun. Well, this is not the time to discuss the details. I have possible future work
Yes, it is
I can't think of a better time a tangentially related topic of money that we were talking about
We're talking about, you know, things we spent birthday money on what about the biggest waste of money of all time that we have spent
Sure
I've got a great answer for this and I think about it all the time and how much I regret it
I spent 100 american dollars as a little baby boy
At king Richard's fair at this giant floppy black leather match
Because I want it to look like vampire hunter d more than anything. I remember that hat. I remember I still have this hat
It's dusty as fuck. It's huge. It's even better. Hilarious listeners. Let me just personally assure you is even better than than you are imagining
It's amazing. It's I'll do a vampire to d cosplay someday and use it just to justify the purchase
Uh at king Richard's fair, which by the way king Richard's fair is like a renaissance fair thing that they have near us
It's pretty it's pretty cool
they uh
I spent 90 dollars on a on a like on like a
Smith uh metal flanged mace, which I named which I named leopold
Uh and and leopold is I guess probably sitting in my in the closet of our parents house right now
Haven't seen him in a while, but he's my faithful companion and if I in a time someday in a time of need
I'll have him around that I do not regret at all
Well then why'd you bring it out? We're talking about because I just wanted to talk about leopold
I guess it is regressed because this is a waste of money
Uh the the thing that I've wasted the most money is and the things that I regret the most are all the things that I've lost
Because I don't have them anymore
I've lost so many fucking things. I'm a clumsy adult and I don't know where any shit is
I just found my original ds the other day after like fucking like eight years of not having it
And it's like all like broken and shit and I love it, but I hadn't I and I don't have my fucking original 3ds
I think that one broke though. There's just so much shit. I don't have that. I just lost somehow
I don't know how I hate so much the the the like the fear of of an electronic device
Like like oh if I like a like a ds or a gameboy advance like if I bring it into the bathroom
What if I drop it in the toilet? It'll be ruined
I can I can I have to put it on my bed
And I and I have to walk, you know, and then I play my switch while I poop now every time and it is the greatest experience
It's too dangerous. It's so wonderful. I I'm never going back. My switch is my favorite thing in the world
It was worth every single cent every other console is garbage consoles are shit handhelds are the future
I mean, yes. Yes. Handhelds are far better than consoles. I hate consoles. I hate computers
I only like handheld gaming devices that that is
Do you remember okay? Do you remember what happened to your copy of like zelda for swords or something?
Yeah, what what you did with it, right? Well the tragedy that ensued. Yeah. Yeah. I know it was an accident
It was on some trip. It was on some trip like either to or from college
I was I was catching my train in in pen station in new york
And I the train was there it was like leaving and I was I had all my bags
And I was like running to jump on this train before the doors closed
And just as luck would fucking have it my fucking ds just bounced
Out of my bag and just like hit the ground and skidded and just fell off the edge of the platform
And just landed under the train and I was standing there looking down over the ledge through the gap
And I could see it there. Maybe like 10 feet away from me eight feet away from me
I was just sitting there and I just looked around like
well
I better get on the train
And then I got on the train and sat down. I was like my fucking ds with nate's game in it is like is like
Eight feet below me like down through the floor of this train. It is sitting there right now and I can't get it
Yeah, you know what though ben?
I I feel content knowing that the little mole people who man the trains who do the repairs at night
They creep out from the woodworks one of their little children probably obtained that ds and and enjoyed it to his heart's content
But no charger. It probably died in three hours
Well, it was the best three hours of that little mole's life
But but uh, but moles are blind so they wouldn't have been able to see it. Yeah
Oh, he could he could play through through psycho kinesis
Nate your story has more holes than hillary clinton's email story
Well, what about donald trump jr. He's done nothing wrong. He's he's oh, yeah, he's done nothing wrong
He's a good name one thing that trumps have done wrong. Hey, they have money. Can we talk about trumps money?
Uh, sure. What's there to say about tv show and the theme song was money money money money?
No, no, no, no, no, no that is that is trump wait that wasn't no, that's uh, uh, uh, that's that is vince mcman's son
That is his wwe song when he comes out. That's the song of the apprentice as well
Really? Oh, I guess they're repurposed it. Well, that's cool. Repurposed it
It's not like the song wasn't invented for wrestling. That's incorrect. It was invented for the song's been around forever
Is that true? Yes. Okay. All right. Jesse once told me like that's his theme song
And I know songs do get written for specific wrestlers
Well, probably I've been correct here. Maybe I've made a mistake. I don't think so. Okay, whatever
In any case, fine. Cool. Good. Was that the apprentice theme song? Was that the idea? Yeah? Yeah
Okay, I regret losing the most is my courage my pride and all of my wisdom
When he joined the piece, yeah
All of my wisdom
It's when you joined you you joined having all your wisdom
It is through the process of joining that you lost it all. Is that is that accurate? Okay. It's it's goodbye. Goodbye
Um, I may have told the story before but there was this one time when I was playing donkey kong country 2 on my
On my little brother's uh black gameboy advance sp
And I was I was getting frustrated because that game's really it's real hard
A real difficult game and I got mad and I threw it across the room because I didn't realize that things break
And it and it broke and that screen was fucked and I didn't know what to do
I just nobody heard it. Nobody was around
It was and it was like during like a like a the middle of the day. So
Uh, did you print out a screenshot from donkey kong and pasted over the screen?
Well, eventually that's what came of it. Like, uh, not not I didn't do that
But he he turned it into a memorial. He he he cut out a little a little uh image of like mario cart
Gba or whatever mario cut advance and he pasted that on and he just kept that as like a little little thing that you could flip it open
How did you make up for this great scene of yours?
This the thing was I I was so upset that well, I didn't I was I was scared really
Um, sure and my little brother was really upset and my dad came home
And he heard about it and he just left and then he came back with another one
But but he was my god
He came back with another one, but he looked at me so glaring like
I don't want to have to do this again
Hey, you know, I felt terrible
Pretty much he was a good dad
But I felt like a complete idiot, but it I didn't learn my lesson because a few years later
Oh
I broke that same brother's uh ds original by punching it
Because because because of dragon quest something or other
I was trying to do the casinos in a dragon quest game on ds and I punched the thing
I realized that if I punch it it might break, but I was so angry. I was willing to test it
And I
Test you really, you know, you really do have like a video game ball of rage inside. It does come out. Yep. I I'm I'm frucky
I'm evil. I'm terrible
When I was I was like eight and I would literally with my my gameboy advance when I lose against the pokemon league
I would just throw the thing as hard as I could across the room and the batteries would go flying out like fucking grenades
Right. No, but it never
That gba still works to this day
Damn, they don't build them like they used to no that uh, that thing's a fucking tank
What the hell is it with white people and throwing controllers? I don't get it with white people with white
White people specific to other races not do that. I would assume they do. I don't know. I've never seen a black man
What about the spicy latin community? They gotta do that. I did I did I did punch uh
I did punch my laptop in the screen one time and just fucking
Here's the thing here's the thing I was in college and and my school gave everyone there a basically a free laptop
That like well, I mean we had to pay for it, but they were like, okay
Well, they issued me a laptop and like they would repair it if it ever got broke
So like one time when I was home vacation
I just like punched it in the screen and just like cracked it all just ruined it while it was on
It felt really badass, but then like for the rest of vacation. I had no I had no laptop
Which was a bummer but then I went back and I was like, oh, yeah, I just dropped something on it and they were like
All right fine
Why didn't you wait until the end of the vacation to do that?
Well, it was it was I was mad about yeah, it was the heat of the moment. It wasn't like I'm not gonna be mad later
It wasn't like a free. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I really want to punch my laptop screen
But I don't I don't know if I'll be mad enough later. So I better I better conserve it
Um, uh, yeah, Ben Ben's Ben's a an angry lash out of things man. Yeah
Yeah, I kicked a hole in the wall that one time
You know the basement one time I I kicked a hole in the wall
But I'm gonna defend myself on that because like me and the parents were like really on the outs at the time
And they'd been and they'd been fucking giving they'd been
Okay, they took me to a shrink and they made they got the shrink to prescribe me riddolin
so for like two weeks I was taking riddolin and
Here's the thing I don't know whether the riddolin like made me fucking hyperactive and that's where this happened or
If taking the riddolin gave me an excuse to be hyperactive because now I could blame it on the riddolin
I don't know which is these is true
But yeah during that time I did like punch a hole in our basement wall
And then my dad our dad got so fucking mad and he made me repair it myself
Like I had to go to the the store and like buy putt like like plaster putty wall putty mix it
Like scrape it on like repaper the wall. It was like he
It took I mean it probably could have been done in a day by a competent craftsman or a couple days
But it took me like a fucking week to do it was miserable and
I was very sad
I think that's a fitting punishment. I think so too. Yeah, I think I think that's fair
But still it made me it really it really was a drag
Fair but I was gonna say it sounds like me and munchie. I've like never done shit like that ever
You know, I'm not a violent guy. I don't know. I don't know. Maybe it's just a thin boy thing
Maybe
Are you calling me fat you piece of shit?
No, I will you don't want to be fit. No, no, right
No, I don't know what it what it's caused by it, but I'm just an angry rage machine because I remember another story
Oh, my god, he's dead. We killed him
The original playstation one
Say or something and I and I I lost real bad and I have never heard
I never even like I'm so seething all my electronics. I have never like I don't I don't play video games with my sound
I went there and they'll they'll like hurt my ears. I oh fuck's sake. Why is it? Okay? Yeah, we hear you now. I can hear you
I'm so I'm so full of rage thinking about give rage. Yeah
That trademark Gibbon Ray
so so guys uh
I'm playing rayman one on ps1 the original playstation disc
I don't have it anymore because I got so mad that I took it out
Slowly and I just had it in my hands and my hands were shaking and you know when you're angry
And you need you feel the need to like really really clench your fists or pull on something real bad
And I had this disc on both hands and I was like
I wonder if I could just twist it just a little bit just a little bit twist it in my hands
And then I snapped it instantly. I was like
And you know my my hands were shaking. I was like
No, you know
I killed rayman's essence
It was the first time I destroyed a video game. I felt like my first time but far from the last
He felt that surge of power and knew he would do this every day
I was real sad, but I was very scared that people would find out so I shoved I slid it underneath the tv
And and I don't know who found it. I've probably somebody found it at some point
But uh, my brother's one says one day was saying where's rayman?
Where is it? Hey, that panic started to rise. Hey hippo. Hey hippo. Where's rayman? Where's rayman hippo? It's like
I didn't do nothing. He went out a good man
He took a trip far away to visit distant relatives. He's not coming back. Uh, don't look for him
There's the sequel rayman 2 the distraction
Oh, that's that's cute. That's hey, but remember that time we had a babysitter and we played frisbee with the final fantasy eight discs
Uh, what a fucking idiot. Yeah, I do. I can't possibly imagine wait. What what?
I was just like
We were just playing final fantasy eight having a great time and he was like, hey, here's a great idea
Let's play frisbee with the goddamn disc and we were like little kids. We're like, yeah
The babysitter suggested it
Yeah, he was the one doing it. Oh
Am I the kind of guy who's gonna play frisbee with his final fantasy eight disc? Absolutely not. He instigated
He instigated this madness. I remember and uh, I do remember that a guy a guy in our boy scout troop
He sold me legend of dragoon, but like the third disc was just broken
I remember that it was like a big fucking deal
And I think I had to get my parents our parents to talk to his parents and be like your son sold my son a broken thing
And like he've like reluctantly paid me back at some point
That sounds familiar that sounds and I remember once that was like my favorite game
But the third disc was broken and I couldn't get past that. Yeah
Yeah, one and then you for my birthday years later got me a new copy of legend dragoon
And it was the most wonderful. I was finally able to be I did what a cool guy. I am you used money
Yeah, I was just gonna say
And you know how I did that with money. So there you go
I have a new god. I have a new question if we want to talk more about money
Yes, we do. Please. It feels like a video game cast so far with all this webcam shit
It's fine. When we mentioned spoonie this question popped into my mind. Are there any people who make more money than you think they deserve?
Oh my god, I mean
All of us I think fall into that category
Ben in the last episode you said that the market gets to chew
So if anything that's making money at all like it deserves to because people are willing to pay for it
Well, yeah, all right. I have to engage in a little bit of double think here
Like yeah, I know that like people people can give will give money to what they value and I think that's fun
But like for me personally, I think like even though I like for example, gym sterling
Like I like him
But I think it is out fucking rages that he makes like $10,000 a month for what he does like that's like that's disgusting
But if people are willing to pay for it, what's the problem? But what are they paying for?
What are they paying for like the people just value his opinion that you know, you know what it is
You know what it is? It's not it's not people don't actually
Think that they're doing him any good because they're not like he doesn't need more money to do what he does
Like like he's passed the point where he he could whatever
They're just people just pay for for things like that people pay for for creators
Just because they want to feel something like they have something to do
They just want to hitch their wagon to theirs and like feel like they're a part of something which is like that's fine
I get that and I won't say that anyone's wrong to do that
But like it's annoying because like
Some people like oh you mean like me for example
Like I need money so that I can actually do the things I want to do and then someone like jim sterling
You're just giving him money to give him money at that point, you know
Yeah, I that that's definitely frustrating a frustrating feeling
Uh, but like on the uh, just this isn't really a counter example
But then you got people who just like that what they do is they game the stock market and produce nothing
And like they just make tons of money and even even look more like
Yeah, I guess you're right. There's worse injustices in this world. Yeah, I don't really know what my point is
I guess I just like I'm just escalating the scale of like this shit gets fucked up
I was just hoping we have high levels point out people on patreon and make fun of them
I don't want to talk about stock market. Hey, you know that you know that you know that porn lady who makes like the high-def
Still images of porn and makes like 30 grand a month. You know her. Yeah. No, I'm very interested
S-s-s-s-s-such
No, she's Saki Chen Saki. Yeah. Yeah. She draws like really like beautiful shiny like fucking fan art bullsh**
I like like
Like like ben I don't begrudge these people for earning their money
But considering like I'm trying to personally get to a level just to survive
On doing this stuff, of course, it's just naturally frustrating that I see these people making so much more than they actually need
Like it is you know, that's all but I don't begrudge them, but I just
I hit some of that I only begrudge people when they're in the same sort of line of work
Anyone a patron I consider especially like a creator like cuz like if it like is say that there's like a load of there's a big
I mean everyone knows there's a huge market for porn people
Yeah, like if you do porn you're going to get money and you're going to get like a lot more than you would doing something else
I can get upset at that. I mean generally generally like it generally the opportunity is certainly there
Yeah, well the point is if a video game reviewer of you know is
Making loads more money than me, and I think I'm better than them
Like it's not a game reviewer. It's it's it's it's it's more I feel
It's just a more relevant
Direction to put rage rather than just at people making money in general
Yeah, I mean, it's more frustrating when someone yeah, yeah when like when it feels like someone else is getting more for the same thing than you are
Yeah, okay, that's fair. That's fair like I don't know like peanut butter gamer for the fact that he survives at all
Well, Spoonie dude his money is gone. He is I don't know
He's making more than most of us. Yeah, not I've checked now making more than him now
And I mean obviously I deserve it. How much he makes nothing. How much is he making like $800, right?
Yeah, I think something yeah, that's about right, but like he's made nothing for months and you know
Like he's got his depression or whatever
But the point is he is not giving his patrons anything of value so why on earth would he get any money for it?
He shouldn't he shouldn't get any money. No, you know, but like that
You know these on to these people into thinking if they gave him a certain amount
He would make a movie that he has no intention of actually making I think he's a fucking scam con artist who deserves to give all his money
He's just said some stupid like like he's not he doesn't deserve to have like
He doesn't deserve to be able to say I'm going to do something because it's just not reliable
Well, he doesn't say anything anymore. I think he streams occasionally, but I don't even know whether he does that anymore
But I guess I don't follow that. Should patreon goals
We consider like a legal contract that these people gave you this much money for this thing that you didn't do
It's like a line
It is a line. I really hate that I would just get away with like
I like this moment to reiterate that I have not forgotten about the reward art that I owe people
If any of you out there are like really jonesing for that and like want it in a timely fashion like feel free to tell me
But for the but anyway
My guilt
How's the name different from a Kickstarter campaign that reaches the goal and then they just run off with the money
You mean like you mean like leaving the weave
It's in the works
Yeah, it's coming. It's coming. Don't let Jess listen to this episode. No, but it is that it is actually coming though. I promise
Stuff like that is that like the free market or whatever if people are
You there's nothing free market about lying and stealing
Yeah, but if you're known as a liar and stealer people aren't gonna pay money for you anymore
Well, they didn't know until you already stole their money. Yeah, I know but that's why I said you can get away with it
Once but after that you're fucked forever. So I don't know why you should be allowed to get away with it
I mean, you know the loud to it's just the way it is
Didn't she actually finish or is like is finishing me like three episodes once you promised to do like a million, right?
And when she did it was like three years late
Then once she said she would do and now she's like hosting panels and getting atheists kicked out of panels
And she's fucking retarded and people don't trust and love this woman who who conned them gay
Anita is the avatar of feminism and to oppose Anita just like to people to oppose her like
She is just she's just obtained this crown. Well, Hillary did nothing wrong and is perfect
But yeah, you know, it's just like for some reason she has this status now where you cannot oppose her without just being
Considered, you know, like a anti-woman or whatever. Yeah, which is you know, whatever
I
Know everyone's already said this but I want to reiterate the people who I think deserve no money are as follows
porn artists porn actors. Yeah
What's the weather? Oh, I completely agree with you much. You want a condom companies condom companies contrast
Yeah, any sort of
What is it a planned parenthood?
Yeah, I really agree. I really agree about I want to defund parenthood
I really agree about the porn actors and actresses because they're they're they're having sex, right?
No, they don't
Anybody ever see that gift of the dude snapping his dick
Yeah
What do you think it means
Yeah, that's right, that's what happens. It's fucking brutal
But it's like
Didn't break it just probably hurt. I mean, I don't maybe get like there's no like
What material is your dick made of like it's made of dick
It's made of a sponge. It's made of a spongy mucus membrane
Coiled up into a kind of foam
Muscle in there, too, so I think maybe it's counselor my dick's nothing but muscle, dude
I do my kegels every day do my cock push-ups. Oh wait, what's that thing? I do my jelking every fucking
Yeah
You joke but after jelking for a full year my dick is now one centimeter longer. Okay, so that's laughing now. It's not fucking true
All right, all right, you know, I'd love I'd love to I'd love to share my jelking story
But it'll have to it'll have to wait for another day because I gotta go I gotta go stream twitch.tv
Stream jelking
Yeah, viewers you'll you'll miss this one today, but we'll do more so go sub me
We might yeah, we might actually uh put them put them there, and they'll be up on twitch
I want to come on after this after this i'm gonna come on save me. Okay. I'll see you soon. I love you. I love you all
I love you, Ben
Is he gone? Is he gone yet? No, no, what penalty shall we give ben for leaving girl? He's still hearing and it's away from delay
Oh, i'm still hearing. What is this? What is it? What is this shit?
I just want before I go. Okay before I go
I just want to say that Nate if you want to fucking penalize me
Let me this is entirely your fault. It was your it was not. It was your fault
I said I have to leave before seven and then you had had technical issues that caused it to run late
All right, so me leaving is due to your technical issues. Okay, I would argue that I don't bear more responsibility
But I do bear the you know the the physical. Okay. It was okay fine. I can I can we can agree on that. All right, okay
Bye-bye. Yeah, okay. All right, seriously though. He's getting docked pay. He's not paying this boy for this
Can we just have a serious discussion about what we're gonna do about kicking ben out of the pcp?
I think now's the right time. That's the right time. Listen guys. I've been sick of Ben shit for a long time. Yeah
I've been sick of Ben for a while guys. He doesn't offer into the podcast. He's got nothing interesting to say
He's got no comedic timing. He's a big. He's a big gay, you know
When he edits the episodes, I have to write the description for him because he never does
Oh, do you do that too? Do you do that too? I sure do all the unfunny ones are from me
I I think that the pcp can be shaved down to like maybe one person if I really stretch it
Yeah, let's just make it. Let's just make it the the tom Oliver show. Which person would it be? That's a good idea
That's a good idea. Um, you're gonna have to find it. It has to be Jeff
Only Jeff has the vision to carry some of the 21st century. Tom has all the attributes of a true pcp member
Depression suicidal thoughts my little pony addiction. What else could you want?
It's pretty good. Yeah addiction
um, okay
Anyway, do you have any other points about money or should we just go to the question?
I have money right now. I'm gonna buy a pizza hut after this
I'm gonna buy a whole pizza hut restaurant Nate speaking of money. Go pledge your parents' hard-earned money to the pcp patreon
Oh, of course everybody. Yeah, how can we not lead off with that everybody? Go?
Yeah, go go to the pcp patreon you get go to go to patreon.com
Go on patreon patreon.com slash
Procrastinators or whatever the procrastinates you get for five dollars. You get the bonus episode of the pcp
All of every month instantly. Yep. All of the you can get access to all of them
And also if you pledge at least one dollar you get access to the special
PCP discord chat and we're all in there and we talk to you fuckers like all the time and it's annoying
Yeah, actually because we love you. It's not just a fucking con. We actually go in there sometimes
And monkey just had a bunch of questions for our failed pcp episode
We just tried to record but they were going to be involved. So if you want to be on the show, it's another way to do it, you know
Yeah, all right. Well, that's it. I think are we good. Yeah, I think that's it
Oh and on that discord like your level of pledge you get like a different color if you want to be a cool guy
So if anybody wants to everybody wants to step up to the plate to be that true handboy 100 dollars per episode tier
You will look like a god amongst the sheep. So i'm just letting you know
This is a tangible benefit here. Do we have like like shirts yet?
The shirts are coming in fact
I was actually thinking that I might sort of film a little uh
Intro to this episode because the last one's already edited and just add it there because like I'm I'm getting I'm getting moving
I'm getting those up. So you might be ready right now, but soon
I gave you the clean the clean shit. You did you did so I've got everything I need to get like the basic shit rolling
All right, fucking there you go folks
Question time. Here we go
That's I think that's a conclusion. We all have we like money money is good
Money is good. I think yeah, I think we've
I think we also decided uh video games are good. Uh, and that's pretty much it
Go go go go go go to twitch.com
dot tv slash give and take and and uh and uh
Subscribe to my twitch channel. Go get an emote. I have an emote now
Go to you know, uh, twitch.com slash munchie wears tiny hats. I want to get an emote
So if you follow me, then I will have a better chance of getting them out one day. That's true
I what would your emote be munchie? Uh, my emote would just be a one
Of course, of course a very fancy ornate decorative one
It'll be there. It would like be like pixel heart like like paul veership, bro
Oh, and to give some closure to last week's episode. I did get my youtube channel back. So you guys didn't have
Of course, I forgot I've already I got it back before the episode even aired. So I'm gonna I was I was wondering
It's weird one week. I'm bragging about my subs and when it comes out my channel's gone
Next week. I'm complaining that it was deleted, but it's already back by the time it airs
We need to stop recording these eight days early. It makes us seem like we're crazy
That's the only way ben has enough time to edit them
Uh, okay, let's let's go to the questions. Here we go. Uh, I'm just gonna acknowledge as a block
Everyone's asking these questions about what is or isn't gay. Uh, well, let's just let's do an episode about that shit
You know, let's just do a bonus episode about that. I think we're gonna do a bonus episode about what's guys
By far the most popular questions we get every single week are about like is it gay to suck your own dick our traps gay
I think is the number one question
I've deliberately avoided them because I don't give a shit
But you're finally gonna get your answer if you become a patron the bonus episode is about this stuff
So, uh, and also if you listen to the insufferable social media argument podcast
We already answered all those questions me and digi so nobody cares about nobody cares about that podcast
That's that's the shitty podcast
Yeah, that's that's like the arm retrieval of your channel
Oh, no, yeah, it's true. Uh, okay. Here we go. So so so everybody a patron that'll be out
Uh, that that comes out like the end of the month. So that'll be in probably like a week from this when you hear it. Okay. Here we go
Uh, that's a terrible question
Nope, that's shit. Uh, oh here we go. Uh hashtag ask bcp. Oh by uh at hylio. Hey, it's my buddy hylio my music guy
Top 10 hottest sonic characters everybody. Let's uh
Shadow the head knuckles. I gotta go with ruse. It's obviously riyuko much. She's fucking gross. She's a woman and she likes sex
What the fuck are you thinking? Did everyone hear here?
Gibbs hilarious joke riyuko my toy because she looks like a shadow. That's funny. I'm laughing
What about sonic himself? He's pretty hot
Sonic's pretty hot
He doesn't have enough
He eats. Oh no, wait, sonichu, of course. So I roast you. Oh, yeah
Roast you probably the whole pantheon is available to us a rose bubbles chew angel chew or whatever name is angelica
That's an angelica rose a chew. I don't know the hottest is because I hate sex
But whoever has the eye who has the most justice and valor
pulsing through his veins is vex the alligator
What about that little bumblebee? I like that little bumblebee that guy's a fucking faggot. He's a beat. I hate you
They're worthless
He's a punk ass bitch. You know what drop his fucking lights out
I like I like the the robot specifically from sonic heroes that that was that is that male sonichu
It's no no. It's the robot that was with shadow and rouge or something. Oh that guy from from adventure battle 2 or whatever
Yeah, that guy was cool. All right. Forget this shit. This is a gay question. Uh, how about uh, here we go
At a die nile 2 2 7 asks if you could restart life from birth while retaining all the memories and yes
You have now. Yes, would you no changing made no no changing major events?
What a shitty question what that ruins the whole question
Why why would you do it if you can't I want to be the baby who predicted 9 11 and called
George bush on the phone the morning of and said
Mr. President sir, mr. President sir, they're about to attack the twin towers and then he just replies
I know
Oh my god. Okay, but you know what I've had a fiction. I've had a thought about this for years
Okay, does everybody remember that remember the movie jumanji the old one not the new one with the rocking shit
Yeah, yeah, so so at the end of jumanji after they finally win after like it's like 40 years later something after they
You know robin williams grew up and that other lady grew up
So after that thing happened so so robin william spent that whole time since he was a kid in the deepest darkest jungle in jumanji
And he survived and you know he did this whole thing
So like he didn't really learn anything about real life, but he did become a real boy
Like he's he's you know a big fighty action jungle man
So that's cool
But that other lady like the lady that was his like childhood friend who grew up and they they finished the game together like
That lady lived to be like
35 or 45 or whatever like a middle-aged woman
Having gone through society seeing everything that happened in the real world
She knows everything and we saw at the end of jumanji when like that year those times just passes normally
When they meet those kids again like they remember everything that happened
So this woman knows every major thing that happened
Uh during the time between like the 70s and like 2000 or whatever jumanji came out
So like why is this woman not the richest person on the planet controlling everything major that happens because she understands
And can predict every single event that happened. Why didn't that happen because that's back to the future
Is a different movie. Yeah, I'm just uh, she she should have been the god
Busted that's the future of shit like that
Speaking of shit like that, you remember you ever know the the
Lion witch in the wardrobe where the kids they you know, they the i'm talking about the original movie
I don't know whether the the other movie has this but
The they they'd live in that world for fucking years and they grow old and they're like, you know late 30s or something kings and lords ladies
And then they go back and they find the wardrobe again
They come back through and their kids again in world war two. Yeah, and i'm thinking
They know what sex is and now they're little children. What's gonna go? What's gonna happen?
There's gonna be child pornographers, of course. Oh, yeah
The only good porn actor
In inception leo de caprio and his wife lived in the limbo area of the dream world for like 80 fully years
So technically he's been alive for like a fuck 130 years. It's crazy
Sort of but yeah, it's sure. That's that's pretty goofy shit. But what what uh, what was the question?
Uh, I can't remember why is jumanji the greatest movie. Okay. Now. Let's move on to the next question
Well, because i'm a level seven christ consciousness member
I've actually been alive for 6 000 years and I've watched humans evolve over time
And I just have to say that it's uh pretty good and I knew
It's gonna happen by just wanting it to happen. I didn't want to
Okay, good question. You wanted the holocaust to happen. Yeah, I mean, I don't know. It's pretty funny. Don't you?
I find that I find that interesting don't you think millions of people die even lose those sea belts
That's pretty interesting. All right. Go ahead. How I got a question. What are all right? Would you rather?
um live for a hundred years or
live
100 million thousand years, but it's the same year over and over again
Oh, definitely that definitely that one for sure that one for sure because I can speed run that shit
Yeah, plus there are billions of people like you'll never get bored because you can always find like a new person to
Fuck or you know mess with or you know, there's tons of stuff you can do even living the same
I might freak out and lose my sanity at some point, but I'm willing to gamble that I'm willing to take a chance
Don't you think after like 30 years you'd run out of art to consume? There's no new art being created
What's the well you can just work on creating it yourself like you can evolve yourself and I'm not entertained by watching
my own art
No, but you can watch people react to your increasingly good art as you learn new shit
You just want to read youtube comments for a hundred million years
It doesn't have to be youtube you could become a fucking sculptor you can change the world you become an economic genius and uh, you know
You gotta do it in within one year
So that's not even that long
But you can spend like those millions and billions of years over and over learning new things that will allow you to speed run that
Shit, yeah, but I think I would just get bored like showing things up like I want to watch the next avengers movie
And I couldn't do that the thing is though. Yeah, you might get bored just with people's reaction because like, you know
You know what they're gonna do, but I don't know I'd give it a shot
I'd give it a shot
What happens if you die in this theoretical hypothetical thing do you just come do you start the year over?
you
No, because then that would be a way to cheat if you just want to get through them
Yeah, I can practice every suicide method and see which one's the best I could perfect it sounds fine
So how about how about oh, how about if you kill yourself for the rest of the year?
You're uh, you're conscious you can feel like yourself decomposing and then when you get to the end of the year you just reset
So you're still like conscious for the whole year. That's fine. All I want to do was just assassinate the president over and over again
So I would find the best way to assassinate the president
Dude, don't talk about hillary that way. It's it's a sin to talk about hillary that way. You can't do his name with was seth rich god damn it
And
Hey guys, welcome to twitch as my new speedrun killing donald j trump
I hope you enjoy
Let's move on here's a question that shouldn't be asked so i'm just gonna ask it to to clarify it uh at read or daryl asks
What is the current status of jeff as a member of the pcp?
Is he really was he really kicked out and banished to the phantom zone of the pcp guys?
We had a we had a just a a simple parting of ways because jeff was doing his own thing
And he he left it really was like we joke about it because it's funny
Yeah, but um, there wasn't really like a any big deal
It was just sort of he doesn't talk he didn't talk in the chat and he were like, uh, you're not really a member of us
Of our stupid gay group
I saw jeff anime expo and he was delighted to see me and I was delighted to see him, you know
He is a good guy. Okay, so that's done. Let's move on
Buy at poor sailing god. What chomps are characters each member most like no no skip terrible question
What do you mean? I like homestuck
I hate oh, please. I want to know what i'm like
Fine, it's a shitty question fine. Uh poor sailing god your question is shit. God mean
Uh, i'm i'm most like lord english
Uh
You're like you're like little uh, you're like a little caliburn. You will be yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I am like caliburn
Because because I hate women and I hate sex
I'm I'm most like uh aqueous of course my hero my god
My god
I drink I I love aqueous more than you love being alive munchie. I love everything on a new level
It is possible and I am proof. Yeah, okay good
Are you briska? Are you gay for yourself? No? Well, I'm not I'm not I'm not
Are you taveros?
No, no, I'm more like I'm more like john
Or terezi or so either one of those I don't know you are a trickster god like terezi. That's
Trickster god
A god of trickery give and take just just a sheer psychological genius
I mean, I'd I'd I'd be more interested to see what other people think I am because I don't know how to
Taveros no
All right, you're not you're not taveros. No, this is what you get
You're uh, you're dirt because you're gay as fuck. Oh my god
Nate you're like dirt. I could I am I am like dirt. I am pretty you like dirt literally stupid characters. Am I?
uh
No, no, no, I think lord anglis. He's grown up lord anglis. He's a real fucking aridon
Oh, he is aridon the literally the worst guy of all that's definitely that's definitely him
Okay, I'll make that. No aridon is a psycho who kills his friends and is just a generally bad person
No, no, no, you don't tell he's like he's literally a migtau. He's literally a fucking migtau elli roger person
That's really is you don't have to read this just for this hero character. You should check him out. He's pretty great
I think you'll like what you see. He literally shoots up his fucking friends because if some person won't go out with them
He literally
He shoots up his entire race. He destroys his entire fucking race because some girl won't go out with them
I always thought I was more of an itachi uchiha
Yeah, my favorite homestuck character. Okay, just take questions garbage. Let's do mine
Bugs good bad or important by jade morrow. We bugs are great
Didn't we answer that last time jane? I would expect better from you. I'm deeply disappointed with his shitty quest
Maybe he's looking at a question from last week that might not have been released yet
Uh, so in that case, I apologize jade. That's true. Are you fucking bully?
Still die. No, no, she she can live. I love jade. She's great. Uh, let's uh, what else we got here. Uh, no, that's terrible
These are all bad. These are one more good one and go to bed because I've been here for three hours
Yeah, that's true. Um, okay, here we go. Uh, oh, it's another one from at porous saline god
So here's a chance to redeem yourself. What's the worst porn you ever accidentally saw?
Oh
That that would be the first one I ever saw which okay, I was I was google imaging search
I'm not fucking joking when I say this funny simpsons images
I googled that
And and I was just scrolling through like like I got to page like fucking 60
I just could not get enough of the funny simpson images
And eventually I came across this was the first porn I ever saw and I felt so bad when I saw it
A cuck it was a cuck image of bart fucking lisa and millhouse crying in the background
Wow
That's great. I'm the one who drew that. I can't believe you found it
I know
It was it was sublime. Oh god all of that that's simpson's stuff
It it's like one guy who does it like I don't know
I don't know whose mom key jones
I've seen that as well. I think that's probably the same like it's just so bad
It's all right. So and after I saw for the first time I literally cried because I was like I saw sex
I know what sex is now. I'm not a kid. I'm not a child last week
He had no this was actually in the future. It hasn't happened
The worst porn I've ever found was also the best porn I've ever found and that was the the legendary pain olympics of of yesterday
I was gonna bring that up god damn it. All right, you there you go. So nominal stuff
It was the back in the old days on spank wire dot com
There is a video known just as you know the spank wire video
It was named after the website
But it's really just a compilation of the best of the pain olympics and it had some good shit in it
A lot of which was inspiration for things that I detail in the triflers
A word yep. Yep
Uh, this isn't actually bad at all
But the only thing I can think of it was kind of bad just by sheer volume
There was this website that was shortly for a very very short lived amount of time was free
I think it still exists. It was called pink tube called pink tube and basically what it was was it was amazing
It was a wall of porn and it would scroll past you and like there would be previews of every single one playing at the same time
And all you would have to do is either highlight one with your mouse or click on it
And it would blow it up and make it big and like you could watch that and then as soon as you were bored
You could close that and it would keep on going and there'd just be infinite numbers of them. It was amazing
Uh, but they were all great. It wasn't bad at all. So that's not relevant. I got nothing
Um, I love funny census images
Give do you have anything to to to top this off?
I don't know about accidental porn
I bet you see some freaking brisks. There's no that's always deliberate. What are you talking about? Yeah fair fair point
But um, I guess there's a couple times where I was just on google
And I clicked on an image. It was like
Before like google could could block stuff like this and it redirected to a page of
Of like, uh, old people having sex and blowing each other
Uh, like old gay guys. I'm like, oh
And it was like enjoy your porn asshole and I wasn't even clicking on porn. It was just like an image of like not even anything
And it just redirected me to gay old man sex and talking lemon party
Lemon party, of course
It wasn't quite that because I also saw that and I'm like good god damn it. Why are the people keep putting this on the internet?
Lemon party's cute. I think those old men are adorable. Yeah, they're just having fun
Uh, I didn't like it because I'm not old
Yeah, yeah, but everybody should check out the offended page on encyclopedia. Dramatica that has some good stuff, too
Sick, uh, can I just shout out just this is this isn't even a room we need to go into but at nyankwan
Ask the question, uh glass is hot or not?
And I just like that it's a it's a picture of a girl with glass
So like I think we know she's got a bit of a dog in this fight. I think
No, you're probably hideous, bitch
Everyone knows I'm a I'm a well-known glasses fetishist. So there you go. You know where I'm at. Yeah
Uh, okay, that's it. No need to go into that any further. Uh, all right. We're all done everybody
Wait, wait, no, no the best question of all time at jero rado red. Who'd be the cutest pcp couple?
Nate did use a classic the bin munchie is a new contender
No, holy shit. That's actually that's actually a real question dude. What the fuck yeah, worst question
Fuck is wrong. Everybody. That's a good question. Jer Jarad. This is the worst question I've ever seen
In my life, that's we've already done
What are you talking about pairing all of us off until like the one two pairings? It has to be jeff
Jeff jeff jeff x jeff is just jeff and i know like the two non pcp members. Oh
And that's a match between them and they're both racist
Of course, what about syde syde and his fedora? That's the ultimate pcp couple syde monkey is my favorite
I'm down with that. That's good. Uh, also gib and me. That's my favorite. Okay, there you go everybody. I'm literally gay. All right
It's dinner time. Hey, thanks for watching everybody. Thanks for sending those questions at uh, uh, we use at tp
Crasneers is our twitter, but you don't have to use that you can just use hashtag ask pcp
If you want to send questions, we do this every fucking saturday more or less
But hey, who knows you might send out a one every every once in a while
So so subscribe to the twitter just so you can fucking see that shit. All right. We're done. Thanks for listening everybody
We'll see you next week with another one
Become a patron
We just did best dogs
That's out and we'll do another one soon. All right. Bye
All right
I'm supposed to
Do it