You just don't get it. I could serve Earth from some alien attack I could pretend my life had meaning.
Meaningless objects can't give meaning or purpose to other meaningless objects.
Meaning and purpose. Ha ha. It would only be in your head, just like a god. It doesn't exist.
There is no free will love purpose meaning or reason to live.
I guess when I think about it, you're right. Love is just a result of hormones in our brains
and all other actions are determined by our brain. I guess everything is meaningless.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best guy ever
leader of a tribe called Quest. Welcome to the podcast with Digibro.
Heyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy
in Hippocrite. In Hippocrite.
Uh, I, you know, I have a Patreon, but it just doesn't matter.
But it would be nice if it would be nice if some coins fell in.
You know, it's pointless overall. We're all gonna die in the universe.
But you know, patreon.com slash my wrist.
That's the one. That's the one.
Pledge me one measly bitcoin per month on Patreon.
A bitcoin is worth like $67 or something.
Dude, I thought it was worth like hundreds.
I don't know if it's a bitcoin. You can only buy a car or maybe a HIV positive blood vessel.
Oh, this, I like where this meme is going. HIV.
Oh, what a good meme. I like HIV.
He never heard that one before.
Let's get right down to it. We're talking about how nihilism.
Nothing matters. Nothing matters.
I'm just gonna go, I'm just gonna go right out on record and say that it's true.
And there's no room for argument on this topic.
No, babe. I don't know what nihilism is. Nate, is there any way you have me know what nihilism is?
I didn't prepare this podcast at all. Please.
I'm rubbing my chakra nodes at such high speed together to elicit an answer from the cosmos.
And I'm getting something from UrbanDictionary.com slash go.
It's nihilism. Definition. It's useless to define it.
Oh, they got...
Oh, what a good one.
I'm pretty sure it has really gotten me.
I know. There's a really long one, but I'll just read like the beginning of it.
Okay, nihilism.
A philosophy based on extreme skepticism in its most basic form before it was clouded by...
Oh, God. Fuck this.
Yeah, that was going downhill.
It's a pretty high IQ to be a nihilist.
It says in parentheses, before it was clouded by ideas involving politics, social rhetoric, sex, drugs, rock and roll, etc.
Oh, my God.
Which we can refer to as epistemological nihilism.
Okay, that's fair because it's about the existence.
No, no, no. Well, that's bullshit because now he's defining nihilism as just one kind of nihilism.
What about the other kinds?
Well, okay. The next part is simply denies the possibility of knowledge of truth, which I think is relatively succinct.
The Catholic Church has really gone downhill ever since Pope Urban made his own dictionary.
It's true, it's true.
Hey, hey, before we get into any of the discussion, we should probably have like a blatant statement for like what each of us are.
Like, like, there's optimists, there's realists, there's pragmatists, there's dentists, there's abolitionists, there's Marxists,
or even the dreaded Beatlejuice, which is a spiritual anomaly trained in the dark arts of Spookradi and Guljitsu.
I'm a dentist in that I will put dents in your fucking skull, bitch.
Oh, shit, dude.
That's awesome.
That's sick.
Ben, what are you? How would you define yourself in this way?
I guess I'm a nihilist. I guess I'm a nihilist and I believe in nothing and I'm real cool.
Yeah, you can say I'm a nihilist.
I'm vaping and tilting my fedora and in my in my sick flame print Hawaiian shirt over here.
Fedora tipping for atheists. Us proud nihilists are more of the cluster punk variety.
We don't believe in fashion or anything for that matter.
Let me tell you how much of a nihilist I am.
I was torn. I was torn on, you know, you can be a religious guy and that sucks.
And you can be an atheist and that sucks, too.
Because, like, as spirit science teaches us, you don't pick just one.
You can't pick being an atheist or being religious.
Don't restrict yourself.
This is just boxes of belief and you're not supposed to be limited to one.
But then there's the middle ground.
There's the, like, oh, well, who fucking knows?
The being agnostic. But that wasn't good enough for me.
I needed to go one step further.
So I dug a little deep and I discovered something that's even more nihilistic than all three of those,
which is a theological non-cognitivist, which is what I am.
Hang on.
Okay, define that.
Well, okay, agnosticism says that we cannot know for sure whether there is a God or not.
Theological non-cognitivism is the statement that the question of whether or not God exists
is ill-formed and does not have any meaning.
The concept of God is ill-defined in language to the point that even asking the question
of whether he exists is not actually asking anything at all and therefore there is no question.
Well, I'm with you on there.
That's the level of nihilism you all are dealing with right here.
Yeah, I guess so.
I would just, like, it depends on what version of God you mean, I guess.
Like, some people believe it's like a literal entity.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is saying about God?
Yeah, I know, I know.
You would have to rigorously define your terms in order to ask the question in the first place.
But the point is that it's not well-defined on a broad enough level.
Oh, boy, I'm reading the definition of nihilism on Wikipedia, getting so excited.
See, there's different types.
There's existential nihilism means that life is without objective meaning, purpose, or intrinsic value.
True.
Obviously true.
Of course.
Moral nihilists assert that there is no inherent morality and accepted moral values are abstractly contrived.
Even more obvious.
Definitely.
But this is my favorite.
Nihilism may also take epistemological, ontological, or metaphysical forms, meaning, respectively,
that in some aspect, knowledge is not possible or reality does not actually exist.
Hell yeah.
The first one is true.
Oh, that's the real, that's the core nihilism.
Also, the second one is not true.
Well, yeah, I'll be okay, we'll see.
Incidentally, I would define a lot of those just aren't easily applied.
Hey, everyone, I just solved the existence.
I just solved the riddle of existence right here for you.
I laid it all out.
There's the answer.
Because I just picked which nihilisms are true and which nihilisms are false.
And there's no room for debate.
Dude, my favorite thing about this is that the little box on the side on Wikipedia is
part of a series on certainty.
Something about seeing these incredibly large concepts, like just thrown around, you know,
I love it.
I'm a label nihilist and that I don't believe labels are important and I don't care to
know what they mean, so I will just make one up.
How will you tell your fluffernutter from your mayonnaise without these labels?
You're fucked.
I just look at them and then I see.
When you're a young restauranteer and you don't label your fucking food, you're going
to go belly up quick before that little brrrr Scottish boy comes in and he slaps you by
the ear.
Well here, when I was younger, I used to define myself as a hedonist and I still do to some
degree, which is a hedonist is just one who believes that the purpose of life is defined
by obtaining pleasure and positive affirmation in this world.
I still, to a large extent, think that's true because the only concrete system we have to
operate along is positive and negative feedback as perceived by our brain.
In a sense, I still sort of agree with that, but I would call myself sort of like a pragmatic
hedonist.
Jesus Christ.
That's the funny thing about all these terms is that whether or not they contradict each
other is so vague because I would say the idea that there's no objective moral value.
That seems obvious, but at the same time, it's very easy to find and describe a functional
moral value.
To me, morality is obviously like anything that brings life is good and brings death is
bad.
I mean, sure, most people would agree with that, but that doesn't make it objective in
any sense.
Right.
Cancer is literally like just mutants and it's, and I don't like X-Men.
Sells are alive.
I don't like X-Men.
I think X-Men should die.
If something promotes death or marvels in the Mackey universe, then it's objectively
bad.
I guess to ask Nate about his pragmatic hedonism.
Do you think that it is in any way contradictory of being nihilistic?
Do you think that there is inherently value in being hedonistic or do you think it's more
like you appreciate that, but it doesn't inherently have meaning?
Well, I'm sort of jacking myself off a little bit by using a term like pragmatic hedonism.
We know.
Right.
This whole thing is fucking jack us off with big fancy words.
The fact that we're even using these.
It's really annoying me because like saying, oh yeah, this has no meaning.
Nothing has meaning.
Well, there you go.
That's nihilism.
But yeah, but like there's no different, like nothing, everything is, we ascribe things
to everything.
There is nothing inherent.
Right.
Inherency doesn't exist.
That's nihilism, hippo.
Yes.
Right, nihilism.
I know that we're all on board with that.
But the fact that there's so many different types is like, it's like no shit.
No shit that there's what there doesn't have.
Inherency in various different aspects of the universe.
But to answer Digi's question, though, so like the actual definition, I think it's just
like makes more sense is it's like this, whatever, pragmatic hedonism is just basically humanism.
So it's like, is human, like what is the, is, does that conflict with nihilism?
And I would argue absolutely not because my approach stems all from, at least I think
people try to say this.
I try to start with what seems to be the truth and then try to, from that foundation of things
that, as far as I can tell, are true, try to get to like the philosophy that seems like
it'll most get things the way I want them to go.
Now when you say true, you mean true like observable truth.
Not like a-
Because there is no other kind that we have.
Right.
There is no-
All we have is-
Object, there is no truth with a capital T.
Fucking observable truth is as good as truth.
So I don't-
Yeah, I completely agree with that view.
You know that thing where like you said, oh yeah, you can never actually touch anything
because your atoms are like pushing against the atoms of a thing.
Yeah, true.
They don't actually touch, you know.
I mean like there's no reason for that knowledge to-
Yeah, it's like you know what I mean.
I know you guys-
It could be helpful.
Like there is a reason for it, for that knowledge to exist and it's simply because without it-
To make you feel smooth, feel smart.
Without it we have like okay, if you're a religious person, then everything we're saying is blasphemy.
You know?
Like just to merely raise these ideas and like it's to make people understand that they're
like you believing in God doesn't make you right.
You know?
Like that's-
So you can feel smarter for not believing in God.
Well, so you can feel safe for not believing in God.
Busted.
So you can not be killed for not believing in God, you know?
It's to bust out all this science.
In casual conversation it makes you an asshole.
You know?
Like to just say this stuff apropos of nothing.
Yeah, if you're like you don't really-
If you're like oh I'm touching you and someone's like oh you don't really touching anything.
It's like a fuck you.
Yeah.
You know?
But like if you're trying to explain this to someone so that they can just like wrap their
head around the idea that you know there is no absolute truth in the universe therefore
we cannot have a religious society because it's based in nothing.
You know?
I guess I do see the purpose of nihilism to come up.
No.
Not in general like just like for once.
Like once.
Like every teenager should have a little pamphlet and says nothing exists you fucking idiot.
And then they read it and they're like okay they never have to talk about it again but
now they know and then they can do real human being things.
There's only a certain degree of like practical application that this knowledge has on your
life because like you're still gonna basically live everything the same way.
Even if you're somebody like me who doesn't believe that like consciousness or free will
are real.
Like you still operate in basically the exact same way and it changes nothing about your
day to day life.
That's why it's so funny to me that there's like 80 terms you know that's why it's hilarious.
I'm a fucking din of lions.
I'm surrounded by fucking medusas and ghouls and fucking monsters.
I am 100% an optimist and I will.
I'm an optimist.
That is not.
Oh okay.
I gotta fight you on this Nate.
Consciousness is the only thing that is real.
You know that is true.
I guess I wouldn't say that consciousness isn't real but I would argue that it's very different
from the way it's generally perceived.
Because everything in the world we experience second hand but our consciousness and our
experiences are they are the only thing that is objectively observable and truth with a
capital T exist in my humble.
In this faggot's humble opinion.
I hear you're coming from that.
Well then you're not nihilistic anymore Ben.
You believe in an objective thing.
Yeah yeah well okay yeah that's what I said.
That's why I said that the ontological nihilism is clearly not true because we can fuck there
are fucking things we can there are things that we can observe are true.
What if they're all a simulation.
But the mind experiencing that simulation can't also be a simulation.
I think okay that's a fair point and to just cloudy the waters as much as possible at the
very beginning of this discussion before you go any further.
I just want to explain to anyone who doesn't know of the simulation theory that it is entirely
possible that the entire universe that you live in right now is in complete fabrication
because think about it.
Which affects nothing.
There's no like even if that is true that has no bearing on you whatsoever.
None of this affects anything.
To even talk about nihilism at all is like the most privileged conversation you can possibly
have.
Like it is it is the realm of we have got we have accomplished our base needs so well
that now we can just think about concepts that mean nothing.
It's pretty funny like no matter how unreal no matter how much of a simulation the world
is if I cut myself right now it's going to hurt and I'll need a bandaid you know it doesn't
matter how unreal it is.
It could matter though.
It could matter.
It fucking could matter.
I would I would argue that that knowledge just like the whole thing about how like pushing
your finger against your other finger technically no matter is touching any other matter.
But then again what exactly is matter is it the is it the potential cloud of electrons
What the fuck is that shit.
We don't know.
Right.
I just wanted to say that I thought it was really funny that nihilism like nihilists
have the least reason to discuss nihilism because of how pointless it is to discuss nihilism
because they're nihilists and yet the Wikipedia article is huge and there's so many different
types.
Checkmate nihilists.
Yeah well hey go look at the Christianity Wikipedia page though.
I bet it dwarfs this.
You mean the Bible.
Oh my god.
The original Wikipedia.
God's been editing that shit since 6000 BC though.
But yeah I guess it can be fun to speculate on stuff like that I guess.
I want to hear Munchie's position because it sounds like he's coming from a different
position than a lot of us in this.
Oh completely.
Okay.
I think you basically have to be retarded and like low functioning like you don't have
brain cells like an extra chromosome.
Hey man I went to college.
You have to go to college to be this dumb to get a nihilism.
Exactly.
As plankton famously said in SpongeBob the Musical I went to college so you know it's clever.
Sinusism and nihilism are just like coping methods for people who have an Hercules the
snake of depression in their crib like I did when I was a wee boy.
Sinusism doesn't have to be linked to nihilism but okay.
I just want to Munchie I think you'd appreciate this.
My favorite explanation of nihilism ever was a wholesome meme that Jesse posted one time.
Where on the left it was how people think nihilists are and it was a guy like crying in the rain
and going nothing matters and then on the right it was.
It was actually the little rad kid from the 90s.
Yeah rad 90s dude on a surfboard thumbs up and he's like nothing matters yeah and that's
how I feel all the time.
For me it's the most it is optimism is nihilism is to be like oh yeah none of this shit actually
matters and I really want to reiterate that like the foundation of this whole thing and
I generally agree with that almost entirely.
I think we might use different words but I think all of us agree on things probably the
vast majority of it except maybe Munchie but like all this comes from foundation of observed
truths that I have then been forced to construct a worldview from so I'm just trying to be as
accurate as possible and I'm generally also a pretty positive person so even though I think
that like the universe is doomed and that there's like no hope of anything that's in it right
now surviving in a few billion years and therefore my existence is objectively meaningless and
pointless like that doesn't matter.
I mean maybe we'll just make you know I was hoping to do that.
You described meaning to things by being alive.
Yeah yeah I mean to say that it's meaningless is to like is to place it within a framework
of like of thing of value.
Well it's just objectively meaningless but it's meaningful within the subjective experience
and I do value the subjective experience.
Well here's the like yeah like for something to matter like what does it mean for something to
matter and it's like well that means that like someone cares about it so it's like so if you
care about something then it matters.
But see I wouldn't I don't quite agree with that.
I do believe that consciousness is a valuable thing and worth you know like respecting and
protecting but like I don't know if like human like if there's if it all ends one day then
that all was cool for the people who experienced it but there was no real point to it.
Well no no no you're missing you're missing the point because the point is that like you you're
saying oh it doesn't matter because in the end it will all go away and like that's fine but like it
doesn't there's there's no objective standard for whether things matter that you can compare to
whether something matters or not is a matter of opinion you know.
The universe does not work on a scale of is it worth it or not.
It just exists and it is and eventually it will die.
I make it my goal to care about the universe so that it does matter.
I want to put it okay.
I think that okay yeah like the like the nothing matters like that's like that like epic like like
like like law sick skill streak is you know nice and whatever.
However I like it when things are I like it when I care about things I like it when things matter
and when things matter I don't necessarily like I of course I am like I I prepare for the worst
and hope for the best.
I know nothing actually matters and I know that there is no real and like you know tangible
like spirit or ghosts or anything.
But you know I just like it when I prescribe mean things because I'm a human and I like to
that's the best part is that for something it doesn't take anything all it takes for
something to matter is just that you care about it and then it matters.
I think the main thing that this is all like based on is that when you're a kid you don't
understand that things might not matter because you think the universe is centered around you.
Everybody's talking to you you're the main character which I would argue it basically is.
Yeah I mean when you're a kid.
Only for Monty though.
Yeah true but then like as you get a bit older you realize that you're just one of many human
beings and you're not actually that special but and you think oh maybe nothing matters
and you learn to be a nihilist but then I think it's sort of like a like a maturing of that idea
in your brain that makes you you know once you think that nothing matters then you can
care about things because there's nothing in your brain telling you oh you should be doing this
because you know other people say that you should do it or your parents or you know some other
higher power or like there's no rules in the universe so you feel better and it's really just
like a like a transitioning period away from thinking that things matter in terms of like
you know stuff that you don't like like you know parents telling you to go to college
and you don't want to go and but you think you have to because it matters and once you realize
that it doesn't then you can care about real things.
But to say nothing matters in that context.
Like the question of things don't matter so why would I go to college that that's that's where
the pragmatic side of this comes in because there's no point in like like if nothing matters
why don't I just lay down and die.
Yeah that's the middle point.
What I was trying to get at is like the middle point is like why don't I just kill myself.
Like I mean some people do that but some people don't and it's like parents say go to college
and you think that matters intrinsically and it's like the thing and then you realize that
nothing matters but then you may come you may come to think I want to go to college anyway
because I think it matters and then that that is that's a good point like it's like there's
an intrinsic truth being told to us and I think probably all of us except maybe Munch when
we were young certainly got fed the college will be the answer to all your problems and
life and what you do and you did OK OK and then like you know it certainly can help in
some ways but like we have all grown up and learned that college is in fact not actually
a magical solution to all your problems economic and otherwise in fact it's a magical problem
that will ruin your life.
I am currently saddled with quite a bit of fucking debt that I'm slowly working my way
out of and in fact I'm not too far away from but like it has been a burden on me for years
and then like all my goal in life now is just to quickly get away from the you know you
know you don't have to pay off that debt because when your parents die then you'll inherit
all of their money and so their money is basically your money so well my parents are going to live
for at least a while.
I don't want to have to pay a student loan every month.
I was just quoting Ben's argument for why he's the last student of us.
I'd like to distance myself from that quote as much as possible actually.
So you've taken it back now I should stop.
I should stop explaining to people that this is Ben's fault.
I felt so shitty as soon as that came out of my mouth.
I was like oh god no come on.
That's an appropriate feeling to have.
It's one of my favorite things anyone's ever said to be perfectly honest.
It's very Ben.
Ben St. you know a stitches head out of the dumpster he's currently in and just spouts
off a one liner like that I don't want to know why.
I hate you.
That's all I have to say.
Oh fuck I completely forgot what I was going to bring up earlier.
Oh yeah.
So time.
Time's not real right?
Hang on.
I saw gun buster.
Well it's like another dimension right?
It's not that it's not real.
It's real because we can come up with a definition of what it means when we talk about time.
I spent a long time thinking that time was in fact not real and it was just a way that
we accounted for it.
This stuff was this way at one point and then things move and now they're this way.
It turns out that is in fact not true because time is a measurable phenomenon in the universe
that can be accounted for.
Time is like something that stuff in the universe experiences but it's not like there's like
an outside of time right?
What are you guys talking about?
Is it time obviously exists?
Is it or is it not true that all time exists at once?
All of the time of the universe's existence.
Are you smoking from the outside at all?
That's a fucked up question because you can't say that it all exists at once because by
saying at once you're referencing the concept of time.
Shit.
How can we get away?
Is there a time when time began?
I think they're probably what?
8.50pm.
Yeah.
Today.
You know what?
I really feel like...
Does the concept of beginning exist outside of what we...
Dude.
I really feel bad.
Doesn't matter at all though.
I feel like I should be the expert on this question because I have like a physics degree
but like I really don't fucking know what to say about this shit.
I fucking have it.
Time has just started.
Before that that was just like a memory, like a made up...
We just thought that all of our entire lives just happened.
Like that was just a joke as a meme.
It started now.
What you're referring to is a very common...
Yeah, go ahead.
Sorry.
I'm just trying to get at that like the end of the universe is already...
When it happens it will always be in the now, right?
Kind of like what CGP Grey was saying about how you don't die in the future.
You always die right now.
It's just not necessarily...
The thing about that isn't quite accurate.
It's not quite accurate to say that like...
It's not accurate.
It's just that we use the word future to mean a thing.
We know the future doesn't exist because it can never exist.
This is all some slippery language.
This is all some slippery language shenanigans.
I'm just saying that the universe has already ended.
Like it's already there.
That's not true.
But it's not here now. It's in the future.
It's in the future. There's time between now and then.
In this moment that I'm speaking.
Digi, are you just talking about the...
I forgot what the term is.
Like it's...
Time is...
Deterministic.
That's the word I'm looking for.
Maybe the universe is fully deterministic
and the end is already written into the beginning.
It's all in a set path.
Actually, you know what?
That's a great topic to bring up because I literally believe
that there is no reason to not think that the universe is 100% deterministic
because the only way that you could object to that
is to argue that free will exists
in some way or that the age is within the universe.
That argument makes no sense at all.
The existence of free will makes no sense.
Exactly.
You don't have to argue for free will to argue against determinism
because there could still be randomness.
That's true.
But the only way you can make that argument
is that you have to say that there is some force that acts on the universe
outside of just physics.
No, that's not true.
Randomness operates.
Some things can just be random. Why not?
Randomness isn't actually real as I understand it.
Is there any evidence for randomness?
Yes.
What is the evidence for randomness?
What I'm saying is that there are only
the types of forces that exist that we know of
in terms of physics as we understand it now.
Things happen the way they would have happened
based on cause and effect.
No.
There's randomness.
No, no, no.
I see the argument for not randomness is
say if everybody does the exact same muscle movement
throughout the entire history of the universe.
Anything that can move moves in exactly the same way
every single time.
Physics would follow, I think,
is the idea.
The whole universe would fall because
a person stepped on it twice.
And if they step on it,
the exact history of them
getting to that place with that particular shoe
and stepping on it exactly the same way
twice in another version of the same universe,
it would fall at the exact same time in the exact same way.
Let me just get this out there
so we can proceed with this knowledge.
The most fundamental physical things and events
happen at a small enough scale,
and at that scale things are determined randomly.
The best understanding of the universe
is that things literally are entirely built
on probabilities.
Isn't that just our best understanding?
Well, it might be.
If it's your best understanding,
it might just be our best understanding.
There could be something underlying it
that is deterministic, but we don't know that.
And why would we think that there necessarily has to be?
It just doesn't seem like it makes any sense
for anything to be banned back.
Oh, that's a great fucking argument.
Oh, it doesn't feel right.
Well, that's our best knowledge.
Our best knowledge, and it gets that quick.
Is it the absolute truth?
I don't know, but it's the best we've got.
I would say there's a difference between
functionally random and truly random.
This is truly random.
Our best understanding is based on true randomness.
Knowledge, knowledge, knowledge.
Here we go.
Here's some knowledge.
Photons.
They're like, what do you call them?
Paradoxical.
They can exist in two places at once, provably.
They did like...
I can't remember what it was called.
There's an experiment where they fire a single photon
in a thing.
And instead of like it being like a dot
that hits one, like there's this sheet,
a sheet of something that
detects photons, it was like
they shot it and it like
appeared in multiple places
even though it was just one thing and it didn't split.
Yeah, it's Young's double slit experiment.
Yeah.
It's not that the photons are...
I don't want to get into it.
Hang on, hang on.
It's possible that something could exist
in two places at once, but that's different from random.
It's not...
Since we're on this topic,
I'll flex my nuts a little bit more
and say that it's not so much
that they exist at multiple places at once.
It's that their existence is
spread across a continuum
of probabilities of location.
And that those probabilities...
Okay, so like the existence is a wave
form of probability that it like
undulates
through space, and that the measurement,
a measurement of the photon's location
will determine
and determine that it's actually located
at just one of those places,
but until the measurement is made,
it is not localized.
It is a spread of probabilities.
Okay, but here's my question.
If under the exact same circumstances
we were able to like...
form this experiment again,
and the first time that we did it before we reset the universe,
we got X result.
If we did that experiment again,
would we get the same result?
Or would it be somewhere else?
Our best understanding
of the phenomenon is that no,
we would not necessarily get the same result.
Okay, well that's important.
I think that's important to understand.
I think...
If I just have the floor here,
I think that all of this has been
the worst experience of my life
with all the reasons.
All of these...
All of these vague,
you know...
Disgusting, smart,
smart terms such as
slice of life, time...
All of these...
All of these terms, like words
and beliefs...
Munchie dropped out of Clown College,
so we wouldn't have to hear these kind of arguments anymore.
He was sick of all this fancy
and that's why he became a street juggalo
where the world should happen.
He dropped out of ICPU.
Yeah, exactly.
Here's my political
and philosophical beliefs.
It's a new thing that I've just admitted.
It's called real meatism,
where I believe in real meat only.
Which means...
All of these things,
like, okay, time.
You can argue all you want about
shit that doesn't matter, like time,
is there a beginning of time?
Sure, it's nice to know that
for textbooks and so we can know more about the world
so we can conquer it.
But that's the thing, I only care about that
because it will benefit me to know that
so I can destroy other civilizations
in my future.
I only care about
things that will impact me.
And I only care...
There's no reason for me
to care
about the highfalutin
concepts in life.
There's no reason to get bogged down
in the minutiae.
This isn't exactly what we were just talking about,
but I bring this topic up a lot
and I don't go into it too often,
but I would argue to you
I think there is an excellent case to be made
that you in fact have
literally no control
over your life.
You have zero control.
You are simply an automaton acting upon biological
impulses that are just physical
reactions to things.
Everything you think you're doing in your life
is not actually you. You're not accomplishing
anything.
You are a witness to the events happening
in your body.
Are you talking about free will or what are you saying here?
Free will. This is about free will.
Yeah.
Sure, I agree.
All of our actions are based on
what we have learned.
But here's the thing about real metism.
Basically,
I operate on
a language
I don't know how to describe it.
I operate on good enough.
Like JavaScript language or Python?
I run on C++ actually.
I'm looking for a degree here.
It's good enough
to say that there is free will.
Because everyone will know
what you mean by free will.
I can move my arm.
I'm not limited by a government
kind of robot.
I can do that.
Me and Victor have been on this weird
Cold War argument across our different
Digi Bros. playthroughs about free will.
Where he's trying to argue that free will
is real and I'm trying to argue that it's not.
But we're really arguing two different layers
of the problem.
I'm arguing it on a
metaphysical or whatever level.
What's the word I'm looking for?
Philosophical level.
He's arguing it on a
everyday life.
Oh my god, let's decide
what your life is level.
The only thing that you can
The only thing that can be
determined by
free will, yes, no,
is what happens when time
travel is invented. If you go back
and there's no free will.
When?
Can you change the future
and do timeline offshoots exist?
If free will will determine
whether that is how time travel works
or if it's the other way
it'll be a different way.
It will settle that question.
When you say
your atoms will not go together
and when you're touching something
you're not really touching it.
It's good enough to say that you are touching it.
That works for you because
you are a human and your eyes can't zoom
in that big.
You don't have that big telescope
in your brain.
That question could be useful.
I'm not saying that it doesn't
deserve to exist or that we shouldn't
research the sciences. I'm just saying
for all intents and purposes
for my daily life
I don't need to know that.
I need to know that in case I am a physicist.
In order to live a human life
I want to say that things matter
and the only
things that do matter to me are the things
that I can observe as a human.
That's such a limited amount of information.
No, but that's what I'm saying.
You don't need to understand anything
in order to determine whether something matters
or not because it's totally a matter of opinion.
Let's get over that.
Matters of opinion are only things that
are human.
Imagine you're at a party
or at some place and you're talking to a guy
and you don't know who he is
and
there's conversations that come up and you're like
did you know I'm touching this?
He's like yeah, that's true.
I like that one.
Because it's not annoying.
But if he starts going
I will actually atom some bullshit
and I'm like I just don't like you now.
You've ruined this friendship.
I want to state by the way
while this has been going on
I still like you hippo, so there.
While this has been going on I decided
I'm not a nihilist.
I am actually an absurdist
and I don't think that's actually
a thing people call themselves.
It's actually just a genre of fiction
but it's a better description because
I feel like nihilism
believes that
there just is no meaning
but absurdism is about
how humans can't find meaning.
Like that maybe there's meaning
but there's no
possible way that humans could ever understand it.
There can't be meaning
outside of a conscious
being that determines me.
That's just nihilism with a clown afro.
Why can there not be meaning outside of
Well, because like I've been saying
like I've been saying this whole time
meaning is just an opinion
You need to be a living thinking thing
in order to have such an opinion.
Are you telling me that if a tree falls
in the forest and no one's around to hear it
it does not make a sound?
Well, I mean
I see what you're saying
and I think it depends on what you mean by sound.
If you mean the physical
sensation of hearing a thing
then no, but if you mean
the concussion of the airwaves then yes.
Yeah, the
the vibrations of the tree
falling down will damage the tree
and then that will be
like you go and record it
like oh this tree has like sound wave
damage we can tell
use this new technology
to hear how this tree fell.
Has it not reached the sound until it's been observed?
Well, if there's a way in the future
there's like a special gadget
that can like scan
the vibration thing
of like a tree.
I don't know, I want to go here
alright?
If there's a gadget that can like scan
a tree to see how
like the vibrations have affected it
we can hear the trees like
ear, like what it heard
we can hear
what the tree is
and that would be fucking sick.
Yeah, like you're saying we could measure
the effects, the past effects
of a tree having fall.
If a tree fell through a vacuum
and made a sound.
How does it benefit the universe to have meaning?
There's no reason for the universe to have meaning.
Yeah, no, there's no reason.
Meaning is for humans to want things.
We don't know that, what if there's something beyond
the universe that has its own
why would you assume that?
Possibly know what that is though.
That's what I'm saying
like absurdism, it's where you can't
you just can't possibly know
because it's hard.
You have no reason to believe exists
if you're asserting that that's real.
I mean are you talking about some
like extra dimensional aliens basically?
Possibly or anything
like it's beyond
beyond my ability to imagine
is what I'm saying. Well I think that
yeah, well they might be different
I think like fundamentally they have to be
similar to us and that they have to be conscious
of thinking beings in order to have meaning.
Why? Why? I don't agree with that.
Because meaning itself is a concept
we have made up for a thing that we decided
that we wanted so like meaning as we
understand it can only arise from like
a similar consciousness.
I can believe
I can believe and agree with the idea
that we can't know where the homestuck is real
but I would like to know.
So the term meaning
is it accurate to say the term meaning
is really defined in sort of like
as the biological organisms are
we have biological imperatives
and we've sort of defined the word meaning
based on our desires and urges
as the creatures that we are
and like what we want to accomplish.
Is there anything beyond like what else could there be?
How else could you define what that means?
To change the subject slightly
I want to know if anybody else has this experience.
Do you ever have moments
where you like you're having
too good of a time
and you start to wonder
if you are actually
like this is all hallucination
like you actually lost your mind a couple years ago
and you're
you're sure.
No, I'm not quite that drastic.
Sometimes when I'm
with my girlfriend
I wonder if she's just a real doll
that I've convinced myself is human.
That's adorable.
And true.
What if
everyone's just humoring me
like
What if I'm convincing
ventriloquist.
That's where
Occam's razor is easy to
utilize.
It's be a lot of work for everyone to like
placate you and make you think.
What if I'm just an insane person hallucinating
everything in insane detail.
What if I'm just in a mental
facility.
Occam's razor is a useful tool
for deciding what's like
helpful, but it's not
a way to arrive at truth.
You don't determine anything
objective by applying Occam's razor to it.
But technically we could all be
we could all be aliens
playing different versions of Roy at the moment
is the idea.
That's correct.
I hope that that's true so bad.
Because then I can wake up and be like oh yeah
a blurb blarp.
In the event that we are all a simulation
would you still say that we think therefore
at least on a functional
level.
In this scenario
where you're just an insane person like begging your head
against a wall in an insane asylum.
And none of you are real.
For all intents and purposes this is real.
This is the same thing with the simulation
like Matrix World.
Does it matter that it's not real because you're
experiencing all these emotions and feelings
in real life.
Functionally and for all intents and purposes real.
You know what this touches on.
It really matters.
Objectivity doesn't exist.
That is true.
Let's talk about this for a second.
There are some things that are objective.
Just throw that out there.
When it comes to what we experience
our whole perception of the universe
and everything we know just comes
through the crude matter of our
senses and what we can observe
and what we can process into our brain through our eyes
our taste buds
our nose. Most importantly our dicks.
All these things.
None of them are perfectly reliable
ever. All the time we hear stories
of people who are hallucinating
so none of these are 100% reliable.
So all of this shit
could totally be fake.
Sure.
Ben you say some things are objective.
Approve it.
The existence of your mind.
2 equals 4?
That's objectively true
because we've defined those terms
into each other in a way that's just
a function of the system of math that we've created.
So that's definitionally true.
But outside of definitions
and things like that
like fucking
Descartes and all that shit.
The existence of the self.
It's a fucking old hat at this point.
I want that as an overheard conversation
in the background of a party
in Rick and Morty or something.
Descartes and all that shit.
So for you could be being fooled
and all the things you believe are true could be false
but for you to believe those false things
you have to exist in some form
in order to believe them.
The existence of the self
even if the things that you think you're experiencing
are not as you believe they are
the experiences themselves are real.
But it's only true from
only you can prove to yourself
that you are experienced.
We are currently proving to everyone
other than ourselves that they are real
but to us we are proving we are real.
I would argue that if you all are in fact real
which I'm going to give you the benefit of the doubt
and assume that you are.
But if you are real and experiencing consciousnesses
then your consciousnesses
and your experiences are objectively real
if they are indeed occurring.
If I write a character
and I write them in such a depth
as though they had full
conscious thought
like what if we are just
characters
I write down that with the Japanese Juggalo
and he is living with me right now
I can look at him right now
so I proved your point.
I don't see how you can get around the idea that you have to be real
you have to exist to experience something.
You could program a cyber brain
right?
Like what if we're all just going
through all the subroutines we've been programmed with?
Which we are.
That's what a mind is
that's what a brain is
that would be
we're all made of stuff.
The constant
with all of this
the thing that is always true
and the most objective thing
it is the biggest
waste of time ever
to talk and think and ponder about this
because it always comes back to
well I guess it might be
That's what you think until now we discover
like they didn't gun buster how to use dolphins
to travel through space
when we get them dolphins hooked up boy
but how can mirrors be real
if our eyes aren't real
on that exact quote
the objective truth shouldn't be pursued
just for normal instances it's retarded
this is what I was trying to get to before
I talk about how
the things that we observe we can't guarantee
that any of that is real or true
like is my color blue the same as what you see as the color blue
what the fuck knows there's no way to prove it
what I would say is that I believe
dude hold on real quick
you brought up that Vsauce thing
and I didn't even need to bring up Vsauce
Vsauce doesn't have a patent on that
Munchy said Vsauce
and when I saw that Vsauce video
it had pissed me off so much
because they presented that like it was this really mind blowing
concept and I literally
just thought that on my own when I was 10
I mean I think everyone does
what if your blue's not my blue
and I was like dude what if your blue
isn't my blue
and I was like are you fucking serious
oh that blue is in my mind
and that was why I never watched Vsauce again
Vsauce is just for babies
it is
I was thinking that as a baby
it's the first thing I fucking said
I just slid out the womb
I said that color is probably
different for you
I literally remember having that
realization and conversation
right after watching The Matrix 2
like me and my family were in a denny's
after watching The Matrix 2
and I was talking to Victor and I was like dude
what if your green's not my green
Matrix 2 much regarded as the most
intellectual of The Matrix series
but anyway
one time I had food poisoning
I was at my friend's house and then
the dad came over and they were like hey are you alright
I was like yeah but I don't understand
why can't I switch to the third person like I can
in video games
why are my eyes in this position only
why can't I see behind me
it's a real thing I actually said
while I had food poisoning that's not a joke
I like that
so
this is the thing that I believe
even though I actually don't have any
concrete proof that it is true
but I believe that there is a
highest level
an objective true
world
would be in a simulation easily
let's say I'm in The Matrix
we're up one level from that
we're looking at my body in a pod or whatever
so this is a higher level world
and that stuff all looks true
and even though the people up there
are still perceiving everything with their eyes
which makes it therefore objectively
not the accurate representation
exactly of what it really is
as true as the Lord Jesus
made it
you can go up as high as you want
through artificial world
through data escape or whatever
I'm talking about if you go all the way up
to the highest one that there is
I'm just saying this from an outsider
you just know that this is as high as you can go
if you know that that's true
the buck has to stop somewhere
it has to stop somewhere
there has to be an upper limit to it at some point
and
even though the people on that level
again they still have sensory organs
probably
perceiving things in the same way that's imperfect
but on that top level
the world that exists there
that is the objectively real
true world
that is the one
no one can experience that themselves
but it is there
and it is objective
that is what I strongly believe
even though I don't know it's 100% true
to me that seems quite likely
that that's the way things work
here's my philosophy
something may exist and all that
all that jazz
but getting a boner is pretty good
so I'm going to do that over and over
that's kind of
that's real meatism
that's a good segue
I think this is a subject that
in terms of nihilism a lot of people immediately jump to
and it's like good and evil
good and evil
is it real?
yes and I am both
at once
can we all agree
immediately that good and evil
have been defined by humans
they're entirely based on our
understanding of what we are
here's my thoughts on that
I strongly believe that
saying that something is good
is literally the same thing
completely interchangeable
linguistically
with just saying that you like it
bad is literally the same statement
as saying I don't like it
that's what it boils down to
people have tried to argue with me on this
and I've never been convinced that this is wrong
it explains everything
we should just replace language with little emojis
we should have a happy face
when you're good
yes
angry face when you see a bad man
you don't like him
I want to be able to downvote people in real life
and things and interactions
I'm gonna pee so bad
I'm so sorry
forgive me
dude
it could be like bronicon
you could have like a little thing around your neck
and if you're happy
turn it around upset
please do not approach me
I'm upset
I like how in real life you want to
lay on yours around your neck to simulate
what it feels like in your head
when you can just use your face
you've got a fucking reins attached to his face
that's what I liked about
bronicon
when are we going back? when
as soon as possible
so
I'm gonna camp outside bronicon to get the new
iPhone
like horse
are we done talking about Niles?
I've got one more point I want to make here
so Ben was saying all that bullshit
that I don't care about
but
like originally
the first life form that came to exist on earth
was functioning based on purely like
attraction versus repulsion
like attraction toward food
in whatever sensory organs it had to do that
and then repulsion from like probably things like danger
or yeah like danger
would probably be the only thing which is
it all just boils down to like
good, bad
like I want to go towards this food
I'm gonna go away from this shit I don't want
and we're talking about like a single celled organism
by touching it
and then it just like tries to stay away from shit that'll
like eat it or kill it or poison it or
whatever the fuck
so like I considering I think that humans are just
you know that organism
evolved and it kept evolving and evolving and eventually we've got human beings
people think that like the system
of morality that's in place you know
like religious terms have been passed down
but it seems to me all
super easily explainable just in terms of
again biological imperatives
so I just want to make this super clear to people
that good and evil
I don't think is objectively
true in any way but what I actually
I actually have a little bit different from some people
and I think that there sort of is an objectivity
element to this
which is that there are
it's even a little fuzzy to say but there are
basically objective truths
in that like there are experiences that are
like positive and negative for people
like death
not all the time but generally
that it is like an objectively
bad thing to do and I know I'm mixing generally
and objectively but like death is
objectively bad but what makes like
life occasionally like less
preferable to death is all like this terrible
shit happening that that corrupts
what life is supposed to be and like pleasure
generally preferable to pain
and so I really think this is my like hedonism
shit I think it makes sense
to like construct your life and your world
in such a way that you maximize
pleasure and minimize pain
and that doesn't even mean like hooking yourself
up to like a pleasure machine
or just doing heroin all the time
would it be like a maximize pleasure
and minimize pain, asterisks
unless you like pain
if so that would just be pleasure for you
it's like your thing
but with a little asterisks like unless not
unless different
but see I'm taking this to the macro level
because I don't even think it's just like
if you're a nihilist I don't think it makes
the most sense to just like or if you're a hedonist
just being really pleasured all the time yourself
I would argue is not actually
the most pleasure you can experience
I would argue that you're missing all kinds of stuff
that you can only expand maybe if we develop
high level artificial worlds
I'm back everybody, everyone stop the fucking presses
I'm back
I think I'm fucking
like the idea that you can't have
pleasure for like
if you have pleasure then you don't know
what pleasure is
and you have to have a bit of un-pleasure
I think this human brain
does that automatically
like I don't think
the human mind definitely
has a quick drop off of like if you accomplish
your life goal in a week
you're going to be bored of it you're going to want to do some other shit
like it's built to
like unless you're literally pumping yourself full of drugs
that's how it incentivizes progress
even then drugs lose their
effectiveness
happiness is a journey
happiness is not a destination because
if it's a destination you'll get there
and then you won't be happy anymore and the way to be happy
is to structure your life so that you always
have a goal to be working towards
that's what I believe
it will be great because we'll always be happy no matter what
there's no way you can ever be fully bored
you can just keep doing things
happiness is my penis
and see that's why
that is where this hedonism
and like humanism intersect
there is no reason to not
just act in a way to like maximize
pleasure in your life but it is not
maximizing pleasure in your life to just literally
go around like murdering people for fun
and then like
cause like that will your life will end very
quickly and unpleasantly if you just go around
doing that and then like doing drugs like
you'll die very soon you got to maximize
in the long term
not a lot of people want
then their pleasure is to do the things
that they want to do
in the case
they're being short-sighted
in the case that somebody likes murdering
it would be in their best interests
to just be really really smart
murder as many people as possible and never get caught
that's how they do that
what if murdering one person
would bring me more happiness
than the entire
lifetime of things that would
ever make me happy will
even if I got shot right after killing somebody
I would be
happier it would be more worthwhile
than having lived my whole life
there is no logical argument I can make to say that you shouldn't do that
but I don't think that's
very com-likely
and of course like this
and the other thing is like if this person
should keep in mind that like okay if everyone
acted like this society
would collapse and then you know other people
wouldn't have the opportunities to do these things
I doubt a murderer cares about Star Trek
why a murderer can still be logical
no no no we're talking about a logical murderer
who just understands this one thing about themselves
well here here's the thing I think
I think the fact that that can't happen
people are too scared to assume
that's what will happen like
if I kill this guy I'll never be as happy
as if I kill this guy they don't know that
for sure unless they're completely
insane and like you can't
have a logical person
decide to kill a person
that's not true because they don't know
what's in the future they may be like
well it's probably
it's like a bad gamble I'm not gonna take it
if I have a sister
and like she is getting like beaten up
terribly by like her boyfriend
and like she is like fully indoctrinated to think
that like oh no it's all okay but like
she's getting her worse and worse hurt and then like
it seems like like he's just gonna end up killing her one day
like he's got a jail work and she just will not leave him
there is a logical reason
to just go and kill this man
to like to kill him to like save someone
there is a reason to do that sort of thing
I don't know about it
but whatever she won't press charges
like it can't be done I'm talking about
a logical argument
I can construct a scenario
where murder is reasonable
correct
I'm just saying someone
whose pleasure is
the inherent destruction of society
by removing society from
being real because there are no more humans left
by killing people
I don't think he's too concerned
one two watch the world
bird there are clap emojis in between
all those words everybody
are we gonna move on to questions now
I've heard enough
I was in the middle of a point and you just memed all over me
go ahead
I'm just saying I don't think those people
are too concerned about like the society ramifications
like if everyone did this then there would be no more
then they are short sighted
because no one else is
first of all that's not what is occurring
Nate's trying to argue about
like what is and is not like the most
like the most like consistent
logical system not about
like what people should actually
do or like what they will actually
like lead people to
like yeah this is not
totally logical I understand that
Nate's trying to argue for like in a perfect world
everyone would think this shit through and come to
like a well reasoned conclusion
right I guess
in a perfect world everyone would do the Macarena
at all times at the same time
everyone would do the Carmen
dance or however you smell it
it could cause million dance
yeah it would be like
you do the
yeah yeah
the one where it's like you put your
fucking hands up to your head and you do the
caramel dancing
that's how real smooth
I'm doing it right now
I'll do it
alright I've heard enough big words
and big converts
yeah anyone
it's a cool thing
it's true except for the ontological
except for the ontological
except for the ontological kind all the other
kinds are true there you go
my ending
statement on nihilism is that
now that you've heard us talk about it
there's no reason to ever put it in the comment section
so don't comment
my opinion is hashtag
real meetism join me
and believing that the only thing that matters
is that humans do
and I would say this is important to me
wait I'm a nihilist and a real meetist then
okay
I don't limit myself to just one box
yeah yeah yeah
I would say nihilism is true
but there is absolutely no reason you can't still
be a humanist and get some of that
hashtag weird utilitarianism going on in your life
so don't be afraid
I agree with literally everybody
okay everything they just said
all right
let's get to some questions
if you want to get your question read
donate to PCP patreon
you can go to the patreon lounge
where we talk to all of our bestest
fans
it's a discord chat
it's not a lounge
it's not actually the chas
well not yet at least
until we set everything up
and also
we read less of these these days
let's get on the off chance
submit one to the twitter
using hashtag askpcp
let's get our designated for question
out of the way
here's our infinity rise one
asks how do you find a motivation to live
if the goal that keeps you going
seems impossible
find a better goal
that's tough
if it seems to be
actually easy
does it seem impossible
because if it just seems impossible
but it is possible
don't stop
if it is actually impossible
then give up
imagine that
the thing is like a little like a bouncy toy
in front of you and then like get your magnifying glass
and like look at the individual atoms of it
and then pick apart all the atoms
one at a time and slowly after like a billion years
you will have all the atoms of that
spooky toy conquered
and I think what you're saying is
it's possible to break it down into the small components
exactly
I said it in a funnier way and I'm god basically
that's great
if you want to become like a beautiful
thesbian world renowned
like Kevin Spacey
my hero
then you know it might seem impossible
but if you really
bust your balls and do nothing but work towards it
for 20 years
maybe you'll get there might need some surgery
if you're ugly you might need all kinds of shit
well I would say that if your goal is to be
like
literally Kevin Spacey
then like you might never get there
but if you make a better goal
that's like oh I want to like
you know do the kind of things
that my hero Kevin Spacey does
then like you can start working towards that
and that's achievable
or if your goal is like
I want to become rich and famous
by the time I'm 25
it's like well
aim for the moon because even if you miss
you're going to fall to the ground
dead
maybe
from the patreon
I was about to ask maybe's question god damn it
fine do it fucking punk ass bitch
I already have a list
I wrote down the good ones
copy pasting them
anyway maybe asks
are you the type of person who can separate the actions
of an artist from their art itself
or does the artist's personal life
influence how you like their art
the first one
it depends
I wish I could separate it completely
but I really can't
I think that I used to be able
to separate it more but as I've come
like I've come to
I guess I've come to feel that like
art is
really just an extension of a person
and so I don't
think I really can anymore unfortunately
I can still appreciate things
but like I can't
I can't fully separate
in the one sense
I would like
I like the idea of just like enjoying art
like oh did you know
that that song you like was written by a
peter far like well I don't care
it's a good song but
I will like if there's a horrible person
that has made a thing
I will do a little bit
I still want to experience it because I like
the thing but you know I'll pirate it
I won't pay the money
for that thing
I'm not going to stop pirating Hitler artwork
I decorate my abode with it
exclusively but it's not about
Hitler
this isn't a Nazi thing what the fuck
leave me alone
I would say I don't I can't
necessarily separate them
but like I will still enjoy
and consume art by terrible
people if I think the art is good
the only time that I won't
is if it has to do with me
personally
because I'm in the kind of position where I've gotten into
fights with a lot of
artists and had people
say things such as a certain
my little pony musician who I was a really big
fan of for a time who said
don't listen to my music
ever again and anyone who
associates with Digi Bro don't talk
to me so this artist who I was
a really big fan of I cannot
listen to even though it's been a long
time now and now if I hear the songs
I'm like alright
you know I still appreciate
why I liked this back then
I probably wouldn't even get into it if I discovered it now
you know but like there's a few
artists like that and even on a lesser
scale like one that was
kind of a weird case is the
rapper Milo who
it's not that he did anything to me personally
but he has a real problem with white people
saying nigga and like
he's like always on about it
and I'm like
you know that you're basically
talking to me
he doesn't have a problem taking like white
people's money though when they buy his album
yeah well he'll complain about like white people saying it
at his shows and stuff and I'm like dude
you're saying it on your fucking album
how can we not say it at your shows
if that's the case I think it would be
more logically consistent to be like not okay
with them even listening to the music because
it's not for them in his mind it's like
for these people or whatever
the way I look at it is like there's no
like if I like the person who's making
it then I'll like the art there's like
and you know vice versa it's just
sort of like a modifier that I put on my
enjoyment of the art itself like I
consume like a comic and it's like
a good thing that I like but it's made
by a bad person that's not like an instant
well I don't like it anymore it's just like
like a debuff well and also
like minus 25%
sometimes I actually think the art can be
enhanced by that being a bad person
like I think so too very famously
like control I'll delete my favorite
webcomic well there's a black metal
band called Bersam which is just
a one-man band this guy Varg Vikerns
who in the early 90s
murdered the lead singer
of another black metal band mayhem
over a financial dispute
he stabbed him 37 times
and pushed him through a glass door
he was in prison
for like 15 years
in Norway and
he's out now but he's also like a hardcore
nationalist
and he's currently
he is currently a daily vlogger
by the way just by the by
this like 40 something year old
Xcon
murderer well black metal
superstar is now also
a daily vlogger
who talks about like nationalism and pagan stuff
and
pagan stuff yeah so and he lives
in the middle of the card he lives
like in the middle of nowhere in the woods
and he's like a huge spur lord
and he's got all these kids
and he lives on like a farm he's great
like in my opinion
the music is enhanced because
it's fucking black metal so like
I want it to be evil
and abrasive and wrong
you know like I want
to know that the guy who recorded this killed
a guy you know that makes it even
better that's that's
why Nate wants all this Hitler
all this all the all the paintings
like it enhances the aesthetic
experience I mean don't tell me that
having a Hitler painting would like not be
an amazing thing that would be so sick
that would be the sickest thing ever
that's literally why controversial things
are really funny yeah
because it's bad funny
right so I think I think for all of us the answer
I get a giggle every time I walk by my hitler portrait
it's very fucking funny
I think the answer for all of us is
like generally yes though
it like like it's not that we
separate it per se but just that we can enjoy
we can enjoy the content
without necessarily
contributing the the artists
like it plays a part in
our enjoyment I don't mean to harp on this
just it just decided I don't mean
to harp on this but like just just the Milo example
that did you brought up like I'm just thinking about that
like is it like okay
so obviously that guy like has is writing
music for like a specific group of people I like
but he's selling it to everybody
but like do you think if he could he would only
sell to black people or something
I mean on some level I think that might
be the case because he has made like
really exclusive tapes and stuff like that
but I mean I don't
think it's that I think a lot of it is more
that he's expressing that sentiment not
that it's like an absolute in his life
but he does express
like the sentiment in the lyrics of his songs
and sometimes it can feel like an attack
on me I just
get behind that at all that logic I just don't follow it
there's this one
thing that I
is like kind of relevant to this is
there's this TV show called the Great British
Bake Off where people bake is a competition
that is serious
do they get a baked as fuck dude
yeah
yes yes
trolololo
alright
this is a show
and it's great and the whole
nation loves it it used to be on BBC
and then the runners of the show
asked the BBC for more money because it was raking
in the viewers and the BBC said
ah no
so they left they just said fuck you we're going
to channel 4 instead
and people there was like a big hubbub
like channel 420 you know what I'm saying
trolololo
we can't don't
you're quite finished
I'm finished for now
okay
channel 4 and there was like a big hubbub
about like some of the presenters left and some of them stayed
and the show was great
it's still like exactly the same show
and I love it but people were like
oh I don't know whether I could
you know betray the BBC
and the presenters that I know and love to go
and watch the same show just on a different channel
like there was a
everyone was talking about it and I just didn't get
like and it's kind of the same sort of thing
like the artist
in this case is the producer of the show
like they said oh he did a bad thing
he left the BBC
and it's like
I don't know it's the same thing
too much
a lot of brand loyalism tied up in that
exactly
brand loyalism is the same
as artists separation
I don't even care if any of us try to answer this
I just want to read this because it's so badly written
it made me laugh
I think it's just an honest mistake
but Han Todd says
sandwich slash restaurant
if you have one
they got like good
good Philly cheesesteak sandwiches
Sub Jarrod at Subway
he's my man
sandwich sandwich
oh boy
a sandwich sandwich restaurant
a lot of little sandwiches
between two pieces of bread
and you're just biting into that motherfucker
alright
question
this one I'm interested in
because I think it could be different for everybody in here
plastic gargoyle
asks
do you guys often experience people acting as though
they're good friends with you based on their consumption
of your content
and what is your view on people treating consumption
for creators content as a sort of analog
for interacting with them
well I'll just jump in and say
that like I started
me and Jackie started a discord not that long ago
and it really took off
and it's like really really active
and I don't
I mean people would send me tweets and stuff
being like nice to me and I'd be nice to them
but like it was not like
friendship per se I don't know
but like I actually have become like pretty good friends
with a bunch of like these people in there
but would you say that was based on the consumption
like there's a difference
to me because I have the same thing
I also have a really active discord now
for my Patreon
when those people talk to me
like we're
I don't know they don't really act like we're all friends
but like it's okay for me
to me for them to like joke around
because we have been talking
like I know who they are
there has been in the past times where people
have come and been like
not really a whole lot
this isn't like a common occurrence but there have been times
where people were like buddy buddy with me
who I just don't know who they are
and I'm like uh do you
this happened a lot of brony con
when people used to follow us around and stuff
and be like real extra friendly when we were like
I literally do not know
who you are you know
yeah stuff like that sucks
but like I think really like when it comes to like
just talking on like on a discord
it's basically the same as
meeting new people except them knowing
your channel is just the icebreaker
and you don't have to do any of that
it is a great icebreaker and I will say
in spite of how I just made that sound at conventions
um
I don't mind so much when people come up
and like know a lot about me because I'm not surprised
because in many ways
it is pretty close to knowing me
like I put out so much content
and like express so much of my life
that like
the amount you I mean yeah there's
tons and tons of my life that you don't see
in the videos but a lot of that
life is reported on in the videos
you know so like if someone
came up to me and they were like up to date
going on with me that wouldn't surprise me
or be weird I'd just be like oh yeah
of course you know
I usually have a pretty easy time jumping
into in depth conversations with my
fans at cons at first meeting
like people I've never heard of but if they
come up and they're like oh I watch all your content
then we can just dive right into conversation
you know the worst thing
I mean I don't want to shit on anyone
so you know but this just does happen
is that
you know people come up to you and say hey
I really like your stuff or like in any
situation online or off
and you say oh thanks
and then they sort of like
feel like there's a rapport going
there's like a conversation and they expect you
to continue the conversation
when they used to have a light board of me
that kills me
I still like I've got a couple of discords
that I run and I will get messages
or like friend requests from individual
people and most people
you know actually to be fair
most people just know that like they shouldn't do that
this is actually pretty rare
I'm shocked how few friend requests
I've gotten from my discord
but I deny them all of course
I've got like hundreds of people in there
and I've only gotten like three or four friend requests
I know I scroll this back right now
I accept that shit man
you don't know anything about these people
yeah I do these are people that I've like talked to
some of them I would accept the request
from if they sent it but they haven't
but like you know
okay I'm looking I'm looking at
I got a message right here that I'm just looking
I'm not going to read it out loud
it's a tiny bit personal
but like I don't know who the fuck this person is
and this person is like wanting me
to like give them my time
like hey let's talk
who the fuck are you
I get that literally every day
and I don't
ever respond to them
but I don't know if that's the same thing as acting like my friend
it's more like the requesting to be my friend
alright stick with me here
but I consider this a form of violence
alright this is a form of violence
you are attacking me with a conversation
and you are
there's no way I cannot waste a little bit of my time
on dealing with this
you are stealing my time for me
even if it's just reading it
this is not a serious
I'm not seriously accusing anybody of this
that goes a little like
what this guy is asking about is more like
acting like they're already your friend
but that the idea of like
asking to be my friend
that happens all the time
and sometimes the phrasing of it
is super bizarre because it seems
to assume on their part that I would
be interested in them in some way
like when I got recently
and apologies if this guy happens to be listening
but it was strange
he said like what if we
met up some time he was like hey
I live in like a relatively near
area what if we met up some time
to see if we
like are as similar as I think
we are or something like that
and I'm like why would I want that
like who would ever want to hang out with someone
similar to Digi bro that's just
I mean I just
why do like I'm not out in the market
for like new friends right now
like it's not something I'm like
like the idea that somebody might be similar to me
but he is Digi so fuck what you want
like fuck what you want
I've got the reason I have
what becoming a friend
with someone is like I have a discord too
I think we all have discords
on my discord it feels more like
that I am just one of the other people
in the discord and like people post
things and talk about things and then I comment
on them and I say silly things
they say silly things it's just sort of like
I'm a community with
my community and that's like the best
situation I'm not like a figurehead
I am both a figurehead and that
in mine like because
I have a whole channel of just discussing my content
and my content comes out all the time
there's definitely a level of deference
towards me in there but like
to me the reason I
have a big audience is that there's
plenty of people like me
you know like there's plenty of people who are similar
enough to me that we can have a conversation
so let's have a conversation here
online that's what the internet's for
you meet people who are kind of like
you and you have some conversations
like not every person who's anything
like me is gonna make me be like
oh well we gotta be best friends
yeah and then like miraculously if you
end up talking to someone and you just like are clicking
and it's just like then like okay you know what
we're hooking up let's let's do something on our
own but I mean that was us basically
that's exactly we are that that's correct that's correct
so see that's that's how it happens it's gotta be
a natural thing guys don't don't fucking friend
me if we have not had a conversation just
don't do it munchie did you have any
you wanted to read out of this chat
before I get to I only have one more but it's
uh I don't know
alright I'll just like I'll do it
just fucking whatever munchie do you
real real quick just want to like delete
yourself from the PCP real quick
yeah I'm just I'm just go ahead and
remove myself from all future endeavors
I'm just gonna Leon Trotsky
myself and fucking remove myself from
all so all the podcast
I'm just gonna delete them all they're all gonna be gone
just put a high-pitched
wine over all of your speech seconds
in all the PCP so far okay
it'll be like Marvel
it's like slender man like
like
like slender man is near you
you'll get sickness oh that sounds good
we should make a let's literally make a channel
that's called PCP minus munchie
where we do that we just upload all the content
there are people who would like to be
really thankful for that
and I fucking think that they should
they should all get the fuck out of here
we should make a channel called
just munchie
we should make a channel
that's like PCP plus
Marvel Hornets where we just all
we just is Marvel Hornets but all of us are the different characters
we should make a show we should make a show where munchie
just literally bitches about my little pony
content creators for like dozens of hours
oh my god can you imagine
we should just make a show
where we read a homestuck
week by week and then move through
weekly munchie don't you ever
fucking say that again munchie do not even
speak of such an idea I don't want to hear about it
alright alright here's one
that I'm just going to answer really fast
HappyD asks
does slash will the PCP have a cap
on the number of members yes
the cap is the current number and it will never
exceed this number again
ever there is no
reason it should or will ever
happen you know honestly
unless it's really festive
unless it's really really festive like the mild point
oh it's like a you know in an
rpgs how you get like temporary party members
who join just like the specific dungeon or something
yeah maybe maybe a little
yeah there might be some guests but there's no
there will be another core
member of the PCP again
the number is going the number is only going
down from here guys
we're cutting corners
I'm going to replace myself with Father Christmas
I thought they meant like
how many people are on each podcast like the limit
to what they can record but I have no idea
why would they mint that that no yeah
yeah no that's already the case
okay okay
just theoretically
it's possible but just imagine the gauntlet
that the next person who's like a viable candidate
to join will have to go to like the years
the years of training
the only way another person's going to join
is if it is a case like Munchie
where literally all of us have known
and been friends with them for like three years
and he had to prove his
worth you know like
investigator was everything I hoped
it would be
change the game
he proved his worth
with the lecture
the parkour 291 lecture
there's no doubt
alright one last question
no digit asks how would you optimize the PCP
delete Munchie
yeah
and it's good
the PCP is a chaotic
blip in the system
optimizing it would mean smoothing out the whole thing
like smoothing out the wrinkles on the brain
exactly oh my god
yeah we don't want to be optimized we'll be deleted
we will be removed
I think if I was going to optimize the PCP
obviously get everybody
in one place
which is what we already want to do
once I'm in a room never just eat the key
I think it would be
easier for us to if we wanted
to talk about like more topical stuff
on the PCP it would be easier
if we could all consume it together
you know that's true like if we all lived in one place
it'd be easy enough for us to all like
go see a movie
that just came out and then do a PCP on it
right after this
that would be pretty sick
imagine the reputation
that our gang would acquire at the local
cinema place
oh my god
the PCB boys
are rolling through again everybody
put your park is on
there's about to be a jizz hurricane
we would be ruffians
I think we're at
we're at a
point where we're probably like
five or six months out from PCP
headquarters starting to become a thing
we're getting close
and I think it's
perfect timing because we can only
stretch random ass
weird esoteric concepts so far
like as you saw this episode
nihilism
like this is a weird topic
and you can only do so many
nihilism podcasts
you can only have so many
you can only have so many podcasts that spiral straight
to weird utilitarianism
immediately and go there forever
all roads lead back to weird utilitarianism
this is clear
it's the rock upon which the PCP
rests
from the beginning of the PCP I think we've been saying
we need to have more specific media casts
but there's nothing that all of us consume
guaranteed enough
that the rikstie minutes will pop up
or Dark Souls 3
rikstie minutes is the worst thing on this channel
it's even worse than Armour Tree
rikstie minutes was like
significantly more popular than the PCP for its time
which was interesting
Armour Tree was been out forever bro
there's only one episode on this channel
that's what I was saying
the special
I just want to read out this real quick
this is just for me no one else can answer
extra Pharisees if you could insert yourself into a movie
that movie in Y
a chindler's list
but what?
as in what?
only the Germans
is the protagonist that guy who played Voldemort
who was the leader of the Nazi camp
that's who I always empathize with
it's really sad that he lost
I actually want to ask this question
I don't think this is a good question
but I could be wrong
because either this guy's a weirdo
or there's more weirdos out there
Pondedator2 asks
how often do you think about speedrunning
while you're playing a game
for me it's pretty much constantly
to the point that I almost can't think about games
in other ways
well that's fun
is this the first time you play through a game?
I mean I will say that
occasionally when I'm playing a game
if I see something
that looks like
something a speedrunner would use
I would say oh that's obviously the speedrun tech
like maybe once in a blue run
that happens
like every so often
I think of a game and I'm like wait
have I seen a speedrun of that game
but that's like months or years after I played it
I don't think about it at the time
the fact that
I am in the
I'm in the midst of people
who like speedrunning
more than they like esports
genuinely sickens me and ever since
I've never been able to forgive any of you
that's my opinion
I don't know that I like speedrunning
more than esports
esports is just a lot harder to get into and follow
I like speedrunning
like a speedrun you just throw on a youtube video
esports you have to like
watch cool ass matches bro
I don't even know where one matches
watches a match of esports
you fucking google it
how do I know what matches are interesting
you're good
you got research
you fucking watch Melee
any day of your life
just move Melee to Melee
top 10 tournament
I know Melee esports
the last one I remember though
is Hungrybox beating Armada with Jigglypuff
and after that I felt like Melee's over now
like we've done all we needed to
that was all I wanted to happen
and it happened and now Melee's over
my friends back since college
have been into the competitive league of legends
scene just like following the
the past
disgusting
I have never understood the appeal
I have not once understood
I get the appeal I'm just not interested
leg of leg
there was a brief period where I was subscribed
to Thorin
the guy who's like a
esports commentator guy
not a commentator but he makes videos about esports
and all of his like broad concept
videos explaining why esports
are interesting were really cool
and good but then he would like
have like a video a day
about actual esports and like
they're all written in such a way
that you need to know an incredible amount
of information to get in
like it's oh fucking
sorry I was interrupting
no it's just like I
I don't even know the rules
of the games that are being talked about
enough to like much less
the meta or the tech or the people
you know like I'd have to
like the only reason I know smash
melee is because I watched that
fucking four hour documentary about it
and even that is considered like
entry level you know
sure it's cool
fucking Sal TV
a TF2
commentator esports guy I love
that shit I love esports
fuck you
on this guy's question
on the guy's question of
speedrunning I'm playing a lot
right now of
of world renowned game
for the Nintendo Switch Mario Odyssey
that literally everyone agrees is a beautiful
masterpiece with no attractive flaws
of any kind
and I do like I'm always
playing that game to like optimize speed
and I have actually researched like
the optimal ways to place for like maximum
height on jumps to like get to secret places
and stuff and like there's a lot of races
to do in the game so like I sort of
think I know what he's talking about but
I don't know it sounds like he's taking it to a higher level
our Italians
I just think it's weird that
he would ask that question
like clearly he's a
speedrun guy
like clearly he has a deep interest
in speedrun so he thinks that way
why would he expect anybody who
doesn't speedrun constantly
to think that way he knows none of us are speedrunners
if he watches the PCP
well we have done the races which is more than most people
have done but like in all of those
we make it very clear that this was like
an intensively researched project
for this one video
you know that's true
I don't think any of us has ever given the impression that we are speedrunners
oh
someone asked me a question directly
they even added me don't do that but thank you
and I just have to do this out of the kindness of my heart
how many hats can you fill in your head
depends on their size
depends on the size of
Munchie's head that day
yeah yeah yeah
how many hats have
you had on your head at once
and I have put four on my
like actual hats
not joke hats
well wait
wait what's a cap
what does that mean
I didn't say cap I said joke hat
oh I have six
I've had six hats on my head
are you stacking them on top of each other
cause that's easy I'm talking about next to each other
on your head to create a full half sphere
on the top of your head
can you get more than two
I've done three
and they've all been real tiny hats
if they're tiny hats you can do it
for sure
and he's with them
he's with tiny hats
alright that's enough
alright oh by the way
okay thanks for listening everybody let's plug our shit
please go
that was the most sensual enough I've heard
enough yeah I meant to just do it
I'm only quieter but
okay in any case I seduce the
I apologize for seducing the entire audience
forgive me
hold on Nate this is a great question
stop by Ferguson in the Patreon
do you think the PCP is too niche
to get a sizable following
no we just need more people to donate
to our Patreon that's the only
that we need to have grow
so please do that
please head on over to patreon.com
slash the procrastinators
there's a total of eight out right now
at this moment you have pledged $5
you're instantly able to access all of them
the latest one is about alcohol
previous one was about ASMR
and it's very sensual
you're going to want to listen to that whole thing
at maximum gain
the next one is going to be fucking out of this world
it's going to be a doozy
so brace your anal prolapse for
imminent destruction
so it's going to be good
let's not spoil it yet
stay tuned everybody
follow us at tpcrastinators
on the twitter for updates and what not
and you can hashtag ask pcps questions
but you're better off going to again
patreon.com
slash the procrastinators pledging
even as little as $1
and you're in the patron lounge when we ask those questions
that's where we read most of them these days
oh we got new shirts
we got stickers people with little chibi versions
of all the PCP lads
the stickers are legitimately great
and we got shirts, pcps stuff
there'll be more merch coming
everything you could want
child of bees going out of the back
it's got to be much
it doesn't matter
child of bees doesn't matter
oh we tied it all up in a bow
I think that's everything
thank you for listening everybody and we will see you next week
I gotta put someone back in their place
bye
yeah
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
why did come
jerking