I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
The year is 2022. The year of Jorts the Cat's milkshake ducking. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators
Podcast. It's November 6th, and this is America.
Well, I'm not in America.
This, I say gesturing wildly around me, is America. How's it going?
It's going quite well. I'm having a good day.
Well, that's just great.
It is.
I'm really happy for you.
And why Ben Saint, are you unhappy today?
I'm not in a good mood. I'm not in a good mood.
What happened with your lecture?
Oh, yes. What happened with that was the render, it's an eight hour video, the render
was going to take about 100, 120 hours. And basically, I should have done this sooner.
I should have done it right away. I would have caught the problem.
I had uploaded a draft version to YouTube because I went into the description to add,
what do you call them, chapter markings?
Right, yes.
And so I was adding them on the draft version, and I just noticed an editing mistake that
happened a bunch of times, and it was unacceptable. So I was like, well, I fucked up. I have to
restart the render. It was already almost done by that point.
Dang.
That was like five days of rendering, and then it finished. And then I just like, well,
I got to fix the error and just start it again. So it's going again, and it is now at 52%
of the second pass.
Oh my God.
It's quite far.
Yeah, yeah. I think it's been going for about a day and a half? No, closer to like two and
a half, two and a half days.
Well, you know, whatever. Doesn't really matter if it comes out last week or this week. I
said last week, it'll definitely be out unless something fucks up, and it did. So, oh well.
I was a little surprised that you spilled the beans on what it was on Twitter before the
video was like uploaded or rendered, at least.
Were you?
Yeah.
I don't know. I just felt like I would have expected it to be like keeping it a secret
until it was ready to be shown.
I thought I thought clueing people in early would build a little bit of anticipation. The
reason why I didn't want to say anything about it earlier was just because like, what
if I lose motivation? What if something goes wrong and I can't do it? I revealed it as
soon as I was like, well, there's no stopping it at this point.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, like I kind of always meant to tease it. So I guess I'll say it again. It will
definitely be out this week.
Unless a terrible catastrophic thing happens again.
Unless a terrible catastrophic thing happens again, which you probably won't.
Yeah, there was a visual effect that plays every so often, and basically for the first
half of the video, the effect was playing like 10 seconds early, which is like completely
wrong. So it was pretty bad. So I was like, well, I can't leave it like that. If it was
like maybe one time that it happened, I'd have been like, fuck it. But it happened like
10 times.
I'm in a terrible mood.
What's so desperate to feel better that I did body weight exercises this morning. I woke
up and I was like, I have to move. I have to do something. So I did body weight squats
and push-ups. They have not been working out, unfortunately. I think I remember feeling
better when I did workout. So if I start exercising again, maybe it will improve the situation.
It is a pretty guaranteed thing, just blood pumping through your veins and stuff.
That's does do something.
That's what they say. That's what they say. Yeah. I went and hung out with an old college
friend of mine the other day, and that was fine. But I felt like I had very little to
talk about, and that made me sad.
That's it.
Like things currently going on in your life or just like topics you didn't have anything
particularly interesting to say about anything?
Things currently going on in my life. I'm not doing anything. I'm not meeting new people.
I'm not even like reading or watching anything. I don't know. I'm not doing anything.
They are making a video. Got my stupid video. Yeah. Yeah. But it's been like five days since
I was working on that. It's been basically done for almost a week. Now what have I got?
Well, I started editing the Slime and Punishment book again. Man, I started this year. I started
this year being like, I got to finish the Slime and Punishment book. And now it's years coming
to an end and I'm just like, all right, got to finish that Slime and Punishment book.
Everyone says Twitter's going to die. I hope it does. Yeah. I regret every moment I've
ever spent on Twitter. Twitter, like doom and gloom. It seems rational enough. I feel
people are like, I don't know, getting a little too worked up over the idea of Twitter not being
around anymore. There was a time before Twitter and we liked that. That was fine. We're just too
used to it, I guess. I don't really believe that anything is really going to change.
No, I don't know. I think Elon Musk wants to make good on the extreme money he put towards it,
so he's going to try and make it as appeasing to advertisers as possible. So the whole free speech,
all the bad people coming back, I don't think that's going to happen. I think it's just going to be
the same until it just becomes untenable and then Elon might try and sell it.
The things that are the most bad, the worst things that I'm seeing for Twitter's future
prospects are that it'll throttle your metrics. It'll throttle your visibility if you aren't
a $8 checkmark. If you aren't paying for Twitter, if you aren't paying for Twitter Gold,
then your results will be not favored in searches, even if people are following you or something.
I don't like people having checkmarks. I also don't like the idea that anyone can buy a checkmark.
I think they should just get rid of checkmarks if they really wanted to improve the website.
I mean, checkmarks have some utility in the proving that this is the actual person,
because there's something for that if it's like a politician or something.
I guess so. But the fact that you can just buy it removes that utility and adds nothing.
It does make it worthless. Any questionable value it might have had, it makes it worthless.
Yeah. I mean, all you'd really need to do, though, to make it completely useless,
but even more so, is to just download a browser extension to block
checkmarked people from appearing on your timeline. It doesn't matter how high up in
the search results they are, they'll just be destroyed. I mean, if everyone did that.
I'd do that. I'd do that immediately, because all the cool people do not want to pay $8 a month
for Twitter. Yeah, but the average Twitter user is not going to do that.
Well, sure. I can't remember exactly, but the idea that if you're following someone,
even if you're following them and you're not following this other person,
their tweets might appear first, just because they have the money, they have the checkmark.
I'm like, well, that's essentially the same as like a promoted tweet,
which I block anyway. I block as many of those as I can, because I don't want to see
things that I'm not following, because they're ads. And so people paying for Twitter,
they are become the ad, so I get rid of them.
Hmm. I mean, my tweets already don't do well and nobody sees them, so throttle
away, I guess. I won't even notice a difference. Yeah, that's another thing.
I don't think of Twitter as a career prospect for me. It's just sort of like a place
where I post something stupid. And if it's funny and make someone laugh, that's pretty good.
But it's not for like, it's not like a stage where I'm trying to put on a performance,
it's just sort of like a like a waste paper basket where I'm got like a bunch of like shit
I'm thrown at the wall and throw it like just thrown it in there. And then sometimes there's
a banger. And I'm like, hey, yeah. I guess there is like the like posting art is useful,
letting people know about things that are going on with your work. Yeah, because people don't
really subscribe to newsletters and email lists. And it's funny how many artists use Twitter as
their main platform, even though it's like it's really not it's really not designed as like an art
platform. It's just it's just where the people are. So yeah.
She's got a post there. I'm seeing all like that. Where are you going to go? Where are you going to
put your stuff? And I'm like, geez, I don't know. I guess Tumblr because that's the only one I've
had experience with. And I guess I'll just try and I never used Tumblr. I'll put like, well,
no, that's not true. I use it a bit, but I never like was attached to it.
I got kind of attached to it. It just sort of it. I mean, it's kind of the same as Twitter.
You just sort of like you follow people and sometimes you see things that are stupid and
people overreacting about something. And then you post your things and then sometimes you get a lot
of likes. It's the most analogous. Yeah. Yeah. I feel you, dog.
I don't know. I don't want to use Tumblr. I should stop. I should stop using Twitter. It's
a waste of time. I don't even like it. I don't get anything out of it. I'm sick of it. I'm sick of
it. I have discord with people I can talk to, which is a finite resource if there's no new people
entering. But I don't know. When it comes to like talking to people, having like a community,
Twitter is not the place for a community really. No, it's really not. I should have made more
videos. I should have put more videos on my channel instead of making all the like thousands and
thousands of tweets that I've written. Should have applied that time a lot better.
Yeah. Coming up on 10 years I've spent on Twitter.
Wow. Maybe nine. I mean, some of those times I was more on it than others. But yeah,
I just want the 10 years back, please. I think I started a little later. I was on there in like
2015, 2014. I was looking through some of my older tweets just because
and I remember that I would only do puns. I would do puns so often and so many of them
that I'm like, wow, I was funnier. These are like, they're so all over the place and a lot of them
feel like I was funnier. I feel like I used to be funnier. They require a lot of like setup,
but they're like, yeah, I read that and I'm like, that's funny. The things I do now are like,
what if I was cringe, but actually not? What if I was base? I don't know,
like the tweets I'm posting now, they're sometimes funny, but like the style of humor is different.
I'm like, wow. I see. I see. I've just, I don't know, I haven't just haven't really been
making tweets lately. I don't really, I was, I was, man, I was scrolling through.
It was for the Simon punishment book. I'm formatting the notes. I'm at, I had written like
notes in Erata, but I decided that I want to add in some records of like me and Chris's DMs
and like the images that she made for me, like like the cards that she made out of the
out of the comic panels and stuff. I decided to put a section or add that in. So I was going through
my old Twitter, you know, replies and stuff looking for those. And oh my God, I just hate,
I'm so annoying. I'm so fucking annoying on Twitter. I'm so terrible. I hate myself.
You have been very aggressive with the, the, the replies to people being stupid.
I, I don't, that's not, I don't, that's not even what I'm, that's not even, that's the,
if anything, that's the one thing that I like looking at my tweets is times that I mean to people.
Yeah. Sometimes I do, I have enjoyed like going through a thread where you've gotten into a
scuffle with someone, like read up everything that's happened and they're always in the wrong, but yeah.
I'm always in the wrong. No, no. Well, I can't remember. Sometimes, but most of the time you're
not. Maybe sometimes, maybe sometimes. I mean, I feel like usually when I'm mad, I'm mad with
purpose, but that's not even what I'm talking about. I'm just talking about, I don't know. I just,
whenever I, when I have like a genuine opinion to express, I don't know. I always feel, I,
reading my old tweets, I'm always like, I'm so ham-handed. Like I'm so, I'm so like, I'm so like
bluntly expressing just like a completely banal opinion, but I'm saying it in a way that like,
it feels like I'm doing something and like it's so stupid. I should have, like I should have just
not said anything. Was it banal at the time or is it just sort of like, like, I mean in hindsight,
it seems banal. I don't know. My fucking stupid, when I was like really like,
when I was really like election posting around 2019, it's like, shut up.
When I'm really, at times when I made some like really stupid, I don't know, you know,
some garbage that no one cares about, like trans rights or something or like, that Bernie Sanders
is good. You know, it's like, why did I, why did I bother? What was, what was the thing you did
by Bernie where Yang or something? Oh, I don't know. I might have said, yeah, that sounds vaguely
familiar. Like, like, how's, like, what's, what's the joke? What am I, what am I doing?
What's the bit? I think the bit was that you liked Yang for a bit and then you're like, wait a
minute, nah. I know. That's not even, I know. That's not funny. It's not funny. It's just sad.
It's just sad. I don't know. So I felt really just terrible. I felt just really terrible reading
through all my, a record of my thoughts and opinions from the last several years. And it
just made me think like, what am I doing? What's, what's the point of me?
Oh, no. What's the point of Ben saying? It's not good. It's not good, dog. I don't know.
Well, I mean, Twitter's always been, I don't feel too good about it. Twitter's always been like,
the quickest and easiest way to be the worst version of yourself.
It is.
So don't feel like that represents you entirely.
Maybe. Maybe. I don't know. I should live in the real world more. I just, I just don't know how.
I've forgotten how.
I think a lot of people have forgotten how. What do you do? You just, you walk around and you,
you bump into someone and then you say, oh, sorry.
That's what I do. Yeah. What do you do? You walk around, you walk around, you walk around outside.
Do you like, I don't know, I take me and me and my, me and my buddy. We went to a bar,
but like, we just, we just sat there. We just sat there and chatted, same as we would have at the
house. Like they say like, Oh, be social, like go out to a bar. Well, we just sat there and talk
same as we would at the house. We might as well not have left the house. Like, what's the point?
Uh, what is the point?
Nice drinks, a nice atmosphere, maybe. Sure. Sure. I guess. Sure. I guess.
Just saying it wasn't, it wasn't like, I don't know. It wasn't like an opportunity to meet people.
No. It never, it never feels that way.
It, I've never experienced a time like that in a bar.
No. It's, it's sort of a bygone age sort of thing. People already have their friends and
go to the bar with them. Yeah, it seems that way. And they meet them earlier in life at school or
at work. And yeah, that's the only two places that seem like the normal place to meet a person
that's not artificial. Yeah, that's right.
Bleak. Bleak.
There was a little bit like with social media, like Twitter or whatever,
you would find like-minded people, you would retweet this stuff. If it was good,
they might find yours and retweet it. And then you'd have like a Twitter buddy.
And then, yeah, and then, uh, you know, hypothetically, you go to a convention,
they just happen to be there or that, you know, you can do some sort of like,
like breaking ice first contact through social media and then become out in the real world later.
Doesn't happen a lot, but it's like, it's something.
Yeah. I guess. I don't know. I don't really have that. I don't have Twitter buddies.
I have people whose posts I admire, but it's not the same.
Yeah. Think about the way the PCP formed. It was kind of that, but on YouTube specifically,
we made videos on a social media platform and it's like, you're good at those videos.
Let's meet up on the internet and we got a Skype.
Let's do a podcast or whatever. Yeah. Let's record a-
We're content creators.
A conversation between all of us. Yes. We are content creators.
Uh, yeah. That was, uh, that was pretty good. You know, I feel like maybe these
problems, the problems of not living in the real world, not having opportunities to
socialize, I feel like maybe those would solve themselves if I could find somewhere inside of
me some sort of passion for anything. And then I would naturally pursue that. And then,
you know, things, things would happen around that. But alas, there's nothing there. It's just void.
Void void. So, you know, it's a truly, truly is a vicious, a vicious and self-compounding
a cycle that I find a vortex that I find myself in I mean and that's why I did pushups this
morning to cope with that cope pushups are good all pushups are good and yeah they felt all right
I would do them again I obviously can't speak for you but like surely um passion for certain
things exists it's just it's just that like they might not be a creative endeavor they might just
be like a video game or like I don't know some probably that you could get into I guess I like
making gummies yeah I guess I like that uh it's it's it's fine it's fine at all I don't know
finding I don't know when you feel like you have not because I felt like that before as well like
seriously like lacking in in a passion for anything it's like wow why would I do anything
hmm what is and like like nothing is gonna lead to anything and it's gonna and I'm fucked to no
matter what it sucks you know it's like they're all like depression talking points you might just
have a big depression that you need to work through and then you'll you'll remember that
you actually do like things but the you know working through depression by yourself is very
difficult because you're in a you're in a bad headspace of space where like your your conclusions
are faulty and based on uh on like exaggerated negative like outcomes that you're imagining
are definitely gonna happen or have already happened and you know yeah your brain's compromised
I think yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah well I mean I guess so I guess that makes sense
uh I don't know get you a therapist for real
oh no there's there there there it is you've got a passion for not getting a therapist
see yes yes the one thing that gets me out of bed in the morning is the idea that I can spend the
whole day miserable like hell yeah another day that's gonna suck it's really it's really like
the obvious thing and the fact that you don't want to do it means it's good it's good for you
hmm well I don't want to do a lot of things I don't want to jump off a bridge
yeah but you don't think you don't stand by a bridge and be like ah jumping off the bridge
I know I should jump I know I should but like I just don't want to not yeah no that's not what I
mean it means it's like um uh when you're like scared of an outcome of something that means you
want to do it because you wouldn't care at all if if you if you weren't scared of failure or scared
of of it being fucking worthless perhaps I'm scared of my video failing yeah so that means
you care about the video yeah I really do yeah I actually like um on on the one hand you know I
sort of in the video I explained this and then I restructured my patreon and stuff I explained
that like okay I want to like focus on these more I can make more of these I can make you know I can
do a reward as like a like we can have a vote I'll let people choose a topic for me you know I want
to lean more into this um and that's like so on the one hand I it's kind of scary like okay well
if the video completely flops it's just going to be really embarrassing and I'm going to be like
well I guess my whole plan had no legs and I overreached and committed a strategic error
and now I got egg on my face what a rube on the other hand it's like oh well if it does succeed
of the video does really well a lot of people pledge like yes I want to see more like this
I love long youtube videos I want to vote on a topic for this idiot to explain it's like well
then I got to do stuff and that's scary yeah uh so yeah but I'm but I'm just I'm just um
the way the way things have been going uh cannot continue you know like once the once like other
than the slime and punishment book which I have been encountering hurdle after hurdle for
like what am I really doing like I'm not really working on any any videos or something
not I'm not like actively drawing comics although I do intend to do more of that in the future so
it's like well if I can turn if I can turn my big hit if I can turn my biggest hit the lectures
into like a a sort of semi-regular thing that I do for a semi-stable income it's like that seems
like that seems like a positive direction to be moving in so at some point I just decided I'm
gonna I'm gonna make this that I'm gonna do that and do my give it my best shot and I just
committed to it followed through on that notion even even though I wasn't really feeling it a lot
of the time even though I'm like oh this video is so embarrassing like oh I look really bad like
oh what am I talking about like oh I I'm repeating myself I sound like an idiot uh I just kind of
had to step outside and look at it from like an outsider's perspective and be like you're kind
of you're those things those things don't matter the object objectively the thing to do is just
is just follow through on this thing that you've already like sunk you know so much effort into
you you can't you can't give up yeah and I didn't it's good it's good to keep busy I would say if
you if you're like um you have you're in between projects that's a moment where your motivation
can like plummet because you're not currently working on anything you have to think yeah um
so you should try doing a small thing that can sort of bridge the gap between the megaman lecture
being released and whatever you do next if the lecture is a big hit you can work on start working
on the next one if it's a big flop you might have to do something else maybe go back to one of your
comics yeah but you should have something going on in the background something you can be saying
you're you're working on you could do commissions that's quite an easy little thing oh I hate
commissions I know that sometimes they're they're really rough because it's like but like it's
something I could I could do them like I could I could do them you I don't really like doing them
so I've I've avoided it mostly yeah uh you could do like a really small short project like a short
comic or uh I guess it's nano-rimon national novel writing month you could write something
I do feel I've been saying this for a long time I do feel like I should write more I feel like I
should try to write essays yeah but make sure you're on the one hand right now on the one hand
I feel like maybe I should write I should write essays but but simultaneously I'm like well but
I'm but I'm but I'm leaning into the lecture thing that's that's mostly unscripted so that's
kind of like two two different things why can't you do two different things I I don't know it's
just impossible for reasons I don't understand you could have lectures and essays yeah I could
I mean I guess there's no like there's no like expectation of like a lecture every month or
anything like that yeah I don't know I would like to write essays but again it's like I just don't
care about anything enough to write thoughts about them I don't know I wish I wish I had something I
was like really excited about and I'd be like man I have thoughts about this thing I'd like to get
them down in like written form and then maybe record those that writing in audio and put it on
YouTube or something that would that would be pretty that would be pretty great I was talking I
don't know if I talked about on the PCP I probably did a little while ago I had an idea for a
hypocrite video I spent a little time um thinking about like how I would go about getting the data
necessary to come to the conclusion because it was like a it was a lore-based video it was like
trying to stitch dark cloud and dark cloud two together in a way that they're deliberately
unconnected timelines could connect in a hypothetical sense and it was just sort of like
okay so I'd have to play both of the games and pay close attention to all the dialogue maybe I'd
have to go to the Japanese version you know there's there's lots of things I could do and I was
stunned to write like a plan I never really got into actually thinking I was gonna do it
but that was that was an enjoyable little like a thought experiment like the the concept of that
I don't know why why I thought of it but like it's a game I like and the sequel is like notorious
for being similar in so many ways but completely divorced from the original story from the first
game the sequel so it's like so why why are they why is it why does it look so similar why
does some characters exist but the story is completely different universe so you just had no
intention at any point of actually doing it I I still might do it it's not like I've abandoned
the idea it's just sort of like that's that's the the the nexus of like a cool idea is something
that I'm familiar with from my childhood I mean I mean it sounds in I'd want to see that video
yeah I mean sounds like a good idea to me I think I might do it it just would require a bit of like
planning around playing the game imagine a hypocrite video in 2022 2023 it'd probably be at this point
just because I've got I've got like um focus on on Clarissa first oh yeah how's that going
um this past week since the last pcp I've hadn't really had a lot of time because I
went traveling for a few days on halloween and I came back and I was tired from that and then
I just sort of didn't work for the rest of the week I was so like hey whatever
so I'm gonna work properly we're gonna get back to it properly next week
um it's just like a mini holiday I suppose
but it's it's it's close to the end like it was last week
close to the end of the like sketching out and sketching yeah
sorry I should know this remind me how many pages how many new pages sketched are there
like do you say like 30 or 50 there's like uh I'm trying to remember uh sketching hasn't started
like the the ending is what Clarissa but blocking it's like 100 and something new pages
maybe 130 I'm not sure I'll have to properly count them because I still might add like a few
on close to the final few shots and then I'm gonna have like a an epilogue bit which would be like
five pages maybe um so yeah it's a lot I might stream it I might stream the line art or something
maybe the sketching I don't know sketching is also quite mentally taxing because you're
it's not that you have to figure out where the panel sits in the page layout and what
information is being explained in the panel but you do need to think of how the body looks how the
pose works the what parts of like how best to portray the thing that I've already decided must
be portrayed in this panel that's a lot of thought it goes into that probably gonna have to draw and
redraw things a lot so maybe I shouldn't stream the sketch but the line art would be like
hopefully very nice and chill and like just hang out it could be something
you know I tried uh streaming uh the uh the other day for rfck and it was mostly successful there was
like a moment where the stream died in the middle uh because my internet just like stopped working
for a sec still disappointing I I don't know what that happens
huh do you know what that happens that that seems to have happened just in calls like you can't
access web pages but you're still in the call yeah it oh god I'm damn it I'm connected through my
I just checked and I've forgotten yeah even even right this moment I am connected through my
mobile hotspot which is terrible it's seriously like every day that like some shit happens and
my internet dies and I have to switch to my fucking phone hotspot and even in that fails
sometimes as well it's it's honestly like unacceptably bad and I don't know why like
it's been allowed to be this way but like I don't hear anyone else complain uh and I don't know who
to complain to and I don't know if it would accomplish anything uh because I mean we have
internet service it just sucks yeah I guess if the plan is not good enough you would just need to
try and improve the plan get a different maybe I can just tell that guy like hey I'll just pay
extra for a better plan yeah that's that's a solution honestly do you have like the thing
that goes in the wall that the booster um yes but it didn't uh like the guy the guy told me
that they already have one that's like okay I don't really understand all right I don't know
what he the the extender is supposed to like extend the signal he told me that like they've
already got an extender but it's like in his room like right next to the the the the router
or the modem or whatever you call it and it's like well what's the point of an extent the
point of an extender is that you put it further away to extend the signal yeah so like I think
I'm already picking it up out of an extender uh I don't know uh so you know what as I as I explain
it I'm thinking maybe I should try it regardless of the fact that he told me it was unnecessary
maybe I should try setting it up I tried setting it up before and it didn't work and I don't remember
why it didn't work but maybe it's worth another shot I don't know yeah I don't know I don't
know if it would even help because it's like I'll have a signal it'll tell me that I have a signal
but then like web pages will just stop loading or like discord will just die or the voice call
will die or the stream will die even though it says the signal is strong and and other other
times it says like no signal or like interrupted signal uh internet Wi-Fi is confusing I tried
to figure it out a while ago but I don't think I really gained any knowledge I think the one thing
is that there's two types of things there's a plug in the wall like booster that uses the
electricity the house and there's an extender which is different and it extends the Wi-Fi signal
somehow with a little antenna and the the booster you plug the router
into it and that goes into the wall and then you use the houses like electricity grid and then
out of another socket you can have the Wi-Fi like be transmitted through the you know wherever you
put the the other socket thing and that's what I have in my room and my internet's fine
shit otherwise the Wi-Fi doesn't reach yeah you can plug like a LAN cable into like the thing that
comes out of the wall so I can have wired boosted internet that's not actually connected to the
router but I don't know too much about it I don't know whether that's a specific brand that's able
to do that or I don't know I thought I thought the internet I guess at my last place was bad
this place is like at least as bad so that's disappointing yeah what were we talking about
before we got on that subject streaming Clarissa oh yeah yeah yeah I guess I was just talking about
stuff that I was doing uh that was it I was yeah Clarissa
oh I did those commissions you know I only got three commissions when I when I had that thing
I did them like immediately and I was like okay I'm on top of things and I got no more so if I'm
still they're still open because I have you know the time I can I can you know nestle them away
as long as I don't get like 50 and I don't expect to judging by the response
so like one or two more I can do so go to Twitter if that still exists and see my commission thing
it's still pinned at the top of my page yeah go to youtube.com slash ben saint slash megaman lecture
to and check to see how many views it's got and if I if should I be embarrassed of myself
or not well every journey every youtube video starts with a single view a single view a single view
and that's your own the uploaders when you're checking it I see I think that video is probably
going to accrue views like steadily over like a long period of time it's I don't think it's
going to be like a smash like hit out the gate but I think more people will like discover it
maybe it'll get a boost for the 35th anniversary later this year you know you know
I do know yeah that's my hope it won't solve my problems but even if it does well it won't
fix my life what are you fighting for what am I fighting for how does he how does he say
far he's kind of you know here's a here's a fact I I talk about the what am I fighting for
clip a bit in the lecture well there was a new running shine there was a new running shine video
this week that just had like the most briefest little like cutaway reference to a clip of zero
going no this can't be happening he didn't even he didn't even play the the what am I fighting for
and I realized that I'm that I'm a hack and I'm a loser and I'm not funny because that guy
he's so far beyond my level he doesn't even have to show the thing he's talking about we all know
we all know about what am I fighting for it's passé to even mention it oh you feel like yeah
you're bringing it up would be like um yeah then we know what we're fighting for
yes oh no yes exactly yes exactly it should it should it just it doesn't need to be stated
it it she goes it goes without saying frankly well I mean there's always the person who's never
seen it before god it doesn't hurt to be comprehensive in a big huge hour long hours long video on the
subject yeah I yeah I mean I'm sort of kidding because like I know that like sort of the whole
point of the video is that it's comprehensive but also it just doesn't I just don't feel very cool
oh no but but my mom said if I made an eight hour long mega man lecture I would be cool
the only thing that can make me feel cool is if it gets like a million views
the only the only thing that will be cool is if it does really well and I look really famous and
then everyone will be like well yeah this video is stupid and cringe but like it performed really
well so I guess the guy knows what he's doing I'm serious I'm totally serious everything I make is bad
by default the only the only way that I can prove the only way that I can even suggest otherwise
is like is if it does well in the market and then market logic trumps like you know gut intuition
and like feeling in your heart feeling in your heart the feeling in the heart is that this guy
sucks this guy's not funny uh dude I hate this video but gotta respect the view count
it literally yes literally yes it's my only hope
uh I feel completely differently I think if something's cool
and nobody knows about it I just feel cool that to have known about it it's like hell you know who
I you know who I think might suck um the uh I'm a little I'm not saying this for sure but I'm a
little I'm a little sussed I'm a little sussed by the umami guy the guy who makes that clown cartoon
uh clown I don't know I think he might be a crypto head like Elon musk fan who I don't know who umami
um um here you will recognize the character uh let me just get an image here for you
yes yes posting now oh I think I've seen like the first like video in this series or whatever
with the weirdo I've seen a bunch of them yes I think I think he might be like an NFT Elon guy
well yeah don't we're not gonna ruin my day I'm not I'm not I have to find that a bit disappointing
because this guy this guy makes pretty cool this guy makes pretty cool videos that are awesome
I don't know this is just I just I just see him I just see him liking some things on Twitter
that I'm like why would he like that well think he emoji no exactly um I hope I'm I hope I'm wrong
maybe he'll maybe he follows Elon musk ironically which is a perfectly reasonable thing to do
yeah I guess at this point it is very funny seeing him say anything Elon's being very funny on Twitter
he's he's really going for it he's having a he's having a good one
it's it's almost so absurd that it's not even worth talking about it's like yeah of course
there there he goes again posting a soyjack meme posting a like an obvious cope post yeah
some obvious cope like 2008 like reddit meme tier thing about like the blue haired Twitter
sjw's won't pay $8 cringe you're right I won't what are you gonna do about it you're you're right
actually uh you know I you know I was I thought it was dumb because obviously I'm not paying $8
for Twitter but and and I hate to say this maybe it's actually good because
I won't I won't pay for Twitter but other people might and if other people do and it makes Twitter
work fine then it's like okay other people are shouldering the burden that I don't have to
but no that's not that's not good it's that's not good if it like throttles the views and like
no yeah makes it uneven so never mind it's bad it's it's it's so it's one thing if it was like
there was a tip jar and you could donate to Twitter to keep it afloat like how Wikipedia works
that doesn't compromise the utility of the platform yeah just keeps it online and that's
that's sort of fine it's the it's the it's the way he's trying to entice people to do it by giving
them all of these things that make them like like uh what's the word like more equal than
everyone else yeah it's like yes that's stupid it's like it's like look at all look at all these
perks you get if you guys buy twitter blue you'll have you'll have priority tweets like that's
great right don't you want more perks for your purchase and like no I want there to be fewer
perks I want everyone to have the same amount of perks which is zero like uh I think he was talking
in like a uh uh investors thing about like the idea of like long-form video on twitter if you pay
um genius and like streaming and podcasts but on twitter like people are going to stop using like
these other platforms like youtube twitch and Spotify to put their stuff on twitter
where they have to pay for the privilege to do that where whereas like the other places you
don't really have to do that at all at least with spot I think you have to pay for Spotify
but not on youtube on twitch tremendous tremendous what what a what a concept he's gonna he's gonna
build x the everything app just like just like just like dr. light he's gonna he's gonna spend the
last years of his life you know on his ultimate creation x which will be an app that has free will
and can decide for itself right from wrong uh been waiting to make that joke it's a good one
thanks uh I think it's I think it's got legs um anyway uh yeah he's just like ooh what what
what functions what what new weird stupid things can we make twitter do and it's like twitter already
does what we want it to do which is a little place to post like short snippets and pictures
snippets and pictures and bits I follow a lot of people who do comedy they just make funny tweets
I'm like haha it's just that some of them are a hit and miss the fact that that it's just sort of
like so easy to like just make a bunch of jokes it's like I'm gonna stand up the the the trend of uh
the trend of people uh getting verified and then uh changing their name to elon musk oh yeah
has been very good I've seen so is that active like that the pay for eight bucks is that already
active I saw emails about it I think so I think it might have happened already um I'm not sure though
so you can just buy the thing get the checkmark change your name in profile picture and just
say something like haha pee pee poo poo I I dump in my diaper I meal on musk and then you get
immediately terminated and then you get 10 000 followers of people that think you're the real
elon musk is like elon send me doge please uh did you see it how's going doing I don't know who
cares let's let's I care I want to see it go down it is doing I mean it's just hovering around 20k
as it's been for a while never mind have you seen um the the firings at twitter he sort of oh he
fired them based on the number of words they written and he kept the ones that wrote the most
in the coding that's so smart which which means that the the the the most inefficient coders
the ones who needed to write tons and tons of lines of code to get something to work
are the ones he kept and all the ones who were efficient and were able to do things smaller
were let go the exact opposite of what should have how do you how do you come up with such a
fucking boneheaded scheme I don't know I don't know why he thought I mean I thought he would know
I mean I would say I would yeah it's possible that maybe the least efficient ones would have
written the most I would say at at best there's just like just no correlation yeah yeah like it
depends on what tasks you have to do and like what jobs you're a part of that the amount of
code you write would differ yeah it's just sort of I mean I guess that that's that's really what
happened he just fired like half the staff just based on like how many words or lines of code or
whatever I heard it was lines of code maybe it was more rigorous than that but knowing Elon it
probably wouldn't have been that much more rigorous I half of them are gone half of there's like 7400
people that work there and that half of them have been fired that's very smart uh I have to be honest
I don't really care that much about the individual employees of Twitter my heart does not exactly
bleed for them just because they got fired like boo-hoo whatever everyone gets fired deal with it
yeah that's not but it does but it is dumb it's it's obviously like a dumb way to manage your
business it doesn't make any sense I mean it's it's the way it reads to me is that he's like
he's so fucked and he's like that Twitter loses so much money all the time because of how many
employees we have and how much money is not coming in oh god please pay for Twitter blue
like we gotta get rid of so mostly stuff just get can't pay all these salaries oh my god
I'm $44 billion in the red or whatever what a freaking idiot what a freaking nerd it's so it's
so funny I mean I I guess part of me will feel a little bad if like it does end up just like
making Twitter unusable sure yeah so I hope it doesn't come to that I hope it just doesn't do
anything uh who just gives up but he probably won't yeah I don't know like people have speculated
a lot of different things people are saying that he's going to eventually just sell it at a loss
to someone yeah because he can't like he's but like $44 billion like nobody's gonna pay even
anywhere close to that for Twitter no no I mean it was so it's gonna be a huge loss so like it was
try his best to get like the $8 a month thing going Elon simps will do it maybe normal people will
think fine I guess and then they'll do it as well but in the long term I don't think that's gonna be
that sustainable I just I just don't know uh I mean
I guess I guess we'll see no I mean it the the wasn't like the original amount just like a meme
offer like he just offered like ha ha for $420 or whatever per share per share oh yeah it was
like oh it was like he made he made enough he made you know it was literally like he was like
lol I'll buy Twitter at like $69 per share Lamar or something and they and then he just like
played chicken with that and then he meant it until he eventually was legally obligated to
have meant it the whole time so like yeah it's definitely a huge loss and it was always going to
be like I don't really remember like the announcement at the initially of like haha I'll buy Twitter
um I have so much money like that's vaguely what I remember it but like I read I read some
some some think pieces about it what was his what was his thought process behind even making the joke
it's that he was just complaining about like Twitter's bad there's too many bots
Twitter's not profitable I could run Twitter better than this
but basically just that I wonder if he was like you know he found this really hot person on Twitter
and he was like DMing them but it was a bot it was a sex bot and he was like fuck my wife left me
and I want to have sex this sucks Twitter still has too many bots I keep going up in there and I
find bots fuck it I'll buy the whole thing and then get rid of the bots so I can find hot uh
desperate mills in my area the yeah the uh the the bots thing was like big that was like a big
part of the thing like he claimed that like Twitter was being dishonest about like the
number of bots that like have accounts on there that that was his initial way to try and get out
of it which leads me to believe that he was like already stuck it was part of his original
complaints about Twitter and yeah then also when he was trying to back out he's like no no they lie
they lied about how many bots they have there's there's more bots than I was led to believe
like how did he let it even though like his initial reason for buying the platform
was that what part of it was that like there are too many bots and I want to solve the bot problem
and then they're like well okay now you have to buy it and he's like no no I can't buy it
I didn't know there were all these bots
like how did he how did he let it get to the point where he had to start making excuses in
order to back out and it didn't even work what did he sign what yeah I don't know like yeah why would
you be why would you sign stuff there must yeah there there was like actual documentation there's
like there was at some point illegal obligation and he just went like lol
which is pretty funny I guess
broken man it's really it's just really funny how like Elon simps are like
lol he owned them he really bought it he owns twitter now and it's like yeah
he really bought it for like five times what it's worth because he like way more than five times
yeah because he like couldn't not do it he didn't want to do it but he had to so like he really
truly who owned who here I genuinely don't understand he played himself completely and utterly
yeah the the the the the Elon I don't understand the Elon is playing 5d chess people
truly it kind of not not to not to really compare them because they're not that similar but it sort
of reminds me of the people in Maryweather's comments who were like angry at someone suggesting
a gender swap and then when he did the gender swap they said like he owned them he owned them by
giving them exactly what they asked for like ah he owned the haters what are you talking about
boy oh boy do not make fun of my idol I tie my self-worth to this man
I mean a lot of people it's a lot of it is people that have like financial
stake like they own share in Tesla or they own bitcoin or they own doge and those people I mean
I don't agree with them but I at least understand that like I have a financial stake in this man's
reputation as like a wildcard genius or whatever I at least understand the motivation for those people
oh yeah yeah hi yeah yeah how was your halloween
oh my halloween was pretty all right I just uh I was just hung out with um
munchie kazzie jones and uh I think that was it and uh we watched um we watched a movie called
The Ritual that was not particularly good it was okay that's good that's nice yeah but you know what
it wasn't that it wasn't that spooky it didn't it didn't it didn't spook me too bad the way that
like Midsommar did so it was all right um I made gummy worms I made like halloween gummy worms but
I made like way too many of them you made like piles I mean I left them at their place so they
still have like piles yeah I made like a big bowl of them and like they already had food so like
you know a pretty limited amount got eaten you know oh well I just I discovered something I discovered
hack I was making those halloween gummies and I made a couple different flavors I made black cherry
and I made orange and then I made lime and the lime ones came out much softer and I liked I didn't
like them as much I like the the tougher chewier ones and the difference was and I think this is
what made that they had the exact same ingredients the exact same amounts of everything in them
the difference was that the black cherry and the orange I had microwaved because you have to
combine the ingredients and then you have to microwave them and get them hot to like melt
melt it all together I had microwaved those in a much bigger vessel because you put it in this
vessel and then you put it in the microwave and then boils and the bubbles rise to the top and then
you let it cool off uh the the lime ones I had cooked in a small container because I had only
made half as much so it had only bubbled a little bit the other ones I had made in a big
vessel and it bubbled a lot and I think one just cooked more water off uh and led to them being
denser and chewier so that made me think like damn there's really like to get like a really
consistent result you you literally have to control for like how much how much do you not not just
like what temperature but like how long do you do you heat it to that temperature because like the
amount of boiling makes a noticeable difference I wonder how you could like could you like um
weigh it before and after to get to to know exactly how much water is has been lost you know
you probably could yeah yeah you probably could that's uh that that's that's something that I've
sort of been meaning to do is like I sort of have the recipe memorized in terms of like
tablespoons I would kind of like to convert that at some point to like milligrams so that I can
have like a more precise like yeah it'd be more it's more more precise that way because a tablespoon
is a little bit you know you can buy different measuring tablespoons and like they're not all
exactly the same they're a little bit they're a little bit sloppy a little bit rough
yeah I'm getting hungry have an eating today maybe I'll go make some after this podcast is over
hell yeah the one thing the one thing that I still value in this world the one thing that'll never
let me down this gummies my my gummy worms will never abandon me like unlike everyone else would
you still love me if I turned into a gummy worm would you would you still love I would love you
significantly more if you were a gummy worm actually
I got Heidi Klum's worm costume I did it was pretty neat that was a crazy looks like bacon
looks like it's a little bit strips of bacon over the face just fucking lying on the ground talking
about it hmm you were no no I assume I'm thinking of the same thing you're thinking about like somebody
was interviewing her she was writhing on the floor oh I didn't see that I saw her like walking on
like the red carpet yeah yeah I saw her like dancing behind like a DJ's table this fucking worm
costume pretty great honestly yeah it was really convincing that she like
did the the whole like makeup around her face so that it doesn't like it doesn't feel separate
I'm gonna say that that worm costume was really it was very much like in line with the zeitgeist
it's just like exactly what 2022 needed it was a real a real hit it fit the time so I mean good job
I'm proud of her oh um there was a uh new new got me his last page by the way
oh hell yeah yeah so um yeah news news chapter is done and I think that means that all that's
missing are that one page that I think simsie is not doing anymore so maybe I'll just maybe
maybe I'll just ask kaiju if he wants to because kaiju was asking me for more pages but I gotta
get on kaiju's ass because I haven't heard from him in a while he said he was gonna draw the cover
and like one other page so maybe I'll give him like another one or two on top of that
and then that and then that's like done yep although I see I see just today
munchy message Nate literally half an hour ago I was wondering about this too because Nate had
showed us the timeline for the project had started and I haven't heard anything from him in a month
yes he said he was working on a thing and now he's made a video which has just come out which I
assume is what he was working on um so he means like it was like a stream right did he make like
a real video he put a video on where he's talking with Sekiro footage about one piece
scanlation stuff hmm okay so I assume that's his project maybe it's not but well I hope you said
he would focus on the the OVA I mean he said he yeah I mean he said he was gonna finish what he
was working on a month and a half ago and then focus on the OVA so I don't know I mean I okay well
I guess maybe that was it and he just said that it was done but he he I whatever I hope he fucking
does it yeah we just gotta add like 40 months 50 months frustrating because because because back
when we initially talked about it he said oh maybe I'll have it done in six months and we were all
like it should not take six months but like I think it's like been six months yeah and he still
has doesn't have it done even though we all said that we should act we should accelerate the pace
faster than that maybe it hasn't maybe it hasn't been six months I think it's been no it's only been
like two or two and a half or three maybe three months since he said six months
still it's just still yeah um whatever I hope I hope Nate gets back to uh you know what I'll
I'll post a little message in there I'll agree and then I'll say yeah what's up and that will let
everyone know that I'm on the side of good and not evil hey just see that new uh is it a new
Jenny Nicholson video uh I did not what's it about it is about a weird theme park it is about the
history and the bizarre operations of a theme park called evermore uh it's pretty good I name
dropped Jenny Nicholson in the mega man lecture video and uh I hope nobody uh holds that against
me and makes fun of me for it I hope she sees this bro um I mean she probably won't
it's okay whatever it's not really it's not for her it's for mega it is it's for mega it's for
it's for my boy mega man shout out to mega man shout out to mega man gotta be gotta be one of my
favorite genders shout shout outs to reploids no it's not no it doesn't work no it doesn't work
what's a reploid I forget I think you've told me before what's a reploid um if only there's a
lecture I could find out if only god you you need to fucking be lectured about it for eight hours
if you don't know what a reploid is it's a reploid is um it's x is the first reploid reploids are the
robots from x series the ones with free will uh so do you know the do you know the difference
between mega man and x I do so mega man doesn't have free will no it's just being controlled
by a player character with a control let me tell let me tell you a funny story uh in mega man seven
uh there's a part where at the end you beat wily and wily's like sorry mega man looks like you
beat me and mega man says I'm sick of this I'm killing you I'm killing you right now and wily's
like what you're gonna you're I'm sorry you're gonna do what huh and uh in English in English
well wily says a robot can't kill a human and and mega man says well in in Japanese he doesn't say
anything in English he says and this is a famous line I am more than a robot die wily yes I've seen
that before yes but he doesn't shoot he doesn't shoot and uh I talk about this in the lecture
obviously but in my opinion uh his line implies that he can do it but the fact that he doesn't do
it means that like he's wrong like he thinks he has he thinks he can do it but he can he thinks he
can go against his programming but he can't but yeah yeah uh in Japanese he's just kind of like
dot dot dot which reads to me like you know frustrated acceptance that yeah wily is right I
can't do it no the robots and mega man they like they have they have personalities
and stuff they have like human intelligence but if they're programmed to do something they have to
do it and it might even be that like they have to like obey commands so it might be that like if
wily tells like if wily tells metal man like come here bow to me right now give me tribute metal
man he's like simply must immediately obey because like he can't go against the will of his uh his
creator is it the creator or is it was it just humans uh it might be it's it's sort of the thing
about like that like the the Isaac azimov like rules for robotics or is it different in English
wily seems to specifically be referencing the uh the Isaac azimov rules of robotics in Japanese
he's not he just kind of says that like a robot just can't disobey a human yeah it might it might
be the case that like mega man robots just simply all obey any command that a human gives them
and they can't harm humans they cannot they cannot harm humans except is dr wily allowing them to
do that that's why they're trash in the place uh there's i mean there's no there's no point in
the games where like it's like uh oh wily has made a robot that can hurt humans uh so it seems to me
that it's all of the violence is robot on robot uh yeah so all the humans are just chilling while
like robots are punching each other yeah yeah like they're humans are just like doing living their
lives or whatever and meanwhile over in the old over in the old you know car factory or whatever
the robots are like going going haywire like blasting each other into into molten scrap
and humans just like oof well if i'll just i'll just leave them to it i guess like what
cars are gonna what do i care whether like you know whether wily's like robot uprising like
whether he takes control of the old bean factory or not like who do i care which rich industrialist
ends up owning these uh these mech these mechanized facilities well if the mechanized facilities are
being bombed and shot with like things are going to rip in the wires out then the factory's gonna
be at a commission and i'm not gonna be able to get my latte oh no prices prices are going up
i can't believe these prices and values uh yeah i i think that like i think wily's robots they
they wreak havoc and they do destruction but i'm pretty sure they don't like kill people
even like gremlins in in x uh i mean reploids reploids are basically human they just don't
have like you know blood uh and like reploids die in x but humans never do like they're just
simply like aren't any humans around anywhere in in x except for dr kane he's like literally the only
one and then he stops showing up in x4 i suppose it's a smart too because like it's a it's a cutesy
looking robot series for kids mostly you can't really have humans dying a lot so you just don't
show them yeah i think they they use they use the fact that like this is a story about robots
to be like well we can have that we can have them die and and they can kill each other yeah
like it can be like really dramatic but for babies and and yeah but it's little kids and that makes
them cry we can get it we can get away with more with more uh grim dark violence a little bit
because like technically they're not human they don't have blood or whatever if bambi was a robot
they would actually show the bullet entering it wouldn't just be off screen oh bambi's mom i
should say bambi's mom was a robot but bambi's normal and then in uh and then in zero like they
just give the reploids blood anyway uh you know i didn't even mention damn it i could have mentioned
that as like another thing that like reploids are more are more human like in zero yeah they
literally bleed blood do they have to like add the blood from like a blood bank it might not
literally be blood it's just like when you slice one with your with your z saber a big like geyser
of red fluid like spurts out it's just uh it's like chili oil um um delicious uh yeah zero has the
cool um anytime when you kill like anything with your z saber it like it has like a custom
sprite where like its body is like split in half and like you can sort of see it's like
red robot innards like along the like the split line and it like falls in two pieces it rules uh
uh
that's it that's all i got that's it watch the my fucking video please okay thanks
oh man i i don't know if i'm i hope there's no more errors in it i mean i found those errors
going through it you know adding the uh the timestamps there i mean it's possible that
there are some that i missed but i mean how many times can i how many times can i watch through
the video looking for more and more errors like it there comes a point where i just have to be like
i can't i can't i can double check and triple check and quadruple check but like is a quintuple
check like just too much am i is it just a diminishing returns at that point i think as
long as you can hear your voice yeah um and it you know you didn't like accidentally cut like a
five minute thing completely out and it's just black video of no no audio as long as it's like
functional as a video i don't think you need to worry too much yeah there there i had thought that
i had already watched it through and like noted down every error that i found and went in and
fixed all the errors so like i kind of i like already had double and triple checked it and then
just in doing the uh timestamping i just discovered like oh some new error was introduced at some point
bummer yeah it's it's kind of a difficult thing because like if you've got like
tons of different layers and such a long timeline and you move stuff and you don't move
everything like every time you go in to change something there's a chance that you'll create a
new error that you'll not know about until you're watching it for the next time yeah and like um
i'd really i just tried to be really careful and like make sure that i was like carefully
selecting everything and like nothing was not getting moved and just i tried to move everything
in like as big chunks as possible to avoid like some small part getting getting knocked out of
whack uh i mean i think it i think it was fine it should be all right the the the worst errors
that i found were there were there was one little bit it only lasted like a few seconds
where like it cut to black in between cuts and there were a few times when there like a clip
would be like cut off a little bit early or a clip would fade into the next clip when it was
supposed to be a cut there were a handful of those and those and those are like not even
very concerning like you almost wouldn't even notice those if you weren't paying attention
so if there's a couple more of those like i don't even really care no but there's um
every every time every time that i like pause the video and i have myself play
in an audio clip where i recorded a line like clarifying something i had the flash stopper
sound effect and visual effects start playing over the footage and the problem was that for the
first like three and a half hours the the sound would play at the right time but the visual effect
would start about it would start about 10 seconds early and it would end about 10 seconds early
and it just looked i mean it just looked wrong uh yeah so i guess just like part of that one
layer that that one effect was on just got jostled
and that's how that's that's how that's how it happened probably
damn that's that's the way the cookie rumbles true damn we're only an hour we're only only an
hour and a half in and i feel like i've run out of things to say oh just like just like talking to
just like talking to john just doesn't got nothing to say of my life empty void void void void
void void um there's not even any like juicy tricksy drama to be upset about
damn now what what without that what do i have
yeah you gotta you gotta manufacture some yes yes
what devilish plan is cooking in ben sainte's head
what if i went to her house and lit fire to him
the drama is the ben sainte's in prison
yeah uh
yeah i don't know i uh i guess i don't have too much to talk about
i was just i was just having a week it was very good week i was very happy
feeling very gay right now feeling very like homosexual that's that's that's fun
hmm all right all right i'm feel i'm feeling yeah i'm feeling yeah uh
do you want to go do you want to uh explain more uh i don't know okay i don't know if i want to
explain more about that um i talked about the gig last time didn't i it was the any other thing
that was happening you did talk about the gig i'll i'll just tell you all right
if you'll i i think i know what you're talking about but i won't say it but uh i think you did
talk about it on your on your paid money spenders podcast right yeah right yeah you seemed yeah yeah
i saw you you announced the money spenders podcast and i said i think i know i think i know what's
yep patreon.com slash give and take
yeah uh do not do not watch the mega man lecture listen to gib's money spenders
podcast yeah you can only do one or the other yes one is like 45 minutes right but it's such a
roller coaster i haven't listened to it actually um buh yeah it's it's uh it's um yeah you know it's uh
i don't know i don't know how to approach the subject on the pcp uh i guess i i yeah i get you
yeah it's private it's private and that's why it's on the money spenders podcast go there if you
want to learn about that um not a great pitch because you no idea what it is but that's fine
yeah i mean it seems reasonable to me um well i'm trying to scrape the bottom of the barrel
of any uh thoughts that i had this week or uh new new shit going on and there's just not
anything yeah the biggest thing has been elon and the twitter stuff yeah which i have kind of
i have not been posting much on twitter and i think i should keep it that way
uh i will i will post a um oh um a teaser announcement when the when the lecture is
out i will i will make a little post about that but other than that i don't really want to be
on there much anymore uh inscription soli got me inscription as well who did so uh soli i think
solis oh solaru solaru there's many names they go by right right right um
yeah i played that for a bit i don't think i don't think i have gotten to
like the big twist but i've died twice and i think i get the gist um there's there's like
room to talk about it i would love to hear how far you've gotten and what you think about it
well um i i enjoyed my first run i felt like i was pretty smart um using the using the things
getting the getting the wins dodging the bad things and i died it's like you know you you
you have little animals and they do damage and i have health and you can block enemies
and some of the enemies can fly over you and hit your life points like in yugio
well it's more like magically gathering it's more like everything yeah
and i'm like okay cool you have you have to sacrifice your little little guys to
to get blood that you use to put down a big guy there's a wolf he has two blood
and so uh the the the thing of like drawing from your hands your deck or getting a squirrel
which costs nothing to put down but can be sacrificed to get one blood is sort of like
it's a that's a that's a cool choice that's a cool dynamic because like you're guaranteed
something or if you get a secret mystery prize that you already know what it could be
yeah and you build your deck as you go yeah yeah uh there's items and things and it's like the
squirrel can this this like do you need to pay for something well then you got to get the squirrel
but like what if you the stuff in your hand is too expensive maybe you'd be better off drawing for
like a less expensive creature card like something that costs one yeah or maybe you just need a
chump blocker maybe you just need a squirrel for a chump to block and attack this round or something
and you might as well just use a squirrel for that because you don't want to sacrifice like a real
creature yeah yeah so yeah um it's got a nice level of of uh our consideration thought process
what's the word i'm looking for you have to think a bit and it's not totally down to what card you
draw you before you draw a card you make a choice and i like that yeah um
strategy strategy uh and then i got to the angler i beat the first uh first boss on my first try
and i was like hell yeah prospector mule got him uh i got all the way to the angler and then i didn't
really have any good cards and i died and then okay then the guys he grabbed me and i know that you
could i knew that you could get up off the table and walk around a bit and there's like yeah there's
like puzzle you hadn't really done that i had done that because he asked you to get the candlestick
or something wait wait that was your first run you made it to the angler yeah hmm i enjoyed
further than i made it yeah i felt like i was doing pretty well because after the first boss he
gives you two health i think i'd lost one health um or one life yeah and uh yeah he restores your uh
your candles yeah so that was fun he makes you go and like get the candle off the the the table
right he's like go get yeah go get the candle you can walk around and i saw that there was a
clock you could fiddle with i saw there was a globe that you could spin other little things you
could click on couldn't do much but i'm like okay so there's puzzles here um yes and then i lost at
the angler and he dragged me away and this is the first death so it's like it's not too much of a
spoiler but he takes out a camera he takes your picture or before that he asked you to make a card
your own death card mm-hmm and so based on the cards you've picked up you have to choose like the
cost and the power and lucky for me i managed to get like a zero cost um and like two three
because i had the wolf so zero cost two three um what what was the zero cost uh i think it was
zero cost card the zero cost was i think i can't remember what it was maybe it was the geck
some it was something that's really small that i could use as the cost of the thing
the yeah it might have been the geck the geck is a is a free card yeah so and then it says
write your name it's like okay it's gib and so i became a card he took my picture and i found
my card in the next playthrough and he's he talks to you like you're someone else so i'm like okay i
see how it is uh you play the game and if you lose you become a card and some of the other cards
talk to you so they presumably have lost the game before and they're trapped you mean um is it is it
stote stote and uh the stote so the author and and the stink bug there's the two i found i found
the stink bug you know you know in the safe because i figured out you can look in the book
you see the safe thing it's like oh hell right right yeah so i'm like that's that's basically
where i am i died again okay and i don't remember what else happened you just took my picture again
but then there was a new thing there was totems and there was bones and i'm like okay you're adding
new gameplay mechanics every time i die so i guess i have to die a lot or something oh right
yeah it doesn't you start out not knowing about bones yep so uh yeah i guess i i just sort of
have to play a lot what the what the what totem did you get i got a squirrel and it did you find it
on a on a table or something i don't remember i did the thing where you go to the little
cabinet and you do that puzzle where you have to like make the thing the counter go to five
and then you can open the drawer yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i figured all those out and i was like
i'm smart yeah and i got all the things from the drawer and uh i don't think i
i think after my second death he says now you will create your own totem
choose the face of the totem uh or something and i made a squirrel that turns when the squirrel dies
it turns into a bee and it goes into my hand i was like okay oh the beehive you gave it the
beehive sigil yeah i think i see which was a bad idea because i want to sacrifice squirrels but if
you sacrifice them they don't turn into bees they have to die so that was the stupidest it's yeah
yeah the the bee the bee happens when they get hit yeah not when they die so yeah that's actually a
pretty that's actually pretty bad synergy although it it would be good if it made a bee when they died
yes um yeah so that i think i stopped there because i was like a little tired um i do want to play
more i do want to find out like like more of a story because like inscription it's like he's
inscribing your name onto the cards and it's like i i noticed that you cannot as far as i know
you open up the game there's a guy who says okay let's see what this is all about and it's like
playing on a crt screen some guy's voice so somebody you're playing a game wherein somebody's
playing a game diegetically and you can't click new game you can only click continue game even though
it is the beginning and there is no like that you click that really that really like frustrated me
at the start it's like why is the i should have been more obvious that like okay this is sort of
meant to be this way but yeah i was a little i was a little confused wrong here like i did think
something was wrong i asked uh i asked steve and he said uh no that's normal so i'm okay so i'm like
yeah you can get you can make some busted busted death cards yeah i i think the i don't know yet
because i haven't played through my second life whether or not both of my death cards are like
attainable maybe it's just the most the the most recent one um but like they're all they're all
floating around okay they all stick around okay so that's yeah so like the better cards you get
the more more powerful you can make some of them with the the sacrificing and the and the putting
around the campfire and stuff um like the more powerful cards you might have at the end that
you can attribute to your death card and then that can be as a useful progress for later you
can build up an advantage over time over deaths so i'm like okay that's that's neat i suppose
yeah i managed i think on like one of my first runs i managed to make like like a free basically
like a free grizzly bear or something like a free four six and it's that's just yeah that's just so
busted it's so busted but the annoying thing is that it's also a card game so yeah you might not
pick it up before you die and i'm like well yeah i still i still lost i still lost even though uh
even though i had that card available because like you know it might not be available at the right
time i had i lost a lot on the on the the the the thing after the uh the angler uh me personally
so uh i i just didn't um the the ang the angler is a little the angler is a little tough although
what did you did you lose on the angler i did yeah okay so i there's there's sort of a way to kind
of solve him yeah i mean i i think i figured it out i think the second time i died was again at
the angler and i'm like okay so he's gonna take one card every so often i have to and whenever i
put a card down he changes to that card so as long as i can put down a card that becomes useless on
his side of the board that'll fill up his side of the board with useless cards but then i will need
to fight through them in order to hit them so i probably need a bird and i didn't have a bird at
time and also fliers are helpful against the angler definitely and so i'm like okay my i don't
have a good deck but also i don't have anything to defend myself and i can't really play anything
because i had two like my my hand was full of things that were too expensive so i had to
keep drawing squirrels and i just lost so i might fuck it and my deck is bad and i hate roguelikes
i'm i'm a little disappointed that uh you have not made it further because there are
just quite a few things that i can't mention uh but uh so i'm trying limiting limiting myself
to non non spoiler talk is a bit is a bit tricky uh but i mean you know you want to you've been
playing like the actual like card game card game yeah and like it's good it's a good uh
it's a good game the to the totems can be really uh at some point i got a um
you know like the the three blood drops you ever had the you ever had the goat
i i want i got the goat in my deck and i never he never appeared i never got him i got a um yeah
i got that three blood sigil on my squirrel so all my squirrels sacked for three blood
oh my god that's that was really good the the best one i think is um have you found the cockroach
i think so i didn't i don't think i chose him when i saw him the cockroach is he's all right
his sigil is really good if you can get him on on another creature uh the one that's just like
when it dies it comes back to your hand uh if you could like if you can get that on your squirrels
like you just you just win uh because like it means you can just you can just reuse your squirrels
and oh yeah well then you'd also need to make sure you have like high blood cost powerful beasts
available to you actually put down yeah i mean preferably also um field mice give us i don't know
what the sigil is called but field mice gives a similar sigil that's like when you play it a copy
of it appears in your hand which basically turns all your squirrels into two squirrels uh which is
pretty good um have you uh have you i don't know have you found any any cards with sigils that you
particularly like um i don't know yet it's uh i like the one i guess i like the one where if you
sacrifice the little black cat you get near the beginning oh the cat yeah you sacrifice it he comes
back and so you can put him again the sacrifice uh one is that sigil is really good uh the best
thing is to is to sack the cat to another card to get it on like a better card that actually
does something yeah i think i did that the first time i like or maybe the second time i was like um
um confronted with the uh sacrifice combined cards thing um i'm like wait if i put this thing
on this thing the this thing then then it's just a straight upgrade because the thing i think i put
it on the geek the geek i think oh that's good something that costs zero and then it can come
back actually yeah that's really good because then you don't even have to pay to play it yeah
so i play it and i can kill it i can play it and kill it and play and kill it even just even
just putting it on like the stote or the toad is like um it's still good because like then instead
of like wasting a space of your board to just have like a sacrificeable cat uh you you actually it's
it's on like a it's the same cost because it's one blood and but also it's a creature that is
actually like doing something um yeah i have not i've put cards on the fire near the camp fire
i have not once had my card get eaten but it's always implied that they want to do that and
they almost do it but then i leave can that happen or is that just a they're like a bait and like
like a scary thing i i never had it happen to me like during the main game in like the in like the
post game challenge modes i have had it happen so it can happen i don't i don't exactly know how
likely it is did know there was a post game yeah there's like yeah there's like challenge modes
like you start with a specific deck you gotta win yeah there's different starting decks the rules
work a little bit differently like um you can only you can only use the fire twice you can't
i think you can use it up to like four times uh but i mean it's it's risky every time in the main
game there's like different uh there's different cards available uh some of the numbers are tweaked
it's called it's called kasey's mod is the the challenge modes um have you found uh have you
used like a mantis or a mantis god i i think on my third life this says choose your favorite
uh team and i chose bug and i got a mantis um i like i've seen mantis is used um you text left
to right yeah i didn't really get a chance to play with it though i think that's when i start
all my third life i was like okay well uh this isn't going well immediately because i chose
a bad thing for my squirrel so my totem is kind of useless
i um at some point at some point i realized the game like kind of mentions this too at
at certain points uh sometimes you want less cards some sometimes you want like there's one
that lets you sacrifice a card to like the lord of bones and there's one and the ones that and
the ones that combine two different cards into one sometimes you want to go for those
i mean because the combo can be good but also just because it like means less cards
so yeah less you can like get your weaker cards to just like you know you don't you don't have
them anymore because like you don't want to draw them yeah that is a thing there's only so much
space on the board and one card per turns like sometimes you just get three things that you
can't play like if you're like if you're if you're getting to like the end game and you
still have like an unupgraded like stote and toad like you don't even want to be like wasting
turns like spending a blood to play a freaking one two yeah they're just they're just gonna outpace
you like that a freaking one two give me a break uh well i will be uh i'll ask you more about it
later when you've uh when you've uh made a little more progress and uh maybe i uncovered some stuff
is it gonna be a skeleton so you're gonna be a skeleton at close
i'm not telling i'm not telling if there's a skeleton is the crazy guy who's you're playing
with is is it actually a mirror and you're playing with yourself
imagine imagine not knowing who that guy is imagine i can't it's five nights at freddy's
purple guy it is very it is very five nights at freddy's looking five nights freddy's looking
ass looking ass room i do i do like um the when he talks that low like crackly noise
so that's a good noise sound effect
the third boss has a has a like music that is like ingrained into my mind forever
because i heard it so much because i died so many times
i lost i lost a lot actually i died a lot of times uh
man have you uh you probably have not played any ant cards right i i think i got an ant queen
and an ant oh at some point and i put them down but i don't think i won well i think they didn't
really do anything i i didn't have like because i could tell what you want is to have
many ants uh to bolster all the other ants and the end of the one i think
in in kasey's mod one of the starting decks you unlock is like an ant deck and it's it's but
it's busted it's op it's like way too good i think it i think it starts you with like an ant queen
and an ant queen and a flying ant and like with just those cards like you play you play the ant queen
you get another ant in your hand or like yeah first and then you play the and then you play
the new the worker ants and the flying ant and suddenly you've got you've got three three power
cards on your side and you just win uh it's good i like i like ants
all right sick yep sick sick sick sick sick um we'll have to we'll have to
resume our inscription discussion later uh what do you think about voicemails uh yeah let's let's
voice let's let's voice um it looks like the first one is an it's two imager links or no
it's two of the same imager link for some reason uh it's ben saint bald arc at let'sgo.com breaking
rad wait i saw this somewhere i mean it looks good this is looks very good
cheesy with a cheesy what the fuck are you talking about that's really good uh this is awesome
mess gummy you're in your underwear with the gun the iconic i mean that is
is that's a look that i would have in real life i like it i like this a lot it's very
nice yeah thank you uh next one is called pedantic acronyms bullshit three two one go
so i just realized there's this big double standard on the accepted pronunciations for jiff
and imager like people will say well jib is supposed to be there with a hard g because the g stands
for graphics and not geraptics except that's just not how acronyms work because otherwise scuba
would be pronounced scuba since the u stands for underwater or they'll say well it's because g words
like gift and girl have a hard g never mind that you know giraffe in other words probably exist
and not to mention like what the fuck kind of word would be spelled with a g u but it's pronounced
g like how we do with imager anyway i think i can say that i settled this debate forever
and if you disagree with me then uh suck it losers solved solved uh doesn't doesn't the creator
of the jiff format say jiff i think he does i still say gift because i'm used to it and i don't
care it looks it looks like gift to me so i just i say gift yeah i think there there's an argument
that because it looks so similar to the word gift is just missing a t and giraffe is a little further
away from from what it looks like that saying gift is excusable at the very least it understandable
like assumption to make i mean why why does the guy that made the acronym get to decide how it's
pronounced uh he doesn't what who gave who gave yeah exactly exactly i don't know it just looks
just looks like gift to me and uh to imager is obviously meant to be derivative of the word
image therefore i say imager i don't say imager i did not know scuba was an acronym you didn't
know did did you know laser is an acronym i didn't know that i don't know what it stands for
yes well i remember that the u stands for underwater something underwater being
uh wait no something okay okay uh forget it technically technically the word scuba is not
an acronym but it comes from the acronym for yeah self yeah self-contained underwater breathing
apparatus but you don't write it with like all caps you just write the word scuba yeah
capitalized normally it has become word yeah pretty much pretty much gives weekly reminder
to watch squat cobbler i already forgot what that is isn't it like uh isn't it just like a pie that
you sit on squat cobbler better call soul is that is that a spoiler i haven't seen i've only
watched the first series of better call soul oh right oh i remember it's just yes it's from a scene
in in better call sol i don't know this um i'll get there you know i should i think i've got to
watch the last i still haven't watched like the last two seasons but why what if what if what if i feel
something it'd be embarrassing that would be so embarrassing if i cared um you got caught red-handed
showing feelings next one is called lemau nate got a video out before you ben get right yeah a video
that he fucking spent like six months working on instead of doing the ova i don't care uh next one
is called am late on the episodes three two one go he's the paladin aesthetic moral rowdy or
killer thing paladin
uh obviously it's killer killers are holy warriors for god
but they're evil they're evil holy yeah yeah they're opposite of a paladin a paladin would
have arrived in a new los angeles city and would be disgusted about everything you see is and would
want to to cleanse it just like they're blaggards they're blaggards who think they're paladins
and they're right yeah i guess i guess i guess if if there's like a an aesthetic similarity it would
be more killer than rowdy rowdy would be like the drunken barthog in in a dnd campaign the the the
barred more so than the paladin a barred or a barbarian yeah definitely the pinkie pie of the
group definitely killer definitely killer uh next one is called cave three two one go
have you seen man cave man in cave no usually cave empty
have you seen caven man he's the new boss in mega man mega man 12 caven man he makes the
roof fall on top of here and there's no way to escape no he just he brings the whole house
down on top of both of you uh the next one is uh it's a youtube link but i do say please weigh in
so maybe it's weigh in all right let's let's let's see what it is at least there's a question
which main six is the most thick okay i'm not gonna watch this on the podcast but i'm not
gonna watch a video from quantum hypologists why the most the most thick is um i would say pink
oh my god i'm scrubbing through this number is involved this algebra wait really this data
collection this is funny this is probably funny um i would say it's a toss up between apple jack and
fluttershy i think apple jack just because of her leg when you when you think of thick
usually think thigh bigness and apple jack is usually portrayed as having a huge ass because
of all the bucking she does well i think it's pinky pie because she's black
she's got because she's got because she's got curly hair she's got type type four hair or whatever
also could she eat also yeah i've seen like an i've seen like an index for like
curt like curliness of the hair she's she's she's into she's into the black hair territory i would
say text texturally but more importantly she just eats a lot of cakes at sugar cube corner
she's always yeah but i would always eat in confections i would always say that makes her like
like more fat in the belly than in the thighs necessarily it's both you could argue it's both
i would yeah i would say pinky pie is close i would say apple jack is the thickest
actually no hmm she's she's more lean she would be more lean because she exercises more i i think
she would i think she would be more lean i mean she would be more lean she'd be kind of musculine
but big big and muscular but still lean i guess pinky pie is pretty good of a choice
i could see fluttershy but i think it's i think it's pinky
yeah that's my pick though yeah you know i i'll say pinky pie as well oh my god
sorry this is not relevant to anything but i just see uh two days ago the real gyms uploaded a video
called the simpsons versus death note so that's oh yeah wasn't there like a simpsons episode that
was a death note parody or did i imagine that what there's like a simpsons episode where lisa
gets a fake death note that's that makes something else happen but it's like drawn in an anime style
that looks awful i hate it it looks very strange i don't like it at all
uh i don't like when the simpsons does things that are too wacky i come to the i come to a
franchise show for a familiar experience and by that i mean i don't because i don't watch the
simpsons anymore i don't want to see that it's just hideous hideous yes they they should have
stopped to miss the sparkle absolutely next one is if tom comes back will you redo the intro um
no redo the intro as in like the music yeah i think that's what they mean
just have a little bit of tom speaking over maybe if he made a new intro
be like okay i can accept a change but i'm not gonna go out of my way to like make a whole new
intro just because tom showed up for an episode
that's my answer did you see tom's a furry now did we talk about that already
what do you mean now he's been working on his movie for years he's out he's out of the closet oh my
god i didn't even know he was in well he well he's a he's an owl his son is an owl i didn't see that
which i guess i see it i wasn't i was a bit surprised that it wouldn't be a raccoon but sure
okay owl is fine i guess furry is when you have an oc uh when you have a son i mean furry is when
you have an oc yeah um next one is ben's weekly reminder played yelp delta room chapter two
okay ben's weekly reminder catch up on one piece okay no spoilers favorite character in
description and fave card i mean if it's no spoilers then that's pretty pretty tough
i don't really have a fave yet i i guess i i guess i like the the drawing of that like
pathetic little guy that grows bigger i don't i don't think i've used the drawing of the drawing
of the pathetic little guy that grows bigger it's like uh when you can choose a card from a boss
there's like oh there's geck there's something else and then there's the little guy
that has the uh sigil that makes him grow after one turn oh he looks like he's like in a family
guy death pose and he's like so pathetic looking and i forget what it's called wait are you talking
about like the uh like the useless insect yeah something useless he's called like a useless
little guy or no wait i don't know i can't remember i think i think you're talking about the the
the useless insect or the or the pathetic insect or whatever it's called which i have like never
successful i have like literally never successfully used that card i think maybe one time yeah i just
like the way it looks it's funny but i never chose a good favorite card yeah i think my favorite
card would have to be i do really like the cat i like the sack sigil a lot um i actually really
like i really like the cockroach and field mice because they their sigils i put their sigil on
something else to just get like lots of reuse out of things um what's what's what's one card that
when i find it i'm like fuck yeah game game over i've won i like my own death card because that
was cool oh you know i like corpse maggots the um it's it's probably not as good as like undying
or whatever the cockroach is called but the one that like when a creature dies the card with the
sigil comes into play immediately that one's actually really good you put that on a really
expensive card and you can just get like a real good card on the board for free i like that one a
lot uh yeah that's that's my answer i can't i can't answer a favorite character without spoiling it i'm
sorry um next one is called regi drako is made out of crystallized dragon energy hmm yeah make
sense no it doesn't that's what no that makes perfect sense of course it's crystallized dragon
energy i mean define dragon energy though like what is well you know it's like it's like when a dragon
does something it uses dragon energy to do it like what separates a dragon from a bear or a
lizard or a fucking anything are they are they mythical but they're not like mythical legendaries
they're just a mythical being that they come from space what is so special about fucking dragons
they're just a special kind of guy just like bugs just like bugs are just guys but they're like a
particular special kind of guy with special energy i would love to see a red bug energy
bug a redgy bug that's made of crystallized bug energy honestly yeah why not uh it's like
you know it's just like that episode of the power rangers where they cloned the pink ranger
and zordon had to be like we have to put a stop to this too much pink energy is dangerous
there's going to be a freaking like nuclear meltdown if we don't like pair these these pink
rangers down to one well it's the same with dragon energy like too much dragon energy is dangerous
so you have to crystallize it to stabilize it and that's regi draco of course just you just
plug like a little you get you get like little alligator teeth like wires and you clip them to
a dragon tooth you can power your generator with it mm-hmm mm-hmm that's right dragon energy uh
dragons in series dragons in parallel
what time isn't it it's 12 20 i woke up early time i like woke up before i was i was supposed to
woke up because like an hour before my alarm went off and i couldn't go back to sleep
uh okay um i'm getting i'm getting getting tired is what i'm saying next one is called uh happy
no next one is called my god cheesy is such an idiot leave cheesy alone leave cheesy alone
he's hustling he's hustling and i respect it uh happy birthday ben okay the next one is called
fr 3 2 1 go okay guys and all of this blabbering
either talk about weed or let's move on to the voicemail we are listening to a voicemail
dear you are a voicemail we're in the voicemails because uh you we have a damn mind
out of your damn mind we would never talk about weed we don't do weed i mean except that one time
i don't do weed everybody else does weed and i just i'm just not i'm just not that big a fan
i've just come to i've just come to accept that i'm just not that big a fan and people say no no
you just didn't do it right no no you just didn't you just haven't tried it enough i'm like no i've
tried it enough no i know what it's like no i'm i'm good i i have enjoyed weed but i think it's a
little uh it's a little hit and miss whether it's like the right dosage and it gets me exactly
how i want whereas with alcohol um it's all the right you know that the right dosage is always
more wow it's it's it's that it's that i can have like an entire beer and um that is it's more mass
per like um inebriation so like you don't really have to think too hard about it you can just
drink and like it's it's like judge later it's it's the the stopping at the exact right moment
is a lot easier with alcohol because you feel it quite quickly with weed you take um whatever
however you take the weed and then over a longer period of time then you slowly realize that you
took one too many of the thingies and it's like well now i'm just stuck like this that sucks i
wish i would have known a little earlier how much weed was just right um obviously over time you'd
get a sense of it but like with alcohol you can just stop a beer halfway if you're feeling too much
uh yeah i mean beer you kind of have the same i mean you can you can end up drinking too much
they're not even it they're not equivalent experiences either i'm i'm just saying that i
feel like i'm more in control of having fun with alcohol when you're taken like an edible you pretty
much have to decide completely ahead of time like how much am i gonna take i'm gonna i'm gonna
commit to an amount like right now yeah and i mean you can't you can take more later if you want
uh no i get no i get you i get you make sense um next one is called ben we all knew it was
a mega man lecture lamal three two one go okay there's no audio uh no you didn't i mean maybe you
did i will admit i think people could have guessed because you were talking about doing a big video
yeah and certain things were ruled out and also you were talking about you were you played mega
man on stream a little bit yeah some people did guess it and that's fine but not everyone did and
i saw and i saw other guesses uh that were not right so not everyone not everybody knew not
everyone and even the one and even the ones that did know that guessed it right they still had they
had to doubt they had to doubt themselves and that was the point the point was not that like
no one can know that i'm making a mega man video the point is um but they don't know for sure
they'll never they'll never know for sure until i tell them um next one is called vvv
one one zero five two two hope i didn't miss it at uploading the morning of dot com uh this is
probably some viny stuff the viny stuff most i look forward to viny comics i really like him
yeah yeah i'm holding this sunday morning hope i didn't miss it there you go your covid vaccine
thanks you may have a small sting for the next few days in your arm goodbye sir
he's supposed to syringe up like that yeah uh-huh so sad i thought you're supposed to be like
blushing like oh sexy nurse oh maybe maybe and then uh oh no am i getting my myocarditis
thump thump thump thump thump thump oh no just another day of suffering for an old
then saint and then uh ew gross look at my little butt what do you stink is that the stink lines
it's it's that or it's maybe like a vape vape scene oh yeah or something it's probably both
honestly. This is so unflattering. Yeah, it's true. It's true. You're in your bed
tweeting with your butt out. Gross. Welcome to Ben St's Mega Man comprehensive
lecture. We will be going into why you should care about Mega Man at all. Mega Man was a
video game character. You know, one thing that was missing from my lecture was
drawings on the board and diagrams. And then in Saab, Mega Man 04, I'm sorry. It's
so crippling and depressing. I cry every time I get into this game. The next five
minutes of the video is going to be crying uninterrupted. Hey, the end of
Mega Man 04 is wicked good and wicked cool and it's wicked sad and it rules. Man.
I hope you wore this sort of outfit. I unfortunately did not really have like a
costume or anything. I wish I had. I just wore my freaking plane going by. I just
wore my purple suit with the Lord of Ghost pin. Yes. Yes, and I had my rip in
that ghost. Rip in the ghost and I had my Z Saber. Of course. I had my Z Saber and I
had my little energy tank sippy cup that I was drinking gridlock energy out of. So, you
know, I did a little something, something. The idea of using a Mega Man arm cannon as
a laser pointer. Would have been pretty cool. Would have been rather difficult.
Rather difficult. Did you know that Mega Man's Mega Buster does like suck back into
his arm when he's not using it? And he can in fact turn either of his arms into a
Mega Buster whenever he wants. But he can't fire them both at once because it
would take too much energy from his solar core. On the other hand, Protoman has a
Mega Buster, but he can't transform it back into his arm. He must have to like
unscrew it and put like an arm, a hand like attachment on his arm when he doesn't
want to be shooting stuff with his protobuster. So now you know. I didn't even
mention that in the lecture because it's not because it's not really cannon in
the games. You talk about the similarities to Astro Boy because the idea of the
cannon going back into his arm reminds me that. I do not mention Astro Boy even
once. Dang. That's the only little robot guy I know.
Well, now you'll know some more.
We all do a fucking lecture about Astro Boy. Do it. Do it. Content for the
content mill. My God. Content.
I guess that's it. That's the last voicemail.
Yeah. Well, pleasure doing business with you.
Oh, I see an Imgur link to a Bo Burnham saying something that I agree with.
That's fucked up. Oh, Burnham is often saying that.
Things I don't know. I still have not seen inside.
It's pretty great.
Right. Yeah, I've heard all of his specials are really good.
Yeah. I watched the previous ones.
I haven't seen inside.
That's all I got. That's all I got today.
Audience.
She's got nothing.
What did I manage to only talk for that? Did we even make it to two hours?
Yeah, we did. Pathetic.
Pathetic.
Remember when the PCP used to be like an hour and a half?
I honestly don't.
Because it was like a larger cost and we went for so much less time.
I feel like sometimes I would be on the podcast and have like an interjection.
And that's it. That's the only thing I did in the entire thing and I was over.
Yeah, they were short. The old episodes, they would be like an hour 20 sometimes.
Like it's fucked up.
That's not content. That's that's not even.
That's nothing. That's that's a puff of air.
All I got to say. Yeah, I mean, I feel like we've got nothing to say.
I got nothing to say. All I got to say is watch it worse.
Watch my stupid Mega Man video. Yeah.
And pledge to my Patreon if you want to send me the message that this is what
you need. This is what you need to be doing, Ben.
If you want to be a YouTuber as like someone that makes content as like a
a form of income as a living, this is a this is the response.
I need to see that I need to see that the I need to see that the support is there.
And if I do and if and if it's and if it does well and it makes a little money,
then I'll be like, OK, well, I'll have to plan the next one.
And if it fails and if nobody pledges, then I will probably just disappear
in a puff of smoke and never be heard from again.
I'm sorry. I'm I'm not trying to hold anything hostage,
but like that's that's the reality of the situation.
If it doesn't work, I'm going to stop doing it. So there you go.
I got some phlegm.
I got some phlegm. Oh, it's the Kovacab.
Coughing up some of that inflamed heart tissue.
Gross, gross, hideous.
All right, I'm going to go make some gummy worms.
Yeah, let's end the podcast.
I'm not going to do that.
I also remember to commission me if you feel like having a drawing.
Oh, yes, that I made.
I'm pretty good at that now.
You've been you've been improving every time I see your drawings.
I think this is this is even better.
The more more detailed, more, more,
I don't know, a
structurally sound.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, stuff like that.
More anatomy, but not like more anatomy.
More body parts, more muscles, defined, excruciating detail.
Yes, excruciating.
All right, that's the end of the podcast.
We'll see you next week.
Thanks, as always, for listening.
Send us a voicemail.
Pledge to our Patreon.
No, not yes.
OK, end of the podcast. Goodbye.
OK, that's the end of the video. Goodbye.