Hello, and welcome to this week's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Happy to have you with us once again, I'm GuyTheBestGuyEver, your anime dude, and I'm
here with a bunch of internet people that I know.
First up, Digibro.
Hey, what's up buddy?
Jesse Wood.
Hello.
Hippocrit.
That's what I was gonna do.
That's gonna just say hello.
Well you goofed it up, and Geoff from Mother's Basement.
Money, money, money, money, money, motherfucker.
Booty rocking everywhere, yeah, all right, excellent, okay everybody, so this week's
topic is something that has been an incredibly contentious issue amongst us, and probably
the rest of the world, since the dawn of time, to be honest.
I got my switchblade ready.
It really has.
Since the dawn of theater, we'll say.
That fair.
And to cut straight to it, it is remakes, re-fucking-makes.
Do you like them?
Are they useful?
Do they help?
Do they expose people to a thing that they wouldn't have seen otherwise?
Do they pollute the original identity of that work?
That's the stuff we're gonna talk about, and to start us off, I'm just gonna read the
Urban Dictionary definition of a remake, as I do so often.
Okay, there's, what is this?
This is shit.
You didn't read it first.
It just has lists of what it remakes.
I did not read it first.
He's just like, oh this'll be fine.
I did read the Remakeful one, which is something else that'll be relevant here.
You know what?
We need to define remakes anyways in extensive terms without using this, because we talked
about this a little bit pre-game the other day, and I was saying we need to really clearly
get to the heart of what we mean, because you seem to think that re-imaginings don't
count as remakes.
Like there's remakes, there's re-imaginings, and there's also adaptations of things, like
different adaptations of the same source material.
There's so many different, yeah, and there's these remakes things, like Crisis Core that
like adds extra shit, and kind of, you know, whatever.
But yeah, there's a bunch of different things.
So we really, like this discussion is about what each of those things are, if they're
good or bad, and then I'm sure there'll be disagreement in there, so let's, you know.
But they're not, this is important, is remasters, which is something else.
Sure, right, like the wonderful Final Fantasy IX remaster that's coming out soon.
Have you seen those fucking backgrounds?
Who has seen them?
Holy shit, is there a worse piece of garbage I've ever seen in my entire life?
Is it a worse piece of garbage than the Final Fantasy VI remaster?
I can't imagine, yes, it literally is, because it's the old looking, actually the models
look good in the Final Fantasy IX, but the backgrounds are these disgusting, J-pegged
pieces of shit that not only look bad, but they make the characters on top look like
fucking 3D models walking on top of a board, in a board game.
It is the most, oh, it's horrible.
It looks like a 144p image that's just been blown up to 1080p, which I'm sure is what
they did.
Why would they not like do what the Resident Evil remake, or the Resident Evil HD thing
did, and upscale the fucking 3D models?
I guess they lost them out.
They have, even on the original PlayStation 1, I guess the backgrounds were downscaled
a bit to fit onto it, and I found out that they have the original high res versions before
they were ever downscaled.
Yeah, because they're posting them around.
We've seen them.
But they're not using them.
It doesn't make any sense.
They took the laziest part.
Okay, but you know what?
We didn't even really need to go into that too much, because that's like a remaster,
or just a re-release, which I'm generally okay with.
HD re-releases.
We are not counting as remakes.
We are not counting re-adaptations of the same source material.
So if you say, for instance, Hans Christian Andersen's Little Mermaid, we're not counting
that it's been made into a thousand different movies, because they're all adaptations of
the book, but they're not remakes of each other.
Anything that's public domain can necessarily be called a remake.
Well, okay.
That's sort of my go-to rule.
And this falls under that, so that's fine.
So we're not counting King Kong by Peter Jackson?
No, definitely not.
Well, I think we could, because I think it's a remake within this.
I think a remake should be anything that's within the same medium telling the same story,
right?
Like, King Kong was originally a film, and it was remade to be an updated version of
that film.
It's the same exact story.
You know, I mean, they added some shit to it and modernized it, but it is deliberately
a remake of that film, but for an audience of 90 years later.
It is entirely a case-by-case issue, and you kind of have to study each one to know whether
or not it counts.
I've never seen the new, I haven't seen any King Kong movie ever, actually, so I'll defer
to you where that one's concerned.
But I think it'll be pretty obvious, and we all have examples of things that we think
are okay or aren't okay, and then are remakes or they're not.
Well, I want to say, like, okay, because with Little Mermaid or something, you know, there's
been a bunch of different adaptations, but I think it's pretty clear they all are there.
Like, Ponyo is an adaptation of The Little Mermaid.
It is not an adaptation, it's not a remake of the Disney movie, it's an adaptation of
the book.
But if you took, like, Dracula, where the original book was made into a film, and then
there's like a remake of that exact film, I think that would count as a remake.
Or the new Wolfman movie, which is just the horror, the Hammer Horror movie.
They made a lot of Hammer Horror movies.
It's when you take something that's like a classic movie, and you say something, this
is like the heart of the issue, and you say, you know what, modern day audiences cannot
appreciate this.
We need to update it so that people will be able to watch it, because that's what's
necessary.
I think the defining characteristic of a remake is that it is something that is specifically
using the original as a basis for advertising or marketing itself.
Yeah, yeah, I think so, a lot of the times.
Watch the new Friday the 13th, because everyone loves the old Friday the 13th.
And you know what kind of is related to it, is like continuing a series that's been dead
for a long time, and deciding to resurrect it, and just like pick up from where, the
reboots are related, but not exactly the same, so pro reboot.
Re reboot is the greatest CG TV show of all time, but I do think you're making some uncharitable
assumptions about why remakes are sometimes made, because you're saying like they're made
because they think that people can't appreciate the original, which is certainly true in a
lot of cases, like the shot by shot remake of Psycho, which basically is just done.
Psycho and Schuller.
Like I watch Psycho, that movie is fucking great.
There's no need.
There is no need to do it for that reason, but for the reason of like reinterpreting
it through a new lens, or giving it to a new director to try their own interpretation of
that style, or that storyline.
I want to ask though, what exactly are they reinterpreting?
Is it the movie, or is it like the script?
Because I think that's an important distinction.
Sometimes it's the script, and sometimes it's like the movie itself, or the plot beats.
Is it even possible for someone else to redo a movie that was like the product of multiple
people's creativity working together?
Can you ever really call something like that a remake?
Is that even...
I think that in certain cases you definitely can.
My go-to example from like recent times, because I think we can agree that most horror
movie remakes are terrible.
I'm not a horror movie expert, but that seems to be the consensus.
Yeah, so like the new remake of Poltergeist, shit, the new remakes, like the new Friday
the 13 remake, shit, the new Halloween remake, shit.
Most horror movie remakes are shit, but the Evil Dead remake is fucking great.
I was gonna say how great that movie is.
And like the thing is that it takes the same plot beats as the original Evil Dead movie,
and remixes them with some interesting new ideas as to who these characters are and sort
of what they're doing.
It adds a few modern things, like the reason that they're not leaving the cabin initially
isn't because they're idiots, it's because the only character who actually knows what's
going on happens to be detoxing from a meth addiction, and nobody believes her when she
says demons are coming out of the walls because, I mean of course you think demons are coming
out of the walls, you're coming not off of meth.
But the thing about the Evil Dead remake, I think a huge part of why it was good, is
because Sam Raimi was like heavily involved with it, as a producer for sure.
I want to bring up that subject, okay, like the, I think that the best way for a remake
to happen, because like with remakes I think a lot of the times it is like you know a cash
grab on something that was popular, but I think that if the original had something to
be improved upon, like even, like it's consensus that at the time it was already needed, like
I think with something like Final Fantasy 7, which I know is, okay because this is the
big one, that's the big one, that's what we're ultimately getting to, but I'm not going to
talk about it too much at this point, because I know we're going to get to Final Fantasy
7, but let's build it up at that point.
But the thing about Final Fantasy 7 is when it came out, it was not perceived as flawed,
right?
It only became that after trends in games became something different, where now people
took a while to parse it, I think.
I don't think people play turn-based RPGs anymore, and that's why they think they need
to remake it, right, because they think it's old, it's an old-fashioned style, but when
it came out-
Which if you ask me is an entirely forced upon opinion, is that real?
Stop, let me finish, guys.
Let me finish my fucking point.
My point is simply that at the time that Final Fantasy 7 came out, those were not flaws.
The turn-based battle system was not a flaw, people didn't perceive it that way, but when
something like Evil Dead came out, it had obvious flaws for the medium even at the time,
where it was a low-budget movie with cheesy effects, with a story that didn't necessarily
make sense.
That was the charm of the movie, and some people like it for those reasons, but I think
that the idea of remaking Evil Dead is like, well, yeah, it wasn't perfect, so why not
try to make another version?
And so they did that specifically with Evil Dead, the Evil Dead 2 or whatever is basically
a remake, but I'd call that a reimagining, and here's the thing with all this stuff.
My big issue at the end of the day, if there was infinite time, infinite money, infinite
resources, I'd say make all the remakes you want to an extent, I've got some issues with
it, but if that's how it is, then fine.
My real issue is if it's worth taking the time to specifically invest your resources
in remaking something when you could just be making something new.
But let's not even get too much into that, because with the Evil Dead example, the first
one and the second one are similar, it's the same story, but it's a reimagining at
its core.
It's a totally different movie, and I think that does justify it.
I don't think that that's something that isn't worth making, because there was definitely
something creative going on there, and that's really why it's a case-by-case thing, whether
or not it's okay.
Yeah, yeah, because the original Evil Dead and moreover Evil Dead 2, the original Evil
Dead definitely not a flawless movie, but at the same time, it's one of the few movies
that has 100% on Rotten Tomatoes, which is kind of crazy.
Everybody loved the movie, even though it was iffy in a lot of spots.
And you're talking about Evil Dead 1?
Evil Dead 2 has like a 97%, it was more contentious, because Evil Dead 2 goes for a lot of balls
of your stuff.
Evil Dead 2 is one of my favorite movies of all time.
I'd say that's vastly superior to Evil Dead 1 personally.
It's much funnier.
Evil Dead 1 is more enjoyable in that campy way, and the Evil Dead remake is a more straight
horror movie that is not going for the campiness, and then if you want more of that campiness,
you can actually get it from Ash vs Evil Dead, the new TV show that they made, which I will
not stop championing, because that TV show, it's got Bruce Campbell in it, it's directed
and produced by Sam Raimi, so it's actually like a legit sequel to the Evil Dead 2, and
it's fucking amazing, but I'm getting off the topic here.
I think to bring it back a little bit, the whole reimagining thing, and to answer Nate's
question about why it's worth it to remake something, I get, yeah, we want to have more
original ideas, but I think there's also some value in trying to make the best possible
version, and the problem is that it's really debatable if you can, because Avangelion is
a great example, where it came out in the 90s, and it was this huge cultural touchstone,
which pretty much created the idea of original TV anime, had this unbelievably deep and
involving story with this great directing, but no matter how you look at it, the production
falls apart in the second half, and the impetus to remake it, now that it made a lot of money,
to me seems obvious, like yeah, the show is already a huge success, and it's already
something that everyone...
Look at the consequences of that urge, Ana's like, what is going on over there?
It's a nightmare, it's taken like what, 10 years to make these movies, and they're
not even close to done?
What the hell?
What a waste, what a fucking waste.
They still haven't gotten to the part that actually needed fixing, which was the last
half.
The funny thing about it is that it's so different now, that it's more of a sequel anyways.
Yeah, there's another huge issue in there, which is like everything is different in
a shitty way, like every change they make I think is vastly worse than the original,
and like, if they just hadn't done it, I'd be happy as a clam, I would've been fucking
over the moon.
It's definitely a weird case, because again, the impetus is obvious, just do the same thing,
make it look better, but then obviously they didn't want to do the same thing because they
wanted to make something different, but the same, it's odd to try to parse, and you could
say that it's worth it to have both versions, and maybe the new one has different meanings
that you could also get out of it, but then it just becomes a question of like, why did
it have to be Ava, you know, why, right, exactly.
I think the iffy thing with that is that it's the same director trying to make the same,
like the same thing twice, and improve upon his own previous work, and I think that that's
a less valuable type of remake than a new director approaching something that they love
and trying to turn that into-
I'll say, I actually honestly, and I couldn't prove this without doing more research into
it, I don't think Anno is as much the director of those movies as people think, Anno's always
listed as like-
It doesn't seem that way.
He's always listed as chief director and stuff, but like, Kazuyo Tsurumaki, his understudy,
he's always listed as director, he hasn't done anything else in the time they've been
working on Rebuild, and his style, he's the one who directed, you know, FLCL and Gunbuster,
I mean, Diebuster rather, and like, the new Ava movies feel more like him, and they're
also-
Right, they feel totally Diebuster-y.
Yeah, and the guy who directed Gankutsuo is also Mahiro Maeda, it's like a big part
of directing the newer ones, like especially part three, so like, I think there's a lot,
I think there's like an understated amount of Kazuyo Tsurumaki and Mahiro Maeda like,
really pulling the unique voice of these movies out, and that's why it doesn't quite feel-
Cause like, Anno's directing, if you watch anything he's made, it's all very slow, very
like, methodical, you know, like there's big moments, but they're always like scary,
and there's none of the like, big, bombastic, crazy thing that happens in the second movie,
you know, when like, the Ava transforms into this other thing, and like, Shinji's a badass,
and it's like, this feels very uh, like, Tsurumaki-y, those things were cool, those things were
definitely super badass, but at the Ava, is it, is it the point, is this what we're supposed
to learn from Ava, Shinji becomes a total fucking ass-kicking monster man?
Well, you say it's not Ava, but now it is Ava, so that's-
I know it is Ava, but it's not like, it's not Anno's Ava, and that's-
And that's exactly the problem with Final Fantasy VII, because when it comes out and
sucks, people are gonna say, well, this is Final Fantasy VII.
Yeah, okay, we need to, we need to, on that issue, we need to bring up how, because we're
talking about this already, uh, the people making the remake, okay, the guy who directed
it was Kitase, he is now producer, Nomura was character designer, he is now director,
and people already throw around the argument, this legitimizes it, this makes it, you know,
like, it's reasonable, the answer is, no it doesn't, because it's been 20 fucking years
since the game came out, Nomura, I mean, and first of all, Nomura was a fucking character
designer, and now he's a director, that's not the same shit, Kitase is a fucking producer,
yeah, go on.
I just want to talk some shit about Nomura, please, uh, Nomura, I blame him for everything
that has fucking happened to Final Fantasy, all the fucking belts, all the fucking leather,
well, all those zippers, I mean, the Final Fantasy VII character designs are all great,
I mean, even Vincent, who's a goofball, is still lovable in his own way.
No, I agree that the character, I'm not actually like, mad about that, I'm mad about the fact
that Nomura does not really know how to design video games, he knows how to-
That's entirely true, look at the fucking compilation, which is his baby, look, he directed
Advent Children, completely got everything wrong, he directed everything in the compilation,
Crisis Core, what people say, it's a fucking piece of garbage, everything new that it introduced
was shit and just had the need to over, the ending with Zack was really impressive, but
completely ruined everything about his death scene from the original that made it so special.
So here, you know, and we don't even need to talk about Durga Cerberus, it's a fucking
stookie, it's poop.
I mean, none of that ruins Final Fantasy VII as much as Final Fantasy XII ruins Final
Fantasy VII.
Because of Shinra.
Because Shinra makes it canon that Final Fantasy X is a prequel to Final Fantasy VII.
Okay, I'll kill every motherfucker on this planet.
Dude, the actual explanation for that is Shinra, right, found the Shinra company, or stays
alive somehow, and then they literally travel from that planet to a different planet.
This is the canon explanation, found that entire civilization, and then eventually Final
Fantasy VII happens.
How the fuck does that make sense?
It doesn't.
It's ridiculous.
So you can ignore it.
Just ignore it.
According to that canon definition, that would mean that the Shinra corporation existed
with the Cetra like a thousand years ago.
That's right.
Yep.
I hate them.
I hate them all so much.
Well, actually, okay, it's possible because humans and Cetra were the same thing, right?
Until the media, until Jenova hit or something, right, and then the, whatever, okay.
I think the Cetra have like sin particles in them or some shit now or something like
that.
Yeah, who fucking knows.
Also, why would the Elbed who worship technology become the Cetra who worship the Earth?
No.
I don't even know.
A lot can happen in a billion years, which I assume is the timeline between the two.
So you know.
You know what?
This is just not one single thing about it makes any coherent sense at all.
Okay, the point is, the point is all this shit happened on Nomura and Square Enix's
watch, and these are the people remaking Final Fantasy VII.
That's the issue here.
And what does that tell us about what the remake is going to be?
I think it's quite clear that it is no longer the original vision of the people who made
that game.
And for that reason alone, it, it, I think it's going to pollute the legacy of the original
with whatever, even if there's one tiny change to the story, like, it doesn't even matter.
Whatever it is will be, the series will be worse off because it exists.
I am not interested in how many people are brought into the series by playing this game
and then even decide to go play Final Fantasy VII because I think that they will have a tainted
view of the game.
I would rather have more people with a, with a pure view than a vast number of people with
a corrupted view of what the game was.
I'm not interested in that.
So, I, there's a lot of, yeah, sorry.
You can go ahead because I'm going to change the subject.
Yeah, there's a lot of, there's a lot of shit to unpack in what Nomura has kind of done
to Final Fantasy and like, I think the thing is that Nomura came into Final Fantasy as
a fan of what Sakaguchi has had done and a lot of, a lot of what he makes seems like
Final Fantasy fan fiction, which is why Kingdom Hearts in his hands is so fucking great.
Yeah.
That's fine.
Totally fine.
Because Kingdom Hearts is just Final Fantasy and Disney fan fiction.
It's meant to be.
Well, I say, I say it's fine, but the story has literally gone to absolute garbage in the
last couple of games.
It doesn't matter.
But ignoring that, ignoring that.
The game, the game plays fine.
The first one was great.
Second one was great.
Yeah.
And, and like when Nomura makes his own thing, like, or not necessarily his own thing,
but when they make their own thing and like the world ends with you, that can be really
great too.
Oh, that rule dude.
That game rules.
Like, I do agree with you that Nomura's direction on Final Fantasy has made the series worse.
And the last guy who knew anything about how to make a Final Fantasy game left halfway
through the production of Final Fantasy 12, the director of Tactics.
Right.
The evilese guy.
Yeah.
That man knew how to make a fucking game and now he's gone.
And he's gone.
He's been fucking depressing for me, man.
This is all just.
All right.
Yeah.
Okay, guys, guys.
We're kind of off topic.
I mean, we're on topic because I know we're off topic.
I mean, I think this is more or less proven that remakes cause nothing but sadness and
misery.
Okay.
Let Jeff finish this point.
Then Digi, you can take it.
I'm bringing it back.
What I don't think is I don't think that the point that it's not the creator's original
vision is necessarily a valid reason to say this, this remake will not be good because
if they were trying to do something good with it, if they were trying to do something new
and different that takes the ideas of Final Fantasy 7 and interprets them in new and interesting
ways, that would be fucking awesome.
But what they.
As much as that idea disgusts me, you might that could theoretically be true possibly.
But what it seems like they want to do, and I'm saying this based on, you know, Crisis
Core and all of those things that you mentioned.
What it seems like they want to do is Nomura wants to take his Final Fantasy 7 live journal
fan fiction that he's working on for fucking ever that is just his head cannon.
This is, he's on Tumblr, he's made, he's talking about how, you know, Tifa and Cloud
have to end up together and all of this shit.
And he's, he's making a very much as objective as true as Zach has to be a Super Saiyan or
whatever the fuck was going on.
Not necessarily, Jesse, because humanity may have all died at the end of the, at the
game.
We don't know.
That is true.
It's ambiguous.
And his fucking compilation ruins that.
It's the most important thing in the entire game.
I hate you, Nomura.
I hate you.
I wish you were dead.
You ruined my favorite series.
Fuck you, Nomura.
Also, Toriyama sucks too.
Lightning's garbage.
But anyway.
Yeah.
I like lightning returns.
Like, I mean.
Maybe that game's okay.
Final Fantasy 13 has at least gotten better since they stopped giving a fuck about the
story and just started making gameplay.
That seems to be true.
You just tested to that.
But yeah.
So, like, the problem, as I see it with this, isn't that they are not making the creator's
original vision.
It's that they're trying to bite Sakaguchi's original vision in trying to make it.
And that, like, I think that if they were trying to make something that was totally
different, that would be fine.
Yeah.
But look at all the advertising remake.
This is it done correctly.
Done as it was always intended.
That really seems to me.
Right.
All right.
Like, let's move on.
I gotta get into this now.
Okay.
I gotta cut a promo here.
All right.
Please.
Look.
We've done a lot of talk about, like, the creators of these games, right?
And a lot of this, you know, you can blame them for making these remakes and trying to
obviously just repackage something that's popular so that more people will buy it.
Right?
I mean, Final Fantasy VII remake, on the sheer idea in most people's minds that this game
is supposed to be the greatest game ever, but they haven't played it because it's old,
and then it comes out and it's new, it will make it sell like crazy, right?
That is true, though I don't like it.
Now, here's the thing.
The problem to me is not necessarily the creators, it's the gamers, and I think in
general the product of all these remakes is that people don't give a fuck about art.
That's true.
People don't care about art.
They care about just being entertained.
They just want to consume shit, right?
You put it in front of them, they watch it.
The reason Psycho gets a remake is everyone knows about Psycho.
Everyone's heard of it.
A lot of people have probably seen it.
Nobody wants to see a black and white movie.
Right.
No one's going to go out of their way to download a black and white movie and watch it, even
if they would probably like it, and there is some level of understandableness to this.
Maybe people don't really have the language to communicate with older art.
If you've never seen a black and white movie, it might be hard for you to sort of process,
and most people don't want to put the effort into watching old shit.
They just say, I don't like it.
This is a very intricate topic that's going to be difficult to parse.
The thing is, because I'm going to bring this back to Final Fantasy VII, I grew up without
a PS1.
My first console was the N64.
I didn't have a Sony until 2003 with the PS2.
I went back and I got really into JRPG, so I went back and tried to play all the old
Final Fantasies.
I played most of the first discs of Final Fantasy VII, which is as much as I've played
of it to this day, but I did love it at the time, like 2005.
I loved the art.
I loved everything about it.
My little brother, Victor, is a very modern spoiled gamer because he's been playing games
for as long as I have, but he's never gone back and played old games.
I go back.
I try to play NES games, Super Nintendo games, all the stuff I missed out on.
He's never done that.
So Final Fantasy VII is getting a remake and immediately he's like, oh yeah, now I get
to play the new one instead of the old one, right?
And so I told him how everyone was, you know, I told you guys, you guys all jumped down
his throat immediately, and then I told him how you guys all jumped down his throat and
he's like, man, whatever, I don't think I can get into an old turn-based game.
And then Nintendo, you know, made cloud in Smash and he got all excited because they
were showing all the aons and shit and playing the old battle music.
Those are summons?
Aons are Final Fantasy X?
Whatever.
He saw all the summons and he was like, oh man, I forgot, Final Fantasy is pretty cool.
I now want to play VII, so I get him, you know, I have it on Steam, so I put it on his computer.
He plays like the first hour and he says, man, this is already the coolest game ever.
And he plays it for one more hour, gets tired and decides not to play it anymore because
he got tired with the battle system.
And like, but I, you know, on the one hand, I can say I get it, right?
Because he doesn't care about video games as art.
He cares about it as something he plays, you know, he doesn't really think deep about video
games.
It's something that a game comes out, he gets hype for a new game that's about to come
out, you know, he's always riding the hype cycle, watching all the previews, the game
comes out, he plays it, and then it's gone.
It's, that's it.
That's, you know, maybe it comes back later when he plays it again, if he plays it again.
But it's not something that like, he's got this grand cultural idea of what games are.
Yeah, let me bring up a point about this real quick.
Because I think an important touchstone for this whole discussion is Red Letter Media's
Jack and Jill video, in which they say specifically how, like, that movie is a corporate, disgusting
piece of garbage that only exists to make money and has no artistic value whatsoever.
But people don't care.
At the, like, the justification, or what they say is like, at the end of the day, who cares
about this movie?
Like, who is harmed by it?
The answer is only people who look at movies as art and are interested in it as an artistic
medium.
Everyone else is fine.
Doesn't matter.
My Asterisk War Part 9 video that's going to come out in a couple days is almost exactly
the same point now that I think about it.
Like, the thing is, with video games, there's this great article, I don't remember what
it's called, I need to track it down again so you can put it in the description.
But it was by this guy who was, like, a teacher of, like, game design or something like that.
And he had this class and he asked everyone in the class, raise your hand if you're a
fan of the Elder Scrolls series.
And like, 75% of the kids raised their hand, right?
And then he says, like, how many of you have played Skyfall and they also have their hands
up?
Then he says, how many of you have played Oblivion and then, like, more than half of
them lower their hands?
And then he says, how many of you have played Morrowind and there's only, like, two guys
left?
And then he says, how many of you have played Daggerfall?
No one.
So these people say, I'm a fan of the Elder Scrolls series, but they've only played the
latest one.
And it's because there's this sort of idea that's very prevalent among gamers because
gaming isn't really recognized as an art form in the greater cultural sense yet.
It's still sort of treated as, like, you know, obviously gamers think it's an art form and
they'll defend it like that.
But then at the same time, they don't treat it like one.
Because if you get into film, if you try to be a film major or something, you will go
back and watch stuff from the 20s and 30s and 40s and you will watch it as a chain.
That's the point that I raised in my Final Fantasy VII rant video back in last summer
where I said, you know, gamers always want to defend games as art, but then they also
turn around and go, well, we need it with better graphics though and we need a new version
of it and we need it.
It's just a prank, bro, argument.
So here's sort of my take on it because I come at this from, I think, a slightly different
perspective from you guys.
You're all a little bit older than me.
Wait, how old are you?
You're young, really?
Get the fuck out of here, pal.
I'm only 23, so...
Well, I don't think any of us is over 25, so...
Yeah, but I mean, like, the thing is, Jesse's 26, I forget.
That difference of, like, two or three years is the difference between having been old
enough to play Final Fantasy VII when it came out and having to go back and play it.
Okay, sure.
And that's kind of...
So I was at a similar position to Digi's Brother, where I hadn't played it.
And the thing was, or the thing is that I went to school for game design.
I obviously am very interested in studying old games as an art form.
And for me, Final Fantasy VII, more than, say, Final Fantasy IX and more than Final Fantasy
VI, kind of came across as a chore to play, because it was in that dip in quality in terms
of, like, visual fidelity and a lot of other stuff where they were figuring not where they
were...
Holy shit, okay.
Man, I'm gonna fucking murder you when you're asleep.
It's good.
It's like somebody really revealed their immaturity.
Well, I think Jeff's point is, I think it's fair that he's actually played the game and
formed an opinion on it.
I'm not saying that everyone needs to recognize Final Fantasy VII as a great masterpiece.
I just think it's dangerous that we have this new game coming out and people won't go play
the original.
Yeah, and that's...
Agreed.
I would rather someone hate Final Fantasy VII than like the remake.
I agree.
Well, I might feel that way about both, but the thing is that VII was harder for me to
play through than VI and was harder for me to play through than IX and was easier for
me to play through than VIII because VIII is fucking garbage, but let's not get into
that whole discussion.
Nice.
Yeah, okay.
Fucking plan.
But so VII has that very awkward, we're trying to figure out how 3D graphics work aspect
to it, and in terms of old games with 3D graphics, it doesn't hold up to the same degree as,
Metal Gear Solid or Mega Man Legends 2 or...
Okay, you better get to your point quick because I'm going to destroy you on this point momentarily.
You're going to murder me.
Yes.
No, no, no, I've got a good retort to this.
Is it the Hippo Crit retort because we could let him finally tell us?
That is exactly what it is.
Magnificent.
Yeah, so...
Yeah.
Let's just finish this point, then I'll...
So, like, what I'm saying is I did actually make a concerted effort to play through and
enjoy Final Fantasy VII, despite that.
But something that I think gets lost is that Final Fantasy VII is, in some ways, harder
to enjoy than the SNES-era Final Fantasies and the late PS1-era Final Fantasies, because
it falls into that middle ground of they were still trying to figure out how to make it
work.
The combat is a little bit on the slow side compared to...
And quick and responsive.
I actually do agree.
It's fun.
It's a bit slow.
Things take a little longer in combat than I'd like.
And I love turn-based combat.
My favorite game right now is Legend of Heroes Trails in Cold Steel.
My favorite...
One of my favorite games of all time is Legend of Heroes Trails in the Sky.
I love Skies of Arcadia, so it's not like a problem with what they're going for.
I love Final Fantasy's battle system in particular, because I think Bravely Default's one of the
most brilliant gameplay-wise games of the last decade.
In terms of battle systems, yes.
Yeah, story-wise, it's hit or miss.
I mean, the second half is kind of, but whatever.
In terms of game design, and I think about a lot of stuff in terms of game design, because
that's what I studied, 7 definitely has some stuff to it, but it's got those load times
or huge fucking pain in the ass.
The graphics in battle look a lot better than the graphics on the overworld, but it's still
like...
Alright, let's stop you there.
I want Hippo to make his defense of the overworld graphics that I really love, and Nate does
too.
Yeah.
I've seen Nate's video, but yeah.
I hate you.
Well, I haven't played the other Final Fantasy games, so I don't know how much, how good
I am of a retort I am, but I played Final Fantasy 7 quite recently to form an opinion
on it for the same sort of reason, so that I could compare it to the remake when it comes
out, and I like all the low-poly, the low-resolution stuff.
I forgot what my actual argument was.
Your argument was that the way that they animate the characters is very expressive.
But the way that all the dialogue is portrayed is like the characters move their bodies because
they couldn't animate faces to express this.
Right, so for someone to say that the animations, they did well with what they had.
Right, and so for someone to say that a remake will be better in every way is ignoring the
things that were the product that they were forced to do, which in this case is the incredibly
animated models, which I love, which is one of my favorite things about that game.
It gives us a very silly feel, that's super endearing, and the remake will not, will not
in even close, be able to capture that level of, you know, comfiness.
I don't disagree, and I do appreciate- It's going to be grimdark as fuck, and I already
wish I was dead.
The voice acting alone is just going to kill it by itself.
Voice acting in games is a huge issue.
I wish it was gone.
It needs to go away forever.
We can talk about that specifically.
The Advent Children voice cast is- At the very least, every game that did not have
a voice cast should never ever, ever, ever, ever be given a voice because I've already
got the voice in my head, anything else to be parable.
I want to make that argument in a sec, but I actually do want to chime in on the graphics
thing that you guys were talking about, because I do appreciate that old school style of what
Final Fantasy VII's overworld characters are basically, is they are big blocky 3D sprite
equivalents.
So what they used to do in the old, old Final Fantasy games is they'd have like a few different
dance animations for the sprites that would like express what emotions they were feeling
in very simple and obvious ways.
And I, you know, obviously I like that because I like Final Fantasy VI, and-
Terra's like scared reaction, like, ugh, face, it's like, it was great.
I love that sprite.
And like, what, the problem that I have isn't that they try to do that in Final Fantasy VII
necessarily, because I can appreciate, like I can appreciate that in other games of the
era that have similar limitations and do similar things with their graphics.
What I don't necessarily like is A, the disconnect between how these characters are presented
in battle and out of battle.
I think it like creates a little bit too much of a dissonance in my mind for this is like
the same world that this is taking place in.
And the other thing that I'm not a particularly big fan of is that that was the point where
Final Fantasy started to try to go for that cinematic appeal.
And having that cinematic appeal with these very expressive or that like cinematic style
with these camera angles and all of these supposed supposed to be cool action sequences
with these-
Oh, supposed to be, he said.
Okay, go on.
With these adorable little stop motion muppets is jarring as fuck.
If I can nitpick your points, I gotta say that whenever I hear people bring up things
like disconnect or dissonance, those just sound like words to me that critics invented
that don't actually mean anything.
Like, where is this disconnect that I'm supposed to be feeling that everyone else always points
out in things?
I think Jesse and Jeff-
Is it because the backgrounds are so pretty and the models?
I think it's totally fine for Jeff to have all those opinions about the game, but I'm
just nitpicking.
Well, I think it's something that like, you know, you can go back and play the game and
feel that.
And maybe you would have felt that when you played it the first time in 1997.
Like, maybe you would have played six and then played seven and felt that disconnect
and that could be totally normal.
But I think-
Like, the thing is, I think seven would have blown me away if I played it when it came
out.
Well, none of that.
I mean, that might be true, but none of that is the issue.
The issue is, does this justify a modern day remake as we've seen it going to do?
I don't think so.
I want to actually bring up Final Fantasy VI, because really, Final Fantasy VII, the original
is to me an example of how to do a remake well, because it's kind of a remake of six.
Not in like the story, but they carry so much over from six.
It's got the same modern setting, Sephiroth is basically a less funny, more serious Kefka.
The final boss battle is exactly the same.
Essentially, they looked at six and said, well, we have a more powerful console now,
let's do this again.
But what makes it not a remake is obviously they made a whole new world and a whole new
story and a whole new characters to base it around.
So if you want to remake something or put a new spit on it, just take the elements that
you liked and make something new with it.
Making a remake entirely like to the point is entirely-
I want to raise-
So is it just not obvious to everyone why they're doing it?
There's only one reason.
They're trying to make money.
I want to raise a point about old games in general and advice to people who haven't played
a lot of old games, because I do think, while I think Jeff's points are valid about feeling
that disconnect and that that's a personal thing that some people might feel, to bring
back to the defense, because as valid as your feelings are, also valid is our defense that
we like I think all four of us on the other side of the discussion like those character
designs and the way they're used in the story.
And I think that people need to go in with an analytical slant towards the way that graphics
are used as opposed to what the graphics are.
Because I think that saying that new graphics are necessarily better than old ones is kind
of like saying that movies are inherently better than books because they can show you
things on screen as opposed to describing them.
Right.
When in reality a book, a great book can have a description in it that's way better than
a shitty movie's image.
And I think with old games there can be Super Nintendo games like say Chrono Trigger that
are so evocative of a time and feel and place that they still resonate with you more so
than a modern game that has really high-res graphics.
If you look at those Shakespeare re-envisionings, you know the ones that do it in messages
with ascii, fucking smileys and shit, that's an extreme example, but that's what it reminds
me of.
It's like trying to reinterpret the thing that already exists in a new way to make it
more immersive.
What you're ignoring in that situation is the incredibly important what that art piece
made at that time says about that period of time, which is a super important aspect
of it.
And I think that when you take the turn-based battles out of Final Fantasy 7, you really
make it a different game and you're not acknowledging it by calling it a remake.
And that's where, again, remakes, that's the issue.
That's a reimagining at that point, I agree.
My stance on remakes in general, which we should have probably gotten to this 40 minutes
ago.
My overall stance on remakes is like, as pieces of art that exist in a void, like if I didn't
take context into it, I don't think there'd be much to complain about because it's just
a different game and you have both.
But in the context of reality where I know people are going to play the new Final Fantasy
7 and take it as the Final Fantasy 7, it's worrisome, but at the same time, no one who
actually takes the game seriously as art is going to do that.
The people who give a fuck are us.
We are the ones who are going to write history books about what video games are, you know.
There's going to be people out there that just fall through the cracks and only get
the newest one no matter what.
I worry for that.
The crux of my position on remakes is, you know, I've seen and played enough good remakes
that I can't just throw the baby out the bathwater and say that remakes are all inherently bad
and they shouldn't exist.
But what it comes down to is just whether or not I trust the people in charge of the
game, specifically in the case of Final Fantasy 7, if you look at Square Enix's track record
for the last, oh, I don't know, 15 fucking years, you cannot trust these people to make
something of the same quality.
Wait, let's ask a question.
Let's look at other Square Enix remakes.
Jeff, you probably played this.
How was the remake of Final Fantasy 3 on the DS?
The remake of Final Fantasy 3 is actually something I was going to bring up as the original, did
you?
Nobody did, because it was Japan exclusive.
Can we really form a comparison?
The thing is, in terms of viewing it as its own property, it's definitely solid.
And I have played old school Final Fantasy, so I know how that looks.
And I have, I mean, the gameplay systems are exactly the same.
Final Fantasy 1 and 2 on the Game Boy Advance, much better than the original NES version.
Tweaked and improved in a lot of ways to avoid all that fucking grinding, yeah.
Or here's a slightly more contentious example, a Chrono Trigger on the DS, less of a remade.
It doesn't have very little cool cutscenes, I mean, that was from the PlayStation 1 version.
They put in the cutscenes for the PS1 version, but it has none of those load times that kind
of ruin the PS1 version.
And it also has a bunch of new endings, some of which are pretty interesting and help to
connect it to Chrono Cross, which some people might think is.
I do like those, but I have to ask myself, was this intended, is this the real story
of these characters that, I know they tie in Shala and Chrono Cross more, which is really
cool because I know in Chrono Cross, Shala exists, but we probably don't have the correct
answer to this, but was this intended, is this the real story of Chrono Trigger?
I think you care a lot more about authorial intent than I do personally.
I think that the writer on the guy who wrote the scenario for Chrono Trigger was the guy
who did most of the direction on Chrono Cross.
The reason why authorial intent is important is because I want to play the game that was
intended originally, and I know there's lots of issues that come up whenever you're making
a game.
Things get cut, things get changed, the corporate stuff has an influence on the artists.
But you know, I'm interested in playing this game that I can say, okay, this was made by
these people at this time, it has, I'm going to interpret it in these ways, and you know,
things are getting a lot more complicated, and maybe it's just me, you know, screaming
against the wind.
I mean, I never helped.
I think it's pretty easy to look at the Final Fantasy VII remake and say, this is clearly
not what Final Fantasy VII was intended to be, this is clearly not what anyone involved
with making the game would have made it, and they've just taken someone else's idea and
because they own the intellectual property, they are allowed to do whatever they want
with it.
And I think that there's so many signs that it's obviously going to be a problem game,
because it's obvious to me that with the whole thing where they have to split it into, you
know, an episodic release, and what that says to me is the game is way over budget,
and the reason the game is way over budget is because it has to appeal to everyone.
So they're not trying to make an art piece, they're trying to make a game that everyone
will buy.
Like Final Fantasy VII at no point had a part where you, after, you know, after you finish
the first disc, you have to wait months for the rest of the game to be released, and then
you have to do that again.
It's not art, it's not.
I do want to defend one thing on the budget perspective, which I think is one good sign
in relation to this game, which is that they're remaking a game that has pre-rendered backgrounds,
and I would say that the one thing about Final Fantasy VII that does absolutely still hold
up is the pre-rendered backgrounds.
And that's something that, you know, I wish we had more of, and my complaints about Final
Fantasy VII's graphics are not necessarily complaints about, I don't think that graphics
from that era can hold up, I just don't think that those ones particularly do.
But the Final Fantasy VII remake is trying to remake a game with pre-rendered backgrounds,
which means that it wasn't, it's a game that never really reused any assets because it
didn't have to worry about storage space in the same way as other games, and it didn't
have to, so like every environment could feel completely fucking different and new and awesome
and not have to share the same fucking crates and barrels from every other area of the
game because they didn't have to reuse those assets over and over again.
And with Final Fantasy VII, the remake, if they're...
You know they're going to reuse shit everywhere.
Well they might reuse shit, but like the thing is that if they're trying to make Midgar feel
like the Midgar that people remember, they are going to have to create a lot of unique
environmental art assets for every single area of that game, which is going to require
a lot more dev time than you would typically get.
And you know what else is something that people like to bring up in regards to this game, is
they say, guys wouldn't it have been great if when we played VII you could explore more
of Midgar, like more sections, okay see the thing with that is guys, the people who could
have theoretically written cool things to happen in those places are all gone.
The thing that's going to fill in these spaces you want now is Nomura, Advent Children, uh
fucking Durgessurbership, that's what's going to be in those spaces.
It's going to be flying fucking motorcycle battles with them.
I just watched that episode of Futurama where Frye delves into his memories and like anything
that he didn't experience on his last day in 1999 was an empty white space.
That's exactly what this is, and it's going to be filled in by fucking Nomura and his
incompetent Kingdom Hearts writing.
So here, yeah, here's like the sort of problem with how they flavored the new version of Midgar
is the old version of Midgar had like a sort of fantasy and sci-fi crossover feel to it,
and the new version of Midgar feels a lot like a cyberpunk version of Tokyo, which is
Look, there was a there was a moment in the Final Fantasy 7 trailer that I saw in Nature
video that officially was the moment when I said this isn't going to be good, and it's
there's a part where you see Cloud running through a tunnel and there's some debris blocking
his path, and then he does that whole side scooch thing where like the character crawls
in between two pieces of debris and slowly moves forward every new game you know it was
it was really it was an uncharted a lot it's in the new Tomb Raiders it's in like all those
it's in the last of us all those games directly from Final Fantasy 15 so get excited for that
guys that's going to be a great game right well right and 15 might be good but do you
want load screens that's that's that's the load screen replacement I would take load
screens if the game was more fun I just think that those moments in in they're in like every
modern game yeah they feel like shit you you're you're controlling normally and then suddenly
you're controlling like not normally right and they'll always have a few of them back to back
just to sort of break up you know whatever you're doing and like I get it it's it's to change the
flow a little bit you know but I had to load screen that's the that's what it is they put
you in a tight area so that they can load everything I'd rather have like an okami load
screen which has a little minigame on it that you can play well you can't do that Namco you
can't do that Namco just lost that patent like this year hey there you go sweet so but like so
now we'll have load screen minigames again thank god I just handed that shit holy shit fuck them
yeah then go suck a dick I think you know well for one thing you probably wouldn't need those types
of load screens if you didn't make your games so overblown look look at Dark Souls right Dark Souls
is no load screens well fucking Dark Souls has the elevators but um well those are fine you know
they work they blend into the world seamlessly they're fine by me they don't make your control
scheme the point yeah the point is they crafted the world to avoid any kind of super no problem with
load screens that are integrated into the gameplay in a way that feels natural like an elevator or
or um I like I I think that how the uncharted games handle it in creating that feel of I'm watching
a movie is better for those games than right for those games sure I saw it those games but yeah
what what you know Final Fantasy 7 being this this RPG Final Fantasy 7 being this this RPG and I mean
it had cinematic moments where you know your controls change you do different stuff but it was
always for like in a mini game you can still control cloud though but right well there's always
like a mini game like you know you're riding your bike and you're slashing people or you're doing all
this other stuff it's always like a creative fun way to change to change the tension of the scene
well let's not let's not you know ignore the like 30 minute long cut scenes that happen sometimes I
mean there's only like one of those I'm not talking about that I'm talking what bothers me like one
of the biggest things that bothers me in games is where my controls change for no reason for sure
like when it when a character slows down to start talking on a calm or something and I have to now
walk weird and slow and it just feels like like like the like I might as well just have dropped
the controller you know like yeah yeah like at least for the cut scene you you have this
understanding that that something that it's pulled away to show you something you know like like it
doesn't bother me too much when the cut scene is like a straight up movie it does bother me when
you're playing like let's say a first person game like Metro and like there's a cut scene
in first person so you sit there and you keep hitting forward on the controller because you're
just waiting to get control of the character and you don't know when the cut scene stops or starts
so you're just sitting there hitting forward over and over again like why why am I not moving you
know but like in in a game like Final Fantasy 7 seeing something like that appear I'm just like
this like why would that happen in this game why would it take control away from me just like
like Mass Effect 3 and the answer is obviously because that's what games do these days you know
it really doesn't matter what we think because if the comment section of Nate's video proves anything
I was just gonna want crap I wanted to end this with a reading of several of my favorite comments
from that but yeah go on people crave mediocrity nowadays you know I'm of the opinion that that
AAA games development has terribly deteriorated and devolved in general or like games today at
least they're all the big budget AAA games are legitimately are legitimately worse in general
than older games and it's 1998 was like a golden time dude right around that I'm inclined to disagree
but that's that's because I have played almost every new game for like the last three years
would you say that more of the new would you say that more of the good new games were AAA games
or would you say that more of them were like more undertale you know I saw one guy well all the
good games that are coming out now the majority of the games that are really you know impressing
people are getting played a lot or successful or good are all you know modestly made indie games
with one or two guys in charge of it should be made by smaller teams I think and not be so bloated
I think yeah a with you know more restrictions it's like the art from adversity thing where like
if Final Fantasy 7 had come out with all the technology it has now back then it would have had
you know advent children cutscenes and it would have been impossible to take seriously I had a
point yeah I just I'm I hate everything I think I don't want it to be fair the way I'm with you
Jesse I think I don't think it's as strict a dichotomy as you're painting with the AAA versus
indie because I think I I strongly believe that we need to start using the terms AA and single a
like I would say AA games would be like Dark Souls what is AAA even you know come to think about
so actually we had discussions like this a lot in the in the chat room for the website I used to
work for because you know these divisions were kind of our bread and butter and the
yes the division between like Dark Souls is kind of in like a weird thing because Dark Souls 1
is probably I would say edging between AA and AAA but then Dark Souls 2 has more of a AAA
aspect to it and Bloodborne is 100% a AAA game to me the definition of AAA
should mean like the studio that made it right yeah like to me the the definition of AAA is not
necessarily what's in it or what like how good it is or how good it looks or whatever it's how
expensive was it no it's what it is um as I know well advertised it it's marketing budget marketing
is what defines something being AAA versus being like a single a and like this is how they think
about it at publishers when they say a AAA game that's their tentpole that's like their that's the
equivalent of a blockbuster movie right and and I I don't think that AAA games even are completely
bankrupt because two years ago we got Grand Theft Auto 5 which is a remarkable game on many many
levels and completely bankrupt I just think that there's an inherent loss of modesty that comes
with the new technology and these huge overblown budgets like you know but the last of us the last
of us felt like a very modest game a lot of the time except during the parts where you had to
load everything about the last of us it belongs I want to say I think what happened to games is
sort of similar to what's going on with the economy at large right that we've got a growing
upper class and a shrinking middle class that's very good I think with I think with video games
because the thing is when you look back at like a list of the top 100 super nintendo games or the
top 100 playstation 1 or games like it's it's always like all of them are pretty on par in terms
of like what they are we're like yeah look at the top 100 ps1 games and it'll be like you've got
Final Fantasy and stuff are like probably the more expensive ones but then you you can't really
tell there's not like a huge difference between like Final Fantasy and Ape Escape in terms of like
what kind of game they are how they kind of look you know or are going down the line you know there's
cheaper games there's the the the japanese rpgs that are like all 2d even though they're on the
ps1 you got like the legendary like no one can stop mr domino they all feel like they're on the same
sort of like plane of existence where like if you played like you know like a cheaper game versus
a more expensive game they all they all kind of feel the same whereas like now when you look at a
triple a game it's like this unlike impossible to comprehend production where you you look at it and
you go where how is this possible because for me personally uh like the overblown hd graphics
actually physically hurt my eyes so whenever i look at it i feel like i'm staring at like god and
it's just beaming into my eye i don't want to say like it's happening i don't like the idea of companies
striving for greater fidelity and i know there's going to be you know uncanny valley stuff along
the way i'm fine with that i just it's when your efforts like i think in final fantasy 15 this will
probably be the case when your efforts to make a game pretty adversely affect how fun it is to play
or your your resources are diverted to that that's when you got a fucking problem as a game and i
think we need i think what i'd like to see is for the middle class of games to come back
you know where i think i think they've been living strong in japan you know i think there's
so plenty of i want to see more like devil may cry and platinum games like platinum games where
it's like they have they have modern graphics but they're not like this is like battlefield
three ridiculous bullshit where it's like it has to be lifelike in order to step to be pushed you
know like just make games that look that look modern but are like fun arcade games that are
that are cool you know like i think i think if we had a lot more platinum games tier developers
then it wouldn't always either be oh this game's an indie darling that has all these amazing ideas
but it looks like fucking shit or oh it's this game that's got like that makes my computer explode
but it's fucking boring you know like i need more of that middle class that i feel like we really
had on the super nintendo and ps1 where like every game was on that same sort of tier you know aside
from like the tentpole games i see there i definitely don't think that every company should be going
for max fidelity i don't really think that any company should because it takes away from the
other stuff that you can be doing with the new technology in terms of building like where's the
emphasis on like the artistry as opposed to the where's like the designated like hundred man team
to be like we got to make this the best artistic piece prop like we possibly can no instead they're
all fucking working on like textures for like leaves on a tree it's like what what the fuck guys
that's not i so specifically when it comes to environmental details like that a lot of
procedurally generated these days like trees no triple a studio makes its own trees anymore
there is a dedicated there are like three dedicated tree populating algorithms that
are okay for for sale and for license to a bunch of play it's it's the same as like physics engines
like everybody uses havoc everybody uses unreal because those things take away from the amount
of time that you have to spend doing that nitty gritty shit yeah and like artists want to place
their own mark on stuff and they do in game companies like i know people who work in game
companies i've worked on games previously um and there is definitely like at every studio at every
level there are people doing something that they they feel proud of and that they want to put their
mark on um or you know obviously there are some people who just want to cash a paycheck but you
there is so much competition for jobs in the triple a industry that to just be capable of
cashing a paycheck you have to be among the best of the best and you have to be capable
you have to have that artistic drive and you have to be capable of there's an entire arc of
shiro bako about this one of the characters goes to uh work for a cg animation company
all it's they they basically do like the car cgs for like every show and video game like yeah
and the the director of the company is just really passionate about cars but if you work there all
you do is design cars forever you know and she's yeah she was like designing like just rims like she
was only allowed to design rims that she's talking to the other members of the company and they're
like yeah after two years i got to move on to tires you know and she's just like oh my god and
then she realizes i want to do artistic stuff i'm gonna go but like everyone who was working at
the company was working there because you will never need work you always will have work because
they always get hired to do cars and so she was like i'm gonna go work for some indie team and
just say fuck it because i need the artistic gratification you know so that exact thing happens
quite frequently around me because uh i live in the same city as the big ea games campus so i know
city is that uh vancouver oh yeah right yeah so i know people who literally all they do is try to
get the details right on every single player in the entire football league or every single player
in and when i say football i mean soccer football like inferior european football yes um yeah or try
to get every single nba players jersey fucking down and the the environmental model uh modelers
all they fucking work on is stadiums and basketball courts and there is a super high turnover at ea of
people going indie like vancouver has a huge indie game scene because people do get tired of that
over time but the thing is um a i i think that there there is some value in having these big
triple a monstrosities because um uh a sometimes they offer really epic uh mind-blowing experiences
like uh i would say grand theft out of five offered that um and b they act as a sort of training
ground and a proving ground for people to uh practice get their 10 000 hours in of becoming
like a true fucking master of what they do and then they can go and they can they can go into the
indie space and make that middle class that you're talking about bro and that middle class is growing
like if you look at steam the biggest games on steam these days are often uh yeah i think like
something like rocket league feels sort of that that i mean it's sort of bare bones but like the
way the graphics are and the the depth of the the engine and everything is like yeah this is more than
just some indie game okay you know what this is all this witness the witness is a good example
well didn't he spend like six years spending like a lot of money making uh making braid and then
or and just reminding uh looking at the steam front page has reminded me this will bring us back
to remakes and is one of the best examples of a sort of middle class level development
and one of the best examples of a remake of all time xcom the new election about xcom uh so the old
xcom uh was really ugly and really fucking hard and uh it's got a lot of i mean it's still a good
game but it's also basically unplayable for a modern gamer and i'm not just saying that because of uh
it's very inaccessible in how it's designed and the new xcom takes all of the ideas of the original
xcom and just makes them palatable to a modern gamer but it so i think it's a it's a remake done right
but then also the interesting thing about it is is that it was like wildly fucking successful
meanwhile xcom the bureau or the bureau xcom declassified the shitty first person shooter that
they made set in the xcom universe was supposed to be the triple a tent pole of uh xcom and it
fucking flopped while uh everybody bought xcom one and now xcom two is the most hiked that's
that's very interesting and i i my my position is and always has been i it's not like every single
remake will always be a mistake but i do think that they are rare and in generally i think the
practice uh isn't as valuable as pursuing new works but here's like here's the my why i think xcom
kind of just i call the exception that proves the rule but maybe you'd say it but the thing is
that xcom is that rare example of they put resources into making a new thing the bureau xcom
declassified and they put less resources into making a remake because the game design was done
and a lot of the world building was done and it was just a matter of like building the game and
yeah and the the remake was vastly fucking superior to the piece of fucking garbage new thing that they
tried to write okay here's my question that's true i mean i always okay going back to my earlier
point that i think a remake should like is is understandable if you're just trying to perfect
the original do you think that the new xcom would have been better if they just hadn't called it xcom
like if they just no no something else i i think it it perfects the original x i'm asking nape like
do you think oh do you think we'd be better off if like if you took an idea you had that you that
you released and it was pretty okay and then you made a much better version of it and said it's a
remake would that be less valuable than if you said well i just reskinned it and now it's about
different characters and it's a different ip well okay the the critical word there is reskin because
like if it really is the same game only you just change like fluff then like what do you that's
that's that's not a substance of what i'm saying is that they change the entire story of the game
they it's it's a remake it's the same thing but they changed the the systems of it to make it better
so it's a remake yeah but it's it's a much better game and i think like if you say that like what's
the point of just remaking something that already existed it's like well they made a good game as
opposed to the not so good one so like well i feel like your argument that they should have made
something new it's like well they did make something new they just it's just that it's so
similar to the old one that you know i changed the my argument is is really about the the use of
resources it sounds like in this case they were because they were already making this other game
they had the assets to use and like it didn't require a massive amount of work to do and it's
like if it's what the artists like if it's better and pretty much objectively then you know there's
really much to complain about but like really your complaints with remakes are one it should be the
same people uh i'm not saying it should or it should it should be something that reflects
the original artistic intent yeah um or otherwise be something totally different because why even
call it the same thing yes and i can agree with that i think like you know i think there's plenty
of great remakes out there and i think that they they could easily have just been called something
else but they needed the brand recognition you know which is frustrating which which which hurts
the art form that yes we take focus away from the original and we put it only on the new one
although at the same time it can often drive attention to the original where there's probably
a lot of people who will play final fantasy seven just to compare it to the remake you know
so i think there's still a lot of potential that it's actually net positive for the original game
okay but your but that's not counting my second argument which is the effort that was put into
making this remake you could have spent yeah so i'll i'll definitely say that like i think in the
end if the result was actually a better game and like it was something they were doing because
they legitimately wanted to improve final fantasy seven and not just resell it to a new audience
then i think it would possibly be justified to possibly use the resources but i i i think like i
think there's a false assumption there in that if they weren't making if they didn't have this remake
project going they would have a different project active at the studio because oftentimes um remakes
square enix we're talking about final fantasy 16 just get working on it you know whatever they
got to do so like in terms of resource distribution a lot of the time remakes like remasters particularly
are like you need like four or five people to work on them that's that's their very small projects
but remakes too can be much smaller projects not necessarily in the case of final fantasy seven
because obviously they're giving it a full triple production yeah yeah but um in a lot of cases a
remake will need to have like a smaller team than a full triple a thing and it's something that they
can work on without necessarily having to have like a full a full staff of um you know a full
staff of writers to i mean obviously this is an example that's helping my point but like like the
final fantasy six remake that just came out like what was even the point of that just re-release
it literally looks worse in every way well that's not a remake that's a port that's a bad port it's
a port with completely replaced artwork which was well no not completely replaced they put a filter
on it which is garbage um like final fantasy six like like what it is is it's just like they took
all of the sprites and then they put them through a program that smooths out all of the edges which
is the worst thing that you can do the sprite artwork so they just look like shit they vector
they vectorize the sprites basically and it's terrible um whereas uh final like the so the
assumption that you're making that uh they would be making or that they could be making
something entirely new instead mm-hmm a i think is somewhat false because oftentimes like they
they are putting less resources toward making the remake happen and they don't have to put as many
resources and uh and be um i think you can go through yeah and be i i think that uh the remaking
something with with a director or a team that has seen the original thing and thinks this was cool
i want to do it my way and better is often super valuable like the example often often like the
example i think it would be more valuable if they changed the name but i think here's some i think
let let let me just i have a few examples beyond xcom going back to movies scarface is a uh remake
of a like a silent film a silent era uh film and uh the thing which is in my opinion the single
greatest horror movie ever made is basically a remake of a very shitty 60s sci-fi movie called
the thing from another world okay you brought up the scarface in a discussion we had before and i
think that's probably an example of something that skirts the line between a remake and a reimagining
because there's there's no way that like that the silent movie has like the same script or or the
same like direct like so much i'm assuming has changed that it really seems like a whole new
thing it's not just like a i don't know what it's based on or anything i don't know if like the the
movie was was the basis of that foundation but like you know that's one of those things that's not
well i don't know and i want to make though nate yeah with your whole uh argument about like the
resources is that like that is i will give you a very idealist viewpoint but i think that it's
possible that they need remakes to make money so that they can make the other dude yeah bet on a
sure thing to make the like because the thing is with square enix specifically like we all know
that they've been bleeding money out of their games they keep saying that every game because they
make such bad choices right i mean yeah they make terrible choices but they release tomb raider the
same week as fallout four that's a brilliant idea or you know even just focusing on the final fantasy
brand like they made three final fantasy thirteens after the first one was not even liked what what
was that about that is not sure that the first one is not liked the first one is well beloved by a
myriad of people who have you just have to look at the sales figures overall okay yes it did i think
it actually might have sold better than any other final fantasy besides like seven i think that's not
because it was good games have done pretty okay and a lot of people have done worse like even after
the second one did much worse like why would you make a third one at that point doesn't make sense
i don't know because they were probably because they had the assets and they could throw it together
that's not a good excuse that's a bad excuse but anyway is that they they are bleeding money
they made a bunch of games that they made over budget even though those games sold unbelievably
well they didn't sell enough to make back the stupid budgets you know yeah we're like tomb raider
sold like fucking five million copies and they still said it was the basis of my criticism is
this is bad art and like okay it's probably a great financial decision but it's making shitty
art but the thing is like if we're talking about this team like let's say i mean if you're if you
were saying resources is like a nebulous thing where their resources could somehow get transplanted
to another studio like well i'm not saying that but ultimate philanthropists and just give all
their you know give all the talent that they have for Final Fantasy VII to a studio that can actually
but like if that's not the case then the question is how are they gonna make up for all this loss
they've had make Final Fantasy XVI just do but they haven't even finished Final Fantasy XV and
they probably already sunk too much money into that game and it's gonna be a financial disaster
well that's their fault dude that's not a thing to make their money back and they think Final Fantasy
VII i'm not saying it's necessarily a good idea but like they clearly think dude i get it Final Fantasy VII
even the original is still a top selling game if you go on to the ps4 and you go to the top sellers
bracket it's Final Fantasy VII is always the top selling game on the ps4 it's it's true you know
that's that's fine i i get it i know why they do it and if i were the if i were their executive i'd
probably do it too but none of this changes the fact that it is going to pollute the legacy of the
original by objectively being a worse thing i know it to be true i'm not arguing that point in the
nothing about any of us say against any remake really matters because we're all just nostalgia
fags that's that's right yep that's all that matters the only one here who's not a nostalgia
fag as yeah you're superior no if you're a legend of zelda ocarina of time on the 3ds fixed uh the
biggest problem to the game unfortunately i still think it's a worse game because it's on the 3ds
and not on my television where i can actually see the entire world here's a difference of opinion
that i have i think that um like i strongly prefer playing games on handhelds to playing them on a big
tv these days well that's weird i like that all the wrong things to me especially especially big
rpgs because with big rpgs i want to take it out of my pocket play a few battles i don't go
anywhere i don't leave my house digi digi digi digi you gotta you gotta listen to him on this one
because he's right playing uh some an rpg on your game boy in bed was how i spent most of my
childhood and it was objectively the best you guys are animals i think that's it all handhelds games
are objectively inherently trash advanced games in there i played it all they should never have
been made they should do the game only sp every game has zero artistic merit if it's not on my
fucking television set or on a screen big enough for me to sit in front of and fucking watch
like a human being not like an animal in a dog house with a fucking game boy advanced a fucking
pokemon made sense on a handheld console because it was like you had you had your your your fucking
n64 that was doing all this crazy shit right but pokemon didn't need all that crazy shit so like
it it was a fucking 2d game that doesn't give me this fire but now you do crazy shit in your pocket
yeah like that's the big crazy shit should be on a big screen where i can fully appreciate it
because of the scale of everything doesn't even that you look up in the distance and you see this
huge mountain you see that mountain and you scale the mountain that's actually the one and only
criteria for whether something is actually good or worthless whether or not it's a handheld or an
actual game which is on a real screen was on game boy and it was the best game ever made and
that's the end of it it's on a console because it didn't have huge scale but
that's right mother three was originally going to be an that is irrelevant to my point you're
saying that you can't make an epic story they adapted it no not the story i'm talking about the
visuals you don't make a 3d game with epic scale graphics like a game like ocarina of time where
part of the appeal is it is that you see big mountain and you go climb big mountain and it
looks huge on your tv as opposed to your little picture why can't a picture be small and still
good here's here's my here's my uh counterpoint to that do you play with 3d on digi no because it
makes my eyes bleed so so here's the thing you play with 3d on that completely no i appreciate
don't get me wrong i know that the 3d in that game looks really good but it makes my eyes bleed
and i can't look at it and my argument here is so we're making the complaint that it's less epic
because you're not doing the thing that makes it like i can't i literally can't it makes my eyes
hurt too much well that sounds like a personal problem but like i'm making the complaint that
it's objectively garbage because you gotta fucking bend your body over like a no you fucking jesse
look at a time you gotta strain your eyes looking at a tiny fucking baby screen
there's no fucking point but why would you not want to be sitting in a chair or a couch or
something comfortable like a human being why do you want to live like an animal why do you want
to be a fucking savage in the one everyone don't play fucking why don't you just go crawl outside
your tp and take a shit in the dirt guys that's shabby as ever you're barely even human a film
a film aficionado make the argument that oh yeah that movie that you saw in theaters and it was
my like like fucking what's a mad max theory road yeah that's gonna look just as good on your
fucking iphone as it does in theaters no talking about that that's the difference between like
it may not look just as good on your iphone as it does in theaters but it will look almost as good
on your tablet as it does on your tv because you're not in a fucking theater a theater experience
is completely different i don't care how good it looks on my tablet i think that even something
on my fucking tablet which it shouldn't be because my tablet is a crappy little handheld device
that fits in my fucking whole pocket and i can't whatever you want why are you why are you gonna
take that away from people who like to watch things on the tablet because nobody deserves to have
anything that sucks i want the world to have things that are good and i want the world to have
good hands and that is why and that's why they should not remake the final fantasy seven remake
it does not deserve to exist you have to know what's good the buttons are too close to my fingers
and they're all too tacky and they suck it's a shitty controller it's like it's like playing
like like like putting your hands on a plank of wood with buttons and then holding it six inches
from your face and you can't be comfortable with it when i could have a beautiful sleek controller
in my hand that is built for hands because it doesn't need to account for screens or how small
it has to be a physical controller so okay so you want to you want to talk about better versus
worse uh so ocarina of time works i would say as well on a console as it does on a handheld i'm
not going to argue that but if you want to talk about the best zelda game which is majora's mask
majora's mask is so much fucking better on a handheld because you can do a bus ride and in that bus
ride have i ever done a bike ride you what the fuck are you talking about what is this about a
bus ride so if he's saying that you can play you can play through a mission by the end of a bus
ride i know the mission a cycle or a side quest it compartmentalizes uh a game that is like it
intended to be replayed a whole fucking bunch i do all of my gaming better on a handheld i do all
of my gaming in 10 hour chunks i don't play 20 minutes of a game and then put it in my pocket
i turn on the tv and i have to sit there all day because if it takes me more than three days to
beat a game i will never beat that game i really where this argument is concerned i'm with matthew
mitosis uh because i had a psp and a d i had every fucking handheld in the world and like matthew
mitosis says in his peace walker a metal gear solid review that um like the game was designed to be
in mission format so that you could play it like on a bus but like right on the bus and you're playing
it and you finish a mission and you've still got five minutes like okay what do i do do i try another
mission or do i turn it off now just wait either way it's not really doesn't really perfectly work
that has happened to me every time i've tried to play every time i ever try to play a game
like a real game on like a ds or something i love like for me the only kind of games i can actually
play the way that mobile games are intended to be played is if it's like don't touch the
white tiles and it's like i'm just touching tiles and then it's over when they the doctor says you're
up and i i hit exit and it's done and the game is over forever you know like i kind of agree that's
the kind of game that i think is a good a good handheld game you know so yeah like for me the
ones that i think are the best are weirdly the big sandboxy rpgs because that those are games
that you can play for whatever period of time you feel like playing and get a good amount except
for 10 hours because if you try to play for 10 hours then the strain on your eyes and hands
will break you and yeah that's the length of time i want to play the game for okay guys guys
so argument is like kind of related to remakes but kind of almost not at all so i think we should
roll it back a little bit you know yeah i just wanted to get heated about that for yeah yeah
we we thought we were going to stab each other over final fantasy seven but we
turns out it was about each other over handheld jrpgs which is let me let me just say that like
i want to be super clear to everybody watching that like when i see an old character like brought
back to life like the first time this happened to me was when i first heard about kingdom hearts one
and i saw cloud was in it that's what made me buy that game i thought that was the coolest thing
that ever happened and because in no way that was celebrating the existence of cloud that was
not something that in any way changed the interpretation of the character and when cloud
got into smash it was the same thing and just today when i saw ramza lugria ramza bewulf the
3d screenshots of him and the new decidia that is a celebration of the character that in no way detracts
from their legacy things like that could not be more excited about them they're fucking fantastic
it's when i have a problem when something comes along and is trying to one up uh someone who like
like sakaguchi is the is the guy and the the writer whose name i forget uh who made final
fantasy seven what it is they're the guys who did it and now we got these new guys i say they're
gonna redo it and you know i i just don't think there's even a ghost of a chance of them really
getting what that game was about and communicating it in a in a meaningful way and for that and i
for that reason i think it will only pollute the legacy and i don't want that to happen
and so that's the real reason at the end of the day i don't like remakes in addition to the other
reasons that we talked about before anime is a japanese colloquial
oh Jesus christ what a bombshell what a bombshell so so you know i just want to ask you know as
our is our special guest of the day um uh jeff mother's basement i just want to ask you your
thoughts on as the only one of us as the only one of us who's met sakaguchi how does it feel to know
that you are advocating the pollution of his artistic vision how does that feel you feel good
about that well okay so for one thing sakaguchi's artistic vision is that final fantasy six is the
best final fantasy but he likes final 97 too it's not like he hates the game he doesn't want it
raped he doesn't want to see it raped he doesn't want to see it raped and you know sakaguchi um
man my my opinion is that you guys should all go play terra battle because uh sakaguchi is making
new cool shit i would love to i should i should um and that's a mobile game by the way better on
handheld mother fuckers um but um yeah i don't play the yeah go ahead go ahead it's it's actually
okay so terra battle pretty cool game it's all about positioning tiles it's kind of like halfway
between a puzzle game like a match three puzzle game and an rpg uh but not like puzzle quest
anyway like yeah it's like puzzle dragon or something i am not strictly speaking advocating
the final fantasy seven remake reaping the shit out of everything that's already been done they're
just going back for another round yeah because i they they did already destroy it with advent
children um and they they which i mean let's be real the only to to to quote uh to quote max
from life is strange the only well not to quote but to paraphrase the only good final fantasy
movie is the spirits within um interesting which because there's not a lot of competition
there but okay because they didn't try to make something that was the same fucking thing wait
wait how old is this girl who said that uh she's like 18 18 oh okay i thought she's like 13 i was
gonna call her hipster that's not so bad no yeah like what she specifically says is she's like i
don't care what anyone says this is one of the greatest sci-fi movies of all time and that game
was published by square enix so um yeah so you know but anyway i am still sour over this whole
i mean they fired sakaguchi over yeah he resigned he resigned to be fair he resigned but it was like
you know that that whole japanese resiner will right tell you thank you coach him it did recently um
and uh well actually i don't know that i can't speak for sakaguchi because he didn't tell me that
anyway i am not advocating them destroying his vision of this game that in part he made for his
dying mother and which obviously was very died she was already dead dude she was dead oh she was dead
yeah yeah so which was obviously which is the most beautiful vision and i love this game so much and
to learn something like that years after playing it my god people what are you doing what are you
doing so so i am not necessarily advocating that i think that a final fantasy remake could
potentially be good and i think that gameplay wise like the thing is this could fun to play this
could rape or this i don't want to say rape over and over again this could fucking destroy every
bit of artistic integrity that final fantasy seven has just like uh shin megami tensei four destroyed
every bit of artistic integrity that the shin megami tensei series has but it's still it's
still a fucking fun game to play which means people still consider it to be a good shin megami
tensei game and this could still be like a good final fantasy game but here's the here's what i would
advocate um get uh what i would advocate playing final fantasy seven if you feel like you want to
play final fantasy seven take out your psp or your ps vita get it on your psp or your ps vita
and play it that way or on steam why do you want them to have the worst possible experience
because it's much more palatable to play it on a handheld where uh the load screen or your ps4
where you won't have to play it play it play it on a fucking place the sony playstation you know
look fill the great thing is you've got options you're gonna love final fantasy seven you're not
gonna want to play it for 20 minutes at a time before breaking your neck you're gonna want to
wear crt television set and a sony playstation with a fucking memory card and one of the skinny
original controllers and you fucking sit there and you take your fucking medicine until you
beat in the fucking game and then you could have an opinion you talk like an animal he's right
it's objectively the best way to do it also you should do it in 1997 if possible or 1990 and be
like eight times of twelve yeah yeah so the best the best way to do it just smack yourself in the
head until you remember what computer graphics are capable of now and then go back and and play
but yeah like so i i think that that game provides a better experience on handheld like all
rpgs but okay i would advocate playing it that way he really wants he's cruising for a bruising
i gotta let's let's let's move on past this point we're getting uh can we end this i i you know i
think we've wrapped up you know what just just i wanted to do one thing before we ended which was
just to read a couple of just to get an idea of what people in general think about remakes like the
the slobbering masses i wanted to read three of my favorite comments on my final fantasy seven
remake video all right here we go uh oh where where they go hang on okay here's here's the first one
that's kind of reasonable uh why do people focus more on the negative side of the remake than on
the positive side i know square enix completely screwed the company in the seventh gen but come on
they can't make another mistake after 13 and 14 love that one okay i've got two more um what is it
i hope you don't get this game after you just made this video this video is pointless and cancerous
and finally my favorite one of all to cap it off by calypso handjack my hero stopped watching after
30 seconds cloud did not wear purple guys a fucking retard stop making videos thank you calypso
thank you very much i think he summed up all of our thoughts he really did he really did
at the end of the day you got to go with your handjack i'm gonna jack your hand all right that's
it thanks for watching everybody uh appreciate you sticking with us for this long one i hope you
have a very special day everybody say goodbye bye bye play final fantasy seven on your
okay
he's doing i don't like him he's dumb you're dumb you're dumb