Christmas evolved from the Roman holiday Saturnalia, a winter festival where men gave gifts to each other.
They also would get drunk, have sex with each other, and beat their wives.
People would act so crazy on Christmas, the holiday was outlawed by the Protestant church until the 1800s.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
A podcast of a bunch of people on the internet talking about things they like and dislike.
I'm the best guy ever, and today we're joined by such characters as Hippocrit.
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas.
Tom Oliver is here.
I'm dreaming of a white Kwanzaa.
Now that's the dream, that's the real dream. The Davoo is here.
I think even the word holiday is offensive because it implies holy, thus divine. Let's just use festive. Come on guys, be PC.
Did you bros here?
This is the dawning of the rest of our life on holiday.
Who is that? Is that Blink?
That's Green Day.
That's right. That's right. That's right.
That's from America.
Right guys, we're talking about holidays. Merry Christmas everyone.
Merry Kwanzaa.
Happy Hanukkah.
Whatever the fuck made up holidays you guys celebrate. I hope that you're having a good one.
This will be out after Christmas, before New Year's, so right in that sweet spot.
Before the important one.
Which is New Year's.
New Year's is the only holiday I care about.
I think that makes like the exact same holiday because they sort of meld into one another.
Yeah.
The holidays are an amorphous blob.
I don't think of them that way. It's a whole week between them, and New Year's is more special to me.
Because Christmas is just about like giving each other shit. New Year's is about getting fucked up.
And that's why it's the best holiday, but we'll get into that later.
Yeah, right. I mean, we're busting this nut wide open and revealing all the secrets within on all holidays here.
This is going to be, I assume we'll spend most of our time on Halloween.
It's like the most important one. It's the most relevant one.
You know, Hippo knows.
It's probably the only one significantly rising in popularity still, where all the other ones are sort of on a public opinion decline, I would say.
It's a slutty ween and whatnot, has really brought it to the mainstream.
But hey, let's break this thing down with a visit to our good friend UrbanDictionary.com and find out what the fuck a holiday even is.
Okay, so a holiday. Here we go.
An opportunity for relatives to come around and say stupid shit like, why haven't you found a wife yet?
My favorite part about holidays is how being single is considered a disease.
There you go. All right.
Was that all in the UrbanDictionary definition? Or was that just you responding to it?
No, no. That's in the definition. That's in the definition.
Also, a British term for vacation. I always thought that was weird.
We don't have vacation as a word, I guess. We go on holiday to summer places.
And Harry Potter, when they had summer holiday and they're going on holiday and whatnot, it was very triggering.
Are we going to make sure to keep this to nationally recognized holidays?
I think just the big ones. Christmas, Halloween.
Halloween's not even technically a holiday. Nobody gets off and work on Halloween.
My favorite holiday is the Eclipse, the solar eclipse.
But see, it's not the Earth solar eclipse. It's the Mars solar eclipse that I calculate using.
I triangulate the position of the sun and the moon in the sky.
Wait, Mars doesn't even have a moon. Never mind. I thought that was going to be hilarious.
Mars could eclipse the sun if it tried hard enough.
Does Mars have a moon? Is that accurate?
Mars has two moons.
Okay, so it's twice as likely then to do Eclipse and shit.
But no, the Earth is like the only...
Alright, so anyway, talking about holidays here, what the fuck are we... God.
Do we want to go through them in order or something?
Let's go from most woke to least woke holidays in order.
Everyone's currently on Google searching a list of holidays.
What are these things again? I remember Halloween.
If you can't recall them off the top of your head, they don't matter.
But big holidays are relative, because in America, Thanksgiving's a big one,
but I'm sure to you, Thanksgiving is not even real.
America is the only place that matters, so who fucking cares?
The only thing about Thanksgiving is that there's Black Friday,
which has permeated the collective consciousness of fucking everybody.
And I generally hate it, because I don't get it.
You just don't like it as Black in the title.
Do you know why they call it Black Friday?
Oh, hippo, do you know why they call it Black Friday?
I don't know if this is something that everyone knows or not a whole lot of people know.
Why it's called Black Friday?
I know.
Tell us.
Well, first of all, like all facts I've ever heard in my fucking life,
I'm sure like next week I'm going to hear that it was actually,
I heard this from a false source and this isn't the reason,
like every knowledge in the world.
I will know whether or not it's true, because I know why it's called that.
Yeah, because you heard it from the real service.
It's because stores are in the red basically all year
because retail is a shitty industry to get into,
and so they named it after their own relieved desire
to finally have Black on the bottom line of their revenue.
And that's what it's called Black Friday.
The idea is we get so many people like literally killing each other
to get their shit that we actually make a profit for the first time.
So that's basically the whole retail industry is completely circled
around the whole holiday season.
It's like literally their business model,
which is part of a whole holiday creep that I want to get into
toward the end of this.
Oh yeah, that's the most important thing I wanted to talk about on here.
Me too, yeah.
In fact, I kind of want to skip straight to that, because like,
Can we?
The holidays we're going to talk about here,
the ones that we all care about, like fuck Memorial Day,
no one gives a fuck.
No one knows what it's about other than the pools close.
Like that's all that I know about Memorial Day.
The pools close, yeah.
Oh yeah, I went into that shit too, yeah, definitely.
Oh wait, do the pools open or close on Memorial Day?
Which one is earlier?
That's like only open on Memorial Day.
The fact that you don't even know just proves your point that it doesn't matter.
Yeah, it's close.
They close on Memorial Day and open on like Veterans Day or something like that.
Like those are like the bookends of summer, you know.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
In America, pools open and close based on the holidays.
No, not the fucking pool thing, the fucking Veterans Day.
I mean, I guess we have like military days as well.
Yeah, we've got Veterans Day where you celebrate Veterans Memorial Day,
which is where you cry because people died.
I have no fucking idea.
Yeah, that's right.
Martin Luther King Day, no one cares.
But the holidays we have that matter are like New Year's, Halloween, Christmas, Thanksgiving.
Those are the ones that have slowly expanded and run way beyond their day
and consumed whole years of time.
Walking through the fucking hallways of aisles at Walmart,
they had Christmas shit up on October 29th.
And it's like, guys, guys, hold the fuck up.
Stop, stop, stop.
No one wants this.
No one here wants this.
Okay, if there was able to sort of spread out the joy of the holiday season in a way,
I mean, perhaps that'd be nice, but really all it seems to do is cheapen it.
Absolutely.
That's because it's not done to increase the appeal and the good feelings of the holidays.
It's to maximize you spending money.
That's why it feels so cold.
As much as people can debate whether or not the mythological cultural figure of Santa Claus really exists,
there is one highly doubted mythological figure that does exist.
It's called the slippery slope.
People like to call that argument a fallacy,
but if you look at literally any human activity ever,
there is not a single fucking slope humanity has never slid down.
And in this case, its retailers became dependent on the holiday season to make money,
so they just take more and more and more and more and they just cannot help themselves.
They are as fat as your fat uncle at Thanksgiving on the holiday cheer.
It is obscene.
Do you know that Santa Claus used to be green?
What made you red?
Did you know he's not got Father Christmas any time anywhere other than your country?
What?
I mean, they call him a lot of things in a lot of different countries,
because he's a weird amalgam of a million things.
When I was a kid, we called him Father Christmas,
because it's like Father like a religious thing.
But I just thought it was like Dad Christmas or something.
Lol.
And then Santa Claus was like, oh, that's the American one.
Everyone knows, on Christmas, we celebrate the fact that Santa is your dad for the day.
Everyone enjoys it.
And once she stays up all night getting ready to steal as soon as he comes down.
Oh, getting ready to beat his father for one day.
Oh, I actually think that retailers got so focused on Christmas that they killed Easter.
Yeah, absolutely.
When I was growing up, there was this holiday called Easter,
that I don't know if anyone still celebrates.
But there was like a bunny, and you had these eggs.
You would like paint eggs, like regular eggs.
But then you would also have like fake eggs with candy inside of them that were hidden everywhere.
And you had to find those.
Is this really like dead?
We do this all the time.
Like this is still a thing.
Do you still do Easter?
I just don't think it's something that adults do much.
I'm trying to explain this so that like modern children can understand.
I don't know if they have Easter.
I think this is still a thing that happens.
I think explaining Easter is like explaining a Nintendo, like an NES game.
I don't think it's that far gone, dude.
Okay.
Well, perhaps.
I mean, me and my family, like up until before I moved away, moved out to Ohio,
me and my family would do our Easter egg hunt every year.
And mostly it was just because my dad liked doing it,
and it was an excuse to get together.
Do you think it's a holiday that only exists in families with kids?
Yeah.
As soon as they grow up, it's not fun.
Unless you're very religious, in which case that's like a very sacred day.
The problem with Easter is that there's not enough of like a party aspect attached to it
for like adults to celebrate Easter.
I think the problem with it is that hiding eggs around the garden is time-consuming,
and I don't care.
Oh, well, I love doing it.
Am I going to be eating mud?
I don't want to be doing that.
I don't love fucking trolling people.
Is that it's becoming a light Christmas?
At least that's my experience with it.
It's more about like you have to, because you used to just get like the Easter basket
that had like candy and whatever, but like slowly it's been like,
well, we need to corporatize this to make money.
So like you need to buy presents on Easter, not just a dumb little gift basket.
Wait, Tom, do you still get presents on Easter in your family?
I don't anymore, but like back when I was growing up, it did get more and more...
Yeah, like I remember that.
I remember that by the time I was like 10 or 11.
I grew up Christian.
I grew up Christian, so like Easter was a big deal in this house,
because you know Jesus was fucking back, kicking ass.
Yeah, to this every year growing up.
As we all know, when Jesus died on the cross, like a thousand bunnies showed up
and cried and cried, and a bunch of eggs were laid by the bunnies,
and that's why Jesus died.
Wait, no, I think this is detailed in the Professor Brothers lectures on Jesus.
But like, fucking, to this, like every time I got like a gift on Easter,
like for my entire childhood growing up, I was consistently baffled
on why I was being given like a gift.
Like don't get me wrong, like in our Christmas basket one day,
there was one magical morning when I woke up,
and we got Easter baskets with some candy,
and in Ben's basket I believe was Mega Man X,
and in mine was Donkey Kong Country 3.
Holy fuck!
And it was like the most legendary Easter of all time.
But I still don't understand why I was given those.
I've never heard of Easter.
I've never heard of Easter presents, that's never been like a failure.
My parents didn't man, I don't know.
I can count the contents of the eggs as presents.
Now quite unlike Hippo, I loved hiding the eggs,
like I would be the sole proprietor of egg hiding duties.
I mean the reason I wouldn't, I mean, the reason I said that was like,
the reason adults don't continue it is because it's a fucking hassle.
It's kind of a demand on your time for an adult.
It's more of a thing that can only be enjoyed by kids.
You can still enjoy giving and getting presents at Christmas as an adult.
When my family got a business and had a rural neighborhood that we lived in with a big yard,
that's when I became an ultra bastard at my hiding techniques.
I'd put eggs on appliances where they completely blend in,
whether you can't see them, I'd put eggs inside a broken part of a tree that you have to open.
You and I are in a unique position because we're older brothers.
Easter is the most fun for an eldest brother for about two years.
It's when you're like 12 and 13,
when you're like right at the age where you're too old to have to look for the eggs
because you'll find them immediately, but your little brothers are still kind of retarded.
Well, the eggs I had, not even I would have found.
Your parents would never hide them that well.
Your parents are just going to put eggs around,
and then your kid brother, you're going to find them all immediately,
your kid brother's not going to find any.
So it's way more fun if you hide the eggs because not only will you do a better job,
but now it's all on them.
There's probably some they won't even find, and it's just going to be way more fun.
But then as soon as they're old enough that they could hide the eggs themselves,
there's nowhere to go from there.
No one in my family extended or even acquaintances is as much of an evil person as me.
I put an egg just straight up in the ground with barely a centimeter sticking out of it, right?
Like barely like a millimeter sticking out of it, right?
See, it's a win-win, the thing with eggs, because if they never find them,
you get to forever enjoy the fact that they didn't find it and it's there,
even though it's plastic rotting away for all eternity.
Now they do find it, then you get to take a victory lap in your cleverness,
because you've been exposed and now they get to see your logic.
But the point is, underneath that egg was another egg.
But like one inch further down.
And underneath that...
Yeah, I am the Dark Souls of Easter, that's what I'm saying.
Incredible.
I was just like, the gutters were always the best.
You got your rain gutter.
But yeah, when I was a kid, there was a period where it suddenly became a toy holiday,
and I think that's what killed Easter, because Easter was like the hiding eggs,
candy, like simple, he spent like $15, $20 on Easter.
And then as soon as parents started having to spend money to buy you a video game
or some shit on Easter, they were like, didn't we just do this on Christmas,
and your birthday?
We can't have every fucking holiday coming along bleeding us dry.
I think my parents were trying to get out of the Easter game as fast as possible,
because I was probably like 13 when we stopped doing that shit.
Our approach to these things with my family was more like,
we were always happy to have an excuse to celebrate something or buy things for each other,
because I don't know, we're all cut through capitalists who are out to get each other
and get the competition.
I mean, not really, but there was kind of that sentiment.
And I personally think the real problem with Easter as a holiday is that it is too kiddy of a holiday,
just in general in the ways I was saying before.
There's no reason why a parent, like okay, because obviously children are worthless and do nothing.
Only parents make everything happen.
It needs more eggnog, they need something to make parents like invest in Easter as a thing.
And I don't know what that would be, but it needs something.
You ask adults why they like Christmas, they're like, ah, eggnog.
A million reasons.
I want rum in my wintry drink.
It's all about excuses to drink.
Well, think about this way, Halloween was probably primarily,
capital-y a child holiday for a long time.
It just took the infantilization of society,
had to catch up to it to the point that now an adult can be like,
oh yeah, I'm dressed enough for fucking crit for Halloween.
And now you're weird if you don't.
Go to a party.
Now it's like everyone goes to hell.
That's like everyone doing it kind of thing.
So at the rate we're at the second biggest holiday.
If you know some 20-somethings, there's going to be a Halloween party that you're invited to.
So maybe eventually the infantilization of society,
give it another generation or so,
they'll be like, oh yeah, Easter, fucking scavenger party, sweet, let's do it.
And then you'll be weird if you don't do that.
We could talk more about individual ones if you guys want to,
I have a larger point about holidays in general,
and I do want to ask, who is, let's just a quick poll,
who is pro-holiday and who is anti-holiday?
I'm pretty anti-holiday.
As a person who doesn't have days on or days off,
I don't really know what to think about it.
I think it's good for kids, it's great for kids, it's lovely for kids.
Keep them for that.
And other than that, I think some people need time off,
but I don't know about holidays generally.
The festivities, you have to do the specific type of festivity.
You have to make a Christmas roast.
What if you don't like roast? What if nobody likes roast?
If you don't like your family?
I would like time off of work,
but I don't know whether I would like to dress up a tree every year.
I know what you mean.
To that effect, I want to pitch a holiday here real quick,
which people have done a lot before,
so I'm sort of reiterating their arguments,
but I think it makes a lot of sense.
New holiday, everyone gets the day off.
It's a national holiday, at least in America and probably everywhere.
It is voting day.
When everyone gets the day off and you can go vote, it's easy,
nothing to worry about, you've got one thing to do.
I think voting should take a whole week though.
I don't think it should only be on one day.
But there is a day set aside where if you can't,
for whatever reason, you've got a day where you can do it.
I'm surprised it isn't already a thing.
It seems very dumb.
It could be a reason.
I'm sure some people oppose it because there is a measured...
I'm sure some people have done studies on what it would be like
if they did that, and they found like,
uh-oh, that means 50% more blacks will vote.
I was going to say, it's very easy to quell the working class
if they're too busy working a 12-hour shift.
Cat-a-fucking-gorkly,
politicians who make the laws and decide rules like that
are all very comfortable with the exact mechanisms
that got them elected, so there you go.
Exactly, which is why these people cannot...
It's ridiculous that we have the people making the decisions
on how to do this stuff are also the ones, like, you know,
themselves, those who should be in charge.
It should be a separate body that decides this stuff.
I got a separate body for you.
So, to answer your question of who's pro and anti-holiday,
I am pro-holiday as an idea,
but I think I'm anti a lot of the holidays that exist,
and mostly because they're just so, like, homogenized,
and, like, it's all the... Yeah, it makes everything the same.
Like, you go out, fucking Christmas is the worst,
and, um, in my family over the last decade or so,
we've done a lot of, like, experimental Christmas alternatives.
For instance, in 2008, we celebrated Festivus,
the made-up holiday from Seinfeld,
and then for the next two years, I made up my own holidays.
One was where we celebrated Hearth Swarming Eve, the...
Oh!
There was a whole video about it.
One of the oldest videos on my channel was a 20-minute explanation,
and, like... I remember that.
Like, cataloging of what happens on Hearth Swarming Eve,
and I basically just took the stuff that happens in the show
and, like, reimagined it for what real people would do, you know?
Right, yeah, like...
Hearth Swarming Eve, ponies all come together,
unicorns, pegasi, earth ponies, whatever,
being friends with each other, regardless of race,
someone needs to remind these upstarts of their place!
Hey! Hey!
Fancy reviews.
Like, fucking, the thing with holidays is they're just dated,
and the reason why they continue to persist with such, uh,
hack-need tradition is because no one wants to look like the fucking curmudgeon
who doesn't want to participate, right?
That's the hardest part, is, like, convincing people, like,
no, I like hanging out with my family,
I like buying you all things.
What I don't like is that for two months out of every fucking year,
everywhere I go is playing Christmas music,
and it's the same Christmas music.
Fifteen songs.
Yeah, the same 15 songs reimagined infinitely,
and the worst part is that none of the reimaginings are any good.
It's all, like, the shittiest quality music playing.
We go out, Dibu, hold on a second, let me do my rant.
We go out, and fucking, like, they'll be playing, like,
this, like, shit-mitty version of, like, some obscure Christmas song
that no one cares about, and, like, there was one,
there's this one that's on the radio right now
that I heard in the department store, and it made me, like,
feel like I was on drugs?
Like, more so than usual?
Dude, did you guys know Did You Broke Those Drugs?
It was, like, this weird, like, I don't know,
it was, like, a feeling, like, the music was just bad
in, like, a way that's, like, hypnotic,
and it, like, made me feel like my brain was rotting out of my head,
like, they were trying to, like, push Christmas, like,
subliminals into me or some shit.
Dude, what song was this?
I don't remember what, it was one of the generic Christmas songs,
like, one of the instrumental ones.
It was, like, a really bad instrumental.
Like, it just sounded like shit.
My thing with Christmas music that I only really thought about this year
is, regardless of the, like, comp, like, regardless of the recording quality,
is that, you know how, like, in a song, by the third time you get to the chorus,
the singer is, like, doing it a little bit differently,
because that's how a lot of it works.
The way with Christmas music is because I think this is, like,
a subliminal, subconscious thing that everyone has done,
is that because everyone's heard these songs thousands of times,
they're sort of singing it as though it's the 2,000th version of the chorus,
so I'm not gonna try and sing it, but I'll do the rhythm of, like,
I'll be home for Christmas,
if only in my dreams.
They sing it as, like, wrongly as possible,
because, like, that's how you do it differently.
What's supposed to be, like, the jazz swing version,
now it's, like, jingle bells, jingle bells,
it's, like, you can't make jingle bells sound cool.
It's always gonna be fucking jingle bells, you know?
Right, exactly.
Like, and the worst part is that it's playing literally everywhere,
so, like, I go out to have, like, Chinese food,
and they're playing it at the Chinese food place,
and I'm, like, I was kind of trying to escape the American Christmas culture
by coming to some foreign land,
but no, there is no escaping it.
They're singing jingle bells in Chinese,
because that would have been cool.
No, they were doing the fr-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra.
No.
Dude, like, I remember, okay, did you, you know,
you watched Todd in the Shadows.
I remember one year, I think it was 2012, he was like,
guys, we seriously need some more Christmas songs,
so he reviewed a bunch of new Christmas songs,
hated them all, next Christmas, he said,
yeah, there's nothing else to sing about Christmas,
we're done, it's an expense idea, it's done with.
So, here's the thing about all the holidays,
but mostly Christmas, they're dated,
but the way that they are celebrated now
made sense for the baby boomers,
it made sense back in the 50s and 60s.
Back in the 50s and 60s, we had three channels on TV,
now we have a thousand, we had one flavor of pasta sauce,
now we have 20, we need more options,
it's just too similar, so here's my proposal.
We need a bright neon 80s style future to move,
we need 80s, you know, neon holidays.
We are now a culture of options and customization,
so here's my proposal.
Halloween and Christmas become merged,
because people want that anyway,
so many people do Halloween stuff for Christmas,
or like, you know.
It's a terrible idea, we never heard of that.
We have to separate these.
It's a fantastic idea.
Are you saying that basically, it's like a pick,
like, okay, the last three months of the year
is holiday time, but you get to pick which holiday,
is that what you're saying?
Yeah, you can do any combination that you want.
You can choose your own adventure holiday.
Fucking imagine, you're sitting down to Christmas dinner,
and a trick or treater comes up to the door,
he's full of gravy in that bag.
Yeah, and also, you know what,
I didn't even think about this until this podcast
fucking throw Easter in there too.
Easter is already too samey, so that way,
like, you get a customization going to fuck on, right?
Makes sense to me.
And just make new years just like the...
I think the problem with the holidays has become,
because I like the idea of holidays in concept,
kind of like similar to what you were saying, Digi,
is that like, I like the idea of just like, you know,
good times, like good food, hang out with family, whatever.
But the problem is because it becomes so corporatized,
it just feels so fake, like there's this,
this omnipresent fake goodness
that's really just an excuse to make you want to spend more money.
Speaking of the corporatization of it,
alright, this is a whole other bag,
a trick to get into here.
Yeah, I saw your podcast, I know where this is going.
What podcast? I've no idea what you're talking about.
The one you did with Rucker Rucker.
Oh, yeah, of course.
This is a slightly different point though.
This is about how every day is like now is a holiday.
Like they've gone through the calendar,
they found it every single day.
That's true.
I have pulled up a list, everybody.
I'm looking at it right now.
What holiday is it right now?
I'm happy to tell you.
Today is the 23rd of December that we're recording on it.
This is in fact Festivus Day,
but it is also Roots Day.
I don't know what that means,
but it is Roots Day.
Tomorrow, in addition to being Christmas Eve,
is National Chocolate Day
and also National Eggnog Day.
Remember to go out and make chocolate eggnog, kids.
When you say national, is that an American?
It's America.
Well, that's the same.
I'm clean.
Oh, and just for the viewers,
just for the viewers' enjoyment,
this episode will come out on the 31st,
and just so you know, listener,
it is New Year's Eve and Unlucky Day
and Make Up Your Mind Day,
according to HolidayInsights.com.
The thing is that all holidays now are just memes.
All of these made up holidays
that are for every day of the year,
they come from Facebook.
Someone makes a Facebook image meme
that's like, oh, this is now National Cookie Day,
and then everyone shares that,
because my mom shares all these.
If it's something she likes,
my mom will be like, oh, it's Cookie Day,
and she'll come home with cookies,
and I'm like, this is a fucking meme, you know?
Right, it's one half meme, one half marketing.
I'm like, hey, we're a brownie company.
Let's make sure what brownie day gets celebrated
and the laws that we can get off tick and ourselves.
Brownie day is National Brownie Day,
where is it, the 8th of December,
National Brownie Day.
Fuck, damn it, I missed it.
I missed it.
By the way, this really reminds me,
I didn't realize that was the case.
Gabe, you know how in One Piece,
in the question and answer thing,
whatever it's called, the SBS,
Oda will just get, someone will send a message
and be like, hey, can this person's birthday be this day?
And he's just like, sure, fine, it doesn't matter, okay.
It's exactly that arbitrary.
Yeah.
What a world.
Oh, I want to talk about my one other made up,
my own version of Christmas,
because the corporateization is why my family
kind of stopped celebrating mainstream Christmas,
which they do again now, because my parents,
my dad grew up with it,
my dad kind of likes having the tree
and the decorations put in the presents under the tree.
That's the main part of it he still cares about.
It's like, let's just make sure
there's a decorated tree with shit under it.
I like that, you know?
Because in some of our weird made up holidays,
it was usually just like they just,
we just had like a big bag with gifts in it
and we just kind of hand them out
and it just doesn't have much drama
to the actual gift giving, you know?
You just were Santa, you just had the bag yourself,
just like, fuck that guy, we got this.
One of the holidays I had made up was called Agarwood Day,
and it was based around the band Agalodge,
who is a black metal band,
but basically their music sounds like winter
and I associate winter with the aesthetic of black metal.
As opposed to Christmas music, just like the exact opposite.
Me too. Yeah, me too.
You know, I'm looking at the window right now,
there's a fucking blizzard going on, I'm in New York,
so it's like, it's snowing constantly,
and I'm like, this does not make me think
like, fast Christmas, I gave,
this makes me think like, Mother North, you know?
So, like...
It's the coziness though, when you're inside
and it's snowing outside, it's the coziness of it.
When you're by the fire and it's all warm,
that's the fire I associate with it.
You don't stay inside cosily when there's snow,
you put on a giant fur coat,
and with a pipe you go out.
Just to summarize it, the idea of Agarwood Day
was I would take an Agalodge song
and interpret the lyrics as things that we could do
on the holiday,
because our family's always been big about
the activities of a holiday.
It's not so much about the religion,
the sitting around with your family or whatever,
we don't really do the Christmas dinner so much
as what are fun things you can do on a holiday.
So, like, one we have for Christmas that we still do,
and I don't know about this year because I won't be there,
but like, we usually make a giant bonfire on Christmas
because we have like a fire pit in my backyard.
And we'll do this thing where we write down
on a piece of paper like something we don't want to take
with us into the new year and throw it into the fire.
Dude, holy shit.
Yeah, so like...
It's like the opposite of like the New Year's resolutions.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like you throw away this stuff
and then on New Year's you pick up what you're going to take
with you into the next year.
Which, incidentally, on New Year's,
which I'll get into a lot,
we have a lot of New Year's traditions,
but my favorite one is that we take our champagne glass
and like, you're not supposed to drink the champagne
until the ball drops, right?
Like 10, 9, 8, you hit one, you drink.
But before that, you write down like your New Year's resolution
on like a tiny slip of paper and you burn it into your drink.
So, like, you then drink it with the champagne.
Right.
Yeah, I did that with you.
I've been having real good luck with...
Yeah, we all did that,
along with our other traditions,
which are donuts for some reason.
We always eat donuts, drink a shitload of champagne,
and we make party hats.
Like, we each make our own party hat
that like is supposed to encapsulate
like everything you sort of did and were in 2016.
Oh, you guys did that when I...
I remember we were around for,
when Radcon at the beginning of this year happened,
those were still hanging around.
Yeah, me and Ben had been doing that.
But yeah, so that's why I love New Year's.
I love that aspect.
I love the creative aspect of holidays,
being like, with Easter, again, the egg hunt,
like that's a great idea of like,
oh, we're going to hide eggs and shit like that.
But the problem is that it ends up being just shit
that everybody does,
and it's not necessarily what your family wants to do.
Right.
I think a lot of like what killed
like Thanksgiving and Christmas for me
is that like my extended family are all kind of,
like we don't really get along with a lot of them,
and like they all kind of live far apart.
So we don't have, like when I was a kid,
it was like, oh, the whole family's here for Christmas,
and I get that.
I totally get why people would enjoy that.
But when it's like just you,
and like it's just your parents and kids,
and it's like, well,
we all bought each other stuff, I guess,
even though we're all in our 20s now,
and like, you know, like...
Yeah, money.
When you were a kid,
you only cared about Christmas
because that's when you got a game console.
You know, you couldn't get a game console
under the time of the year.
I think that, yeah, if it when I have kids,
I think I'm gonna try and like,
make loopholes to make them not care so much
about the getting shit of Christmas.
I'm just gonna buy them a console when it comes out.
Or when a good game comes out.
You know?
Or rather, they're gonna be like,
what the fuck's a console?
Yeah, who knows.
Yeah, well, fair point.
Console gaming might have been about 10 years.
I've been thinking about the commercialization of Christmas,
and I think, I mean, I don't, you know,
jump into it like, I don't embrace it myself,
but I do like that it exists
because it allows me to judge myself and my family
above all the stupid people who buy into the commercial,
the buying the stuff, the cheap Chinese plastic
and the millions of lights and just, yeah, fuck you.
I had a nice, I had a nice meal.
I gave a gift that I knew my people,
my family would want to them,
and I saw them open it and it was great.
And I had one party and that's all I need,
and everyone who goes beyond that
is just somebody who I can laugh at.
So it's like even funnier.
So I like the commercialization.
It's pretty good.
Hippo, I'm glad you reminded me of this.
A few weeks ago, I was standing outside having a cigarette
on my front porch, and I looked down the road
and a few houses down.
I see a guy get out of his truck
and he put something on the ground
and then slowly what inflates from the ground
is an eight-foot-tall minion.
Oh!
Dressed as Santa Claus, like wearing like a Santa helper hat.
Well, you know, eight-foot-tall minion.
Eight-foot-tall one of those sorts of things.
I overheard the guy talking to his neighbor
and he goes, the neighbor's like, oh, my God, right?
And he's like, yeah, she told me,
I told her I wanted to get an inflatable.
She said, I can only do it if it was a minion.
And I said, fair game.
Dude, on the line, around me.
There's a bunch of inflatable minions.
There's one house that has like three minions
in front of it. What is with the fucking minions?
I'll tell you what the fuck is with the minions.
Mom's, everyone's mom.
Despicable Me is a mom franchise.
There's just no two ways about it.
I think my mom kind of thinks they're cute, too.
This is scientifically proven by me through my life.
I go up to everyone and be like, what's up with all the minions?
What's up with Despicable Me? Why is this so popular?
I don't know. Hey, mom, I love Despicable Me.
I love the minions. They're great. It's just a mom movie.
And mom's, yeah, minions are mother's things.
That makes sense to me.
This reminds me of something about the holidays.
It makes a weird kind of sense.
No, no, no, no, no. Because the main character of Despicable Me
like raises three adopted girls.
He is like a mom kind of character.
Yeah, he's a mom character.
Yeah, but they only talk about and show and pick the little weird yellow guys.
Nobody has merchandise of the characters of that movie.
Well, because the minions are the distillation of the feelings that you feel when you watch,
that a mother feels when they watch the big movie.
I'm going to get a fucking inflatable fidget spinner.
That'd be pretty sick.
Especially if it does spin.
Dude, only if you could actually like, imagine having a giant inflatable spin.
If it's fun.
Yeah, actually, spin. That'd be pretty fun.
Or especially like maybe Santa Claus is like flipping it around with like the,
some meme glasses and shit.
I just want that Ajit Pai meme as an inflatable.
On my lawn.
He's very festive.
Right.
Do it.
But Tom, what were you saying, dude?
I was just going to say lawn ornaments.
That reminds me of like something that I always just found really just dumb about the holidays.
Like the try-hards who like deck their entire house out and like all these lights and all these decorate.
There's someone who's down the street from us like every year.
It's just his entire house, all of his yard, all of the fence.
Just, just, just like, I can't imagine this dude's power bill.
It must be insane.
Dude, he's peacocking so hard.
He's pulling so much pus.
Well, that dude.
He's slagging so much pus with that.
I gotta tell you.
It's ridiculous.
Tom, I gotta tell you about this guy in my old neighborhood.
There's this, walking down the main road that goes into my neighborhood.
There's these two houses directly across from each other that are always like pulling out all the stops on their Christmas shit.
No one else in the neighborhood's like this.
It's just these two guys.
They're obviously competing with each other.
But one of them has gotten to the point where during the holiday season, they put like a full monitor in their window and just play like live footage of Christmas carols.
Like, like on stage.
Like they play like live Christmas carol performances like all day and night on a fucking huge monitor in the window that you can hear when you're walking past the house.
It's fucking insane.
Dude, the weirdest, the weirdest one that I ever found is my, it was like two years ago and my mom, my mom is totally into all this shit.
She loves it.
She'll never do any of it herself because she's too lazy, but like likes being the observer.
So she demanded that all of us get in the car and drive somewhere.
Yeah.
So we drove.
We used to do that when we were kids.
Our whole family would pilot a car and drive around.
This was a bizarre experience.
So we go out of our way like 20 minutes to this house.
And we had to like turn on, I think we had to like turn on the radio or something.
It was like a radio, like a smartphone thing and you hit a button and a whole thing would play on this person's house.
You could start it whenever you wanted.
Just this guy's house.
Incredible.
He decked out everything and it was like responding to like an app or something and you would make it like auto play.
That's cool.
And I'm just, and I'm just like, I appreciate the technical prowess that would need to be like done to do this.
But at the same time, what the fuck, man?
I can explain this because down at the beach by my house, like on the main beach, there's this stretch of road that they turn into a light show during Christmas time.
And basically it's like you come in and it's like that.
It's like, I think they give you a CD or it was a radio station or something like that.
But like this was when I was a kid.
So it wasn't no app or anything like that.
You would drive down this stretch of road and like you're supposed to listen to this particular CD while you're driving and like the music matches up with the lights.
And like, like, you know, if you're driving at the correct speed, you know, right?
So Tom, I think that's what he might have been inspired by something like that.
Tom, did you ever go to Los Alets by any chance?
Like where I lived in Massachusetts, like right at the street once we used to go to the Fatima trying a lot.
They had a lot of displays.
Dude, guys, you know what was like the craziest lawn ornaments I've ever seen?
It was these refreshing breath mints seen after the TV show Lawn Order. Lawn Order mints.
That's what I had. I had them. I ate them. They refreshed my breath.
Who, who, who? Excellent.
By the way, everybody, May 6th is National Beverage Day.
Don't forget to drink a beverage on May 6th, National Beverage Day.
Wait, wait, like just completely no specific.
It's just beverage. It's just beverage.
Just drink water that day.
Don't forget. Do not forget.
I guess I've been celebrating that all my life.
I celebrate it every day.
It's really been watered down, if you will.
Oh, yes!
Guys, I want to say something about New Year's.
Now, I'm going to tell a story and I don't know if I'm either going to seem like a weirdo to everyone
or will actually seem like I'm really on the level with a lot of people around the globe.
So, it was last New Year's, so I was with Digi and Ben, and they were all like,
oh man, DeVoo, you want to go and watch the ball drop?
And I was like, yeah, yeah. I always heard of the ball being dropped.
I vaguely understood what it was, and they were like, wait, you've never seen the ball get dropped?
And I was like, yeah, man, I'm living in a different time zone my whole life.
There's never been a reason to watch the ball drop, to which these two East Coast for Life boys were like,
you're right! Holy shit!
Never even fucking considered that.
So yeah, I've never even knew what the ball drop was, because to everyone who watches the ball drop,
it's so ubiquitous and culturally understood, they never bothered to explain it.
I just hear something about someone's balls dropping, and I'm like, well, I guess it's worth watching.
It's just weirdly, yeah, when you told me about that, I was like, of course it's an East Coast thing.
That makes perfect sense, but everyone lives on the East Coast!
Because it's from New York. It's based in New York, and all the channels cover it and stuff.
But yeah, I never even considered the fact that it literally only makes sense
if you live on the East Coast of the United States, or a certain part of Canada.
I remember, I think, maybe two years ago, I had done my New Year's celebration.
I watched the fireworks over Big Ben, and that's the London thing.
They don't drop any balls, they just have a big fireworks display in the middle of London,
and it's on TV, and we watch that.
And then five or six hours later, I'm still awake, got a lot of alcohol, just happy and stuff.
And then I see you in the chat, you guys are like, oh, yeah, happy New Year, and I'm like, yeah, fuck you, I win.
I'm indeed.
Incidentally, everybody start gearing up for August 4th, National Clown Day,
which as everyone knows is the Saturday during International Clown Week!
Wow.
Alright, I'm sorry, go on.
Dude, how do you feel that your birthday is 808 today?
Like, that's pretty cool, right?
Oh, yeah, 808, 808, 808, 808, 808.
Dude, also, I have another holiday to close.
I've said this before.
On August 8th of this year, it's sneak some zucchini onto your neighbor's porch day.
What the fuck?
Yeah, okay, go on.
Is that for real, or are you dropping new ones?
It is on the screen, I'm looking at.
Sneak a zucchini onto your neighbor's porch day.
Indeed, that's correct.
What if I don't have a neighbor or a porch or a zucchini?
Or the ability to sneak.
I'm like stuck on that one.
I'm like, I need some fucking explanation for that one.
Well, that's just, I mean, they're all memes, but some of them are more real than others.
That one, I was making my own videos.
That one clearly just some guy thought of it would be fucking random.
It's probably a fucking meme from an adult film show or something.
It's like a tagline for this day, which is, now that's nasty.
That's like, that's like the best phrase.
Was that a fucking family guy?
Yeah, I just feel like.
I have no idea.
Anyway, back when I was making my own videos and was all into reviewing and stuff,
I felt that October 10th should have been National Reviewers Day,
because the date you write down is 10, 10.
10 out of 10, the best score you can give.
Oh, I like that.
So like maybe on 10, 10, you review either something that you consider to be a 10 out of 10,
or you review Ben 10.
Sneak a zucchini.
Sneak a zucchini under your neighbor's porch day is 8, 8.
It is my birthday.
Yeah.
What in the fuck?
Well, everybody.
That's your birthday too.
Well, everybody, if you want to sneak some zucchinis on my birthday, let's make that a thing.
I just get caught.
You die.
Celebrate Digi Bro's birthday by fucking leaving zucchinis on people's zucchinis.
What the fuck?
I think my last holiday-based proposal, and this one is entirely self-interested,
is to, there's going to be a caveat here.
There'll be a way to make up for this.
Eliminate all three-day weekends.
Hold on.
And then just make everyone take all of Shark Week off.
Because I hate three-day weekends.
Usually it's because I was counting on doing something when the store's open again on Monday,
but oh shit, one of the like five dozen three-day weekends hit me up the ass.
Now I got to wait another day to get it.
I can never be prepared for it, you know?
Like, a dude fucking found an entire pair of continents, and we have to celebrate by not working,
be more like Columbus himself, and actually get off your ass and do something.
Don't take the day off, bullshit.
Take just the week of Shark Week off, and just absorb yourself into the sharks,
and don't work for a week, and then that will be so much more simple and easy to keep track of for me.
There's some logic to that.
Okay, condensing all the time up to a week.
Okay, I'm still stuck on this Zucchini thing, but this website that I was reading about it on
is a website called National Day Calendar.
And each day, it tells you what the next day's holidays are going to be,
like what all the national whatever days are going to be for the next day.
So posted on August 7th this year was the August 8th list of holidays.
So there was National Sneaks from Zucchini into your neighbor's porch day,
National Happiness Happens Day,
National Dollar Day, and National Frozen Custard Day.
Now I'm going to read you there right up on one of these for National Dollar Day, because it's short.
So okay, National Dollar Day.
August 8th commemorates today, Congress established the U.S. monetary system in 1786.
It's National Dollar Day.
The first U.S. dollar bill wasn't printed until 1862, and it didn't bear the image of George Washington either.
Sam and P. Chase, President Lincoln's Secretary of Treasury, was featured on the first greenback.
How to observe, so they have sections in this.
First they tell you what it is, then they tell you how to observe, then they tell you the history.
How to observe, spend or save a dollar, depending on your preference.
Use hashtag National Dollar Day to post on social media.
Here's the important part, history.
Within our research, we were unable to identify the creator of National Dollar Day.
However, the origins are clearly related to the establishment of the U.S. monetary system.
I imagine it was spawned from the womb of the invisible hand of the market.
A few scrolls down at the bottom of National Frozen Custard Day, history.
Within our research, we are unable to find the creator of National Frozen Custard Day.
They probably made these up themselves.
A couple of them.
The zucchini one's history is that Tom Roy at WellCat.com created this zucchini holiday while doing years of news and talk radio.
Can we all just read off the holidays that correspond to our birthdays?
I got eight, but I'll just blow through them real fast.
We got St. James the Great Day, Children's Day, Spring and Labor Day holiday,
while Pergis Night...
Well, Pergis from Fates Day Night, not Fates Day Night, but Bible Black.
No!
Madoka Magica had Well Pergis Night as the big final boss that kills everybody.
Really?
I don't like this first and better because there was lots of chicks with dicks.
Then we got State Holiday.
Also, Children's Day is a major Japanese holiday.
I don't know if that's the same one.
Because of all them lollicons, if you know what I'm saying.
Dude, then we have the Taiwanese God of Medicine's birthday, Education Day in the Congo Democratic Republic,
Carnival Day, Showa Days for Japan, International Jazz Day and Liberation Slash Reunification Day in Vietnam.
Holy shit, you're right.
Incidentally, when Hitler was killed, April 30th, Fall of Saigon, April 30th, my birthday,
and when Osama bin Laden was killed, I think it was April 30th somewhere.
Basically, a lot of fucking conflicts end when I show up, which is kind of inaccurate.
Well, hey, I pulled up mine. Let's see, July 1st is my birthday.
It is Build a Scarecrow Day.
It is Canada Day slash Dominion Day.
Dominion Day?
Dominion Day.
That's like...
It's DA Space Minion Day.
It is Creative Ice Cream Flavors Day.
International Chicken Wing Day and most appropriate...
That's not bad. Most appropriate to my birth, International Joke Day.
You got really good ones. I got really shitty, boring ones.
You got Hitler's birthday or something. That's not bad.
No, his birthday is April 20th, actually, but his death day is 30th.
Okay, okay. Well, there you go. That's mine. Anybody else want to read theirs?
I'll go. Oh, no, Hitler, you go first.
No, I was just going to say I don't know whether I could even find it,
because if I type in National Holidays, it comes up with like...
Just type your birthday and holiday stuff.
Here, I'll link you in the chat. This is what I'm using. It's just like a list of...
I mean, it's going to be all American things, though.
Oh, that is true.
I was trying to find whether there's like a list of English ones.
Is this like a Wikipedia thing for it, I think? Like, days of the stuff that...
I mean, Tom could do it if he wants, though.
Yeah, I got mine pulled up. All right, so my birthday is November 8th.
So the holidays are iPod day.
What the fuck?
What the shit, dude? That's terrible.
Okay, all right.
Pythagorean Theorem Appreciation Day.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I like all the better ones than me.
Wall carpet day.
Wall carpet? The fuck.
Yeah, that's what it says.
Okay.
Silence support the value of life day.
You mean...
Wait, like a pro life?
Is that science supports the value of life?
I don't know.
If that's a pro life, damn.
But here's the best one, and the one that I feel I've been horribly negligent in celebrating.
Spontaneous elevator sex day.
Not bad.
I know what I'm doing next year, for sure.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Damn.
Wait, like, can they...
Are they allowed to encourage that?
Look, I don't know, but I'm just gonna...
It's like, it's my birthday.
You know what else it is today.
That's not a good pickup line.
Okay.
Did you know it's spontaneous sex, elevator sex day?
That's amazing.
Oh, my God.
And they're trapped in the elevator.
They can't leave.
They're definitely finding a way to celebrate that holiday.
That's the great...
Okay.
I know I could make that happen.
I got stuck on the wall carpet one.
Wall carpet day?
I don't know what the fuck a wall carpet is.
And when I go on the floor, you fools.
What the fuck?
Is it if you want to do a epic prank and even somebody that they're a Spider-Man?
I typed wall carpet into Google, and all I've gotten is wall-to-wall carpets.
Like, not anything about a carpet on the wall.
And then I searched wall carpet day, and instead I got National Lumpy Rug Day.
Lumpy Rug Day.
I mean, you can hang a rug on the wall, theoretically.
Is that what this is?
I don't know.
I'm lost.
Okay.
Hold on.
This is on a...
Okay.
First of all, this is an entire website dedicated to noise cancellation.
It's called acousticsfirst.com, materials to control sound and eliminate noise.
Man.
I can see why you're such a product reviewer, Tom.
You're based on iPods and sound insulation.
Yeah.
It says acoustic myths and realities, carpet on the wall.
In the disco days of the late 1970s, floor carpet was often used in studios as acoustic wall treatment.
But I guess it's not actually good.
And so they're talking about...
The gist of this article is that wall carpet's not a good idea, as a sound canceling.
Okay.
Sorry, I got really sucked into wall carpet day.
Digi, did you want to read...
Were there more of yours?
Did we already go through all the answers?
You went through the important ones.
I mean, I got mine, but it's not that interesting.
It's Meteor Watch Day.
Meteor Watch Day, okay.
Oh, that's where everyone sits.
You go to the park, and you look for the big girls, the meteor girls, and you're like,
Yeah.
Okay.
Isn't it true that we can predict when meteors will actually be visible?
So shouldn't Meteor Watch Day just be whatever day has meteors?
Like, every time there's a meteor that people are talking about, I'm going to hear about it on Twitter.
That is Meteor Watch Day.
It's the day when Twitter's like, hey, a meteor's coming close to Earth today.
You should look out for it, you know?
With a little luck, you can see a meteor just about any night of the year, apparently.
Okay.
That's what it says, but I don't get it.
A little luck?
You'd better live in a fucking Alaska.
Wait, what day is your birthday again?
30th of June.
That's right.
So...
Thanks for doxing me, Nate.
Oh, no.
Yeah, the only thing on here is Meteor Day for that on the website I'm looking at.
Right.
Who else needs to...
Wait, is that everyone?
Yeah, I think that's everyone.
That's everyone.
I'm trying to think of real holidays again.
How very interesting.
We haven't talked about Halloween yet.
That's true.
I'm going to come out and be the guy who doesn't like Halloween at all.
Not terribly into it, no.
Okay, the dressing up aspect, I kind of get, but if somebody goes to conventions, I don't
feel like I have to wait for a holiday to do that.
And all the outfits are the same shit.
Everybody just goes and does the same fucking Halloween outfits.
The thing...
I've never been to a Halloween party personally, but...
I lost my virginity at a Halloween party, so I will always be grateful to Halloween.
Go listen to the How I Lost My Virginity episode of the PCP if you want to hear that story.
But guys, you're not fucking cool unless you lose your virginity on Spontaneous Elevator
Sex Day.
You're right.
It's Spontaneous Reversal.
Do not ask permission.
It's got to be spontaneous.
During...
When you celebrate that holiday, how many fucking references to a shaft do you think are made?
Holy shit.
Oh my god, this isn't the only shaft you're writing.
Halloween is...
It is very...
Like I said earlier, it's good for kids.
Kids, it's great for making funny little costumes and, you know, trick or treating.
But everything else, like the going out to a party...
First of all, October's cold and parties happen at night.
So, and getting in a costume may or may not cover you up well enough.
That's part of the point, is that the girls go out in the slutty outfits and they're cold
and so they need men to keep them warm.
That's why men go to the parties is to fuck all the slutty...
Dressed as the fucking wolf, man.
I mean, yeah, that's definitely the idea.
Yeah.
They're definitely hook-up parties.
I've never been to a Halloween party like that.
I don't know, maybe I'd like it, but in general, I don't care.
I don't like the kids coming to the door.
I used to pretend to...
I used to be tasked with standing near the door or being the guy who goes to the door
and hands the bowl to the kids and say, here's your fucking stuff.
Let me take a step back on this Halloween thing,
because I think there's really two different Halloween holidays.
There's the normy, widely accepted Halloween, which is the combination...
If you're adult, it means you go to a party.
I don't care for that.
And if you're a kid, it means you go trick-or-treating, which was fun when I was a kid.
I'm too old for it, so I'm not gonna do it anymore.
I'm okay with that Halloween.
The Halloween that bores me and that I'm not interested in is the nerd Halloween,
which is where every single year, everybody who likes horror at all,
transforms their internet presence into nothing but horror themed shit for an entire month.
And as somebody who's not into horror or its aesthetic at all,
every October, I'm just like, oh, here we go.
I'm gonna hear about all the horror classics again.
I agree with that a lot, especially...
It's really a very mild annoyance, but it is still annoying,
just to see absolutely everyone from October 1st change their Twitter avatar and name,
so they don't know who anyone is.
Let's talk about this real quick, because give you right now,
it is Christmas time and you have a Halloween avatar
that inspired the greatest webcomic ever created,
Pumpk and the Gang, or whatever it was called.
Bail Jape.
I drew that Pumpkin Girl during October,
and I just thought, that's a cool face.
I'll put it in my profile picture, but Halloween had ended,
and I thought, wouldn't it be funny to just do the wrong thing all the time?
So I'm gonna try and keep this tradition going.
I'm going to be Halloween during Christmas,
and I'm gonna be Christmas during something else.
April Fool's or something, I don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna change my name when people have changed it back.
Oh man, we definitely gotta talk about Valentine's Day as well.
I think the frustration that Digi expressed towards the Super Halloween nerds
is something that if you are a person who likes to watch lots of reviews and analyses,
you can relate to people like James Rolfe.
Halloween is legitimately his religion.
He's as fanatical for Halloween as anybody's parents are for God.
It's fucking nuts.
Remember that fucking guy?
Most of you have listened to the biggest problem in the universe.
Remember that fucking guy they had on Two Years in a Row,
who was like the Halloween guy,
who was very seriously, legitimately trying to argue
that Halloween needs to be recognized as a national holiday.
But his reasoning is because it's cool.
He had no real reason, but he was very passionate
that this needed to be a real national holiday.
I'm just like, what is wrong with you, dude?
I think what should be is it should be that Halloween,
the day after you should have the day off,
because everybody does shit all night, especially kids.
They gotta go to school the next day and they've been up all night out doing bullshit.
That's lame.
Eating syringe filled candy and whatnot.
They're tuckered out.
Halloween should either, the next day,
November 1st should be a day off,
or Halloween should be rescheduled to be the last Friday of October,
so nobody gets fucked over.
I think Halloween kind of keeps its punk edge, though,
by the fact that choosing to celebrate it
is sort of choosing against your other responsibilities.
There's something to that.
It's unrecognizedness from the government keeps it punk.
When I was a little kid, I definitely liked Halloween more,
because my mom was a big Halloween decorator.
We had tons of Halloween shit,
so she would cover the house in scary spooky crap.
There was this pop-out calendar thing,
where it was basically like a big spooky mansion,
and it had a bunch of doors with numbers on them.
Every day, you would open one of the doors,
and there'd be a monster inside.
It's sort of a game where every day you have to open another door on this thing.
I think the moment I realized I was too old for Halloween
was when I was not excited to open the doors.
On the Halloween calendar, it already works.
I'd seen all the monsters so many times,
and I don't fucking care.
No more trick-or-treating for me.
Just eating my brother's candy from now on.
How do you feel about these...
You see, high schoolers are even older.
Guys like ironically trick-or-treating.
I've seen that. I did this a little bit in high school.
I think I probably did it a little bit when I was 14,
because I was going out with my little brothers anyway.
I was like 17.
I was living large and in charge, man.
But I'm done with that life.
We used to get...
One of the first trick-or-treaters you'd get every night
would be a 17-year-old kid
with just a little bit of football face paint on,
and they'd just be wearing their football jersey,
and they'd be like,
I'm like a ghost football player.
Fuck off.
My mom would chew those kids out.
I legitimately did the whole homeless guy thing at least once,
because I was just really lazy.
I think if you're going to give out candy,
you should always have a second bowl of bullshit
for people who suck.
Hey, not bad. Not bad.
You should be able to differentiate
between good and bad trick-or-treaters,
because there is a difference.
You just give licorice to all the shit ones,
and then like...
True.
Re-seize to all the good kids.
This year we did not...
So I live in my own place now.
The reason we stopped celebrating Halloween
not only was because we moved into a house
that was too big for all the decorations.
My mom tried to Halloween that front yard.
You guys know what my front yard looked like.
It's fucking huge.
She tried to decorate it,
but there just wasn't enough stuff
to make it look cohesive or scary.
So she just kind of gave up.
We also never once got a trick-or-treater
in the nine years we lived there.
Because you're on a fucking highway.
Yeah, exactly.
No one's going to bring their kids along.
So when we moved in my new place,
I was like,
oh, we might get trick-or-treaters,
but they gave us these little signs
that they're like,
you have to put this sign on the door
to indicate that kids can come to your house
or else they won't.
And we just didn't end up putting it on
during those out.
We bought a bag of just re-seasoned kit-cats,
because I was like,
I'm going to be the best house on the block.
I'm only going to give re-seasoned kit-cats
the only two candies that actually matter at all.
If I go out on Christmas or Halloween,
I will throw out all the rest of the candy
for my brothers.
I just want the re-seasoned kit-cats.
The only really good candy.
And those flavored Tootsie rolls,
the lime ones or whatever.
I remember so vividly one day trick-or-treating.
This is like my greatest memory.
Starburst is great too,
but I got a full-size three musketeers bar.
A full-size!
Hell yeah.
It was unbelievable.
It was the greatest day of my life.
That's the greatest thing ever.
When you get the full-size,
you're just like, holy shit.
It was so decorative.
I remember this really cool memory
of childhood Halloween time
where we went trick-or-treating and stuff
and we got all the candy,
but then we brought it into the living room
and Dad had a cassette of the Monster Mash playing.
And we were like the three of us,
me and my two brothers.
Something about your dad being there
listening to the Monster Mash sounds inherently hilarious.
It's very easy to imagine.
It goes down listening to Monster Mash.
Just kind of gyrating a little bit.
You just reminded me that we had a horror CD
that my mom would put on and blast out of the house.
It was like all these horror-themed songs,
but we'd have the window open and be blasting this
so when kids came by, they'd hear the spooky music.
But it was all songs like Monster Mash.
These retarded-ass 50 songs that aren't even scary.
And that was just this memory of that being on in the background.
And we had this big pile of candy and sweets and stuff.
We put it all in the middle.
And then me and my brothers diverted up
based on how good our costumes were.
We argued with it, but it was basically like
the bulk of the evening was us deciding who would get what.
And if there was four of something,
we had to decide who would get the extra one.
And it was a nice memory.
I do remember loving Trick or Treating.
I loved making costumes.
I didn't make a lot, but I remember my favorite one
was kind of like at the end of when I was starting to get too old for it,
where I made a paper mache Ichigo...
Kurosaki? Oh my god.
Yeah, Ichigo Kurosaki Bankai Hollow Mask.
And I painted it with the things.
Hell yeah. The Vizard Mask.
Yeah, the Vizard Mask.
I got like a little plastic katana,
and I painted it black with poster paint.
And I walked around and I was so cool.
I was the coolest kid, except I wasn't.
But it was so fun.
Shit, there's a term in Bleach for like...
It's called like a flash step, only in Japanese,
where you can like...
It's like their teleport equivalent.
I bet you were just flash stepping everywhere from house to house
at light fucking speed using that Bankai.
Oh, I was.
Incredible.
Yo, are you gonna like turn the subject to like April Fools or some such?
I was gonna go to Valentine's Day next.
I wanted to talk about Valentine's Day.
Oh, so many I forgot about.
Valentine's Day is a fascinating holiday to me.
You know, I kind of like Valentine's Day.
And I like, like conceptually, I think it's a good idea.
I like that there's some holidays that are not for everybody.
Yeah, it's interesting.
And everybody who like...
There's always like the singles awareness day
and all that shit on holiday on Valentine's Day,
which I don't...
I feel like that is people trying to co-op someone.
Like, look, Valentine's Day is just not for single people.
Like, you don't have to like make it about yourself.
You don't have to like make a big show.
Oh, everybody else is in a relationship and I'm depressed about it.
Like, just don't celebrate it.
Just ignore it.
It's one thing for it to be a holiday for not for them.
Like, we don't celebrate, I don't know, Scottish holidays.
But the same thing is that there's not like tons of Scottish merchandise
in the stores all over the place.
It's true for ages.
Yeah, it does kind of shine in your face.
I don't think Valentine's Day isn't like that.
Like, it's not nearly as bad as Christmas.
There's not like music for it.
I mean, online.
It's hard to like forget that it happened.
Yeah, if you're just like going to Amazon to buy something,
you're gonna know it's Valentine's Day.
I mean, I know that the...
Like, I like the Valentine's Day, like, even as a single person.
Like, I like it as this just general celebration of like love.
Like, I love when everyone does the waifu like cake,
where like anime fans will always like take a picture of them
like with a real cake in front of their monitor and their waifu on it.
And I fucking love that.
And I did...
So one year on my anime blog, it was Valentine's Day.
Everybody was making their Valentine's post,
bunch of people with cake and their waifu.
Everyone's just making waifu jokes.
So I wanted to do that.
Jokes, he says.
And I had my waifu pillow of...
What's her name from Senkoku Basura, Uesubi Kenshin.
Oh yes, my waifu.
What's her name?
She literally wasn't my waifu.
I just had this random pillow, because it was like cheap,
and it came with a magazine.
And I just wanted to own one.
So I had this dakimakura,
and I took a picture of like me like,
like hugging the dakimakura,
making this like wild and crazy face.
But like, I also wanted there to be the food element.
Like, I'm sharing a meal with her, but I didn't have any cake.
So I just made myself this enormous egg salad sandwich.
It's just this photo.
I'm gonna find it for you guys.
There's a photo of me like, making this like crazy face,
hugging a hug pillow, and holding a gigantic egg salad sandwich.
And it's like, happy Valentine's Day from me and my waifu.
It's fucking great.
There really should be a holiday that involves eating egg salad, by the way.
And this, by the way, is me when I'm like 17.
So like, I look terrible in this picture as well.
I gotta find it though.
You know, what would make Valentine's Day like,
not depressing for so many people?
If part of the holiday was, you're expected and encouraged to
like confess love to whoever it is, and it's not weird.
It's like, it is not weird.
That's part of the holiday.
It is not weird, no matter what.
That is technically a big part of Valentine's Day,
especially in Japan.
It's like the confession, like giving people chocolate
and like confessing that you have feelings for them.
But it not being weird.
I don't know how you can beat that demon.
It's impossible, but it would make it like not a problem
if it was just a normal for people to say that
and to get it out of their system.
Because a lot of the time it just reminds them of it
and they feel like they can't say and it's just bad.
Like I never used to like it.
I don't think about it too much now.
And in fact, the large amount of people who constantly like
poo poo it every year makes me like it more
because I don't like being with the crowd on that.
That's stupid.
I don't want to wallow.
And what do you think about this thing?
It's kind of what Digi was saying before
about co-opting it for people who don't really deserve it.
Like when you're a kid and they make you give like
cards to like literally everyone
instead of just like one person or something.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, that's kind of bullshit.
I hate like fucking thank you cards for birthday shit.
It's like I don't...
Chew chew chew.
We should not do people the disservice
of making people think that they are cared about
if they are in fact undeserving
of people liking them or caring about them
because then they won't improve themselves
and you know, fuck that.
They should know that they're worthless
if they are worthless so that they can one day not be worthless.
It says be mine and it has a picture of a bee on it.
Yeah, I don't like cards
because I don't feel like they're really expressing anything.
You just picked it.
You didn't make it.
Ever since I was a kid I've always been like...
These don't make cards a lot.
Yeah, I wanted to make cards but then I just...
I just feel like holidays in general
they're meant to relax after work
and I've never in my life felt like
I've gotten enough work done to deserve it
so that's why I'm having a problem with holidays right now.
You know what?
Actually, this is a thing about holidays in general.
My favorite thing to do on holidays
and I kind of feel this on like...
For example, my favorite day to exercise is on Friday
because everybody takes Friday off
and there's a lazy piece of shit
and so when I'm in there I get to feel so superior
to everyone who's not in the gym on Friday.
And similarly, my favorite day to like go for a run
or workout is like on Christmas Day
or something like that.
I feel so superior to all those waste space out there
who are not grinding away this day.
Oh, it's the best. It's the best.
It's my favorite.
It's my favorite day to do work on Christmas
and holidays when everyone else is lazing around.
Okay, unfortunately I couldn't find the picture
with the egg salad sandwich.
I did find a very similar picture of me
with my waifu pillow that is missing the sandwich
but let me read you the...
Maybe she ate it.
I do have, because unfortunately the post I made
was on an old website where all the images are broken
but I still have the text from it.
It says in line with the otaku tradition
of sharing a nice Valentine's Day confection with your waifu,
here you can see myself and waifu Uesugi Kenshin
munching down on my special God's Left Nut Sandwich.
It's got turkey, ham, and roast beef
between an egg salad spread
made from mayonnaise, mustard, Texas peat, hot sauce,
one boiled egg, salt, pepper, and garlic.
All on two gigantic whole wheat sandwich bread slices.
Damn good eating.
So a happy Valentine's Day to everyone,
whether you're celebrating it with your waifu or all alone.
Watching people get senselessly murdered out of spite.
Because I'd also written a post that day about...
Because Valentine's Day is named after a massacre.
Like, it's from the Saint Valentine's Day.
I thought he drew the snakes out of Ireland or something.
Isn't that...
Well, here, let me read you this Patrick.
Let me read you the intro.
That's right.
I made a post called Saint Valentine's Day
and Five Senseless Anime Murders.
It says, you've heard it before, no one's really sure
about the origins of Saint Valentine's Day.
Historians have only found traces of various stories
wherein someone named Saint Valentine
always gets horribly murdered by the end.
And your candy hearts are stained red with this blood.
So then I made a video about, like,
my top five anime massacre scenes,
and that was my Valentine's Day post.
Word.
The Otaku audience would appreciate that, I think.
Oh, yeah.
Go check it out.
If you want to read posts I wrote almost a decade ago.
But yeah, Valentine's Day is an okay.
It's an okay boy.
I mean, I'm the kind of cuck who will buy,
like, lots of shit for a woman anyways, so...
Yeah, I like all these things.
You know, that's the thing.
I actually hate the violence that is imposed upon me
by society of forcing me to buy gifts.
You should have seen me buying gifts this Christmas.
Oh my god, it was fucking agony.
I hate spending money on these fucking assholes.
Like, the people in my life who know that I care about them,
they know that I care about them.
I don't want to be fucking tricked into buying people gifts.
Hey, I just love how you described, like,
the cultural obligation to give gifts as violence.
Who are you, Stefan Malanu?
I know, right?
I'm exaggerating, but still.
Interesting point you bring up there, Nate,
because, like, I think one of the things I like about holidays
is that, and I think this is what a lot of people like about it,
is it gives you an excuse to give people presents,
because most people are not thoughtful.
Like, most people will not buy their friends and family shit.
And, like, in many ways,
I do think the holiday is part of the problem,
because it gives you an excuse to not be thoughtful.
It's like, well, I'll buy something for him on Christmas,
but, like, every other day of the year,
you never think about that person.
But, like, sometimes you meet those people,
those legitimately great people who just, like,
buy you things because they saw it
and thought you would like it.
What are the best gifts for spontaneous
and at some point randomly in the year?
Spontaneity and thoughtfulness
are the cornerstones of any good gift, obviously.
Oh, man.
Gifts like elevator sex are best when they're spontaneous.
Exactly. Oh!
I think the funny thing about holidays is, like,
because I love giving people, yeah, those kind of spontaneous gifts,
if it's, like, the right one, which is very rare.
But on holidays, because it is so mechanical
that, like, you get somebody a gift,
I usually just, like, literally give people
exactly what, like, like,
like, I'll go shop for it with them.
You know, like, I don't care if it's a surprise.
Like, I'm gonna spend a hundred plus dollars on you
for Christmas.
It might as well be something you really want, you know?
So, like, let's make sure it's something good.
The ideogation does make it much more difficult
and less personal and just less special.
Yeah, exactly.
Like, I bought, this was the worst thing
I've ever done in my life.
I had to buy my sister's boyfriend a gift,
and I bought him some fucking mustache wax.
I've never met the man. I know nothing of this man.
And I had to buy him a Christmas...
I had to buy him a fucking Christmas gift.
That feels, like, dirty.
I feel gross that I had to do that.
Like, something has gone wrong
along this system that forces me to buy someone
who I have no fucking connection to
whatsoever a goddamn Christmas gift.
Something is wrong.
You got it, you got it.
I was bullied.
I developed an amazing technique for gift giving,
and I think a bunch of you
have been given this gift from me as well,
and you will continue to be done so.
In fact, you'll probably get this on the 26th,
because a couple of you I'm going to be meeting
right after Christmas.
Is it dinner?
My gift is always I will buy you food,
because, like, I love eating out with people,
I love buying people food,
I will just cover everyone's checks on Christmas,
and that's my gift, you know?
That is an amazing, yeah, you gave me that for my birthday
at Walker House fucking A.
Yeah, great, you know?
I love just buying people food
and being like, there you go.
That's not a very thoughtful gift, though.
It's not thoughtful,
but everyone will be happy with it.
And it's very me.
It's something that comes from my personality.
It's my problem with most holidays
is that they're so cookie cutter,
I just don't feel like I'm being creative,
and it just feels stupid.
The best thing that ever happened
to Christmas for me as an adult,
because as a kid, we got game consoles
every year, you know, whatever,
and it was like video games and anime DVDs,
whatever, we're old now, right?
The best thing that ever happened is that
my dad, because he used to be my dad
would always ask us, like, what do you want for Christmas,
all that shit, and then when we went back
to doing traditional Christmas, he was like,
I'm not asking anybody what they want anymore,
I'm just gonna buy you guys shit.
Like, I am just gonna show up with a bunch of shit
that none of you know what it is,
and weirdly enough,
my dad is amazing at giving gifts.
My dad is the one responsible for my robe.
My dad's the one responsible for my
giant coat that's in the
fat and dangerous video.
The iconic coat, the iconic robe.
He's responsible for buying me
silk pajamas
and slippers
to wear around the house,
which I didn't use to do, but after he bought
them for me, I realized I loved them.
So a lot of my image has been crafted
by Christmas gifts my dad has given me,
because he knows how
to find stuff that he knows I will wear.
And I look at it and I go, oh,
fuck, you're a genius.
Granted, that's only half of the stuff.
The other half is like, he tried to buy me
like a home brewing kit, that was
a total waste of money.
He bought me a rice maker, I ended up giving to shade,
so it doesn't always work, but you know.
Sure, but it's a net positive,
clearly. That is
absolutely the downside
of a cutthroat capitalist family
like mine is, where like,
my dad specifically,
sorry dad, but I blame you for this,
he will just ask me, just tell
me what you want, I'll buy it.
And so what he doesn't realize he's doing there
is he's putting literally all the work
on me to like, figure out exactly
what to buy.
I consider a good gift is to
do the work for, show you care,
go out and get me something, like put in the
it's your job to do this.
What we used to do is my dad would give us
my dad would always tell us like
you have $500 for Christmas.
So like, you know, figure out what you want
but go up to $500.
And so I would sit there for like an entire day
granted I love doing this, but I would sit there
on like Amazon all day like crunching
numbers, like trying to figure out
what combination of things that I
most want will equate to $500.
I feel a little hypocritical on it
because in some ways like you're saying
it is good, like I can get exactly
the things I want doing it, but like there is
a bit of magic that's lost in the
little there. It's just better when it's
fucking spontaneous. Now stop me if I've
set this story on the BZB before
but it's the best thing that was ever
given to me and it was how
I got my computer, the one
for editing. Basically I was beginning
my video, YouTubeing career
and the first step was to buy a microphone
so I got all the shit, got the interface
and I plugged it into my computer at the time
and it didn't work. There was like a driver
issue. Now I could have like, you know, gone
downstairs to record it in the computer in
but like, I'm way too much of a teenager
for that shit. I don't want to record
when everyone's around. I would die. So I spent
a straight week trying to figure out how to fix
the drivers and there was finally the nuclear
option one night. I'm like, alright, I'm going to push
this nuclear option and see if it fries my computer
or fixes the problem. Woke up the next
day, fried my computer. So I'm like
ah, so I walk downstairs
all like just defeated, just sort of
like in a serenity, like a Jesse
level of defeat at this point, right?
I walk downstairs
and my dad's in the kitchen
and I'm in the kitchen and
I tell my dad what's been going on, you know
how like my entire week has just been
like go to work, you know, do the business
the window cleaning business with my dad, come
home, try to fix the microphone problem
no progress, right? And
my dad who had just 30
minutes prior looked over
the finances for our business
for the previous month and it was
like the biggest windfall
profit month our business had ever had,
right? Super in the black
so he's like on fire right
now with excitement about the money
and I come down and talk about this and he goes
let's buy you a new computer
and I was just like, oh, it was
super cool. So like literally
we packed up and like
my dad is not very
spontaneous, like he's very like
oh, we're going to go somewhere today, like there's going to be a
fucking project to get ready to go, right?
Everything has got to be planned. So he never
does anything this all at once
and we got a new computer and just like within
three hours I had a new computer
and it was just
and then literally that evening he was like looking at more
finances and turns out it actually wasn't all that good
after all. So I was just in the perfect
fucking window, the perfect
fucking window to get a new computer. I know I've
told this before but that just reminds me of
of like me and my brother like saved
up all our pennies and allowance for like a year
so that we could buy a PlayStation 1
and we buy like that in a couple games
and then just on the way home my dad's
like you guys need a TV. Let's get you a TV
too. He just bought us a TV
and I was just such a
wonderful thing to do. Yeah, that was great.
It touches me to this fucking day. I love that TV.
I literally
love that TV.
What are the holidays have we not talked about yet?
April Fool's Day, the piece of
shit, terrible holiday. Didn't we have
a discussion about April Fool's at some point?
I think we did. I know
Hippo was on a podcast.
The same way as Hippo was with Valentine's, I'm very
fucking against people being against April Fool's.
People were being such hipsters like it's not funny
but shut up. It's a great holiday. It's a great
fucking holiday. It's overused. It's
abused. It's not a great holiday
but I don't like complaining about it. Yeah, exactly.
I don't like April Fool's
That's stupid.
I've also heard the origin of April Fool's
Day. It might be fake
but I've heard it. Who knows the origin
of April Fool's Day?
No one? Okay, so
Mr. April is a fool
and they called him that. So originally
at some point, hundreds of years ago or what
not, the beginning of the year
was April the first. Like that was New Year's
was April and so
at some point they changed it. I don't know why
and so there would be a lot of people
on April 1st who forgot about that
being like, hey, happy new year
to which they'd be like
you April Fool
you have no idea
you don't remember and they're like, oh shit
I'm an April Fool
and so I guess it just became
I really want this to be a true story
I'm an April Fool
I realize
that that makes a lot of sense because that's the beginning
of spring kind of and then
that means the year is in line with the seasons
and I like that's how Japanese school
works, right? Like their year starts
Yeah, I think so
I thought the origin was
like the Ninja Turtles were hanging out
in their sex dungeon and April
falls in and she's like
ooh took my turtle
you know
something like that
I like April Fool's a whole lot because
I think that
it used to be anyway
that was the day the internet got creative
because everyone would
it wasn't just that people did something interesting
but it was always something way different from what you're used to
the best was the web comic XKCD
which is a stick figure comic
that was really popular in the late 2000s
and
April Fool's
because he was a programmer and he would
completely re-design the site into
some kind of elaborate game
like some kind of weird like
it either be like a text adventure or
just some kind of crazy ruse
if it's done well it's great
yeah a lot of the internet would turn into that
and there were annoying parts like for instance
don't try to download any torrents that day
because it's all going to be weird shit
but sometimes it would be hilarious
like people would put out troll subs for every new anime
cause April first is like
the first day of the new season for anime
so there's always going to be some shows that come out
like the first episodes that day
and people would always make troll subs for them
probably still do and it's fucking hilarious
but um
the first time I watched Queens Blade
episode 1 was April Fool's troll sub
but like
websites would just get crazy
and there's so much stuff that
none of that can be done anymore
because too many people make their money online
and you can't change it that severely
cause like youtube
the year when rick rolling
really caught on youtube made it so
every link on the front page
took you to rick roll
like 2009 or so every link
and like that was fucking epic
as like a gag but like youtube could
never do that now cause it would ruin
people's like careers
like people would have like
fucking thousands of dollars just like
sapped away because they didn't get the click
through that day you know
and like it's just
it's sad to think
that this is just one more victim
of like the internet's
imagination you know
I've never liked
the way the
meta of April Fool's has shifted
like it did it used to be very creative
and it's not so much
I mean it is also that
people and websites
can't do that now because of money
but like creators and stuff
they used to have like creative
things that they did and
you didn't always expect everybody
to do it because it was like
you know not everybody it wasn't that huge
but now it's like
if you don't make an April Fool's video
that's the big twist
like if you make something that isn't lazy
and isn't stupid and isn't
then you're actually
I was remembering back when I was on Newgrounds
a lot because like every year there was like
they had like the McDonald's parody
for April Fool's they had Numa grounds
Poo grounds, China grounds
Kevin Bacon Day but I remember
2011 was when Tom Fulp announced on the site
guys we always go too far
with our April Fool's they're too obvious
this one is very
very subtle and I remember
thinking like wait what was the parody
because I remember like people swarming the
boards trying to figure it out
so it looked it up just now there was no joke
there was the joke that nothing
changed
yeah I love doing April Fool's videos
because I try to think
like I don't just want it to be a fake
video I want there to be some point
behind it like the year
where I did the Attack on Titan review
and it was just like all the most generic
ideas of reviews imaginable
and don't forget them when people do stuff
like that because I just I want to be kept on
my toes you know like I want
to every once in a while something shakes
it up and like because it's April Fool's
Day like it just gives
everybody a little bit of an in
like when Rick and Morty came out
and like they the new season of Rick and Morty
they just like ran the debut episode all
night long on April Fool's and like
it's such a weird shocking
thing to do but because it was April Fool's
people are like accepting it
because right no that's what they
don't forget the legendary serial
punctuation review of Duke Duke and forever
back when we thought that game would never exist like
the joke of that video
wouldn't have worked nearly
as well if there hadn't been a holiday for it
it's the same way as you know National Brownie Day
is just an excuse for everyone to have a brownie
it's an in right it's always an excuse
and comedy
relies on set ups so April Fool's
Day provides a very unique
once a year setup
that certain jokes need to survive
but but there's also
what about the fact that like every April Fool's
Day everyone's like okay
what's it gonna be this time so like there's an inherent
like anticipation there's always
there's always the joke
there's always a challenge right you always have to
the way I see it the way I see it
you gotta look at April Fool's like this
if you are gonna post something
on April Fool's Day make it a joke
if you have something you need to post that day
just save it for April
second like like like that
that day should just be like
weird joke content
and I think that because there's a lot of
people who get mad like all
it's all mistracks I just want my normal content
and I'm like dude
like people who are putting out normal content
on that day I think are like muddying it
like it should just be weird
shit all day and then like
I don't know I think that we're allowing it to
fucking take over the area for the day
I wanted to take over I want there to be
a time where everyone is just forced
to experience
weird shit all day exactly
yeah I want to stop making things
it's not really necessarily
it's not really necessarily there to
trick people although it's a sweet bonus
it's really just an excuse to be a fucky
for a day
I mean it's not
multiple things I was gonna say one
a lot of the time it's not that weird
it's just sort of bad
a lot of it's shit sure
and it just makes me feel upset
that they even spent
any seconds making this
terrible thing
what happens with all the holidays though
there's always gonna be the channels who are like
last minute oh I gotta have something
for this holiday let me throw some bullshit up
and they'll make like a 40 second
you know
April Fool and you're like I knew it was an April Fool's
video because it was 40 seconds long and it came out on
April 1st like what is the
joke here you know but like if you're gonna
go all out with it then it's worthwhile
what I would say is that
I think it could be
if you're going to post on April Fool's you should
try to make it funny even if it's short and whatever
but I don't think
you shouldn't post a real thing
but if you're going
to post a real video it should be
the most bombastically
incredible video you've ever made
and like two hours long
like a feature length film on YouTube
just so that people can be like
what? or
or you should announce
something bombastically unrealistic
on April 1st
people think that it's a joke for months
and then actually do it
that's a clever funny thing to do
yeah that's what I'm saying
it should be a day of funny clever videos
and like personally I put
more effort into my April Fool's videos
than probably any other holiday videos I've done
because every time I do try to jump on holiday bandwagon
it's always last minute because I'm not passionate
about the holidays I don't give a fuck
about Halloween
like I've made like maybe
one or two Halloween videos and it's always
like super last minute
and it just sounds like
alright let's drag out the five horror anime
that exist and talk about those again
oh somebody's going to write about Junji Ito
big fucking surprise because there's nothing else
to like tie Halloween to anime
because there's like no horror anime
out there you know and like we're all going to
be tired and wrote if we keep doing the same thing
every Halloween or every Christmas
every Christmas is going to be
we're past that well yeah we are
but like if people keep doing it
like you are officially contributing
to rote bullshit
but April Fool's Day
the floodgates are open for you to do literally
anything and like you can really
mix it up and like show people
how you can be creative outside of your format
you know and I think that's what makes it cool
well you should
like celebrate St. Patrick's Day on April Fool's
that's what you should do
that's a good idea let's
I think we've touched quite a few holidays here
I just want to say one last thing
I just realized
that is quite accurate for
like people like
like if you have
instead of making something that's just
bad or like shitty
as a joke you could just show them
some other aspect of
the stuff you do like you could
you could post a rap on the main channel
Digi or something like
as an excuse
like it's always an excuse
an excuse to show your main
people something that else
that you do very well
oh my god that is a good idea
that might be what I do on April Fool's
next year it's like just post one of my rap
like some really fucking weird
rap music video
with me like although
I don't know if that's what happened
when Bro Science made
his rap video I don't know if that was on April Fool's
or not but that did not get received
well but that's unrelated
well it's more of an excuse
than just any other day I guess
but then people are going to think that like oh yeah
this is a joke like oh it's shit
agree well if they like it
but it changes the way they're going to pursue it
okay but whatever have to have the comments
on all my raps are always like
oh my god he can actually rap
like they always expect it to be a joke
you know yeah yeah
okay guys good talk
let's go to questions
oh yeah I got a great
extremely related question
from the PCP fan
discord which you have access to
if you're a patron
procrastinator's patron lounge
patreon.com
we usually answer questions from there
vulture asks
what's your guys' new year's resolutions
didn't we answer that
literally every time for the last
like six months or so
4k
I don't I think so
4k I can never remember
4k 120 hertz
well I haven't been on if we have
I'm undecided
if my new year's resolution should be like
something I realistically know I'm going to do
or something I like hope to do
I think that's the more responsible one
it's like to set your goal high
so that you have to like really
work to reach it
I've already made my new year's resolution
and it's not a new year's resolution
because I made it earlier
so I don't have one
that's the smartest thing to do
my new year's resolution is to make
six figures this year
oh that's a good one
I've had a lot of money based
ones in the last few years
I guess my just yeah
my year resolution is to
go full time with the shit so we'll see
we'll see how that works out
Tom do you have any new year's resolutions you want to talk about
I haven't
really put too much thought into it
I was thinking probably I'm just going to make
my new year that I actually get in shape
I know it's super fucking basic
but I'm going to be 30
I feel like I can't go into my 30's
being fat
so fuck that shit
it's amazing how much you can transform yourself
physically over the span of just one year
if you're dedicated to this stuff
Tom are you going to be the first 30 year old
in the PCP is that coming
Ben right a little bit
Ben will be in April
Ben will be 30 I believe
Ben will be first
we can never go back guys
yeah we're getting old
we'll be in there
I have to do something impressive
to hit 30 because
I'm going to have a crisis
I'm going to have a mental crisis
and I might just kill myself it's very possible
it's good that you're anticipating though
it'll give you some runway to try to steer
steer it correctly
I need something really good to happen before November 8th
and I turn 30 otherwise I'm just going to be like
my whole life has just been a complete
joke
just don't kill yourself on your birthday
or the next day as those are also
my dad and girlfriend's birthdays
so
it would be a real downer
if you kill yourself
I'll give you convenience if you kill yourself
give me like a two day lead
to celebrate my family's birthdays
I'm glad that your
girlfriend's
comfort for their birthdays is more important to you
than your actual death
I'm just saying die on like the 10th
so I can grieve you not on someone's birthday
you know
like if I'm going to be in mourning
I'd rather not ruin someone else's
birthday you know
so just let me know
I'm going to make sure you don't die
alright from
I can't decide
my new year's resolution is to not be
tipped over when people do questions
I have a role to play
what's gonna happen
my resolution is really just
not eat really delicious unhealthy food
all the time just because it's offered to me
because it's only because it's offered to me
if I'm just like alone with my own devices
as I was
in Digi's house where you had to eat your own food
I just like you know as long as I could walk
to the store I would just eat healthy food
and I feel better in the body
but you know if someone's offering me chimichangas
I can't pass them up
so yeah pretty boring resolution
alright instead of a resolution
I have a new year's resolve
because it sounds cool
my new year's resolve is to have
a video on hypocrite
every single week until the end of the year
and I want them to be recorded
and done by
June
I want to do the entire year
of content in half a year
that's my goal
like so many of us have tried to do
I have succeeded in this by the way
I have made this
not the whole year like that
but I have successfully worked months ahead of myself
and I know it's doable
especially at one video a week
I think you can do it
because this man put out a video almost every day for a month
no you did do a whole month
and then a second month almost every day
with the Kirby month
well I wouldn't call it almost every day
but anyways
the next question
this one I just want to read because it's funny
it asks
if you have siblings
who is your parents' favorite son
also for Nate
where did your parents go wrong with Ben
where did they fuck up
it was right at the start
he just went down
when he came out
he's like
for my one piece of reading
comrades you'll know that I am the
Rosinante and Ben is the evil Doe Flamingo
only reverse the Chad
roles between the two
and you just got all the worst stuff was Ben
all the great stuff was me
that's all I've got to say about it
it was pure genetics
alright here's one from the gobs
what's your opinion on snow
I'm curious about this
mine has changed a lot
I like Jon Snow
I'm with Jesse from Pokemon
in saying snow, snow, I love it so
that's uh yeah
remember that one
Jesse had to eat snow
remember when Jesse was poor in that Pokemon episode
and she fantasized about when she was a kid
they would eat like snow sandwiches
and like snow desert
I remember snow sandwiches
Jesse should do a remake
of that song
no you gotta have the Kendrick Lamar
I'll never mind
anyway
so it's snowing balls outside
right now
I'm living in a park
like the exact like city
in America that gets the most snow
like that is this area
is like the shit storm
part of the world
and I gotta say
it's interesting
back where I'm from
a couple inches of snow
in Virginia Beach would shut the whole city down
and it was fun, it was great
we'd all go out and play in the snow
cause it's so rare
when you only see it once or twice a year
and you're excited about it
and you're like oh we can make snow balls
and snowmen and like Radcon 2
happened with a huge snowfall
and we made the fucking
handboy winter war
I wasn't involved with that
but you guys made a great fucking well
we had some fun
vlogs in the snow
it's a great time
and the fact that it shuts down the whole city
makes you kind of just
everybody just kind of is at home
up here in the north
nothing shuts down
and it snows constantly
like the amount of snow that we would have gotten
once or twice a year of Virginia Beach
we get almost every day
there has only been like three days in December
where I saw grass
it has been snowing consistently
and it stays for a long time
cause it's so cold that it wouldn't melt
so it took
almost a whole week
for our last major snowfall to melt
again so like
there's just always snow
and it really like
changes your lifestyle in some ways
when it's that constant
where like every time you want to use the car
you gotta clean off the car
and like if you want to leave the house
you need to be wearing snow boots
cause like your shoes will just get immediately soaked
so it's like
and you're gonna have to leave the house
cause it snows every fucking day
like you can't just be like
for like three months unless you're like
gonna clean off your car every time
and put on snow boots and
you know today I
almost wrecked my car
people have been
did you skid? did you do a swerve?
oh I did a big swerve
everyone, all of my fans
have been constantly nagging me to get winter tires
they're like dude you're gonna die
get winter tires or you'll die
and I'm like ehhh
I'm only gonna live here for one winter
I don't want to spend that like 100
however much money it costs for winter tires
for one winter
but then today was one of those insidious days
where it was like at first it was raining
but it was like an icy rain
so we go out and it's fine
but by the time we're coming back home
now the ground is all icy and it's starting to turn
into snow and everything's kind of shit
and I of course try to be slick
like I have to make a left turn into my neighborhood
and there's like
the last thing you should try to do is be slick
I made a huge mistake
because
there's a car coming from the other direction
and I have to make a left turn into my neighborhood
and I'm like
alright if I go fast I can beat that guy
you know
the rational thought would have been
come to a complete stop and let him pass and then go
but I'm like no if I'm fast I can beat that guy
so I try to go because this is what I normally do
so I try to go fast
and I immediately swerve all the way off into
the bushes
like right next to the sign from my neighborhood
almost hit a
could have hit a brick wall
could have gotten hit by that guy's car very easily
we were extremely lucky
that all I knocked over was like this wooden post
that was in the ground that nobody cares about
and so like you know I've got a little scratches
on my car I got out of there just fine
but I was like man this was lucky
and this is
clearly a warning to go get
winter tires you know
the winter has only just begun
you're gonna go all the way through March
like this
I'm just hoping like
cause I'm trying to drive to fucking Boston
on Christmas day
and like I don't know what the snow is gonna be like
that day so there's
there is some chance
there is not a terrible idea
cause you can take the train all the way to
self-station
I don't even know where a train is or how long that would be
but I could look into it cause
cause there's a chance I won't be able to go to Boston
and I'm like well I'm not
driving in that you know
sure
could be an option
hey so I'm sure Tom
had a similar experience as you grew up in the same part of the country
yep had dealt with a lot of snow growing up
it was kind of a hassle
but so while I hate
the cold
I hate cold temperatures more than anything
in the world they are paralyzing
they are counter
to life
the antithesis of everything that I wish for
in this world
I do love hanging out in snow
and then coming inside and being cozy
having escaped the winter
you know what I like doing I like skipping that whole first part
and just being cozy
no cause you gotta suffer so you can feel
the joy of being inside again
you're just a masochist
this is the same person who grinded the ultimate weapon
in Kingdom Hearts 2 you just like pain
I do
like I agree with Nate on this
like
it snowed once a few days ago
and
the rain brushed it away immediately afterwards
so it was like I gotta get out there
I gotta make something I gotta make a little snowman
and it's cold and you know and all that
and I roll up a ball
and I roll it
so that all the snow in the garden
is in the snow
and it's very big and very heavy
and I fall over it and I drop it
and I build it back up and I fall over it
and it's like I was so
like my coat was like kind of
warm like the fact that I was moving
so much and lifting big
lumps of snow all heavy it was like
getting sweaty and it was
great and then I fell
on the snow and I just
I was just warm and cold at the same time
and it feels so good to exert yourself
to a ridiculous extent
and then come in and just be like
as you pull off your winter clothes and you're free
and it's warm and it's glorious
cool down and warm up at the same time
your hands need to warm up
but your body needs to cool down
it's like weird and you don't get that very often
that is my aesthetic
I love being inside
in a warm, biofire is preferable
with a snowy outside and specifically
snowing is
peak decadence
the best temperature improvement
in my life because like as a kid
I go out into the snow and within
two seconds my ears are dying
of cold I don't know why my ears
are just really sensitive to cold and like
if I put on ear muffs or a hat
or whatnot it would just get way too sweaty
and then get cold but
when I grew my hair out when I was
13 as it remains
just the tiniest little increment
of hair draped over
the ears completely warms them and I've
never had that issue since and it's
really cool it's like yeah everyone should
grow their hair out that's why I grow
my hair and beard out during the summertime
my hair's not curly enough to do that
I'm just wearing ear muffs
Question from Jolly Bones
what is the worst type of Christmas gift
one
that I had to work really hard to get
so my parents like arranged
and my parents would just like pay for
or anyone would like pay like when I had to work really hard
someone else could like buy for me
especially if it's not that expensive
like if I had to work hard then I'm getting like
nothing out of this
what do you mean by describe what would be a hard work for a Christmas gift
I had to arrange
the delivery location
I had to find
all the logistics about how to buy this
like it was like a portable
heater or something like when I lived in my last
apartment that my parents willingly bought for me
but like I had to do all the work
to arrange everything
and it took me like days of work to like
get everything just it was just like a weird situation
happening but like I had to put in a lot of
work and all they did was like
just send a check afterward and it's like
there's a gift and yet I worked so hard
to make it happen
I hate doing that I really hate that
yeah gifts that are burdens in disguise
exactly exactly
I would rather just not have to deal with it
I think you should
never buy someone a gift under the
assumption that they are going to like
use it
like because when my dad
as I was discussing before he got me like all those
like the robe the slippers the pajamas
and also a
brewing kit and of those
the robe and slippers ended up being
something I used and so he was lucky and he was
correct there but like the silk pajamas
eh like they're not really
comfortable they're kind of weird to wear
around and then
the brewing kit was like
just so okay
better answer gifts that the person giving it
to you doesn't understand themselves
because he bought me this
home brewing kit thinking this would just be
like yeah you're going to make your own beer
but like the
shit is super complicated like you need to
have like a fucking chilled room
to store this shit in you know
like you gotta have tons of stuff
like I mean that doesn't come with
barley and like hops it's just like a big
jug and a bunch of tubes you know
by buying that he's he's he's his gift
to you is fucking homework
right and it's like wow thanks for like this
extra I mean it could have been cool it probably
would be really cool if you like did it I
I hate being given a burden yeah I
I get why he would think I'd be into that
because I love alcohol and I like you know
like homemade kind of stuff
but like I'm also lazy as shit
and like this stuff was really complicated
that would be a good gift if you expressed
interest exactly exactly I
had ever said like I want to make my own alcohol
great but like he just bought that for me and the
thing is that one of the parts
was like kind of broken and
we didn't figure that out until
like a couple days later I
thrashed the box that night
because some
dramatic stuff happened that Christmas
where one of our friends got kicked out of
our group of friends and I was
shit-faced drunk and not handling it
so I just tore up this box because it's
just a big box I can let out my rage
on so there's no way to send
it back so it's like a hundred and fifty
dollar brewing kit that never got used
and I was just
like I feel bad
but at the same time why
the fuck did you buy me this like
you know I'm sorry I tore
up the box so we can't send it back but
you should have had the foresight to know
that rather than buying me a home brewing
kit you should have just bought me a hundred fifty dollars with a beer
you know yeah
I would have loved that
in this case for sure
I have any answers I can top that so yeah
I hate gift cards
it's categorically worse than cash
just give me cash
it's better
it's more useful
like I get the fact that
people want gift cards because
they thought of you like oh I know
you like this so it feels more personal
than cash but it's just it's less
useful there's always going to be a situation where I could use
ten bucks and I have ten bucks in fake
money and it sucks
I'm curious about something what do you think will happen
when we get off of this bullshit paper
fiat currency that we're all wasting our time
with and we all go full crypto currency
what will gift exchanges
be like with that I mean will it still be like
here to have this
do you think we're ever going to be all using crypto currencies
eventually yeah
like in cowboy bebop for example everyone uses like
is that a cryptocurrency
I think it's just like a digital currency
but it's like it's very similar
we're already on digital currency for the most part
paper currency is pretty
pretty pretty pretty bold
but like once like as long as
this brings bebop to mind
I want us to name our global currency
double dollars like in tri-gun
I don't know why they were called that but it's
double dollars I think I know why
inflation got so bad
this actually we just got to double up
I remember I think what the idea behind
that was like so like the people in tri-gun
crashed on this planet and like rebuilt civilization
and some things they just fucked up and like
they read like it's like they were just people
who were like had no idea what was going on so they like
read a lot of literature and there was like a typo
somewhere of like instead of a dollar sign
there were like two dollar signs and they're like
okay I guess like where did you hear this
I've never heard this lore before
I you know I'm reaching back like more than
ten years to like fanfiction.net
yeah I don't know maybe it's coming from
my head I remember reading that somewhere
and really being certain of that but
it'd be a cool thing if it was true
I will say about gift cards that like
there is an interesting like manipulation
element that you can like force people
to spend money on things you think they need
for instance recently
recently um
and I don't think this was the intentions of this gift
but uh but um
May's mom gave her a
a $50 gift card to the grocery store
and I thought that was really
interesting like as an idea like if you had
let's say that you have a kid
who is bad with money
this is not the case with May
I don't know why her mom got her that gift card
but it made me think about this
that if you had a kid who is bad with money
and you gave them
like like a
a gift card for a place that you know they
need groceries
and like you don't want them to spend it on
heroin let's say
that would be a reason not to give
somebody cash like hey I'm not going to give
you money you could spend on just whatever you want
you have to spend this on groceries
holy shit the odds of me giving to a homeless person
just went into like from a zero to the single
digits
if you give them a gift card
do you mean? yeah
pass the gift cards to homeless people
well I mean
there's something I suppose
hey I've got a question here
I'll give them a World of Warcraft subscription
I've got a funny question here
from our pity question section
on the
twitter
using hashtag askpcp
at senjo42 asks
could you self administer
a needle
which is interesting to me
could anyone do it?
I can't even have somebody else
administer me
I have like a straight up panic attack
from that shit
it's not even the pain
it's just the concept
it's a utterly disgusting thing to me
I think with like a good old sit down
of training I probably could do it
you know I would hug
a hedgehog that was
disguised as a hedgehog
I would do that
and there would be an accident and I would be like oh wait
damn it now I'm cured of AIDS
I don't think that's how that works dude
it took so much work to get those AIDS
putting aside the whole
whether I could like find a vein
or like you know the smarts of it
I think the question is really about the like
it's really about like the pain aspect here
needles don't hurt at all
like there's
but it's the anticipation right
it's the fear
I find it so utterly disgusting
just the fact that they're like
these like vessels pumping
through you
utterly disgusting
let's get off the needles
I was going to say I like this
and also I want to tell an embarrassing story about Ben
where we both got our blood drawn at one time
and like I was sitting we were both doing it
I got it you know they injected me or something
and I was like okay that sucks but not that bad
but Ben
like when they came to the needle with him
like you guys can probably relate to this but he was like flinching
and like the biggest most like
caricature movements like
like they wouldn't even bring the needle that close
flinching is just the beginning for me
it just goes down from there
I usually cry and scream
the closer you get the more my hands turn
into fists and
the stronger I become
I find the
the active needle so disgusting
I would rather they just took a knife cut me open
and bled me out
I would be much more comfortable
with just like hacking like a big
gash in my arm
like the aesthetic of the needle
you find like disgusting
just the fact that it's like going into a vein
it's disgusting
enough needle talk let's get one last question
before we're done
from grey nine
what do you want for Christmas
I want a switch
I want a Nintendo switch
I want to play Splatoon 2
and I got to play Bayonetta
and Metroid Prime 4
and that's what I want
give me a switch
Gib left because he didn't want to hear gross talk
but that's over
we're talking about what we want for Christmas
what do you want for Christmas Gib
a needle
I want
what do I want
something
I asked for a little Meta Knight plushie
because I have a little Kirby plushie
and I want a little Meta Knight plushie
because Meta Knight is a fucking cutest little guy
I like plush things
and he's like
he's so fucking stern
yeah it's great
I asked Santa Claus
for Xenoblade Chronicles 2
for the switch
because I have very little experience
well I watched a friend play most of it
it looks like a big meme game
but it's like the first big RPG for the switch
and I love my switch more than anything
and I just want another game
so I'm gonna play that shit
I saw a bunch of like anime
just anime cutscene I've ever seen
in a video game
from that so I'm really excited to see
just how deep the rabbit hole goes
in terms of just literally being an anime
that's what I'm talking about
Davoo what do you want for Christmas
I want a stopwatch
you can use your phone for that
well here's the thing
I'm gonna explain
so I use stopwatch as the key track
of how long things take
that way I can figure out what things I'm wasting my time on
so stopwatches are vital to time efficiency
the problem is
pulling out your phone
is antithetical to time efficiency
you see the issue there
a stopwatch doesn't have
any fucking apps on it
stopwatch doesn't have twitter on it
so there you go that's why I want multiple stopwatches
you can theoretically put your phone in airplane mode
but in any case whatever works best
the holding like
like PE class
you got the stopwatch you go click
I want multiple stopwatches
I want a stopwatch for
last time since Eaton
last time since Bates
stopwatch for how long I've been in this conversation
to know when I need to wrap it up
not this podcast but like
you gotta be on the lookout
when you're in a conversation with someone
who you agree with politics on
because then it just becomes self affirmation
the game for 5 hours
eventually the amount of time it'll take you to
manage all these stopwatches
don't worry I have
a fucking alarm clock for that
I've just imagined
like DaVoo's having a
kind of annoying conversation with his dad
and he brings out that because the stopwatch is a universal thing
he knows what that is
if you bring out your phone it's like oh it's just looking on his phone
but if you bring out the stopwatch it's like oh he's timing you
DaVoo is timing you
this shit and you click it
writing this fucking face
yeah I know I've actually
you wish for the 17 seconds of my life
yeah hey well what I want for Christmas is
world peace
and I want it by way
of legal weed everywhere
yup there you go
did you know guys know that didgy bros so
smokes the weed what the fuck
I don't even care
if that becomes the meme because I
literally smoke every fucking day now
so like yeah it is actually true
like you can meme it all you want
I'm just gonna embrace it as an identity at this point
yeah it was really interesting like didgy
you mentioned like halfway through this podcast
you're like yeah I went out on the back
patio and started smoking and I was like
wait wait cigarette
yeah cause I was like he's smoking weed
I'm having a problem with this how dare you mention
you actually smoking a cigarette something that's
actually a lot worse for your health
well I guess I'm actually okay with that one
no I smoke weed indoors it's not
it's decriminalized here but you know
still keep it
still federally not good
I think
smoking weed
world peace won't come from
just having legal weed
we need it to be free
I just was going to originally say weed
the weed thing and I thought world peace
would be funnier but then I decided to say both
anyway that's it for this episode of the
procrastinators podcast right
hey hey that's correct and everybody
don't forget get your questions
answered most likely
or more likely if you head over to our patreon
and pledge as little as one dollar
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
you pledge five dollars you get access to all
our bonus episodes the new one
will be out like tomorrow I think after
this comes out so if you sign up now that
thing's coming out tomorrow so get ready for that it'll come out
on the patreon feed you'll see it there
send us questions on the twitter
hashtag askpcp for the handful that we answer
there and uh... don't forget about
com or something slash people slash the procrastinators
we got a bunch of merch it's still
there's still time to buy things for Christmas
next year if you act now
don't forget fucking guys
don't ever you dare forget about sneak a
zucchini under your neighbor's front porch
day I'll see you there
I'll need Tom's
plug as well
iTunes
and what else where are we
it's on google play
iTunes and google play for the two guys that
listen on there but hey
you guys give me twenty dollars a month
so keep listening
do we have a way to track the numbers on those
google play's numbers are
pathetically bad
but iTunes does not keep track of
numbers so I have to go into Bluehost and figure
out how to track numbers that way
so yeah we still need to figure it out but we will
I'm lazy alright well it's too much back room
shit everybody goodbye
goodbye
I'm done
sleigh bells roasting on an open
fire
snowballs
flying through the air yes
I'm recording
that's the end
myself I'm
sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a
deadline
don't want to do it