This is a podcast called The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
A variety podcast running since 2015.
We're here. Oh, let me turn that down.
We did it. It's Radcon 4 Paradise.
We have a house that we're in right now, and we're all friends.
And here we are, just experiencing that in real time.
Who are we?
Where The Pro Crastinators Podcast, individually, we are Ben Saint.
Yeah, this mic position sucks.
Sure, screw it a little closer. It's very like you and Jess basically.
Jesse, Endless Jess, Munchy J. Trump, Best Guy Ever Meet, Gibbontake.
Hello.
Digibro.
I used my special move. Get high.
Tom Oliver.
I love video games.
And we're here just to talk about whatever we feel like at today's PCP episode that we're all part of.
Now, as a part of why we're here at this house, we had a Kickstarter link in the description
so you can just look at the Kickstarter, which we have already funded.
Yeah, right.
And as a part of that, there was a reward tier where you could suggest things and talk to us
and tell us what to do at Radcon.
Be quieter, is that what you mean?
No, he's saying to move the mic arm because it's completely in your face.
Oh.
So move it just down.
I can't.
Down like so.
What?
You will be audible if picking up everything.
It's fine.
Okay, okay.
Aim it upwards at the very least.
It's barely a mic up.
No more microphones.
It's fine.
No more talking.
Why don't you go on?
So, as a part of the PTA being a thing that can suggest things to us, we asked them questions for this.
One of the questions that they asked us was, did you, bro, you said that, do you know their name?
No.
Here, I'll get their name real quick.
But they were lovely and they asked us, what?
How do you feel about the Rad content that you've made so far?
Do you want to go over what we've made so far?
Oh my God.
Well, we got in and we started making like vlogs and dumb shitposts right away, which are all great.
That's pretty much what I come to Radcon to do.
Everybody else is always like, oh, I've got a plan and I'm like, I have no plan.
I have cameras and I have you people and I'm going to make you entertaining and put it on the internet.
It's paradoxical that the big things are kind of the least important long term, the least memorable.
To a degree.
The streams are always the best.
Like a really good stream where all of us are shouting and having fun is the best time.
I mean, I think that all the big videos are great too, but like they basically exist to give like form to the Kickstarter.
Yeah, yeah.
Whereas like the real purpose of Radcon inherently is to get all of us, you know, creative people in one place and make shit.
And so it's like, on the one hand, we always try to make it so like there's certain things that we guarantee because, you know, so that we can have like a justification for the Kickstarter goals.
But we try to leave as much time as possible unaccounted for just so it's like, you know, the magic can happen.
Got to have that serendipitous content.
Yeah.
What was that first one we did about something?
Okay, sorry.
Patches from Dark Souls.
Sucking my dick, sucking my cock.
Yeah, ain't nothing.
Touching my dick.
Touching my balls.
That's what it was.
Yeah.
Pooping on a cock.
Well, yeah.
These are just the things that I say in my everyday life.
So they're all jumbling in my head.
Okay, besides all the bullshit that like sucks, we have made like a billion and a half lectures.
We have.
This will be like.
We have three so far.
And we're not done yet.
We're doing two more today.
If you count the Brad Garling House lecture.
Brad stopped by and he did one real quick.
The Brad Garling House lecture was really fucking good and I cannot wait for that.
Is it?
Do we want to reveal all the ones that we have done?
No, I'm trying to figure out how many we've done.
I think it's five.
One, two, three, two, three.
Oh, good.
Three plus Brad Garling House.
There you go.
Yeah, that's what we've got.
We have two more.
And we've got two more on deck and possibly more as well.
Wait, no, no.
It was five.
I stayed up all night writing my fucking notes and now I'm depressed and I hate you.
Well, but the point is that this is going to have like an exponential growth of lectures
from last night.
Like double one point five or two point five times.
Something like that.
Sure.
Last time we had three, right?
I did one.
You did one.
Final fantasy.
I did one.
He's a four.
Four.
No, you did one.
Yeah.
So we did five last time.
Okay, so we're going to have an exponential growth.
We're still going to have more than last time.
Five.
Yeah.
It's like picking up Munchy like twice as loud as everyone else.
Just the loudest name in the world.
Well, I did that and everyone yelled at me.
No, the problem was that it was blocking Munchy's face if we were trying to move the arm out
of his face.
That's all that matters.
Shanagins, everybody.
It's Radcon.
I love it.
Well, let's talk about, I mean, the little bit at least, we already did the big stuff,
the big ticket items as well.
The OVA and the music video.
Songs coming at you soon folks.
Those are intense.
Those are fucking intense recording days.
Yes, as they were.
Those are two days of nonstop recording.
Like consider that like when we do Radcon, we usually expect there to be like constant
live streams.
Just like, oh, well somebody will have a chance to live stream while we're doing something.
This was not the case for those two days.
It was just like ball busting.
We broke our bodies.
We were bedridden some of us.
Did he say that?
Just because you're old as fuck, you like jumped and you jumped like three times.
Tom was bedridden.
Ben was bedridden.
We all had to nap, man.
We don't have the energy.
I was just tired.
I have sort of three problems.
Sleep.
Everybody else?
Yeah, you could have like sleep issues.
You're on your own.
Yeah.
You could have a lot of issues, Ben.
I'm just fat.
Cool.
Fuck off.
Ben's just stressing out about fucking delegates for Bernie.
Yeah.
Bernie sleep.
I also am convinced I'm going to die.
Oh, because the plane, the plane right home.
The plane and the coronavirus.
Wait, are you afraid of the plane crashing?
Yes.
Okay.
So they're separate.
Yeah.
Crash into the coronavirus.
You will live the virus though.
First of all, you won't even get it.
First of all, when you do get it eventually, then you will live.
That's true.
No.
There's only like a .2 percent chance that I die.
It's like 1 in 500.
I suppose.
That's pretty good odds for the coronavirus.
You don't want to risk that.
What if I gave you a gun and I said, hey, spin this revolver.
There's 500 holes in it and only one has a boat.
Pull the trigger.
Not everyone has a random chance.
If you're old and inferred, you have a much worse chance of dying from it.
No, that's including age.
I'm already more sick of hearing about this stupid virus than I am about.
Yeah.
Hearing about Greta Thunberg and Billie Eilish combined.
Well, what if you combined Greta Thunberg and Billie Eilish?
And gave them the coronavirus phase.
Thank God.
That would be so stupid.
Well, then they combined would be so young that it would be impossible to kill.
The nation would be mourning and I would be celebrating.
Anything of note that's happened that we should let people know while we've been here?
Apparently this stream going on has once again killed our previous streak.
Well, what can you do?
What in the fucking shit?
That was the best stream of all time.
That was the most base stream in history.
Wait, is it over?
What? No.
No, no, it's fine.
The stream we did all last night.
Every time we do a stream, the previous one gets the fucking...
That means if we stream again, we will kill PCP episode 200.
Potentially, but unless we download it first.
Wait, what are you talking about?
Did the last one get deleted?
Yes.
Why?
Someone said in the chat that when this stream went live, the last stream disappeared.
Just like what happened to us last night.
Well, there's nothing we can do about that right now.
Let's see if we can solve this problem again.
We were planning to...
If anybody still has it open, download it.
Yeah.
Fuck, I forgot the name of the guy.
One guy.
He managed to save the last one.
He saved everything we did in one guy.
So I really hope we can save that one too.
What the...
I'm gonna cry.
Why is YouTube the worst?
They've served their purpose in acquiring super chats.
Let them be lost in a seed of time.
Wow, I hate you.
You don't understand.
You don't understand the clutch Yoshi's Island moments that you missed last night.
I'm sure they were really great.
Hey, we're talking...
This is unspeakably retarded and we have to stop now.
Sure.
One thing, since it's big numbers episode, you know, 00, I'm gonna be a little bit reflective
and Mr. Kuhlman, or my Kuhlman, however you prefer to be pronounced against Iranian,
asked, what has changed in the last Radcon?
And I want to add onto that, where do you guys think you will be at in your develop psychologically
by next Radcon?
Where do you think you will be?
Where's the momentum of the group going?
Depends on how long we think it will be before the next Radcon.
That was also another question that someone also asked, how long do you think the gap will be?
I mean, it's too...
Probably...
Too numerous to know.
One year or less then.
Yeah.
For the next Radcon.
Because this...
We definitely waited too long to do this one.
We shouldn't wait two years.
No.
We shouldn't wait...
I was thinking like a year to a year and a half.
I mean, the funny thing about it...
Depends on what time of the year we want to do it.
When we first started doing these, the idea was that like we...
Because we had gone to BronyCon yearly on our own dime, we figured we had between us
the money to each travel like once a year to meet up.
Yeah.
And so the idea was like, we'll just go to my house.
But then we were like, we could do this more than once a year, so let's do a Kickstarter
and then we can do it every six months because we'll pay for it once and we'll Kickstarter
at the other time.
Then we all realized that like, oh, we should only do this if we're going to Kickstarter
because why would we spend all that money on flights when we could potentially fund it
this way?
But that also means doing it more rarely as it means organizing a Kickstarter every single
time.
Yeah.
So it kind of went from like being like, we'll use the Kickstarter to do it more often to
just we'll use the Kickstarter to do it at all.
Now it's a question of how often do we want to do a Kickstarter and have to gather up for
10 whole days?
Well, see, the thing is, is that there are like smaller meetups sometimes first throughout
the year.
So I remember specifically there was a big meeting meetup.
Yes.
To get a win.
October 3.33.
Yes.
Because that was not October.
That was January.
Okay.
Last year.
Well, I mean, we are getting to the point where we are starting to like be next to another
kind of normally.
Me and Ben see each other like every fucking day.
It's a nightmare.
Tom lives nearby even though we never see him because he was crippled.
And then he won't come to furry conventions, even though we asked him to come to furry
conventions.
And he won't even respond.
It was in time to come to the furry convention.
What's fucking wrong, Tom?
What's up, dude?
Let's talk about this later.
Fuck you.
I'll kill you, Austin, right now.
Please do.
Nate, and did you're going to like gay marry or something?
I heard that in the grape farm.
It could happen.
That's the current plan to move to this very area.
That's been your plan for like four years.
Okay.
Well, here's the thing about me as opposed to everyone else.
I have plans and then eventually they all happen.
You know who else had plans?
Elizabeth Warren.
And look what happened to her.
Yeah.
She failed.
I succeed because I'm a man and a woman cannot make it in the presidency.
This is what I learned.
That's what Bernie said.
Even I voted for Jill Stein.
Hashtag Bernie was right.
I'll vote for Elizabeth Warren because I believe in the dream, but I know it can't happen.
That's my vote in my favor.
What were we talking about?
We were talking about where we're going to be by next red card.
Very likely I will live in this area.
And what has changed since the last red card?
I quit my job.
That's one big thing that happened to me.
That's a big thing.
I quit my job to become a YouTube's man.
It hasn't worked out for you.
And still going like this.
Yeah.
But I've got aspirations to make it go like this.
To at least reverse the damage.
If I could at least be neutral, that would be one thing.
I mean, you know, whatever.
The whole point of me just stopping to do a Viagra was like, well, this doesn't seem to
work in the way I hoped it would.
Time to try something else.
And I'm just going to do that as long as I can.
And then, you know, either it'll get better or not.
If I have to, as I always say, I'll get a fucking real job and just do YouTube on the
side the way I did for a very long time.
And I don't even think it'll be that much worse.
So frankly, I'm just very confident things will go just fine for me in life.
Do you foresee that it's going to happen?
Huh?
Like, do you think that you will?
I don't know.
I mean, it seems like not a ton of people actually succeed in making YouTube their career long
term.
Really?
So I'm just open to that possibility.
I mean, I don't honestly really care either way.
I have a preference, but I'll just do whatever I got to do.
And I'm going to keep making YouTube videos no matter what.
So to the audience, it should make basically no difference other than perhaps the speed
at which they come out.
So yeah, I'm just going to be here doing my shit, trying to make things better and hopefully
making money enough to do it.
If not, I'll do other shit.
That's it.
Low stakes here.
So, well God, how many years ago did I come through here?
Two years.
Just under two years.
Jesus.
Okay, so you quit your job.
Yep.
There was also me and Matthew with two.
Resounding failure.
Would you say that?
Well, I'm exaggerating a little bit, but kind of, yeah.
Okay.
You used to be here some time.
That was the one goal.
I mean, I talk about the shit a million times people know.
I just summarized it right there.
That's everything going on in my life.
Nothing else of interest.
Hippo, what's been going on?
You, like, died, I think.
Were you already dead by the time the Rack on 3 happened?
Were you already not doing epic, cool video game reviews?
And rick and mad-dosh?
No, I think I was still, yeah, that was 2018, right?
Early 2018.
Yep.
Yeah, by the October 2018, I decided no more Hippo Crit.
So, the things I recorded at Rack on 3.
GRPJ Kingdom Hearts 2.
GRPJ Kingdom Hearts 2 is not out.
I mean, we'll never be out unless I find the time and the inclination to just do it for no reason.
But yeah, like, I've switched gears from being a YouTube gamer review person because I realized,
I don't really, like, ultimately it's more of like a passing interest, I realize.
Just the fact that it is a career that people can have,
maybe think that I should pursue it as such,
but I didn't really feel that I was that into it.
So, I stopped, I went back to what I really liked,
which was at the time I was in the process of finishing Beljape.
So, I went hard on that.
Actually, I can't remember when I started Beljape.
I think it may have been around the same time,
or it could have been, like, happening throughout the whole year.
But it was not a serious thing when it first started.
Well, in the sense that it was not your fault.
No, no, it was just sort of like,
would it be fucking cool if I made something?
And then everyone responded no, and you kept adding it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just throwing balls around.
No ball games.
So then...
I did Beljape.
I think April, the following year, in 2019,
I finished it, April, May, whatever.
I tried to do a Kickstarter and that failed
for making a plushie of it,
but I was very much into doing this as a thing.
And so, I think, for the rest of 2019,
I didn't really do much, but I was planning
and crafting certain stories and stuff,
and doing, like, hundreds upon hundreds of Google Docs
with, like, world-building shit
that will eventually see the light of day
in certain, like, comic forms or whatever.
On the side of that, I have been, like,
continuing with my writing job freelance stuff
that I'm doing, which takes a long time
to get anything made.
I don't want to, I keep saying, like,
oh, we're just about to make it real,
but then it's sort of like, oh, there's a setback.
We have to do something else.
We have to change the script
or, like, get a different screen right over.
But there's significant progress coming there.
Significant progress,
but I don't want to jinx it again,
so I'm just going to not say what stage it's at at the moment.
I mean, the idea of, like, that even being your job
is, like, in a weird, mega-alternate dimension
where it kind of, like, is brought up,
where it's like, yeah, I had this job,
we're, like, doing a thing by,
and then it's kind of elaborate on that.
Once the first thing that I have my name on
as a writer of is a real thing,
then I can say, I'm a writer.
This is what I've made.
Until then, it's like, I'm dabbling in it
and dabbling in it and, you know,
if you could fall through,
it would kind of be difficult at this point.
But that's sort of the two things that are going on,
is, like, freelance writing work
and then my own personal comic hobby
in the beginning of 2020.
I started the Lord of Ghosts comic,
which initially started out as,
like, a very small idea, fan thing for Endless War,
your and Ben's thing.
We'll talk about that when it comes to that.
But, yeah, I'm just doing stuff.
Then Radcon 3 is, like, hell yeah.
I want to see my friends and be cool.
Cringe.
Yes, yes.
Big cringe, bro.
I can't count.
I don't know if this is the case,
but you have gone, like, completely different medium
of, like, artistic expression, basically.
Like, you went from, like, a video man
to a comic person.
I was always, like, an art boy at school.
Sure.
Videos, like, I got into making videos
through my little funny stuff
because I made a video on a whim
and I got great feedback.
I always thought of you as an art guy
because you drew your own stuff in the videos.
Like, you drew give and take.
So, like, from my perspective,
anybody who can draw at all
is automatically, like, an artist in my mind.
Like, I just compartmentalize you.
I mean, I don't think of video as non-artistic.
Well, I don't mean like that.
I mean, like, if you can draw,
then you have the ability to sell art in my mind.
Like, if you can draw with any competency,
then I'm like, oh, you can make money doing that,
and I can't.
So, you're an artist.
Yeah.
So, I got into video for basically just, like,
like, happy feelings.
Like, oh, I got loads of notifications,
like, some subscribers and people saying
I really like these videos.
So, that, like, propelled me forward.
But it took me a while to realize that
editing is boring, and I don't like it,
and I hate it, and it sucks,
especially when it's with video games,
because unlike, you know, a pony show or whatever,
you're, the footage you gather
is not, like, prepackaged as to what it is.
You have to film it yourself.
Yeah.
And you have to find, and the games are really long,
you have to find specific moments
if you want the footage to be correct
to what you're saying.
And it's hard being an analysis guy.
I like video games, but I don't really
care too much about analysis.
Like, I like hearing about it,
and I like thinking about it, but,
I don't know, it just wasn't really my thing.
So, you switch away from that.
Yeah.
Do you think that you will have another
major medium shift by Recon 5?
Where do you see yourself going?
I mean...
Will you finally kill yourself?
Don't take it away from you.
Everybody's got to get asked that question.
Yes.
Okay.
No, I think, I think in terms of, like,
medium shifts, I got into the drawing,
because, like, drawing and, like,
art and comics, and, like, it might not be
comics, but it will be, you know,
creating worlds.
It might, I might go harder into writing.
I might go, like...
Harder into boner?
Harder into boner.
Into, like, animation, like,
creating a world, creating characters,
doing cool, like, making of stuff.
Like, making a cartoon, like,
you know, stuff like that.
I don't, I don't imagine that I would, like,
switch and do something completely different
exclusively.
Like, I like, I have in, like,
aspirations to make, like, music,
and albums and stuff.
Yeah.
It can't be...
Sattled with one medium.
No, I like, I mean,
I don't know what I like, but I just
have a propensity to get into a lot of
things that I just, like, oh, I like that.
I want to do that.
I want to make gorillas.
I want to make, um, fucking,
uh, video games that I've seen already.
I just want to make homestuck.
I want to make things that I like and
just do it, but I did it.
Um, but I think, like,
the most, like, the thing I'm most
proficient in is drawing.
So I'll probably be doing something like that.
Yeah, forever.
Now, speaking as a fan of you,
I am very charmed by your audio, visual,
community, timing, and aesthetic.
And you obviously can draw.
And you have done animations before.
That, I mean, that's what you just school for.
Yeah.
So more hippo animations would be, like,
dude, that's the best of both worlds.
That's, like, not here.
I have been thinking of, like, doing,
like, with Red Man and Gun Girl,
just, like, really short, like,
webisodes, just, like,
you know, the Red Man comics,
where it's just Red Man saying some bullshit.
Um, I could easily make a really simple, like,
like, five minute, like, non,
like, YouTube algorithm,
or optimized, like, length of video.
Uh, just, like, old school animation,
like, five minute, two minute, cool thing
where Red Man says,
uh, I'm stupid.
Like, and skateboards off.
And everyone claps because they like it.
Yeah.
Like, that would be, like, a nice, like,
money sink that is just cool to do.
Yeah.
Sure.
It wouldn't really propel me anywhere,
but it would be cool.
I like cool things.
Epic.
Um, die.
Did you, bro?
Who are you?
Yeah.
What?
Who am I?
Who are you?
Yeah.
Where were you last time?
I kind of know where you hooked me,
but I'm fine.
Wait, let me tell you.
Radcon 3 could be seen as the,
the beginning of my tailspin
as I dove into the ground and died.
I feel that.
So, you know, it was, it was,
it was Christmas of 2017.
I came to Boston to visit Munchie
and Nate and Tom and Ben.
Yeah.
Did you actually show up to that?
I don't think you...
Very good.
Live in Boston.
Were you there the same time that I was?
Everyone's there for Christmas.
Oh, yeah.
Everybody was there for Christmas.
It was a double date thing.
Yeah.
Double date times two plus one.
Before Radcon 3, right?
Yes.
So, we all met up in Boston
and Munchie was like hard-selling me
on how Boston's a cool place.
And Nate was like,
oh, I've always wanted to live in Boston.
And we were like,
all right, let's move to Boston.
We'll do PCP,
we'll do Radcon 3 in Boston
so that we can like house hunt
and scope for shit.
Now, at this time,
I was throwing around cliff
like a motherfucker,
spending a lot of money on weed,
spending a lot of money on paying people
to help me make my videos,
such as you or Tom or Jesse,
all of whom I hired to do like contract work
on videos.
I was like,
this is my way forward is I'm going to start
using the extra money I have
because I was living very low cost of living
at the time.
Like, you know,
weed aside,
I just had tons of extra money.
So I was like,
I'm going to pour this into having other people help me
and that'll be how I make my stuff better.
And I'm also going to work on only like big,
interesting projects.
Because I had made,
we have accepted mediocrity at the start of that year,
a video that was very popular,
that was just calling out YouTube.
Shout out to DeVoo.
Shout out to DeVoo,
who is the only reason that video is good
because it's just an unscripted rant.
You're really quiet in the mic.
I am?
Yeah.
Hello.
It all sounds fine.
Is anyone there?
Don't trust with it.
Hello.
Okay.
Anyway,
so,
yeah,
I'm like trying to make bigger videos
more fucking real ass content.
And then it kind of began
when I started the,
when I did the Finish or Fail video
where I wrote the script really quickly
and I sent it to DeVoo
thinking it would take like a week.
And while he was doing it,
like, you know, while he's doing that,
I'm going to start work on my next big thing,
which is going to be how they marketed.
I remember at Radicon 3,
you hyping up how they marketed.
In fact, I was wearing all those munchy bumpers.
How they marketed were recorded.
Yes.
All of you were supposed to be involved
in how they marketed
because the plan,
the original plan for this series
was that it was supposed to be
exploring the marketing of different shows
and then using that marketing
to promote the videos themselves.
And so the main show I wanted to talk about
was Pop Team Epic,
which was developed basically
as a marketing gimmick.
Like, the point of the show
was to use this,
this like popular comic strip
as a vehicle
and like fill it with memes
and fill it with shit
that would get people to tweet about it
and just like promote itself.
But then the rest of the show
is all this like weird fucking animation
and like super outsider art.
And so I was like,
I want to do that.
I want to make a Pop Team Epic video,
but like the idea is that
it seems like a Pop Team Epic video,
but it keeps veering into
other people's content basically.
And so like there would be
just a munchy segment,
a Tom segment, you know,
and each one would be
in whatever your art style is
just brought into this video.
There'd be tons of memes,
tons of references.
Like I just wanted to imitate
the feel of the show in the video.
And so like that was going to be
a very expensive video to make
because I was going to hire everybody
to do their input.
And I'm like, this is my way forward.
Spend money to make money.
That's what they say, right?
So that's the eight inch.
So, so...
It's adage, did you?
Adage.
You got yelled at in the two...
I don't care.
Anyway, so I'm working on
how they market it.
I'm conceptualizing it
while that video is in the editing bay.
Radcon 3 is coming up.
I'm so, I'm like all I'm focused on
is planning how they market it.
I don't work on the planning
for Radcon 3 at all.
And it was made clear
that I could not bring my girlfriend
to the Rad House.
So I was like, well,
I'm not going for seven days by myself.
Fuck that.
I have all this extra money.
I'll just buy a fucking hotel room
and you can stay in this hotel room
for this whole time.
It's funny to think back,
there was a man long ago
who once asked to bring his girlfriend
to Radcon.
We had a similar policy for that.
So it really just seems consistent.
Oh, you mean Jeff?
Yeah.
Well, I mean...
In Jeff's case...
Damn.
Destroyed.
In Jeff's case...
Obliterated.
It was that he was already there
and asking if he could bring his girlfriend.
Right?
Wasn't he...
Wasn't it like, like a week before
I am really...
I don't think he was like expected to be there
and he just decided he wanted to come
or something like that.
Something along those lines.
It was especially weird
because it was just like my house
and I was like, oh, I don't know
your girlfriend.
Like, I kind of know you.
I kind of trust you.
Yeah.
I don't know your girlfriend.
You just started dating.
Well, regardless.
So Radcon 3, you know,
I got a hotel.
We did that.
Radcon 3 was great.
Lots of good stuff came out of it.
But most of the main content
was stuff that was going to take a long time to edit.
And again, just like this time,
I mostly came and did like tons of behind-the-scenes stuff,
random...
Like, I try to get stuff out during Radcon
because for the audience, it's like,
we hype it up.
We're like, oh, Radcon,
we're going to be here for a week.
And then for them,
it's like they see a few live streams,
I guess, and nothing else happens.
And they're just like, oh, Radcon's fucking gay.
You know?
No, there has to be stuff coming out during Radcon
so people feel excited about the event.
It's my mentality.
But then, like,
doing all that work for the PCP,
I come home and there's nothing for my channel.
There's nothing for me to show
for Radcon 3.
And I haven't finished conceptualizing how they marketed.
And Davoo is still working on my other big video.
I don't remember if that came out
like before or after Radcon actually happened,
but I think it was afterwards.
I think it was working on it while I was there.
I think it was after, but I'm not sure.
So, all of that in mind,
when that Finish or Fail video finally came out,
it dramatically underperformed.
I'm expecting it to get like 300,000 views.
It gets like 50,000 views.
And its main purpose was to advertise how they marketed.
So, the fact that it failed
as an advertising platform for that series
already made me like, uh-oh.
Like, I fucked up.
Also, Finish or Fail took way too long to come out.
And at this point, I made another huge mistake.
I was really obsessed with Denzel Curry at the time, the rapper.
And I had the idea to make a documentary about him
because he was just starting to, like, blow up.
I don't remember that.
There were tons of interviews coming out with him.
And, like, his fan base was getting really passionate.
If I had done this documentary,
it would have been the best idea of any of the ideas I had.
It would have been, got by far the most views.
Denzel Curry blew up really big not long after this.
So, and he definitely would have retweeted my video.
So, like, and I knew all that at the time,
which is why I wanted to do it.
But adding in another big project,
which as I worked on it continually escalated in scope
because I kept wanting to make it better,
rewriting parts of it, doing more research, adding in more clips.
Suddenly, I've got just hours of interviews
downloaded on my computer that I have to sort through
if I want to find everything I want.
And I was just like, this project is becoming overwhelming.
Meanwhile, we're trying to house hunt to move to Boston.
We have to leave at the start of May, you know?
So, I've got, you know, this big hole in my content
from when I did RadCon.
I've got two big projects in the work.
Neither of them is close to done.
What do I do?
I'll record a bunch of Bloodborne Let's Plays,
and that will, I'll use those to, like,
just fill the gaps while I'm moving.
So, I record, like, 20 episodes of Bloodborne Let's Plays.
No, it had to be, like, 30 or 40 episodes,
but we released, like, 20 of them.
And then we had 20 more that were supposed to, like,
pad the gap after we moved.
But they, the hard drive, when we moved, like, failed.
So, I did not have access to these Bloodborne Let's Plays.
The second we moved, because we moved, you know,
on the first of the month,
is when my Patreon takes its monthly hit, right?
So, the Patreon, because of the fact that
for this past month, nothing has come out.
I'm working on two big projects.
Nothing's actually materialized.
My Patreon just goes,
straight down, lost, like, over $1,000.
Oh, my God, really?
Yeah, it went from, like, over $4,000 to around $3,000.
And this is right when I moved into a house
where the rent was $2,300 a month,
and I had to pay triple rent up front when I moved in
because of the fact that they didn't,
they let me move in because of my credit score,
but they said, like, they didn't think I made enough money.
So, like, to prove I had enough money,
they made me do, like, a triple down payment.
So, the end result of this is that it was also tax time
at the same time.
And when it came time for me to go to file my taxes,
because of the expenditure of the move
and the triple down payment,
I only had exactly enough in my bank account
to pay my taxes.
And I was like, clearly, I am not going to pay these
because that would leave me with no money
to move around with if anything bad happens,
and then something bad immediately happened
because me and May had a dual mental breakdown
about a month into living in Boston.
So, after that, everything was just, like,
all plans, any ideas up to that point
were just, like, all this is gone.
Like, I don't care about how they market it.
I don't care about anything.
I just care about making money
and pulling myself out of this tailspin
because I will be fucked
if this continues the way it is.
And it was immediately clear
when winter came,
like, we thought that we...
I loved the house that we were in
because it was big and weird
and had lots of odd hallways,
and I was like, I'm going to decorate this place
because it's super cool.
But, like, I couldn't afford to put anything in the house.
I was like, I have no money.
I had, you know, 15 grand in the bank,
but in my mind, that was just tax money
that needed to be held on to, you know?
I mean, if I think of it that way right now,
I have negative money in the bank.
But, like, you know, the...
Were we talking about Radcon 3?
Yes, we're the space between Radcon 3 and now.
Pardon me, Professor.
This is the How We Got Here story.
Okay.
So, Boston, huge bust,
lost a lot of money,
spent a lot of time recovering,
put out a video every day for a month,
and then I just spent, like, this whole interim time
trying to figure out, like,
what am I trying to do with my career?
Like, because I think I've pretty much
reached the height of what I think you can do
with, like, just anime analysis videos.
Like, my videos...
I've made a video that's, like, as good
as I think this can get at this point.
And, you know...
Do you have one specifically in mind when you say that?
I would say The Great Anime Director Who Time Forgot.
Okay.
Like, that video is my favorite one I've done,
and it's pretty much just perfect.
Like, there's nothing I'd change about it.
It's pretty much ideal, and, like,
having already made that, it's, like,
from that point forward, any new video I do,
like, I just think of it as, like,
try to make it that good.
Like, the one I did recently on The Most Underrated Anime.
Like, I would consider that pretty much the same.
It's not as well-edited,
because Davood didn't do it, but, like,
as good as you can really get with an anime analysis video.
And it's like, I want to see if I can do something else.
So I started working on lots of other projects
while we were in Boston.
I started writing novels.
Started trying to work on video games.
Me and Tom were constantly coming up
with all these crazy, big brain fucking ideas
that would usually fall through,
because we did not have time to work on them.
We did I Am Games.
We were live streaming.
Heavy into branding.
Constantly changing gears.
Finally moved to Virginia Beach after our release was up.
Everything has been much better since moving here.
Just quality of life.
Have money in the bank again.
Able to do things just more easily and better.
So, yeah, ever since moving here,
life has been great,
but it's also been moving extremely fast.
From my perspective,
it feels like I've only been here for like a couple months,
and it's been almost a year,
just because I have not stopped working.
And one of the coolest things about being
in the middle of the East Coast is
people tend to just be passing through.
So, like, mates passed through.
Don Jolly passed through one time.
Econ and Nino came up.
And so, like, I've just kind of been doing these, like,
micro-RAGCON-esque events
where, like, two people come to my house
and I just force them to make content all weekend.
And through that spawned can-tent,
so where do I hope to be by RAGCON 4?
Five. Five.
Depending on how long it takes,
my expectation is that the PCP will have
basically been cannibalized by can-tent
and IM games.
And that will be the central brand
that me and Nate will over with an iron fist.
Everyone who's not Nate and Digi are all like,
oh, okay, cool.
Well, uh...
One more reason not to support can-tent.
Well, there's nothing you can do to stop it
other than not watch, because there is no patreon yet.
But one day it's coming soon.
It does need you.
Keep an eye out for a Kickstarter, one of these great spots.
That would actually be really cool
if you guys started a patreon and split the fanbase
and there was a war, and the PCP finally...
I don't think you guys split the fanbase.
...finally self-destructed and died.
Did the Pajikast cause a split amongst PCP fans
because it does a separate patreon?
I think that's too neat.
The degree is there. How do we know?
Okay, what I meant by cannibalizing the PCP
is not that it would cause any kind of yordle
than the audience. What I meant is that
can-tent would simply grow so large
that it would be in everyone else's best interest
to be a part of can-tent instead of the PCP.
That's my plan.
Yeah, sure. That would be pure benefit to everyone.
No, I'm not being...
I'm not being sarcastic. I want that to happen.
I know you do.
Yeah, you know, I forgot to mention can-tent.
I don't know. I always under...
I have such an aversion in life
to overselling things and overhyping things.
I'll do anything to avoid it.
I wouldn't know it's can-tent.
Because immediately after it started, basically,
there was the whole channels got...
That did happen to us. That was a big event.
Honestly, when the hack happened,
I made no assumption that it would ever come back.
I just assumed it was gone.
I was like, I'm not going to work on this until it's back.
I fucking... I'm not going to give
any energy to this.
For the record, that would just go into the fucking void.
Quick summary for the ages.
My fault the channels got hacked due to a fuck-up,
doing some deal installs and bad software.
Seven channels of ours got hacked,
but they are now all back.
They have all been restored, so that's good news.
We killed the guy responsible.
Brad is deceased, he will no longer live on today.
You'll all see the story of it.
It's quite deep.
It is truly a legendary tale.
Okay, so Nate hopes to be a YouTube
main man and be making money.
Yep.
Hippo wants to progress as an artist
and make more stuff
and be a real boy who makes comments
with that guy and say,
he makes comics.
Did you want to be making money?
I want to be better known as a writer
than as a video maker,
but I don't think that's going to happen by Radcon 5.
Oh, we didn't even talk about it.
You have a whole novel series that you're doing.
I have a novel series.
Let's try The Road to Radcon 4.
Yeah, everyone's favorite.
Road to Radcon 4, which we should work on
concluding while we're here.
But also Kusomega.
I have a very large...
My plans for Kusomega are quite
ambitious and I hope to have them
all done within the year.
But I want to make it like a...
I would describe it as like
a micro sprawling franchise.
Like, it has
elements of everything, but they're all
small, you know?
So that's like my vision for it.
Okay, so being a writer and making money.
Can 10, both of you.
Also, to answer the previous question,
what's the best thing to come out of Radcon so far?
The Brad Garlinghouse
lecture was probably my outright favorite
thing we've done so far.
I thought it was just so...
I mean, it felt that way in the moment.
I haven't seen it back, but it felt
really, really good.
The lectures have all been great.
It's enough for me.
Tom, you've been crippled for the past
like 100 years.
You gotta turn the camera to Tom.
I'm getting to it.
Yeah.
I've always been crippled my whole life, but now
it's just physically represented
in physical form.
So Radcon 3 to 4.
What's the journey?
Well, Radcon 3 ended.
It was pretty fucking good.
Then
everything, I guess, changed with my
content. Like, because me and Munchy were talking
up, we're gonna do Investigator,
we're gonna do Schloss, we're gonna be sick.
We did our art apology, we committed
Sepuku on camera.
It's weird to think that Radcon 3,
Investigator and Schloss, we're still
in the works. Yeah, they're still on the table.
We made big
bold promises that they're coming.
We basically said if we don't finish
these, we will kill ourselves and we're still
here and we lied completely.
You're doing...
Okay, comics are cool.
But you're making a video game?
Which is way cooler.
Well, he's not making a video game right now.
You have made a video game
and planned to make more.
You're not making a video game?
Well,
I got this whole big...
I talked about it in the video we did.
Yeah, go watch the Digi's creative consultation
with Tom Oliver where he talks about how
Azumi is currently
more expanding
as a brand beyond... It was always supposed to be
a multimedia brand character.
Since the game is taking so long to make,
it's currently looking like
doing other things with the characters.
Gotta build up the brand first, so then the game
can come in and be fucking
based as fuck and not cringe.
So pretty much all your
energy is on that?
Yeah, I'm trying because
someone is actually talking about this on the live stream last night
which is deleted, press F.
Somebody save it.
They were talking about why aren't you doing programming
and it's like, well, to make a really cool video game
you gotta do programming but you also need 3D
modeling and you also need animation.
And it's like, well, I can do coding
first and have nothing to show for it
because coding by itself is boring and no one cares.
Or I can learn the animation of the 3D
first and have tons of content
come out with that while I'm learning it
to build up the brand and then do the coding
and that seems like
the more intelligent path of acquiring these two.
This is typically why video games are made by teams
of people.
Toby Fox.
That's true.
So the idea right now is
I had this whole thing where
me and my friend Matt, we were doing
a big accountability group.
We had a bunch of people in there trying to keep ourselves hype
and then a bunch of people we brought in were all doing video games
and they peer pressured me into making a video game
and so when I came up with the Zoomie
my idea was like, okay.
I've been trying to make big, sprawling,
crazy fantasy stories for like a decade
and every single one of them has collapsed under its own bloat.
So what if I made a character
and worked in a way that was
purposely, completely opposite
all of my natural inclinations?
What if I just made a purely aesthetic character
with no story, with no lore
and it was just fucking cool
and that was the only guiding principle.
You could pull a George Stancy, the opposite of every natural instinctive guy.
Exactly.
And the character took off in a way
that nothing else I've ever done has.
People were doing fan art like instantly
and it was just like, I did it.
I figured it out. I cracked the code.
Gotta get those furry bucks apparently.
So, base.
They were just like, you gotta make a video game
so that's where the idea came from is like making a video game.
So the big moonshot project with like
all the fucking deep, cool things
is all in this video game that will happen in like 40 years.
But in the meantime
I made a cool like guilty gear style shader
so I can make cool 2D that looks 3D
or 3D that looks 2D.
It's fucking sick. It's gonna be dope.
And as soon as Radcon is over
it's back to the grindstone
and I got like
4 books and comics and like 4 commas
and animations and maybe doing some
AMV music videos. It's just like learning 3D
learning animation
and just putting a zoomie on everything
and hopefully that'll work.
Tom, I think
they're making some sort of like
new train system
that's better than the meter rail.
It goes from Worcester to Boston.
So when that happens, move to Worcester
so we can actually see each other.
Cause we live like the same state
when you're like a decade
you're gonna get Tom before I get Tom.
I have empty rooms in my house
my friend.
Is there still hope
or intention for that to happen?
I mean, it'd be cool.
Tom has said from the start
that he has no desire to live in Boston
as he hates Boston.
It's not even that I hate Boston.
I hate cold.
Cold is really bad.
The Nor'easters have been a blight on my life
ever since I was a wee lad
and they never end.
I hate that a lot.
I don't know.
I'm still hoping out hope that somehow
we can all
converge on one location
because it is still the dream.
It will never move to Virginia Beach. Virginia Beach can suck shit.
Damn.
We've had a great time this whole week.
This is not Virginia Beach.
You say that, but one day the dollars
could tell a different story.
That's stupid.
We'll say it.
We don't want it to happen.
What a weird sinister sentence to say to someone.
Ben's always so dimmical.
Guys, nothing on this fucking earth could ever
compel me to leave this city where I have
some connections to some places.
I lived here for a year and it sucked.
They would like completely change your life.
But being a bitch, I don't want to move to your dumb city.
It's not my city.
Well, you're moving there.
I mean, maybe.
You're the one with the head of it.
Ben, it's like a moral, like, indignation
against cars.
Well, yeah, sure.
I also don't like Virginia Beach.
What?
I mean, for what it's worth, at the time, I didn't like Virginia Beach
because we lived in the shittiest part of Virginia Beach.
Now I love it.
Every location to be is identical
because I live inside and I don't do anything.
So I have no interest in where I live.
This is someone who's lived their entire lives
in their bedroom and then finally once he moved to Boston
and was able to realize, oh wait, the outside is cool.
I go outside every single day now.
I use the public transport every single day.
Look, I live in...
Then it pays $500 rent, right?
Or around there?
Less than $500.
So he's literally able to live in Boston and have a great time.
Thanks for having my back.
It's a shitty place to live.
I would rather live, I don't know, like California.
Somebody's nice, Hawaii.
That would be nice.
The reality of my life is that I am inside working.
The quality of life, things better.
Being here in Virginia Beach is way better than the place I live currently.
But the reality today
is that I'm inside doing it.
Honestly, the reason I live in a better place
is because it would make my girlfriend happier
and she would be much happier living here.
That's the main reason that it even matters to me a little bit.
Other than that, I mean,
if there's any degree of just more convenience
by living in a place that's just less nice,
that, like, work is my priority.
Being able to do my work well
and efficiently and whatever,
that's, like, 90% of what I care about in life.
And then the other 10%.
So, I mean, if people don't agree with that, fair enough.
But that's just why I think
that I don't care where I am.
I'll just do anything as long as it has, like, the bare minimum shit
that I need to get by.
I'll travel to places once in a while
when I fucking feel like it and go do fun things.
I don't think anyone's opposed to coming to Virginia Beach to hang out.
Except Ben, he just said that he is.
I said I would never move.
I said to hang out, yes.
Okay, fair enough.
I'm going to go to Virginia Beach and that's okay.
Ben just put in this, like, it will never happen, man.
Because he doesn't want to live here before.
I don't want to come here before.
I mean, for what it's worth,
like, it's not as though we need Ben to move down here.
Like, he can come, like you said, visit anytime.
Yeah, there's very clear, like, network of people
who, like, can work together.
What happened in Boston, particularly
at Radcon 3.33,
like, what became clear, at least to me,
was that, like,
Munchie and Ben
have no real interest in, like,
being YouTubers and, like,
making a main, central pillar of their life
be doing YouTube content.
It's like, you guys want to do Endless War,
you want to do your own art, you have your own community.
There are literally only two people in this room
whose goals are remotely similar.
Right. And it's Nate and Digi.
Exactly. You guys should have a blast.
You guys should have a blast.
But, well, you say that it's only two people
except that Tom also has,
like, for him it's quite easy
to just kind of
be in things
with us, like,
I don't know, for Tom,
Tom and I have talked a lot about his
I'm trying to, like, not speak for you
while you're not paying attention, but, like...
I was just checking chat
because nothing was going wrong.
Because you've talked about before how, like,
you have your own work
and you're very passionate about, like, your personal projects
but you also find it almost easier
to, like, just work on someone else's thing
and, like, be a part of that.
Especially if it benefits you monetarily.
As someone who's been a fucking hermit their entire lives
and has no real-life connections,
collaboration is cool, especially when
it's in person with other people
and you can vibe off each other's hype
because the hardest thing for me to do on my solo projects
is motivation
because everything I feel like I'm doing myself
inherently has less value
because I'm a broken man.
But, like, and when you and I were trying to work together
on I Am Games, like, it always came down to, like,
I have my own YouTube career
but, you know, I would take time away from that
to try to make I Am Games more of a thing
and you have your 3D career
and you try to take time away from that
to make this more of a thing.
But, like, ultimately, it was, like,
you know, one of us
would have had to make it, like,
the real focus of our career
for a while for it to work.
But, like, me and Nate
are living in the same spot
and we were, like, we had the time
to do a show, like, that we could
put more focus into.
Then I feel like it's
it makes more sense for you and I to do that
when, like, you know, our goals are literally the same
whereas yours are, like, more ancillary
to that. It's, like,
you know, you're not trying to be a YouTuber
you're just down to do YouTube videos
if there's, like, a successful venture
here that you can easily slot yourself into, you know?
It doesn't even have to be successful
just, like, hey, there are people that are, like, doing cool things.
I'll be a part of it. Why not?
You know, successful is a
subjective term. And to me, any
channel with, like, 1,000 subscribers
is successful in my mind.
Like, because that's so high above
the baseline of what I had before I started having
subs that, like, a thousand subs
to me is always, like, oh, you've already got your foot in the door,
you know? Sure, sure.
Anyway, I don't know what I'm talking about.
So, Ben.
Yes, where have you been
since the last radical? Where do you hope to be?
Uh, I guess we made
Endless War. Yes, we did.
That was pretty funny and wacky.
Uh...
Like, a month after we got back from
my country. From my
perspective, it has always seemed like that has just
been you guys' entire lives
since then, but is that how it's always
happened? Basically.
Um, kinda.
For a while, I was, like,
making the game
and then, like, lately
I haven't really been making it, but I've been working
on Slime and Punishment, which is adjacent to it.
Um...
Uh, I don't know what else to say
about the time in between. I mean, I guess I was
making more comics. You moved back
to Boston. I moved back to Boston. I did the
Vapors 2 Kickstarter, which I was still waiting
on. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Uh...
Um...
I had two kidney stones.
That was my favorite part.
Uh...
Lost 50 pounds
got really woke.
Gained 50 pounds in my energy.
Uh...
I don't know.
I've just been
fuckin' around.
Fuckin' around on my tablet in Manga Studio
making a bunch of bullshit
for, like, two years.
Where do you want to be the retcon 5?
Um...
I was doing the same thing, but with more
people watching.
That's it. Not more money, more people
watching. I mean,
tomato tomato.
Uh...
I don't know. Is that a boring one?
Yes, extremely
excruciating. Cool.
I'll probably, if we end up doing...
That was torture.
I totally forgot I was supposed to do
those creative consultation videos with everybody,
but if I did one with you, one of the questions
Tom is, like, is there a dollar
amount you're, like, hoping to reach?
Um...
What, on Patreon?
Yeah. Not just, like, through your Patreon,
just, like, in, like, your total income
in a month. Like, is there, like,
a number that you visualized yourself as,
like, oh, I'd be, like, really happy if I was
just making this amount?
Um...uh...
I kind of feel like I already am past the
threshold of, like,
I make enough that I can keep
doing what I'm doing and I won't die.
That's good.
Is that your only ambition, though?
Yeah, pretty much.
No, not really. That's so cool.
It's pretty fucking smart.
It's pretty fucking awesome.
As long as...just gotta keep my
biological functions continuing
so I can keep generating
digital imagery
to be disseminated throughout culture.
Yeah.
That's the only goal.
I don't know what song it is.
I don't mind stealing bread
from the mouths of
Nicaragans.
Wait, wait.
But then he says,
well, I can't feed on the underfed
when my cup's already
overfilled
so I'm going hungry.
I'm going hungry!
Hey!
Sure.
I guess that's me.
Excellent.
I guess that sums it up, huh?
Do you have any other aspirations whatsoever?
Do you want everything to be exactly the same?
But you have more money now.
What would I change?
I don't know.
You don't have to improve in some way
that I can't understand
because I'm not you.
I'll just get better
doing my shit now.
That'll just happen.
I don't have to worry about it.
That'll just happen naturally.
We are desperate for some insight
into the mystery of Ben Sane.
I don't know what you want me to tell you, dude.
I knew this would happen.
I'm just vibing over here.
He's just vibing.
Jesse, do you care?
Do you care about your own life?
What?
What happened between Radcon 3 and now?
Everything bad
and nothing good?
No, everything was already happening at the point of time.
That's true.
I don't know.
The entire period
of my life
between 2016
and 2020
is just a constant
dark spiral
of abject misery
and pain.
Then I moved and I guess I got a little bit better.
Now I'm here.
Where do you want to be
by Radcon 5?
Rich.
I mean me too.
I don't know.
I've been like really
I'm in this
transitionary period
of realigning
goals and pursuits
of really trying to branch out
and get back to being a human
and doing stuff outside of the YouTube bubble.
I've been
I've been getting back into stand-up.
I've been doing some stand-up stuff.
That was really legendary.
Back a million years ago.
I've been
learning how to have fun again.
Teach me about that
because I don't know what that's like.
I got into edibles.
Oh, never mind.
Exactly.
I started going to the movie theater alone
and that's pretty fucking cool.
And so
I try to take
some time for me
out of the week where I just go in my car
and on some adventure
to anywhere.
Sometimes I'm like I'm going to go to the big movie theater
two cities over
and sometimes I'm like no, fuck that.
I'm going to go to the woods and walk around
in the woods and explore.
And sometimes I'm like I'm going to do some
other shit. I don't fucking know.
So anyways, I've been doing the stand-up thing.
I've been working out a lot.
And my ultimate goal with the working out
is to get my body
looking really good and then
finally do
what I was supposed to do
10 years ago which is
trained to be a professional wrestler.
Thank God.
This was the turning point
mistake of my entire life.
When I got out of high school
a million years ago or so
I had like
people give you money at your
open house or whatever so I had
like a thousand dollars or something
which at that point was the most money I'd ever seen in my life.
And
I was looking up wrestling schools because I didn't know what else
to fucking do with my life
and it just seemed cool
and I found a guy
Truth Martini. He had a wrestling school.
He's a cool guy. I've seen him on TV
and like Ring of Honor and stuff.
So he's a real man
and I'm like okay I'm going to go to Truth Martini's
wrestling school. It was like a thousand bucks to get in
but then it was also
like a thousand bucks for like a laptop
and
I bought the laptop and I started making
videos on YouTube
and it was the fucking
it was the ground zero of my entire
horrible life. That one decision
ruined everything
so now
even though
I'm not 20 anymore and it might be too
late
but I do have
I still harbor these aspirations
of being involved in that business
some way in an official capacity
either as a wrestler
or even as a manager or an announcer
whatever the fuck
but my goal is right now
to get in shape which has always been a goal anyways
because I've been out of shape for many fucking years
so I'm doing that. I'm doing stand up.
I'm trying to I want to do more
like get more into music and stuff
I'm glad with people. I've been like
reconnecting with friends that I've let
friendships that have gone to the wayside
as I've been more sucked into the
YouTube lifestyle
I've been hanging out with my friend Cody the Roo
I've been acting more. We've been like
writing skits. I wrote a pilot
that we're planning on filming at some point
for a 6 sci-fi series
it's gonna be dope
Flint Rat films
YouTube is the channel
and
yeah, I'm just branching
and even to the point of
looking up
normie work which has always been
a dream of mine is to just be
You mean movies? Is that what you mean by normie
work? Well no, that's part
of my creative sickness
but I've been looking up
like give me a fucking job
please you know
Oh, normie work is when you work with your hands
and you okay
I think that's normie artwork
No, we're like
I used to work on a farm
before all this started I was like a gardener
and like a sheep shearer
what do they call the guys who
heard the fucking bastards
Shepard, yeah, that was my job
I can't remember the name of it but that was my job
for a while
you know, bailing and stacking hand stuff
and like I loved working on the farm
like I love physical labor
and it's like
my body's pretty broken down now from
sitting at a computer desk for 11 years
but like man, I don't know
fucking put a hard hat on me
let me be, I fucking, the movie
they live with Rowdy Rowdy Piper
which is
supposed to be like a dystopia
right? He starts out the movie
he's living in a shanty town
just like he just walks into a construction
site and gets a job and it's supposed to be
like this is the beginning of the movie where he's
like poor and destitute and it's the sad part
but like I was watching the movie again
the day I'm like this part of the movie
that is the poor, humble beginnings
is my dream I just want to
wander into a town and be
ripped and buff and
someone puts a hard hat on me
and I live in a shanty town and eat beans
out of the can and work
physical labor every day and get my little
my $250 paycheck
and that'd be
pretty fucking cool
those are achievable goals
but then also like I found, I was like
looking for other work and I found
like I started looking for writing jobs
because that's a thing that I'm actually good at
and so I found one that was like
looking for a
science fiction ghost writer
and it's like we're a magazine or something
just like in that episode
of Star Trek Deep Space Nine
where Captain Sisko
was in the 1950s
as a science fiction writer
it was like hey, we're a science fiction
publication or whatever
we just want someone to
write the prose, we'll give you the characters
and the big story beats
and you figure out what to do
and I'm like I could apply for that fucking job
that'd be fucking sick
just write a novel and get paid for it
and not have to like, huh?
where do you even find job listings like that?
like Craigslist and shit
the same way that normal people all over
the world find jobs
I finally realized oh yeah I can do that too
I don't have to be on fucking podcasts
every week of my life
wait, sorry
if you have more you can go, I just remembered something
I don't want to interrupt though
no I mean that's pretty much it
I mean I still, I'm pretty much a retired
YouTuber at this point and like I'm kind of like
I'm kind of at the point where like
it's time for Endless just to go away
like he's had his run
it was mostly a failure
he can be, I can like
I don't know redefine him or something
like you know I get bored, I got bored of drowning in footwear
I got bored of drowning in horseshoes
I'm kind of bored of
Endless just and it's like
I don't know maybe like I'll keep the name
as like a rap name or something but like
I'm really considering like
completely changing my channel
and all my channels and like
finding a way to do something do everything
entirely differently than how I've been doing it
I feel the temptation to do that
about every month and then I
do that about every six months
well I have
plans that I don't want to go into
but I am thinking of like doing stuff differently
and I still
am making videos
because I have to keep the revenue coming in from Patreon
but that's all it is
I keep getting comments and I keep having to
clarify this of people like
where is Jess? Jess never uploads
videos anymore, Jess doesn't
make videos, I make videos
I have videos coming out every month
they're just not on YouTube I don't post
them publicly because I don't care
I have zero desire
or inclination to be a public figure at
all it is a cancer and a poison
in my life every second that
I am not being
a public figure I am much happier
so
like I am still making content
I am a creative person and that's never going to
change but
most of it is like exclusive to Patreon
right now while I figure out
what the hell else I'm doing in this
transitory
period of like
fuck it you know what I'm saying
you know what I'm saying
Ben would you forget
oh I was thinking
ok you were talking about finding
normie work I
haven't really been thinking about this because
I have been
before Radcon I was trying to crank out
the finale to slime and punishment
and um I haven't really
I don't know
but sometimes when I'm not
like when I'm not working on something like that
sometimes I think about
looking for work as like
like if I wanted to get like a job job
I would really like it
if I could be some kind of artist
on a project like an indie game
if I could be like an in-house artist for an indie game studio
I think that would be cool
or basically any project
that like wasn't overly
restrictive that like an artist's role
on any project that like I could
that I could like have
some creative like input on
that I wouldn't have to like stick really rigidly
to a template or something
I would just
like um I don't know
like when you made t-bap
I was the guy who did the art for t-bap
it would be cool if there were other things
that I could work on and I wouldn't even be
too too picky about it just anything
that like I could work on and then
if people saw it they'd be like oh
you're the guy who did the art for whatever
x thing
I guess I could even
do it for like a
like a comic or something
it's just so fucking hard
every once in a long while
I'll go on Craigslist and I'll just look
for like art gigs
and it's all shit and I give up immediately
I've looked like the only like
indie game jobs I've been able to see
is like UI designer
for like a mobile app and I'm like
no that's nightmare
that's like worse than working on a cubicle
honestly that sounds
totally thankless and pointless
and just like a waste of human effort
makes me sad
okay who's next
it's a tough thing to pin down
I'm sure there are opportunities out there
there are people who want artists but
how to find them
why pay artists when you just go on twitter
steal their artwork
go on google.com and google
sick UI and then just download that
but then you could also google search
hot anime pussy and then you could
jack off instead of doing that
at all so what's the point
I find this
interesting broadly speaking
aspiring to normie job
aspiring to normie job maybe kind of thinking that
you think that's a normie job
that's not really a job
in a sense that's not a feature
I don't really aspire
I don't aspire to that
I would only do that because it would be
like boy I should
lights are falling
I only think about that because it's like
maybe living
on just enough money
to not die immediately
is like a little dangerous
it's risky
maybe I should
aim a little higher than that
financially speaking
well if I was going to pursue that
I guess it wouldn't be too bad
to do it in this way
the way I just described
working on art in a way
that's not really restrictive
I would be okay with that
the ultimate goal
is that I can just fuck around
and make whatever I want
and I'll have a big enough
or dedicated enough audience
that I can just survive on that
if I were to go and do a job like that
my dream scenario would be
the lights are falling
is that on?
okay cool
they've been up the whole week
they've been good boys
the dream scenario
is that I do that
maybe I work for a studio or something
we make a project and I do the art for it
and it's hugely successful
and then I gain cloud
and it's like oh you're the guy
who made the thing for that thing
oh I know your work
and then I gain
my own audience
this is really your coke or a wish
you want a game, complete
no I just want cloud
I just want cloud
because cloud is
cloud is life
because if you got cloud
people will pay you
people will support you
just because it's you
that's what I want
I want to make my shit
and I don't want to work for anyone else
because I'm a communist
and I don't want anyone else extracting surplus value
from me because that's rape
and I don't want that
is it fair to say who aspired to be a demagogue?
what do you mean?
to be a cult leader
cloud man who gets to bend people to his will
and enact vengeance in the world
well my schools have so far seen purely financial
which is so sick
I wouldn't say no
if I type saw that on Craigslist
I might send in a resume
cult leader wanted
I'm just talking about being independent
I'm just talking about being able to
survive
without
getting bossed around by the man
you know if you could apply
to a cult leader position
the sort of internship experience
that you would need would be
being a youtuber
yeah that's what you're saying
um
oh
I was going to say in terms of cloud
I don't know if any of you ever used it back in like
2012-2013
there was a website
why would you do that?
shut up
to victor
love you bro
there was a website back in like 2012-2013
it might even still exist
called cloud with a K
and you would just type in your name
and one of your social media accounts
it would rank you in like how much
cloud you had
it was extremely confusing
and nobody could figure out
we have social blade now
which also is not
really that accurate
both of them are like
both can make you seem like you're way more famous than you are
they definitely seemed like
best case scenarios
and as someone who was living the worst case scenario
definitely not representative
like it's funny because like
Saber Spark has almost a million subscribers right now
and like on social blade they say
he makes like $500,000 a year
and he's just like
not even
remotely close
well we've all answered this question now
let's go to other piece of your memory
Gino, what have you been doing
since we were at con 3?
no
well I wanted to hear from Gino
he's a star and he's continuing to be
a star, thanks Gino
alright Munchy, bore us with your story now
hey
what?
there's a sibling rivalry going on
Gino's like the new guy, he's so fucking huge
I know what I'm saying
it's magnificent
what happens in the last
I mean in this war like you were saying
that's been my whole life
and since it stopped being your whole life
it's become my whole life
I'm still, I'm not like active on the server
I'm making slime
nah I gotcha
I'm not as involved in the servers
you are
your presence has still fell
that's the most important thing
just don't forget me
I say
so I'm in punishment finale
it's coming out like
probably like right after redcon's done
ouch
I've gotten into doing because of endless war
and because of other stuff and getting really into
weird stuff and that's kind of
what will lead into where do I want to be
but redcon 5, just like
in case you don't know
for a thousand times, but in case you don't know
in this war is a game
that me and Ben made
it's about slime
oh of course, I started to crack
in punishment
and you can play it
and you can enlist and rise your killers
and those are our games and you should play it now
do it, please
what are we going to get
endless war 2
it's time, I need the new version
I need 3D graphics
I need microtransactions
I need a season pass
why do you need a sequel to a game
that's an ever evolving organism
because I
I'm against live services
as a principle
it's a bad business value
what about free live services
the jury is still out on that one
I love free things and I hate live services
so it's just like
what?
I guess that's why I don't play
I don't know what to feel about it
while making
endless war and while
doing other miscellaneous podcasts
and stuff, I kind of realized that
podcasts are boring
not that I have a human hatred of them
or that they're like, oh I hate them
I want them to die
maybe
we'll let the viewers decide
I guess
I don't know, I just don't really like
personality driven content that I make
because I don't really like doing it anymore
but it's cool if you like it
and so
I was doing endless war
there's nothing more boring to me than my own personality
you feel the same way?
yeah I do
and so I was doing endless war, I was ramping down
doing all other sort of personality driven
podcasts and shows like that
I traversed the world
on a summer of pain too
I went to hippo's house, we did game for a day
and I did a road trip
and it was nice, I've really been trying
to focus on being like a human being
because like for all my entire life
all I would do is sit in my room
and I wouldn't leave my house at all
and I realized that's like a bad recipe
for being an artist because if you're in your room all day
then you're gonna make really bad, boring art
which I was making
and so I decided to get out of the house
and instantly I felt my quality of life
immediately improved just by leaving the house
and talking to my real life friends
for even like a second and it was great
that branched into going to college
and I started my first semester in college
and I'm in my same semester right now
hashtag split break, hashtag fuck pussy
hashtag free Cuba, hashtag
80 million dead
and it's been really
very interesting
I've been very happy that I went
I feel like being an actor
in the world which is something I have not been
since I was a wee lad
I have not like talked to people
that I don't know IRL
since I was like 12
and so it's a very interesting
cool experience and I'm happy to be moving along
in my real life
and I think that that will improve my art
as I think it has been
with stuff like once in cactus and in this war
continuing to be interesting and cool
so where do I want to be in Radcom 5
I want to, I have ideas
and I want to get into specific projects
but here's where my brain is at
I want to make new experimental art
using technology
during the between the last two Radcom
or the last Radcom me and Tom
were killing Code Hall, where is it law
well I'll tell you where killing Code is
it's in endless war and elsewhere
and in lonesome cactus
that's where killing Code is where all my energy and my brain power is
I became a coding god man
and I want to use coding to make weird experimental art
I want to be personality based
I want to make cool fiction to make people happy
and I want to live my life like a normal person
but also be weird, freak at the same time
I just want to be a person in the world
doing cool shit, I don't care about making podcasts
I don't care about YouTube, I just want to make cool art
that's experimental and cool
hell yeah, hell yeah
I don't think any of us really
wants to do personality driven content
well the why is it that everyone does
because it's easy to expect
I don't consider what I do to be personality driven content
wait
who so mega isn't
but your entire thing is like
there is a YouTube trap
that we all fell into for a while
did you make a video about
I find this director interesting
these are the reasons why
yeah I guess that's his personality
as to why he thinks it's why
all my videos are about things
okay okay
I don't think that being
like I don't think it's a binary
or a personality driven show or not
I think there are degrees
I think that like
historically at the very least
you have presented yourself
as content
people interpret it that way
I think when you're
starting out as an artist
a good way to market yourself
is to make it personality driven
and to make it seem like
it's not just my art that's good
I'm also good look at me I'm important
you kind of have to go through that phase
and do that
but I think all of us here
have done that for long enough
and now we can maybe make something more humble
I think injecting my personality
and my content has mostly
only ever heard it
I think that my content would have always been
way more popular if I never injected myself into it
I sometimes feel similarly
wasn't there a whole like idea
where it's like your videos are drifted away
and that's how you were during like modal
soul days and that big long vlog
where you started doing colored chip
hue value things and you're like
oh let's get back to the real Digi Bro
and your entire fucking entire
brand is the Godzilla journalist
it's my opinion and nobody liked it
nobody was into that at all
that was when I started losing all my patrons
and people were like stop doing drugs
and making your vlogs purple
how is the rant hole not personality
personality driven content that is your main source
they're all about things
like pay for you because they like your personality
it's not
personality isn't everything about what's in your brain
it's also just like your thoughts
I was going to say the rant hole
after dark is personality based
is it
but maybe that's not the main
I don't know if you consider that your main thing
after dark is dead it's just rants now
well yeah, rants then
the rants
is it that they want my personality
or that they want my perspective
they want both
I think of those as different
no I don't think that's different
okay
when I think personality driven content
this is retarded
all content that has anything to do
with your views on something just is bad
is this the point being made
maybe it's not
you would have to be purposely trying to be the most
stupid person on earth to think that that's what we're saying
and intentionally trying to
mis-ingenderize
all art
is autobiographical inherently
that's why the author is objectively wrong
but
it's okay to say
this project doesn't have to be about me
every once in a while
okay
so the way I would put it is like this
when I go into making a video
the mentality is like
here's an idea, here's a thought I had
how can I express that idea
in a way where the audience will best understand it
the way that I understand it
and if the
like if that thought
is a natural result
of my personality
it will require a lot of my personality
and explaining myself to get to that explanation
and I think that
most people
view that as egotistical
and it's not egotistical
it's just autistic
I don't have enough reference to refer to things
other than myself to explain things
so like
there's always been this idea that
Digi makes content about himself
and it's like that's true
but it's always just kind of been because
it's easy to make content
it's easy to use yourself for comparison
it's easy to say here's what I would do in that situation
you know
I think it's sort of like
the end goal
by
a method to get people
to care about an anime
is to tell a personal story or an anime
which is what you do
what personality driven content would be
is a vlog channel where
my life is the content
Casey Neistat I would consider personality driven content
and it's not just
him himself
but his editing style
has a personality
and it is the draw of the video
nothing that happens in the videos is interesting
at all almost ever
it's just his daily life
it's purely his energy
his editing style
and yes a lot of people watch me for those reasons
and I do think that
most of my patrons are
fans of my personality
probably above most other things
but I don't consider
the personality to be
what is driving the videos
individually and if it is it's usually
not a good thing
we need to step way back
this is not judgment of good versus bad
personality does not mean bad
the only reason I was saying that it was
boring is because what Ben said
I view my own personality as boring
I think most personality
driven content is boring
because nobody is as interesting as concepts are
so inherently
something like Casey Neistat's videos again
they have an aesthetic kind of vibe
I might resonate with him
as a person but there is no
intellectual content I forget those videos
as quickly as I've seen them
they are just fluff entertainment content
that makes you feel
good for the duration of watching it
and I think that my stuff
can have that effect and that is a good
benefit of the content but what I hope
my content does is get you to think about
the stuff I'm talking about
if your main take away is
I love listening to DigiBro's voice
I'm glad you had a good time
that wasn't the point here
hopefully you also thought about what I was talking about
it does have to be one or the other
I feel like it's a very clear spectrum
it's undeniable
that a lot of DigiHeads
just like you and will follow you
to the edge of the earth
it's totally fair to say that people like me
for my personality
it's just that I feel a lot of the same way
that you do about
I find myself annoying and boring
I don't like to listen to my own
podcasts and stuff
in fact most of what I release
these days if it's a podcast I do not listen to it back
I just publish
because unless I can remember
that there was something that has to be edited out
I will go back and do that
to me it's just like
I'm over listening to myself
endlessly about things
I just have endless ideas
and so I will provide those
to the rest of you who do want to hear me
you have endless ideas
we have endless wars
true
and I have
endless jobs
thank you
we can go on for over an hour
we're fucking done with this question
it was that one question
it was one question
I mean that was just the topic of the
it became just the topic
I guess it did
that was like two years of time
it was a good topic
I mean assumably
episode 100 would have happened around
Radcon 3 right?
yes it did
well then this was a good topic
thank you to whoever suggested it
there were more questions
there were
most of them were kind of slight variants
and they weren't that cool but I will go through them again
just for the sake of completion
I know we will see
I'll grab my phone now that it's charged
and look through them too
it was a big old time
everybody continually to talk about this question
this is very cool
they had rablon about something
that no one cares about
who said that
give me a name
no no one said that
I'm saying you do that while I look for this
not necessarily
that you always do that
but please for once find it in you
to be boring
I can't
no where inside
anything that's not just astonishing
Bernie's only 150 delegates
oh yeah
Bernie Sanders dude
hell yeah
so how about that
coronavirus
dude I definitely have it
dude they might cancel WrestleMania
I'm hearing
the NBA
how am I going to find out what happens
to AJ Styles
calling the undertaker a cock
it's a great question
most of these questions are variations
of what we were just discussing
there's one where it's like
how much of the peace of the change
since the last ritecon
is there like a lifejack going on
again if you donated
a certain amount to the kickstart
for ritecon 4 you're able to become a PTA member
a secret discord for those PTA members
where they can tell us things to do at ritecon 4
and this is one of the things that they can tell us to do
they're going to ask us questions
so that's what is happening right now
is this a live stream
or a pre-recorded thing
that's what I thought
there is a chat but we're not looking at it
those people didn't buy their way
well what if someone's super chat
we'll check later
can you do this more than god intended
if there's no questions
there's a super chat but we won't read it
yes
destroy it
I mean maybe we want to
exit maybe
what are your daily morning routines
I saw that one I didn't know if that would be interesting
does anybody have a morning routine
here's my morning routine
oh hey by the way this is the thing that started
since the last ritecon which has like a couple posts
my munchie scripts
tumblr check that out
for the content about what I'm going to say
way into like
basically using machines to rule my life
for me because I can't be trusted to make a decision on my own
so here's what I have here's my morning routine
I get up
my alarm is going off and I set it up
so I made a thing where
my phone will only stop
doing the alarm when I scan a QR code
that is inside of my shower
so I have to go to my shower
to scan a QR code so that my alarm
will turn off and then
once I'm there I'm like I have my clothes already
set up there from the night before
so I literally just get into the shower
so I don't have like a decision making process
like oh do I want to get up right now do I just want to hit snooze
no I'm already in the shower
I already have my clothes here man
I might as well get naked and shower
so that's my morning routine
then I get up sometimes I get breakfast
but I usually don't because breakfast is fucking stupid
and then I just start working or go to school
and that's my morning routine
what app does that
there is an app called
it is
alarming for Android
and you can see it so we'll scan a
barcode or a QR code and I made a QR code
that says wake up and then
I have begun to settle into more of a general
routine for my days in life
that's good as opposed to like
the dark times where
my life was just an endless fog
of grey matter
read munchy strips you'll vibe on
guess it you'll vibe hard
where do you find munchy strips
you've seen it before you've read it before
it's my time oh munchy strips
yeah
I've gotten into a routine of like
I wake up I fucking
you know brush my
ass and shit my teeth or whatever the fuck
and I fucking
I fuck around and I go to the gym for a couple hours
and then I come home
and then I usually just fucking chill
and I do that for like
the first 20 days
of the month about and then I remember
that I have to create content
to get paid
and so then I like cram on the last fucking
day of the month like oh my god I have to do something
on Patreon oh my god oh my god what have I done
and so it's
and then like I have like a
my day off from the gym
where I instead of going there I go on
a silly adventure to like the woods or like
a comedy club or something or some city
and
and then also I travel a lot all across the country
because my fucking girlfriend is on the side of the country
and I'm fucking terrible
and yeah we're desperately
both of us trying to save money
to get a place together
but it's also hard because
seeing each other costs money
so every time that we see each other
it bleeds from the funds
of saving up to see each other permanently
so
how can we help you to save money?
patreon.com
slash endless jazz
what will we find on there?
yes I have yes everyone
constantly has to be promoting
the endless jazz text post
on Patreon if you are somebody
who is capable of reading
you should become a endless jazz
they have become my pride and joy
if you're like most people and you can't read
you might not get the same benefit
the text posts are among my best
accomplishments as a person who makes
things they are good
and they're only available on patreon
and if you pledge and see
them you'll be helping me eventually
have a really good life hopefully
I'll tell you my morning routine
because it used to be that I just
jumped out of bed immediately
went straight to the computer and just
went about my day
but now that I
have a wife and usually
wake up at the same time
it's more like we
battle over whether
we're going to get out of bed or not
for about 45 minutes
I finally do and
most of that time is
me in the back of my mind thinking
okay on the one hand
I really want to get up and smoke weed
immediately but on the other hand
this bed is very comfy
and I have the warm
love of my wife so I'm going to stay
here as long as I can
but the second I get up
I'm going straight to the bomb
so the second I get up I go straight
to the bomb
usually though
actually I'm exaggerating because
usually what we do is
anything that needs to get done for the day
I try to get it done like the second we
wake up so that I can start smoking
so like it's usually
like oh
we'll wake up and I'll be like what do you need to do today
and it's like we got to get groceries
we got to go here and then we just do that
right away get food while we're out
come home
I smoke and then eat
and then I spend
usually the afternoons just
chilling, smoking and watching
shit and then at night I just work
constantly and
and sometimes the work doesn't end
that sounds like a pretty good routine honestly
for so long I got into this rut
of just like
timeless nothing where because I had no
structure to my days and it was
just like a meandering like I got a
piss and shit now I got to eat now I got
a computer set on my desk now
where like the months would just
go by and bleed into each other and I wouldn't
know what's happening
it's sounding like you are
going to have to be under quarantine for two weeks
when you get back home
what like self quarantine
I don't know
I don't want to be in a box
what is this
is it a europe thing or is it a UK thing
I don't know may just message me
and said hippo might end up in quarantine
for two weeks when he goes back
we are on a podcast
I don't know if you forgot because these people just
said things randomly but you can continue
what you were saying on this
art that you are supposed to consume
for that to watch
well I guess my point is that once I did
get out of that situation and the whole
furnace room basement era
which was not good
and I know that it was a meme that it was not good
made Jesse sad again guys he was way better
when his life was worse
I made it a meme
that it was not good
I guess so that's true
I made it into a joke
and a meme to cope with it
but that does not really
express exactly how terrible
it really was however bad
I made it out to be it was worse
it was much worse for a very long time
but like
and because of that
I was kind of like stifled
as a human
like not being able to
figure out like what I even
wanted like I couldn't see a light
at the end of the tunnel and like as soon as
like that changed and I got out of it
and like
I'm not saying that everything is great but like
there is a light now and like I have
I have goals and like
I have things I know I can do to reach
those goals but I'm like
as soon as I was out of there
I was able to
like figure out
who the fuck I am now
like when it started I was like
22 and then I became like a
gormless mass of depression
for eight years with no
personality beyond that
and so now I'm like
figuring out and like I had two
epiphanies
that have like almost completely
changed my entire mindset
I realized
for the first time
one that I have always been
a hippie
two that I have always been
a fucking cowboy white trash
hick and now that I finally
cowboy baby
and now that I understand like I finally
realized like all my everything that I feel
all these like emotions
and philosophies that I've internally
that I cannot articulate or express
I finally realized oh wait
it's because I'm literally a fucking hippie
the like the formative
years of my life were spent on
a hippie commune
that's why I am the way I am
and then
I also realized and then before that
I grew up in a fucking trailer park
and I have I've got the hick
in me and like I just need to embrace
that so I started I started like
I really buying all these like crazy
horse albums just like just
injecting Neil Young into my bloodstream
and just I know what you're talking about
when I moved down here it just so happened
that the song that like the new big song
was that
yeah
they said the tax man and I was like
I haven't paid my taxes they took my car
and I got hooked on oxy
code and I was like hey I need drugs
they shut the lights off
hey I don't pay my bills
I want to kill myself too
I feel exactly at home here
so now that I finally understand about myself
that I've always been a hippie cowboy
I can finally like
base my goals and decisions
and the way I live my life
around that and it's been a vast
improvement because now I realize
I do want to wear
flannel and cowboy boots all the time
I do just want to drive around
and like adventure all over America
and like see different cities
and like have Memphis barbecue
and fucking you know and I do just want to
fucking do drugs all the time
and hang out in my bed and be fucking cool
and shit and now that I
figured that out it's like hell yeah
bro
vibin
epic
hey here's a question
who uh by proxy it ten
who was the hottest member of the
pcp in the beach oba
well you'll find out when it releases won't they
I mean are we gonna spec you are we gonna like
me because I was in a hot car
driving you
there were two people
whose ass were out
and uh out and about
those will probably be the ones that
your eyes get drawn to
yeah fair enough for the record
it's me and
hippo
it was me because my makeup was on flea
you're
on about the ass
the visible ass
did he say the ass
well he said who was the hottest
and I said it's the amount of
ass Ben you look awesome
and you should wear it like just all the time
I should I really should
finally
finally I crack the code
you can just
paint a better face on your real face
what is each of your preferred methods
of wiping your ass with no toilet paper
I fucking hate wiping my ass
it is the fucking worst part of my day
every day of my entire life
have you thought about investing in a
he knows
I think about it every goddamn day of
my life on this earth I pray to the gods
please somewhere get me to a place
in life where I can
where I can afford to install a bidet
in my fucking toilet
dude I had a bidet I hated it
how could you hate such a wonderful thing
I mean I tried it once
and it felt horrible and I was like never again
what feels horrible then
like it's like a fucking
scratched paper onto your butthole
no that feels fine
well I wet the toilet paper
so it's gently
wait how do you wet it
what ball it up run it under the faucet
for a second this is the most passionate
I've ever been on the PCP podcast
I hate wiping my ass
I fucking hate it more than anything
in life I've never heard it before
basically you do it before are you shit and then you like
no no it's shit
and then I ball up some toilet paper and then I run it under the faucet
just get it a little wet
if I have to
how far away is the sink from the fucking toilet
most bathrooms are not that big
you cannot get up after
you have to wipe and then get up
you cannot get up
wait wait
when you get up
you're walking and watering around and it's just spreading your shit
yeah no it's spraying shit
you can do it in a way
that like your cheeks don't move
and you don't get shit over your ass
you squat and knock
well I mean just like a little
like a bird
like in my bathroom
all I have to do is just kind of twist to the side a little bit
and I get
all I have to do from the toilet
is like twist it a little bit to the side
and I can get it wet and it's fine
you're fucking disgusting
you don't even fucking wet your toilet paper when you fucking wet
where would I meet you
I can share me an ultrasonic
it's just fucking spot
it's you cleaner
okay I'm gonna waste water
I'll tell you
that's shit
there was somebody who called into the dick show
one time because dick swears by the bidet
and this man said
if you got shit on any other part of your body
would you only use a dry
implement to wash it off
this is true I thought about this
shut the shit down I gotta step in
I want to have a story because I use the bidet in Japan
if you want to hear the bidet story
that's a fucking nightmare
second of all let's get fucking wet wipes
yeah that's just basically
use wet wipes
wait hold on he's not galaxy brain
because I have a problem with wiping my ass
and it might just be
because I'm unhealthy and fat
but this motion
causes my rib
this area you are fat
sear with pain
go under the front
hold on
you get your balls
oh sweaty on
my argument
wet wipes are not
are you not wiping your ass because you're in pain
no I am wiping my ass
I'm just fucking suffering that's why I'm saying
wiping your ass sucks
what's your preferred method of wiping your ass
when there's no toilet paper
I don't understand the question
if you don't have toilet paper how do you wipe your ass
there's only one way
you stick your ass over the sink
and you just wash it with water
and you just wash that
of course I've done that before
that's enough you have to
if you don't have toilet paper
you don't have to sink and not the shower
I mean if you don't have toilet paper
I guess my first emergency method
would be like well maybe
I'll just like find a paper towel
and then I'll just vary
I will tell you that I have both had to use the paper towel
I've had to use the just jump in the shower
yeah just jump in the shower
yeah
in Vietnam they use leaves
where do you get leaves when you're in your bathroom
I mean well they shit out in the woods
this is a topical question to ask
because toilet paper
sold out everywhere because America's retarded
and you know this question
that's why I always keep leaves in my purse
because I don't have toilet paper
unironically isn't that
one of the reasons Japanese people carry around
those tissues
because like in a lot of Asian countries
those are the only toilet paper
the fuck that's a terrible kind of toilet paper
in the Philippines
public bathrooms almost never have toilet paper
aren't there like some like weird like
limitations of like certain places in Asia
where you can only use like X amount of squares
of toilet paper and then you're fucked
and then you're on your own after that
but the actual answer to this was
like okay you either find toilet paper
or you do what you gotta do without toilet paper
and in some situations
that's just gonna get fucked
we're in a public restroom
about the idea of just using my hands
and then washing my hands afterwards
unironically, yeah
you gotta do it
you have the tools
it's literally easier to wash your hands
than your butt, we should all be wiping with our hands
I mean kind of
that is the way
I don't sign off on this
wait, I will never shake hands again
if this becomes the cold shoulder
it's due to all the motions though
it's easier to wash your hands
it's just more work from the think of it
all you'd be doing is smearing shit with your hands
no, not true because I mean you can get yourself
there's just no good solution to the problem
of shit and there never will be
it drives me bonkers
unironically had the thought that like
toilet paper is a sign that we are still
barely out of the fucking cave
we haven't even gotten to the three
seashells yet
one day I'm gonna become elevated
hey, here's a totally separate question
we might have answered this before
but it's just a good one on a occasion such as this
is it full of rifa?
wait, wait, wait, before you do that
I wanna adjust this, because son of Marowak
said to talk about the failure of the poll yesterday
and he was mad all day because
okay, we played
Super Smash Bros. last night
because at the moment
that Nate checked the poll
Super Smash Bros. was ahead by one point
by the time we started
streaming this was no longer the case
Scott Pilgrim was winning
there had to be a cutoff point
it was just that moment when Nate
looked at his phone that he said
smash is ahead by one point, that's what we're playing
so to you it seems like a cruel deception
but in reality it was just bureaucratic
delays caused
this incident
but perhaps we'll make it right
in the future, we'll see
okay, is it full of rifa? just ask
what video should I introduce
you to new people as the PCP
any suggestions?
did he mean specifically the PCP
or like each of us in the video?
sure
Nate, who? what?
it's gotta be Ben
you're in log in part 1 and part 2
or like I would say
for your videos, if you're into smash
watch any of the smash videos
it depends what they want to see
my favorite
best guy ever video
is Uncovered Final Fantasy 15
and Head in Hell
and Evening in Hell
that one is probably
incomprehensible if you don't know
what the fuck was going on
which nobody did, so the video is incomprehensible
basically everybody but me and you
happened to witness this weird
Final Fantasy event
but also
I have a BGE Essentials playlist
for a reason, I choose
to be all the best contents in there
so link up that playlist
but also
what would be the best for getting into the PCP though?
just like episode 1
I mean there's probably better episodes
things we can't get into
is the one that most people see
your thing last night
was unironically
kind of fulfilled that function
at least in terms of
finally being
able to explain some part
of this madness that is my life
in a way that makes sense to me
I did like that about it
but that's free PCP history
means it needs to die
the first episode was me
on it
that one's good too
things I can't get into the episode
there's your easy answer
there's a helicopter
there's a big loud noise
I know a loud man, Munchy
what should people get into for you?
it's gotta know
that you have to
get into this warplay
you basically have to know who me and Ben are already
I would say either
first episode of Armour Treeble
and then follow that through
and read Humphduck with us
The Deal Nation Lecture obviously is a classic
and then if not that
then The Spice of Bro packed
or still in your dad
the first live episode
any of those
I guess give or you
for me
readBailJap
old-school underground mix tape which is where I took a bunch of my best
verses from all my other albums and made like a very accessible version of them
so like that album is pretty much just designed to be like your intro to
Digi Bro music kind of experience. I always really like the art is all about pushing your buttons or
turning that one. Art is all about pushing your buttons. It's the first thing in the
essential Digi Bro playlist. The essential Digi Bro playlist is not a collection of my best
videos but just the ones that I think if you watch them. Found in Ideology. Right,
because so much of the way I talk about shows is different from other critics
and it confuses a lot of people and so it's like if you watch these videos
you'll understand where I'm coming from and like art is all about pushing your
buttons is the first one in there because it's just to explain like look I'm not
always gonna talk about every element of every show. I'm gonna talk about the
interesting elements of every show that pushed my button like what stood out to
me because that's what makes the experience meaningful to me. Also we
have accepted mediocrity also an excellent video. That is a good one as well.
Tom where should they go for you? Just go to my Twitter I guess I mean that's where I'm just living right now.
At Tommy Oliver Says on Twitter you can play. You need it Tom. You gotta get your fucking website out so you can start killing people.
It's halfway done. I was working on it before. Obviously you can't have made any
progress on it while at Roundcon but it's just driving me crazy because I go to
your Twitter and it is a useless way to like get into you because you tweet way
more than just your own art. Yeah well yeah I have also made it into
Zoomy Twitter but I haven't done anything like that. It's like I get it Tom you support
Gamergate. I don't need to repeat it.
Hashtag not your shield. The fight continues. It's not over yet.
The Endless War Twitter and the Zoomy Twitter should like ERP.
Have you seen what I've been doing with the Endless War Twitter lately?
Yeah of course. It's just like key words Endless War, Slime, Retweet.
I just searched the word Slime. I just find like funny Slime posts on Twitter and just retweet all of them.
So Ben how about you?
I mean I guess I would say my comics at stcomics.com.
If it was a video I guess I would say depending on which way the wind blows for you either the
Sonichu lecture or the Nuzlocke one. Yeah the Nuzlocke.
It's probably starting with Genesis. I'll probably do another one at some point.
I don't know when but like oh I was thinking of doing one with Temtem.
I was thinking of Nuzlocke and Temtem. I don't know.
But it's like in beta pre-release right now. So I probably wouldn't do it until it's a season full release.
Do you want anyone to get into you at all? Do you want that?
Patreon.com slash Endless Jest of course right? Yeah.
I mean Patrons where everybody should go. Just give us money. We promise it's worth it.
Oh yeah Patreon.com slash Give and Take. Ben St.
I got 50 bonus podcasts. Patreon.com in general. Everyone know what Patreon is.
We literally all have Patreon. Everyone knows. Yes I don't.
He's got only fans though. I will after this.
Send me that link as soon as it's live.
AshleyMadison.com slash MunchieJ.
I don't want to tell my dad about this. Don't worry.
Check out my Seeking Arrangements page. Looking for a baby daddy type situation.
I'm the baby. No.
Well I mean we pretty much got through all the...
Wait I didn't answer.
What? You didn't answer?
I think we're pretty much done. I mean we could go on.
Are you done? They're not just you speak.
No. The best video to get into my stuff. I peaked very early with a video called Reapers.
Reapers. If you are into Mass Effect then yeah.
I'll tell you how you get into Jesse is you watch the fuck series.
Those are the most easy accessible videos.
Yeah I guess.
And they're all hilarious.
The way I got into Jesse was fuck cars.
And I need you to understand how young I am and how old you are.
When you made that video I watched it.
And then I showed it to all my friends at the library in sixth grade.
You know the funny thing about that video is when I watch it back.
It's like so obvious to me that first that I was just starting out and trying to figure out what my voice was.
And second that I had just started listening to a lot of Bill Burr.
Yes.
I'm just talking like Bill Burr in that video.
Yeah. It's very noticeable that you're really confident that you are like a Bill Burr AVGN.
Yeah.
That's me. The Bill Burr AVGN.
I mean if you're going to be something it's not a bad thing to be.
But other than that actually you know what? One video, the one video to get into endless stress I would pick sound criminals.
Yeah. Sound criminals and everyone loves unanimously.
Like the one video I've made that everyone unanimously enjoys is the autumn video.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
People like really, people blow smoke up my ass about that autumn video all the time.
And so cool.
I guess that must be the one.
I don't like, honestly like everyone, it seems like a lot of time people talk about me and they're like, oh endless Jess.
Hoshu finale, meta stuff, standing in front of a bookcase angry yelling at the camera man.
It's like, dude like when he grew the neck beard.
Yeah.
When he grew the neck beard it really came into his own.
All that, but like this, I guess this is how I've evolved.
Like I hate all of that shit.
Embarrassed of all of it.
None of it matters to me.
The Crystal Empire video is still an old favorite.
The Colt Corona.
Oh yeah.
Colt Corona is gold.
I will never, I will never not love Colt Corona.
He's one of the best things that ever came out of me.
He is my son and I love him forever.
Him crawling out of that little baby castle.
Yeah.
Stuck with him so powerfully to this day.
Everything involving Colt Corona is gold and will always be.
It's true.
I think like my, but my favorite videos of mine.
I think it's possible.
I've never seen this.
Reasons I love auto videos.
You've never seen.
I saw it.
I don't remember it.
Yeah.
They were gross.
Oh yeah.
I have a like on it.
So clearly I did watch it.
I also really like the Arnold's Thanksgiving one that I did, but I don't think anyone fucking
gave a shit about that video.
I do remember that one, but I also remember the best Christmas episodes one, which also
the Hey Arnold holiday analysis, which is also great video.
I just as, as my tone evolved, like to the less like trying to be like hostile and cool
and like ego guy to the more like laid back stuff like the other, like that's the tone
that I like the most.
And the videos of mine that I like to watch back the most are like the not a reviews.
Yeah.
Those are all good because they're like, those are like the fucking not a review on which
in the hundred night is the only place where my opinions on me, Ponichi have been expressed
on the internet.
Well, those are like the most pure because like those are like deliberately the least
ego driven videos.
That was like kind of the point of them.
And that's kind of why they're called not a reviews because like I'm saying in the title,
you don't have to take this seriously.
This is not.
And so like, and saying that up front, freeze me to just goof off and say whatever dumb
shit I want and not have to act like it's important.
Not a review is such a good title because you immediately like give yourself a free
pass.
But you also get the search result of exact review.
Most of those videos are good.
And I like them.
And everything else I've ever done is shameful disgrace.
But we're not what you just said.
Are you saying that we've exited the hostile and cool faces just and they're the warm
and gay phase.
Warm and gay.
Is that a reference?
No.
It's just.
It's just pure organic.
It's just good.
I think we have one last question to exit on here guys.
It's how much capitalized do you guys love each other question mark question mark question
mark?
A lot.
Hey, hey, everypony.
Welcome to the fucking sub dick show.
No one even fucking slightly cared about anything that just happened the past thursday.
No.
It's good.
Guys, I slept like three and a half hours last night.
My warm and fuzziness is at an all time low.
You just can't.
I cannot stand a single one of you.
Well, let's just address.
Oh, thank god.
The reason we do rad cons.
I don't know why.
We don't have a meetup so we could go to anymore because we all like being around each other
and just we all say it and then it just comes true that when we are together it's just a
way good time and it's just always nice to hang out so I'm real happy for it.
So somebody suggested Jay and I said, hey, why don't you guys all sing a song together?
Oh, I'm supposed to be working right now.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Myself, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
Yeah.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Thank you.
Thanks everybody.
See you later.
See you in another 200 episodes.