Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben Saint and
this is Gibbontake.
That's about the, oh god, what's the phrase? That's about the long and short of it. That's
about the, that's true.
That's about a spicy meatball. That's a Moray. That's a me, Mario. That's a me, Mario.
No, sometimes it was just a week goes by and then I'm like, oh, a week went by and nothing
really happened.
Yeah, I feel like we just did the last one. I mean, what did I do this week? This week
I watched GameStop Plummet.
Oh, yeah. What about that? You had some, didn't you?
Yeah. And in fact, I bought a little, I bought some more as it continued to go down. And in
fact, I have an order to buy even more if it goes down further.
Ben, sounds like being stupid is what this means.
No. I mean, it's, I mean, it's so cheap now that like, why not? Right?
I have heard like the narrative of like, this is hurting the billionaires is sort of being
perpetuated, like, in bad faith by people who were who like started the whole thing.
Like they wanted people to buy into it and to put money into it because then they'd be
rich from the stocks that they bought initially.
There's a smaller amount of people who got off.
There was an incentive to like push that, that like the narrative of that further and
further, even if it wasn't necessarily true. I think I've learned like since then that
it's not as clean as, oh, the billionaires all lost money. Lots of other people did make
money.
It's not like I don't think it's not like I don't think that the people doing it had
a vested interest in pushing that angle to encourage people to jump on the bandwagon.
But I don't see how it like wasn't actually Melvin Capital versus retail investors.
Like that is what it was.
Largely, I wish I could remember exactly like the way it was explained to me, but it was,
there was this, what was it, like financial something blog that I read.
I'm stupid. I can't remember it.
I think that's us, honestly. I mean, do I trust?
Well, it was quite well written. Like it acknowledged that the, you know, it's definitely
hurting some people, but like ultimately the people who, you know, the game of chicken
sort of thing, like the last people are more hurt by buying in when it's at the top.
And then I know it's just sort of, I don't know, I feel a little differently about like
how it's because it's gone down now. It's it's less doing anything and people who got
into it at the peak of the hype, maybe just ended up losing a lot of money and not doing
a lot of damage to the billionaires that they were trying to do.
And it sucks for them. That's this is, this is, this is a terrible argument.
This is a terrible argument. Like, yes, obviously, obviously, if you bought at the peak and it's
gone down, you've lost money. No shit. No. This is why I shouldn't have brought it up,
because I can't remember the argument, because it was quite compelling. I was like, I guess, I guess,
yeah, fuck it, whatever. I was just trying to make conversation because I'm on the Procrastinators
podcast. Why would you, why would you try and make conversation with me? Why would you do that?
Why would you try and be on the Procrastinators podcast? I don't know, Ben, maybe it's because
I like you, maybe it's because I like talking to you. Shut up.
Okay. I think there are two ways to look at it. You could say like, oh, okay, the Wall Street
Bets people pushed the narrative that, oh, we're going to stick it to the billionaires.
And it was just a, you know, that was just their angle. But I mean, you could just as easily say,
oh, you know, some financial blog or whatever, or some like some other, some other investor,
who knows what their motives are. I mean, maybe they want to do that because they want to throw
these, you know, the retail investor under the bus. They want to make like a pro-capital argument.
I feel like those two things are like both entirely possible.
I just think that it was sold as a lot more simplistic for like to get people interested in
investing to the detriment of a lot of people who put too much money into it and have lost
quite a lot. There's the thing that was going around like Wall Street Bets have been like
suppressing posts that are talking about people like losing all of their money.
It's not Wall Street Bets fault. If somebody bet everything, if somebody invested more than
they were willing to lose and then they lost it. I mean, I don't know. Is there no culpability
at all? Yes. Like even slightly for exaggerating the harm that is being done to the billionaires
and because like none of these, well, not none of them, I guess.
Nobody knew how it was going to shake out. In fact, nobody even really knows how it's
shaken up because it's still an open question whether they've covered their shorts or not.
I think my issue is I'm quite a cautious person. I took my time. I didn't want to jump in straight
away and I kind of waited too long for it for me to even jump in at all. Then it turns out I can't
even do Robin Hood and other things are not as good. So it's like, well, whatever, fuck it.
It's like a fidelity account like me. Yeah, but a lot of people who got into this
obviously, they didn't know how the stock market worked exactly and they were going
off of what other people were telling them and a lot of people went into all of this
quite uninformed as to the repercussions. I don't understand your argument. Yeah,
they shouldn't have done that. I think I just dislike hype a lot in general and this is one
of those instances where maybe the hype caused more damage than was necessary.
Speaking as someone who literally lost money because of the hype, it's my fault. It's my fucking
problem. Yeah, I just feel like there's trying to be like, it's difficult to say, oh, morally you
should, I don't know, put a warning. I don't know what the solution would be.
It just sucks that if not all the information is given and there's hype, people are going to
do things emotionally and I don't know. I don't know enough to make a really strong argument here,
but I'm just saying. I just think people are responsible for themselves.
Who's fault? I mean, this was not like, there was that one guy, a deep fucking value, but
he wasn't the one running the whole hype machine. He was kind of behind the whole plan,
but it's not like he was out there. None of them knew that it was going to blow up like that.
Yeah, that's true. It's not like I'm trying to blame somebody for other people losing money.
That's not the way I'm thinking about it. Here's my issue. Let's assume that as an
actually the shorts have been covered, like the whole thing is done, it is down and it is
going to stay down and continue to go down. There is no more gasoline left in the GME machine.
It is a lost cause. It was a failed attempt and it didn't work. It spiked for a minute and that's
it. I mean, that could be the case. It's pretty likely, it's fairly likely the case, but nobody
knew how it was going to shake out. It was not known that that would be the result.
So it can be true, both things can be true, that the stick it to the billionaire sentiment
was sincerely meant and that did not occur. I know, I absolutely believe that it was
sincerely meant at first or at least majority of people were like, I'm not saying the narrative
is completely false. I'm just saying that there was an invested interest in certain people who
got into it early to keep the narrative going. And I was saying like the on Wall Street bets,
the Reddit thread, people's posts about how they got into it because of the hype and they've lost
their life savings. Stupid, obviously they're at fault for that. But those posts were being like
suppressed to give the impression that it was a lot more successful for everyone than it was.
When you say suppressed, when you say suppressed, I mean, I mean, the like the front page of
Wall Street bets was covered in people like, and it was the same thing on like on like the
when I was in Bitcoin, I would sometimes look at the Bitcoin subreddit, and it was the same thing
then it like the front pages is covered in posts that are super fucking bullish that are all like
this shit's going to the moon, the shit's gonna go as high as this is gonna go infinitely high,
we're all gonna make a million dollars because that's what people want to see. And that's what
gets upvoted. And that's what, you know, that's what ends up getting most visibility. That's
just how red it works. I guess, sure, I heard that people's posts were being deleted, not that
they were just not getting upvotes. But I, I haven't looked into it myself. I just heard that it was
on a Wall stream. Well, here's okay. Okay. Aside from the the GME thing, right? That's that's the
thing. I'm very annoyed. I'm very annoyed about Dogecoin. I don't like it. Yeah, I don't know
what's been going on with that. Exactly. Well, basically, while the GME thing was going on,
I don't know if it was all Elon, but like Elon was in part of it. And every time Elon tweets
about anything, like, the market does weird shit. So Elon et al, while the GME thing was going on,
he was like, Oh, dogecoin to the moon. And then it did. And it's like, it went up pretty high. And
I like saw it shooting up. And I tried to get a Robinhood account to get some. And they didn't
approve. They only approved me like, like two days ago, like my and I don't need I don't even know
if I want to use it anymore. And I don't know, I thought it was just going to spike momentarily,
but like, it's still going up, it's it's gone up even more today, it's almost back up to like
where it peaked at the time. So like, it's still rising. And that's fine. That's fine and everything.
But I'm it really pisses me off that like the GME thing was like, okay, we can be skeptical of a
one, but supposedly it was like about something. It was like, Oh, let's like, you know, little guy
beat the hedge fund managers, it was about something. And then Elon et al, just make just do like,
hey, guys, look at this other thing, haha, funny dogecoin meme currency, crypto of the people.
And like, that's fine. It's fine that people made money on that. But it's really, I think it's
really despicable of Elon to like, do that at that moment, like what, why did the why what was
the need for it? It didn't even have anything to do with it. It's just like, at a moment,
people were thinking about stocks, he was like, Hey, look at this other stock.
And it worked. I mean, yeah, people love Elon, but like, what's despicable about mentioning it,
even knowing that it would like spike dogecoin? Well, I don't know. I mean, for one thing,
maybe people who might have been considering the GME thing might have been diverted to doge.
Right. Okay. I mean, the fervor was about GME and AMC and Nokia and all that.
And dogecoin didn't have anything to do with it. But I don't know,
because it's funny and because it's Elon. I mean, it's, there's a lot of reddit energy
in the entire thing. It's, it's just sort of like, haha, like, I don't know anything about this stuff.
But it's like, what everyone else is doing. Oh, cool. Elon's also tweeting about this other
thing that's also money related. Haha, that's really funny doge. Very currency much. Wow.
Yes, I know. That's, that's what I said, and it makes me really mad. Yeah, I mean, I suppose.
I don't know. I mean, it's not, it's not just sour grapes, because like, I'm fine. I'm fine with
the fact. Okay, on the one hand, on the one hand, like, I, yeah, I do, it's not, it's not about the
fact that like people made money. It's about the fact that Elon got his way. That's what makes me mad.
Yeah. Also, yeah, if you, if Elon owns dogecoin, this is like, wait, does he?
I don't, I don't know. I mean, he might or he might or he might not.
I thought I've heard that it was made by some of, I guess, whoever made it doesn't necessarily have
most of it. Not necessarily. Um, that's the thing that like, fucking, that McAfee, I saw
like a little YouTube documentary about John McAfee, and apparently he would do a thing where he
would invest in crypto and then he would do like a public circuit, appearance circuit, talking about
the crypto, pump up its value by getting it exposure, and then just sell it, right? So I don't
know if Elon's doing that, but like, if he owns, if he owns dogecoin, or anything that he tweets
about. It probably, I mean, like if he sees like, oh, all of these Reddit bros are getting interested
in stocks and shares and investing, maybe if I get some dogecoin, I can get them to pivot over
to investing in the thing that makes me more money. Maybe. It would, it would be uncharacteristically
intelligent for Elon Musk. So I don't know. I mean, he knows how to make money.
Uh, and I'm sure he, he understands, I'm sure he understands like what his, what his tweets
tend to do to the market. Like that time that he tweeted that like his, the Tesla stock was too high,
and then it went down. I just hate him. I just really hate him. And I am upset that he, that's
something that he likes happened. That's pretty much the long and short of it.
Preach. Yeah. I feel like that, like generally speaking, all of this stuff is just made,
like the major good, I think, is just letting a lot of people understand how fucking fake everything
is in terms of like finances. A lot of people become disillusioned to it. And that's,
you know, good because it's true. And now they know, but yeah, there's not much that can be done
about it immediately. But I think, I mean, yeah, I think, I mean, everyone already knew.
Well, I don't think everyone knew quite to the extent because everyone's just heard of stocks.
And they don't really, like the layman, the layman doesn't know quite how like
manipulative stock people are. They just assume, well, they're just doing things. I don't know.
They make money by, like they have no idea that it's all based on, I don't know,
deliberately fucking with real people. It is a good example of like the economy being
imaginary. I mean, I don't think it's gonna, I mean, I don't think it's gonna have like
convinced that many people that like didn't already have that opinion, you know.
I guess not. Well, I guess that's the case of like everything. I guess it's all just like
death by a thousand cuts, you know, like in terms of like showing like people understanding that
like, oh, the system is rigged. I mean, I think you're right. And that a lot of people know that
things are rigged and, and like, it's not fair. And there's like a class of people at the top
that are too powerful. And it sucks. There's just different difference in opinion of like,
why, whether that's a problem. And if there is someone at the top, who is it? And what should
we do about it? Some people would think it's the Jews that are at the top, which is dumb.
Laws, right? That's good. Yeah. And then other people would think that it's not a problem
because they want to be at the top. Yeah. So it's like, yeah. Man, the mindset of like,
the mindset of like, imagine believing that like, whoever is at the top, like,
obviously deserves to be there because they are there. And if they didn't deserve to be there,
they wouldn't be there. They must have, they must have earned it somehow, right? Like,
like, like things must be fair. Like the world must be a fair place where merit is rewarded.
Therefore, whoever is at the top must deserve it and must also be the best person in addition to
being the most successful because how because it would just be fucked up if it were any other way.
So yeah, it can't be. Well, feel a lot of that, feel a lot of that attitude.
When I go to fucking Twitter, and I see these fucking liberals replying to Brooklyn dad Defiant,
that filthy weenie piece of shit about that lady smashing her guitar and saying it's racist that
she did that. Yeah, what the hell was that? I didn't catch all of it. I only recently. I don't
know. I don't know. It was, I guess, I guess some band performed on SNL and like the woman
guitarist smashed her guitar and Brooklyn dad Defiant is like, um, what's up with that?
And all these filthy, these filthy goblins in the reply is like, um, a real display
of unwarranted white privilege. Oh, do you know that starving Africans would love to eat that
guitar? And just, just as opposed to warranted white privilege as opposed to warranted white
privilege, um, I don't know, just like a, just like a bunch of liberal hand rigging over shit that
doesn't matter. It really doesn't matter. Literally just like rock, literally just like rock and roll
is dangerous and gonna end up corrupt our kids like so uncouth. I don't know how these people
take them so seriously. Like in a in an abstract sort of way, you could say, oh, she has the money
to smash guitar because she knows she can buy another one. But like that's so like irrelevant
to everything. Okay. Okay. The thing, the thing about that, the thing about that is how, how
fucking dog brain we do you have to be to like, okay, there's the guitar that she's smashing
couple hundred dollars versus like this woman is appearing on SNL, right? Like that is like,
oh, this woman who's appearing on SNL, you know, that's fine. But like smashing a guitar is just
an unwarranted display of privilege. Are you fucking kidding me? Like that's like the guitar is
nothing. Right. If you're trying to like criticize power should be like, oh, this is like the, you
know, here's here's a person who's getting this like huge, this huge platform to like promote
themselves, you know, this is this is like, this is a huge, a huge opportunity that represents
like a massive, you know, potential future earnings for this person. It's so much more than the guitar,
right? The guitar is like, is like a, a mode of dust in the, in the, in the avalanche of what this
event that you are witnessing is. It could be that being, being on SNL means that she has the
money potential to smash that guitar, whereas before she didn't. And it's like, I mean, I,
I mean, I would, I mean, I would think it was stupid and dumb to be like, um, no one should be
on SNL because that means they have too much privilege. Like, I, like, I would think that's
stupid too, but at least you would be like, you know, you wouldn't be missing the forest
for the trees quite so much, right? If you want to hyper focus on something stupid.
Surface level, woke brigade stuff. Yeah. Right. Right.
That's what that's what was making me mad today.
Did you see, did you see Chris Chan tweeting the, the slime coin and the pins?
That's so fucking cool. So fucking cool. She's got the red man pin and the red man pin.
She's got it all. And, uh, and then a predict, predictably a bunch of like, a bunch of like,
very obviously mentally ill people, just like swarming in the replies to be like, um, Chris is
bad. Um, Chris, you are. Yeah, I got one of those. I muted the conversation. Posting an ugly picture
of you, posting an ugly picture of you, like screaming at a web camera to, to own you, followed
by, followed by a gift, a funny gift of a dog going, what? To make you look foolish. Haha.
I, I don't get it. I mean, I guess I understand, um, like if you're so like frothing at the
mouth, like raging that you would do that to every tweet they post. It just sort of,
it's the same people. It's got nothing to do with anything. It's just, it's the same people.
Christian is, is showing that she got a box with stuff in it. Look at this. Oh yeah. Well,
you're Chris Chan. So. Oh yeah. Well, look at this, like ugly drawing someone did of you, stupid.
It's, it's the same people too. Like I've seen some of these like accounts. I mean,
some of these accounts are just explicitly called like, you know, Son of Choo fucker 666 or whatever.
So like this is a dedicated account for this purpose. And others just seem to be like, others
just seem to be like, otherwise kind of normal looking people, but who like just are following
Chris just to do this stuff. And it's people with like, it's people with like six followers who,
I don't know, other than that, like they just like, I don't know, retweet like announcements
about Marvel movies or whatever. It's like, like a crossed arm reaction channels, you know,
those, those sort of things where they're just, it's got that sort of vibe to it where it's like
they're, they're very angry and very insistent on things that are really unimportant all the time.
And they all tend to have their arms crossed with their angry furry avatars, nothing against
furries, but it is funny. Okay, there is one, there is one person though. Okay, there, there are
a few people who are the same, except instead of posting like, I hate you, they post like,
looks nice Chris or whatever. And these are some of these people also have like, Son of Choo and
Rose. These are like, young or young or like, either young or mentally handicapped artists
who draw, you know, Son of Choo fan art, and they, you know, they have their own little click in this,
in this weird. I would tend to assume it's more that they're, they're like mentally handicapped,
because I don't know if Son of Choo is like a hot thing that the kids are into at all.
Well, no, but I mean, there could be some. If there's, if there's any kids around, it's the
people making the, the, I hate you, Chris Chan accounts, the 14 year olds who like go to cringe
compilations. That's probably true. But, but there's this one person who honestly, like,
gives me a very uncomfortable vibe. And it's not for any reason you might think this person,
this, this girl, she, she replies to things. And everything she says is a reply that's like,
do your best. It might not be much, but I know you're doing the best you can.
Heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart. And like all her posts on Twitter are like
comics that she's drew, she's drawn, she's not very good at drawing, but whatever,
she'll post like a page of her comic and be like, I know it's not much, but I'm doing the best I can.
And it's so creepy. I do not like it at all.
But they're doing the best they can, Ben.
I don't know what's going on there. It was like, no, she, she posted this
in response, like I posted the crystal, the crystal Chris sent me and she replies,
it's not much, but I know whatever it is, I'm sure it's wonderful. And then a bunch of like
heart, gift boxes, emojis. I, what's the, what, why say it's not, I don't know, doesn't look like
much. I don't know. I know that I'm, I know that I am like seeing mental illness here and I probably
like should just, I don't know. I probably shouldn't worry about it, but it's, it's, it's
sad. Like it's, it's like, it's stressing me. It's distressing me. This person seems to be in a,
in a bad way. This is like their mode of operation. And I'm strained optimism at all times.
I mean, she sounds, I mean, all of her tweets sound like she's trying to make the best of a
situ, of a situation that she is on the verge of tears over. And that's regardless of like,
whether it's like she's, she made something and wants people to see it, or just other people
are having a completely unrelated conversation. Oh boy. I mean, it could be sad. It could just
be learned behavior from hearing, like if it's a, if it's a mental thing, like an autism thing.
There's a lot of, when you're talking to someone, I don't know, I don't know, like specific scientific
like things of, of this is this mental illnesses. This is that one. But sometimes like you'll hear
them repeat phrases that the parents have obviously said to them and things they've heard on TV.
And, and so little of like their actual thoughts on things. Oh yeah. Gotta make the best of the
situation. I may be that a parent who was upset that they were handicapped and they
tried to make the best of the situation where it's like, I don't know, I could see that happening.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess I could see that. Sometimes I, there are some, some tweets I see and some
like accounts that I see tweeting over and over again, give me a vibe that is like weird in some way.
And I'm like, sometimes I get a little like weirded out and like kind of fucked up about it, like,
God, this person, this person seems like really fucked up. This person is like, kind of scarier,
like it's depressing to contemplate what this person is like. But like, I don't know, a lot of
the time, I don't remember like how many times have I like known someone online who's weird and
then I meet them in person and like they're not as like bizarre as they seem on the internet.
I try to tell myself like probably most of the time that's, that's what, that's the case. Disabled
people are not that strange unless they're like an extreme case. Like you can, you can hold a
conversation with them. They may not have like much like interesting things to say, but like
it's, they're generally normal. They just have like weird fascinations with specific things.
Yeah. Yeah. And, and repeat phrases that they've heard rather than learning how to, I don't know,
come up with a run. You know what? Like honestly, the, like the, the fact that this, this account is
like so, it's so consistent, which makes me think maybe you're right. Maybe they just, they learned
this, this, this behavior or this, these phrases and I'll just kind of like, I'll just say that.
Yeah. That makes sense. I don't know. It's a whole, it's a whole, it's a whole milieu. It's a whole,
like, it's a whole cadre of people that just start around to respond in whatever preset way
they have decided on doing whenever Chris says anything. Oh, yeah. Oh, never,
whenever Chris says anything. No, no, I'm just thinking about disabled people in general.
Oh, okay. They feel to me, because I've, I've worked like, like volunteered. I've told that before,
like volunteer work for helping disabled people in like summer camp stuff. And they seem so much
easier to just be around because they're so lacking in judgment. They're like a normal person.
That makes them easier to be around? Well, huh? That makes them easier to be around?
Yeah. Cause they're just, I don't know, like for lack of a better term, I can think of,
they're simpler. They, they have what they like and they don't assume a lot because they find it
difficult to understand a lot of things. Obviously, things will set them set them off, make them
upset, like they have emotions and stuff. But like, if you're, you know, amenable to them and
it's, you're not like doing anything that annoys them. They're just, they're a lot less, I don't
know, I feel less at ease when I'm among teenage normal people, like non-disabled teenagers than
I am disabled people. Well, yeah. Cause who knows what like regular teenagers are scheming?
Like who knows what they're plotting behind your back? They're laughing at you. They're laughing at
you when you're not, when you're not looking. They're laughing at me because I don't know something.
But when it's disabled people, you're laughing at them behind their back. So it's much, much more
comfortable. No, it's not true. It's true. I know. I walk to, I see a disabled person,
I chuckle to myself, but I know they won't mind because they didn't hear it. I go,
you go, what a, what a rube. And then they show me their Thomas the Tank engine
sticker book and I'm like, oh yeah, cool. Nice. You got, oh yeah, cool, but on the inside you're
like loser. Who the fuck has stickers these days? Chris told me that I should make decal sheets
of the pin designs. That's the thing where like you, that's the thing where like it's on like the
back of plastic and like you rub it onto something, right? I've heard of decals for like cars. I assume
yeah, you could do that on phones and other things. Yeah, I'm not sure what that is. Yeah,
it's like a sticker, but it's like, it's like a sticker, but instead of like sticking the material
onto it, it has like the image is like on the back of the plastic and you put the plastic on a thing
and you like scrape the front and it like transfers the image directly onto the thing, right? So it's
like a permanent sticker with no like plastic layer that it's printed on, which I mean, I could do
that, I guess. I could do that, I guess. Oh, the profit margins wouldn't be there. It's all about
that profit margin. The thing I would equate it to, by the way, is not like, they have less of a
judgmental side mostly because their mental faculties are like kind of young compared to the
physical age of their body. So they'll have like, you know, a brain of a 10 year old or whatever.
And children, you don't laugh at them for being into whatever. I do. Well, yeah, sure. Stomping
on kids all day. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Kick them when they're down and they're always down because
they're short. Yeah, but it's just like working with kids that they're very like simple and easy
to understand and they don't judge you too much. Anyone too old is like, ah, this is like, there
could be drama with this person if they might have ideas that I disagree with. Ah, fuck. Why can't
people just be into weird things? They might be a Pete Buttigieg supporter. If somebody has
that Pete Buttigieg sticker book, I'm not going to. Hey, watch this. Look at my Pete Buttigieg
doodles. It's like, no, I'm not going to. That's not cute. That's not nice.
Did you see that? Did you see that drawing of Ronald Reagan? The one that like, it was like a
Congresswoman did, right? Like a 30 something Congresswoman did like a child's fucking like
pencil sketch of Ronald Reagan and she has it hanging in her office. Yeah. What is it with
Congresswoman these days? I don't get it. What's going on? Well, I mean, I'll tell you is that the
GOP doesn't have any standards. The GOP will just elect any fucking person who it says that they,
I don't know, will continue austerity politics. I can't, I mean, I didn't pay attention to the
politicians and senators and whatever or MPs. I didn't pay attention to all that when I was
young. So I maybe people this insane have been being voted in for decades and I never noticed,
but now that I'm more like, like, like, it's just so bizarre to think someone could be that
brazenly stupid and then get elected. I mean, most people don't pay that much attention to like,
you know, they're like district representatives. Sure. Yeah. Like that's below a lot of people's
radar. So like in some counties, you can get elected for that kind of thing with like relatively
fewer votes than you might think. And nevertheless, you fucking work in the Capitol building after
that because I don't know. Yeah. Not to say that a badly drawn picture of Ronald Reagan is stupid,
it's just very cringe. I don't know why you would be proud of that drawing. I mean, it,
I mean, it is stupid. I mean, because it's, I mean, it's, I mean, imagine you're an adult,
you're an adult and you're like, look, I drew this. First of all, it's terrible. Some people cannot see
their inability to do artistic things. I don't know whether that's necessarily a sign of lack of
intelligence. Maybe it is. It is. Of course it is. Well, I don't know. I don't know whether I sound
good when I'm singing. When you, when you, when you, okay. I mean, it's cringe because it's a bad
drawing and she like didn't recognize that too. It's, it's bad to like, look, I, I, it's just a
bad thing that like I do, I like this, this politician so much that I like drew them and I
hung it in my office. Like that is quite childish. Like, no, like that would be true even if it was
a good drawing. And the third and most importantly, it's Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan is a, is a
fucking a dogfucker who is in hell. So nobody should, nobody should like him.
Dude. So that's, it's a three pronged cringe attack.
Ronald Reagan, Donald Trump.
You need I say more?
No, please don't.
Uh, um.
There are new candidate, John Old Jefferson.
John Old, John Old MacDonald.
John Old Tron.
John Old Tron 2024.
How, how long is it going to be until a streamer is like running for office
or a video maker, a content creator? Because there's a lot of them now.
Oh, I mean, I, I, well, I guess, I mean, no, the Sargon,
Akata, when he fucking became the, did he, no, he ran for MP.
I think he ran for MP. I don't think he became one.
Let me check. I don't know. I honestly don't ever think I found out.
All right, let's find out.
Yeah.
Carl Benjamin is a British anti-feminist YouTuber.
A former member of the year. Yeah. So he's a member.
What way? I guess I don't know what member of the party means.
Member of the party doesn't mean much of anything.
He was one of his unsuccessful candidates for Southwest England constituency.
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, so basically it hasn't happened yet. What a fucking bitch.
Yeah. Well, well, I mean, you said run and like he did run.
I mean, be elected. That's what I meant.
Oh, could you imagine like, I don't know, destiny running and then getting elected?
Yeah, imagine that on a podium. It'd be pretty funny.
I don't think, I don't think destiny would though.
I think that I think that would be more work for less reward than what destiny does now.
So I don't think he would do it.
True, but he might be like swayed by the potential political power that could enact more change.
He would run, he would run as a spoiler to AOC when she runs in next in 2024.
He runs just for that. And then accidentally wins.
Um, maybe. Oh my God. Oh, this is so good.
This is so good. The first, the intro, the intro of Sargon's Wikipedia page
includes the thing that he said I wouldn't even rape you.
What a fucking jackass. What a fucking joke. I fucking hate this guy more than,
he's like in my top five. He's like in my top five, like people I hate the most.
Oh my God, he's 41, 42, he says.
How old do you think he was?
I don't know. I guess I thought he was in his 30s, a little younger than that.
Nah, nah, he's an old, he's an old fuck. He's a relic.
And when I'm 41, I too will be a relic and I hope someone will throw me in the fucking gutter
and forget about me.
Um, oh man. Oh man.
Um, damn, I'm going to be old soon.
Soon, haha.
And then, and then what? Can I, I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
Then you can buy a cane and you can actually use it and it'll be like a cool thing to have.
I don't even know.
You can get like a cane with a podron at the end.
I don't even know like what I want to do with myself like this year.
So I don't, I definitely don't know what I want to do when I'm like 40.
Like, I don't know, I know I want to finish that thing I've been working on.
And I guess I want to finish a bunch of the comics that I left unfinished.
And then I, I don't know.
I don't know. I've been, I've been, I've been like, I've been thinking like, I don't know.
Maybe this, uh, maybe this whole comics, maybe this whole art thing is like just not
doing it for me.
Maybe I've just like, maybe I should consider myself a failure at this point,
having like been doing it for this many years and having only produced as much as I have.
You know?
Uh, sure. Yes.
I'm fatically agreed.
I thought so.
Me too. Good. Okay, cool.
I mean, there's, there's no such thing as like starting too late.
So like, that's, that's, that's not what I mean.
That's not really what I mean.
Like if, if you had never done comics before and then you started at 40, you could still get somewhere.
Yeah.
The fact that you've done anything before this point means that you're a leg up on anyone who
does start at 40.
I, I, I, that's not what I mean.
What I, what I mean is not that like, oh, it's too late. I haven't made it yet. I'll never make it.
It's that like, I, I've been doing it for a while.
And I have, you know, only accomplished this much.
Should I have been doing something else?
Like, should I start doing something?
Well, that's the, oh, I have no, I have no fucking idea.
I have abs, I have absolutely no other idea for what to be doing.
I mean, like, I guess at that point you're getting into it.
Like, what is the meaning of existence sort of talk?
Like if, if you're not exactly,
you want to live because that seems like it works so far.
And then beyond that, I don't know.
You need money to live, so you need to do something.
So you can pay.
But aside from that, I don't know, like nobody really knows.
And it's hard to like put a, put a real hard label on what you need to do.
I guess I just see, I guess I just see,
I see fucking like artists on Twitter or whatever who are like, oh, you know,
I, I'm, I'm, uh, I have too many ideas and I can't draw them all.
Like I'm over, like there's so many things I want to do.
There's so many like, you know, story ideas in my head that like I have to get down
and there's not enough time in the day.
And like, I'm not like that.
I, I'm not overflowing with like ideas.
I have like one idea.
I have like one thing that I want to work on right now.
I have a bunch of old ideas that I never completed that I could finish if I want.
I'm not, I'm not bursting with like, oh, I know, I know, you know,
all these things I want to do.
I don't know if anything is even worth doing.
So, so I am like, am I doing something wrong?
They seem to have a clue that I don't have.
I mean, surely you had a moment before where you were like,
I want to do this comic and that comic or even earlier than that in your life.
Like everybody has moments of like passion and they,
they feel like they need to exist so that they can do something specific.
And at the moment you just are not feeling it in, in, in the way that maybe you used to.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm, I'm not, I'm not.
Not feeling it lately.
Maybe that's, maybe that's to be expected.
I don't know.
I mean, I mean, I'm like, I'm like, I'm, I'm feeling the thing that I have,
like, you know, that I'm working on right now.
And then, but aside from that, I'm like, even it's, it's hard to like even,
even that I'm starting to get frustrated with because it's taken longer than I wanted it to.
Which is just like construction.
Yes, which like, of course it did.
Everything, everything always does.
It's just another, it's just another thing that
it's like, oh, it was supposed to be done by now.
It's, it's, it's supposed to be done by now.
Just like all that other stuff that I never finished.
Well, hang on.
If it's supposed to be done, like it's taking a while, but you also feel like,
wow, when everything's done, what am I going to do?
Gee, nothing, I guess.
Like the, the, the, the feel like conflicting thoughts.
Like you feel like you don't have enough, you're, you're wasting time,
but the time you, you, you have left, you feel like you would waste anyway,
or like you, you don't know what to fill it with.
Yes.
So what, what the fuck?
I don't know.
I mean, I guess, like, it's easy to like,
to know that something could have been done quicker
if you had been working harder.
I don't know.
Would, would you feel like it would be, you would be more into it?
Had you already been working harder and therefore more have, of it had been created?
Yeah.
If, if I, if I was where I expected to be with it now, which is like done or almost done,
like if I was almost done with it right now, I would be like, fuck yeah, this shit is like,
we just got to, we just got to put the finishing touches on this and then it's go time.
Like I would be excited about like, you know, putting it out soon.
At the moment, it's like maybe, maybe a little less than half.
And I'm like, oh, I still have that much left to do with it.
And I'm like afraid.
I'm like trepidatious that like, will I, like, I'm like, oh God,
am I, am I not going to finish this too?
I mean, I am going to do it.
I have to.
I'm not going to like do anything else until it's done.
But it feels like, I don't know, you ever, you know, when you start a new thing,
when you start a new project and you feel like that sense of like,
I don't know if I can do this.
Yeah, I've had that recently.
And I know from experience that like, if you just keep going, you can always do it.
Even if it ends up being a little different than you thought it would look, right?
If you are flexible and, you know, if you just keep, if you just keep trying,
if you just keep chipping away at it, it will eventually be done.
You can, you can do anything you put your mind to.
It's true.
So like, but I still, I'm, but I'm, so like in my mind,
I know that I can do it, but in my heart, I am deeply, I am feeling very strongly
that irrational feeling of perhaps I can't do it.
Right, sure.
I feel like that quite a lot with a lot of my work where it's like, I drew the Clarissa
comic and I'm like, I look at it and it's like, I know that if I was, maybe it took a little
longer on it or I worked, I did work very hard, but it was like a, like a quite a
sharp deadline.
Like it was only a month I could do all that work in.
If I had done it a little slower, it would have been better and I know I can draw better
and I know I can improve and it's all of this like potential.
But like, I envision that and then I see that the work I've done is not as good as I imagine
I can do and at some point I start to doubt whether my image of potential success even
exists and maybe I was overestimating myself, my abilities.
Maybe I am as, as like shit at things that as people assume.
Absolutely you are, for sure, 100%.
Yeah, like sometimes I, I like, I don't know, there's a few moments.
All that bad stuff I say about you all the time, 100% true, I'm conferred.
It's like, occasionally people will leave a comment on something saying, wow, I had no
idea you could do stuff like this when I said something smart or I made some good drawing.
And it's like,
You said something smart, it's like, wait a minute, you said that?
I didn't realize Gibb was smart, I didn't realize Gibb could draw, I didn't realize Gibb could
animate, it's like, I knew I could, but I just never did it yet.
And it, it, it frustrates me because I can't, I can't like point to them and say,
you should have known because they could, they couldn't have known.
Well, that, well, that just means they, they hadn't seen that stuff before.
That means like people are finding your stuff fresh that they hadn't seen before.
No, but like, like everyone, at some point, everyone who's ever seen anything you've ever
done didn't know that you could do that, right?
True, true.
But I guess what it, it makes me feel of is that I give off an air of being low skilled
because the things I do end up showing people are like sketches and rough things.
And I'm like, ah, fuck, I could like spend two hours drawing this better, but whatever,
I'll put it up, I'll put something up.
And then people get an impression of me that I feel is not representative of my skill level.
And it's entirely my doing.
It's just, it sucks because I get, I get impatient and I want to post things before
they're finished.
But look at it the other way around.
Every time someone says, wow, I didn't know Gibb could do this.
That's one more person who no longer has that impression, right?
Yeah, but I shouldn't have built the impression that I was shit at so many things.
Well, I should have, I should have stayed, I should have stayed completely silent and
hidden in, in, in caves under the ground.
And then I should have appeared only when I was already a genius.
But that's like impossible.
It doesn't work like that.
Yeah.
You gotta suffer.
That's just the way it is.
You have to be upset and there, that's all.
Yes.
And I am.
And that means I'm doing, that means I'm going, I'm going to the moon.
I've got the, I've got the, I've got the killer mindset.
The shit mindset that makes me sad.
And that's going to, that's going to carry me to the top.
I need to maximize my tears so I can lubricate my way to success.
Water slides to the, it's a race, it's a race, it's a race to the bottom.
It's a race to the bottom and you gotta, you gotta lubricate your slide down.
It's, it's like, it's like Sonic.
If you, if you get a really fast, if you go down as fast as possible
on the way back up on the other side, you'll be like, zoom in up to the top.
It's like, okay, we gotta go as low as we can as fast as possible to get that momentum to shoot to the moon.
Trust us, trust us.
We'll come out the other side.
We'll come out the other side like a rocket.
We'll all be through the center of the earth and out the other side, like pew to the sun
to Jupiter.
We're going to Mars.
We're going to Mars with daddy Elon.
That's all a rich tapestry.
A rich, a rich laver, a rich, uh, a juicy, um.
Yes.
Yeah, okay.
I have to pee.
Give me a minute.
Oh no.
Eleazar, cut it, cut it all, cut it all, cut this.
Right, Eleazar, don't cut this.
I'm going to say, uh, Ben is peeing right now and I can hear him peeing and it sounds disgusting.
It's like, oh, gross.
Listen to that pee.
Put in a sound effect of, of, of water, like splashing and then, and me saying, oh, you Ben,
stop peeing on the pee CP.
Now use that clip and then cut back to whenever Ben is back and he'll be none the wiser.
Oh no, Ben, stop piercing.
There's piss everywhere.
You can use that clip as well.
Lay them on top of each other.
So it sounds like I'm, that there's two of me.
So that this is very obvious that this is an edit and it's not truly happening.
Oh no, Ben, stop, Ben, stop peeing on the pee CP.
There's piss everywhere.
All right, Gib.
Yeah?
I think, I think you should have a seat before I tell you what I'm about to tell you.
I'm sitting already.
That was a test to see if you would betray me and you failed.
What?
If you would tell Eleazar to put pee sound effects over the pee CP to embarrass me.
You failed the test.
Gib, I'm sorry.
So it wasn't actually, you didn't actually pee.
No, I did, no, I did, but it was also a test.
Impromptu test, impromptu quiz.
That's the thing about me is like, I'm, I'm, I'm exhausting.
I'm just an exhausting person to be around because I'm constantly like setting up like,
like little like, like tests and hurdles to jump over and like,
and fanciful riddles to be solved if progress is to be made.
You have like a nightmare.
Like a zip file of every DM.
I've ever given you so that you could use them to the greatest extents.
Didn't, didn't Jesse say that he had that on all of us at Redcon, at Redcon 2?
I feel like he did.
He did.
He was facetious, but I don't know.
He, I don't think he was ever going to use it.
Okay.
I thought it was, I thought it was facetious.
I, well, I couldn't, I couldn't tell if it was facetious or not.
And I, I assumed it was somebody else.
I won't say who.
I don't want to embarrass them in case I'm wrong, in case they were wrong.
But somebody else told me that they were like,
I don't know if he's joking about that.
And I was like, huh, um, he was probably joking.
There's no way, like, there's no way that he would actually do a thing where he's like
expose on the PCP.
They said, I don't know, what would they like?
No, you're right.
Like what even could there be anyway?
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Also, I've never said anything bad.
True.
Me neither.
Don't listen to the early episodes of the PCP.
No, those were all, those were all cool.
You know, we all, we all, we were all laughing maniacally.
We were just being cool.
Do we know what I'm saying?
We were though.
We were being wicked cool.
We were unironically being based.
Most of the time.
I don't know.
What are, what are we, what are we doing?
What are we doing here, Gib?
What's, what's, where's, where's this all going?
Like in the universe?
Like, what do we do?
Yeah.
We're here to.
Where's this headed?
Where, where, where, what's the, let's see where this is going.
Where's this all going exactly?
Well, it's the heat death of the universe,
which I'm very excited for.
I'm going to stream that.
That's going to be some great content.
That's going to be some great content right there.
I'm going to post it to my, to the future,
to whatever future thing still exists that you can stream on.
Dude, imagine like streaming like across like galaxies
and aliens responding in, in super chat,
but like 10,000 years after you finished.
Oh, like they're getting, they're getting the Twitch stream.
Yeah, they get the, like millions of years from now
and millions of light years away.
Yeah. And like, like thousands, like millions of years later,
like people will start getting super chats that have long since died
of old age.
And the aliens are like all based.
The aliens are like, the aliens are like,
they're sending the super chats to, to Twitch in the, yeah, I see.
I see.
Like all of the, all of the messages.
God, I hope the Twitch servers is still running then.
Oh yeah.
I hope Amazon still owns everything.
Otherwise they will never get those fucking alien bucks.
It was alien crypto.
That's kind of funny, the idea that like all of the,
all of the, the things that are being sent out will be returned.
And like if the aliens like pick up on a meme, for example,
they will come a thousand years too late to the party,
saying that meme in chat over and over and gets like,
what the fuck is this ancient fucking shit?
The cake is a lie?
What?
They're like, they're like,
they're only just learning about Reddit.
Super boomers.
In a hundred years.
Ten thousand years from now, they'll still think that like
minions memes on Facebook are so funny.
That's a pretty good idea for a, for a story.
I guess it is.
That's homestuck.
I guess that's homestuck.
I guess it, but different.
It did, fuck.
It is homestuck.
Aliens and memes is homestuck.
It's like a, what's that one?
It's a little bit like, is it your name?
Or no, what's the early one?
The one about the, the girl who,
or guy who goes into space or whatever,
and they have to text each other and it's like light speed.
So there's like time dilation.
Did you made that video about it a million years ago?
Is that interstellar?
Or I don't know what you're talking about.
Is that a game or a film?
No, it's a film.
You remember, did you did that video
that was the overview of all the movies
that that guy who made your name made?
And one of his early ones that he made all by himself was about.
Was it an anime movie?
I guess it must be.
Yeah, yeah.
Your name, I thought was like a book that was turned into a thing.
Well, it became a movie.
It became a, it became an anime movie.
I'm thinking of like, um, something.
Okay, Makoto, no, I gotta get it.
Makoto Shin Kai, one man anime.
What is this one?
No, okay, she and her cat.
She and her cat was the cat movie that he made.
And then, fuck, what was the one about fucking time dilation?
Now that you're talking about anime,
I kind of vaguely remember those phone involved.
Okay, Makoto Shin Kai, voices of a distant star.
Voices of a distant star.
There we go.
What was the point you was bringing with that?
Oh God, the plot of it.
The plot of it is that like a girl,
I think a girl and her boyfriend,
he goes into like space to be a spaceman,
but they want to like keep in touch and like they text each other.
But because of like time dilation and interstellar distances,
the texts are like further and further removed in time.
So they're like getting texts from each other
when they were like teenagers,
like when they're fucking old and shit or something.
And they, I don't know.
They don't just break up and fuck other people
because who gives a shit?
I don't know because it's very romantic.
They'd never know.
They just could have been talking to an AI.
It's like he joins the army to go into space
and the AI, the AI programs him an AI
that will pretend to be his earth girlfriend,
sending him time dilated texts for the rest of his life.
Yeah, every so often she'll like the AI
will slip in a little like pro military,
like stay, you know, like it's really cool
that you're like in the military and fighting for, you know.
This is really helping,
hey, this is really helping the GDP back home.
Yeah, keep up the good work.
Like all like, oh, he's still, he's like, he's like 80.
He's like 80.
He's on like a distant galaxy or whatever.
And he's still, he still thinks he's getting texts
from his 18 year old girlfriend who is now 19,
you know, in his frame of reference.
So, you know, getting up there, but, you know, still hot.
And then he dies.
Wait, wait a minute.
So if the time, wait, if the time, like she's only aged one year
and he's aged, you know, so many years,
but like how have they been communicating?
Surely he would be like sending her a message every microsecond
from her perspective.
Like, like 80 years worth of texts come like within a week.
I don't know.
I haven't fucking watched this shit.
I don't give a fuck.
Maybe the movie explains it.
I don't know.
When he's on his death bed, he says, he's like, I guess,
I think, can I send nudes, please?
Just one.
He's on his, he's on his death bed and he's like,
wait a minute, there's a fucking plot hole.
This doesn't make any sense.
This movie sucks.
Licks of the camera.
He was the reviewer the whole time.
Oh, that's, that's another thing.
A movie where the reviewer is the main character.
It was called, what's his name?
Doug Walker's already made like 14 movies.
So it's too late.
It's too late.
No, no, no, those are movies made by people who review media,
but I'm talking like a meta movie where the reviewer of the movie
is the protagonist and he's like, this sucks.
I hate this character, meaning myself.
That's, I mean, didn't M. Night Shyamalan make the movie critic,
like the villain of Lady in the Water?
I guess he wasn't reviewing the movie he was in specifically.
It's like, wait a minute, that's a plot hole.
Okay.
The plot of the movie, it's the, there's two reviewers.
There's a good guy reviewer and the bad guy reviewer and the good guy reviewer.
His quest, his hero's journey is to convince people that the movie he is in
that you are watching is right now is good and the villain is to convince you
that it is bad, convince everyone that it is bad.
And it's a battle of attrition.
It's like a Sherlock Holmes thing where one of them is trying to like
point out plot holes and the other guy is like, no, actually it makes total sense because
yeah, it's like, it's like, um,
and the villain goes, ding, every sort of thing.
It's like, it's like Death Note, right?
It's like an incredible like battle of wits and they're like constantly outsmarting.
It's like, aha, a death of the author though.
And you're like, oh no, my entire argument is crumbled.
And, you know, just make a whole series about it.
Yeah, six seasons in a movie.
That's content rich.
That's content rich IP right there.
It's like the sequel is him grappling with the idea of sequels.
The movie is called Re-Colon Viewer.
Or Re-Viewers, I don't know.
Fuck yeah, this is, this shit, you know what?
I take back everything I said about not, now I know what I'm doing.
I'm making this shit for the rest of my life as soon as the secret project is done.
Fuck all that other shit.
Fuck, uh, fuck Biscopades.
Fuck the champion.
It's on to Re-Viewer.
I mean, it's just a winning formula.
Really, the best ideas are the ones that make you laugh regardless of whether they're good.
Yeah.
Because the stuff that makes me happy is like thinking of, I had this,
this is, I didn't end up doing it because it was so stupid.
But it was just like, I was thinking of getting a random YouTube video and then
just occasionally replacing one of the nouns with
dinner from like Zelda, CDI, cutscene, YouTube poop quote.
Where the king says, I wonder what's for dinner, getting that clip and just saying,
like Marques Brownlee with the new dinner phone.
And I was laughing so much at the idea that I could just do that at any moment.
I could edit that and it would be so easy.
So easy.
It would be nothing could be simpler.
It was just the funniest idea and I'd laugh myself to sleep.
It was great.
Fascinating.
I didn't do it though because it was so pointless.
I had other things to do with my life.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
Life's the little things though, you know?
It is.
Yeah.
One day, if you don't stop to make a YouTube poop once in a while, you might miss it.
True.
Yeah, life comes at you fast.
What the fuck are we talking about?
Nothing.
Anime?
Fuck that.
Fuck that shit.
What is your favorite anime?
Dark Souls.
Oh, it is made by Amiyazaki.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
My favorite Amiyazaki movie.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Someone's made that fucking joke before.
No, nobody's made that joke because it's so stupid.
It's so obvious.
It's awful.
Everyone else was too ashamed.
But it's a race to the bottom and I won.
My tears are lubricating.
I made it.
I got there so fast, I'm going to shoo up the opposite slope up the mountain.
Speedrun being so depressed that you become God.
Oh, God, speaking of becoming God, I beat Noida.
I beat Noida.
I was playing Noida again right before we started.
I had to stop playing Noida to record this stupid podcast.
Noida is so fucking cool.
I can't even stand it.
You beat it?
I beat it.
What's at the bottom?
A boss.
Well, I will know.
Okay.
I mean, should I spoil Noida?
Do you want me to spoil Noida?
I haven't even looked at the game, well, except for that one time.
So I don't know.
I don't really like rogue-like things.
I mean, it's not.
Random chance for upgrades annoys me.
Oh, it's so fucking good.
I mean, okay, I'll just approve that I'm a badass.
I'm going to spoil Noida.
Cover your ears for a second.
You get to the bottom.
You get to the last level, and you fight a boss.
You fight a boss, and you kill him, and you pick up this thing.
You pick up this mysterious thing called...
The place you go is called the work, and you pick up this thing called the salt,
and you put the salt in this machine, and the machine activates,
and the entire world...
There's a shockwave, and the entire world turns to gold,
and you also turn to gold, and you die.
And it's fucking cool.
But apparently that's like the bad ending for babies, and there are like...
If you do other things along your way to winning,
you can get other endings where you don't die or other things happen.
And also the salt is apparently called other things in other circumstances,
and there is a whole bunch of like...
Okay, this is fucking crazy.
You can...
There are all these orbs scattered around the places,
and you've got to get orbs, and you've got to get orbs,
and more orbs means you get different endings.
And there are secret places, like to the left of the starting area,
there's this giant tree, and if you climb this giant tree and go over it,
there's like a whole other section over there.
And if you go to the right, and instead of going under the mountain
to start delving down into the mines and get to the real ending,
if you can climb over the mountain or like burrow your way through it,
you come out the other side, and there's like a whole desert over there,
and the desert leads to some other weird shit.
And if you go into the sky, there's like a secret altar there,
and if you place emerald tablets on the altar, you get stuff for it.
And if you go even above that altar,
you can get to an infinite zone that is also called the work,
but it's in the sky, and if you go above the sky work,
you can go to the moon.
You can literally go to the moon.
So it's like terraria, but they actually have where you can jump to space.
A little bit, I guess.
I mean, you go to the moon, and apparently the moon is made
of a unique material that is found nowhere else in the game,
and it is called cheese.
And if you bring these like secret essences to the moon
and give it to the moon, the moon will crack open,
and these like secret fluids that are like nowhere else,
that are secret rare fluids will like explode out of the moon.
I mean, it's obviously awesome.
I haven't done any of this.
I've just been reading the Wiki about all this.
It's fucked up, man.
So does that mean the the player character is Wallace or Gromit?
The player character is an alchemist.
This is something that is not, it's not really,
it's not really stated anywhere.
The name of the game, Noida, it means witch in Finnish.
So you think you were a witch, but I think you are actually an alchemist
because like the end of the game is about turning things to gold,
and there are other monsters in the game that kind of look like you,
that are called things that are like alchemist name,
and everything in the game is named in Finnish,
and I guess the whole thing is based in Finnish folklore, apparently.
So fucking cool. Oh my god.
I do like the whole cheese moon thing,
but more importantly, the fact that you can go up and up and even up her,
I like secrets behind secrets.
I'm not exactly sure how you get there.
If it's just a matter of finding a way to go high enough,
or if there's some other thing you have to do,
but the moon is there, you can go to it.
I didn't know that the entire map is connected,
because like you finish a level, you go through a portal,
and it brings you to like a temple,
where you can fuck around with your wands and change your wands up,
and then you go down to the next level and you do it all over again,
find a new portal, down to the next temple.
I didn't realize this, but apparently the entire world is connected,
and I found this out when I went down to like the third level, the snow area,
and I just went over to the right, and I went really far to the right,
and I found a rock wall that just went up and up and up,
and I was like, okay.
So I climbed this rock wall for a long time,
and I eventually found that it was the opening under a rope bridge
that I had found earlier for another secret area in the first area of the game.
The rope bridge goes over a gap, there's a lava sea,
and then there's a rope bridge,
and then there's this other temple where you can find an orb,
and a secret boss appears if you take the orb and you got to kill it.
So I climbed up from the third level all the way up to the first one,
and I didn't even know that was a thing you could do, but I did it.
Cool.
Cool, cool fucking game.
Super, I love it more and more every single day.
Have to got to recommend, hey, post in the comment if you fucking beat Noida,
bet you fucking won't, cowards.
I had, I don't know, I was, no, I'm going to resist the urge to go on a whole tear about
all the cool ones that I built.
The one that I won with was essentially just a machine gun.
It just like, that was it.
Simple, effective.
I've been playing a lot of Minecraft.
Recently.
I listened to the Money Spenders podcast at patreon.com slash give and take,
so I know that you've been paying, and if you listen to the other podcast
at patreon.com slash Ben St, you would know about Noida.
Then you can hear me talk about my wands, if you want to know how I did it,
if you want to know how I achieved the ultimate high level gamer achievement
and beat Noida, you can listen to that over there, and I will explain everything.
Yeah.
Dab, dab, dab.
Okay, but anyway, Minecraft.
Yeah, Minecraft.
I've been furiously getting the big upgrades in this one server, and I have now the drip.
I've got a full set of Netherite armor.
And-
Is that better than Diamond?
Yes, it's the one that's slightly better than Diamond Armor, and it doesn't burn,
and it floats in lava, and it's very cool.
And let me just check.
I'm just going to log on to the server so I can see, because I've been getting so many
enchantments, like enchantment books.
I'm just going to list all the enchantments I have, because I think I have every possible
good enchantment on all of this armor, and I'm just proud of my gamer breaking blocks and jumping.
It's not very difficult.
Actually, there's taken a while to load whatever.
How do you get Netherite?
In Netherite, you have to, in the Nether, with the updates, there's a new block called
Netherite scraps or something.
You break a block, and it's really hard to find.
There's only like one, maybe three in a cluster.
You get it, and then you smelt it into Netherite scraps.
Oh, yeah.
Ancient debris.
It's a block called Ancient Debris.
You turn it into Netherite scraps.
You combine those scraps, four of those scraps, with four gold ingots, and you get one Netherite
ingot, and then you take a diamond thing, and you get a smithing table, and you combine
the Netherite ingot with the diamond thing to turn it into a Netherite thing.
I see, I see.
So, yeah, it's pretty cool.
Yeah, the moment I've got on my Netherite helmet, protection for aqua affinity,
which means I can breathe underwater, I think.
No, that means I can mine things underwater, as if I were on land.
Unbreaking three, respiration three, which means I can breathe underwater, and mending,
which means every time I get experience orbs, it mends the armor.
Oh, that's cool.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, I've got mending on all four of my things.
My boots are the coolest.
They've got blast protection four, feather falling four, which means I don't take damage
from falling that much.
It's got mending, it's got depth strider three, which means I walk and move really fast in water.
I can walk upper waterfall, I can walk against the current easily, and soul speed three,
which means I can walk super hyper first on soul sand.
Only on soul sand though, so in the Nether, right?
In the Nether, yeah, but I can build a road with soul sand and then zoom across faster than
normal running, and then I can also run on top of that.
So yeah, really, I've been doing work on my secret project,
and I've been playing Minecraft on the off hours, and I love Minecraft.
It's just so nice, I don't think it's a nine to five I'm working right now,
but on my secret project, my thing that I did talk about on my Money Spenders podcast,
Go Listen, it has taken up a lot of my normal working hours time, and on the weekends,
I'm basically doing nothing but Minecraft and podcasts and streams and stuff,
listening to vowsh vowsh.
That reminds me that we have, it's been a little while since we did a Shekels for Hackles,
maybe we should do another one soon.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
I have not been watching any Vosh, or any, I don't know if Vosh is considered bread tube,
but I have not been watching any like bread tube lately.
It pretty clearly is, why do you think so?
Yeah, why would you, what do you know about it?
I don't know, when I, I mean I know all about Vosh, like I've seen a bunch of his stuff,
I was watching it a bunch for a while there, I don't know, I guess when I think of bread tube,
I think of like essayists more than streamers.
Oh yeah, okay, he's a person on YouTube who is bread flavored.
Yeah, yeah sure, I have not, I have not been, I mean I haven't been watching,
I haven't been watching Thought Slime, who I was watching religiously for a while there,
I haven't seen the new ContraPoints, the last two ContraPoints actually,
I haven't watched the new Philosophy Tube yet, I am just like, I don't know,
I am just not feeling very motivated to think about, or I, I don't know,
feel like I kind of like get it already, you know?
Yeah, I find them to be generally entertaining, especially Philosophy Tube and ContraPoints,
just video wise, they're very like good.
They are.
And so I've been re-watching a lot of those.
I mean, I, I mean, I really like, I really like Sean, what was the last one he did?
What was the last Sean film that came out?
Didn't he, didn't he, I don't know if it was recent, but I saw he was,
made a huge long video about World War II and how stuff happened.
Yeah, that was it, that was it, it was, that was, oh, the bombing of Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
Yeah, yeah, why did the nukes, I got like 10 minutes into that,
but then I got distracted by something else and I haven't gone back to it.
That's a good one, that's, that's a pretty good one.
Um, it's, I mean, it's more about history than like him making,
I mean, he does make the case for why the bombing was bad,
but it's, although a lot of it is like explaining the history
of it and like what was going on with like Japanese politics
and American politics and et cetera, et cetera.
Um, that's, that one felt more history-ish and less bread-to-be, although I mean, it's both.
Uh, lol.
Um, I watched a video about Quentin Reviews.
I saw this video recommended to me and this guy was explained,
he was like, he had made a previous video called like the fall of Quentin Reviews
and he had made like another update video to that,
specifically about the DMs thing with Sarah Z and Lindsay Ellis.
And this guy, I mean, I agreed with some of the things he said and he, he wasn't,
he wasn't even like, he wasn't that harsh.
Like he was very critical of Quentin, but it wasn't,
he wasn't like unbelievably so and he was very, he says like,
you know, Quentin isn't like a complete lol cow.
He's not like a, a, a complete train wreck.
I just find him very fascinating because he has his like very like pathetic personality
and he makes, and he gives some examples of like how Quentin is very like,
very approval-seeking in general and very like, you know,
whinging and stuff.
Um, but like a bunch, a bunch of the time it slips through,
it slips through that like what this person, what this person considers to be a fall of a Titan,
so to speak, is like that he, you know, decided that like, uh, uh, you know,
actually like right-wingers are bad, right?
Like it slips through that like this person has,
so there'd be, there'd like, there'd be an like quote unquote objective,
but once in a while you're like, this person has an opinion and I can, and I can tell.
Oh wait, his, his angle is Quentin reviews doesn't like right-wingers
and that's why he's a Fallen Titan.
Well, that's not really his argument.
That's his argument is that Quentin is like,
bad, he behaves badly and he's cringe for all these reasons and he gives it,
you know, pretty reasonable examples of like, yeah, of like, yeah, that is pretty cringe
that he did, that he did and he said those things true.
But then they're saying like,
as he, as he's talking about it, he will, he will touch on like, oh, and then,
and when, you know, Quentin changed his politics and when he talks about that,
he, it's like, uh, this person is not neutral.
No, that's, yeah.
It, it really, oh whatever.
But I mean, I guess, I guess.
Like, I don't know much too much about him.
I watched a few of his videos once and he seems, he, I think he was like,
one of the first YouTubers I had clicked on a video on that had a more reasonable
view of, of things like, like Anita Sarkeesian or something, like he was criticism,
like it was the first left E thing I'd ever looked at.
Okay, okay.
And I was like, huh, that's interesting.
But then he's got,
since then he's like, he's like quite normal, not that interesting, not, I don't know.
Okay, well, I mean, famously he had that bit where he like,
in the middle of an unrelated review, he went on the rant about how much he hates Trump.
That was, yeah, I, I heard about that.
And it's like, okay, that's a little cringe.
That's a little cringe.
And I think we can all agree.
We can all, you know, left or right, you know, like black people, hate black people,
we can all agree that that's kind of cringe.
I kind of remember it being relevant, but I don't know.
I thought it was at the beginning, like if something, something, something,
okay, here's the thing.
I kind of hate Donald Trump, blah, blah, blah, obvious things.
And then he went on to talk about a cartoon or something.
I can't, I can't remember really.
But like, I don't feel like that was super cringe.
Had Trump in it or something?
Or was it, I don't know, I don't know.
But the, but the, but the point is like, you know, some, some people,
like, like when this guy was talking about that event, he doesn't, he says that it's cringe,
but then he talks about like the fallout.
He talks about, he specifically mentions monkey.
He talks about like the fallout that it led to with people like monkey
over Quinton's quote unquote divisive politics.
He specifically calls these divisive politics saying orange man bad and how like it cost
him friends that he said stuff like this.
And, and like that's when it's like, it's not just, it's not just about the cringe
for you though, is it?
It's not, there's more to it there.
Just, just say it, just fucking come out and say it.
Didn't Quinton go on that podcast with monkey, monkey and, and plemin and rusty cage?
What was it called?
State of the YouTube?
Yeah, I think he was on that.
I don't know, maybe he was.
I know they had, I know they had the thing where like when monkey got banned,
Quinton like said, ha ha, fuck you.
And then everyone was like, and then everyone was like,
no, Quinton, that's not cool.
He's been banned from YouTube.
You can't say that.
And Quinton was like, oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know that being mean, I didn't know that being mean was mean.
And like, that's very cringy, that's very, that's very, that's very cringe.
That's very cringe because if you think that like, oh, you know, this is serious.
I shouldn't, you know, gloat over the, I, okay.
Why would you do it in the first place?
People said, yeah, then why would you do it in the first place?
People said, like this, this guy argued that like, oh, Quinton said that people
shouldn't be censored, but then he was happy when monkey was censored.
That hypocrisy.
If you think that monkey is bad, if you really think he's terrible,
then just, yeah, just, just be happy that he got banned.
Like, what's the problem?
Who cares if people, if like idiots call you a hypocrite for it.
You're not one unless, I mean, unless you are, unless you said like,
no one should ever be banned from YouTube.
And then someone gets banned from YouTube and you're like, haha, you know.
But I don't think that's the case.
Yeah.
People apologize a little too easily.
Quinton, Quinton is the kind of person who was like, yeah.
Yeah, like I, I would much rather he like make a statement and stick with it.
Like if he doesn't like monkey and he thinks monkey's bad to say it.
Sure.
Then just, then just own it.
Then just own it.
The fact that he took it back is like, well, why did you,
did you want to score points by saying that?
Which one do you actually believe?
Yeah.
True.
You gotta take a stand, it's all in your hand.
You know what that is?
It's a song, probably.
That's the opening theme song to the Animorphs Live Action Nickelodeon television series.
Oh.
I wonder if there's any more Animorphing Time.
I listen to every episode of Animorphing Time, the leftist Animorphs podcast.
And I ran out.
There was no more to listen to.
They only released like once or twice a month.
Sad.
Sad but true.
I crave more.
I could probably, I could probably read through the rest of Animorphs in less time
than it would take me to
listen to the rest of that podcast that will go through the whole series.
Because you can read these books in like an hour or two and each episode is like that long or more.
So, you know, is it efficient?
No.
But it's funny.
Brrr.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sorry.
That's my Animorph impression.
Brrr.
Should we go to VoiceMails?
You said that we had a lot to get through, or at least a lot of them.
We may skip all of them.
Why?
Am I floundering?
Are we floundering?
No, but we've been going for an hour and a half.
You're right.
We have.
Yeah.
Okay.
We do have, yeah, we have a shit ton of VoiceMails this time.
I don't know why.
Okay.
You have it?
You have it up?
You're ready?
Uh, yes.
Okay.
The first one is called My Fence.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh my god.
Fuck are you?
Okay.
Until next time, sayonara.
Oh, hey, you know what?
Always nice to hear a friendly voice.
In the, you know what?
We're off to a riotously good start, I would say.
Okay.
Polite, polite Japanese clapping.
Next one is called Less Child Abuse, Please.
Parentheses.
Site is spelled verped.
Three, two, one, go.
Discourse around pedophilia and maps is so dangerously fucked.
Like the way it is now is what you'd imagine if you wanted to maximize instances of abuse.
As a society, the terms pedophile and sexual predator
are often treated as interchangeable.
We imply that anybody who is attracted to children must be abusing them.
But that isn't true.
Actual cases of abuse are more often to do with children being easy targets
for people in positions of authority.
When it comes to actual pedophiles or maps, it's a totally different story.
By and large, they know it's fucked up and intentionally deny their sexual impulses.
They don't choose to be that way and usually actively wish they were not.
But if society constantly tells who you're a monster, you often start to believe it.
These people bear the weight of sexual deprivation under society that tells them
they're basically as good as an abuser already.
They can't tell anyone about it for fear of repercussion, so they have to bottle it up.
They grow to hate themselves and are under perpetual mental duress.
This is not how you get someone to live a healthy lifestyle.
This is how you get someone to give in to their vices and or kill themselves.
People don't realize how many are secretly struggling with this.
Pedophiles are among us whether we like it or not,
and our goal should be to support their efforts to not give in.
Virpend.org has a bunch of testimonials and resources to help understand the issue.
The branding of virtuous pedophiles is really bad,
but I suppose that's inevitable in this realm.
I guess I agree with all that.
Yeah, I guess I'd have to look at the Virpend, V-I-R-P-E-D.
There is something really off putting about the name virtuous pedophiles, though.
That is, I don't like saying it.
Like, yeah.
Oh my god, that is just what it's called.
That's just what it's called.
I mean, yeah, I mean, it's true.
Welcome to virtuous pedophiles.
Oh god, I have heard that before, and it makes sense, and I believe it,
that actual abuse often is just a case of a person can do it.
They're in a position where they can do it.
That's why it happens so much in the church historically,
is because that was very much a situation that these people were empowered to do it, so they did it.
They were empowered not because it was a sexual attraction thing necessarily,
or is that also part of it?
I don't know, but yeah, it's more about can you than about, oh, you have a mental condition.
Yeah, I definitely agree with the idea that you can't necessarily help your vice,
not your vice, it's your predilections, what turns you on is sometimes out of your control,
it's your actions that you can control.
Sure, and I mean, I totally agree.
So people, if they end up having an attraction to children, obviously they should never do that,
and the way we treat the conversation around pedophilia is very,
like, no discussion necessary.
If it's even slightly potentially the case, then we should just scorch the earth, burn,
and just destroy them.
No room for any discussion at all because children are involved, and I get people's
wariness, because it feels very weird to even think of the phrase virtuous pedophiles these days.
I think if it is the case that people have these things and they don't wish to act on them,
that is at least evidence that not everyone who is attracted to children
is necessarily an abuser.
So yeah, I guess there's a discussion to have.
Yeah, I mean, I am for whatever, this is the tough questions, we're dealing with the PQ
right now, the pedophile question.
And the answer that I prefer is, in it first, a solution that results in the fewest children
being abused, which yeah, it's probably the case that letting people that are like this,
and like you said, they are going to exist no matter what.
So letting people like that get help or whatever that looks like,
and not be shamed just for existing, as long as they're not hurting anyone.
And then secondary to not abusing children is, in addition to that, also dealing with these
people who are making their doing what they need to do not to hurt anyone, dealing with them
humanely is also good, so I agree.
Controversial statement there maybe, but yeah, sure.
No, this guy's right.
Yeah, I agree as well.
It's just frustrating, because I know the issue is so much about anybody who would want to have
the conversation, runs the risk of being just shit-talked and thought of as a pedophile online.
Like, oh, you even think about defending, like the rehabilitation, that's just major cringe.
You're probably a pedophile yourself, actually, and then it's all like-
As a registered Democrat, I want us to be as open and generous with pedophiles as possible,
because I stan all of them, they are all my gods, they are my kings and queens,
and I won't let anyone besmirch them.
Yeah, I don't know how to go about this sort of thing, but I guess verped, verped.
Who we are, FAQ.
I'm not going to read the website, I don't care that much.
I'll at least skip it, I mean, I don't know.
I guess.
Next one?
Yeah.
Okay, okay, next one is called cringe or based, episode one, three, two, one, go.
Based.
Nice.
Oh, clever, clever new show on the voicemails.
We have to guess if it is going to be cringe or based each episode.
Well, what an exciting new chapter in the PCP.
I'm so excited to see the next one and to be correct when I flip that coin.
Okay, next one, don't forget to eat your greens, three, two, one, go.
Don't forget to eat your greens.
Nice.
Sure.
Hey, this is apropos of nothing.
We've talked about this a little bit.
I've mentioned it and we have kind of like skirted around the idea and it's but it's been
floating around like maybe I don't know how I feel about it anymore.
I mean, should we rebrand the PCP a little bit?
Because we're like things are clearly different now.
Should we do that?
I keep, I have thought for a while that we should, but it almost feels like it's too late,
but like that's stupid, right?
I guess it's not too late.
We could change branding and it'd be like the Ben and Gibb and sometimes Tom show.
Yeah.
What would we, what would change though about like the show itself?
What would, would we talk about specific things or?
What if we got, I mean, just if I'm, if I'm spitballing here, what if we got like a new theme song,
maybe a new intro?
We don't really do like, wait, I don't, I don't watch this garbage.
Does it still do the, the oblivion fall like animated, like spinning intro?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I mean, maybe we could change that or, or, or get a new one, get a new theme, new song,
new thing, new, new banner.
I mean, we wouldn't have to change like the thumbnails or anything.
The thumbnails are fine.
I don't know.
I just feel like it would be appropriate.
I guess you're right.
I just don't know how to go about it.
I don't, I don't know.
Would we change the title of the podcast?
Would we like new podcast, episode one, or would it just be?
No, no.
Procrastinators.
Hey, I mean, it would be fun.
I mean, okay, imagine, imagine that the PCP goes on for another five years, right?
It would be kind of a, it would be sort of weird to have like a period of the PCP where like,
okay, this was the period where it was mostly Ben and Gibb, right?
And, but only like the latter like portion of it has like the different theme song.
Like most of it just sounds like any other is like branded the same as any other part of it.
But like the latter piece of it is like branded differently.
I guess the, when I say it out loud, when I say it out loud, it doesn't sound like that.
Who cares?
They'll just be like, all right, who cares?
Who gives a fuck?
We should change it.
I think we should.
Maybe we could change the name to be instead of PCP, we could just have the Procrastinators
or like the Procrastinators podcast, like a, instead of PCP, I've never really,
I don't know, I just feel like PCP is like, it's a drug thing.
And like anyone new will be like, where, where are they going to do the drugs?
When are they going to do it?
Maybe, maybe.
I mean, it's like a pun that has never been relevant at all.
It's true.
I think, can we, can we put out a call for like a new theme song?
Can we have another contest?
We can have a little, yeah, another little contest.
And then any suggestions for like, you know, ways to change the way the show looks.
And here's, here's, here's what I think.
Here's what, okay, you know what, you know what?
Let's just say that like, hey, anyone who wants to, anyone who's interested, who thinks it would
be cool, can like contact us, maybe add us on Twitter or whatever.
And shiv is like, if you want to try and like write a new theme song or make a new like banner
image or anything like that.
I don't think I would change the logo, like the channel icon.
TPC, CD thing?
Yeah, yeah, that seems like going, that seems like going a little, a little far.
But yeah, I don't know.
We're looking to rebrand.
And if you think you would be funny to do something and you can show it to us.
And if we use it, we will say thank you.
We will say thank you.
We will shout out your thing if you have one.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Um, okay, okay.
Next voicemail is Kringus Bingus, episode four.
Are you ready?
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, dear PCP, it's me, Kringus Bingus.
I'm going to get right into it.
What I creamed that was the fact that over the weekend, somebody got my credit card information
and used it to pay for some OnlyFans, somebody's OnlyFans.
Sorry, that was me.
Only like $35 of OnlyFans transactions.
And it was really silly.
So I had to cancel my card and I was driving to the bank to get a new one.
So that's silly.
That's very Kring.
What I binged was some anime.
There's some good seasonal shows that have a few episodes out that I enjoyed.
No.
There's also an older show.
From 2017 called Aka 13.
It's okay.
It's pretty good.
It's like a political drama type of thing.
I enjoyed my time with it.
Aka 13 never heard of it.
A follow up from last time, I said my mom had COVID.
I did not have COVID and she's doing okay.
I just wanted to get a check in about that.
This is Kringus Bingus signing off.
Thank you, favorite PCP voicemail caller.
Thank you, Kringus Bingus.
We love you.
Always nice to get an update from Kringus Bingus.
I like to bing at Kringus Bingus instead of bing.
I never kring at Kringus Bingus and I always bing Kringus Bingus.
Very good.
Wait a minute.
Before we go on, I just remembered something that I want to shout out.
I have not shouted out enough of Krugsmash on this channel.
Is that the Digimon or the Dwarf Fortress?
The Digimon person.
No, it's the Dwarf Fortress guy.
Yes.
Someone, okay, it was a lemon tart from who worked on the PCP dating sim.
He was part of that.
Messaged me to be like, Ben, I gave Krugsmash a try.
I watched the splatter face, like you said, and he was like, thank you.
It was great.
It was a masterpiece.
I loved it.
I'm going to go and watch Monster Killer the Fortress series next because it was so great.
And I was like, yes, fuck, yes, excellent.
Love it.
That made my day.
I hope more, I hope other people discover Krugsmash through my recommendations.
He is back, splatter face is over.
He has gone back to a new quote unquote fortress called the watchful eyes.
And the watchful eyes is sick.
It is nothing.
It is completely different from all the other fortresses he has done.
It rules.
It's great.
But don't go right into watchful eyes because it is a direct continuation
from scorched fountains, which I think was a direct continuation from Honey Stoker,
which I think was a direct continuation from Monster Killer.
So you could jump in anywhere, but it's better if you go back and watch the older fortress,
at least as far back as Monster Killer, maybe even further.
I don't remember.
So I was just very fucking excited.
Just very fucking excited that Krugsmash is back to back to watchful eyes.
Cool.
Okay.
Yes.
Very cool.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Tomgtomg how to resurrect the podcast.
Ah, thank God.
Three, two, one, go.
So first of all, the way the podcast is right now, it's not dead, of course.
There's still people watching it.
They call the volcano dormant when it's like low activity is to sleep for a while.
So I think that's why we should call the state the podcast is in.
Currently, it's dormant.
So the way that we fix this is to have another rag con because that always brings the spirits
up as a good rag con.
Like in the past, rag con has brought people who supposedly left the podcast back into the
fold.
Maybe not immediately, but like slowly.
You know, there was another rag con.
Plenty of people who have supposedly left the podcast would probably go to it anyways.
Right?
Yeah, like that's true.
I stopped the voicemail.
That's true, but we can't do it because we have things that must be
delivered on from the last one, which are actually being, believe it or not,
they are actually being produced.
It's definitely slower than we would have liked.
But yes, nothing has been like, aside from the stuff that we haven't started yet,
like the dojin.
Well, the stuff that we haven't started yet is not started because the other things that
have not been finished yet must be done first.
Does the dojin need anything to get done?
Well, we never really settled what exactly the dojin would be.
I had some ideas about what it would be.
My ideas, though, were that it should tie into the OVA and Road to Radcon.
And Digi has still not finished the final chapter of Road to Radcon,
despite me asking her several times to do so, despite you asking her several times to do so,
and her saying, yes, she'll do it, but she still hasn't done it yet.
So we can't do that because I think it should be a tie-in.
So there's that.
My idea is that it should be, well, whatever.
I've explained that enough.
At some point, there's only so many times you can just ask her to do it and wait.
Should I write it?
Should you write it at this point?
I don't know.
It feels wrong because I don't know what it was supposed to be.
It does feel wrong.
Well, okay, I have a few thoughts about this.
It does feel wrong because the Road to Radcon was like absolutely a Digi creation.
It would not have been, you know, I don't think anyone else could, like,
it wouldn't be the same if anyone else made it.
On the other hand, slightly mitigating that is the fact that now, like, two years later,
if, like, everything, is it two years?
I don't think it's two full years.
Almost a year later, almost a year.
Yeah.
Almost a year later.
I mean, after everything has happened, a lot has changed and, like, Road to Radcon 5
now will not be what it would have been, but I still think Digi should write it because,
I mean, I still think it's, it should be Digi that makes it.
If she won't do it, then I guess someone else will have to, even though that does seem completely wrong.
Right.
I mean, we should definitely make sure if we're going to do it that we tell her beforehand.
Sure.
Just in case she was gonna get around to it.
I don't know.
I have no doubt that she has every intention of eventually getting around to it, but, like,
eventually must be on a reasonable time frame.
And I know that sounds hypocritical considering how long it's been that, like,
the other stuff is still getting made, but I was saying, I was saying before that, like,
the OVA will not be an infinite amount of time away.
The OVA will be, like, coming, you know, probably in the medium to short, not short,
in the slightly longer than short, low, medium range future.
If you understand, that makes perfect sense.
And therefore, if we want, I would like to just have everything done before the OVA is done.
I would like the OVA to be, like, basically the last thing that comes out.
Yeah, yeah.
And with it, everything else that is associated.
And have that be, like, okay, it's done.
We deliver it on everything it's done.
And only then could we even consider a Radcon five?
Five, yeah.
Radcon five, I mean, even if we wanted to just do one right now, there is a pandemic still.
I would want to wait for that to, like, ease up a little bit more.
For sure.
I mean, I would prefer it if, like, we were all vaccinated by then.
Yes, that's going to take a while.
Because it's all like, well, for, it'll be a few, it'll be a few months at least.
Sure.
All the people that prioritize people with conditions are prioritized and they still
got to build, they still got to, like, create millions and millions of them.
The rollout plan in my area estimates that, like, the vaccination will be
available for the general public around April or May, which probably is an optimistic guess.
And I would assume that that's the earliest it would possibly be.
When you say general public, do you mean?
I mean, anyone.
You mean, like, no bees getting vaccinated yet?
No, I mean, I mean, they are being that, they're rolling it out, but it's for, like, only, like,
you know, right now, like, frontline workers and then, you know, like, be at risk and stuff.
And then eventually around April or May, it becomes, like, anyone can get it.
Sure.
Is the plan anyway.
So yeah, that's true.
Lol, I forgot about the pandemic.
Okay.
So about, yeah, the Rotoradcom thing is a little bit of a, of a bottleneck.
And we should, I fucking posted in the chat about it yesterday,
but whatever, we gotta, we gotta figure something out.
I really do think we should get, we should get cracking.
Yeah.
Okay.
Anyway, next voicemail.
Yep.
Is all right.
Next, next one.
Timmy Jimmy, Powder Game Pixel Limit.
Three, two, one, go.
I don't know if anybody still cares about this, but the guy who made Powder Game is like Japanese.
So his English interfaces are kind of terrible.
If you go open Powder Game and look down at the bottom right, there's a button that says Dot S,
and that is the Dot Limit of the simulator.
So if you click it, it cycles through so you can increase it.
There still is one, but like-
This must be why when I was playing Powder Game.
It's a lot more than, than the small one.
Stuff would just like stop appearing.
It can do even more crazy stuff with more, more, more pixels on the screen.
So, so now go play the game again in the middle of the podcast.
Now there's 20 more seconds of your voicemail left for you.
Genuinely, yes.
I love, love hearing about people just hear, hear them experiencing something,
being like, oh, that's cool, because I know it's cool.
And that's me, I did that.
I, I told you about the cool thing and that feels good.
So play the game again in the middle of the podcast.
Thank you.
Okay, nothing.
Cool.
Well, what was it?
Is the Dot S Dot L, does that mean large amount of dots?
He said Dot S.
Okay.
I clicked on it.
Oh, maybe yeah, it means dots.
Well, that's funny.
Well, you should put stuff in the game until you can't put any more
and then click that to change the limit and see if you can then put more stuff in.
Uh, I'm, I'm playing the game.
Hey, um, I'm, I, I'm, I gotta say, I gotta say, uh, so like these are all definitely, uh, Tommy
J. Again, these are, you know, Tom G, Timmy Jimmy.
The next one is terminal, germinal, then Thimble D, Jimble D, then Thinky Jinky,
to Bajuba, Thongjong, Tom Jump.
Oh, oh, I hadn't noticed.
So, yeah.
So, um, I mean, we literally told him not to do this in the last episode
and it's like he didn't listen.
So I'm, I mean, these aren't the worst, these aren't the worst voicemails,
but they're not great either.
And like, I don't know.
I don't know.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna start the next one.
I'll start the next one.
It's called FTL is Good.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, you like roguelikes and roguelites, such as Stone Soup.
Uh, have you ever played FTL?
I know about FTL.
Faster than life.
I have not played FTL.
It's really fucking good.
It's like endless entertainment.
I heard it's good.
I can like, it's just simple enough that I could actually like play it in class because of this.
Okay, that's it.
No more.
Next one is called Thimble D, Jim, yep.
I've heard FTL is good.
I never played it.
Next one, Thimble D, Jimble, College Solutions.
Three, two, one, go.
I just want to add on an addendum to the college discussion as like a thing that you,
if you're in high school, or preferably about to start high school,
something you can do to fix this, like in your own life, you know,
avoid a lot of the averse effects.
Because so I only had to take about three, three gen ed courses in college.
And the reason why is because I took 10, 10 AP courses in high school.
And I got college credit.
Okay, that's it.
No more.
Yeah, what he's saying.
Yeah, you can take things.
You can take AP.
This is an American high school thing.
You can take AP classes in high school and they can,
you're, they can sometimes count for like college credit or you can,
you can, you can, um, what's the word like, um, qualify out of taking like certain gen ed
requirements, uh, because, you know, they'll count you have being like taken like,
you know, elementary, uh, you know, chemistry or physics or whatever.
If you do the AP class, uh, yep, it's a good idea.
Next one is called.
Thank you, Jinky.
More college shit.
They're all a minute 30, three, two, one go.
So I have some more clarifications about the school shit.
So Ben or whoever, uh, you've seen my resume.
No, perhaps you remember computer science.
No, I didn't read your resume.
Computer science is a very strange field because it's the sort of thing where, uh, where,
where theory is like constantly relevant to the actual practice of the, the, the field.
Like, you know, of course, theoretical physics, like modern cutting edge stuff.
I have stopped only occasionally.
Okay.
That's cool.
Uh, computer science sure is fascinating.
Uh, next one.
Tuba juba equal line B carrot parentheses.
This is me three, two, one go.
As I record this voicemail, I'm going to do it.
I finally, I think I've finally entered into the class of person that can afford to patron
other people because like I made money off of that fucking, well, not off of the game
stopping.
I made money off the doge coin thing that happened a little bit after that.
I sold it just the right time.
It was perfect.
I think I was supposed to like hold and ride the wave, but I would have not made as much
money if I did that.
And I don't think the Wall Street people, like how come Tommy J gets to make money off
doge, shorting the coin?
So I don't think I like, I was on the side of the bad people.
You know, I don't think I stopped them.
Doge coin is not bad.
Other people from fucking them like they deserve.
You know, anyways, I have money now.
I made a lot.
I think like I've finally entered into the class of person that can patron other people.
So of course I'm not going to patron the procrastinator podcast.
I'm going to patron Jeff so that I can see all of this hidden Jeff's content that people have
been fucking yapping their mouths about.
And I can't see any of it because I don't have any money, but I do have money now.
So I'm going to do it and I'll report back whether it was worth it or not.
You should patron me.
Gibb.
You might spend this podcast.
What Gibb, what?
I don't know if we're going to have to cut this or not.
I'm, I'm actually upset.
I'm, I'm honestly upset.
I'm genuinely offended and angry.
And I hate this person so much.
I hate Tommy J so fucking much.
I cannot fucking stand him.
Jesus Christ.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm seething.
I'm seething.
Do you want to let him know?
Do you want to keep this in?
What do you think?
I don't know.
What do you think we should do?
I don't know what to do.
I'm at a loss.
I'm at a complete loss.
Okay.
Next, next voicemail from Thong Jong.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh my God.
Everybody has always been saying,
oh, if you want to know what's going on with Jess,
just patron her.
But you can see the patron videos.
Uh, no, stop.
Nobody says that.
Nobody fucking gives a shit.
Nobody fucking gives a shit what Jess is doing.
Who fucking cares?
Fuck you.
Oh my God.
Uh, that, I'm skipping the rest.
That's it.
We're going out on a sour note.
I don't want to give this person.
No, no more.
Tommy J.
I will never, ever, ever play another voicemail of yours.
Fuck you.
Go to hell.
All right.
Fuck off.
I'm, I'm, I know I'm taking,
I know I'm taking this too seriously.
But you know what?
I'm, I'm valid.
I'm valid.
No, I'm with you.
He was just going on about whatever he wanted to talk about.
It wasn't a question.
It wasn't like, I have something to talk about on the
parochrasmators podcast.
It's just like, here's something I think about and want people to listen to.
Here is, here is the rub.
He's lapping as, as a member of, of the show.
Here is the rub, Tommy J.
I will never play another voicemail that has your name on it.
And if I recognize your voice, which I will, because I know what you sound like,
I will not play it.
And I will tell Ellie Azar to edit it out.
You will never hear yourself on the PCP ever again.
Do not make another voicemail.
If you do, you'll be wasting your time.
Fuck you.
All right.
That's it.
Next voicemail is called Homestuck Preservation Final.
Hopefully three, two, one, go.
Okay.
This is an addendum to the whole Homestuck Preservation problem.
The offline archive I previously mentioned does not fucking work.
Flash is dead and so is that archive.
Sorry for the confusion.
What you need to do is you need to go, you need to Google the unofficial Homestuck
Collection on Google.
And the first result should be bambosh.github.io.
And it's the unofficial Homestuck Collection.
Follow the fucking instructions.
You have to download an asset pack.
It is, in fact, the entire thing.
Now, when you start it up, it's, you go to the map because you're like,
oh man, I want to skip to my favorite part.
There's nothing there.
The reason that that is, is that there's a settings page
that enables a new reader function.
Okay.
You can disable that in the settings.
So you can have the entire thing, but like for new readers,
it like doesn't let you skip to later parts and spoil yourself,
which I think is interesting, but also shitty considering I've read the entire
thing and I just want to fucking see spades slick.
Anyway, have a good day.
Fuck that Homestuck archive I talked about earlier.
True.
I'm not having a good day, but thanks anyway.
Okay.
I guess I have nothing else to say about that.
Yes.
It is just good that there is a Homestuck.
It's good, it's good that there's a Homestuck.
Man, can you believe that we share a planet,
we share a planet with Homestuck.
Oh wait.
We live on the same earth.
The Hussie project came out.
Did you play it?
I bought it.
I haven't played it yet.
I meant to.
Okay.
Yeah, I haven't played it yet.
You can talk about that when we both played it.
I was, I'm so stupid.
I literally was gonna, but then it was like, oh, but noida though.
I could beat it again.
Okay.
Next one is called a plus one.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, it seems that I have something to show now, so I will.
Ilzon.me, that's my new website.
Please go check it out.
That's I-L-U-Z-O-N.me.
Yeah, that's it.
Wait, maybe he had a voicemail last week and he has posted this.
I don't know.
Before that episode came out or something.
It says five days ago.
Oh, I mean, I don't remember playing.
I don't remember whether we played a voicemail from him or not.
This, this is not like, why would he think that we would know
what the also is in regards to?
Maybe he, he probably can't see everything that happened in between.
I don't know.
But we've, but we've played all the, he would have had to,
if he left a voicemail about something,
it would have been more than five days ago.
So he would have said whatever he said and then at least five days,
probably more later, he called up the voicemail and said,
also, I have a website and here's what it is.
No.
Okay.
Next one is called plus two, three, two, one, go.
And what is going on on that website?
You ask why it's ego month thing done by me every day, all January,
all black history month, the shortest month.
Who is this?
Who is this person?
I think he may have been the guy giving comic recommendations at one point.
No, that guy's accent was like fucking un unbearably thick.
Uh, well, this is not, this is not that guy.
Maybe we'll see the guy who called us out.
It was on who, who are you?
Who the fuck are you?
Why are you?
What, what is this in regards to?
Fuck off.
Christ.
Next one is another Tommy J.
No.
Next one is after that is thousand lung man from Nate fuckers at michelkillers.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, how I've waited for this moment.
Nice production value to see him here.
Wait, where is he?
Where is Nate?
I wanted to see him.
He was meant to be here.
Oh, true.
Here, we live in a doom timeline.
I really like this idea of a man with a thousand miles.
How much he means to me.
How much I want to fuck him.
I wish to fuck Nate.
I am with the league of Nate fuckers.
I like leaves me breathless.
The idea of like a like a weird creepy like lung based monstrosity is pretty cool.
I don't know why he has so many lungs.
Never.
Oh God, I'm going to say it wrong.
You ever heard of a Hecaton Kyrie's?
Nope.
It is a Greek monster.
It's from like mythology, I guess.
I think they like were like from around like the time of the Titans,
like before the gods took over.
They were like the name means hundred handed ones.
And they are just like giant fucking clusters of a hundred arms that will grab you.
Do you like the cluster from Steven Universe?
Yeah, yeah, actually.
Yeah, pretty much.
They're not that big, though.
I mean, it's only a hundred.
It's only a hundred.
Give that's that's just ridiculous.
It's just ridiculous.
All right, pretty good.
Next one is called Seeking Goss.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, I just want to be real quick.
I don't need, you know, any torque and hog off or anything.
I was just wondering, where do I find what happened between Digi and May?
I don't need you guys to talk about it on the show.
I just want to know where to go to hear her talk about it.
I mean, she she made a video.
May made a video, I think.
I don't know if Digi ever talked about it, probably not.
I don't think so.
I mean, if you're seeking goss, there are places to go.
He specifically said, I want to hear her talk about it.
And she made a video.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, I guess he could have met either of them.
Well, Digi, yeah, I don't think Digi ever did talk anywhere.
So I don't know.
Honestly, it's been a while.
I forgot the specifics.
They broke up.
It's as much as I can remember, really.
There was definitely stuff that happened.
There is, I mean, yeah, sites.
I wouldn't recommend going to like, what was it called?
The stupid place where the idiots go.
Kiwi farms?
Yeah.
I think a lot of people there would have been talking about it.
If you really want to know.
But I don't know whether any of that is true.
Yeah, I mean, there's a lot of speculation there.
A lot of speculation and a lot of like, oh, I bet I know what happened.
Yeah, I love that.
If you want, yeah, I don't think Digi ever really made a thing out of it.
So I don't know.
Sorry.
Unless she did and I'm forgetting, but I don't think I am.
Okay.
Good question, lol.
But if you want, I mean, if you want the short, I mean, I don't know.
I mean, I could just say what happened, but like, is it worth it?
I mean, I honestly forget.
Well, I mean, they, there was the, you know, there's a little publicly available information,
you know, they said they had the break in that someone broke into their house or something or
something.
That one's got a big asterisk and that one's got to get big asterisk and an or something on it,
because I actually don't know what the fuck that was.
And then, and then they broke up and then May went to go be a fucking right wing shithead
with Ethan Ralph Lamal.
And now she's a, you know, now she's insane.
Yeah.
She was always insane.
True.
She was always.
Well, I mean, I didn't know I had no idea.
She was always dumb as fuck, but now she's free.
Now she's free to be as dumb as she likes and embarrass herself in whatever way she chooses.
Lamal.
Cool.
And I think that's basically it.
That's the gist of it.
Next one is called Alaskan Weeb 321 Go.
So I'm going through things, not a little bit behind, but I just know some got to the episode
where you guys were answering the voicemail about accidents and everyone thinks it's about
southern accidents.
So I haven't been down here in the south too long, but I've noticed that there are
roughly speaking about three kinds of accidents that you run into.
You kind of run into the Morpheus Accent, which is very long, slow and raw.
You can, uh, it's more common among men than among women, but it's very slow and raw.
Then you got more of your, uh, your Bible Belt Accent.
Those ones are a lot more nasal, uh, which my anger is often used to refer to it.
Pretty common.
Then of course you got shield, Bailey Accent, which ain't really from the, uh,
from the south.
It's a lot more from like the Appalachian, Gold Belt, but it was loved in with them anyways.
And second of all, Palin's not from Alaska.
She's from fucking Idaho.
Everyone up here fucking hates her.
Fuck Sarah Palin.
Sarah Palin.
Uh, uh, oh yeah.
I didn't know she was from Idaho.
I know her as the Alaskan, so that's, that's new.
Um, there's, yeah, there's, there's different, I know there are a bunch of different kinds
of southern accents, um, and I've heard people do a bunch of different ones.
And when I hear them, I can be like, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, they're totally different.
But like, I couldn't actually identify for you which one is which in, in the wild.
Uh, yeah, it's true.
It's true.
It's all true.
It's true that people do be talking different sometimes.
People do be talking different sometimes.
That, and that's no joke, lol.
Uh, speaking of which, the next one is called Funny Joke.
Warning, not a funny joke.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey gamers, no more funny jokes for me.
I'm all out of them, but that did get me thinking.
What's the funniest thing that you think you've ever done?
That I've ever done.
Be born.
The funniest, I mean funny in like deliberately funny or funny in like a laugh at me kind of way.
Um, I don't know.
I mean, I dress like a freaking freak in high school.
I wore, I wore suits all the time and I had this like weird, like this giant like creaky
red leather coat that I would wear all the time.
Uh, just the way that I, just the way that I looked in high school was probably the
funniest thing I ever did.
Honestly, if I'm, if I'm being honest, um, anything else?
I, I can't think of like, when I was young,
I was becoming a pony, becoming a pony tuber was a pretty funny thing to do.
Actually, I guess that is funny.
That might be it.
Actually, an ironic pony analyst.
Yeah, I was a little, I was a little ironic.
Uh, I was less ironic, I think.
I just liked, I just liked thinking about it and it was like a big thing at the time.
Um, when I was young, I wasn't like into a, like a goth or or emo or any sort of
weird thing that you look at it back in cringe,
which is also almost more cringy because it's not funny.
It's just like you were just quiet and did as you were told.
And that's the cringiest possible thing, but it's not a funny cringy thing.
So yeah, I guess brony analysis is probably the best thing I've done.
Yeah, I think, yeah, I think that's a winner.
That's the winner.
Uh, um, okay.
Next one.
Oh my God.
Cringus bingus bonus episode.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, it's Kingie's penis.
Here we go.
I'm just calling because you wanted me, I listened to the last episode and you wanted
me to talk about my feelings on pain pizza's art style.
Yes, please.
I remember watching some pain pizza videos back when I was in high school.
And I liked those videos.
They were fun.
I watched the pain in stocking video.
I watched, uh, that's really the only one I remember off the top of my head.
But, um, he did a bunch of cool videos about cartoons and I liked them.
They were good.
I think his art style is okay.
It's like very 2000s, like mid 2000s.
It's like 2000s, but like a shitty version of it.
It's not really my thing.
But if you like it, then, uh, then I guess that's okay.
What I hate about it is like, I see what he's going for.
I think that I can get a bonus cring this week.
A thing that I cringed that was, uh, was, uh, Tommy Jay, uh, that Tommy Jay guy.
If you're listening to this, um, you don't need to send in like a billion voicemails.
Just, they just think of one really good one every week.
Yeah.
Like Kringus Fingusy.
Tommy Jay needs to be more like Kringus Fingus.
We all do.
That's my advice.
Kringus Fingus signing off.
Thank you.
Kringus Fingus.
Voice mail?
Voice mail.
Pizza Party Podcast.
I think he's already in the voice mail.
Well I wish, I wish I could put, if I could put him in there again, I would.
Um, Um, Ben, uh, I think you missed, uh, Cluster Punk Kitchen right here.
Oh, I did.
I skipped it.
Cause it was, it was, it had the, it was just color different cause it was played.
Okay.
I'll play it, I'll play it in a sec.
But, um, okay.
I was a little harsh before when I said I can see what he's doing. He's failing
He doesn't always fail like I said last time. I think sometimes his art is like a passable
Like okay. Yeah, it's that like cartoon network like, you know
Super flat
Style sometimes it's like it's that and I get it and it's okay and sometimes it's that but like bad and ugly and it looks terrible
So it's not like I don't get
It's not like I don't get what he thinks the appeal of his art is I just think that it fails to be
Appealing in that way a lot of the time. Do you think it like it comes across as half finished like a first draft
Something sloppy. Yeah. Yeah sloppy some a lot of the time
Actually, I actually to be fair
I actually really like the drawing of me that he did when I was on their show like that's an example
I think when his style works and it's fine
Because I was in it. Well, I mean, yeah, but it's a good drawing in my party
cast Ben St
With yeah PCP's Ben St. Oh
Yeah, yeah, I remember that that was a pretty good
Yeah, it looks about like it feels good, but then I don't know
He's a bunch of those images in his pitch. We're just like this is this is garbage. This dog shit. This is like
I
Can see what you're trying to do and it's like half working
Okay, yeah, next one is called a cluster punk kitchen
and it it comes with a
image and the image is
This I'm gonna post it in the
Editor links to put it on the screen there
Morsh oh from link Zelda link Zelda CD from link from you
Yes, okay, three two one go
frying pan to the back of the head
track him underground
Grab your Nate seal his fate
grip your pussy
prepare to mate
suck the semen from his dick
Mmm, that's good schlick
This recipe is brought to you by the League of Nate fuckers in this house
We fuck Nate all day long until the clock strikes 8
Take a bite change your life
Gross
What is that is that is that like an actual League of Nate fuckers those another
Yeah, the thousand long man was also Nate fucker. I think he also said he was I think he also said he was in the League of Nate fuckers
Am I crazy?
Like the Nate heads the Nate heads have been radicalized it's like when Q it's like when Q got proven wrong
It's like people were like, oh no Q was wrong. Oh, no the storm didn't happen
Oh, no, we didn't get the day of the rope. Wait a minute. It's I've been I was already radicalized
But now I'm super radicalized now. I've become like a mutant strain like an offspring and off growth of this movement
I've become like a freak. I'm gonna take matters into my own hands
So, you know pretty good pretty exciting pretty exciting developments
They're gonna be knocking on our door again, I'm sure. Oh, yeah, so I don't think we've seen the last of
Okay, next next one is called trial of the golden bitch three two one go I
Hit bedrock in my bedroom playing new doom with a soft rock and MF doom and a shroom sandwich
I
Just
So I did you song, right? Yeah, honestly good cover. I like it like it more than the original
Yeah
Yeah, okay
Good thanks for the voice. I like I like the bit where it's it's like
Okay, I mean that part had had some charm to it sure
Um
Next one is called wait next one. Oh shit. Yeah, there's a whole there's one more page
We're gonna last we got a blast. We got a blast three two one etymology go
of
The word you that you guys were discussing it is literally people mispronouncing exactly the same word
They were saying the same word. They just couldn't they just had an accent that made it sound different
And that's where that word comes wrong
You're that's not true. That's not true. What is that first of all? That's what first of all
That's what a bastardization is
Yeah, it was
Yeah, it was maybe started as that's what a bastardization is that you started as a mispronunciation and it became its own word
Jesus that is what a
bastardization is
Yes, yes, yes, I understand. Yes, I understand that they derive from a common root the
F
Christ, I'll Christ I'll fucking mighty. Okay next one large nose man not Jewish three two one go
I
I can smell him
With my incredibly large nose
He's so close
You thought you could hide him from us
But you're wrong
A big oopsie on your part
You can't keep Nate from the league forever. Oh god
We will find him
And when we do
We'll fuck him
Okay, all right go for it
I feel like these guys need a bit of a like a pose as a team because shit got just just got real like fan art
It was a large nose man
thousand lungs man and
And cluster punk wait the cluster punk kitchen have a
another name
No, I think that was in the in in that voicemail. No, okay. Okay. Oh, I had the the image
He does how he looks like yeah, I guess so
All right next one is called pro gesticulations three two one go
He pray
Forgive my absence. I have news to share
Word finally reached us that the time of revolution was at hand
The triumvirate of jack's jesters and jokers was somewhat caught on a wares. Thus. I was all they could sin
I was airdropped onto the capital building in the fires of uprising and my goal was
Simba's
Placing a dude live iris into the u.s. Network that would disrupt all the attempts at policy making with mark hamill as the joker
laughing highly base-boosted
Unfortunately, the plan hit a snag near immediately as I was
Shorten the face and then rushed to a hospital where I was later arrested with a previously existing warrant out for my arrest
I've been busy essentially clawing my way out of the intense minimum security prison
They left me to rot in after all this time
I've finally been able to check in with my base to report my failure
But I look forward to catching up on all the news and seeing how my comrades have overthrown the oppressive
percoise
I'll keep you posted pcp
I can't believe the joker went to the capital
percoise
Birgway bourgeoisie
Birgways birgways. Yes. Okay. Birgways king
The the the petite birgway
The only petite birg I'm interested that I'm getting that white castle if you know what I'm saying
Uh
Okay
Good luck. Next one is called hi-ben three two one go
Hi-ben
It's me your old pal
Tommy j I don't think that's true. Inclusive mine
prolific
PCP voicemail
an official member of the pro
Crastinators podcast
No
I know you haven't forgotten me then
It can't I sure did
sitting here
Since we last spoke pondering
As you know, I often do
Ben you know how often I've pondered these questions that I have
The question I've been pondering recently
Ben
Is
Well
What is
patreon.com slash ben
Yeah
Next one. Hi, Ben. It's me the real Tommy j. I've been thinking about how we left things
Three two one go
I've been thinking a lot since we last spoke been saint of history recently
Very recently I've been pondering many things as I often do
Being Tommy j these were an hour apart by the way estimators podcast
And I've come to a conclusion
I don't think this game of ours will ever it. No, it's homie j. No, what do I do without you?
live without you
and you
You cannot live without me there to
caress your supple feet
using only facts and logic
We're like we're like, uh, we're like yin and yang me and Tommy j
Oh tragic, uh, how do I have to end this way? Okay next one wish upon a star confederation three two one go
Hello, this is dick jk nidus on behalf of the wish upon a star confederation
We specialize in fulfilling the wishes of individuals and their families who suffer from unfortunate circumstances
I'm calling as a representative for my client who wishes to join your podcast for a single broadcast
Oh, no, he does not carry any outstanding credentials, but wished me to inform you that he is indeed based
My client suffers from an unfortunate hereditary disease that is described as such we can't say no
And from his family lineage are in danger of expiration shortly upon giving birth
It is unknown as to why this phenomenon occurs the way it does
As such my client's mother had only one wish to quote her
Get my son on the pcp
I would like to read a statement from the sun
based on
Bum bum bum
Please consider an open invitation to my client. That's not where I thought that was going. Thank you
Why does cubo want to be on the pcp? I mean we have to do it
So I guess we have to do it. I guess you'll be on the next episode. I guess we got to get cubo
you just
You can't turn you can't turn down the
I thought it was going to be tommy j
I thought it was going to be about tommy j
Ben you're obsessed ben you have to let him go. She's living in your head rent-free ben. You're obsessed
Okay, next one is called pancakes the haunting of ben saint three two one go
Oh
This is marron pans artwork
I am here to haunt you ben saint marron pans artwork
I will hover over you for the rest of your life with my slightly inadequate
posture
And I will kiss you and make your art just as shit is me
Oh
Is this like a a self-deprecating bit like marron pan
Maron wait maron maron pan is not pancakes with craters. Huh maron pancakes. You sure
Yeah, it can't be why well because we know who maron pan is so why would this person have been
Why would this person have been signing their their voicemails pancakes with craters?
If they were if they were maron pan, they would just say they were maron pan. What art is he talking about? I'm
Didn't maron pan like post something in the I I've only like I saw maron pan talk about entering an rfck art contest
With something he he did enter the rfck. He entered the crafts contest, but he entered it with um
Screenshots of the rowdy rough house. Oh, that's he's been building. He was building the rowdy rough house by the way in the
PCP minecraft server and he also and actually this is a good time to mention
He said that he's gonna make the server free to all rfck people
Which I didn't know he had the authority to do that, but I guess what do I know?
Uh, it is what it is and he said he's gonna do it. So he's probably gonna do it
Uh, so if you're an rfck person and you want to see the full scale, uh, mlaca calm that's being built
Uh, I mean just fucking PCP minecraft server is the place to to do it
Um, well, okay
I don't know what artwork he's talking about though because that was just screenshots of the game
So I'm confused. Sorry. Sorry pancakes. I'm stupid. I'm too stupid to know what you mean
Uh
Next one is called pancakes ben you blew it warning quite loud base three two one go
You blew it
You blew it all up
God damn you
God damn you all to hell ben saint
You had him
You had cheesy manfredo. Yeah, and you could ask you could have asked where the god damn pizza
party
Was I
I went there
Me and cheesy were there together
I should have I should have asked again though. Honestly. He's right. I should have asked again just to like
Just to make sure that it wasn't just a terrible dream
Uh, next one is called llcs aren't used by giant corporations. You fuck
Did I say did I say they were?
Okay, three three two
Three two one go
Hey, uh, I just wanted to call in and say that the uh, dumb ass who called on last week rambling about limited liability corporations
I think that was tommy j by uh, you know giant corporations
To dodge liability for things that's not how it works limited liability corporations are not like
A fucking rank of package that uh, larger corporations get it's like a completely separate kind of entity
Uh used by sole proprietor proprietorships and uh
Like small partnerships between a couple people to uh, you know have a separate kind of uh
Safe area for their assets of the company and their own personal assets
So that if some asshole decides to sue them or they make a mistake
They they're not going to get completely blown out of the fucking water with a single lawsuit and die horribly in the gutter
Uh, I mean thanks and whoever the guy is go fuck yourself. You're an idiot. That's that's tommy j and I completely agree. Um the uh
Yeah, I don't really understand a lot about it
But I know yeah llcs are not big corporations and I know just because like yeah, if you're a nobody or you're just like
Starting up a little fucking like rinky dink operation
The thing you would apply for is is like to be an llc. That's like
Little shit stain companies. I think I don't know. I don't actually know how it works
Next one is called Ben goes to Aldi three two one go
Hey everybody, it's me Ben saying
I'm recording this audiologue of me going to Aldi to pick up some keto bullshit
And I don't go there. I order it right now. I see a black woman in the bath
I should greet him the only way that I know how
Shut up. Hello my negro. How are you doing today? Uh, wait, what?
What am I saying?
No, you'd understand. It's the formal greeting. I fuck you back me up on this. But please put the gun away
It's um
remember that movie um
Fuck is it called blast from the past the the brendan frazier movie
I don't know the one the one where he's been in like a bomb bunker since like the fifth the cold war
And then he comes out and is like, oh, wow the world didn't end
and he's like
He's like, you know, he's got an old mindset and he's like walking down the street
This is like when he right when he comes out of the of the bunker
This is like the very beginning of the movie and he walks by like a black male lady and he's like well bless my stars
a negro and she's like
Uh, huh? And um
That's me
Living under a rock since world war two exactly exactly
okay
next one
is uh
Them snakes could it be?
Could it truly be?
Let's find out three two one go
I can't it's him they suspended me on twitter
How dare they do this to me all I wanted to do was simp for the cute snake woman
But I guess I can't do it anymore. I will have to simp for someone else
That's why for the last few weeks. I have been fucking
Nate
That's right
Not then snakes as well having his halls penetrated by my many snake bodies and
Super fetuses
It didn't even take much convincing like an eel slipped into a japanese pussy. There was very little resistance
I hope michelle is listening to this
Everyone doubted me but none of them thought to ask her word when
One michelle or 28,980 snakes
That's a lot of snakes
The answer is queer the league of night fuckers is real and we are coming
Oh, we are coming
Nice
So the league of night fuckers is is a is like a group of
voice modulated
Villain super villains that all want to fuck Nate. I would I would describe them snakes as a sympathetic anti-hero personally
Er true
But I'm sure they would appreciate the villain like label it would be like epic and stuff
um
They'd be in super villain weekly
It's just a bunch of fucking monsters. I was just a bunch of fucking monsters
Fuck
All of the high high production value all of the high production value voicemails are just nate fuckers
They've all they've unionized
They've they're they've unionized. They've made demands and they demand nate
Um
Okay, well, I mean this is pretty based pretty based arc. We got going here. Uh pretty fucking scary also
Uh, I think there's more
Next one is from lost tapes archive number six my own tape
three two one go
This next tape is from myself
I made it with my cum
I will clay it with my bum
No, this is both
Oh
That's quite the big package you have though. Are you sure you don't need help
Handling it
Oh, it's okay. Michelle never has to know
Oh well
Oh
This tape was brought to you by the league of nate fuckers as far as I like to call them the league of michelle cookers
Audio jungle
Audio jungle audio jungle
Um, oh god
This is this is this is relentless assault
Next one is called mate plushie sale ends now. Uh, here we go three two one go
Time's almost up to join the fucking league
Nate best man. This is the last day to cut michelle before she goes away
If you fuck him then I am gay fuck now make rion.com for it slash bansay delete your pledge
That means no more patronage at hip and saint store
If you fuck nate his feelings will be sore banspore speak pipe.com for slash
Nate is grateful for your hard proteins. The more you fuck the more he screams. This is your last chance today
It seems
$20 a
It's a little too much a little too much
It'll be it'll be it'll like become a segment like we do the pcp we do the voice roles and then we do the nate fuck segment
I think I think they deserve it. I think they deserve to fuck nate. Honestly
Um, I'm I'm certainly not gonna stand in their way. Uh
Okay, um
Next voicemail is called kill three two one go forget devil inside
Who am I kidding? I was born to kill
you
But no all this is a wake-up call to what I really believe
What I really am
What are you saying? What I'm saying is
I'm the joker, baby
What the what the fuck was that? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Okay. Next one is joseph three two one go
My name is manjaina
Joseph manjaina
I'll kill you
Okay
Next one is called phallic classic edition
three two one go
Hey, I heard you got a big cock. Nice. Nice
Yay
Thank you for noticing
Uh, next one is called why nate the best guy ever needs to come back to the pcp
This is from sec. Yeah second. Yeah sec. Yeah
Second best guy ever at pcp.biz
Hmm very professional that is
three two one
Go
I ain't need nate to come back. Nobody needs nate to come back. I still fuck bitch get money. I don't need no nate
Wait what was that uh, was that uh, rule my ass batman? Yeah, I'm gonna listen again
It sounded like him, but I am not sure
A little bit. Yeah, it might be is maybe lull. Uh, well, he's not thank thank god
He's he hasn't joined the league yet. We oh god, if rule my ass batman joins the league of nate fuckers
It's over. It's over nate's gonna get fucked
He can't defend him and michelle can't defend against all that power
um
Okay, next one is cross emplemon new bad old good three two one go
Someone touched on how they're phasing out of being a fan of emplemon and I couldn't agree more
What emplemon used to do particularly well and what I think most people came to his channel for was his ability to create a
Long-form narrative about an obscure topic
Basically, he used to tell stories and what made him so good at this was his dedication to finding every relevant detail and skill
In creating a coherent theme out of the puzzle pieces that he digs up
This is apparent in his connection to crab mentality in the hungry box video the supposed curse that dale urnhart had on the
Daytona 500 track and the connection he draws between himself and leafy is here
On the other hand his recent videos completely lack a long-form story and or details that come together to make the whole package
Feel cohesive his video about the thing did have all those themes and messages
But it was really more so picking apart this one movie and so it felt more like a standard video essay
His fruit of the loom video was literally just him describing the mandela effect and acting like he was breaking new unexplored ground in
Philosophy and sympathy for the villain has nothing connecting the media properties
He discusses except they have good antagonists making the whole video feel painfully surface level
It did at least get me to watch whiplash though, which was amazing
Yeah, I feel that analysis. That was that was a pretty good. That was a pretty good
I feel like I completely understand now
Yeah, definitely the story aspect is is lacking at least
I I have never
I have never watched any emp lemon. I mean if that sounds like really cool content
um, it sounds kind of like what wang does I guess but like
Better, I don't know
Do you know wang that I
Oh, wang is another guy. He makes um, you know, he'll make like a
Sort of like a down the rabbit hole kind of thing
But like shorter and he'll just like explain like, you know, some weird story about like, you know, some guy who
Was misunderstood on the internet or some like artifact that was lost and what what happened to it or whatever
Or um, you know stuff like that. Um
Yeah
yeah, the
it's like, um, the
The jump between talking about
Like things that you have a
Like a passion for and then just making videos because you are a youtuber now
I feel like that's the stage employment is at the is at the moment
All these things that you talked about before were like he already was into them and like
The villain is like everyone knows what a villain is and it's it wasn't very
Interesting it was just sort of like here's some I don't know
Yeah, good and good voice mail. Good voicemail. Thanks cross. Thanks for thanks for breaking it down for me
Uh
Next voicemail is called one weird trick to learn Japanese quick not clickbait
Three two one go
Hey guys, I'm many weeks behind on the podcast
But when tom was talking about learning Japanese, I thought I could give some advice
So the best way to learn Japanese on your own is using this method on the site called refold.la
The gist is that the best way to learn a language is not by studying textbooks or trying to become conversational quick
But instead by immersion in the language. That's right. I'm talking watching anime dramas reading manga
All those people who say you can't learn Japanese by watching anime are dead fucking wrong
I've been learning kanji reading manga and watching anime
I'll be it with Japanese subtitles for like six months now and I can actually understand quite a bit of the dialogue
You could totally do the same thing for watching tokusatsu and kaiju movies and shows
The best part is that it's free wanikani costs like 200 dollars for lifetime membership and honestly
I don't think it works very well ganky textbooks fucking waste of your time
You're not gonna learn Japanese by reading a textbook and Japanese classes like during kovid fucking forget about it did
So unfortunately, it's not one weird tip to learn the language instantly
It does take some time
But it's worked pretty well for me and it's designed to get you experiencing content in the native language very early on
Give it a try and uh, let me know guys. Love the podcast. Thanks. Thank you. Um wait, so
Is there like some more to it or is the advice just like just watch anime and you'll learn Japanese
He said a website and
Yeah
I
Might have I might have misheard
Refold no, yeah refold dot la the roadmap to true fluency. What is this?
It's a step-by-step guide for learning any language from scratch
We explain exactly how to combine media strategic study and educational technologies to achieve high level language fluency faster than any other method in the world
Well, okay, so it's more than just it's more than just watching anime or reading. Okay, so yeah
I guess this is like instead of just like blindly watching anime you can have like a more of a
Uh a goal oriented approach to it
Okay
Okay, uh, I mean I I would believe that it does
Without knowing like exactly what the methodology of this place is I could believe that it would work
but like as long as you are like
You would need like a certain basic understanding
You would need to understand some a little bit of basic Japanese and like sentence structure and stuff
And then, you know, if you're watching it and it you know, it would probably be really tedious at first
You you would have to be looking up words, right? Like as you
Like as you watch and like you encounter stuff you've never seen before like you're not just gonna learn it just from seeing it
You'd have to like stop it and be like, okay, what does that mean?
You go look it up
And then you're like, okay now I know and then you come back to it and now you know and and you
Go like that, right?
Like it's not just watch it
uh
Develop basic established skills tools and habits for immersion learning and then you develop basic comprehension in a narrow
Slice and then you convert your required language to speaking ability stage four coming soon
Stage state the stage is stage zero refold philosophy stage one lay the foundation stage two build comprehension stage three
Learn to speak stage four coming soon
What could it be
Learn to read. I don't know but yeah, that sounds interesting
I'm not neat. Maybe I could do it with something but it's is it just about japan? No, it's a language any language
Did you did you quit learning arabic?
No, I I well I did quit as in that. I'm not currently doing anything about it
Um, but yeah, I could I kind of want to continue
Yeah, because it's it's a very cool
Script to to like to be able to write in that would be cool. I think
I mean it looks pretty cool. It does
truly
uh
Well, that was the last that was the last voicemail and we are budding up against the three hour limit
Eleazar says that we can't go over three hours because it breaks his computer
lame
Yeah, so we should cut it off here. We should wrap up uh patreon.com slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes now
actually for real
The behind the scenes episode is out
Uh, you can listen to that. That's our latest bonus episode
We've got like a million other bonus episodes. There's like
Gotta be like 50 now, right? Uh for five bucks. Yeah, uh, what a deal
If you pledge now if you go to if you become a patron now, you can fuck Nate. That is our uh, that is our main
Uh, good tier is the fuck Nate tier at five dollars. You can fill all of his holes
Uh
That's I asked him no consent necessary. Oh, yeah, you're right. No, I didn't ask him and that's makes it better
Um, I paid Michelle five dollars to look the other way
It's no problem
Okay, uh, it sends us a voicemail to speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail unless you're tommy j in which case don't do that
uh
Any last words?
Nope, that was the show. Okay, you listen to it. Bye. That's sorry. Sorry. You listen to this. Bye. I apologize. Goodbye