Okay, I'm gonna zoom the fuck out and it's gonna start like this.
Okay.
It's quite a place.
You are a part of a social media experiment right now.
We have come up with the hit new trend.
Viral marketing.
Check out this shit.
Advertisements.
Online.
You're watching one right now.
You got some shit.
You got some shit on your face.
That's just called passion for internet viral marketing.
What you call shit, I call fire.
I call charisma.
I call dollar signs in my eyes when I see advertisements.
Marketing.
Branding.
Merchandise.
You're hired.
Yes, yes.
I'm in the ground floor, baby.
Welcome to the procrastinator's podcast, episode 142.
Yes.
We're the reason people are dying.
There's a special live episode from Radcon 3.33.
There are no lectures.
Please stop asking.
You cannot.
Everyone's leaving.
Everyone's leaving tomorrow.
We can't do it.
We can't.
We can't fucking pee brains.
Can't fucking handle it.
Maybe we should just tell people in general why we're here together.
That'd be pretty cool.
Why are we here together?
First of all.
My name's not Nate.
I'm the Jester King.
Refer to me by my full legal.
I am Nate.
Welcome to the procrastinator's podcast.
So the reason we all got together here was because we've just been talking for a long time about our various future plans.
And people were asking us about stuff.
So we got together here.
We're at Digi's place outside of Boston.
And we thought we would just...
Give me a dress.
You can see nary a tumbleweed.
Ignore another man.
We just thought we'd get together and hash out as best we could some future plans for future shows.
Not necessarily exactly PCP related.
And I don't know.
I guess we won't get into it too much.
I think there's something that may have just rendered this entire meetup moot.
As you see.
It's just my attention.
You know, I'm on the ground floor.
You know, I'm up in forums.
I'm in message boards.
I get...
I'm in IRC chats.
I get updates on the web daily, bro.
I am online as the so-called online.
And I found some crazy technology.
Apparently, there's an app that will allow you to talk to people from far away.
So if you are at different locations, you can talk to one another with your voice and possibly even have a meeting of some sort to exchange ideas to little to no cost.
Wow.
If only we'd known this existed, we could have just not done this entire trip.
Yeah.
That would have made this whole thing a complete waste of time and money.
What do you know?
Fuck yeah, dude!
Fuck yeah!
Woo!
Uh, well, I'm just glad to see you guys, no matter what.
That makes me one of us.
This has ballooned out from I came out here for fun, for pleasure, for raw, un-untamed pleasure.
And then I think you were the first one's dog pile.
I mean, I just said, well, let's have a meeting.
Let's all meet up and talk about stuff.
Uh, and yeah.
I mean, I figured part of it was because Nate had not come home for the holidays.
That was an element, yes.
He was missing the old fam, up here in Boston.
That's true.
That's fair.
So yeah, he came to see his mama and papa.
Yep, briefly.
And then came over here to Jack Dick for two days about where the fuck are we gonna try to set up a PCPHQ!
As the meme has been going for fucking five years.
Would you say it's fair to say that PCPHQ is not what we discussed?
I mean, depending on how you look at it.
It's who's living where.
Conceptually, what PCPHQ has only ever meant to me is more than one guy lives in the same place and does a show together.
So PCPHQ is already here right now.
Yeah, this could be seen as a PCPHQ because we're doing the PCP in a headquarters together.
It is a PCPHQ, but not the PCPHQ.
It's a temporary PCPHQ.
PCPHQ is really more of a state of mind.
The real PCPHQ was the friends we made along the way.
We're having wars with various cities so they can pledge and they can offer lower tax cuts for their PCPHQ.
I'm thinking it's like when you're fighting a battle and they set up a temporary headquarters on the front lines.
That sort of HQ.
I've always envisioned PCPHQ would come into being basically when we moved up to the next level of content creation.
It was like a soft green light for it to be actual PCPHQ, which in my mind always involved a studio or could be in somebody's house.
I think the second that there is a permanent fixed setup for multiple members of the PCP to do a show together.
That is what the thing has been.
What do you call it? Doesn't matter.
But that is the thing that we've been building towards is get enough of us in one place with a permanent setup doing a fixed show that is not an audio part.
The biggest obstacle is the goal.
That sounds like the goal.
Anyways, how's IM Games doing?
IM Games is doing okay.
That's exactly what you're just describing.
Two people in the same permanent place doing a show that isn't an audio part.
You could say that that is a PCPHQ project.
I guess so.
It makes sense.
Are we going to get into all these things or are we just cock teasing people who actually can?
Cock teasing is just funny.
We don't want to say anything too.
We did not come away with this having a decided plan.
We don't have a concrete plan here.
I don't want to hype up our fans.
I'll tell people this.
On the idea of what we would go on, we generally are all on the same page.
We have general technicalities.
Mostly we understand where the others lie and we have something going there.
The biggest thing we're still working on has always been by far.
The biggest obstacle is actually getting the human bodies in the location and figuring out what the best place is to do that.
It's always been true that the best way for that to happen is to make more money.
We've continually made more money so it's become more possible.
That's absolutely true.
But we still haven't made enough money for it to be easy.
True.
I think that our vision was that we would just have this constant up the escalator of how much we're making.
Then we'd reach some certain cross some threshold where it becomes like,
oh, we can fly all my fucking dudes out to the same neighborhood.
It's not at that level yet.
Well, it's always been, I don't know.
It has worked out that it seems like some of us have to individually find success to even be in a position to attempt to do that.
Which is more or less what's happened.
I love talking in vagaries at length.
There's nothing more to say.
We can tell them some of the places we're looking at, but what's the fucking point?
We can at least say that if you and I get a place in the same neighborhood,
we guaranteed we'll make a Red Letter Media rip-off show.
That's true.
If you want to see us rip off Red Letter Media,
aka the plebe and the weave except it's me and Nate,
then just give us a couple extra dollars so we can expedite the process.
Do what you can.
Do what you feel comfortable with.
If that sounds like gay shit, then kill yourself.
Hey, do you want to inspire a new spin?
Shit.
Oh, you left it at home?
I tied it.
I tied it already.
Yeah, but it's all downstairs and there's girls downstairs.
I can't fucking kill myself with girls around.
You know, you shit yourself when you die?
You're so embarrassing.
Well, what else is going on in the old heads of our men?
There's so much startups.
There's so many startups that I've been starting recently.
The Kickstarter's are just through the fucking roof.
Not like I've gotten a lot from them, but there are just a lot of them.
I've got a Kickstarter.
I've got an Indiegogo.
I've got a GoFundMe.
I've got a Patreon.
I've got a LinkedIn.
I've got a Subbable.
I've got a LinkedIn doesn't pay you any money.
But it could.
It's not a crowdfunding platform.
Obviously, you're not using the platform the way that I am.
I've got a Teespring.
I've got a can that I put in front of me out of the fucking subway.
I've got a Teespring, a spreadsheet.
I've got a Pinterest.
I've got an Etsy.
Fuck yeah.
A print all over me.
That's the premium shit.
Think that about it.
I can't think of any cool, fucking sick anecdotes.
Like, oh man, the other day, just saw a homeless guy do so cool.
Because for the past three to nine years of my entire life, it feels like now.
We've just been stewing and fucking stewing about hardcore business real life bullshit.
And frankly, it's melted my mind to a complete mush.
And I don't have anything to say about anything.
We spent like 90 years yesterday, like fucking at the park playing Pokemon Go to the Pole.
Yeah!
It was fucking sick!
Woo!
Oh, dude.
Oh, fucking dude.
I'm air high five with all those.
I'm so mad.
Because we were doing a raid.
And I was going to get someone to train me.
They're fucking Pokemon.
And they didn't.
What a bitch.
I was going to catch a heatran yesterday.
I did catch a shiny totodile.
So that was cool.
Four.
Fucking Pokemon Go.
Four shiny totodiles.
Got away.
Miss the heatran.
And that sucks.
Everyone's like, oh, Pokemon Go is so interesting.
Guys, please talk about capitalism.
We want you to talk more about your weird political bullshit.
We listen to it every episode.
And it's never enough.
Every episode is political garbage.
But it's never enough to satiate us.
So please go arm to arm.
Because the last time it came up, I mean, I know that's like you're joking kind of.
No.
But people wanted to know the end of the conversation that was happening with capitalism stuff.
I was like to fucking fight about it.
It was getting really heated.
But we were all so tired from that episode.
Which episode was this?
The one that just, the last one.
I did have one point I wanted to make that I kind of regretted not shoving in there.
Which was simply this.
Well, I do literally believe taxation is theft.
I still think that some injustice is warranted for the sake of the greater good.
Which is effectively leftist politics.
Which is, that's the point.
So do I think that all taxes make no sense and should be stopped immediately?
No.
Because like, you know, a doctor has to fucking cut you open and hurt you a little bit to fix the disease inside.
Similar sort of fucking thing, in my opinion.
How fair would you say the comparison from taxes to rent is?
Pretty similar.
Yes.
Yeah, relatively similar.
With rent, you have the option to leave.
If you live in a nation, you don't really have the option to leave.
Where are you going to do?
Not live anywhere?
Not pay any rent?
Well, I mean, if you say like rent in general, I mean, I suppose that's fair.
Well, no.
Because like, you can't really choose to find somewhere else.
You can live without a house over your head.
You can live.
I mean, you can survive.
You're homeless people all over the place.
I mean, it depends on the kind of life that you want.
Here in America, you got three unalienable rights.
Life, liberty, pursuit of happiness.
Don't need a house for any of those.
Well, I mean, it just depends on the kind of life.
Like, if you want to be, for example, a online content creator, you're going to need internet.
Yeah.
Well, you have the ability to pursue that happiness.
Yes, you will have to pay rent, but that is because you made the decision that you wanted
to be something other than homeless.
That falls on you.
There's no one else's responsibility over there.
Sure.
Whereas taxes is like, like you said, you can't leave.
Yeah.
You have no option.
You just have to pay it because you made income in the country.
You know?
They actually could move somewhere else with lower taxes.
That is theoretically possible, but it's just much harder.
I mean, even like leaving, like you'd have to leave America and find a country that had
no taxes.
And that's really difficult.
Which probably I haven't looked, but probably doesn't exist.
But you're going to, I mean, you can't really find a house that doesn't ask you to pay anything.
Right?
Yeah, there are some places like that.
That are literally free to walk in.
I mean, like, you know, if somebody's just like some weird benefactor situation, I mean,
Ben lived in a place for a little while that like someone had just.
There was, we were, we were suing, they were suing the landlord because the landlord was
trying to evict them without notice or cause.
So there was a six months period where the fucking legal shit was going down where no
one was paying any rent to live there.
Magical.
We've really hit the ground running.
Haha.
Welcome to the PCP.
Yeah.
All right.
Everyone's going wild over this banana pizza.
It's fucking crazy, dog.
Shut the fuck up, Skeeter.
I'm with Patty.
She's getting all sad and glossy-eyed.
Sure.
May have put a little bit of stuff in her drink, I'm saying.
But hey, listen.
Patty, she's mine.
Back off, Skeeter.
Patty, listen.
You can't, you have to eat.
You didn't eat all day before the big track meet.
Your body needs food.
Patty!
Or eat some of this banana pudding pizza.
You're gonna fucking die.
Patty, it's the next big thing.
You're not gonna believe it.
Buy gold, Patty.
The fucking cops are coming.
You don't want to be caught off guard.
We'll buy the bottom drop.
You're gonna need two things.
You're gonna need water and gold.
You're gonna need banana pudding pizza.
That's gonna be the currency in the future.
No one's gonna want to eat anything else once this hits.
Hey, hey guys.
Yeah?
Let's do the intro again.
Let's restart.
You guys, you brought this up specifically.
It was you who made it.
Everyone's prepared for a big fight.
But I don't think anyone here among us is like ready or willing or wants to fight about
something that obviously nothing.
No, you weren't.
You weren't.
And 300 or something like that obviously nothing.
You were, no no you were right.
Yeah.
You were right.
It's terrible.
Yeah.
I was mistaken.
Ah, okay, good.
Fantastic.
Oh.
Did you have been doing this thing all night where he just silent write something down
and then shows us to us?
Uh, I...
I don't know what the like expected response is, just like, haha, fuck, yeah, did she sick?
I mean, have you seen the world famous probably up to a million 10 million views by now.
Video, noogle, on this very channel, uh, uh, inspired by just didgy writing on this board.
So clearly the dividends are paying off in triplicate, if more.
Yeah, we've made a lot of money off of Google and Tugel.
We're going to be launching 3Gal next year.
That'll be after Tugel inevitably fails.
Oh, you have a little bit of a pity.
And then the subsidiary of 3Gal Seagal,
you kicked me out of the Tugel share.
I was 50-50 with you.
And now you're starting 3Gal without me?
Well, I got other friends who need to pay their bills, too.
This is never mine.
I fell down.
Just like my love life.
The invisible hand of the free market
just gave you the middle finger.
Just scooched you right off the edge of the Grand Canyon,
right into the slime scene.
Digi, you know that thing that you always say?
It's like a catchphrase.
It's like holy shit, but for the new age.
I don't know what anyone else is doing.
No one knows what anyone else is doing.
That catchphrase you said to us last time?
What the hell are you talking about?
I don't remember that.
Anyway.
It says the invisible hand of the free market.
It's invisible.
Nice one.
I'm showing it to the camera.
I can't see it on the screen.
It makes it extra bold.
It was in relation to how everyone,
knowing the PCP talks about their working shit,
you don't know what anyone else is working on.
I don't know what anyone else is working on,
besides in vague, vagaluridies, right?
I feel like I know what everybody's working on.
OK, well, cool.
I think.
Cookies are done.
Who the fuck is making cookies?
I heard a ding.
It sounded like cookies are done.
Let's talk about what we're working on.
That's interesting, I think.
Yeah, I mean.
All right.
What are you working on, Hippo Crit?
What am I working on?
Hippo's got the most interesting shit going on.
Yeah, he does.
He doesn't want to talk about it.
He never speaks to it.
That speaks to that.
Well, I'll speak about it in private.
But I'm writing scripts, screenplay.
This competition has to happen a thousand times forever.
Where we're just like, Hippo, tell us about what you do.
And you say, well, I'm writing a script.
And we're like, holy shit.
Yeah.
It's great.
And then the episode goes by.
And we're like, Hippo, what the fuck are you doing?
I don't get it still.
Still writing the screenplay.
Oh my god.
Wow.
I'm writing dialogue.
I'm doing stuff to make a potentially feature
film of 2D animation for families and young children.
I'm not a family, can I get it?
We have to clarify, this isn't an internet gay thing.
This is real life.
Yeah, this is a real thing.
This is like non-gay.
I'm freelance hired writer to do this.
Like the goal is for it to be on a network.
The goal is to be on a little bit more of a credible media
platform.
To be profitable enough so that it doesn't bankrupt anyone.
So that we make our money back and it'll be pretty good.
And people see it.
But mostly so that the people involved, me and the director
and the head of ART, the company I'm in at the moment,
it's just basically three people.
And I'm not really part of the company.
We're all just sort of freelance.
It's just like the director.
You get some equity, man.
The director, I'm the head writer.
And then there's like the ART guy.
And we're all working to put this.
I wish I was head writer on something.
Me too.
To put this.
Actually, I don't.
But I feel sorry for the opposition.
So that the company and each of us
could get a main recognition so that we can make more stuff.
Because that's how you do anything
is you are known by people.
So like we make it.
Exposure.
Yeah.
Exposure, there.
That's what I'm working on in the real world.
In the internet world, I'm doing a webcomic.
And it's pretty cool as well.
I don't really know what else.
I guess I quit YouTube, but I already talked about that.
I don't know if you want to get on the show,
because it's so early in the planning.
But we were talking about this the other day of our Oost
accord.
And we might be working together on something, maybe,
if it pans out.
Yeah.
I think it's so fucking cool.
Wait, can you feel ever so slightly less vague?
So I know what you're talking about.
Something with jailbait.
Oh, I don't think I heard about that.
You said jailbait?
No.
Something with jailbait.
Something with jailbait is involved.
That's what you write when it's like the NSFW,
like Undertale, but like an animal tail, like jailbait.
That's what you type in if you want the rule told you to hold it.
Obviously, you started out on YouTube in the internet as a whole.
What do you want your ideal balance
to be between those two worlds?
Because obviously, we all think that the real world stuff
is super fucking neat and cool.
But you love the internet as much as we want you to be on.
Well, it's not like I don't love the real world.
Sure.
Because I have no writing experience
beyond what I've done for this gig, this writing gig.
So I've learned a lot very quickly,
because you get exposed through people talking about things
and you read books that they recommend.
And then I know more than I did.
But it feels scary, because I didn't go to college for that.
I don't really know what I'm doing, but I'm figuring it out.
And once the fruits of my labor start becoming real things,
I can show people rather than just like,
yeah, a couple of years down the line,
or maybe the film will be in production.
Well, there's a video, right?
There's a trailer.
They can't, no.
The trailer's secret, and no one can see it.
Well, because it's not the final trailer.
But this is just an idea.
No, it's just fine.
They can know that there's a secret trailer,
because it's cool and mysterious, but they can't see it.
Link in the description.
Well, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So what do you want the balance to be?
Other balance?
Like what would you just want to do,
like have this be your job, because it's
fulfilling in a lot of ways to you.
and then come home and then make a comic page or to a day?
Um, all the balance, yeah, in terms of work, I want the writing to be, like, I don't want to
let it slip by, like, I don't want to be like, oh, there's this thing I could be doing, I could
be writing, but, you know, I'm more interested in this, like, stuff that is, like, less immediately
viable, like, if I'm tied to someone else's work who is also trying to make it real and work.
Then it's like, it's more likely that that's going to be a thing and that's going to make me
money and then that's going to further, like, make me money in the future. So it's, like,
a better investment of time. So I want to work hard on that right now.
Big industry, dude.
Are you waiting to say that?
True. It is a big industry.
Pipo's got that big industry energy.
And, like, fucking, um, the writing, I wanted to be, like, 70% or maybe 80%. Like, the stuff
that I was doing on YouTube, it always felt like a hobby, even though I was trying to make it a
real thing. It's just, like, I could never give a shit enough about it. The webcomic stuff is,
like, more fun and I enjoy that a lot more than the YouTube stuff, but it still feels like a hobby
because I'm, like, I'm still, I don't feel like I'm good enough at drawing to be, like, you know,
making people, like, turn heads or whatever. But, like, doing the writing stuff, I would be getting
better at writing in general, so, like, my comics will improve. So, like, maybe it'll be, like,
I don't know, it just depends on, like, who gives a shit about the, the, the, the hobby
comic stuff. Do you see yourself becoming a fully offline creator? Do you see yourself
becoming, like, like, a writer by trade and online and that stuff? Or, or is the goal always to
become an internet patron of man? The goal, I think, is just to be a hybrid. Okay. Yeah. Like, I don't,
I don't see, like, it used to be you're either an internet guy because you're young or a real guy
because you're older and the internet wasn't really around while you were growing up. But, like,
there's more people now that are in the industry from, like, doing internet stuff, like me. Like,
they made DVNR accounts and people hired them because, like, they liked their art.
Like a sugar and whatnot. Yeah. And, like, Lauren Faust as a DVNR, Faust as a DVNR as well.
It's like, um, internet and it's like, you can have both. I can be known as, like, the guy who
writes the thing or I can be probably more well known as the guy who writes that comic.
And I get money for both, probably. Yeah. As long, like, as long as your work's getting out there
in one form or another, right? Dude, that's me. Nice. That's like you as a Muppet. Yeah, he's got
Muppet Nose Syndrome. There we go. Yes, that's what I'm doing. Thank you for taking
my everyday deuce interview with me. I hope you've enjoyed this wonderful evening. I asked this
because my mind's been completely in, like, my future as these are the, like, the, like, literally,
like, as we speak, the final days before I'm applying to college and if I don't get into any of
the ones that I applied to this year, it's real sad a little bit. So I've been thinking about,
you know, my future, if I get it, if I don't get in my, my path in life, what I want to do this year
in general. And so I've just been interested in these, I felt this way more or less for a couple
years now, but really it's sunken now. But I always feel like I'm on the precipice of something,
not just me personally. I know that feel, bro. Yeah. Yeah. I used to constantly say that phrase,
like, oh, I'm like on the cusp. Yeah. I always felt like, oh, I'm on the cusp. And a lot of the
times I was on the cusp, and then I crossed the cusp into a new cusp. Yeah. It's like you're,
oh, I'm on the cusp of 100,000 subs. And then I hit that. And then I'm like, oh, now I'm on the cusp
of 200,000 subs. And it's like, at some point, there must be some cusp that you round. And then
you go, I'm satisfied with having crossed this cusp. I don't need to cross another cusp. Do
you think it's possible? Do you think that's like a real thing? I think you're always going to want
to get to the next stage of something no matter what. You always want to be making progress.
Imagine if you retire, but you're still like a cabbage farmer. You're going to be like,
I want to farm these cabbages even fucking harder. Even if you don't get out of your
field, professional field, you're always going to want to get to a new cusp of something. Right.
For me, the thing that I want to do the most is I want to be able to work on more things that
aren't for-profit strictly by having the things that I work on that are for-profit make more
profit for less effort. So I want my for-profit ventures to reach a point where I have found the
perfect balance. Because with my main channel, for instance, it's always been for-profit and also
for-passion. And so it was always about getting better, covering material I wanted to cover and
stuff. But I reached a point where the things I sincerely want to do are not going to make my
channel more profitable. Just doing whatever I want, doing what would suit me best is not to
say that a type of video that I would super want to do wouldn't be successful, but just I don't
necessarily want to just do video. I like doing music a lot. I like working on other projects
that are just weird or not marketable. And so I still am not making as much money as I want to
be. So it's like, how can I make it so I can take time away from my main channel to go work on these
other things without that meaning that I no longer have the standard of living I want to reach?
So the biggest reason I've put so much egg in the basket of me and Nate doing a show together,
for instance, is that I think he and I could do a show that as long as the setup is perfect,
if everything is in its right place and all we have to do is just deliver, then it's a type of
content I can imagine being good for less effort in the individual production. Where me and Nate
just having a conversation can be an entertaining piece of media. And if it's well made, if it's
like well structured, then, you know, I think people would like it. And then like, if that's
where all our income comes from, I don't have to worry about making four main channel videos a month
or, you know, a certain number of Patreon exclusive podcasts or whatever, it could just be like, hey,
I go to work to do this fun video project, and the videos are good and people like them. And then I
go home and I just make weird songs and fucking learn to draw and write a book or something, you
know. Do we pay the editors enough to have them cut out things if we don't want to be in the podcast?
Yes, we do. Would you say it's fair that you are maybe not banking on this show taken off,
but you are putting most of your effort into the show you're doing with Nate? And do you think
that, how do I phrase this? Do you think that if this show does not take off or does not
succeed, you're going to be in deep shit? No, the opposite will be true, because-
It'll be way better than I expected. This is basically like a producer's sort of scam, like a
smoke screen. Well, like, like part of, this is part of why we're trying to talk about moving
somewhere cheaper. Like, where I am now, I kind of am in that kind of circumstance where it's like,
if I was putting my all into something me and Nate were doing and we lived here and it didn't
work out, then it would be like, it would be, you know, harsher. But like, no matter how much work
I put into the thing I do with Nate, I still have the main channel. I still can do four videos a
month on it and make money, you know. And at this stage, like what's keeping that channel alive
is like, I just write a bunch of scripts and I send them to DeVoo and he edits them at whatever
rate he can and that frees me up to explore alternative business ventures. So like, that's
where I Am Games comes in. Like, I've probably spent more time on I Am Games than I have on my
main channel in the last three months. It just isn't as instantly profitable, but like, you know,
it is growing. So it's always like this weird constant like min-maxing of trying to figure out
like what can I do that will that will add profit to my life without taking away time for me to just
live and do what I want to do, you know, like what what business ventures will make me more money,
but I can still make an album every month or whatever.
There's a question I've been thinking about for a while and I've contemplated it myself,
being somebody who does YouTube and has a job. How much sense does it make to position yourself
as a YouTuber such that your primary focus is to basically clock in for your like, you know,
nine to five, like four days a week. Yeah, doing your YouTube show that like is your for-profit,
you have to do it. It's like you're there to be profitable as and then like and then you're spare.
Oh, now I get to do the funds. Well, I mean, at least you've got creative control. I mean,
that's a huge thing. That's a huge thing. I mean, the kind of show that we are playing that we're
trying to do is fun to do. Like, I agree. It's a type of show that I like watching and I like
creating. Like, I love red letter media. It's like, yeah, fucking half of the thing I consume on
YouTube. Please don't call it red letter media ripoff. It makes you sound so gay.
Just call it pleaven the weave with you and me, please. The pleaven the weave was founded as a
red letter media ripoff. Of course. That was the idea. It's all just a degrees of separation. It's
out of degrees of separation. I mean, I consider about not making us not sound like
if you ask me to describe the Digi Bro channel, I would say, oh, it's an ego wrapped ripoff or
it's a Mr. Plinkett ripoff. Like we've done videos in the voices. Like my biggest video series is
called Your Anime Sucks. It is a YMS ripoff. Like, I don't find anything wrong with that because
all creativity is a ripoff. Okay. I understand. I feel you. I think it's doing something that's
not a ripoff. All I'm saying is that I think you could describe the show in more flattering
to me. I mean, it's good. It's not just that. The reason I like to describe it that way is that
like that to me is like a really intense promise because like nobody does higher quality versions
of this style of content than red letter media to say we're doing a red letter media ripoff.
Like we're going to it's like saying we're going to hit that level of quality and that to me,
if somebody tells me I want to make a video that level, then I think, oh, shit, like that's serious.
Ripoff is not a flattering term whatsoever. It's extremely like derivative. I mean, well, yeah.
Everything's extremely derivative. I used that wrong. I used that word wrong. I mean, it's bad.
Derogatory. That's what I was thinking. Yeah. Anyway, I'm not even honest. I don't even give a
shit. Like if everybody thinks it's a shillgasm, then whatever. Like all that matters is when the
episodes come out, if they're entertaining, I don't give a fuck if you literally think it is a
straight ripoff. If you watch it and you like it, that is what matters, you know?
It's not like red letter media fucking invented the two man talking.
Sure. No. It's just Teebacked that. Yeah. That's right. That's right. Fuck yeah. We're
going to go back, dude. So almost there. The biggest things that will set us apart is we have a very,
like obviously we're going to bring our unique aesthetic, our unique approach to comedy and
who's ours. Whoever's involved. Anybody who happens to be on the show, just like with
Pleeve and the Weed, where it was me and Jesse's unique voices and then everybody else who got
involved, every guest episode had some of that person in it. The episode with Munchy is a very
Munchy take on the Pleeve and the Weed. God, I wish it wasn't.
It's old Munchy. Very, very 2018 Munchy. Oh yeah, 2018. Back in the day.
Yeah. Completely different. Now I'm only quiet Munchy. What's up guys? Quiet Munchy is back
for this episode. Just wanted to say that I'm having a good time. My mom's upstairs and doesn't
want to hear me recording. She says I'm banned from recording on the PCP if I'm doing it secretly.
What's up guys? It's me, daddy. I'm here to record a daddy rap. My actual real life father is
upstairs and he can't know that I have a daddy's fashion or something like that. Or else he might
be too happy and decided to do stuff that even I won't go to. We better just not open that can of worms.
Talking about Digi, talking about being the cusp of things. I guess just like future stuff is on
the mind and I want to know how everyone is doing because I feel like, I mean, I don't know, what
tale is all this time? We don't talk that much in the PCP chat. We do way more than we used to.
But I mean, I feel like I know what Ben is up to. I feel like me and Ben hang out. We have our own
venues. Yeah. I mean, I just assume everybody knows what I'm up to because it's always the same thing.
I have no idea. You know what I'm, what do you think I'm doing? Well, I guess what you just told me
just now. I mean, well, that's like future plans. But like, what do you think I'm doing? I think
you're sitting in your room and you're writing all day for anime reviews. That's not even slightly
close to true. Okay. Well, I don't know. I write maybe an anime review like three days out of the
month. Okay. I spend a lot of time on I Am Games and just having living life. I mean, I spend a lot
of time watching anime for a finish or no finish or fail. Yeah, finish or fail. Hey, wait, Digi,
you paid me $100. Do you not want to use the intro? Is something wrong with it? Like? Oh,
that was the intro for the other for like the the main channel version of finish or fail,
which I canceled because it costed a lot of money and didn't get any views. Okay. So you're just
going to not use that? I mean, I could. I didn't even think about it. Like, I literally never even
considered. I'm not scorned. I'm just saying get your money's worth out of me. You're absolutely
right. I just never thought about it at all. But uh, yeah, I'll do it. I'll put it in there.
So hard to make. Going back slowly to the topic I was saying before, I'm just wondering for my
future plans, if one day I'm making weaguas and I'm just like, man, I sure hate making these. Sure,
don't enjoy doing this job that I have to do to live. And I guess I'm wondering if
if youtubers are way too spoiled and whiny babies, because like I go to my job, I go to my job five
days a week and I put in my hours, like whatever, more than eight hours or whatever every fucking day.
And like, it's it's nice that I can my job is that I can't really leave it at the door. I have to
check emails and be on top of stuff. It's a real professional job. But like, to a degree, you can
kind of leave things there and you can leave. I feel like I don't want to give youtubers too much
fucking shit. But I do feel like the burnout rate, just specifically in the sense of like,
you're still doing your stuff, but you're just like, man, this sucks. I don't want to do it. And
then things just take longer to come out. The fucking the weird thing about youtubers is that like,
you make up yourself what your obligations are. That's true. And something I've been trying to do,
and this is kind of like my it was sort of my resolution going into the new year, was that I
wasn't going to like, meme myself into believing I had to do any particular thing. Because like,
I'll get it in my head where I'll be like, Oh, I have to do a video about like this type of show
or this length or this whatever. And like, I have to launch this venture and like, at the end of the
day, like, what succeeds or fails is so like up to chance. And so like, there's predictable elements
to it. But like, what people will want from me. Like, you know, maybe I make a video that is about
like the newest show. And I talk about it for 35 minutes. And I'm analytical. I'm funny. And the
video gets 300,000 views. Probably I'll gain some patrons based on it. But also, maybe I like, release
some random song. And like, one guy's like, that's my favorite song, I'm pledging $40. And like,
that's a better return on investment. Right. And it was just something I wanted to do. You know,
so it's like, yeah. And this, this is kind of what happened to me last year was that like,
when I went monthly with my Patreon, the idea was that it was just you're paying for everything I do
on the internet. Yeah. And there were some people who like, I have patrons who don't even watch my
main channel content who are like, I don't give a fuck about anime. I don't care.
We're the hardest of the hardcore audience, the one deepest in your shit. Yeah. Like, if I go down
a route where I'm only trying to appeal to those guys, I start losing patrons who only care about
the main channel. And if I only do main channel videos, I start losing patrons. Like, there was
a period where it seemed like everybody was telling me they wanted me to do like, big, long,
serious videos again. So I went, okay, I spent like a whole month on this Makoto Shinkai video.
And like, it came out and people enjoyed it. But it like, it wasn't enough. Yeah. Because a lot
of my fans were like, well, you like, this was not worth losing you for a whole month. It wasn't
worth not getting my deluge of podcasts that I listen to every day or my all my random vlogs,
you know. So like, at the end of the day, I always have to strike a balance between these people.
And the best way to do that is to just do what makes sense in the moment, because everyone
responds to passion. Like everyone, I did these couple of boogie pop vlogs, because there's new
boogie pop anime started. And like, everybody who watched them was like, this is my favorite
listening to you talking about anime forever, because I clearly care a lot.
I didn't watch this yet. But I when I saw this, I immediately hit the spark of, oh, I bet did
you really give a shit about this? And I was like, watch these at some point. Anyone else?
I'm starting to feel like an icy draft blow across my, you are, you are shoeless. I am
shoeless. I'm most sockless. Do you want me to turn the heater on? I mean, it won't affect the
audio. I could, I could do it. Hey, I got it. I could do with the heater. Wait, wait, hold on.
I just want to say, I'm not texting anyone. I'm not sexting. Don't worry. I'm writing down notes
on my phone. So don't think I'm not paying attention, talking to the audience exclusively.
Cool. On, on this, this point of not meeting yourself into oblivion, I, I like that. And I was,
I've been thinking about that recently. And that's kind of what I've done. Like, uh, uh, but like,
if I wanted to, if I was so inclined, I could announce today, guys, uh, just letting you know,
not making the ghost in the shell video, just letting you know, it's not happening. I'm doing
other things. If I did that, that's going to be a sound bite. What would be the real consequences
of that? A few people would probably be a little grumpy and maybe a few like hardcore fans would
feel jilted and might like unpledged. But my channel has grown beyond this like promise I made
years ago. I'm still going to make it. But I, when I think about like people, this is fascinating
to me. I think so many YouTubers box themselves into a corner with their, and just like,
they didn't even plan to get there, but where they find themselves in, they feel trapped.
And honestly, I don't even blame them. I think this is some sort of weird psychological prison
we built ourselves. I will say this, that like, I've put myself in a position where people do
get mad at me for canceling projects just because I cancel so many projects. Because to me, it's like,
I have an idea for a huge series that if it does succeed, I will go through this whole series.
But if I put out episode one and nobody gives a shit, then there's no reason to continue the
series. Like I created it under the impression it could be a huge success. So like, because I've
done that so many times, there are people who are like, you know, I start up a series and they're
like, I refuse to get excited about anything you're going to do. Maybe they don't like the,
I mean, if you make episode one of anything might not turn out as great as the idea could
potentially be flushed out to be. So maybe that's what the criticism is about. But sometimes it's
just like, sometimes like, for instance, with that finish or fail that you did the intro for,
like, I had written that in a relatively quick fashion thinking that it would be a one or two
week turnaround for editing. And it ended up being a whole month turnaround. And like, because of that,
it had the impression of Digi Bro didn't put out a video all month. And then because of that,
it only got it only got 60,000 views. And I was counting on it getting like 300,000 views. So
like, it was and I had poured a lot of money into it. So it was like, both the money and time.
It's like, I couldn't have afforded to do it again. If it was only if I was gonna have to wait for it
to build. So you're saying that in the end, you decided not to salvage the idea, but to slaughter.
Is that actually canikers? Thanks to actually do this. Yeah, I heard it. I heard it. I didn't believe
it. But I heard it for myself. He has two little plastic no he has a plastic gun and like a price
checker. He's got a magic gun. Where'd he purchase that cat, Icarus. Link sling car. That's the joke.
That's the joke. Tectonic improv. We were listening to Digi. Hey, I think a lot of people who might
not be in the Digi sphere, but in the journal piece of piece here, because I'm sure you've explained
this in Patreon podcasts and stuff like that. I'm sure a lot of people will want to know, like,
what the fuck was up with like being so weird and weird all the time. What if you mean like with
the weird like visuals in my videos? No, no, no, not like that. But I mean, like, making all like,
like, dude, we're fucking entering a new age, we're in the gecko estate, I'm gonna make all these
fucking high quality videos nonstop, you know, fucking a market marketing that marketing show,
how they marketed, fucking finish your fail, high average from now on, how they market a giant
so long fucking series for two fucking years, gonna go crazy, get ready for this shit, dude.
I have a YouTube thing, I have a YouTube thing to say Digi. Remember, I think it was a cool,
sorry, did I interrupt? No, fine, do it. Did I? Okay, do it. I think it was Digi does anime and
you put the footage in like a little tiny TV, like to get around copyright. That was just what
I was doing on my channel for like a year. Yeah, well, because it was the, it was before I realized
that you could just use 10 second clips. Well, I was making, I was making the Winnie the Pooh video,
and I tried, I used 10 second clips, but it's still got copyright claims. That's Disney shit.
Yeah, because that's Disney shit. So I had to use 10 second clips and put it in a tiny TV and
fuck with the contrast and brightness and put over like a static overly video effects on it,
just to get around copyright protection and have it, and have it monetizable.
And people in the comments were like, nice, nice Digi bro, Digi does anime reference, dude.
And I'm like, no, no, this is art out Digi. This is art out of adversity. I would never.
Well, okay, so Digi, you can see a silly sigh, just what the fuck was with avant-garde Digi
trying to do weird, like, hugely ambitious projects for a while and then just like stop
literally moved to Boston and lost all my money. Okay.
Well, because like last it was it started last year last December. I was like, I had been doing
just like nonstop deluge of small content. And some people liked it, some people didn't. And like,
people were like demanding that I start making like more meaningful shit again. So I was like,
okay, I'm going to make bigger, better videos. And I made a couple. And then I had an idea for
like, because like I had rewatched like a bunch of Jesse's videos, like the whole horseshoe
saga, I rewatched like a bunch of demolition D videos. And like, basically, I was like, man,
I really want to do more with the medium of video, like I don't want my stuff to just be
because my usual style is I just write a script, like without the impression it's going to be a
video. Like I just write it like an anime blog post like I used to back in the day. And then I
send it to DeVu and he edits it. And like he can go really crazy with the editing if he wants to,
or if I like, you know, request that this video be like really, you know, over the top. But like,
I wanted it to be better integrated stuff like stuff that was made for video that made sense
best as video. And so like the best idea I had of like, how can I talk about anime in a way
that will stay interesting will allow me to talk about big popular shows without having to review
them. But like I can talk about their history and like interesting stuff about them. So how they
marketed the whole idea was like, I can talk about Attack on Titan or something, and it's not an
Attack on Titan review, it's how they marketed Attack on Titan. And then I talk about the marketing
and then the way I would market the show was that each show I talked about,
I would market my video the same way the show was marketed. So the whole gimmick was supposed to be
that like, if for instance, there was a show where it had like a heavy Twitter presence,
then I would make a Twitter for this video and like do something similar to what they had done
that I talked about in the video. And the main thing that this all hinged on was that episode
two was supposed to be about Pop Team Epic. And Pop Team Epic marketed itself by having a whole
like ton of different artists contribute like short pieces to the show. And like all of it was
like stuff that could survive as Twitter video or as gifts. So like there was tons and tons of
people posting like three minute clips from Pop Team Epic on Twitter. And the show was created
as a marketing gimmick. Like that was the idea. They looked at this comic and they said we could
do all kinds of marketing experiments with it. So I was going to make that the second episode
of how they marketed the first one was more to explain basic marketing principles. And then
the second one would just be like utterly insane. And I was going to hire all of you to do parts for
it like hire everybody I knew to do like little three minute bits and then market it heavily
through Twitter and all this shit. And like it was going to be this big sprawling thing to just
have popular content that's actually good. Like it was just how can I make something that's both
good and will be successful by marketing it. So yeah, I started working on it. But the thing is
that episode one took too long to make partly because I got involved in several other big
projects at the same time where I started making a documentary and I started doing this other
shit and I was looking for a house. So it was like I just didn't put enough time into getting
episode one out the out the door. And then when I moved it was like I lost so much patronage
from the amount of time I had spent like working on all these big videos that I was like well
now I can't afford to take any more time away to work on big videos. I need to get the content
machine running again. So as soon as I moved in here I immediately launched the gecko estate
because the idea was these will be like hour and a half long videos that will appeal to my core fans
like the people who are unsubbing right now, the people who are unpaturing, which funnily enough
while a lot of those people did like it some of them had just stopped following me in general.
And so they just didn't even watch those videos like so there was no opportunity to like bring
those people back into the fold because they just weren't even paying attention.
But like you know so that was my first plan and then I was like oh my god living here
is expensive and I still haven't paid my taxes. I need to just work on making money for a while.
So then I was like now I'm gonna make fucking all populist videos and like
when how they marketed episode one was complete I just didn't like it enough. Like I didn't think
it was worth posting or continuing because it wasn't at the level of quality I wanted it to be on
because it was supposed to be an expensive venture. Like I was going to buy materials to build sets
and to like you know have poster arrays and have like people's art in it and like that was why you
know like for Finish or Fail I hired both you and Tom like I think 50 bucks a piece to do art for it
and like what did Tom do? Tom made a CG can of beer that I used very briefly at various parts of
the video because that one of the shows like the Finish or Fail ending has a preview for how they
marketed and one of the shows was like a show made as a marketing campaign for beer. So I had Tom
make me a beer to like show the way that they had done it you know. Anyway point being that like I
was intending to spend a lot of money on it and then when I couldn't spend money on it like when I
didn't have the money to spend it just meant the show wasn't gonna be what I imagined. And so like
by the time I could have even started on episode two I couldn't have paid a bunch of artists to
work on it if it was going to be Potthym Epic. Potthym Epic wasn't relevant anymore so it wasn't
going to be like real flash video. Right. So what you're saying is may ruin your content.
Got it. Thank you for validating my theories all along.
Make Tao. Make Tao. Make Tao. Make Tao. Make Tao.
Do you think that the hello market could come back when you have more money?
I mean I basically just came to the conclusion that the only way it would be possible is with a
Kickstarter campaign behind it. Like it would have to be funded up front because no matter what
it's going to be expensive and it's like it's just not it's not worth the turnaround like what I like
it was born out of this existential ennui of like I want to do content that will succeed but I also
want to do content I will personally think it's good. Watching demolition D videos will do that too.
Even though I really only think that he had like a couple of great videos towards the end of his
career like he was getting better and better. He retired right after he made like the best videos
he had done and then it was just like he's gone. I have two questions. First one just just to know.
So what you're saying is is that you're you were going to make all these crazy videos and then you
ran out of money and so you didn't and it just is like that's over and yeah it's pretty much I mean
it's just it couldn't it was no longer feasible and it still is not feasible. Okay okay sick all right
I want to know specifically what was the inspiration behind the the meme of marketing like this marketing
because marketing is a way to like I was looking at how does marketing like lost like all meaning
because it was used like in every single sentence you ever said for like months. Well yeah it was
it was a meme. The point of it was to create a meme that would make that was the marketing. Okay okay
my attempt to market the show was to constantly remind people of the show and just say how they
marketed how they marketed how they marketed as a series of the narrative how they marketed a series
of the narrative like you would just get it in your head and you would have to fucking see the
thing at that point you know. I mean that's what marketing is. When it dropped. Just repeat yourself
constantly. When the when how they marketed dropped I was like oh it's that thing it's that thing I've
heard. Yeah I've heard this and what is it. Wait wait wait does this brand have merchandise?
Whoa whoa whoa whoa. It has branding. It has the market. It has content. It has the other one that
starts with an M. Marketing. What was actually released was not like what episode one like I
stripped off the first like seven minutes of it that was like all because like originally the first
part of the video is all just establishing context of like what like how shows are marketed in
general. It was like all live action so it was like all these parts of me like using whiteboards
and stuff to explain. Does that exist anywhere in the world? Yeah well I haven't posted it online
yet. At the end of that video I'm like become a patron and you'll be able to see the uh the
uncut version and I never put that version together. Boy make that I want to see that intro. I want to
see the director's cut. It's like six it's like six minutes but the audio was not very good and
like we had just moved in so the house is weirdly barren and like it just looked and sounded like
shit and like DeVu I had thought like because I was doing a style at the time where I was occasionally
doing heavily edited vlogs or like I would just talk into the camera but then I would add tons of
shit on time. Was wearing an onion on my belt. That was the style at the time. I had expected it to
be like that but when I sent it to DeVu he didn't really add that much to that section and the stuff
he did add was like weird and jarring because I just didn't give him enough direction I guess.
So just that whole section I hated it and like he had finished it like almost two months before
I released it. I just was like well this is this I don't even want to look at it because I'm so
disappointed with it and I still had to do all those commercials that are in there which were
all just patron backer rewards so like so anything weird about the video is because it's not the
video it was supposed to be like it would have made sense but like because I'd already given up on
it it was just kind of like let's cut this thing in such a way that I can ship it out and then never
have to think about it again. Dan it's interesting because we always make fun of like producers who
do those things with movies. It's usually out of necessity you know. Yeah of course like nobody
wants to make like a bad movie I'm not even saying it was a bad video or anything but yeah I still
liked it. I still wish there was a number two. There could be in the future but it would be like
the approach I had because I had like a huge list of shows I was going to do and it was going to end
in like a three-part like film length like movie that was going to be How They Marketed Digi Bro
so like well there was going to be How They Marketed How They Marketed and then How They Marketed
Digi Bro. Oh the ultimate how they marketed when you kill yourself and then as a martyr as a
sacrificial artist that's the ultimate marketing tool. Why do you remember Van Gogh? Because he was
like gay or something right? Well the ultimate sacrifice being gay. He must have. I think he
did kill. I know he cut off his ear. I think he killed himself. I thought he died if I could
disease him. Because he only ever saw one painting two his like brother-in-law and I'm pretty sure
he killed himself. I'm not sure. He might I'm not sure Hemingway killed himself. There's him.
Yeah yeah yeah. What he's most known for is killing himself. David Foster Wallace if that even
is his real name. He killed himself. Hunter S. Thompson killed himself. Why Hunter S. Thompson
do it? I'm going to kill myself. Okay. He was like no. He was in his 70s but like if you watch videos
of him at the time. Guys if you need if you need to talk to someone call the suicide hall. His life
style had taken a toll on him. Yeah right. Didn't seem like life was probably that enjoyable. Girls
if you want to commit suicide call my number stand. I'll be out dude. But uh apparently like Hunter
Thompson had said at some point that like the one thing that kept him like that kept him going was
knowing that at the very least he had power over his own life that like he could like knowing he
could kill himself at any time was like a source of strength for him. Okay. And then one day he just
fucking was like well I'm tired. Time to catch this check I've been writing for the last 20 years.
Well I mean it's 70. Not bad. Yeah not bad. I think he was in his 70s. So I feel like it's
probably pretty uncommon for people to kill themselves at that age. I feel like most most
suicides are probably younger people. Most suicides aren't older people. Really? Yeah.
Yeah. Old people kill themselves. I mean it's probably like a spike at youth and then like a
low or whatever. I mean it's like when you're young even if you fuck up your life really bad
you're like well at least I'm young. And you're also like physically resilient and more likely to
survive the attempt. I think also yeah Thomas like yeah I mean old people falling in the back
knocking the door down. Thank you fucking god. Okay what would it be fair to say that instead of
trying to do all these these big big budget blockbusters you're trying to settle down and
make things work which have already proven themselves. Like right now I'm just like running
every imaginable get rich quick scheme I can. It's not about getting rich quick though it's about
how does this sustain a long term business model. Maybe that's what you mean though.
But like yeah okay get rich in the long term. Yeah yeah it is. Like for instance something
me and Tom have been working a lot towards is defining alternative revenue sources. So like
doing things like selling merch or like more intimate products because like the videos themselves
it's like it's hard to define what people want or what they're like how do you tell somebody
like what your videos are worth or like something one guy might think that the main channel video
I spent a month on sucked and he doesn't care. And then the next guy is like oh this uh this
like three minute video of you just like ranting about something is my favorite thing you've ever
made. So it's like it always comes down to just like this vague sense that people pledge because
they just kind of like me in general and or like the way things are going but like if you're selling
a t-shirt then it's like the t-shirt is worth $20. If you pay for it you get the t-shirt you know.
And so like having those less complicated things mixed up in it is it's comforting to know that
there's like a product you've assigned a value to people are paying that that amount to get that thing
and there's no questions about it there's no like feelings involved it's just like buy things you
like you know. I do like Patreon has always been like a weird model uh yeah yeah but we've talked
about that before. And also just like you know a lot of a lot of our reliance on Patreon has always
come down to like the most hardcore people will pledge the most money but like you can also just
get people to give you money for things like a lot of a lot of those hardcore fans while they
like because it's such a weird and vague sense of like how much a video is worth they just
basically pledge whatever they think they can afford long term. Yeah. Whereas if you sell them
something they might even pay you like like let's say we made a t-shirt every month there are some
people who might only pledge like two dollars on Patreon but because there is a concrete product
and they want to support us it's like oh I'll give you $20 every time you make a new shirt
you know and that's basically a $20 Patreon you know. Yeah more like they just feel more
aggressive about it. Right exactly and there there are a lot of people who like don't even really
give us money but we'll buy products we sell. I'm sure yeah there's plenty of those. You know what's
always struck me as interesting though with the Patreon model it's the people who are the most
into you and feel like maybe they like I am not the kind of person who donates to anyone's Patreon
that's not who I am but my patrons obviously are and everyone's patrons are so I'm not trying
to shit on my patrons or anyone's patrons but like what the business model there relies on
attracting the people who are the most attracted to you and I immediately find that like a weird
relationship what I would much rather have is people who just generally kind of like me I would
rather have more of those than like the cult following who like really care because frankly
I can never have the kind of like one-on-one relationship that's kind of weirdly implied
by like being a patron or like part of a patron discord. I mean I wouldn't even call myself
sorry guys I don't think I'm friends with most of my patrons I think I'm associates or like we
communicate and I am acquaintances. I mean at least acquaintances. My patrons have like kind of a
general fear of me of my irons. That's what I want for them. Me too. Me too Digi patron heads.
Nate I always I've always liked about Patreon. I always I've always enjoyed the fact that
theoretically I could subsist on only a few people. Well you know I don't like it though.
I feel weird about people like I don't know like like you got like cam girls for example and cam girls
have a thing going on and I don't think youtubers who have patrons are too far away from a cam girl
especially me. Especially me. You got guys who give like thousands of dollars to some of these girls
or whatever and like that's obviously like a romantic thing and it's like they're doing it for
like a relationship almost and that's like weird and off-putting. Well to me I'm more than happy
and I genuinely want to have a relationship with the people following. I would consider many many
fans of me friends. I have an entire discord chat which Ben and hip are both in the golden
childhood founder. I would consider everyone and they're a friend and even some people who aren't
in there. I could name I could name drop easily dozens of people from our fck who I would consider
friends. Sure sure and who I like. I'm not saying I'm not saying there's nothing wrong with the way
you think I'm saying we think of things differently. Yeah and I feel the same way to a degree. Like
guys like Lee one of my biggest patrons he's been around for a long time. We get along quite well
we talk all the time I like my pager discord. I feel like it's weird to even quantify a relationship
that way but like I like him he's a patron but like there's this there's this monetary thing
that hangs over it that makes the whole thing a little bit strange not like a pure like friendship
we met up and we broed out or whatever and frankly I kind of like a more corporatized
sanitized thing or like honestly what it makes me think about is I feel like we are cultivating
YouTube shooters like instead of school shooters it's like YouTube shooters we're like getting
these people we're like teasing these people almost with like we're like people like me or
whatever uh they're like because I don't know like I attract a certain kind of guy who's like
alt-right migtail dangerous like my videos are like for basically past Nate as I feel like a lot
of people make stuff to like fix their mistakes along their path so knowing who I was probably
like lowly guys who are like you know uh don't know a lot of stuff about girls and or I don't know
maybe see me as a little bit of a role model and stuff well how mark what this is a big-ass
chapstick uh it's fucking it's blood orange flavor it's grunge I love it um hey this isn't a big
thing did I just invaded I just invaded the girls podcast yeah yeah yeah I was a male presence
invading a female space that's what they call rape my friend uh guilty as god
anyway just like red country you'll be able to fucking sync the videos together you can
find the part in your stream where ben did that and check out yeah so yeah watch it watch them on
two monitors they are live they're live on um fuck what's like what's your youtube yeah yeah the
how the cropping cropping your kids oh they're your kids okay what's cool uh I I completely
understand the want to have like like what did you say as well like a product you put out
they're paying for that I'm into building walls my yeah exactly that being strong beautiful strong
walls make good neighbors they do unironically why do you even have a picture just why not just
say like there are no rewards this is just unironically so that people will pledge me more
because they feel like they can get closer so I am absolutely yeah you're inviting this myself
absolute tap dance on that line of it that's correct no I've completely crossed the line I'm way
past uh yeah but I mean I mean I never would have known what it's like unless I try it so I mean you
know uh I'm not saying I'm gonna shut it down or anything I have no intention to I'm just the
relationship is interesting I frankly don't understand people who give money to people online
because I don't and I never have I mean I patron although you know what I'll say I almost even
you've been patroning me for a dollar a month for like two years meaning you've given me like
$20 and I appreciate that I've been patroning you five dollars like a million billion years
when I find myself in a situation where I can get a thing for free you got your you got your name
in the video you got your name in the poo video in the credits at the end what am I gonna choose
between free and paid like there is no choice I just well go to the free option maybe it's like
for a lot of people yeah we we make content that they like and it's like you know what you can you
read one piece for free but you'll buy volumes every now and then or you know like because you
like it that much I mean I from well let me say let me say this I'm a little bit of an idiot and
just talking out of my ass because I actually was very tempted the other day to pledge to nexus mania
as the only person I've ever been even tempted to patron to because he just seems like such a hard
worker and deserves good things in his life true and for that brief moment when I didn't actually
pledge I sort of understood I believe a lot of it is like a sense of like be the change you want to
see in the world because that's always how I've approached it is like I patron people because
I want this type of content to feel as though it can continue yes you know it's like I I see like
someone like me um you know I have a even if I talk about a lot of popular things and even if my
opinions are shared by a lot of people I generally have unpopular opinions yeah and like yeah if you
want to be like you know really really popular sorry usually pays to have the popular opinions
yes so if people are like hey you have an unpopular opinion that I share I want to make sure that you
are able to keep having your voice heard then like that's usually why and they'll they'll give to
something like that and like most of the people who I would ask if they're not doing it for a reward
tier like if they're just giving money with with that they don't care about the rewards it's almost
always some kind of like yeah I want to prove a point by like giving money to this I think it for
me I want to align myself with this that too for me I don't pledge to a lot currently but I want
to pledge to way more for me it's as simple as I mean what everyone says at the end of the video
if like it's content please yeah that's why I've been a long time patron of Japanese emoticons
yeah me that's true uh there's I use their services and I appreciate the what they bring
to the table culturally there are many small youtubers with small patreons small penises
and small penises as well that I genuinely think you know there's a good chance if this person
doesn't make money and they'll just stop these people are making content which I love and I watch
like every week do I want that to stop no I want to make sure that I that I just personally get to
have this content in my life yeah I mean in my opinion in many ways it comes back to benefit me
as somebody who has a patreon yeah because like it normalizes patreon to have more people on there
there's more people like it like the more people are successful through it the more people will
get one the more the cultural understanding will be that you can promote art this way yeah and so
it's like you know in some way just like being a part of that system will come back around to help
me as a creator too you know shout out to walters world travel youtube series he's like a dad I feel
the same way I feel like you know if you're a patreon person you know it's nice it's nice it's nice
to at least it's nice to be putting your money where your mouth is a little bit so I don't pledge
that much but like I think I pledged like a dollar to the hippo I think I pledged a dollar to mage
and maybe like actually japanese emoticons dot me might might be it that might be yeah that might be
I also like until moving here I just had like more money than I knew what to do with so like
the part of the reason I would patron people is it's just like well you need the money more than I do
so I guess I haven't been in that position yeah like if I if I have like it's like a lot of the
people I patron it's either because I am a huge fan or I'm a friend of theirs or I just like
legitimately like their content more than my own yeah like if I watch somebody and they have a
patreon and I think like this guy is an inspiration to me then it's like I feel as though I am getting
something like like I'm getting something tangible from them like yeah you made this video that was
amazing and it made me want to go make something amazing and I'm gonna give you money for like
in trade for that that all makes sense I guess it's just a little bit of the objectivist in me
that just says my job in life is to make me as good as I can possibly be including monetarily
so I'm just gonna hoard all my money and build myself up so I can be the you know a fucking
rock eventually you will have so much money that you eventually not know although I could also see
you just putting all of that into a fund for your kids college or something so like certainly that
would be on the on the to-do list for life at some point yeah I mean like if I was a millionaire
this would be a different a different ball game but I am not I am not close in them give it another
month or two give another give another patreon.com slash best yeah see how it goes I can't wait to
become a millionaire and the federal reserve sent you the gold play button yeah yeah oh my god
I wish real life was as cool as you did you just send me a gold dollar bill did you guys I don't
know who this was they said you're a gold tombstone random guy I saw on Twitter today but I just
saw some dude just said like so this is a cool interaction I had with YouTube he's like hey guys
like at Team YouTube whatever I've got 158,000 subscribers and yet you said you're like denying
me getting my silver play button could you tell me why they said like hey we've reviewed this and
apparently you've either violated our content guidelines or you've got too many strikes it's
like okay here's the thing though I have no strikes and my I have not violated the content
guidelines in any way would you care to tell me how though we cannot comment any further you are
ineligible for the button but like I don't know where I fucking saw it was just on Twitter somewhere
but uh fuck YouTube I guess is the point just just I still don't have a silver play button it's been
fucking you gotta talk to him again dude YouTube just would be so better off if they just all you
could do nothing differently in this situation but just explain the reason because if you don't
explain it it looks like you're hiding something how many new people how many new people yeah past
the hundred thousand like every week like it can't be that many it can't be that many no I mean I don't
know what maybe a hundred I would I don't know be surprised if it was even that many yeah I mean
sure there's some data on that something there's probably data by the way I'm coming soon you better
have that fucking silver play button ready for me because I'm coming for it YouTube I'm gonna
want it day one so get to work I mean coming for that gold I'm coming for that diamond I never
get it Nate they they sell uh face diamond 10 million I've seen that I've seen the fake ones
right that's what I'm gonna get I want that fucking button when I cross a hundred or now
they get you give a plaque instead of a button now why maybe when I hit 20,000 I'll like carve one
for myself out of like balsa wood yeah good idea did you and Nate yeah real question why are you
both doubling down on two companies which you both hate because YouTube is still the biggest game in
town and for the cut for what I'm doing it's by far the best option will you switch if there is a
genuine actual real alternative capillary alternative you know what I'm probably just upload
to both and then just like play the fucking field because why not just I'll optimize on every plan
I mean I'm thinking of doing like a bit shoot and shit it's just that I don't really think my content
is in the realm of like danger for being like destroy like with Viagra the goal of Viagra I
will tailor my fucking shit to work on YouTube whatever that requires I will do it it is a business
to succeed on YouTube requires frequent uploads oh there it go I would say that you
damn boy yeah thanks um you survive somewhat because no one hates you
you're very good at not having enemies I feel like that's a lot of the reason why no one comes
out because I think it's because I'm a middle child and I'm the mediator of the fan you gotta you
gotta you know you it's just like it's just like it's just like Dale Carnegie says and ways to
fucking uh how to make friends how to make friends and and influence people yeah if you don't have any
enemies find a way to make some because the most steadfast allies are enemies you've turned into
friends it's just like how Skeeter says and Doug funny people are going wild for this pizza as Dale
Carnegie also says in how to win friends influence people tippy that yellow haired pup that my daddy
bought for me for 50 cents was the light and joy of my childhood until one tragic day he was killed
by lightning not 10 feet from my head anyway on to what else I was saying no further elaboration
you know uh it's a great book I uh it's true I don't seem to have many or any enemies even though
I've said some shit that people don't care for in the past these because I'm so damn conciliatory uh
and maybe it makes me I don't think I'm a pushover uh but I do think a lot about how to not fuck up my
life and that's a big one that's a big one not just making people hate me I mean whatever even on the
basically anytime you're in it I hate you name what are you talking about correct where you're
saying Tom every time we're even on the pcb and we have an argument like that like I've noticed
your strategy is basically to always like find a point of agreement or something or at least yeah
or at least say the words that kind of sound like you're agreeing well it's gonna help them they're
retarded because I hate so much like I could argue with a socialist all day I could say like no
capitalism's good and like a harder comic could be like no communism's good and like I'm sure they've
got good things about kindness like I'm sure I would say good things about capitalism like we're
wasting our time doing that shit what we need to be is go way the fuck back and be like okay so do
you think it's actually okay to like take the the the sweat off of someone's brow we like worked it
as capitalism would like say and they'd be like yeah for this reason I'm like okay here's why I
disagree and like but that's a meaningful debate not just like 400 million dead in Russia versus
you know like the poor the working poor are oppressed in the whole west or you know the way
I feel exactly the same time I want to have productive debates slash arguments not just
waste my time this is the way it is for everyone on the pcb yeah where we all say something fucking
retarded and they're ever and else is like that's obviously stupid and then they dial up and then
we all dial it back to what our actual point is was easy which is extremely reasonable
like all agree on yeah yeah yeah I mean like personally like I I will go out of my way to
frame things as stupidly as possible it makes me so mad it's so the conversation can last longer
I mean like I'm trying to fill time on a show where we have to have like yeah we gotta talk about
something a big part of it is something that isn't even real honestly I've trained myself to speak
this way and like granted I've always been long-winded but like I have to put out hours and hours and
hours of content every week I can't really come up with new shit to say all the time and most
arguments have been had before so it's like how can we have this argument in a way that will be
really dumb and waste everyone's time so that we can fill in our content that is so true
we were kind of talking with with econ about this yesterday uh about like I mean at least I was like
the purpose of media and like is it not just kind of wasting everyone's fucking time to not just be
like like read a textbook on whatever it is you're arguing about don't fucking watch like uh the
Lion King to learn about why revenge is not whatever the fucking point of Lion King is uh but then
econ made a very reasonable point of uh what media does is it it's basically the Huey's law
should I say which is totally redundant whoever it's like it it packages a moral and you fucking
take it down you're like I learned why the lions are like good because it's bad to just kill people
and kill your you know your brother so that you can be king you shouldn't do that I don't know why
if it's a bad example a bad choice okay undertale undertale
is good the moral that's what I learned so I was a little bit cynical about like if if media even
has value because I feel as I think I said this before but as I go forth on my crusade to talk
about anime and video and shit I'm letting you know right now I'm gonna be talking about same
points forever it's just gonna it could recontextualize in the different show that happens to be the one
but the the fundamentals are the same and I've elaborated them many times in the pcp that's
what it's gonna be if you read any author or listen to any speaker yeah like that is what they do
yeah they just repeat themselves I mean does you have to do you try to speak the truth and I
guess you could say that it's about you want to find the one way they're able to deliver it aka
like the entertainment value that's applied to like perhaps that way you deliver that message
that actually gets people to swallow it I mean oh I get it now there's there's been a ton of my videos
that like people will watch it and go like oh you already said this in an after dark video yeah
but like in the after dark video it's like I just had this idea it's just exploding out of me for
like 25 minutes it's not really well phrased it's not like thought through and then like sometime
later I think about it again and I'm like oh now I know exactly how to put it in a way that more
people will understand and I can make like a full video out of it and so it's it's usually just about
like how can I keep repackaging this statement in ways that will give it different nuance make
different people understand it and make the content feel different you know yeah yeah that's the point
I guess like you know it was interesting I saw this guy um Aziz Ansari he's like uh he's like a
American Muslim activist and he's had like some arguments with like Sam Harris but wait he said
a very interesting thing one time he described him as an activist but he's like comedian an actor
oh sorry it's very famous it's not Aziz Ansari it's um it's Reza Aslan that's right yes I'm pretty
sure it's Reza Aslan that's who it is not not the comedian uh him and Sam Harris like had some
arguments and like a while back he just came out he's like I've been debating people on like
philosophy maybe his thing is like you know Islam is good you know we just need to like
whatever doesn't matter um he's he's making this point he's been like I've been debating people
like Sam Harris and other people forever nobody fucking cares it's not changing hearts and minds
got a better idea I'm going to make tv shows that like show positive Muslim characters and like this
is just what I'm doing now it's it's the point is the same it's like convince people that like you
know Muslims are good or whatever and uh this this is just gonna be a way better way of changing
hearts and minds and uh yeah that's media for you I guess I mean you gotta trick people into thinking
they came up with the idea themselves that yes yeah that sounds like Huey's long action indeed
they watch a show it's like got like I don't know like a Muslim kid maybe he was like bullied by like
the the mean Christian kid in that episode and then at the end the Christian kids like man you
know maybe we're not so different boom you just indoctrinated a thousand ISIS members right there
lining up in the fucking trenches uh yeah so I guess that's how I got there I guess that's literally
what I've been saying I'm doing only it's my philosophy not his philosophy which means it's
better which means it's better yeah I guess a lot of people do that and uh yeah I guess that's it
sip and tea like kermit over there but that's none of my business
but but but recruiting members of ISIS that's none of my business
anyway he says calling up his business agency we've got two more boys
yeah
on the bottom of the cup is like join
that episode of the simpsons with join the navy yeah but in fact Yvonne Etniage yeah
that Yvonne Et CC right wait no CC Etniage for Isaac yeah you're right you're right
well uh what else we got going on we could we could do some of the questions I put out a hashtag
wait how how long have we been going anyone can we tell what we gotta be in an hour right
definitely over an hour I would I would think oh go start recording oh it's 905 now
oh don't actually oh style I just want nervous what are we at what time we have no clue how to
tell okay I'm sure we've been going for a while and hopefully it recorded if not well fuck me
let's just do some fucking quick okay so we can't do the voicemails today
because we don't have them wait that button doesn't say go live does it it does we're recording
yeah we're recording yeah we're not we're not free about that way oh um right on hey hey by the way
I'm checked out I'll see you guys tomorrow we're not we're not on fat 32 right now are we no I
got it okay thank god uh uh uh so no no voicemails right now because we can't do it live like this
it'd be weird and hard so um twitter questions I did some pretty questions all oh my god all salvage
swatter swatter swatter swatter swatter swatter swatter swatter swatter swatter
here we go okay now swatter uh yeah okay let's get some more bongo uh if you guys want to pull out
your phones you can look at them too my step my dad she's fcp and I'm so not used to this hat I know
there we go all right uh searching latest I believe twitter for my phone I can't why did you guys
all delete twitter from your phone because it's literally do not have self-control like me just
just turn the notification this is self-control what did you call me a human robot yesterday
wasn't anything was said I don't think I called you a human robot Nate this is better than I don't
remember never mind never mind this is like this is like even better than self-control it's robot
oh god all these questions are already shit um this is why we don't do it anymore um these are all
bad why at the world we feel bad about your question um okay here we go this one all right
this is whatever kind of cool at rad a cool gamer asks what piece of media do you feel the worst
about liking the pcp avril Lavigne yeah what's that avril Lavigne's entire discography uh uh huh
a life's like this uh huh yeah that's the way that's the way it is and it is though but it is though
damn many of a type avril Lavigne is a choice life but she's into my japanese shit with her
hello kitty song she loves kakakawaii kakakawaii i never even heard that one before i think my answer
is he's singing parts i've heard a clip i saw a clip of it i think i feel the worst about liking
rap music from artists who are not okay with white people saying the n word i know what you mean
i know what you mean yeah yeah like when they adamantly in the songs are like yo white guys
don't be singing along to this shit and i'm just like come on guys like or like just a lot of there
are like a lot of rappers who have like an active disdain for their white audience hey i've got i've
got a question about that i've been i've been considering considering that issue do you think
because like okay if you are uh uh one of these people one of those people selling to the world
do you think it's is that a reasonable complaint to make considering that you're selling to a lot
of those white folks maybe if you said i don't want white people to talk about you've talked about this
before have we yeah yeah you know what i guess at the end of the day like the point of their music
is to be emotional to express how they feel so like if they feel uncomfortable with white people
saying the n word then like you know it's fine that they want to rap about that it's just like
when you're listening to something and it seems like it is attacking you personally and you can't
really argue back or you get the sense that this person would not be willing to listen to arguments
back then it's just kind of like you just can't help but get pissed off hearing it i know what you
mean i know what you mean uh monchi what are you most ashamed of like i i don't really have any media
that i'm ashamed of i mean i i like every i don't believe in like guilty pleasures really i like
everything that i like if i didn't like it then why would i like it i don't know well it didn't
necessarily ask if you were ashamed to say what do you feel the worst about like feel the worst yes
so like there's other ways like i i'm not ashamed of liking that music i just feel bad
because i like it yeah i know that the person does not like me um i guess i feel bad about
liking generic youtube shit just because it just because it like eats up your time and ruins your
life yeah and also i just feel like i'm not supposed to like it like i don't know sometimes i'll
upload youtube and i'll feel like what like what's the world like what what's it like out there past
past the forest and i'll go on the trending tab and i'll watch maybe one or two videos and i'll
think ha ha yeah okay and then close it and i'll think i should have hated that like like it shouldn't
have been even lukewarm or anything it should have been like i like i actively dislike this
and anything that's trending yeah if i see it and like i shouldn't like this this is horrible this
wouldn't be trending if it were worthwhile yeah hey monkey away asks why are you guys so averse to
talking about big topics you have passionate opinions on it's a lot more entertaining than
Nate's gay ass vacation stories i guess we did briefly touch on well we tried it we tried it today
and it was bad i didn't actually want to talk about capitalism because like yeah i don't like
i don't really admit i am no expert on economics yeah i don't i don't really feel qualified to talk
about it either passionately about have we not talked about well there's always the jq which we
might want to get an answer here you know i didn't know what that was i found out like a week ago
what the hell is jq it's a jewish question what is that oh he doesn't fucking know i don't i don't
i'll check tom's q and a for sure yeah i found myself restraining speaking about things that
interest me basically every single pcp episode i'll have notes and i'll be like wait a second i
forgot none of these people have the same interest in me time to delete half of it why would you
think so like why do you think that like what's the kind of stuff you bring up because like if
it's something like oh like i watched this anime that none of you guys have seen and i wanted to
talk about it like obviously i wouldn't talk about that i don't think there's any it's like that but
for instead of like shows is interest like like what's an interest you have that you don't think
any of us would be interested in talking history history's interesting to everybody it isn't
history i feel like an asshole every single time i i talk about like what what is something
historical that would not be interesting to people i don't know i think a lot of people
will consider it a rather boring school type subject in my mind related to some if you have
like there's a point to be made by history is not boring school is boring i mean i agree from my
perspective if anyone says anything i didn't know it is automatically interesting like yeah no matter
what in taking information i didn't think the thing is more like munchie doesn't know whether
we would make a good conversation piece he doesn't just want to say things that no no i don't i also
don't want you to just bring up history anecdotes with no like particular point behind them exactly
yeah so that's why i don't do it this is i'd be a weird asshole for doing that i mean i mean why
would you want to do that well no i'm saying i want to talk about history and other things not just
that but like why would i do it on the pcp when this is clearly not a good avenue if it's entertaining
and i guess everyone you know i don't bring up stuff i don't think it's entertaining for the
exact same reason and like well that sounds boring and gay so i think it's entertaining to me but in
this context with these people and for this audience no why i mean if you had like let's just
say you read a fucking book and like which i have i can't i don't believe you but like if you did
okay uh and there was like some like you fucking the the you know whatever the fucking fall of
pompeh and like you were like guys just listen to this fucking story about this thing that happened
in real life and then you told it in like a sick way or something like that i don't know maybe that'd
be cool i know i know i know a fact that we all be interjecting and joking and being like hey hey
hey munchy i know i know a fact about pompeh tell me if you heard this one in pompeh it was common
for people to just write on walls yes a lot of graffiti a lot of our enemies would say pom gay
and i was i remember i read i read a thing about like stuff like like archer archer not architects
archeologists they found like that all these messages carved into walls and stuff around the
city including the ironic joke everyone writes on walls but me that's good there's a fuck ton of
sex and pompeh that guy went on to bake homestuck yeah he then he then carved 18,000
hundred words of a story about it's about well it's a story about these four kids they don't
communicate in person they they but they they are friends through their wall star and they
erupt and they all die yeah but but they get transported to a new island yes uh where they
have to play a game to bring the old one back i like to imagine an old romanism just carving away
today's your 13th birthday though it was 13 years ago you were given life as only today you've
been given a name and people just looking on and whore like what the fuck is this guy do imagine
if someone just yeah they just carved like like a story prompt and they went yeah yeah and then they
do like a lot like rp like over like a whole thing and they had like tell like good fun like dnd
campaign or something over like a fucking over the side of like an industrial complex we could just buy
a wall and buy a wall right right we can build a wall yes that wall yes that wall see that's
what we're not all right yeah when that was the high point of this whole episode it was good time
to go out on a high then we have to build the wall we've decided right um we got a lot of people
asking for lectures let people talk about they want more lectures we don't have time we don't have
time i know if you guys want more lectures give us a shitload of money so that we can fly to each
other's place and lecture each other about bullshit so intangible you know i hate making it like i've
always said like hey guys if i make more money i'll finally be able to go to youtube i've always felt
bad about promise that because it's so vague and not concrete i mean it's the way to think about
i mean it is literally true in this case i don't think it's deniable that if we had the money to
group up we would do lectures i mean i would have needed extremely successful yeah yeah like
none of us knew that this was gonna happen far enough ahead of time to prepare i mean i was occupied
with i have i have i have like two and a half lectures maybe ready to go in the chamber but
it really none of them well none of them are like ready to go they all need they'll need research
i only have one and i have to do like extensive research to make it possible i i have can tell
after the show i'll tell you right now it's okay it's about the co-heating cambria album narrative
that sounds great that i would love to hear that i've got buddies who told me about it
tectonic improv's uh uh a top a top the fourth wall linkar is a top the fourth wall is a good
one to tide you over it's good it's it's it's very much like one of ours also there's a bunch of
really funny parts where it seems like the friends the friends that he's conscripted to listen to his
lecture seem really they're mostly okay but every now there's like one like heckler in the crowd
he seems like mad to be there and there's a couple of times where like they have some banter back
and forth and it's not quite sure like is this serious like are they actually mad at each other
are they gonna have words after this oh yeah yeah it's great that narrative compelling i did yeah
good i'll let you watch that um oh you can also watch down the rabbit hole different style but
same kind of content you know i'm thinking i'm thinking monchi wait wait wait about the down the
rabbit hole i mean i have i've mentioned the um the the poos adventures of in the lion king heart
fantasy films that's like a short one i've been thinking about maybe making that into like a down
the rabbit hole style video instead of a lecture because i don't know if there's enough there to
make into a full lecture but even if i do that i still have at least one lecture that i definitely
want to do but down the rabbit hole thing sounds sick yeah yeah yeah that one's been it's it's time
it's time to deliver on that one because the world still doesn't know yeah world still doesn't know
about lion king heart fantasy films there's some intense shit going on now tom are you reading
a question or something i was reading a question to monchi but he's been consumed by pizza tell me
uh uh uh the people want to know uh businessman when is newgill coming to
fucking linux well let me tell you boys and girls newgill is gonna come as soon as you give newgill
some of those fancy numbers i'm not talking about counting up i'm not talking about dividing
i'm talking about those three magic numbers on the back of your credit card you give that to me
dr newgill and you've got three or four newgill hqs in your hometown back of your yard in your house
in your bedroom using your machine to mine cook your currency to fund our operations our entire
thesis our entire plot here is to get you your information your dog your wife your family in
our system back them up and make sure they back up on your hopes and dreams as we drive you into
the fucking ground new go new go new go new go new go new go new go oh we fuck fuck fuck fuck
two go two go two go two go two go two uh uh we got we got one great question uh as i as i
hastily asked guys we need questions right now stumbling out of the gate comes out oh my phone
what's popping shit all right this is the best you could do under such uh high pressure
um all right these are shit uh me cool man asks when will you create your next masterpiece
which i find an interesting question i fucking made a masterpiece yeah if you don't say it
yeah
excellent how do you like go on i feel that my my latest album the world over yeah it's the greatest
masterpiece i've ever created so i am not due to create a masterpiece for the next day i have to
go listen to it day i didn't listen to that one uh uh i'm where did what beats did you use for it
it's entire no it was entirely me rapping over the dot hack sign soundtrack all right and uh i'm
gonna i'll probably make a video explaining the narrative behind it because it's a concept album
let's do and then i think there's some people who will enjoy it even more wait what's it called
the world over didn't you see my video that was like apocalyptic cyberpunk trapped in the internet
anime soundtrack mixtape the world i saw that i didn't click on it
the work on those titles and thumbnails dude it's the i mean i thought that was a perfect title
that's like a title that would make me click on it look the zoomer demographic doesn't agree
clearly i guess so but uh it's it's uh it's by far the most work i've ever put into anything
probably hey so we have the billeted cuppings but this is a provocative question that i like
and it's uh in light of recent events asked mr bones what are your overall thoughts on
monkey as a content creator considering that he was was decided to be too hot for youtube he
could not exist on here yeah i think that i mean i guess i can understand youtube's reasons why i
don't agree with them yeah i don't think he should have had his channel terminated but i guess i if
you if you put a gun to my head i could tell you why they probably did it for pr reasons i
suppose that i don't think it's fair it's like his stuff is like asking about whether you thought
it should get deleted from youtube or just your opinion he's just saying like i mean considering
recent events of him being deleted from youtube like what do you think of him as a content creator
i think he's a hard-ass worker which i respect he is definitely a hard worker but he has always
pushed the line of edginess and like like monkey would say it's jokes which i agree with and i would
100% allow it if i was platform but considering youtube's corporate squeezing of things i i do get
that they think that like like the kind of a little bit of line blurring humor that monkey uses
that it obviously it's not he doesn't fucking endorse elia roger but like when you make lots of
edgy jokes uh i just i get why like you know the normos are not going to be like oh i get it this
is a joke and i don't like elia roger they'll be like like he actually he was literally cited
in in someone's i forget this was like on some news channel or something about how um somebody
please put this in the description somebody's gonna know this or in the comments it was like
somebody made a video about like incels like the rise of the incel threats and like used a clip of
monkey's video about elia roger as like look as like this this is what we're dealing with yeah
where is a literal parody comedy video but the thing is though if you just watch it and you
don't know it's a parody like are you how if you saw like a clip you might think well okay here
we go i mean it's obvious to me but i'm also like steeped in context yeah yeah as a real i'm just
saying the joke got old i've had enough mumpy jones it's time for money james to make money james
money james money james money james money james by the way uh just a small update on this uh you
know how uh sheep over made a channel called jungle jimmy or whatever deleted it was it's not owned
by monkey it was owned by sheep over deleted it's really yeah i mean that's what sheep over just
tweeted uh whatever was called jungle jimmy boy oh they are going hard to yeah they didn't do that to
fucking uh keemstar when he said uh drama alert is run by another person i'm just the hired actor
to be honest but i guess monkey was this is too much this is too much shit i don't i'm surprised i'm
really surprised they don't want them they do not want them uh i guess their minds made i mean
they didn't do that to mike the smoker mike the smoker got his channel back i guess they consider
him less doing tobacco reviews i just don't understand how they have a how this laser focus
i'm joking i just i just think it's funny that mike the smoker is a real thing it's like the the whole
like the the the eye of sauron that is youtube fully did turn its attention like we can all
like we say you know some some shit here that mike had us flagged but like we're under the radar
it feels like the full light of god is shining on monkey in judgment and saying you will not be
here you will be removed for because we want to do that somebody somebody made up their minds
somebody decided yeah yeah it's so weird i mean what do we think about i haven't seen
constantly a while but i used to think he was i don't know i have no reason
yeah i actually said the third the third video those videos are made of you know ellie rodgill
killing video in a while but you know i'm sorry i haven't made another time for one kid it may have
been me who reported his channel i'm just going to make all of those videos and it no i reported
his channel no it was me we let's we all we're all money james money james money james money james
money james no i'm money james what else we've got uh uh what is objectively the worst job
existence youtube um have you ever pooped without peeing uh that's a provocative question i don't
think that i have speed i don't i don't think that i have i have fire too i have many times
because oftentimes i take a piss and then realize afterwards that i have to go back oh well that
counts is i think you're double dipping that part yeah yeah you're double dipping yeah by the way the
worst uh uh question about whatever was from c20l okay that is a is a cuddle to all cuddle to all
key to all yeah c to all c to there's someone called cuddle too long i believe cuddle to all
who i see around it's gotta be this time i'm not here right it's gotta be what else we got um
can you guys have the pcb war i rl in boston somehow um link link gums do we got to beat the
shit out of these fucking idiots i feel like we're the slime guns out boys i feel like we're in a
state of parlay as the leaders of the various factions we we've met up to like have a war council
and established the terms like the geneva convention yeah that's what that's what that's
all been about dude it's gonna be so fucking easy unless we're just steam walls everyone when you
unite the killers and the riders will they ever be united is the question of course we're we're
we're united right now hey by the way i ate some of your banana uh pudding and pepper on a pizza
killer's in the cathedral right now at crusaders fucking get them
i need that pepperoni pizza and that banana pudding i gotta put them together it's a combination
too powerful to be left in rowdy hands i have a recipe for sledge face a recipe for banana
pudding pepperoni i'm not gonna tell you what's in this but i swear it's gonna change everything
directed towards me and but we can put a fucking food banana we gotta put that in a pizza
banana pizza in the in the food court yeah it needs to be like the ultimate item the ultimate food
item did you get that today is that what happened uh no no it's a it's a dug funny episode
yeah he just rants about dug funny literally everywhere there's nothing nothing happens that
i can't relate to dug adventures in bluffington all right here we go so this is juicy shack me
asks uh nate are you creatively past your prime is everything we get from you now on soul dead
and heartless uh sick dick uh that's yes i gotta be a hard yes uh i would the answer is god i hope
not because i've barely done anything uh so if i reach the end i had very little to say from the
start uh no i mean like i said before i feel like everything i do for the rest of my life is kind
of going to be repackaging the same ideas i'm generally talking about on everything but i i would
i guarantee you i'll find cool ways to do those in entertaining ways uh as we go forward i literally
have amazing ideas for content like several times a day way more than i could ever feasibly create
way most of it i end up coming down on the side of like i don't know if i'll ever find time for
this like yeah like over christmas break because i i went to um i went to uh may's parents house and
like just didn't work for like five days and like the whole time we were watching christmas movies
and i had like this really huge idea of like an epic ranking and bass analysis video an idea for
like a how the grinch stole christmas video like reviews of like several other movies it was just
like a diehard like i thought of like a like a whole like a new way i could take on diehard and
explore like why that movie's good and like just all this shit and like one of those around christmas
i have no idea if like if any of these like all of them i know would be successful videos but do i
have the capacity to write them and edit them and give enough of a shit all the way through production
while still working on other things that's the question did you watch it's a wonderful life
this christmas i did not it's a great it's a it's a tradition for me i love that it's great
but i didn't watch a lot of i watched a lot of christmas movies i hadn't seen like i hadn't seen
diehard so it was like i watched for the first time and i was like oh my god it actually is good
it actually is good uh and uh i was really interested in exploring did he diehard because like
other people don't get too far into my my theory yeah okay he was dead from the very start it was a
dream sequence uh to answer this question on me a little bit more from the beginning of best guy
ever i had like four videos planned one of which was the current log and stuff that's done another
of which was the ghost the shell stuff not done and i've got there were two more beyond that that
from the start i planned on making and i've made one of those and i'm working on the second of those
four um i don't know what the fourth one is i only know two and three i'll give you a secret it's not
the best anime ever but quite the opposite that that is true that is true um uh uh yeah i won't
go into any more details i like to surprise people in general but i was gonna say but yeah well it
doesn't matter uh uh when those are done and i will let people know when those are done just
because for trivia sake at that point if you see my content drop off completely because i'm just
like well i fucking said everything i got to say fuck i don't know what i'm gonna do uh fair enough
but until that happens no i'm not bankrupt yet so i've got things to say about stuff uh yes i feel
like i haven't yet shown like my full power in anything you're like it freezes second form right
now you haven't gotten five yeah like i i don't feel it took a while for him to i've i've had like
ideas but i've never really fully embraced any one idea to like make it a proper like properly
create it yeah right so like i yeah i want to see one day it's all up from here one of the things we
should link this in the show notes uh a lot of people haven't seen it but like the animation you
just did for the end of season one of rfck like oh uh s s descent s descent is one of my favorite
things made in recent years by any of us it's on it's on uh the hit not the hypocrite channel it's
on the give and take it's on no no it's on given fortress given fortress given fortress to pay this
is well this is out yes it's been out since like july it came out in like june or july or maybe before
that yeah that would be a concept was so good and i know it's like based on stuff it was based on
like home stuff but it doesn't matter like i loved it so much that every sense there's a lot of
original stuff i yeah absolutely i like man i would love to just see like i don't know give
does like whatever but like brings like this stuff and i'm like man i feel like that would be i feel
like that was the beat that i was seeing a glimpse into unleashing of your full power level and like
i mean maybe it'll never happen maybe you'll just work on big stuff but like god would i love to see
more of that i like the game that you made for escape snakes or yeah run away from snakes run away
from snakes again loved it it was just like came out of nowhere superman's got like leaderboards and
like three miles oh yeah it does have leaderboards that's fucking cool yeah it's fucking dope as
shit uh so yeah i don't know like i said there's all these things around like to to imagine them
perhaps in one way coalesce until i don't know maybe like a webcomic that has like this i mean
that's what it is it's part of a webcomic um hey would be super cool i'm gonna give a signal
boost on unrockly the given fortress two for a video that my friend ethan editor of armor
table edited oh yeah it was a live stream that we did and video is epic and it has like 300 views
and it's great yeah you know i've never seen it wait i don't even know if i know about given fortress
two that's not given because there's given gaming yeah given given fortress two was like my my my naive
attempt after like marathoning like all of german 985 and star underscores videos on tf2 like all of
them um i just wanted to be one of them so i like started a tf2 gaming channel where i was going to
be like a cool guy but now there's other stuff but like i i i don't think i'm well it just becomes
like a shit rump channel after he abandoned it for so long and then it just became funny like
i have this channel i never use what if i put the ufo things on there yeah um so like it's secret i
mean yeah there was that one time we were setting up the the stream for right on three and i streamed
the stream on there yeah oh yeah right yeah yeah i do remember that i think i had just thought that
it was the same thing as given gaming when i heard you say that i'm not surprised i uh does anyone
else i love to when i'm testing a stream i use the bestgaver live streams channel because it's
got like 800 subs and those are the those are the true heroes those are the the deep deep shit people
they're the deep shit uh and they know what's up they know the secret jokes and me
uh pretty sick it is pretty sick i think gaming or fck something that had it's gone it's gone
uh there's something the question was about uh full potential oh yeah are you creatively
bankrupt yeah are you creatively bankrupt god no no i can listen i mean go look at endless war endless
war has only endless war has only just scratched the surface of the kind of the at the the like the
depths of totally totally pointless but like but totally richly engaging like total clusterfuck
possibilities have like we're so fucking cool we have seen there's like like like i've got we've
i've got the secret project that i'm brewing down in the dungeons of the uh of the of saint
ben's cathedral right now description it is it is being worked on it is the biggest most ambitious
it's so big that i can't even do it myself i need like community like people like people
have been have volunteered to like contribute pieces to it and when that's done that's that's
gonna be like that's like the first step that's like the first step to like a whole new like
dimension of things that the game could have in it yeah and the future so not even not even
fucking close i'm gonna go to my grave i'm gonna go to my grave fucking like oh what if i what if i
what if i did this like oh what if they what if what if what if the weapons could wear hats
oh dude dude ben do you want to get matching uh slim core insignias on our tombstones
do it do it up hey quick aside from pejoro bit of thorn uh not a question but a helpful comment
when pcbhq becomes real i'm going to write was your favorite anime on a brick and threw it through
one of the windows okay sick i can't wait appreciate it framed tom are you past your prime i think
i'm still probably ten years out from hitting my grind i kind of feel the same way about me but
fair enough like this is like the first time i've had a really clear idea in a while of what i want
to do and like i can clearly visualize what it's going to be read your cop right now while i'm talking
uh no i just it's it's fucking sick and i know exactly what i want to do over the next
like tom tom tom it feels to me like lately you've hit your story you've hit a straw yes
oh my god hey hey tom gonna say
because he loves it the reason i say that
is because before you you you before we're like like like a year ago whatever
you're like do i even belong in the pcb i've been grandfathered in do i have i earned my place
yes but not anymore because you are a fucking huge ass big bone fat ass motherfucker you have
so much fat in your bones you're just all muscle you look so fucking smart and funny and great
you're like best pcb member we're all down here and you're up here zoom me off killing code
i want to play the demo i want to play the demo tom i humbly request fan art of this
finally the first pcb board we're just gonna do it ourselves
how could be so stupid damn that's wise oh god speaking of which cool i'm glad you like it
on this job dear erik c bass asks uh has masturbation or pornography ever significantly
gotten the way of your productivity sick i love i love this meme of tom being bloated
uh the 20 new patrons here give tom a bloated you're in the club i would be so hot i would join
but i don't think i can fit it all the way down just do it with a huge cock
such a huge handsome it's not about hitting the target it's about feeling the feeling
yeah feeling the vibe it's true um and you can do it at home ladies and gentlemen give me a big
yeah you can blow tom yourself today at home oh you should get ice and lab microphone like this
yeah we'll just boom when are we doing in the comments below hashtag bvvv
boom
when are we going to mass produce tom oliver and send him to houses around the
country so that he can so everyone can blow their own tom i mean maybe in the meantime when
tom goes full transhumanist and we have the data version of tom then we can distribute him to
lower sex dolls and we can populate the sex dolls with the personality of tom it's like it's like
you're an organ donor now you're just like a brain a mind donor like a personality donor or
something duplicate yourself and become an object you get your sex doll from from out of its box
and it says in a low gravelly voice just go back from the gym rave for some time and you just go
like
well this was weird in what way uh well you know i think i think no one ever says nice things about
me or such as my dad i think we've basically we've gone through all the questions i think uh
two hours go from it where can we go from there really straight to the grave uh yeah i guess
let's wrap it up i'm feeling good you know i'm pretty hungry yeah if we all want to go get some
but is there enough to go around
all right guys what a group one a group one come on everyone get over here
spread your fucking legs this is the work all right yeah one two three
see you next episode everybody
i'm doing nothing
i've got a deadline don't want to do it
oh
Yeah, it's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock why being a kid is so hard.