I'm this far from the mic, and I'm this far from the mic.
I'm very close to my mic.
And I'm this far from the mic.
I'm here.
And we are...
These far as from the mic.
I actually said that the way Mumkey does at the end of all his let's plays, he always says,
And we're...
Yay!
I didn't hear it.
Hello everybody, and welcome to a new Pro Crastinators Podcast.
This one's at 360 degrees.
I guess we should all look at the thing, right?
That's the audience in a while.
I see that my zoom is right in front of my face here.
Oh, I'll try to adjust it a little bit.
Yeah, let's see what we can do here.
Ben, despite what he may say, Ben doesn't enjoy a ride in his face every once in a while.
Alright, maybe like this.
I don't know what to do. What do you want from me?
No, Ben, you're visible. Yeah, you're good.
Okay, but now it's completely mitigated the benefits of it being on a switch.
Benefits.
Look, audience, you've never seen a 360 video before.
Click the screen with the mouse dragging around or use the lesson key.
And look around and watch us like you're really there.
Why don't you just hand them some fucking training wheels while you're at it?
These fucking simpletons.
We can't figure out what the giant fucking arrows on both sides of the screen mean.
Alright, we don't have a topic, but we have a 360 degree video.
That's what it's really meant.
We've got visuals instead of a topic, which is even better.
Yeah, it's a splash over substance. Everyone knows it's the best way to go.
That's what I'm known for, I think.
Yeah, something like that.
We've got Victor playing Bloodborne.
To represent what the audience should be doing when watching the CBC.
That is an impressive shot.
If you move the camera, you can look at what we're talking about hopefully.
This is a podcast and a list.
We all decided Victor's game was more interesting than each other.
The idea here was to have the ideal viewer being demonstrated for the audience to observe.
This is what you should be doing when listening to PCP.
You should be on a game playing Bloodborne specifically.
Two questions. One, should this just be a multi-topic general PCP
where we go through whatever we feel like talking about?
We're trying to decide on a topic for like an hour now.
We can't do it, so we should give up.
Should this become a...
Jesse gets up with that microphone and cuts an epic promo on all the things making him mad in 360.
Well, maybe.
Jesse is no more. You can call me microphone Jones.
I have no true identity.
No one can see my true visage.
I thought for sure you were going to say you were broken.
Broken Jesse, yeah.
I like microphone Jones better anyway.
Microphone Jones.
Microphone Jones has put one facet of the vessel that is now called broken Jesse.
It's very great that he's wrapped up in a winged approved blanket.
That's very interesting.
I don't know which fucking knot it is on that thing.
I've seen it somewhere.
Well, Jesse's closer. He should do it.
But his nose is like an all-new level if I do say so myself.
That is...
Oh, God.
It looks okay from the front, but that doesn't look okay at all.
You know, 360 videos are cool because they're like turning videos into video games, basically.
Yeah.
It's crazy to watch them.
I use this point extensively in my video thoughts on 360 videos.
The first time I watched a 360 video, I'm like, I'm in a Valve game, you know?
Yeah.
Well, we complain about that. Well, I complain about that.
Is now the time to hear our grievances about Portal 2?
Long last? No.
Whoa, we never did that one.
We have grievances about Portal 2?
We never did the Portal 2.
Some, yes.
I mean, there was a heated debate over whether Portal 2 was as good as Portal 1.
Portal 2 is better than Portal 2.
No, my friend.
I say Portal 1 and Portal 2 are like completely just as good.
Not even close.
Portal 1, Portal 2 has more stuff and if the Portal 1 is more pure because it was the original.
And all about pure.
Let me air my long-standing grievance that I've never resolved that all of you don't
think that being original is worth more than being good, but it absolutely is.
Oh, that's a good topic.
You're already kind of resolved that one.
I think we kind of agree, you and I, a bit on that.
No, I'm the only one.
No, because like...
I'm the only one who's pure.
Oh, okay.
Oh, wait, maybe we did.
I mean, we did argue about that, things we can't get into.
How is Portal 2 not original?
She turns into a fucking potato, you dolt.
It's because it's Portal 2.
You know what?
Think about it, think about it.
I'm too aggressive of a note.
Yeah.
We're not adults.
Okay, how about this?
I take it back.
Originality has more value than...
He's like a good gentleman.
He's a nice guy.
Yeah.
All right, let's check it out.
Originality has more value per pound than references and callbacks and like cultural appropriation.
Let's say that.
Wow, I could totally agree with that.
Yeah, but I think that appropriation references, remixes are like more easy to come by.
And therefore they comprise more of a diet.
I felt like last time this came up, no one even acknowledged to me that originality had inherent value in that.
No, we did.
I said that.
That's not how I remember it.
I said it has inherent value, but also that like if the next thing that comes along iterates on it and makes it a better version.
Yeah, and it's a better product.
If you stipulate that it's better, then sure, it's better.
Well, yeah.
If you build on it and that makes your argument better.
It's now better.
I guess because...
I can agree that if it's better.
I just made a video recently that like has a lot of references to other things.
Some references are like really specific and I'm really glad about that.
Then some references are like kind of a general, like I'm referencing it through.
Wait, you talk about the one, the 20 minute one about action scenes.
No, no, I'm talking about...
We tried to watch it through that.
You don't understand what the fuck you were talking about.
Couldn't make it.
It was very confusing.
My side channel is not really for consumption at all.
You're just going to walk around your own room now and you do Davugos to sound?
I don't know.
Anyway, like I was...
I'm talking about the Radcon trailer I made.
It's got some references to like specific things and it's got some references to like general tropes.
And it's got like one or two jokes in the night thing or like a regional that like don't come into place.
So they can just pay us to our conversations.
The audio is not going to work like that.
I don't know what you mean, dude.
It's a 360 video.
They turn it towards us.
No, unfortunately, I would love that.
Wouldn't it work that way?
That would be pretty cool.
If you only heard which direction.
I really wanted to become like a choose your own adventure style thing.
But the only problem is you can't do audio that way.
But like I want it to be that whichever direction you look in, it'll like continue the video.
Wait, wait, wait.
What were you saying?
Speaking of choose your own adventure, I want to give everyone a game to play.
Can you spot the hippo in the room?
He's around here somewhere.
No, not you people.
You guys know.
I'm talking about him.
Yeah, don't look.
He's ruining it.
He's around.
He's like a touch of the corner.
I don't know which way the camera starts.
The camera's in every direction.
Yeah, their view field does not see every direction.
It sees one direction until they change it.
That's my point.
I only see one direction.
One direction is the grand final.
We're talking about how Action Giraffe is the greatest original character of all time.
This is Hamony's my best friend and he has AIDS in that order before.
Wait, and here's another best friend, Hippocrite.
All of a sudden your sunglasses look is freaking me out.
Suddenly.
Well you're going to have to deal with it.
You're suddenly a creature to me and it feels real and it's like fucking me.
Do I remind anyone else of the channelers from Dark Souls?
Because that's what I'm going for.
What the fuck, no.
They have three sets of eyes, like you know.
Well you have a fourth.
I have like a fifth now I think.
One, two, three, four.
There's five here somewhere.
I really think there's another one.
Oh wow, there's another one layered behind the blue one.
Yeah, that's right.
I really think that Hippo and Action Giraffe need to meet and befriend TJ Henry Yoshi.
Oh my god.
Yeah, well can anyone really befriend a man of that low caliber?
There are also animals that wear sunglasses.
Well Hippo doesn't usually wear sunglasses.
Guys, watch on your 3D camera.
Watch the perfect spiral you can make with Hippo when you throw them.
Here he goes.
Some depictions show him with the shutter shades,
but others give him the visor that that character from Ace Attorney has.
Right, yeah.
Some theorize that that's what's meant to be going on there.
He's the greatest meme of our generation.
TJ Henry Yoshi.
It's cool that we have all this stuff set up and then it's potentially recording properly.
Yeah, well said.
Isn't that neat?
We could only pray.
Yeah, we could only pray and have like a thing to talk about.
Well let me resolve what I was saying a minute ago.
The point is, I think I was slightly more proud of the mostly original jokes
that kind of are like their own thing.
Slightly more than the references.
Absolutely.
Any reasonable person would be.
Yeah, but the references were more voluminous.
What are you talking about?
What references?
The trailer.
The newest trailer for Radcon.
Oh, I thought we were still talking about Portal.
No.
Now we get back into Portal, right?
With the fact that Portal 1 has this portaling.
And it's like, oh my gosh, why did I never...
Portal 1 is a fucking tech demo.
For the Masterpiece Game 2 budget.
Objectively false.
Objectively true.
It's perfect.
Here's my impression of Portal 1.
Oh, I'm a bunch of white rooms.
The end.
Wow.
What a fucking...
Portal 2 is a fucking case study in how to add extra bullshit that wastes your time
into a game.
Like levels?
Extra bullshit.
It is not all great.
Like a story.
Like the backstory to how GLaDOS got her voice was really a wonderful addition.
No, it's not.
It's cool.
Why is it not cool?
Because it's not cool.
You have to tell me why it is cool.
It doesn't work the other way around.
Your people are really...
You're getting on microphone Jones' bad side.
You don't want to know what kind of a temper microphone Jones has and you really need
him to go in.
When I first watched the Matthew Matosis video where he complained about that, I'm like,
okay, yeah, that's...
Don't pretend like I hold the thing that's...
This is the original opinion.
Shit.
Well, it's like...
It's one of those things where if you look at all the things that you've classified that
constitutes good storytelling, it's like, I guess it doesn't do them.
But when I was playing the game, I didn't mind.
It was just sort of like...
It's literally turning your brain off.
Mr. Jones, I want to defend Matthew Matosis, but he hasn't released a video in like a year,
so it's whatever.
You throw him out with a bath water.
Yeah, put him in the fucking garbage.
Yeah.
I have a defense, so by the way.
No, it doesn't.
One of the two things he said, which is that...
Oh yeah, sing it.
You can't.
No one can sing it.
My fucking defense!
You deserve to hear me sing it.
He said, GLaDOS was a real character.
Now he's a real character.
Well, thank you.
You've got feet, eyes, no ears, buddy.
That's the worst opinion I've ever heard.
What's the worst opinion?
GLaDOS was a meme character to begin with.
That's not true.
What was the depth of GLaDOS' character in the first game?
First of all, she's an AI.
She doesn't need a complex or deep motivation.
GLaDOS in the first game is very funny and very unique the first time you see it,
but then after you play the game once and you play it again, all the jokes are old.
Oh yeah, so what we needed was Portal 2 where they shove her in your face more.
Oh, that was so much better.
Now she has some emotional depth.
Now she's got a tragic backstory that we can all relate to.
It wasn't even tragic.
Her backstory has nothing to do with the person that she was made by.
Well, you guys are just being a bunch of fucking snobs and cynics.
Of course it's better that she had a tragic dog.
That's not a real criticism.
You're just saying shit because it sounds cool.
She's way less compelling this way than she was as just a rogue AI.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Who's really compelling about a fucking AI?
There is some kind of wicked compelling because I was fucking compelled when I played Portal 2.
I was born with Portal 2 which is better than the greatest game of all time.
Wow.
I've never played any of the Portal games.
I'm not joking.
Get out of here Donnie bro.
Half-Life 3 is my favorite Portal game.
Now, to stop talking about superficial elements like story, I have a level design.
I hope that doesn't mean.
There's more levels in Portal 2.
The levels are more intricate in Portal 2.
And they have more depth.
There's more depth.
The levels are bigger and there's more going on.
Bigger doesn't mean better.
In Portal 1.
But deeper does mean better.
And it's not deeper.
Here's what it is.
Some of them are deeper.
The first time I played Portal 1, I was like, this, I was like, I can't believe it.
All my life I've seen cartoons where people go through portals but it's just a bunch of blue swirls.
This has the idea that you can see what's going through the portal when you're seeing it.
That's so revolutionary.
Every show that has Portal is now sucked in comparison.
But you only got that traditional revelation.
Here's what it is.
When I first played Portal 1, I thought this game is genius.
But then when I played Portal 2, I thought I am a genius for beating these incredible levels.
The puzzles were literally harder in Portal 1.
Yeah.
The puzzles were so deep and had so much to do and they were so multi-layered that I really got a lot of satisfaction.
There was so much easier in Portal 2.
I didn't get as much out of that aspect of it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
When watching other people play it, there were like many puzzles.
The first one I was super stuck on.
When you see someone else play a game that you've played or you see Person A and you see Person B play it,
and you see how they're better or worse at different parts, Portal 2 for me was the ultimate experience of that.
Because I played it and I saw like two different or three different people play it.
When I first played Portal 1, I really felt like it was not good and it didn't get good until Portal 2.
You're lying.
You're telling me lies.
What the fuck?
I don't believe you.
That's all you really want to say.
Portal 1 is a boring two-hour piece of shit.
All you do is solve the same puzzle over and over again in the same room over and over again.
Portal 2 has a story, it has levels, it has better everything.
You're out of line, Microphone Jones.
I can't take you seriously anymore, Microphone Jones.
Microphone Jones is unleashed and out of control.
You know what? I think, you know, I said that I thought you were both the same.
The only argument you really need is that Portal 2 is objectively deeper.
There's literally more mechanics.
You literally go deeper into the game.
Right, okay, but that's the thing though.
It less thoroughly explores each of those mechanics than Portal 1 does.
Therefore, it is a less perfect version of the video games.
I played through Portal 2 in the...
I played through Portal 2 Co-op and Portal 2 Co-op.
Portal 2 Co-op's great.
Portal 2 Co-op has an entirely new dimension which is that there's four active portals at once
and they've got all the new mechanics with all the different kinds of goods.
It's amazing.
Oh, and by the way, custom levels.
Yo, I made a custom level.
I love the one custom level I made in Portal 2.
I was back when we started...
Did you see this earlier?
Yeah, I know.
Well, how the heck else am I supposed to get everyone's attention?
They're back when we started talking.
You just go, hey!
Boom.
And then you start talking.
Okay.
Well, here's the thing.
Portal...
I know, this is bad.
The central mechanic of Portal is the portals which is thoroughly...
In Portal 1, in Portal 2, they do all these extra additions around the portals which are
not as good.
Yeah, like a super good game of story.
And GLaDOS being way cooler.
Oh my god.
Oh, Bentley is so cool.
He's got the voice of characters that have heard of a million other places.
He doesn't even sound like a robot.
What a great idea for a character.
What the fuck are you talking about?
My point, he sounds like a human not a robot.
Can you, can you, Wheely?
Whatever, yeah.
What did I say?
Bentley Bear?
Bentley Farm for Bentley.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, that's right.
In Portal 1, the thing that makes GLaDOS great is that like, is the, is the, is just the
fact that she comes off like a, like a robot at first and you slowly realize how many like
weird personality traits she has.
That's what makes her funny and awesome.
I guess so.
She's pretty consistent though.
Okay, let's agree to disagree on Portal 1.
Talk about how shitty Bloodborne is because I genuinely hate this game and it's high times
when I'm not going to play this game.
No, man.
Bloodborne's a good shame.
We'll possibly say negatively about this game.
Then he can't beat the final boss.
That would be a big problem with the game, right?
Oh, and that color palette is too consistent.
That's my biggest complaint.
You've fought Garmin like four times anyway.
I fought him twice and I fucking got tired.
Well, whose problem is that?
That sounds like a personal issue.
No, you know why this game is fucking annoying?
Why?
Okay, it's designed to be hard, which is fine.
All the Souls games are designed to be hard.
But in all the Souls games, you don't have to fucking grind for 20 minutes every time you
die.
You get more fucking Bloodborne.
You actually do have to do that.
This game is a piece of shit.
Remember when you were a promising young man and you made a Demon Souls review, which
has the exact same need to grind in it, but you beat that game.
You don't need to grind in Demon Souls.
You fucking ruined it.
You have to grind in your fucking world on one.
You have to do it.
You're a supering child.
You peasant.
You fucking brother.
You are only mule.
Yeah, you are absolutely mule.
Absolute mule.
Absolute.
Yes.
I'm going to delete you, Jesse.
What I did was I just grinded it up like 150 vials at the beginning and then never had
to do it again.
I really am surprised by that because I had to farm many times.
What's the problem with grinding when just playing the game normally is awesome.
You could just be running around in a circle, killing the same enemy over and over again,
having the time of your life.
It's an amazing game.
How can you look at this game and not think it's amazing?
It's like shit to the game.
It's like a game like an arc, like a Final Fantasy.
Grinding is fun because you level up in your stat scope and you're always dealing slightly
more damage.
That's not how it is in Bloodborne where you do literally the same thing over and over
again.
So the grinding is less fun in Bloodborne for me?
Completely.
And I'm a grinding connoisseur.
Because pressing the R button is the most fun thing in the entire world of gaming in
Bloodborne.
And you know, I got to say, if I had to name, if you asked me like top 10 moments in all
video gaming, I would say pressing the R2 button to completion in Bloodborne.
Dude, we should do completion.
I hear you laugh.
Two-handed.
Hold R2 all the way.
Oh yeah, that's how you call it.
And then ka-ching!
But blam!
Most satisfying moment in video gaming history.
Yeah, that's how you, you call it two-handing.
And me and my brother always call it double fisting.
That's the only term I use for fisting.
Yeah, I'm still, I'm still thinking about it.
It's like, okay.
No, I don't know.
I don't want to talk about video games.
I hate all of them.
I don't care about Portal.
Man, no.
Let's talk about the video games.
Nobody likes us because we're a bunch of gamer boys.
They like us because we're a bunch of psychotic, imbecilic, idiot assholes
who scream at each other about fucking how big our wings are.
That's true.
My ween.
Are you guys seeing my ween?
Oh wait, wait, guys.
Check out my new shoes.
Check out these new shoes, dawg.
Look at these suede shoes.
Brown sand shoes.
From every angle.
This is just the everybody attempts at another topic
and gets shut down by everyone else's podcast.
Let's talk about shoes and how cool they are.
They are cool.
All right.
We can agree on that.
Ask Nate about his shoes and he'll tuck your dick too.
I'll tell you.
I'll suck your dick.
I wore these flip-flops sitting in the Philippines.
Wow.
They're all really issues.
They are falling apart.
You should be the main man in a bed like that.
I thought you shared fun all the time.
But life doesn't always work out the way it should.
I need to be conscious of the fact that whoever's listening to this
is only listening to one audio track.
Because Jesse certainly won't.
Neither will I.
I don't listen to any of our podcasts.
I unsubscribed from the Procrastination the other day.
I can't blame you.
I've had any secure with all of these goons.
Time to move on.
But unfortunately I moved on in the direction of his house.
Wait.
I take back that.
Why would anyone be subscribed?
Because I hate that shitty meme.
And nobody should say shit.
Hey, wait.
Let's talk about the sweet PCP trailers that have been coming out.
Yeah.
Let's talk about...
First there was the Kaon opening.
Oh, yeah.
And then there was the Davoo...
It was the Davoo PCP...
The Red Count Trailer.
They...
I don't know.
They bloomed large in my personal consciousness.
Do you remember the person who made the Kaon ones?
So we can shout them out and tell them how cool they are?
I forget their name.
His name was Endless Jack.
It was the coming YouTube hero.
Hey, it's the Gibbo.
Gibbo, while you've been walking around, have you been saying anything?
Uh...
Yeah.
Your audio is still going on in our audio, right?
I don't know what you mean.
Also, your laptop...
Is it recording even?
Disconcerted.
Okay, well, whatever.
It's going to be God's word.
We have no idea what moments might have just...
You know what's been captured, budget?
Ha ha ha ha.
Like, in the background of the audio.
Not in the background of the audio.
Overpowering the rest of us.
That's probably the way it should be.
It's probably for the best.
It's a secret.
To everybody.
I have a suggestion to give to all the camera-designing people.
Because I was thinking, the next level after this is a podcast where you hit arrow keys
to move the camera angle around.
But how could that be filmed?
Drums?
What?
360 Drums.
But that would only work with live footage.
Here's how you do it.
You know, strip lights in a theater that line the...
Imagine instead of a little light that you have on the steps.
Every light instead of being a light, it's a little lens.
That's how they film the matrix, the 3D scenes.
Yeah, something like that.
But it's like a stringy.
And you can tape it up along the wall and record your whole house simultaneously.
And use the lassoed here.
You say simultaneously really fucking weird.
That's like the 10th time I've noticed that.
Microphone!
You know that's a reference to the time cube, right?
The what in the whole thing?
Yeah, that's right.
The time cube guy.
Yeah.
How can a box have six sides when it's the front, the back, the left, and the right?
Those are the sides.
How can you get off the bottom on the sides?
Is this one of those memes that you guys have?
You said before, the first stage is fewer than a quarter of a minute video.
No, time cube is fewer.
Also, time cube...
Also, this proves God, because God, you know, in some places he's just one guy.
But in some times he's three.
He's three in one.
That's not four.
You know, it's only three.
The time cube is this old psychopath who was on G4 in like 2005, and he was explaining
the time cube that the Earth is broken up into four quadrants, and each one is actually
experiencing the same time, but it's a difference.
Yeah.
But it all happened simultaneously.
And he's got these shiny white fake teeth.
Are you talking straight guys?
No.
You guys actually watch this right now, and it would totally show up on the 360 video,
and they'd be able to watch the video.
Let's give it a try.
Let's experiment and do it.
We're going to progress the media.
Oh my God, is this going to become like a mystery science thing with us watching shit,
and that's a great idea.
I want that.
That would be so bad.
By the way, the K-On! opening was by Doon Coon.
Doon Coon.
Thanks, Doon.
Thanks for coming out.
This is going to be a podcast.
I'm going to get a reaction video all at once, because you can look around on it.
And it's a secret time cube.
Just start time cube, and it'll be the amount of time you give and take, I guess.
People, I apologize for this.
I apologize for me and for my friends.
We're all horrible.
But now we're going to watch better videos, and you can watch them with us, as opposed
to just watching us.
Don't watch them on your own computer.
No.
It's going to explode.
Simultaneously.
It's back on now.
All right.
So, watch the red lights.
Tell the mystery as to how much just got cut out, or how much you had to...
Some of that.
Do you think it filmed the time cube at all?
I hope so.
Who knows?
That would be the worst place to have not had the video.
Yeah.
Maybe we'll have to do another.
We'll have to do another like it.
Perhaps.
Well, we'll certainly have plenty of times.
I'm all for just filming, like, a million mystery science theater videos of us shitting
YouTube videos.
That's actually a great idea.
Yeah.
That's actually a better idea than the PCP.
We should get rid of the PCP.
And you're pleased with that.
Do you guys want to discuss anything?
I do want to hear the airplane.
Yeah, me too.
Yesterday, I was so fucking angry that I could have cut the greatest throw-mobile time,
but I was also too tired.
I didn't give a shit.
I didn't want to tell anyone anything.
Now, I have to like go back in time and try to reignite that spark.
It might help if you came out kind of in a security blanket.
You didn't see me for who I truly am.
I'm a sexy boy.
You should show off your fucking body and strut around this place with that fucking mic
that you can walk with.
That's true.
And this is the ultimate promo.
They can follow you.
Do it.
Although the mic port is not very long.
You're putting me under a lot of pressure right now.
I wish to know what happened at the fucking airport.
All it takes for me to get mad, to get re-mad, is to just start reciting what happened in
my mind, even if it was 10 years ago.
I want to know what the deal is with the guy who was stealing the fucking bananas.
I need to know what that guy did to cause this problem.
No, no, no.
I feel like he told us.
No, no, he didn't go into detail.
No, he refused to tell us so that he could tell us on camera.
He's had a total like a restaurant list going right now.
Let's do it.
People of the world, if you thought 9-11 was bad, you don't know about 9-12 yet.
September 12th, 2016, a day that shall live in infamy, a day that shall live on in the
nightmares of everyone in the world for the rest of time once I tell the story.
I don't actually feel like telling the story.
You know what?
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Now you got a solid answer for it.
I don't even remember what happened.
I fucking want to know.
You know.
I built this up so much.
The story is just going to be, I went to the airport and I got to miss my flight.
It was pretty poopy.
Yeah, but why'd you miss it though?
It was only like a 10 minute, the first flight was like a 10 minute flight, right?
Yeah, cause I couldn't find a bus.
What was it called?
Gun.
Car.
Plane.
I give up.
I couldn't find a plane.
Well, okay.
One time I missed a flight because, so I get to the desk at CVG in, in Ohio or Kentucky
or whatever.
And the guy at the desk says, sir, your flight leaves in 50 minutes.
You have to be here an hour before your flight leaves or you can't go.
And I said, what?
And he's, no, he's like, this is policy.
And as I berated him for the next, about, it took 10 minutes of yelling at this man to
go.
I can make it.
It's right there.
I need to go now.
He said, he eventually like called people and they were like, okay, fine.
And they let me run.
Automatons.
And when I got there, they had just finished the boarding process and I was not allowed
on that flight costing me 24 hours of waiting time.
Worthless.
So that guy cost me that fucking flight.
Dragon their fear.
Yeah, that's right.
Coming up your date.
Whatever they can to be a fucking nuisance.
You know, everyone who knows me, everyone who knows me in my real life, they know that
I have like a psychotic physical aversion to bureaucracy or process of any kind.
I do everything I can to avoid it.
You know, anytime I get on a plane, I try not to pack too much.
I try to pack life specifically because I don't want to deal with like baggage claim
and all that ridiculous bullshit.
My dream in life, my one goal, my one aspiration is to someday get on a plane with no baggage.
To just travel with nothing but the clothes on my back and the sweat on my balls and no
other bullshit.
That's the dream.
So I packed my suitcase the other day before I go to this fucking airport.
I got a fucking flight to Chicago and then from Chicago flight to here because you can't
just come here.
They can't just do what I want.
No one can just do what I want.
Everyone has to get in my fucking way deliberately.
It's a conspiracy.
A global worldwide like driven conspiracy to make me miserable specifically.
So I packed my bag, the same bag that I've gone on a plane with like four other times.
I know for a fact it's a carry on bag.
I've carried it on multiple planes.
I've never had to go through baggage claim ever before.
So I get to the fucking airport place and I say, I'm here for my plane, cunt.
She says, oh thank God, Lord Jess has arrived to sample our automobiles of the sky and go
where we may.
So I take my little bag, she says little bag, she says little bag, take my little bag to
the plane.
I go through the fucking plane corridor and when I go to the plane, some fucking broad
takes my bag.
She just like jumps out of the woodwork like a monster in an haunted house and grabs my
bag and slaps the red sticker on it and takes it away.
And apparently this was like a valet thing because the plane was so fucking rinky dink
and small that there was no baggage spots in the, I've never fucking done the valet thing
before.
I've never even heard of it.
So she didn't explain it to me.
She just took my bag and I'm like, um, that you can't take that as a carry on.
What are you taking me to?
She's like, no, I'm taking it.
I'm like, okay, come on, just fucking taking it.
You can't fuck with these people.
So I just like, okay, I just have to allow these maniacs to take my fucking stuff.
And this is precious cargo.
You want to know what's in this bag, the precious cargo that I'm transporting.
More than anything.
First of all, I've got like four or five of my favorite shirts in there, which if any
one of them were to be lost, it would be a mass shooting by me.
It would be, it would be like 10, 9, 11s at once.
A lot of bullets.
Yeah.
Like in the World Trade Center.
I World War II by plane.
But um, so I have a bunch of shirts, my favorite shirts.
Shirts that I specifically picked out because like, you know, when I'm on camera at Casa
de Conran, I'm going to want the perfect wardrobe.
I got my Kelly Bundy shirt.
I got my Misado shirt.
All the best shirts.
And not only, not all my shirts, I got my laptop, which has my entire life on it.
All my stuff that I've read over like the last eight years, if that were to get lost.
Delete.
So I've got a bunch of my favorite shirts.
I got my fucking laptop.
And oh yeah, my best friend, Colt Corona, is in that fucking shirt case.
He, you know, he begged me to bring him along to let, to allow him to tag along in this
journey.
And I said, I said, brother Corona, I knew you'd come.
So I threw him in there.
So I've got basically the most precious cargo imaginable.
This fucking lady just jumps out of the bushes and takes my suitcase and tosses it into some
fucking plane.
Oh, I don't know.
The purest creature that ever lived.
Colt Corona.
Yeah.
The only one of us who deserves to be here.
So I get on this tiny fucking plane.
And of course my ticket has a seat number on it because God forbid anyone have any autonomy
in picking their own fucking seat.
We have to be treated like a bunch of kindergartners.
I think, in fact, I think even kindergartners would be allowed to pick their own seat and
clap.
Treat it like an obsolete mule.
Yeah, that's right.
Exactly.
Well, let me tell you about the obsolete mule that I met on the plane because that's exactly
what came up to me.
You know, I'm fucking looking at, I'm trying to decipher this fucking number because it
can't just be a seat number.
It's got to be like a letter and then a number.
And every seat has like three letters on it and four numbers and you've got to decipher
them.
So I go into the back of this cramped fucking rinky-dink, tiny-ass, ball sack plane and
I get into the back of it and I pick my seat and I'm like, okay, I fucking see it, I guess.
They're gonna fucking, they have to micromanage where we sit like a bunch of fucking sardines
in a can full of sardines.
So I'm sitting in my seat and this fucking guy comes up and he's like, I'm just eating
and I hate to bother you.
But is that a C-A-12?
I am, you're in my seat, you're in the good seat by this little smelly bitch over here.
You know, I hate to bother you like, shut up, you know, you love to bother me.
He's loving it, dude.
He's fucking fucked.
You goat Jesus.
You slut.
You aged slut from hell.
You know, he's fucking, he's taking so much joy in just being a smug guy and saying,
hey, believe you made an error in deciphering your ticket seat.
So, you know, he makes me get up and cross the aisle because it's so important to him
that he's sit where they tell him to sit.
You know, if only our politicians would take a leaf out of his book and encourage
cross the aisle.
You know what I'm saying, folks?
What the fuck are you?
That's a political expression.
I'm sorry.
I have no idea what that means.
It's a real thing.
Watch your madness.
Delete.
Yeah, delete.
That is a whole different meaning.
It's just as if it's mind-blowing that people care so much about the rules.
Like, I believe that if nobody gets hurt by you breaking a rule, you have a moral obligation
to break the rule.
You have a responsibility as a member of the free human race to break every rule that
won't hurt someone.
If you can get the same result by breaking a rule or not breaking it, you should definitely
break it because everyone else would not break it and that's lame.
It is lame.
That's true.
I think it's about, like, judicial precedent.
Like, well, the last guy broke the rule all the time.
Yeah, but you have to stop breaking the rule because now it's causing a problem.
You've got to be out there setting a new precedent.
That is true.
Yeah.
Then what happened?
I'm still on that fucking guy who gave me a guy on the seat.
It's not like there's some fucking, it's not like there's a bunch of knights patrolling
the plane, making sure everyone's in the right seat.
No one's going to give a shit.
Just let me fucking sit here.
Let me have the fucking window seat, you monster.
That's an evil fucking animal who would take me out of a window seat and put me in an aisle
seat.
I'll seats are the most miserable fucking thing.
Well, that's what I didn't want.
Well, I sat in it first.
That's all that should matter.
On my flight over here, I just, like, I just half the time, my face was pressed right
up against the glass.
That's the best part.
That's the only thing that matters in life.
The only good part of the entire airport experience is that brief moment when the plane takes
off and you get to look out the window and see this horrifying world get smaller.
It's the only thing I look forward to about the whole miserable experience.
And now I'm stuck in this aisle seat next to this smelly old broad who's like 60, but
like 160.
Yeah.
That's her age.
160 year olds on top of each other as one person.
And she's pulling out a fucking sandwich from a brown paper bag, like a fucking rube,
like some kind of kid in school.
And, you know, you can't even look out the window at all when you're in the aisle seat
because then you're also looking at the person.
Yeah.
So if she looks back and sees me looking at her, looking out the window, she's going to
think I'm in the aisle seat.