Hey, it's The Pro Crastinators Podcast again.
I can't believe it's been again so soon.
I can't believe we didn't get canceled after all that racist shit we said on the last episode
that they let us make another one.
Oh, they said that was exactly why we're getting renewed for now.
They brought me back on.
They had to drag me back out to be the radical centrist to keep you in check.
Sorry.
Whichever one of the Koch brothers is still alive smokes his cigar and was like, ah, these
boys are exactly what we need.
Give these guys a billion dollars.
So we're going to fire Eleazar and we're going to have a whole team of corporate editors.
We're going to have real production.
Now the podcast is really dead.
We're going to have a real podcast soon.
Oh, what a week.
What a week.
Right off the bat.
I'll tell you what I'm excited about.
The Vapors 2 books, they are in the mail and I'm looking at the tracking numbers and
they are like just like a couple hours ago.
They made their way.
They had left Florida.
They have arrived in Massachusetts.
And so I'm assuming they will be.
They will be in my grasp.
Maybe tomorrow.
I don't know.
It's coming.
It's been so long.
I forgot to even spend money on it.
I've been writing, right?
Right.
Everyone who spent money on it is going to have forgotten.
You couldn't.
You could have just pocketed all the cash.
Damn.
Fuck.
It's going to be they're going to forgot that they spent however much they spent.
It's going to be they're going to get it like for free.
It's like they're just going to be getting a free present from me like they didn't even
pay for it at all.
Yeah.
I looked at the thing and I completely forgot that one of the stretch goals was like the
Ben St. Heart pin.
I didn't realize I forgot I was getting that.
Yeah.
Everybody gets that.
And everybody gets a dollar.
Oh my God.
Everybody gets one dollar with class war and a hammer and sickle.
I'm going to frame that as my first dollar that like literally like actually.
Incredible.
My first communist dollar.
It'll be for me.
Yeah.
Vapors to Kickstarter achieve full communism and all it cost was $10,000.
I wonder how much it costs for America.
Only Stalin had known that communism was that cheap.
Damn.
There was a.
All right.
Right in.
Right in with the politics.
I saw a great video.
Actually, I'll just I was doing.
I was doing my my my Patreon podcast this week.
This month.
I was terrible.
Don't listen to it.
Do not.
I repeat.
Do not pledge at patreon.com and listen to the latest episode.
It was bad.
I am ashamed of myself.
But in the comments, Janess, who was at Radcon, we met her at the meetup, she left a comment
and she told me about this video called it's fuck it's called like responding to every
yes.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
You commented on Twitter.
You comment.
Yeah.
We're like answering every like criticism of communism or whatever.
And it is.
It's just a video where he goes through like all these different arguments that you hear
all the time and just kind of like, you know, does a little debunking of each one each
one.
It's really good.
The guy's channel is called spooky scary socialist.
It apparently took him two years to make this video because it's like 45 minutes of like
his little like puppet avatar, like fully animated with like mouth movements, like explaining
it.
What a fool.
Yeah.
For real.
What?
Wait.
Like a stop motion puppet or a hand?
No, like like a flash.
No.
Like a flash puppet.
A flash puppet.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
It's not like well drawn or anything.
That's the whole thing.
Very meticulous.
It was wasted effort.
It was very much wasted effort.
But at the same time, I like it.
I like how I like watching it talk, but at the same time, it wasn't it probably wasn't
worth two years.
Exactly.
When he could have just voiced it.
He could have just put it over a static image and it would have been fine.
During those those two years, VTubers have become a thing and have completely made that
production pipeline bloated and silly by comparison.
You just got to get live 2D and have it do all the automated keyframes for you.
Oh my God, you're right.
You should have just pitched up his voice made a cute little anime waifu that have a
million views right now.
I should get live 2D.
They don't even need like good lip syncing.
No, they don't.
Wait, should I get live 2D?
I think everybody should.
I was trying.
The inevitable end game for all of us.
VTubers are the downfall of society.
If I can like live 2D like version of punk, but it was too complex and I ran out of time.
I wanted to do it for like my like draw streams in August, but it was too much work to do.
You have like a 3D model of punk from the game, right?
I do.
Were you trying to use that?
I try to convert it.
Well, live 2D, you start with a drawing.
You start with a drawing and you make it like a puppet.
You make it a puppet.
But the 3D stuff, it's absolutely abysmal, terrible, horrible.
Very complicated.
I needed to convert it to some other program and open it in that program so that I could export it as something else from that program.
And the list of like the tutorial list was so long and convoluted that I killed myself and I'm dead now.
Wow.
Well done.
But I will do that.
I do want to do that like a little punk, like while I'm drawing or whatever.
I have a webcam, but like it's punk there or some other character.
One of them.
Any of them.
Pretty cool.
A gun girl.
Could you like stream and maybe you have like a little like discord chat window open and someone else on like a webcam
whose face is like controlling the punk puppet and like they like play punk through this model.
And it's like the two of you can have a little like back and forth.
I don't know.
I'm coming up with this on the fly.
So like I'm drawing.
I'm on the cutting edge.
I'm drawing.
You're drawing and your webcam is showing you but then like over here is punk who some other person who you are in a discord call with
is moving and puppeting them with their face.
Pretty cool.
Some advanced technology.
Pretty freaking cool.
The real reason you would get a Vtuber avatar is so that you don't have to show your face.
That's what I would do.
Well that's boring.
Why stop there?
Why do the most obvious thing?
We've already been exposed.
There's no there's no saving us now.
We might as well just go.
The only Vtuber I like is the bunny girl in the made outfit with the big titties.
Which one?
No there's one.
There's like there's the dog girl.
No there's the bunny girl in the blue.
There's the bunny girl in the blue.
I don't know single one of them.
She's special.
Well I just saw a gif of her.
I just saw a gif of her holding a giant carrot.
It was pretty cool.
She's special.
She's my waifu.
Nobody else is on the entire internet.
That's right.
That's correct.
She's like rabbit from Winnie the Pooh.
Who I thought was a girl growing up.
And I had a huge crush on first orgasm I ever had.
Jacking off to rabbit from Winnie the Pooh.
Is that true?
No.
I mean I would be surprised really.
I did think rabbit was a girl.
Ben's gendered enough to make that to be true.
That's believable to me.
I thought rabbit was a girl because he had because he gardened a lull.
But I still didn't think he was hot.
Think of all the progress Ben's made.
The fucking communist man he is now before he enforced such strict gender stereotypes.
He thought rabbit was a girl.
Only women are involved in agriculture.
Rabbit wore a fucking apron.
Yeah.
I think his character is an effeminate man that does things that women are supposed to do.
He acts like a mom in the one with the bird.
I forget the one with Kessie.
Yeah.
He nags like a woman.
All the signifiers are there.
I think rabbit might be trans guys.
Oh.
Which way?
I don't know.
Time to watch a new cartoon and talk about it with a little avatar in the corner.
Time to make a really long YouTube video.
Go through all the problems of making a live 2D puppet and then just make knockoff mysterious Mr. Enter videos with it.
Just have like a sans eye Winnie the Pooh OC and he sans eye Winnie the Pooh.
What?
When he's got the blue glow in his eye.
I know what you mean.
Winnie the Pooh.
Cause you gotta have a Winnie the Pooh Sona.
It's too powerful for this one.
What's your Pooh Sona guys?
Hey guys.
So I've made this new the Winnie the Pooh 100 acre wood tabletop RPG.
You gotta pick your race.
You're either a stuffed animal or a real animal.
The two have different bonuses and malices against each other.
They deal different damage types.
It's like a rock, paper, scissors type thing but there's only two of them.
So you know.
One is just better than the other.
Yeah.
What about human children?
Is that the third one?
Like human child beats the shit out of stuffed animal.
Well it's like Kyogre and Groudon.
Real animal kills child and then stuffed animal forces the real animal to choke when it eats it.
It's like Kyogre and Groudon and Christopher Robin is like Rayquaza.
I know what that means.
That makes sense.
He flies up in the sky?
Yeah and he's got airlock.
He's probably flying above the sky because he's a real person.
And he has something that the toys can never have.
And at the end you climb on his back and ride him into space.
You know?
Yeah, I remember that happening in the show all the time.
So it checks out.
You gotta climb up the Eore Hill and watch the clouds do their crazy aurora thing.
And you just take off and you gotta come on, come on Piglet.
Oh Piglet, we gotta catch fucking deoxys.
There's a meteor headed towards us.
We gotta catch it.
His defense is really low.
Piglet, I hope you learn false swipe.
That all makes a lot of sense to me anyway.
That all checks out.
Yeah, yeah, you know.
That's the sort of like...
Bringing that back.
Long time viewers might remember that.
I don't.
How far did you get?
How far did you get in Winnie the Pooh's grand slam or whatever?
Oh, not very far.
I think I got to Tigger.
It was just who was like the third guy.
I got like halfway through.
But I started to tap out when it actually started to get tough.
Like Rabbit was like, yeah, I could deal with Rabbit, but then...
Since I've played all of the Dark Souls series since that episode,
I can confirm that game is harder than Dark Souls.
Not to me, definitely true.
Yeah, I think...
I don't know, there comes a point when it's like,
you have to be like pixel fucking perfect.
And I just could not read the pitches at all.
I had no idea what was happening.
Now it bested me.
And I've beaten like Super Meat Boy,
and I've beaten all kinds of hard games and shit.
I beat Downwell.
Downwell's kind of hard.
It's not that hard.
I can't beat Downwell.
I always get unlucky.
The way to win Downwell is just to use Floaty.
My strategy is use Floaty,
hope for early knife and fork,
and just increase your max health.
But you can go the other way too,
where you just go full on hyper offensive,
kill everything before they have a chance to damage you style,
which also works, LeMau.
Yeah, video games.
I love video games.
You know, I've got some video game thing to talk about.
Maybe, I don't know...
Have either of you played World of Warcraft ever?
I played a little bit of Cat of back when it came out,
and that's it.
I played...
I fully leveled up a character one summer
when Wrath of the Lich King was new.
Cool.
And that was it.
I didn't do much raiding or anything.
Yeah, I've been...
Since they announced like a year ago,
or a number of months ago,
World of Warcraft classic servers are now a thing,
which recreate the world before the Cataclysm.
I remember when that was coming out,
a bunch of my roommates were talking about it,
because all my roommates used to play World of Warcraft.
The reason I played it that one summer was because a bunch of them,
who I went to college with, were like,
hey, Wrath of the Lich King coming up,
Ben, you should play.
You should play with us.
And I was like, okay.
I didn't end up getting that into it.
Have I ever mentioned that the people I live with,
or a bunch of them anyway,
a bunch of the people that I met,
and the way that I got this place that I live in right now,
they were a bunch of people who came from this forum
that it was called the TLDR,
and it was for people who were banned from the World of Warcraft forums.
No.
Yeah.
This is like the click of people who congealed around this house.
Incredible.
Yeah, there were these bunch of miscreants
who were banned from the Warcraft forums
and formed their own forum.
What did they say?
Did they say nasty words?
I don't know.
I got to imagine that there's as many different reasons
for having been banned from the World of Warcraft forums
as there are stars in the sky.
Well, yes.
Anyway, I just thought that was a nice anecdote I would share.
So, World of Warcraft, I was a big World of Warcraft freak
in my early university days,
or maybe, no, it was before university,
but it was like end of school,
and I was playing it all summer like a big loser.
But then, there's been a number of expansions.
Wrath of the Lich King was really big and hype,
and everybody loved it,
and it was like snowy, like Mordor,
you know, like cool, epic.
That was the cool time,
and then the expansion that came out afterwards
was the Cataclysm,
and it changed a lot of the level 1 to 60 content
in Azeroth permanently.
And I have hated the game slowly,
ever since that point,
because they just ruined so much about the things I liked.
And I'm going back now to World of Warcraft Classic
because they finally said,
fine, we'll let you have the thing you've been asking us
for ever since Cataclysm.
We'll finally let you buy this thing,
and I've been playing it.
Generous of them.
Well, it's so funny,
because they were on record, on stage,
someone asked them a couple years ago,
can you release Classic,
and they're like,
no, you guys think you know what you want,
you don't.
Yeah, it's been so annoying the years.
Ever since Cataclysm,
I played it once,
obviously because it was new,
and it was like,
wow, a giant dragon called Deathwing
burned everything.
That's pretty cool.
I play all the new content.
I see all the new quests,
and I had previously played
and seen every other prequest
before the world changed.
So I knew everything.
I knew all the differences.
The biggest difference was
they made it far more convenient
to the detriment of absolutely everything
that made Water Warcraft good.
It was so much about...
They did that to the Classic.
Yeah, they did it.
It's been slowly over the expansions,
because the level cap raises every time.
They need to make it possible
for a new player to get to the highest level
in a timely fashion.
So the amount of experience
you need to gain lowers slightly.
But with Cataclysm,
they redid all the old quests
to make them fundamentally more streamlined.
You go into a place,
and all of the quests
send you out into a small area
near the Quest Hub.
You do the quests,
you come back to the Quest Hub,
and they lead you on to the next area.
And you go through the entire zone
like a theme park ride, almost.
You never really need to think.
You never explore.
You just go on the track that they provide.
And you can technically not do that.
You can technically not do any of the quests.
It's just like,
there's no content if you do that.
So they turned it into a theme park
that sucks and is boring.
It's fine the first time,
but once you've seen it,
there's no joy in exploring the world anymore.
So I've been stewing about this,
and especially how they said,
you don't know what you want.
It takes so much longer to level up in Classic
in vanilla Warcraft.
It takes so long to level up,
and it's difficult,
and you don't want that.
I'm pretty sure.
I liked leveling up.
I had fun with the game when I was leveling up
and exploring the world,
and then when it got time to start raiding,
I was like, I hate this.
It's awful.
I've never been into raiding.
It was not fun.
The whole thing with raiding
is that it completely becomes
the multiplayer aspect
is the high level.
The world is what I like,
and I always liked the architecture,
the big chunky bone buildings
that the orcs use.
How could a bone be that big
that they make a tent out of it?
What creature could have made this bone?
Never explained, but it's great.
Just the visuals were my favorite part of playing.
That was like that.
PS2 was something that really got me
into low poly and stuff,
because I grew up with it, obviously,
but going back and playing wow,
and being able to really stop and examine everything
and trying to figure out how everything was made
was so fucking cool,
and that was one of the big catalysts
that made me think, I want to do this.
It was just the way they crafted everything.
Everything was all boxy,
but there was a lot of artistic flair to it.
Oh, it was such a good design.
Beautiful.
You said, Tom, you played
when Cataclysm came out.
All the quests were super fucking boring
and dumb, and I hated it.
It's not like
War of Warcraft Classic was like
the quests were way more interesting.
It's just that
the slowness of
the progression
and things like
the mounts cost
like untold amounts of gold
in the early game.
And now in the new games,
they're really cheap and you can get them,
and if you have one mount and one character,
you don't need to get them for a new character.
My greatest wish
when I played
was just to level up.
All I wanted was to level up
my fucking clothsmanship
or my tailoring skill
enough to make the flying carpet.
It took me so long,
I was like, I can't believe it.
I can't believe I have my flying carpet now.
This is the greatest day of my young life.
Yeah, I mean,
War of Warcraft high-level content still,
each expansion they have, all that stuff.
Cataclysm is really just a sticking point
because it removed
well-structured quests that were designed
for the zone that was built
around them and
replaced them with a shitty
theme park that is really dated
compared to all of the other content.
It just
sucks a lot.
I would make a big analysis video
comparing every single quest
and saying, this one's bad, this one's good.
Old, yeah, new bad old good.
Yeah, old good.
And I've just
loved playing.
I didn't mention this,
but the reason I got back into War of Warcraft,
because I know it's really addictive,
is like
a treat to myself
for having done the Clarissa
Tezuka thing, so I'm like,
I'm gonna play a video game and I'm gonna let myself
enjoy video game.
And I played it and I'm
it's just
mind-boggling.
How much better
designed
the pacing of the game
is when it's slow, when you're just walking around
because you have your quest log,
you actually have to read the quest
and listen, like, read
where the guy says to go,
and it doesn't tell you on the map.
You just have to know, like,
okay, head south and then
do east when you get to the bridge.
And then if you think about that, like, okay, that's there
on the map, I can go
that way and do that quest all on its own,
but there's two quests to the north.
I should probably do those first because it'll be quicker
and I can loop back around
to this point. It's like this strategy,
because of the slowness,
you want to use your time efficiently.
And it's just
a far more engaging experience
than just sort of walking to the guy who has
the exclamation point
and looking at the minimap to see where the enemy
is and just clicking on them.
I've probably said this before.
Yeah, I remember
just having a good time
just, like, running around Azeroth.
I got my raptor.
Oh, man, I bought my first raptor. Fuck yeah.
Time to run across the barons or whatever.
Oh, there's some mountains. Like, can I climb those?
Like, fuck yeah.
I love the baron's mountains the best.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And, you know,
I want that flying carpet.
Oh, it's going to take me so long.
It's going to take me so much gold to train up all these skills.
Oh, flying carpet though. It's okay. I'll put in the work.
Oh, fuck. Oh, no.
I had a point I was going to make.
Oh, and I was going to say that I had the same thing
in Final Fantasy XI.
Was 11 the online one or was it 12?
I think it may have been, yeah, 12.
12 was the offline one.
11 was the online one.
Okay, yeah, yeah. The first online one.
They, um,
yeah, when I was like, I got bored.
I got bored, like, doing local.
I couldn't really figure out the quest system because I was like a stupid kid
and I never played a fucking MMORPG before.
And I was like, well, I guess I just go kill monsters.
Like, this is boring.
I don't want to fuck with the multiplayer.
Like, oh, god, making, like, guilds
and, like, joining groups, like, that seems really complicated.
I was just going to, like, walk into the wilderness
and I just, like, walked across the entire world
and I got murdered by, like,
over-leveled monsters in every area.
But I was like, I'll just find my way around them.
Just squeeze my way around things
so I don't die and get to
go across the continent and just, like, yeah, I made it.
Okay, cool. I'm done with the game
and I'll play it again.
I got everything out of it that I wanted.
I do love shit like that.
There's been multiple times
in World of Warcraft
where it's just sort of,
especially the first few times I played it
on a, like, a new character.
I'm like, I'm going to explore, like, at a low level
and I'm going to go into a place I'm not supposed to be.
If I stick to the road,
maybe the wolves won't jump at me
from, like, 40 feet away and kill me in one hit.
Maybe they won't do that,
but they still do.
But you can, you know, you get your ghost,
you walk back to your body, you move a little,
like, a couple feet forward
and then you die again and you keep doing that
until you get to a safe place and then you're, like,
level one in, like, the really high level zone
place and people look at you and they're like,
whoa, what the fuck?
They point at you and they say,
lol, out loud.
Now you can die really fast.
It's just great.
It's the world of Warcraft.
The Warcraft sucks.
Like, gameplay is, like, okay,
but the world is great.
It's a real fun place to be.
I feel like that was the entire point from the beginning, right?
To take this, like,
game that's, like, a real-time strategy game
that, like, pulls you so far out
from, like, the actual, like,
events and, like, environments
and then drops you in this one individual
and now it's all around you, this thing that, like,
traditionally you saw from such, like, a high
angle, now you're in it.
That must have been the selling point initially
and I think it just kind of got lost
in its own, like, meta game
and now that's what, like, Blizzard makes it for.
Like, trying to, like, build around, like,
the end-level content for, like,
addicted players to keep them continuing to
give them $15 a month for another decade
as opposed to, like,
building up that world.
I don't know.
They have made some pretty interesting things,
but, like, largely
it's just more of the same.
It looks a little different
and it's addictive and there's
lots of numbers and lots of, like,
things you can complete.
There's lots of achievements, like, oh, do one
thousand of these. Oh,
I would like to do one thousand of those, but that'll take
a long time. Ha-ha, Blizzard
rubs their hands. I've got to get
their money now. They're gonna
spend money more.
I hate it when those big money men
rub their hands together and smoke their
cigars and go, nyeh, nyeh, nyeh,
nyeh, money please.
And I willingly hand it over because
they have my video game.
Damn you, Bobby Kotick, you got me again.
If only he didn't own the means of production.
Ah, fuck, here you go.
Don Nuts.
Oh, yeah.
Nah, shucks.
I only bought three months, but
I'm probably gonna want to play it more than that,
but I am only playing it, only
playing it on the weekends,
on Wednesday, and after streaming,
which is still quite a lot.
I mean, I'm gonna try it to be
like a good boy and not like a good girl.
I don't know, fuck genders.
It's too hard.
Ah, you killed yourself just there.
Ah, you fucking killed it.
Ah, call the fucking gender police
on this fucking...
The gender police, like the vegan police
from Scott Pilgrim.
You used the wrong pronoun.
You're gonna get disintegrated.
If you...
I don't know, something, something,
if you look in the mirror and you
explode, I don't know, whatever.
Shut up.
Hey, shut the hell up.
Shut up, self, the one who brought up this joke.
Hey, shut up. I want to hear what you were saying.
Keep going.
I think I was done with the World of Warcraft stuff.
I just really like it.
It's really nice.
I recommend World of Warcraft Classic
and
running around in the Barons
and Molochor.
I watched, I watched
Folding Ideas video
on the World of Warcraft
Classic
and I was like, okay.
He had some
opinions about it and I was like, okay.
Why did you say that you watched
a video and didn't...
I don't know what the video was.
It was just
him talking about World of Warcraft Classic.
And he said
this is what it's like, and I said
okay.
Well, I just told you what it's like.
Yeah, but
I thought I'd mention that somebody else
also told me.
Aw.
I thought I was going to build a career
off of this.
I thought I was the only one.
The only one who's like
thought to talk about it.
Oh no.
Everyone else is just suffering in silence.
Thinking that they're not allowed to talk
about it, but they can.
You're going to be the whistleblower.
You're going to blow the whistle on this whole
thing. Bring this whole house of cards
tumbling down.
Not today.
Sad.
Alright.
I got a thing.
I got a thing from this morning.
Early this morning.
I've been up all night.
I got annoyed. I got an argument
on my Discord server.
I'm not going to name any names or anything.
That's not the point.
The point is this was a thing that annoyed me.
I guess this is like an MI the asshole
kind of thing.
Here it is.
There's this tweet that's going around.
It's got these four girls.
It's like, oh, these are like
four lefty politics girls
who like guns
and whatever.
And they're hot.
They're leftists.
And what do you think about that world?
The squad.
It's like, okay, fine.
And I do think
that three of them are pretty hot.
And the fourth one
is also conventionally attractive.
But I
don't like her face.
Honestly, I think her face
I think there's several unattractive things about her,
but in particular it's her face. I don't like it.
When I see it,
it's like, I think it's gross.
And I
it's not important why.
It's not important why, but I'm like,
so I go on my discord and I'm like, I can't stand
seeing this tweet anymore.
I have to say
this girl who's like, oh,
these girls are so hot. I'm like, this one's hideous.
This one's disgusting. I hate them.
I didn't say I hate them,
but I was like, they're hideous.
They're awful looking.
Just one of them.
One in particular.
Who I feel like
the whole like, am I the asshole?
Like when you say that,
it seems pretty clear that you are.
I don't know.
I felt like I was re I feel like it's reasonable
if you have to ask the question
you're you already have the answer.
I feel like it's
I feel like it's reasonable
to say
I think this person's ugly.
Not even to them.
It's subjective, right?
How can we really say objectively
if you're correct or not?
I think, all right,
there was a whole hubbub in your discord
and I skinned it.
I got the gist,
I think.
So it's like turned into a thing because
we kind of just cut you off.
There was kind of a longer here.
Just for reference, I will show you the image
and I will say that I think
is very unattractive.
I am not. I do not like
her appear. I do.
I do not find myself excited by the appearance.
In fact, I see it and I want to
leave.
Absolutely have the same skirt.
I mean, you'd have to ask them
if somebody's going to have to change the thing about it is
the thing about it is the one that I the one that I don't
that I don't like the look of
is one that I followed because
I liked their tweets. I like the things that they wrote
and said.
But seeing them,
I'm like, I hate it.
I hate seeing this
and I don't want to see them anymore
because they're that ugly to me
and so I unfollowed them because I'm like,
I like, I feel like
a girl like this is probably
has made the joke before. It's like, I hope you're all
following me for my political opinions.
I'm not my breasts or whatever.
And you know, it's probably like,
everyone's just following me for my breasts
for my face, for my
because I post naked pictures of myself
and all that shit.
But you know, I have these political opinions
and I hope I'm being respected for those too.
But for me, I like their tweets
and I hate how they look.
And I think there's probably some irony in that.
I don't know.
Man, I said, I was
I was pretty rude. I was pretty rude about how they look,
but like, I don't know.
So what?
It's not like they're going to see it.
The reason there was a hubbub in
the in your discord when you posted
all that is not because
you know, they're arguing
that she, you know, if she heard
what you said, she would be upset.
It's just that it looks
weird and feels weird
to have someone
just come in and say, isn't this bitch
ugly? I didn't call her a bitch.
You didn't call her a bitch, but like, it's
that vibe, you know, and people will be like,
I
don't know.
I don't really want to be, I don't really want to be,
you know, discussing whether or not a person is ugly
or not.
And it's just sort of like, they didn't
understand why you had this
opinion. It's just a weird thing to say.
I don't know.
Because like, is there
something, is there like one,
I don't think there's anything wrong with thinking someone
is extremely
unattractive. Well, yeah.
And that being said, I don't think there's anything wrong
with saying so. If it's okay to think
it, I feel like it should be okay to say it
in a context that's not like
harassment, which it wasn't.
Right. Is your contention
simply that the tweet
is presenting this person as like
one of four very attractive people
and you don't see it there and you're merely asking
the question? Well, the reason why
yeah, I mean
the reason why I had this feeling
it's like, I kept seeing it and being like,
I don't agree. This is like
clearly the prevailing opinion
is that these four are all
attractive and to me
it's like, but I really don't like how that one
looks. I don't like looking at them. I literally
unfollow them because
they're repugnance. That seems so
unusual.
That's like, huh? Like, am I
the only one? I'm unique. I'm different.
I'm the alternative
man. Well, I am.
Well, I fucking am though.
I clearly
do not in the majority
on this question.
Yeah, I mean, I don't particularly find her
attractive either.
Okay, but a lot of
people do. Right.
Clearly.
And I don't know.
So what if I'm like
well, hey, I disagree
not even on like a fucking platform.
I think it was entirely a vibe thing.
To criticize someone's opinion
it's like, ooh, what did they say?
There's some intrigue there. To criticize someone's
looks
is just sort of like a dead end
and then, I don't know
it gets
people's cogs turning as to why you would
bring that up
and then they come up with like some
conclusions and they're like, Ben, are you like
a misogynist or something?
Or like, what's going on here?
And then you're like, you have to defend yourself
and then it's like, it gets heated
because like
the reason like, yes, you don't need to
find people attractive and
isn't it interesting that this person
who everyone thinks is attractive, I don't think is attractive?
I'm, you know
I don't know. It's just sort of
I see why there was a big storm
but I don't think there's really anything to talk about
with it.
Well, I'm sorry to waste your time.
No, I'm not wasting
you're not wasting time right now.
I'm just, I'm just
I don't know.
I just really hate, I just really hate
how she looks. I hate it.
I do. I feel that strong about it.
I'm sorry.
It's irritating.
Because it partially
to a large extent it's not
necessarily like
what she's shaped like.
It's like the face that she makes
which to some extent is like a choice.
It's like an affect that she's putting on.
There's something about the way
the way that she's communicating with me
through the facial expression she makes
which rubs me the wrong way
and pisses me off.
That's not the entire, that's not the entire thing
but that's part of it.
I just don't like
it doesn't really affect my thoughts
how or why exactly
you dislike her face.
Right. Cause I don't know
how I don't have the same reaction
and there's really just nothing for me to say about it.
I feel like that's the reason
that there was
discourse because it's like
what does everyone say to this? I don't know.
Well now I'm embarrassed because
if anyone in my discord
who is listening to this will be like
oh I was there for that haha man
that really got under Ben's skin haha
rent free LeMau
and I don't know
you're right. Correct.
That's it.
Again.
Well okay then
mission accomplished I guess.
I'm sorry
I apologize
for wasting everyone's time with that.
LeMau
All right here's
I got um
actually I'm gonna do an announcement actually
I'm gonna do an announcement for a brand new thing
that has been cooking
over on
a brand new discord
Whoa what?
Doon Koon
member of the pro and on
cast and fan of
the PCP allegedly
quote unquote
I was in my stream
talking about stuff talking about boobies
haha that's what I like doing haha
haha I was talking about
big boobies and mummy milkers and that was
you know it was a pretty funny idea
it was pretty epic it sounds like an epic time
it's like a podcast like the big boobie mummy milkers
and I tweeted it as well
and then people said are you a big boobie
or a mummy milker
and this sort of spread into
like an idea was planted
at Doon Koon's head
and she
she's going by she for the moment
she decided to make
a clone of endless war
where it was
but boobs instead
because the endless war source code
is just available so you can take it
you can edit it and now
there is a brand new text based
mmo that you can play right now
in your discord browser called
big boobies mummy milkers
haha
you go on you go
into the server you can
wait is do you get milk
no you get breast size
so here's how it works
here's how it works you go
you go in you have to
drag in the list into a big boobie
a big boobie or mummy milker
a faction
factions are exactly the same
there's no difference at all
and then
oh wait no it's not
there's not no difference because the big boobies
can jiggle
like exclamation point jiggle
and the mummy milkers can
exclamation point squirt
and you know
understandable
I'm with you so far
then you have to go to the titty bar
and you have to exclamation point squeeze
to gain breast size
I don't really know
squeeze what
you go to the titty bar and you squeeze titties
your own
I don't you know it doesn't make any sense
but it's just mining with reskin
so instead of getting slim you get breast size
you could check your size
exclamation point size
and you think your breast size is a number
it just keeps getting bigger
okay sure
every so often you get a
mutation I mean fetish
and you get fetishes
for squeezing
sometimes you do
all of the stuff that
is like in endless war in mining
has been turned into a boob thing
so
occasionally you will find an extra large boob
and you will squeeze it and you get more
boob size from that
other times it will be like
boob minesweeper
where you have to decide which
it's a
there's like a very difficult to unhook bra
and you have to use the coordinates
like minesweeper
to get it
to open it
it's booby themed endless war it's called endless expansion
big boobies mummy milkers
it's free and open and you can join it
and there's boobs
in it
you can post images
wait a minute
and there's boobs in it
there's boobs in it
no shit
I'm so glad that endless war has finally
experienced the
staple of all open source software
which is pointless ridiculous forking
it's finally happened
yo that's fucking based
yo pop that discord
link in the description
I will
not open like as we're recording it
but it will be open like in a day
so I will do it then
then how do you know any of this
cause I've been in there testing it
man on the inside
I am the big boober
duncun is the mummy milker
we're taking over endless war
everybody's gonna say
ever since munchie left endless war
sucks I'm gonna go to big boobies mummy milkers instead
duncun just wants to take everything
just wants to take everything we've got
first
the pcp
superseded by the pro and on cast
and now endless war
obliterated by endless expansion
big boobies mummy milkers
I can see it now
can't we have anything
not with this kind of performance
well I can I have like a
50% stake in the big boobies mummy milkers franchise
I'm taking you down
with all of us
it goes down together
yeah yeah yeah
you fucking
no fuck
shit no
well
sad
you know in titanic if jack had big boobies
he would be alright
they probably would have kept him warm too
maybe we solve all the problems in the world
that's just what I think
yeah
so yeah
go there right now
subscribe in list
like, comment, subscribe
jiggle and
squirt
and like and subscribe
it's exclamation point
and not exclamation
question mark
did I say exclamation point every time
it's question mark
like gib being like that's my symbol
from like pony
alright that's debts deep lore
yeah
that's way down on the pcp lore iceberg
actually it's probably not
that's probably like second or third level
yeah
I've been thinking about a pcp
iceberg thing I think somebody did make one
they did
a long time ago
in the last rfck contest
I think it was
vintage
no fuck
oh god
the shy guy
he starts with a v
oh no I feel so stupid
yeah venice
made the iceberg chart
which was
we spent a long time
going over it
even me and munchie didn't know
some of the things on there
but we also thought that some of them were weirdly placed
and we had a good round of discussion
I would move this here
and I would move that there
wait is this what I think it is
what else would be on this level
on this level
those things are fun
it was a rousing good time
a rousing
oh yes
what about the pcp one
I don't know
I was just going to say
I could think of a few
pretty deep
how deep do you think the sly 2
pcp secret episode is
wait
the sly 2
is that
it's a secret pcp episode that happened in a
call when I was playing sly 2
and I uploaded it
it's so secret I don't even know that
I don't know about this
this is a deep shit
when I was in the pcp chat
I was recording a lets play
or streaming or something
I think I was streaming
and then people funneled in
I think digi was first
and it became a pcp episode
like unofficial
I don't remember this
but it sounds like something that would happen
people are going to go look for that now
sounds pretty cool
people are going to go look for that
and relive the glory days
wow
I guess that would be pretty
deep then
I'm trying to think of something
but even that is
something that is on the internet
and some people were probably
there for it and saw it and remember it
I'm trying to think of something that no one would know
my innermost fear
yeah
or like
maybe some throw away detail
from some
radcon1 vlog or something
I don't know
I think to qualify it does have to be
like posted somewhere
yeah
they wouldn't have known about it
unless it was posted or at least streamed
the thing with those things is
obviously we're involved with the pcp
we know everything that we were in
or at least we were there
when it happened
but the viewers
not every viewer of
the procrastinators watches
or listens to every single episode
and every single related video
of all of our stuff
can you imagine
it's feasible that
something has only been seen by
60 people or is remembered
by 60 people and maybe got 100 views
it's just a stupid little vlog
but in it is a secret moment
that those like
few can remember
probably I've forgotten as well
I don't remember what happened
back then
I don't even remember what happened
do you remember
do you remember when it was
radcon2
and Davoo went around asking everybody
their opinion on Undertale
after it had been out for a year
I remember the video
I don't think he asked me
but I remember the video
oh for sure
oh there's things I filmed
there's things I filmed at radcon1
that I never made into a video
there's like
an image or two
that was posted
during the time that was being filmed
but I didn't do anything
with the footage
I was going to use it for something
because when I had like my
penguin mask and my green screen suit
and I was crawling through
the Digi's house
attic
like towards the camera
I was going to be spooky
I don't
I have trouble remembering
what happened at radcon1 vs radcon2
the way to remember
is that radcon1
was only a few of us
radcon2 had Jeff
Munchy
and Tom were you at radcon1
I was not at radcon1
I was at radcon2 though
wait so who was at radcon1
that was like right when I moved in
with digi right so I must have been there
you were the
dvoo was dvoo there
I believe dvoo was there
in radcon1
I think so
yeah you guys were there around the same time
so it was dvoo, digi
it was Nate, Ben, me, digi and Jesse
I think I was the only one who really wasn't there
and mage obviously
and Munchy
I didn't know at the time
whether he was officially on the PCP
ooo yeah I don't know
because radcon1 and radcon2
happened like a few months after each other
radcon2016 was like
autumn or winter
of 2016
wait okay
this is gonna
this is probably gonna be really annoying
to someone who's listening and knows all this
I can't believe these guys don't remember
their own fucking lives but whatever
because
Munchy joined the PCP
after monkey did
and monkey was not a member during radcon1
and 2
but munchy appeared
it was at radcon2 so like
what's up with that
munchy was at radcon2
do you not remember get the pizza now
wait no that was radcon3
I remember he was there but was he not a member
he was at that point I believe so
that's why he was there
I think Jeff was there
yeah Jeff was there
munchy was not
am I wrong did munchy join after munchy
munchy joined after munchy
and they were very close
similar at the same time
but only by a few months I think it was just
after radcon2
that munchy went to Digi's house
and they did let's plays or something
and then after that
but he wasn't in the PCP yet
he just was adjacent
okay
oh wait Jesse, Jesse was at radcon1
or just 2
yeah he was at radcon2 and 1
and 1 okay
the things that
I don't believe in the weeb
was that
I do remember believe in the weeb that was radcon2
that was definitely radcon2
what even the fuck was radcon1
I remember we had Digi had
like the
3 dimensional 360 camera
and they wanted to try it out
yeah
and we had a PCP recorded like that
radcon1
was it was just like
it was basically just like
Ben and DeVoo are moving in
just like anyone who
wants to should just come
and hang out for a while right
that seemed like a general premise yeah
yeah yeah the first
radcon was like what if we didn't go to bronycon
and then the second radcon was
let's try and fund
another one
by doing this thing no the second one was
by accident like we're doing the plebe and the weeb
but we could also fund another radcon
and then the third one was like everyone should
just come for that anyway
the third radcon was like actually the first
like funded radcon to happen
yeah yeah
radcon3 was when like
the concept of radcon really
solidified I think
um
like yeah before that it was all just like
well we're doing this other thing so why
not
all just get together and I don't know
whatever happens happens lol
and then we had um we had like
was it like radcon3 and a half
or whatever at like did you
place in Boston yeah that was
yeah
I recall yeah I came
because everyone was going there and I was like
I don't want to miss out so I got a little plane
take it and I flew over
um it was fun seeing everyone
no it was it was fun
we just sort of hung out in the room and went
to eat a couple times
yeah I went out with munchie
and
got Chinese buffet and it was
cold outside I remember
very little and we played pokemon go
or something did we
did we go eat in like Chinatown
or something I think we did
ikon was the I think
appeared for a little while
unless I'm thinking of some other time
wait was that the time with the stinky tofu
it may have been
I think it might have been yeah
no no
no maybe
there was a lot of like small gatherings around that
time and then
culminated with radcon 3.5
I don't remember if that was the time with the
stinky tofu or if it was when
I came up from Georgia
with ikon
and then we got that fucking stinky tofu
oh yeah it was it was definitely when you came
up because you were telling the story of the stinky
tofu when we went to that
same Chinese place again
during radcon 3.5
wait but
no no no but
whatever it was called that was
before I came back up
from no was I living
in Massachusetts again for that
oh okay I got him switched I got him
switched okay
because that was when we had Nate come up
and everything because we were talking about
where did you was going to move and if Nate was
going to move with them and there was a whole
had that big long sit down we were talking about
Tulsa versus wherever the fuck
and it led literally nowhere
imagine
oh that sucks that whole thing
sucks there was no there was no
point to it it was a long conversation
that was very circular and
not much headway was made unfortunately
I think I just left to go
and like
steal
the cock cast girls avocado
and maybe get drunk I don't remember
oh yeah they had a
thing they did a thing down there
yeah there's a whole separate podcast going on
downstairs while we were upstairs
it was better it was better down there
I got really mad at Jack
Jack 3 sucked and I played it and I hated it
no Jack 3 is good because you can nuke the whole city
Jack 3 is bad because it's too linear
you have to do all the missions in order
and you can't explore anything it sucks
yeah but you can make the missile
that goes
and everyone turns into like a grease
mirror on the ground
yeah but that's way later it's not fun to
like speedrun into that point you have to do
so much bullshit before you can actually have fun
fine
fine there's a fine line
just take this from me
just take this from me I have so little
and now I have nothing
gee why did you give it to me
I don't know
can I have it back please
nah nah too late
but okay I'm sorry
furtive ben
furtive little ben so easily
crushed under my boot
nooo
wait a minute
no we're not going there
we're not doing that sir
fan art fan art
fan art no shut up die
no shut up die
I watched a movie
this week I never do that
I never ever do that
but I was um
the books are gonna be here and I'm a figure in
like might as well get ready for that so I've been addressing
envelopes I have like so many
uh fucking
I addressed 300 envelopes
and I think it might have been a waste because
like there were like 300 and change
people who like made orders
uh so I
there were like 330 or something
and so I addressed 300
thinking like okay
probably there will be a few people who don't like
reply to the survey and maybe like even
a couple that like forget that they ordered maybe
you know I can't get it to them but like
you know I'll have 300
will be like plenty but like
less than like like only like
160 have like actually replied
so I might be left with like all these address
envelopes so like if anyone's
hey listeners listeners if you pledge the kickstarter
please give me your survey give me that
survey so I can get your freaking shit I got
I got an I literally have an envelope here
with your name on it just waiting
just waiting to be shipped
I gave mine and
you did I wrote yours
I wrote yours down I wrote yours to Tom
yeah I did mine immediately I got that notification
it's like slam slam
that hyperlink
I got the
I got I got mages
I know mages real name
I already knew her first name but now I
know her last name so
secret knowledge
we'll be abused later for sure
her name's kind of cool actually but I won't say it
out of out of respect and
and honor and Bushido
I should have done Nate's envelope but Nate didn't
actually answer the survey he just like sent
me a message saying like
this is my address I don't know why he did
that but he did so
I gotta do his too
but anyway I was
I was doing all these envelopes and it took me like you know
it took me a long time well I'm very meticulous
took me like
a couple days like several hours work each day
to get it all done
so I was like so I put on a movie
and I put on this old movie
that I had heard of before someone
I was I was watching a youtuber
called Jose who does these long
videos about like
old sitcoms like 90s sitcoms
sort of like breaking that he did
he's one about Roseanne he was about
married with children he has one about
uh
there's another one whatever and I really
like these videos and
he I was listening to the married with children
one and he he's talking
about one episode and where like two
couples like argue and he compares
to this movie
who's afraid of Virginia Woolf and I had
heard of that movie but I didn't know what it was about
but he compared it to this episode of
married with children and I was like
what would a movie that's just about like
two couples just sort of
like interact like talking to each other
about stuff be like and I went
and I watched it and it was great
it's a great fucking little
screenplay and it has
awoken in me a desire
for more movies where nothing happens
um and just people talk about
stuff uh because I really
like I really liked that I really
like who's afraid of Virginia Woolf I really like
12 angry men I really liked
my dinner with Andre only there was more media
available where people just talked and nothing
happened if only people could easily create
those things
if only there were so there were yeah
hmm where could I find this untapped market there
just waiting I'm sure who
knows who knows
but I made I made a tweet earlier being like
recommend me recommend me
more shit we're just like
nothing happens and it's just about people
talking about stuff because I like
it and I've gotten quite a few
uh Twitter recommendations so
maybe I will go and look into some of those
uh soon
um soon
dairy who's afraid of Virginia Woolf
was it real I was I was gripped
I was very I was gripped the whole
way through I was like
haha haha what are they gonna say
it was I was glued to the screen
but not really because I was
just listening I was mostly
listening but I still completely understood
what was going on it's like you know is it
is it old old like
ah see I'm from the old
times and I talk like this it's not
that all that's this from the 60s
oh okay um
but it's in black and white um
the the
uh everyone everyone
is drunk the whole movie
and like watching the movie made me feel
drunk which made me happy
haha
it was it was it was intoxicating
in quite ways
than one yes yes
um now it was that was
probably the highlight of my week uh
to be honest
sad I know
actually no why is that
that's not sad a good you find a good
oh I really like a film that I really like
yeah that's yeah that's the highlight of my week and I'm not ashamed
yeah yeah nowadays like
the normal media
uh like
potato chip food that you
eat is like I saw a funny
meme on Twitter the day oh
oh oh
kill me now like like watching
a real actual thing that people
put effort into is is a good
nobody does it I don't do it
nearly enough I mean
I love
long
boring YouTube videos
like the one I do like the ones
about that I just the hose ones
about sitcoms I
will watch every fucking uh
summoning salts like history
of a speed run video
and like other channels that do the same
thing I'll just put that shit on auto
play and just let it go
um I am I can
talk about Bill and Ted
yeah that sort of stuff
I like it too but I also
don't like it I know that I don't like
it because I don't remember it
there's a occasionally I remember a video
and be like god that was a really interesting video
I want to watch it again sometimes
it's good some sometimes
like I'll put something like that on and be like okay
this will be on while I work and then I'll get
work done and it's like yeah cool
and other times I'll be like I'll put this on
while I work and then I'll get distracted
or I'll be a few but you know
maybe that's not the video's fault
right like maybe it doesn't I was just
didn't wasn't feeling focused that day
and and I would have gotten distracted
by something
do you do you always I guess it's just
kind of part of my workflow now
do you structure your days in any
fashion do you like have like
work days and like relaxed days
no
because that's how I
I feel like it's a good way to get over
the the random
not being able to focus
is allowing yourself to do
whatever you want
to relax and not work specifically
not to work on some days
so that other days are more like
you wake up and you know what you're supposed to do
even if
even if like it's like a creative
thing and you're setting this wrecking
your brain like how do I do this
and you don't get a lot done it's still
like better than
getting distracted and watching some
YouTube videos I feel
every day is a work day
unless I have plans
which is rare but occasionally
happens and then that's a
not work day
but then it's like okay well
every day is technically a work day
but I don't actually
work on every
quote unquote work day because
I feel like every day
well yeah I mean that's exactly why
I like structure them
to be like not everywhere
every day is a work day because if every day
is a work day for me at least
um it causes me
like
to do work
really badly where I don't
build up any momentum and I just feel bad
that I hadn't done enough work on all the
days instead of feeling good
that I did a lot of work on like two of the
days
yeah
because there's that thing where you build up momentum
you start work which is the hard part
and then if you're still working for hours
and hours you can get a lot
more done in that time because you're already
going you're already moving
yeah the initial momentum is the hardest part for sure
when I yeah
like um the times when I've
been most productive or when I'm like
when I'll have a period where I'm like
wake up start immediately
on the thing that I've
been working on lately
you know kind of go through the day
no take breaks maybe but like you know pretty much
work on it and like go to sleep
thinking like tomorrow okay
I made headway tomorrow
I gotta work on this part of it
go to sleep wake up like
okay gotta work on that
thing and then start again immediately
that clarity is like so
fucking hard for me
I have so many projects I'm trying to do and it's like
which one do I work on and it's like just picking one
is so difficult because it's like which one
is the most optimal which will help
my quote-unquote career
it's the worst question to ask
it's terrible
and I'm cursed by it all the time
the best answer to which one is the most
efficient is which everyone is the
least efficient because at least you'll be doing something
oh it's a never ending
never ending pain never ending pain
you just gotta choose one even if it's
the worst possible choice it's better than
not making one that's that's what I think
oh I mean it's it's completely true
but I'm just a
fucking
idiot
I have um
I have a have a couple things
I could be working on right now I have
I have
the the sonichu 102 lecture
which needs a little more editing
and I have to make
some do some shit with that and then I have
the um the next slime and punishment thing
which I've kind of started on
uh that's
yeah I've mostly been working on that
as like a distraction from the
from the the the video because
like I haven't I haven't decided
like what exactly I want to
do with the end of that that video
and I kind of just don't want to think about it
because it's because making decisions is hard
whereas like with the slime and punishment thing
I'm like okay I have a pretty I have a vague idea
of how I want some things
to look in that so I'm just gonna
kind of uh you know I can just
like do some of that bull just fuck around
with that and like you know it doesn't have to
it doesn't have to
I don't have to really commit to very much
just kind of chip away at just like a thing or two here
and there that's all you know
finishing that is like a future bends
problem whereas like
with the sonichu video it's like I could
finish this like right now
and then that would be present bends problem
is like you know the decisions
I made with regard to that and I want
my problems to be in the future
not in the present
you know that makes sense
yeah I I know
but I don't
accept it I will kill you
Ben say okay
okay oh no
Gib has complete authority to kill
us now because you have
completed an entire fucking
ridiculous comic and like
no time at all and you're already starting a second one
and that godly power is just too
much for me I can't stand to look at you
the bright pure energy emanating
from your form burns
my mortal flesh
hmm yeah
I did
I did a good comic one
time I did that once
kind of you only get like 30
days of like a credit for
the glow and then it just fades
you gotta earn it again it's unfortunate but
I don't make the rules
the corona the vapor comes out
I'll see the book and I'll be like
oh my god I remember the vapors
wow this came out like when I was
two years old I just said corona
meaning like a halo without
like not not like the virus not like
the virus that's not we're demonetized
that's too late sorry I didn't mean to I
didn't mean no okay okay
vapors came out
when I was you know
when I was in elementary school
I was reading the vapors and I thought
when's the next one coming out and it
never did the end
and then I decided I would make them
haha
uh
I got
I got a message from
from Jade Morro
today because I was
posting
about the vapor at guest artists
I have like a thread that I want to
finish up where I post like a little like
hey check this person out about all the
guest artists and the latest when I posted
was was was Jade
and they they messaged me
because I had included in that
post a
birthday drawing that they had made
for me the like happy birthday
because it was my birthday and they put like
me and some cool stuff there was
Magda and Phantom Horn and a bunch of
little little funny things
there and I'm vaping and it's very nice
and I really liked it and I put that in
as one of like the sample image of like this is this
person's art style and they and Jade was like
oh you save you save the thing
for me from that I made and I was like yeah
I love that and they were like I made
that I made that back when I was in high school
and now I'm in and now I'm in college
and I was like oh my god
oh that was you that I'm
so old Jesus
oh it's the worst the worst
panic is setting in
I literally can't stand
that thought
everybody's got down to youngster
gross disgusting
fucking younglings
I just feel like an outdated human I feel like
I'm running like old firmware and I can't be
updated and it's just like
I can't interface with
social.exe whatever
exists now the new version
I'm not I'm not sure
I'm not sure which is a scarier
thought like the thought of being
like
the thought of being like I'm I'm here
you know I continue
I continue to like age
whereas it feels like the user base
of the internet is not
meaningfully aging there is a certain
like sort of young adultness to it
that is constant yeah and I
am becoming progressively older in comparison
to are they gonna like force us to go on
to Facebook exclusively at some point is that what
happens but but like
that's a scary thought or there's
like oh no I do age
out of it and I go somewhere else like where
the old people go no I think what happens
I don't know which is worse the new internet
just starts and it's gonna be new apps and things
that we don't understand like tiktok's already doing that
like although the young young kids
are on tiktok you know like the 15 16 17
year olds like people who understand the new
new new internet
tiktok is not like a replacement for other
social media it's like the biggest app out
right now
I feel like there's probably a new tiktok already
that we're not aware of probably there probably
will be and then tiktok
there's the one that there's the one that donald trump
made an account on right wait what
am I crazy I feel
like I saw a story that like there is a tiktok
competitor and like donald trump made an account
or maybe it wasn't him maybe it was like
mike pancer some some governor that supports
our stock I hadn't heard about this no it was
called like triller I think
what
no trill
I don't want to look for that it sounds scary
yeah wait wait trill I'm gonna google
triller trump
oh boy
yeah trump no no
no it's trump jr
that's right trump jr
joins triller and claims tiktok
could haunt kids forever
story from business insider that's a boomer sentence
business insider just some
kid said something about a thing
like he's the president's son
but he's just some kid
I mean no he's like
he's gotta be like 40 something
wait not not baron
trump
donald trump jr he's like
an adult yeah he's an old man
I don't know who that guy is
I thought he only had like a tiny boy
no no no no he's got a bunch of sons
that are all like adult
and then he's got the one who's like
minecraft kid who's like a
isn't he like a furry or something
or there was no
like jesse I think like jesse ventura's
kid is like a furry no no no shaggy
two dopes kid is a furry
there's
there's something about baron trump
I think maybe he like posts about anime
or something on like whatever
he's like he's like a weeaboo or something
like that cool who isn't these days
yeah that's not even that's not even
interesting
get get get good baron trump
uh
donald trump jr looks like
looks like roosh
he's got a beard like roosh
oh god I don't even know what roosh looks like
I don't like it
that pickup artist
I know who roosh is I just don't know what he looks like
yeah give ass 2
right yes I don't
like pickup like you like you pick up
artists
you pick up me put me down
if only it was that simple
yes
pick up artist is a person
who helps like carry
priceless works of art from museum to
museum
pretty pretty cool
I just googled roosh and I don't want to
look at him anymore I don't like it I don't
like it I think a response to my funny
pickup art
sorry it's time for me to retire
guys I think I'm not funny
oh sorry
sorry you got to go on facebook exclusively
now you've you fumbled
one joke and that you only get one
everybody gets one you're done
oh
to the boomer farms with you
but what about um
uh
the arrow in the knee do you remember that one
oh you're just digging your grave even further
the cake
maybe the cake was telling the truth
the whole time
there will probably be people
listening to this podcast who barely know
those references
dude it's great I
the whole thing about getting old is like
yeah it's kind of sad you know the grave
and all that whatever cool
but one thing I have found
increasingly funny is when I
realized that somebody is old
young younger than me
which is often
like they're like quite a lot younger
then I it
has become increasingly funny to just say
things that were around when I was
around like young and there are no longer
around just to rub it in their
faces they don't care in any way
they have no reason to care but I just
it's just really funny that I would just
oh my god like you don't even
know VHS and they don't
laugh but I laugh no
it's really funny I wouldn't laugh either
it's only funny to me
but it keeps getting funny I don't know about that
it keeps getting funny like the older
I get I'm just gonna say
you don't even know what a cassette tape is
so young and
they're like shut up shut up
there's oh oh my god
oh my god that reminds me
holy shit I almost
I almost don't even want to talk about
this because I feel like
it
ah fuck it you know what
it's the podcast
I was considering if maybe I should
make like a video about this but I don't know what I would
even say about it to be honest but um alright
so my friend
Hargadine
sent me
something in the mail
and by sending me something in the mail
I mean left it on my
on my front porch
and bolted in the dead of night
um
and you're not going
you're not going to fucking believe what it is
like I like a goat's head
like what is it
it's
I can't say it
I can't I can't
I can't make myself verbalize it
because it's beyond belief it defies
description
I feel like I'm in a dream
is it a Benzite themed
flashlight
no
no it's both volumes
of the official Avril Lavigne
manga
what
how
I've only read the first one
but I'll get to the second one
when was that so difficult to say
I mean it's funny
I don't know
I just can't believe it
I just can't believe
that I'm so blessed to live in a world
where I
not only exist but I
am the proud owner
Avril Lavigne's make five wishes
volumes one and two
what does the
wait what does it look like
how good is the manga
um
does it feel Japanesey
no not particularly no
and it reads left to right
so you know it pretty
poser manga
does it look like we're just how to draw manga books
from the mid two thousands
no it's
it's a little manga ish
but you can tell it was drawn by like a western artist
and like it's fine it's okay
uh um it's very
what's the plot what's the story
it's very rough it kinda looks
like it was drawn with a ballpoint pen
well uh some of the panels are
very sketchy
and in a way that is like
you're telling me the guy who got contracted to make the
Avril Lavigne manga didn't put his heart into it
it's a
it's a girl
well it's a girl artist and a guy who like
wrote the story okay
I mean I guess I'll just say it
it's drawn by Avril Lavigne herself
no it's starring Avril Lavigne
Avril Lavigne had nothing to do with it
but she's starring in it
and then created by Camilla
Derrico and Joshua Disart
um
the okay the plot is
and again I've only read half of it
it's it's basically just a monkey's paw
like it's literally a monkey's paw
story about a like a
girl who
has like she's like a kid
who's like sad about stuff
and doesn't like school and whatever
is unpopular or whatever
and she finds this website
called makefivewishes.com
and she orders something and
which what shows up is a demon
and the demon has
like these five horns and she can like
make a wish and like crack it
and it's literally just monkey's paw right
she can make five wishes
um and there's and stuff happens
uh she's like oh what if I was
I wish my boy would notice me
like oh I wish this old man that I don't like
would go away
you know it's like oh that's
bad that's uh you know bad things
are gonna happen if you just make wishes really nearly like that kid
uh the the only
relevance to it at all
is that she's a big Avril Lavigne fan
and Avril Lavigne
is like her imaginary friend
and it's basically just like her
her her better nature
like when like she like
is being cruel to an old man
Avril Lavigne is like
the voice of her conscience being like
stop don't say these things
and she's like yeah I hate you
you're old and ugly and Avril's like oh
you shouldn't have said that that's mean
um it's just like D.W.
and her imaginary friend from Arthur
it's like these did
did D.W. have an imaginary friend?
right wasn't her name?
oh yeah that rings a bell
was never a huge Arthur fan
well you missed that
some good shit
I mean I mean I read the Arthur books
Arthur PCP lecture
in second grade
I mean we should make like Arthur analysis
videos about each episode
with our Arthur Sonas
we have to make them drawn
like as our actual selves in that uncanny
valley style that Arthur uses for
real life guest stars
oh yeah
I don't know what you're referring to
look up Matt Damon Arthur
I think Matt Damon was on Arthur at one point
and he just looks like a real person
face on an Arthur character
it's very strange
oh my fucking god
that's how they had guest stars on Arthur
they just look like
that's so bad
this can't be real why would they do this
why would they fucking do this
how else did you know
it's Matt Damon
what the fuck
yeah it's
interesting stylistic choices
they just have fucking full human faces
yeah it's very weird
what the fuck
this is
bad
it's so bad
I can't believe this
alright we gotta put that
Ben it's strange to me
cause I just you being you
I would have pegged you as someone who
watched Arthur I was at least familiar enough with it
to know what this was about it just seems like
something you would know about
seems like in your real house
no
when I was a little kid in second grade
we had the Arthur books
in the school library and that's how I was familiar
with them and then when I was a little older
there was the show
but I was like oh I read these books
when I was in second grade first grade
like that's like a little baby show
so like I was like no I don't want to watch
this Arthur cartoon that's for like
fucking little baby childs
but I think uh I don't know
apparently it was kind of a pretty good kid show
people seem to have mostly
fond memories of it but I was like
not interested I haven't seen it in so fucking long
I have no idea if it's any good or not
but they're just things like Matt Damon
that are just burned into my brain
I feel like it was pretty good
somewhat funny
and like wholesome
family entertainment
mm-hmm
but I don't really recall it too much
there's like a couple episodes that I remember seeing
multiple times
where like DW
breaks the airplane and Arthur punches her
and he gets in trouble
you shouldn't punch your sister
I don't know
there are a couple like clips
that like I guess they've made some pretty
like
meta jokes on the show
every now and then and like I think I've seen
a bunch of those on like YouTube
whatever in a way that's like
okay I'm sure every episode wasn't like
that but you know these are kind of funny
these are interesting
I remember
I mean I remember one joke from it
that I really liked and it stuck with me for years and years
you know there was the theme song
every day when you walking down
the street
you get along with each other
I remember they had the one episode where like
they have a little sequence where
brain they tell a little brain
side story and they play like
the brain version of the theme song
and it's like
every day when you walking down the street
you stop and think
hmm
and that's it that's the end of the song
like yes
cool
I stop and think
I do
brain does
end of song
incredible
cool good job
they did like a South Park parody right
they did
and that's pretty weird
that Arthur would do that
yeah
if you're a little baby kid you shouldn't be watching South Park
that's for grown
that's for the parents who are sitting there watching like 17 episodes
of Arthur with their kids in a row
and there's a little bit of levity to like make sure
they're still alive you know and they haven't died
mm-hmm
God bless you
God bless you Arthur
I am really perplexed
by this line and the second image
I posted tell Arthur
this is Matt Damon
hardfark saying tell Arthur
he'll never eat lunch in this town again
and he appears to be naked
he does
what is happening
what is happening you just got to watch them
to find out
is that like in sync
I believe it is
or Backstreet Boys maybe one of the two
wait
did one of them have a black guy
you know
why is that one darker
I don't remember I think they're
I think they were already
we're already in the thin line already
let's take some risks
I don't remember
there being a darker one
there are those pans but what do I know
okay cool cool
um
alright
how do we how do we fucking oh right
the Avril manga
I don't know should I make a video where I review
Avril Lavigne's Make 5 Boys
I haven't finished yet so I haven't said the ending
you should do a
like one-to-one like parody
of a Likara review
where you
do the voice and then you talk about
the Avril Lavigne manga
and post it online
and that's what you should do
I
I would probably do
if I was going to ape anyone
it would be Jenny Nicholson
and I would probably do one where I just like
sit on my bed
and look into the camera
because why not you know that's engaging
I'm there I'm making eye contact
with you the viewer it's quarantine
you're starved for affection
you're starved for connection and I'm giving it to you
let's laugh together
over the strange cultural artifact
I really want to
kind of like the idea of like a
high up camera
view
sitting on his bed talking about
Avril Lavigne did you say swole
Benzane small Benzane like like
oh small Benzane okay
I prefer swole but
but sure okay
that's
the unfortunate thing about
Avril Lavigne's make five wishes
is that
like you know because Avril is such
like a non entity
it's not that weird
like the story is not that weird and it's not like
really it's not like
super bad or like
ridiculous it's just like pretty normal
the actual story is pretty like
okay it's a monkey's paw story
about a sad girl oh well
darn you're only you're only halfway done things
could go off the rails
let me see let me let me flip through
and if I see anything going off the rails
um
could be a demon fight oh my god who knows
is she is she going Super Saiyan
I mean you've already have my attention
is she
oh my god she's like glowing
there's got to be a metaphor
she can't be literally glowing
oh my god she's
okay no I'm not I'm not gonna spoil
myself I'm not gonna spoil myself I'm not gonna
tell you what happens all right six
okay I'm ready for the video
I might do it might be
kind of funny I'm gonna do
I'm gonna I'm gonna do a cooking video I'm gonna do
I'm gonna do a how to make gummies video
um but you know what
tragedy struck this week
because I was like well
I'm almost out of my worm syrup
time to buy more powder
and uh it's it's
not it's not there it's not on Amazon I
can't get it they're like out of stock
and I don't there's no no nobody else sells
it wasn't that a problem last time
didn't you just have to wait well
last time they stopped selling
the syrup which is why I had to
get the powder again and like re
like reformulate the whole thing because
I'm like okay well now I don't know the
I don't know what the original
like concentration was now I gotta figure that out from
scratch and I finally did figure it out
that was okay great problem solved
I can do it with the powder instead
but now the powder is gone too
and I'm thinking like
is this like is isomolta
oligosaccharide just like a vanishing
resource on earth and they're just like running
out and there's no more like why
please
what am I gonna do
and I'm thinking like you know they
stopped selling those gummy like the
gummies that have the same main ingredient that I
was why I started making these they stopped
selling those at Whole Foods I don't see them at Whole Foods anymore
and I'm like did they just vanish is this
have they just like stopped farming
this powder does it just not get produced
anymore like what what does the powder made
of how does it get made
the powder is made of um
oh fuck what's the plant
it's made of it's not
chicory root
um wait
actually it's time to start a farm
then tapioca it's it's
it's soluble fiber extracted
from tapioca okay
just do that just get tapioca
and soluble fiber
listen yeah
yeah you yeah that's the
that's the tricky part that's the tricky part isn't
isn't it just just go to go
to chemistry our chemistry and
and say hey how do I do this and then
we extract the soluble fiber from tapioca
and they'll say oh oh you
fool oh you simpleton oh here
let me let me show you let me come to
your house god you fucking idiot
check the FAQ before you post
there's
there's another
thing there's a similar
powder called inulin
which I have some of that
and I'm going to try using it
instead and it might work
like exactly the same and be like a
viable substitute or it might not
I don't know um so
I guess we'll see how that goes
I don't know and the future
is uncertain
I just I'm a drift
I'm without an anchor
in this gummy sea that I'm
sailing I don't know where
when I'll find the shore
and the storms are brewing
if you if you catch my drift
I think I do it's bad
news for worm boy
it's bad news for worm boy
and I'm all out of mango flavor
it's the second best flavor
mango and passion fruit easily the best
flavor is buy a mile
peach is pretty good I guess
the company that I buy the flavors from
like those ones are good
and then a couple of them are like bad
like their cherry is just like bad
like I don't know how you fuck up cherry
that's like so simple but it did
the cherry tastes like ass
apple bad pear bad
it's a shame because I really like
pears
I really like like green apple
and I like cherry I like I like all those
and you think they no those are bad
I'll never buy them again
passion fruit though
that's my favorite it smells so good
it tastes so good
I can't wait to eat a gummy worm
I can't wait to eat it
I can't wait to make them but oh but I can't
there's no more powder oh it's gone
okay okay
okay
um well
I have one more thing
I could mention it's a bit of a weird
topic though it's a bit of a heavy topic
base
and it's this is just a question so
I was uh you know
browsing the pornography
sites to see some
whoa whoa whoa what the fuck
I know
give there's
this is this is a children's program
what every
time we every time we post an episode
we click the little box that says is this for children yes
shit hey children
go to pornography.com they know
I know that and you know that
but you're not allowed to say it
we're not allowed to acknowledge that
universal truth anyway
this is a this is a moral
quandary because I came across
um pornography
like a drawn stuff
of jaden animations
the youtuber
the the story time youtuber girl
lady yeah I don't
know what she looks I've never seen her in like
no it wasn't it wasn't her
in real life um
it was her character that she uses
in all of her videos with the the
hair and stuff yeah
and and they you know
it was a sexually
it was a porn with her
as the thing
okay amazing
hmm
like my first thought was
that's not correct you can't do that
because jaden animations is not a character
created by jaden animations
the that's just how she
chooses to portray herself
in the videos where she talks about very
personal things and that is her
for all intents and purposes
and then just because it's a cartoon
people find it
to be okay to make pornography of it
I'm not I'm not sure
where like it's it's
it's weird because it's like
no I don't
think I agree with you I think
I think if it's a it's a cartoon
avatar I kind of think it's fair game
well this is what what I was
wondering about because the
cartoon avatar aspect
regardless of that there's been like
I mean there was game grumps porn
like of John and Aaron fucking each other
and Danny and Aaron and this is like
that human beings they know what
everyone knows what they look like
pornography of them
they don't seem to mind they think it's funny
as far as I know
but like
I feel like
jaden herself would is not
the sort of person who would be okay with
this and so I feel like
is is it a is it a case by
case thing is it just sort of like a
politeness like if they don't like it
maybe don't do that because it's
that that is there like
is there likeness in all the ways that matter
well
and it's not like a character designed by
them I don't know
are you say like
when you say don't do it
I didn't say that
but I'm playing
it yes
well like
I don't know do you mean it shouldn't be allowed
I don't know I found
it to be a question
like because it was good art
and
I'm like well it looks good but like
I feel a bit
weird about it because I know that she would
not like this
because I you know I've watched a few of her
videos I know what she's like she is sort of
I don't know self-conscious
about these sorts
of things
so it's just sort of the context
of it being
her and like the
like I'm not trying to like
decide on like what is the rule we should have
for all things I don't know
if it's if it's okay to do it with the
game grumps
then I don't think that like her
the fact that she wouldn't like it
means that it's not okay to do it
I don't think it's not
it means it's not okay I just think
it's
probably shouldn't anyway like I don't think anyone should
get in trouble for it I don't think it's quote-unquote
bad but I think if
it's someone's
representation of themselves and you're
projecting like your
fantasies onto a real person
essentially
and they're not comfortable with it it's probably not like
you probably shouldn't but like it's the
internet you're not going to be able to stop it
and like if you're jaden animations you kind of have to
like know going into like becoming
a public-facing figure that this is just
one of the things that happens to you
yep
sorry
uh yeah
I mean I was
at first you know I was like
humming and hoeing over it
and then I went to see the artists
like they clicked on their name
their name was like signed
and they had their twitter account and
their attitude was sort of like
what pushed me to making it
to thinking that it was wrong because they were like
in the comments like they had this
pinned and in the comments
people were like you can't do that this is immoral
this is like this is a real person
and there was a very clear
divide of people who just said
um get mad
go cry somewhere
fuck you nobody cares
we'll we just want a fat
and um
the people who are like
you know trying to be a little bit
you know moral
about it
and uh I just
I just I didn't like the attitude of the artists
because the artist was like
fuck you go die
if you don't like it
I'm gonna keep drawing it and it's like
I guess like you can do that
it's not like I'm gonna try and stop you
but
it just got me thinking because it's not something
I had not come across that before
even though I did know about
Game Grumps stuff though I guess I had come
across it before
there's already been a thing I just like
more of a visceral like reaction to that one
I mean
I don't know do is it
is it okay to do that with like
Aaron and Dan
John whatever
I mean if they're if they don't have a problem
with it I kind of
I kind of don't see what their opinion
has to do with it
well I guess it's just sort of like a courtesy thing
like if you ever want to get along with
them and they don't like it and you do it anyway
then you're not going to be
able to get along with them but there's
you know the whether it's wrong or right
to do I think it's
it's there's no like
hard and fast rule like you should
be allowed to do it
and the people who approve of it
will like it and the people who disapprove
of it will not like it or you
and that's just how
it will be
well
I think if
I mean does she know about it
I she said anything about it
like I don't know all
this is weird because there's
lots of them like it was wasn't just
one artist it was like a whole tag
and I was like oh oh
okay
so it's big enough
that she probably has heard about it
I don't know if she said anything about it I don't follow her
too closely I mean I wouldn't
if I were her
yes
but uh
that's the
event that happened
on thepornography.com
that's pretty weird
what's the
URL for that
what's the uh
send me the link
so I can like really get an informed
opinion about that
I can't remember the name of the artist but I guess
I can go look and find it
if you actually want to see it
no I don't know
I actually
I don't even know what Jaden animations looks
like what her avatar looks like
it's like barely anything right
it's just like a little brown hair
long brown hair I think
it's a stick figure with a purple shirt usually
and the brown hair with distinctive
curls in it
and it's like you know
iconic I guess
the bigger talk people animation
things
story time
okay
I remember
wow
I google it
and I don't even have to google Jaden animations porn
and like one of the first results is like a picture
of her like getting a wedgie
and like her butt cheeks are kind of showing
so like okay
yeah I mean it's I guess it's
it's just one of those
things where it is a female
and it is there for
yeah that's the thing that was
annoying me a little bit there were some people who were saying
I invoke rule 34
like that's like that
I mean I understand that's like the funny joke
there's porn on the google search
there's porn on the first page of the google search just for Jaden animations
okay this isn't even like this isn't even
niche it's like yeah
rule 34
if it exists this porn of it does not mean
that it is like okay
to do and like should be okay
people people were invoking
rule 34 like it was an actual
oh I see I see
and it's like stupid
it's like oh well yeah
okay yeah that's a terrible argument
it's like um oh well didn't
you know that this thing
always happens therefore
it is good
right right very stupid
something an idiot would think gotcha
yes
but uh well
I mean people have drawn
like my characters
but not of me
I think
well now it's gonna happen
not too late not anymore
I don't know
I keep thinking
like well it's you know it's okay
to do it with the grumps so why not Jaden
but it's like
was it okay
is that is that violating
Dan and Aaron's
fucking autonomy or whatever even if
they don't care like is it not
okay to do am I just
am I just drawing on precedent
it is an interesting set of questions
is it dealing more
with real people that are not
explicitly like in the
the porn industry
like you could draw a porn of a porn
artist and nobody would have bad an eye because they already do that
it's sort of like in the same
way that it's not right
the sort of like celebrity
um
candid photo culture
where they try to get upskirts of like famous
women coming out of the car
like that sort of stuff it's not right but I also
don't really care because they're celebrities and they have loads of money
and I don't know
anything about that world
it you know it's like bad
for them but it's not so bad
that I should like fight
for their rights because it's
it's not it's not that big of a deal
really
yeah
but then again it's like it's
it's a complicated it's a complicated thing
agreed
you can't fight every single battle
yeah I'm going back and forth
I think
I don't know what to think about this
sorry
shall we
if you have something to say in the comments
and you haven't already commented
and left then you can
say something in the comments and will
tell me tell me what to tell me what to think
please
the one time will ever divert
to commenters for our opinions
ah
well that
sure was a diversion
um
what do we think are we are we
it's time for voicemail I think it's time for voicemail
yeah we're closing in on
almost two hours
oh shit right now
how did we do that
well we're really smart
we're really
you know there's not there's not that many
there's not that many today there's only one two
three four five six
seven
eight nine ten eleven there's only
twelve emails or voicemails so
oh we're gonna
we're gonna blast through these
I gotta open up the voicemail tab and
do time flat I would say
in Toronto do we have any
do we have any
familiar names
yeah one or two yeah a couple of
names I recognize here
very good
right
I'm ready
okay uh first one we're gonna do
is hobbies and productivity
three two
one hobbies are not meant
to be productive and anyone who thinks otherwise
is a fool
if you're doing something as a hobby and your main goal
is for it to be productive over being fun
you should have made that thing your job
dumbass the point of
a hobby is to relax and not be
productive so you don't kill yourself
from fucking
burnout
um so if you're trying to be productive with a hobby
it's a side hustle it's not a hobby
anymore
yeah well um
you know a lot of people
want to make their would want to make their hobby
their job in some way
that's a lot of people's goal
you're doing something on the side with the hope of
making it your main thing
I think the problem the things
with like the people
have issues with hobbies and things is like even if
you're doing something as a hobby like if you're just drawing
and like I just want to draw for fun you know
like with social media and everything like everything
has metrics now besides just I'm making
money off it versus I'm not
and you get into that mentality of like now
I'm like in a market and competing with other people
and because I'm trying to just like
get recognition and that kind
of makes it feel like a job even if you're
not trying to make money off it or make it your job
hmm yeah
I mean
me like a big number me like a number go up
exactly when you I mean
when you're being
you could be productive in a hobby
even if it's something you're not monetized
like if you're if you're just gardening like
for fun you can you know
you can be productive have a productive day
in your garden I think what they mean you know
all these flowers are like you know well fertilized
now I think what they're talking about is like
being productive at the expense
of the
relaxation which is the main point
right like if being productive
in the garden is what makes it fun then of course
that's part of it
but like if it's a fucking chore
and you kind of dislike it
then it's not a hobby it's something else
it's a fucking work it's
it's a chore literally
yeah
if you're starting to stress about it
you know yeah
yeah you have a motive
there at some
level of consciousness besides just having fun
yeah I have a hobby
in crochet and I haven't touched
my yarn in months but that's fine
I'll get around to it when I
feel like it
hmm
I guess my hobby would be
yeah I guess worms are my hobby
yeah that's what I was gonna say
like I don't think you've ever been stressed about that at all really
well
other than like just like the
the toil of doing the work
I mean it stresses me out to go on Amazon and see that
they don't sell isomolto oligosaccharides anymore
well that's more stress with capitalism
then
everything else
of the other Sakurai that made smash bros
yeah fructo oligosaccharide
was the smash bros guy
but that's not stress from my hobby
that's stress from an external
force preventing me from doing it
I guess I am gonna
turn that into if I make a video about that
which I want to I guess that would sort of be
turning it into a side hustle I guess
technically I might make ad revenue off that but like
a couple thousand people
I just want to make that like just because
I want to I think yeah I think getting the word out
like making money from something
doesn't necessarily make it a side hustle
especially if it's something like a video where it's almost
incidental you know but like
if you were like making that video like okay I'm
gonna make this I'm gonna start building an audience to try
I'm gonna rebrand
my whole my whole online persona
I'm gonna be the worm guy that's where it becomes
a side hustle
sure sure sure
um yeah
alright
thanks for the call
next one literally
Fapper321
hello pcp
I want to
personally congratulate
the entire fanbase
for not ever
audibly jerking off
during these fucking voicemail so
I
mean
I wonder I wonder if maybe
there were some in the past and Nate
they didn't make it through Nate's quality
controls we'll never know
we will never know
um but nowadays anything
goes it's it's anarchy baby
uh next one
phallic person
2 1 go
hey I heard you had a big cock
nice
thanks man
you heard right
right back at you brosif
uh
well that well that that just makes my day
yeah gotta say
send that send that voicemail
next week as well
yeah keep keep it coming keep it coming
uh if you know what I'm saying
uh next one
zinthus about poetry
3 2 1
yeah so like
6 years after finishing school I'm back
to reading and trying to recite poetry and shit
you're so fucking old dude
you're so fucking old
cause I had like this thought
isn't poetry like based
when you think about it
this primary mode of distribution
was oral or through newspapers
aka through the only
real mass media at the time it was
invented so in essence it was like
the only real
fast snappy disposable media
that could spread in a society in the past
what is
the modern equivalent of fast disposable
media that can spread like a disease in modern times
memes and youtube
videos exactly boys
what I'm saying is meme compilation
videos on youtube is the equivalent of
Edgar Allen Poe and Mikhail Minesko
fuck yeah
alright
alright I like your hustle
um
so poems were memes
memes are poetry I think
is the point
no I think
no I think that a
a poem could
express a meme like there might have been poetic
memes or so what we might consider memes
today like
well nursery rhymes
is that a form of poetry
or like a limerick or something right
yeah
like a joke
in poetry form like
the raven is not a meme
I quote the raven every day
I always go to my friends I say
quote never more
and they're like
they're like I loved it
when he said that
no
just awful just a disaster
frankly your analysis
just mantles itself
it doesn't need us to do it for it
for you
try harder
next one is greetings gents
three two one go
hey my dudes
that all is well
today I got a few things in my mind
but first
I have a buddy here
that really wants to talk to Ben
oh god
is it the samurai
god damn
you have all been had
no
I knew it
how to taste
revenge
samurai tennis
also hippo
hero
anyway
beno san
you shall regret
abandoned
asshole
but until next time
sayonara
sayonara sensei please don't rape
thank you for saying hello
I feel included
hey hippo could you maybe like
talk to this guy and talk him out of this whole
like this whole rape thing
it's a rape thing
remember when I got raped
canonically by Joe Biden
after my pokemon battle
against him during
a nuzlocke
conquest
yeah that's canon
and you can go back and forth
I didn't realize Joe Biden was in your nuzlocke
I believe Tara Reid
because
after Joe Biden was finished
with Tara Reid he went after me
and yeah the evidence is right there
we have him on recording
you can go and listen to it
it's all there in black and white
I have evidence
post on twitter go to twitter and post at fbi
I have evidence that will lead to the arrest
of a Mr. Joseph
Robin at Biden
and then link my
nuzlocke video please
thanks
I just realized you called me hippo-chan
that's cute
thank you
uh
like chris-chan
no
why would you do that
well you know
you know even
chris-chan
didn't know that chan
was like a girl thing
back when it was
boy chris-chan
he was just like oh yeah
in anime sometimes people add chan
but also it's a pun
because my name is chris-chan
so chris-chan
haha
and his last name is chandler
so it's a triple pun
oh wait that too
yeah I guess it's both
I guess it's both
chris-chan
it's a very universal name
it's just too good to pass it
it's like onion there's so many layers
oh my goodness
it's a terrible samurai
and please
please no sexual assault
next one is from
jeffqueen
3, 2, 1, go
nigga's name is
jeff
can you imagine?
nigga pick one is jeff
is it josh? is it george?
imagine if you ask my name and they say
it's huge
what?
no
it's hard when I don't know
what your name actually is
that joke did not land
I mean I like the noise
shush
I don't come to whatever
backwards country you live in
and critique your naming conventions
no you know what? I will
hey you sound
you sound like South American or some shit
and let me tell you
let me tell you what's wrong
with the hispanic
oh no we're gonna lose all our South American viewers
of which there are actually quite a lot
the problem with Hispanic people
is that their names and addresses
are really fucking long
they're all really fucking long
they all are like four lines
and every line is like six words
it's like oh calle de la puente
de la puerta
de la sol
8 slash 12 slash 49
you know in
Puerto de las muertes
en las
Costa Rica
por favor
in Canada
or whatever
they're all like that
they're all fucking like that
and I don't care for it thank you very much
so fuck you
at least Jeff is only five
letters you piece of shit
thoughts?
prayers?
okay alright
it's really long
really fucking long names around those parts
okay next one
is from vintage
3 2 1
go
alright so I just want to correct
that samurai guy
who keeps calling him
at the end of every single one of his voicemails
he says until next time
Sayonara
Sayonara in Japanese
like
the kind of phrase you say
when you're expecting to not see someone again
or not expecting to see someone
for a really long time
it's like what people say when they're leaving
or like moving away
for many years
when they're not expecting to see someone for several months
they say Sayonara
the most common way to say
goodbye to someone who you're expecting to see again
is Jane
so yeah fuck you
fake samurai guy
damn
maybe the idea is that he says Sayonara
to trick you into thinking that you will never
see him again
but he says until next time
Sayonara
right?
you will never see me coming
until next time
maybe it's like
maybe it's like poetic irony
like
you know when I
betrayed my clan
and burned down the temple
and stole the sacred scrolls
or whatever, stashed them away and ran off
in the night
maybe like right before that
I said Jane
but I should have said Sayonara
and now he's saying it
right?
yeah
cause he's like yeah you get it
and I'm like oh I understand
I completely
I understood the symbolism all along
actually
I understood the message
but I pretended not to
to lull him into a false sense of security
and it didn't work
and I am being threatened
with sexual assault regularly
but you know
when some you lose some
um
but sayonara
thanks for the
kagebushi nojutsu scroll
I learned that
is that shadow clone?
does my Japanese
do my Japanese
education
kagebunshin clone
very good
yeah
well I got that one
and I got the one genjutsu
that like puts someone in like
fucking torture hell for a thousand years
in their minds eye
that was pretty good
that was the only two I know
wasn't that Bleach as well
is it?
I never watched Bleach
you know what I can't remember any of the names so I'm not even going to try
forget it
isn't it like
it was in Yoko Mundo
and it was like one of the bad guys
and he was the science bad guy
and then the on our team
science bad guy
with the weird war paint
and the sarcophagus chin
did a weird thing
he had
gold earrings and chin things
oh is it like
who's that guy in one piece who's got the sarcophagus chin
the hypnotist
oh jango
yeah jango
and yeah
he did some sort of
super science sword
attack thing
that fucked him up so that he
experiences
things
like extremely slow motion
such that it takes so long
for him to like to raise
his arm would feel like a thousand years
as passing and he's just sort of left
there stunned bummer
and then you know big bummer
sucks for him
sucks sucks
pretty dang bad I would say
um
what are we talking about
we're doing the next voicemail
which is lefty larry
hey let's
what's going on buddy 3 2 1 go
hey there pcp
I'm a long time listener
and I just wanted to let you all know
that despite what your comments say a lot
this is by far the best
era of the pcp
I really love the low energy
chill episodes that just have
nice updates on everyone's life
wandering me and during conversations
and then
a voicemail box where everyone gets
played and anything can happen
this is by far the best time
I especially appreciate how
all of the people that have been appearing on the pcp
for the past few months have been the ones
that have reasonable
humane politics
going back and listening to some of the older episodes
are just dog shit
hearing people's
just completely insane
and uh
inhuman takes
on a lot of things
very frustrating so
I enjoy this moment of respite
while it is here
also to give uh
congratulations on exploring your gender identity
I wish you the best
in it
and I encourage your journey
no matter which direction it may take
whatever it does that makes you feel best
I love you
hey guys sounds like we got a real
sounds like we got a real soy boy in here
fucking cock beta
what a piece of shit
the first like 20 seconds
I was waiting for the shooter dropping like there's no way
this can be wholesome
where is this actually going
but no it seemed to be pretty legit
cool thank you
um pretty good
lefty larry
I think I appreciate
I think I'm picking up what you're throwing down
um uh
yeah uh yeah
dab uh dab uh
dab uh you know
jiggle jiggle
shut up shut up
uh comment you know
you know fuck the comments
fuck commenters you know what that's my problem
is I read the comments too much
is it time for commenter rules number three
commenter rules number three just shut up
shut up
over and over again shut shut up
and don't read them
there we did we did it
yeah those those you follow those two
rules and you can't go wrong
um that's pretty good that's pretty good
I think I think we've covered all our
all our bases there um
yeah all right
sick um okay
next up margar's
challenge three two
one go
friday september fourth eleven
fifty five p.m.
this is margar
I'd like to inform ben saint
and ben saint's former sensei
that I have trained in the ways
of murder origami
and I will defend
impossible I stole the scroll for that though
you can't
the fem boys cannot be allowed
to roam amok
unchallenged
so sensei
and mr. t
assuming you are not the same person
or even if you are they are
I challenge you that's canon and ben
I hope this
favor and sign of good
faith between us can start
to mend our broken relationship
that's all for now
um
I don't uh
who's this again
is the guy who's in voice challenge
ten voicemails he's left
or about him being in voice challenge
I remember
I put a stamp on some paperwork
and I like you know put it in a box
and then I just I don't remember
you know that was like that was like weeks ago
you know
somebody went to ben people go to jail all the time
I can't remember
I can't remember every single one of these people
you've been sending goons to beat him up every week
oh more goons
um yeah
I mean sure
I mean I do that with everyone though
I can't I can't I can't make heads or tail
these people okay alright
um listen
uh
I don't know how you found the sacred scroll
for murder origami
uh um
but uh
you know
it's win-win for me either sensei
takes you out or you take him out you know one or the other
so you know
it's just a bunch of bullshit I don't have to put up with anymore
uh you know I'm excited
that's pretty good this word's good for me
alright there we go alright things are looking up
uh
bass okay
next one two things
three two one go
alright so I've got two things to say
um
last week
you were wondering if my voicemail
title
title centrist voicemail
was a joke and uh
no it's not a joke
and secondly
uh I don't think we should free the nipple
because uh women
uh they're gross they're yucky
and I don't want to look at them and um
mm-hmm
uh yeah basically
sympathetic I mean
yeah
because they all look like that girl
they all look like that girl in the
freaking lefty girl gun squad
and I hate their face
and I don't want to see that shit
I think cover cover it up
they should they should invent
the reverse bikini where it shows
the nipple and it shows us everything else
hahahaha
now now we've got some big big
ideas going on over here now
there's a market for that I think
um
yes
enslave enslave the nipple
it's the opposite of free it right so
yeah yeah yeah
yoke it
like like as in like like an ox
like you would an ox
that would plow your field
for instance
um oh no I don't remember
what we were just what was happening
huh was that a voicemail did we
just hear a voicemail
Ben are you are you alright
Ben why is it every episode there's
something dangerously wrong with you
wait wait
we just listen to a voicemail yes
what yeah it was it was two things
and it was the guy who was the centrist and wait what
what did he say he said that the last one
was not a joke yeah it was
serious and the second free the nipple
shouldn't free the nipple because girls are gross
we were just that was
not like something that we stopped talking about
you literally just finished the sentence
yeah I know I know it's not my fault
like it's not my fault it wasn't even attention
this is what happens when you're on keto for like
a year straight you turn into this
no no your brain your body
starts like burning your brain fat yeah
yeah that's the only fat reserves left
it just starts burning your brain cells
no he burns ketones
and they go to your brain
and your brain likes it
like a little too much apparently
your brain is like hey thanks
for the ketones buddy and you're like
anytime anytime pal
okay alright
alright hey what was that voice
don't we just listen to
shut up
next one is slime season
sounds pretty cool
in my opinion
three two one go
hey buster do you like in this war
do you ever wish new los angeles
aka new milwaukee was a real physical city
you could explore
in minecraft
come join the pcp minecraft server
we've ripped a map from crackasy.net
and using advanced slime technology
we ported it into minecraft
as a 600 by 1000 block floor plan
to build an accurate massive
slime city now we're sitting
up streets and buildings starting with
downtown knackillic
so all your rough houses and cup kids
come on down and get sweaty
whoa what the fuck
I don't even I can't even
I can't even imagine what that would look like
I think I don't have to imagine much longer
apparently
I haven't seen it but I have heard that yes
maron pan has
ported the map of endless war
that doesn't even make sense
into like the floor plan
what the city would like the structure
the district shapes
and then I guess
is inviting people to build the city
on the map I think
that's on the pcp minecraft
server which you can get on
with the well the link
that's certainly
that's a fucking that's a fucking
that's a yeah link in the description
that's fucking weird um I guess
I guess there's no reason not to mention now
I was gonna bring this up after the episode
but I think
I think we should do a shackles for heckles
this week
probably before this episode even comes out I don't know
I'm thinking maybe Wednesday
maybe we do it Wednesday this week
Wednesday was for me
the Wednesday before you are listening
to this viewer
um yeah I was gonna bring it up I wanted
to do one this week uh I don't know
maybe Wednesday we'll see but I'll
I'll fucking add everyone or something
I don't know
and I mean
hey that's interesting we can check that out
and I can you know
train up my fucking contrary malamar
a little bit more because that's pretty
that's pretty good shit
I was gonna find like a goal to have
in the pcb minecraft server because when I go on
I'm like I don't know
if I see a cute pokemon I have to get it
and then I have it and I look at it
but I don't really do anything
my goal is to have a good team
and I was like but I have to
play the game
yeah I mean it's hard it's really hard
um
because like you have to actually go get them
which is like I usually just fucking build shit
I'm fucking
on showdown that's how I beat munchie
slime fest I just fucking like hit some buttons
on the pokemon over there I didn't have to do anything
um
dude was that the last slime fest
ever
well I mean I don't know about ever
well for a long time like like Ben St
goes out on top
well yeah
did we talk about that on the pcb how I went
5 and 0 in the last slime fest
undefeated
two streak
funny I don't think we talked about it
we talked we talked about um
we talked about um
Tom did you see those 3d models
on the fucking slime
slime monopoly
uh I saw I did not
I think I might have seen did someone like
3d print them or something I thought I saw like
no it was it was they were not
no they were their models
tabletop simulator um
custom monopoly with
like little pieces
that are 3d models made of
multiple endless war characters
I will show you a screenshot just so
you can get an idea
of what we were talking about smearg made
all of this stuff in I don't know
what program she used but like
probably blender yeah it's
it's like a game it's the game and it's got
a whole deck of cards I saw it's fucking
sick it's all these pieces it's got
the statue in the middle there's all these
there's more than just these but like this is just what's on
like one corner of the board um
I don't know I still I'm still
not over how good it is that's really cool
um yeah yeah it's really great
um but uh yeah
and then and then after that you know we had
slime fest and you know
crushed it
undefeated for five five
wins no losses I am
I am the pokemon master
um maybe
of all the like three
times that I have canonically engaged
in pokemon battles in rfck I
have won them all
um be doopity
and then I beat his dad munchie
and now this is very
a ghost spin
around
oh
wait where did this come
from uh smearg
posted it a while ago before
all the slime monopoly and I saved this this
little spinny I should
I should go look for I should go look for the
other ones because this is really nice this is really
cool um
um
wait how do we get on this topic
I was the the
slime season
oh yeah I was I was just gonna
say yeah if we do uh
shackles for heckles you can scope that out I'm very
curious
like is it
is it just kind of like the map
sort of recreated in blocks on the ground
I don't know
we're gonna we're gonna have to go to the
stream and find out all
I'm just imagining like like to build
to build like a city on top of it
it would have to be huge like to build
like a disc like to build buildings
in each of the individual districts
because there's like what is like 33
districts I think
and like to put stuff
in each one I don't know I'm curious
okay well I'll have to I'll have to scope it out
it's quarantine these people
all have the time so that's true
that's true I don't know but everyone's
going back to school though
everyone's going back to school
just all
about a zoom and fucking
lining away
yeah yeah you're right
fuck it
um
alright awesome
awesome uh last one this is
the last voicemail I told you we'd blast through
them uh prol
jester
three two one go
kitty dinkity
dickity deck
are we still pretending the social
contracts in effect
the police don't serve us
and money trumps reason
but is violence
an answer
or truly high treason
he he
oh oh
he
solve my riddle
all present
I
feel like there's
that felt like it was there was going to be more
so it was uh
it was simple
what was he saying
I like this is the social contract
uh no one void
I think I think what he's saying is uh
a cab
oh
well good
right I read that right right
I I think that was part of what he was saying
yeah I'm going to
do it again this is nice
the social contract
has been broken because money
is more effective than
reason is is violence
the is is violence
good or is violence bad
answer good bricks
through windows please
is violence an answer to
the police
stuff
or is it high treason
or is he asking is police
or could he be is police violence
the answer or is it high
treason in which case it's bad
the problem with the rhymes leaves a lot of wiggle room
for interpretation I guess we could
I guess you could read that either way
um uh
I'm going to read it as
violence from us the people
which is good
because uh it's
we've you know because a cab
uh into
they don't pay attention
unless the bill unless a business burns
down Ha
funny funny
funny funny jokes funny jokes
funny jokes for the jesters today
funny funny jokes and gaffs
and goofs and jabes and
riddles
uh that's
the end of the show
And on that note, burn down your local credit union, and then go to thepatreon.com slash
tpcrastinators.
It's The Procrastinators, tpcrastinators is the Twitter.
Jesus Christ, yeah, it's The Procrastinators for, you know, a million bonus episodes, a
whole fucking host of fucking backlog bonus episodes.
Too many to count.
Drowning, just drowning.
Literally too many.
I cannot tell you how many there are, because it surpasses human comprehension.
Are we going to mention that we missed one?
We did miss one this week, or this month.
Or we haven't done one yet, and we might just not do one this month.
There's still time.
There is still technically time.
Yeah, we could still get one out this month, and then do...
It could be fashionably late with the bonus episode.
We could, yeah, yeah, you know, we should.
We should still do one, even though we're a few days into them.
You're right.
We should.
Okay, well, we don't have one yet, but we will hopefully get around to it.
I'm just saying, the more people who are waiting for the bonus episode, the more pressure and
incentive it'll put on us to actually make one this month.
So if you want a bonus episode, get your friends to sign up for $5 a month, and then we'll
feel more obligated to do it.
So, you know, everybody wins.
We will only do the bonus episode if 10 people become patrons.
If we get 10,000 likes.
Yeah, hmm, yeah, hmm, die.
Leave a speakpipe at speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail.
If you want to get in on the Anarchy, anything goes.
There's no quality control.
There's no floor.
There's no skill floor at all on this shit anymore.
It's all been removed.
The guardrails are gone.
We took the bumpers out of the gutters on our on our week weekend bowling trip.
I feel like balls are like rolling the the the bumpers have gone up because now like
even if you're crap, you're still get in where oh yeah, you're down.
You'd have to be good.
We laid down a big old we put the training wheels back on, you know, it's all it's all
bumper in fact like like imagine the bowling alley and instead of just bumpers in the gutters,
the bumpers extend like all the way into the middle, right, just a straight path, a narrow
path on the middle of the strike.
Just like pitch the bowling ball with inhuman strength that are still ricochet off the walls
where it's supposed to go.
Have I ever mentioned that I knew a guy one time who bold like Fred Flintstone?
Like he no, he did.
He had he he would use the lightest ball and he it was like a skinny this was like a skinny
tall guy and he would with glasses and stuff he was like a nerd and he would like hold
the ball and he would like slowly kind of like creep towards the line and then instead
of like a swing, he would just kind of like jerk his arm out from his chest where he was
holding the ball to and kind of twist it in the air and it would like thunk.
It would go out and then arc and thunk on the on the floor and then it would like slowly
roll and he he pulled like a fucking he pulled like a 270 he pulled like literally the best.
I haven't seen that much bowling but he pulled like one of the best games I've ever seen.
This guy was like really good and he had the most bizarre fucking technique that I've ever
seen.
Okay, this had to get my bowling anecdote in there before the end of the episode.
Every time for it.
Yep.
Patreon, Twitter, Speakpipe, Minecraft River, well yeah, you do all this PCP related stuff
and then go to twitch.tv slash Gibbentech to watch me draw a manga because that's cool.
That's what I do.
Wait, you're not done with that?
I'm doing another issue.
That's why I said he was a golden god.
Oh god.
Yeah.
Wait, is this, is this, okay, is this like you finished the part for the Tezuka and
you got to finish the rest, right?
And now he's doing more.
I'm finishing the rest.
Right, okay.
I'm doing it all.
Okay, okay, okay, I see.
Yeah, yeah, do that.
No, I can't, I can't, I can't argue with that.
You should probably go do that.
Too powerful.
All right.
Fuck yeah, we did it everyone.
Another episode.
Oh, oh, oh, and the Big Booby Mummy Milkers podcast.
There's not a podcast, it's not a podcast.
It's not a podcast.
Maybe there's a podcast.
Don't join, don't join the server.
You know what you should do?
Squeeze, jiggle, squirt.
If you're not sure if you're someone who's been on the sidelines and hearing all this
stuff about endless war and you're like, ah, sounds kind of gay.
You should go to the Big Booby Mummy Milkers server and be like, hey, this isn't gay at
all.
And, and then it can be like your gateway drug to endless war.
You can be like, now they're just going to steal all your thunder because they're going
to do the, the, the, the maybe slime.
A hundred percent, a hundred percent, always effective method.
Just take something, put tits on it, triple your income instantly.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it cannot be.
It cannot be.
We'll see.
We'll see how it pans out.
Impossible.
Um, by the way, this is, um, actually today, this Friday, yeah, Friday, I will be judging
on, you know, maybe late later tonight after that whole fucking manga thing, uh, twitch.tv
slash rattyfuckers cop killers.
I think unless, unless it gets postponed for some reason, I will be judging the war on
quickville contest, uh, the latest art contest from rattyfuckers cop killers, where it's
about draw a fucking waging war on quickville in retaliation for the slime or for the bicarbonate
soda rain.
Uh, so that should be funny, assuming, assuming there's good entries, uh, uh, I don't know,
remains to be seen.
All the good ones usually come in at the last minute, so I guess we'll see.
Uh, yes, good, good, all this fucking, all these commands.
All right.
Are we done?
Is it the end?
Are we ended?
Okay.
Bye.
End of the episode.
It's over.
Bye.