The Pro Crastinators Podcast
We're on the PCP. It's an internet show. It's a podcast. You know it is. It's me, Munchy.
We have Digi here. We have Danger Boy. It's the best guy's ever new character. It's Danger Boy.
Hello, everyone. I'm currently falling at light speed from the top of a skyscraper headed towards the ground.
That's where I'll be reporting in for this entire podcast, so I'll send you updates periodically.
He's going so fast that rubber bands, the point where he can do an entire podcast, will take something to himself.
Yeah, that's right. Time has slowed down because I'm approaching the speed of light or something.
That's so dangerous. I love the editing.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Hippo, it's you.
My drug of choice is tea.
Rayman. When's Rayman 2? Come on, let's be serious.
That's my drug.
Let's get serious. We were all choking around, but come on.
I need to get pretty high for that.
We have been.
Fuck. I'm not dangerous at all.
Oh, my God. It's Danger Boy Sidekick Mild Lad.
Oh, no. I don't want to see what you're going to do, Master.
I can't look.
He's a slave.
I'm just a boy. I can't take the weapons.
Today, on the podcast, there was politically correct, morally aligned, conventionally socially acceptable podcasts on the internet.
We're talking about fucking weed.
Drugs, this is not just the weed podcast, except it literally is just going to be the weed podcast.
We all know it's coming. We all know that's just what is going to happen.
I decided that on the off chance that this was supposed to be an intervention,
because I was had a sneaking suspicion you were just going to pull an intervention on me,
so I thought the funniest way that could happen is if I was showed up as high as humanly possible.
And that bomb rip I took at the start of the show just now was so heavy that I thought I was hallucinating
what Nate was saying in his intro, because I thought it was too funny to be real.
What an endorsement.
The Urban Dictionary for drugs is so fucking long, and it's like a realized Wikipedia article.
I don't have time for this shit.
The beginning part is pretty good. Just that first little paragraph there.
Drugs are chemicals that alter, block, or mimic chemical reactions in the brain.
This causes an alteration of the body's normal processes,
causing physical, faster heartbeat, deeper respiratory diseases,
and so on, hedgehog bubbles, etc.
The fact that the fucking Urban Dictionary article is like this is funny.
It's like a parody of itself, because it's making fun of how, in a way,
how people who are into drugs get extremely serious when it comes to the topic of defending drugs.
There's no means. It's just like, oh no, we need to give you all the science,
because like...
It's like enough joking around, enough joking around.
Yeah, put on the suits, and we like, you know, quaff our hair back.
We have a lot of fun here on Urban Dictionary, but this is important.
Far better of description is the definition for weed.
God's gift to the world brings peace released wisely past the blunt dude,
but they take sums up all of our opinions quite nicely.
Just for the record, I think it's, we've done this before,
but let's just read off, of course, our entire podcast is drug-themed to begin with,
so we are the PCP, and PCP, aka Angel Dust, is, again, we've read this before,
it is the scariest of all drugs, according to Urban Dictionary,
was used as a horse tranquilizer, makes the user hallucinate,
become extremely violent, and not feel anything.
People have been known to do horrible things to themselves,
while under the influence of PCP, do not use the PCP, it will ruin your life.
Yeah, it definitely is, like, a drug that is highly destructive,
and I am a huge fan of PCP as a joke because of the whitest kids-you-know skit,
a gallon of PCP, which is one of my favorite skits of all time,
so when we had the opportunity to be called the PCP, I jumped on it for those reasons.
When we're gonna get PCP brand soda, and exclusively sell them non-two liters,
or like bottles, but in gallons.
Oh, that would be fucking awesome, that's genius!
We gotta make a PCP drink!
Oh, shit! I feel like this is really doable!
It's just a gallon of munchies pee.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, again, doable.
That would make sense, yeah, it's still doable.
We just have munchies, buy gallon bottles of water,
build up with piss and mail to the people, that's totally normal.
Dude, you've seen how much piss I can piss,
like all the times I piss on the show, I do it in like two McDonald's large cups.
Yeah, I've seen the piss cups, they're fucking...
Munchie, we could actually, like, I feel like there's some people who would buy this,
you have to be 18 before we can sell your piss, probably,
but I feel like...
Probably.
And I don't know what the tax is on me sending that much liquid, but, you know...
Once I reach 18, there's gonna be so many content, like, opportunities,
there's gonna be so many new things, like once I'm 18...
Oh, no, dick is gonna be everywhere, like...
I know!
You know, you guys saw a lot of Eric Andre's dick,
wait till you see fucking Munchies, like, I'm 18 now.
That's come up later this fucking year,
get fucking ready for that shit.
And with all these restrictions and limitations happening on YouTube in general,
and it seems like the weight of the world is shifting towards Pornhub
as, like, the main uploading site for, like, most of the world,
so I just think that in the years to come,
we're gonna be seeing a lot of Munchie content on Pornhub,
just, you know, regardless of the context within.
Yeah.
It's an exciting future.
I really hope that's the world we're heading for,
is where, like, Pornh is just into...
I mean, I always thought it's a little weird,
and when you think about it, that YouTube has banned Pornh,
because if Pornh and other videos were on the same website,
like, it would be more convenient for everybody,
the only problem is that people don't want to present themselves as having...
You know, we wanna keep those identities separated for social reasons,
but if we didn't have that social barrier,
if, like, sex and porn were, like, just acceptable things to talk about,
like, there would be no reason not to integrate those.
Well, what's that one...
It's, like, that video on YouTube that's, like,
see a penis inside of a vagina,
the one where it's just, like, a straight-up, like,
documentary of what it looks like to come inside a vagina.
That's pretty cool.
I'm gonna go watch that right now.
I'm pulling it off.
Show notes, everybody. Show notes.
The future of PCB is all of us in a sauna with no towels on.
We're just pure, fucking, unadulteratedly naked,
and we're doing the podcast from within a sauna.
Our bodies are glistening. That's coming up in, like, two years.
All right.
It's fucking set to porn music, and it looks...
I mean, this is great.
All right, all right, yeah, it's actually pretty good.
We already did that.
Let's start off with the podcast with a very important thing.
Who here is straight edge?
I'm straight edge.
Define straight.
Yeah, please define.
I kind of wish I was.
Well, hang on. Let me pull up fucking straight edge on UrbanDictionary.com.
No, let me do this. I know the history of it,
because straight edge comes from the hardcore punk scene in music,
where certain punk bands, because the members of the band were so young,
they had the X's on their hand that meant they couldn't drink,
and some of them took it as, like, an identity thing.
It's like, well, we don't, like, we are an anti-drug band anyways,
so people started wearing those X's on their hands
and calling themselves straight edge in, like, straight edge punk
was like a subcategory, basically.
Dude, that's like the punk version of those, like, purity rings
that, like, Mormon kids wear and shit.
All right, cool, cool.
But that's what to be straight edge.
Traditionally, to say, like, oh, you are straight edge,
in, like, either, like, rap or punk is usually...
So would you say it's like a mental thing
rather than a literal, like, I have not imbibed any of these things?
Yeah, it's more like choosing, yeah, it's more of an identity thing.
Because I have technically done one weed,
and I have done a lot of drink of alcohols.
I don't know whether that's covered in this book.
That's very much not straight edge.
Catch me in the garden out back doing all the weed,
pulling them, planting them, just going nuts on those weeds.
I did so much fucking weed, my lawn was barren for two years afterwards.
All that grass was gone and inside of my stomach and lungs.
Well, yeah, all right, all right, but the good question.
So who is straight edge here?
I would pretty much define myself as basically straight edge,
for the most part.
But you drink alcohol.
Well, but, like, so rarely.
Like, at Radcon 3, I don't think I drank a single drop of alcohol
the entire time, and it's because I just don't care.
I mean, we didn't have that much to me.
That's true.
To me, getting drunk or whatever is just like a distraction.
All I am, what gets me high in this life, it's 100% true,
is achieving my goals and getting work done.
That's all I care about or want to do.
You don't need to get high to have fun.
All you need to do is achieve your goals.
But I will tell you though, I will tell you though,
I wouldn't say I'm 100% straight edge, you know, like clinically,
because I do two great drugs.
One is caffeine.
I've started drinking coffee, basically every day.
Not much.
Well, that's the thing.
I'm currently consuming the two drugs of choice in my life right now.
One is caffeine, which isn't really that big a deal.
The other is probably the most insidious drug on the face of the earth.
It is a nightmare.
It is ruining society.
Esther Jackson.
No, it is sugar.
I am currently consuming a gigantic pudding cup I bought from Whole Foods,
specifically for this podcast.
Listen to me.
Alright, Nate, you get to be straight edge.
You're allowed to be straight edge because of this faggot ass thing
you're saying at the moment.
Hippo, I know you drink and do it with me.
I do drink on occasion when it's like a party
and it's like, well, I need something in my hand, so I may as well.
So I don't have a cock, so I'll take a beer.
That'll work instead.
I mean, that would be kind of cumbersome
to hold some guy's dick in that way.
You'd have to coordinate your movements really well.
Would they be like...
Well, you arrange a big circle where it rotates around
and everyone gets visited like the part of the table
with the snacks that they want, but okay, go ahead.
Do you want me to do a Patreon if you're a gay male?
Just do it.
Patreon Skyrockets.
As literally everyone in the audience thinks, wow, that was just for me.
I think what I would define as straight edge is like,
if there's no reason, but you still think,
yeah, I'll have a drink, then you're not straight edge.
Or I'll have a smoke.
Yeah, that's a good way of putting it.
Yeah, yeah.
If there's no societal pressure on you,
if there's no advantage other than I'm bored
and I just feel like it, then yeah.
So I guess I'm not straight edge,
because I have drunk on streams and just generally.
Yeah, I guess so.
So there's words of you drinking that I can give to the police.
Yes, I am under 12 years old.
There's degrees of straight edge and I guess being not straight edge.
No, there's fucking not.
That's the whole point.
Being straight edge is like an absolute identity commitment.
But I mean, but I do once in a while like you.
Then you're not fucking straight edge.
You fall short.
I mean, for what it's worth.
No, you're like that guy in Scott Pilgrim who ate the chicken parmesan
and there's not vegan anymore.
Can we address the fact that Nate is staunchly anti-identitarian
in the first place and therefore should not even begin to describe himself
as straight edge when it's like an exclusively,
the term exists for identitarian purposes.
It's like, I mean, yeah, I guess so.
For practical purposes.
So we can identify how much people care about drugs in the course of this podcast.
I mean, I would describe the origin of it as very similar
to the origin of the term social justice warrior
when like they actually called themselves that
and then eventually like people started in the same way that people
not call people.
Oh, you're like straight edge because they're trying to say basically
we're not going to invite you to a party because you think you're boring.
I feel like there is a practical usage of the word here
that just means someone who doesn't consume like drugs or alcohol on a regular basis.
I mean, is there another word that I should use instead for that?
Like clean?
Just say I don't drink because I fucking care about my body.
That's like at least two more words.
Here's how it is.
If you don't do it, if you don't do it on the regular,
if you just do it very, very occasionally, then you're straight edge.
I would say the health nut.
Because that's the core reason he's not drinking.
If you do it like mildly to all the time, you are bent.
You know, it's funny that you say I'm a health nut.
In my mind, to all the actual health nuts out there,
I'm an embarrassment and a disgrace that I'm even eating sugar right now.
You own cans of beans at all.
That is to be a health nut.
Every time we go grocery shopping, we come home and immediately eat a Lunchables.
That is the first thing that happens.
Okay, so you see, men of your lifestyle live in the depths of depravity.
You can't even fathom how high the ceiling is, how high the ceiling can go.
My parents are vegans, so I absolutely know where the ceiling can go.
But you can still eat sugar though, and sugar is death.
I want to ask you though, Nate, if you had given up on your body,
if you decided you were like, oh, I can't be passionate about this anymore
for whatever reason, something else is more important,
do you think you would take up casual drinking?
Well, no, because the reason I don't drink is specifically because
it just is like a night waster, in my opinion.
What if you were in a situation where you had to waste the nights though?
There was no choice.
Yeah, if the night is just...
I'm at a Christmas party, and I'm there just to hang out,
and I can't even work if I want to.
At that point, there's no reason not to drink, so I would probably consider it.
What if things were different, and the reason why you don't like something
didn't exist, would you do it then?
No, I mean, that's the real...
When I go to visit my parents around Christmas time,
I can't even do work if I want to,
so there's no reason to not drink, so I'm much more likely to do so.
The reason I'm saying this, Munchie, is that I want to characterize him
as it's more about his health and his productivity,
whereas I feel like people who are sincerely straight-edge
would not have drank even if they had to waste the night
because they are against the existence of these drugs.
That used to be me, I'm not like that anymore.
When I was a kid, I was legitimately scared of alcohol,
but we'll talk about that later.
I thought of the thing, we've got straight-edge, which is that,
which is you would not take it even if...
Yeah, and then you've got bent, which is the middle,
and then you've got twisted, which is like the heart...
Twisted!
You're coming to work!
I mean, you can actually measure when you reach each of these phases.
If you're someone who just smokes a little weed every now and then, you're bent.
If you're someone who just drinks every now and then, you're bent.
If you're someone who does both, but not together,
you're like, you know, you're like getting there.
You're like, you're turnt, you're turnt, you're turnt at that point.
But if you do them both at once, you are twisted.
You're twisted, man!
That sounds good to me.
Are you straight-edge?
No, I am worthless.
Everyone, please, in the comments, let me know, are you straight-edge,
bent, turnt, or twisted?
Hashtag bent, turnt, etc.
Also post that on Twitter with those hashtags and make those memes.
Somebody make a graph of this and make that a meme.
I was just about to say, check the show.
And make sure you tag us in it, god damn it.
Tag it with PCP, put our logo on there.
We'll give you the PNG.
There will be a straw pool in the show notes right now.
Click which one you are.
You're straight-edge, you're turnt, you're twisted, or you're bent.
There's a straw pool.
Go vote there.
I'm going to guess right now, majority of the audience is straight-edge.
I'm going to go over 50%.
That's my guess.
I'm going to say 40%.
I think we have a lot of, straight-edge, we have a lot of ponsons.
I think we have a lot of ponsons who don't comment as much.
Because they're too busy being high.
That's possible.
Because they're too fucking high, dude.
I think it's going to be like 30% straight-edge, then like 30% bent.
And then like a little bit of them are twisted, and more of them are twisted.
I think that the sheer scope of the straight-edge selection of our fandom
will make Ben's gigantic body look minuscule by comparison.
That's what I think.
I don't know why I said that.
I am a massive human.
I am a Titan.
So, Ben, do you just like drink regularly?
Not even that.
Well, you know, I go through phases with stuff.
I will go like a long time without like drinking or smoking.
And then at some point maybe I'll pick one up.
I forgot you smoked.
I'll do it for a while.
Yeah, yeah, tobacco.
I don't think we don't like it.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where does vape fall?
Yeah, where does vape fall on the straight-edge, too?
Okay, yeah, people argue about that.
I think that the evidence is pretty good that vape is, if not like healthy.
At least not anything you really need to worry about health-wise.
People fucking try to debate me about that.
Cures cancer.
Yeah, exactly.
So, you know, I guess that, I guess, I don't know.
I don't know where that falls.
I mean, we don't do that much bad either.
So, I'll go for long periods without doing it.
I'll go for long periods without doing anything like that.
And like, I don't like doing it.
It doesn't feel good.
And like, I feel worse about myself when I do it.
Because it is.
It's just a big waste of time.
It's a big waste of money.
Waste of money.
Yeah, yeah.
I only do it when I'm sad and when I feel like life isn't worth living anyway.
Well, we'll see that.
Well, that's no good.
That's no good.
That's your body telling you to stop.
You need to listen to what your body is saying to you.
My body is saying, destroy thyself.
If somebody's doing drugs because they just want to have a great time, that's one thing.
If someone does drugs as a retreat from the real world, I mean, that, to me, seems like
that's the biggest thing to be avoided.
Well, drugs have never been that enjoyable.
I've done some drugs, like drug drugs, that have made me trip balls.
And I haven't really liked it or wanted to do much of it.
Picture Ben, picture Ben downing a Tylenol, stepping into a room full of little marbles,
and just be like, I'm tripping balls!
Whoa!
It falls into a ball pit hilariously.
Yeah, that was Ben.
I drank two rock stars in a row, and I had visions.
I shucked two Advils onto the hibachi grill, and I soaked those in as my whole.
I gotta say about that thing about whether or not weed is like healthy.
So I have smoked literally every day this year.
Like, there's not been a day that I have not been high for most of the day.
And I gotta tell you, it is definitely not good for your lungs or throat to smoke.
There you go.
Well, there is no shit, dude.
I would even say it's really bad for your lungs and throat to smoke.
I don't want to make this into a dark place, but Digi's voice has undergone something of a transformation in the last while,
which is another reason you should stop.
First of all, I think my voice sounds great.
I mean, I sound like shit right now because I literally took a world-ending bong rip at the start of the show.
But that's what I mean.
It's not as though it permanently damages your throat.
I mean, it can eventually erode your throat away.
If I were to smoke the way I am now for the next 20 years,
I will sound like fucking Johnny Cash on his deathbed or fucking...
Sure.
What's his name?
The...
Gotta be a chocolate Jesus.
You know what I'm talking about?
Uh, no.
Fuck it.
George Harrison.
Oh, no, Tom Waits.
That's the guy.
I'll sound like Tom Waits if I fucking do this for that long.
However, and I don't intend to, this is just because I'm like,
I just discovered it and it's fun and I can get away with it for like three or four years, you know?
Okay.
Until I have...
Three or four years, okay.
Well, once I have kids, I'm not gonna smoke weed all the fucking time.
But...
So...
It's...
Sorry.
My fucking mind just would completely blank.
Yeah, we're just talking about throat.
If it's hurt, if there are horrible health effects.
Yes, it fucking...
It definitely hurts like to...
When you take a gigantic rip, you're going to like...
I have coughed up, like, I've like vomited from my lungs.
Like, I've vomited flat.
Oh, boy.
And that shit is disgusting and it hurts.
Yeah.
And some...
And if you go out in the cold, while you have like, smoking your lungs,
it fucking hardens in your lungs and it feels like you're dying.
So don't do that.
When I was in Poland, I would smoke on my balcony.
And it was winter time.
I was there in Poland in the winter.
And as you can imagine, it was bitterly cold.
And from smoking on my porch in the bitter cold,
I developed a cough that lasted for months.
Like, even into the spring and summer, I was still coughing
from how much I had fucked up my insides doing that.
I think it was mostly the cold, actually.
But the smoking, surely, didn't help.
And that's my story.
Drugs are great.
Drugs are really nice because they give you a fleeting satisfaction.
That's really nice.
And it gives you cough for literal months afterwards.
That's a real...
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Guys, I don't know if this...
You know, it's a trade-off, but it's worth it.
I'm sorry.
I was still on the search for C. Penis inside of vagina on YouTube.
And I found a video called...
I found it immediately.
Well, I actually didn't find it, but I found another one
called Two Brother Inside She-Elephant Vagina.
And there's a man inside She-Elephant Vagina.
I didn't see that T-Bap episode.
I didn't see...
Yeah, that was the...
You know what?
I'll just link it to you.
I don't know, like, will we get in trouble if we put this in the show notes?
Because it's on YouTube.
It is a man inside an elephant vagina getting fucked
and the elephant comes all over him inside the elephant vagina.
Wait, the guy is getting fucked?
This is from, like, a movie.
Yeah.
Wait, the guy is...
I don't understand.
Is he...
You know what?
This is fucking madness.
How does he breathe?
I'm not clicking on it.
Well, it's a pretty big hole.
No, no, no.
The guy is that...
It's...
I'm not clicking on it.
There's a man inside of an elephant's vagina
and the elephant is getting fucked by another elephant.
So there's a gigantic dick, like, passing over his head
and coming all over him.
That's right.
How does he not...
Just watch the clip.
It's right there.
I don't want to watch the fucking clip.
Look, there's a lot of room.
There's a lot of room in there.
It's not, like, real.
It's like a goofy comedy movie, like, retarded, fucking...
It looks fake as shit.
Wait, is it Freddy Got Fingered?
It looks like...
It's similar to Freddy Got Fingered.
I don't know.
I haven't seen that movie, so maybe...
Oh, I just saw the computer.
Yeah, it's pretty...
Okay, you know what?
This has nothing to do with drugs.
Oh, hey, how about porn?
Porn's a drug on your brain, right?
It kind of is.
Probably, yeah.
Okay, here.
Let's change the order here.
Let's get back on fucking track.
I want to say my opening statement.
Weed use...
And again, this is going to be, like, the weed cast.
Weed use is not inherently a problem.
It's weed overuse is the problem.
I don't care if you're...
I don't know if you're...
What's the term?
Bent.
I don't care if you're bent.
I just want to smoke a bowl sometimes.
I don't want to be around you while you're high, but, like, you know, whatever.
I don't care.
But when you are twisted, when you reach digilevels, that's the point when shit starts to go south
and I start not wanting to be around you or associate you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
This is the intervention.
I mean, I know what you mean.
I know what you mean.
I had a friend, Nick, when I was young, who...
We would, like, do weed occasionally, and he would just be around and watch everybody,
like, get high, and he just enjoyed observing and being, like, the one non-high guy.
So there's an element of that that's kind of fun.
It's, like, when Tails gets trolled, when Tails and Cheeto Man are, you know, they're
trying to get high and Doug Funny wants to hang out and smoke weed with them, and everyone's
like, oh, we don't want to hang out with Doug, but Cheeto Man's like, nah, Doug's cool, Doug's
cool, but then Doug gets too high and gets really weird about the time that Skeeter gave
him a handjob, and then he bites Spyro's dog, and then he throws up from weed, and Tails
makes fun of him for being a lightweight.
I don't know what the relevance of this story.
I just wanted to talk about that for a while.
What's that flaky lecture coming out?
Probably in, like, a week.
Okay, cool.
Maybe even by the time this is out.
Tails gets trolled like that.
You know, Munchy Electro out now, everybody.
Munchy Electro's out on his channel, so go watch that shit.
Hey, you have to send that to Dick, did you?
Oh, I did already.
Oh, there you go.
There you go.
Okay, what were we talking about, Munchy?
We're talking about how I don't think weed uses a problem, but I think that weed overuses
a problem.
It's a matter of scales.
A different amount comes a different in kind.
Well, you know, here's the real shit here is, like, what does someone want to do with
their time?
Like, I don't think it's fair to criticize people, even if someone who gets blasted out
of their mind every single day and just doesn't do anything productive.
I mean, this is just how I feel about life in general.
I'm totally, like, egalitarian here, or libertarian here.
As long as you're handling your shit, what business is it of mine?
Like, what you do with your free time?
It's got nothing to do with me.
I would imagine that would not be your position, because I thought you want people to be productive
and just do their work.
I do want people to be productive.
There's two things happening here.
On the one hand, people can do whatever they want with their life, and I would like them
to be productive, but on the other hand, if you come to me, having not been productive
and say, listen, I didn't get my life together, please help me, I will look down and I will
say no.
I will say die.
I will say no.
I mean, I gotta tell you that, like, weed has made me way more productive than before,
so, like...
Well, that's what I'm saying, you know?
If a person can do weed and be more productive, fantastic.
If they do weed and they're not productive, I mean, that's their business to work out.
The great thing about being high all day is that you pretty much can't really go anywhere
or do anything, so all you really can do is work.
It's like, I'm just here at my desk with what's in front of me.
I know I want to do at least eight hours of work today, so let's just get extremely blasted
and zoned in, put on some good music, and fucking just work all day, you know?
So, that's been just like every single day for as long as I can remember at this point.
Great.
Which is like three minutes, basically.
Well, so, we can't judge what your life is like.
Because I have three cells left.
Sure, but you're basically a public artist, so, like, you know, that works for you.
You can do those sorts of things, and we obviously don't have insight into, like, your day-to-day
life, but we can see what's been produced, and so that's the one window that we have
to, like, critique, such as it is, you know, this change in lifestyle.
There are two pillars that hold up my entire being, and this goes back to the very episode.
There are two, like, tenets of my entire personality that are completely contradictory to one another,
and I have to battle them on a daily basis.
The first pillar is you can do whatever you want, and the second pillar is don't be retarded.
And those are clashing constantly.
I agree, sure. People can do what they want in their free time, you know, sure.
It's if it's recreational, you know, whatever.
But I don't want to be around people who are retarded, and I think it negatively impacts them
on a social, economical, and just, like, physical well-being.
I think it affects them on multiple levels.
So, like, sure, I'm not gonna fucking call the police, but I think that you probably should
probably think twice, and this is my opinion, so I'm gonna fucking say it.
You know, I hear you on that, Munchy. It reminds me a little bit of something, though.
I think you're being a little bit, I mean, it's totally understandable,
and, like, you're probably right about most people doing these sorts of things.
But then, I think to myself, you know, not everybody fits the exact mold,
and really, like, what they should do is necessarily in line with, like,
what the most average person in society should do,
aka, like, you know, not go crazy doing drugs.
Well, like, I'm thinking of, for example, I was on Twitter yesterday,
and I tweeted out, like, a video from Whiplash,
where the kid, the main kid, like, breaks up with his girlfriend,
because he's like, listen, all I care about in life is drumming.
That's all I want to do. Therefore, I don't have time for a relationship,
so I'm ending it here. And, like, the girl, I mean, and just everyone's response,
I tweeted out about how inspirational I found that,
and, you know, I didn't really articulate, because it's Twitter,
exactly in what ways I like that.
I just admire his, like, commitment to his goals.
But then, like, everyone starts being like, um, actually, he, like, is really shit,
and he shouldn't have done that, because it's, like, bad, and you need to live a balanced life,
and, like, sure, if you, if you, like, are a normal fag, then, yeah,
you'll probably be happiest in life doing that sort of thing.
This is why I fucking hated The Princess and the Frog,
because in the end, the message was, like, if you don't have love,
you can't just be a strong, powerful woman.
I straight up, that is my favorite Disney movie, because I just ignore the ending,
and I just don't, I do not learn, I just watch the beginning,
and I'm like, this is the perfect woman, I love Tiana so much, et cetera, et cetera.
Uh, so, like, people, people are really eager.
My point is that people are really eager to, like, want to say that, you know,
people should live their life, that's exactly it.
But there are lots of individuals, like, in Digi's lifestyle,
it seems to me that doing lots of weeds is not going to inherently be necessarily a problem
to a degree, to a degree.
Because there are things like, well, yeah, go on, Munchy.
Two things to that. First of all, this is anything different than the Furious episode.
This is, like, a blanket statement to appeal to the general audience here.
There will be outliers, there are people who do not, you know,
even though they are twisted, they live perfectly, like, serviceable lives,
there are tons of musicians and things who smoke weed, and, you know,
the fucking Beatles smoke the Bola Day, and, you know, they're the Beatles, so it's fine.
I was about to go into a point about that, because, like, as much as I absolutely...
Whoa, fucking hold on, bitch, I was in the middle of a two-point thing.
Okay, okay, Gib will go after, just hang on, put a pin in that.
Yeah, yeah, so there's, like, you know, you can...
They couldn't smoke on a Bola Day.
It's a matter of scale, it's a matter of overuse,
and it's a matter of, like, not just, you know, doing it because you want to,
it's a matter of overuse and me being around you.
So, like...
Well, okay, are you being selfish there, though?
You're saying what you want them to do for your benefit.
What has this entire podcast lead up to this point B?
It's us shouting our opinion at the audience, and pretending that it's not correct,
and what should have happened.
That's what this entire podcast has been for, like, what, like, 100 episodes now?
Why now is this a problem? Why now is me saying what I think the world should be?
Now, like, suddenly, like, twisted and, you know, devilish.
Because your reasoning is that you want to impose your standards on other people,
and, you know...
Nate, that's what you do every day, and that's not a problem.
That's just how you believe.
Well, I don't know. I feel like I'm pretty careful to make sure that people understand.
Nate, you are right now imposing the belief of, like...
That people should do what they want, that's right.
Yeah, exactly. As opposed to, like, the, you know,
if Munchie holds totalitarian beliefs that we all need to be, like, under God,
and that, like, he was imposing the belief that Munchie should win.
Stop trying to fucking now.
I'm not saying I want to ban every, every, like, ounce of weed on the place.
No, no, no. I was just, I wasn't saying you actually thought that I was being rhetorical.
Of course.
Well, okay, Gib was chiming in with something.
What about the beans? Tell us.
Well, it was, it was...
The thing that I have is that, as much as I absolutely hate to admit it,
weed and drugs and mind-altering substances,
despite how much I hate this idea,
do actually result in artists being really creative and cool.
They have and will and do result in really cool stuff.
But the problem I find with, like, things
is that people aren't doing the hard stuff anymore.
I think people should be stopping weed because it's baby shit.
It's too, it's too weak. It's got, it's got two, three of the letters in week are in the year.
Three of them?
Wait, only two.
No, three.
That's most of them.
Wait, like, like, weak as in, like, seven days?
I mean, that's accurate.
Yes.
And, and fucking, they should be doing,
they should be doing the hard stuff.
They should be doing LSD.
They should be doing acid.
PCP.
Fucking PCP, Red Bull, like, all that really dangerous about the world to you.
I find...
So that we can make, like, new, new Beatles stuff, new Pink Floyds.
Well, again, again.
Like, I want people to be incredible.
But the thing is, weed is, like, quantity over quality.
People smoke all the time and it's the amount of time that they're out of commission.
They're not really more creative.
They're just sort of, like, ugh.
But they're not, like, they're not, like, putting themselves at risk.
They're like, if they put themselves at risk,
they would die more and they would be doing less all the parts of the day.
I'll tell you, because as you experienced firsthand,
because you tried to smoke with me and you kind of didn't have that much
and it didn't end up getting you high at all, right?
Yeah.
And it very much is just like drinking.
It's like, how much you put in is how much you get out.
You can have a couple beers and get a light buzz and just, you know, carry about your day.
You can have three or four beers and be like,
hey, I'm having a party or you can get obliterated
and, like, you're gonna be the life of the party,
but you might not remember it tomorrow, so it's a risk, you know?
And with weed, if you get that high,
like, you get so high that you're gonna, like, see shit
and, like, really fucking deeply experience the media you watch and all that shit,
like, you have to be willing to risk the fact that you're gonna be on a bad fucking, like,
you're gonna think about a lot of shit you didn't want to think about
about your past and all the worst things that have happened in your life
and, like, how you're a piece of shit
and you can't escape that mind prison and you'll be there for hours.
Like, if you cross that threshold into being what I call mega-big-high,
if you are mega-big-high, you're going to just cross over into this other world
of which there's no escape and that's why most people I think, like me,
who the first time I smoked, I got that high and it was, like, fucking nightmare,
people who tend to end up that high when they smoke are just like,
I don't want to do it regularly, because...
That's how I felt when I did it.
Right, exactly.
I feel like people, like, I like munchy.
I don't like people who smoke.
I don't like the smell.
The smell is like, I mean, I have a story about why I hate the smell,
which I can get into later, but, like, the...
I don't like hanging around people who are, like, intoxicated or in some way
slightly beyond normal.
Well, I don't like that person.
So I would prefer people to just not drink and smoke, like, every day,
but to do it, like, once a month, but get so drunk or so high
that they do something incredible.
I would prefer it to be, like, an explosive thing,
rather than just, like, a small burn throughout the entire of their life.
Like, if you're, like, out dealing with people who are, like, drunk or high
and, like, you don't know them, like, I personally am pretty wary of, like, just...
You know, because they're unpredictable and it's like, well, I don't know.
I do not want to interact with any, like, higher drunk strangers.
I don't understand, like, the idea of going to a place where, like,
you know everyone's drunk and you don't know who any of them are,
but, like, everyone there is volatile and, like...
Yeah.
Like, if I'm going to be...
It's like the club.
If I'm going to be super drunk or high, I'd prefer to be those around people I know
and trust because I'm in a more vulnerable state, you know?
Yeah, totally.
But Gib, Gib, let me just...
I just want to clarify with Gib on one thing, because I just want to...
I liked his point and I want to expand on it because I think I agree with it.
It's like, so, Gib, you were saying before about, like, you think people are just, like,
they're doing it too much and they're, I don't know, maybe you mean, like, using it as a crutch.
It's quite a quality of a quality.
Like, the amount of hours you spend doing that thing when you could be, like,
you know, chugging a big old whiskey bottle and going insane just one time a month instead.
Oh, well, okay, I see what you mean by that.
And that's basically more efficient.
What I see, actually, there's a lot of people I respect in the world,
like musicians and whatnot, who do a lot of drugs, and that's all fine.
You know, the Beatles did it in their most famous band ever.
Like, to me, the way I think of it is, there are, like, people alive right now.
Like, guys like Sam Harris, for example, who, he's a neuroscientist,
and he has done a bunch of drugs, because he's, like, an atheist.
He doesn't believe in free will.
You know, I find him a pretty inspiring guy.
And he has done really hard drugs.
But the point is, like, he's such a serious guy.
And he has, like, put in the work to put himself in a place.
Like, he's gone, like, as far as he could go, like, practicing, like, meditation and yoga
as a way to, like, understand human consciousness, which he's really interested in.
But then, like, you get really far with that path.
And then you start to, like, your gains start to level off from your understanding.
And once you've, like, become self-disciplined and you've done this research,
it's at that point where I think using drugs to then push yourself harder
than, like, a human being could go, now that you've put yourself in a position
where you can actually capitalize on this.
Like, then doing drugs makes sense, because then you'll really be able to appreciate it.
Whereas opposed to, like, if you've got, like, an 18-year-old college dropout,
or 20-year-old college dropout, just sitting at home is like,
yeah, I'm gonna do weed, and I'm gonna be, like, the greatest musician of all time.
Like, never practices, like, never do anything.
That's definitely a part of the aspect of, like, the things.
Like, if you're the sort of person who, obviously, is dangerous,
but, like, it does have, like, more impressive results than just doing a weed every so often.
I want to, I want to see it.
To do an LSD.
I want us to get away from the, like, the, both the artist and the burnout side of it for a bit,
because those are kind of, I think, like, stereotypes about, like, people who smoke weed.
But I think the vast majority of people who smoke weed are just normies
who smoke it to literally, like, because they work a normal ass job
and they don't do anything afterwards, you know?
Wait, hippo, I just want to say that I don't even disagree with you.
And I have that right down here on my notes.
That, like, again, it's, like, if you're an artist and you want to take a weed or LSD,
you know, like, you know, twice a month or whatever, I don't, you know,
I don't have hard numbers or anything.
But, you know, if you want to take it every once in a while, casually, I have no problem with that.
It's just when it becomes a part of your identity,
becomes a part of yourself, becomes something that you do every day,
part of your routine.
If you can't eat without weed, you cannot fuel your body.
If you cannot intake sustenance without weed, that's when it comes up.
Yeah, you got a problem. You got a problem there.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
That's why I was saying to close out that so you can go on whatever the hell you want.
Yeah, anyway, I think most people who smoke are just, like,
and this is the reason that 420 is, like, such a symbolic number.
Like, what it really means at the core is because it's right after you get home from work.
Like, that's the idea.
You get home at four o'clock, you roll up a joint for the next 20 minutes,
and then you smoke at 420.
It's a way that normal people who live without much to do, like, to entertain themselves,
like, especially poor people, like, is the, you know, the most people who smoke weed,
because you can just relax and, you know, just sit around and do whatever,
watch the regular ass TV or whatever the fuck you do.
Um, same reason other people do this with a six-pack, you know,
guys who come home by a six-pack of beer and they drink a six-pack every single fucking night
because they just work at the shipyard and they come home and watch TV all night,
you know, and then they get fat and have kids and they continue doing this until they die.
I have a suggestion for these people, though.
They should, instead of doing that and spending all that money on weed and whatnot,
they should come home, like, have an internet subscription,
just, like, do, play some relaxing music, whatever you want to do,
and take that money that you would have spent on weed and put it in the bank,
put in a 401k, save that shit for retirement, my dude.
You'll feel so much better.
I mean, these people might not have a...
It's kind of a big ask to have a reliable internet connection.
To have a bank account? Is that really much...
Wait, the internet connection is not...
The internet connection was the part I was talking about.
Well, I mean, we're talking about people in first world countries here.
I think that's not...
Yeah, we are.
I mean, we're talking about...
I feel like a lot of people would, when they retire,
would just want to sit around smoking weed anyway.
I can't go into this conversation without just bringing in my baggage
of how much happier I think everyone is when they're using their time
as productively as possible.
I just think that makes people happier.
I mean, I don't begrudge people having something to wind down
after a long day of work.
Of course not.
I just don't think that...
I don't think most people have the capacity to do what you're suggesting, Nate.
Like, I don't think a lot of people literally...
To save money?
I think that most people do not have...
Well, yeah, definitely not to save money.
Most people do not have the cognitive capacity to save money,
nor to have a second life outside of work.
Like, most people come home and they're just fucking exhausted and done,
and they just want to kick up and not think about anything
because they do not have those kinds of complicated thoughts
that lead people down other paths.
So boring.
It's unfortunate, but like, these people...
These are the people who need this shit the most
because all we need them for is to be the worker ants
running our colony of the fucking world.
Like, all these...
I mean, the worth of normies in society
is that someone's got to run all this shit.
We don't...
Us intellectuals who just want to go to a Walmart
and like fucking...
If you...
Yo, catch me an intellectual at Walmart.
If you have the IQ that you can watch Rick and Morty
and you just want to like hop down to the Walmart
and grab a fucking, you know, a quick case of whatever
soda fucking caffeinated thing you need to get through your day,
someone has to be there to sell that shit to you.
And that person, like, needs to be there every single day
doing this demeaning job that has to exist,
but like, so, you know, these people...
We need these people and we got to keep them satiated.
We got to make sure that they're not fucking pissed
because if they're pissed, they rise up.
Well, you know, Digi?
You know, Digi?
That's all the reason.
That's the only way to fulfill your life.
It's not the only way to get dopamine.
This is why...
Yeah, but it's a good way.
It's a cheap way.
The most important thing is that we need to get post-scarcity
so that people, even these people,
can choose to not waste their lives
as shitty jobs like this.
I figured out how to like replace weed
as like a way to give people the dopamine rush that they need.
Fucking make playplaces for adults.
Finally, please.
I just want to go in one of those...
I want to be like, you are old enough to be in here.
In fact, you're too old,
and that's why you're allowed in here, yes.
Incidentally, something that I want everyone to understand,
and this is part of why I started smoking so much weed,
is that when I went to Portland
and I saw what it was like there,
I realized that when weed is legal everywhere,
fucking everyone will be high most of the time
because it's super cheap
and it just puts you in a better mood
and it gets you through the day
and no reason people won't do it
because if you have a...
especially in a city like that where there's good public transit,
you don't have to drive anywhere
so there's no reason you wouldn't just go around high all the time.
So that's what it's going to be like
and the reason is that the amount that I smoke in a day,
and I smoke a hell of a lot of weed,
but I smoke an amount that's equivalent to buying a Big Mac once a day.
It's not...
But only if you're somewhere where it's legal.
That's not true where I live.
I pay way the fuck more for weed
because it's not fully...
it's not sold in dispensaries here.
But in places where it's legal, it's so cheap
that everyone's going to be doing it all the time
and when I realize that that's where the tide's turning,
that's going to be...
that already is normal in some places
and will be normal everywhere in America soon,
there's no reason to even think of it as differently than that.
Richie, why are you concerned with being normal?
Why are you concerned with being a little bit normal?
Well, I'm concerned with it because of the fact
that I am terrified of doing anything illegal
and I have never been someone who does illegal illicit activities,
except for in the most safe conditions imaginable.
I think you're being really selfish here.
Think of all those hard-working cartel members in Mexico right now
and we're going to put them out of a fucking job
if we legalize weed.
We can't do that.
How can we do that to them?
Fuck them.
We'll replace them with robot cartels.
We have to keep the cartels.
We keep the cartels, we automate their job.
Yeah, and then we just tell them...
Yeah, robots aren't allowed to kill people.
Replace the poor with poor robots.
To the people who come home tired after work,
I don't...
I sympathize.
I sympathize with them.
I understand why they would want it to happen.
But what I would suggest is that you should go outside
or get a hobby, because I know what it's like.
What if you live somewhere where you go outside and you get shot?
The internet, man. The internet.
Maybe it's idealistic and maybe it's...
I don't know.
Maybe I'm coming from a place of...
I hate the Procrasteers podcast.
I fucking hate it.
I can't get through a single point without literally every single host
constantly cutting me off for no reason.
I'll be in the middle of a fucking sentence.
And everyone, like vultures, trying to jump on me
and cannibalize my point.
The point where it's unrecognizable.
I don't get a single word in edgewise.
The point that I'm trying to make is why I don't...
I won't be able to go outside, because I know what it's like to be inside all the time.
I know what it's like to be inside and be just...
And not do anything.
I know what that feels like.
For myself, I think that's what's best is to go outside and get a hobby
and do what you love and do art or something.
I know it's a blanket statement that's what should be done for everyone.
Sure, there are outliers, but I shouldn't even say that.
I shouldn't even start up with my movie review.
This is just my opinion, guys.
Everyone's top ten list will be the same.
That's a given in this climate.
This is a conversation about weed.
We're talking...
We're having a conversation about what we're trying to find these lines.
This is literally the purpose of this conversation,
where is the line, when is it okay,
what is the parameters of how people should use it.
The reason I'm bringing up these talking points
is that I'm literally just talking about shit that literally every rapper raps about.
The reason weed is talked about so much in rap music
is it's almost always presented as,
this is the way that our people get through life,
is that we have nothing and this is what can make us happy.
They probably have a little bit more,
if they save a bit of all that money that they spend buying weed,
to advance their careers,
or try and move out of their terrible neighborhood,
or invest in whatever...
That's what Jay-Z says.
How much money do you think you're going to save
by putting away a little bit of weed?
Jay-Z encourages smoking weed,
but he does encourage not buying dumb bullshit like expensive cars
and frivolous spending.
Alright, here's the difference between getting some weed
and then getting some nice soda that you like.
There's no difference.
It's the same...
That's why I compared it to a Big Mac.
People buy these things because it's a step up from,
like, gruel, it's a step up from,
I have to eat Pop Tarts and Ramen,
but it's...
For me, growing up,
getting to eat fast food was something special, right?
We wanted...
That was better than at home dinner,
at least in my household.
My parents can't cook for shit.
And we were poor for a lot of times,
so we just ate crackers, nothing.
So going to a...
And we were a bunch of skinny, picky kids.
Even if we had options, we wouldn't have eaten any of it.
We would just go to McDonald's and be like,
wow, this is a step up, this is a real meal that I'm enjoying.
And now as an adult, I see that it's like disgusting filth
that I wouldn't touch because I know A, how to cook,
and B, I can go to a better restaurant.
But when you're in a situation where you don't...
I'm so hungry.
You know, I'm getting...
I'm actually making myself really hungry, too.
I lost my point in train of thought.
Well, you know, that was a very interesting point there.
The difference between weed and soda
is that you don't get high from soda,
and that you don't get, like,
a dopamine rush in your mind from soda.
That's actually not...
I mean, I feel that way when I haven't had soda
for like a month, and then I drink my first one.
That's how I feel when I drink a soda.
When you're not desensitized...
You get fucking high from drinking a Dr. Pepper?
When I'm really desensitized,
I'm somebody who reacts really strongly
to any kind of stimulus.
I drink a sip of an energy drink,
and I feel like my whole vision changes.
That's the level, because I don't drink it that much.
But when you get yourself desensitized to something,
it loses that effect.
When I drink it, there's been times
where I'm drinking Mountain Dew every single day,
and I need it just to get through the day,
and when I stop having it, I feel miserable,
and then I fucking scrounge together
whatever money I could find.
This is something I actually did when my parents
cut me off from Mountain Dew one time.
I was just fucking scrounging together dollars
to ride my bike to 7-Eleven
to secretly, covertly buy it,
because I was so addicted to it.
But when I stopped drinking it,
the next time I had it over a year later,
it was like, oh my God,
the sugar in this is so overwhelming.
You gotta drink that diet, dude, dude.
It's all about the diet, dude.
I'm fucking feast of the diet.
I will proselytize the diet soda is the greatest.
It's a fucking miracle.
I just went through this myself.
I never drink soda.
I barely eat sugary stuff,
but just fucking...
I bought a high-ball, organic,
grapefruit juice energy drink,
and I drank, it's got 40 grams of sugar in it.
40 fucking grams.
So, for me, like, a dessert,
a glass of orange juice is so rich.
It's so rich.
It is my cake,
a fucking glass of orange juice.
And this high-ball energy drink is the same.
I think the thing Munchie was getting at, though,
is like, weed gets you high
in, like, a very specific way
that, like, you can be,
like, completely incapacitated
if you're the sort of person
who, like, reacts that way to it.
Ben, what are you laughing about?
I just envisioned a world where, like,
Nate's eating his beans, right?
But it's, like, his day of the month
that he's gonna treat himself.
So he sneaks a jelly bean
in there among the regular beans.
Oh, no.
And then, you know, he's...
But he doesn't know where it is.
And it comes to surprise,
and when he hits that secret jelly bean,
it's the ultimate coom.
Dude, that...
It's like when you finally bite into that cyanide capsule
you've hidden in your teeth, and I just die.
That's what it's like.
That's a funny issue.
He's just got a bunch of frijoles negros
and he just throws one sweet, delicious
licorice jelly bean in there.
Everybody's favorite.
Yo.
Okay, but here's the real question.
Was he saying something?
The thing I was saying is that I feel like
if weed became, like,
one of the many things
you could just go into the convenience store
and buy, like, you get a chocolate bar,
a chocolate candy bar,
something, a thing, a soda,
and a weed, you know, it's all there.
That's, like, literally what it's like
in the places where it's legal.
Like, the dispensaries you walk in,
it's like a bunch of cheery-eyed people come up
and, like, everything's presented very nicely.
It's like an applesauce point.
Huh?
Go on. That was the middle of your point.
But that's how it goes, baby.
I was just, you know, telling him about dispensaries.
The point was that I think
it can, I feel like
as long as people,
like, I don't know actually whether weed
is addictive, like, cigarettes are.
I assume it isn't.
But, I feel like
it wouldn't be that big of a deal
if that just became a normal thing, because
you know, you just need to
anything to realize that
anything can be, like, self-destructive
and, like, can ruin your life
and make you retarded if you have too much of it.
I guess it's just like a thing.
You've got to make sure that people
in general learn
not to do big weed all the time, all day,
otherwise they won't be able to get anything done.
Uh, Digi, I'm happy that
you compared it to fast food, because that's actually
one of my points here. Fast food
is great every once in a while. You can walk into
Chipotle, and Chipotle is, like, one of the best
meals that I have, like, every single time.
It's great. I love Chipotle. But
if you eat too much of it, you're going to get fucking fat.
It's going to affect your overall health, and you're, like,
well-being. Like, socially, people are going to make fun of you because you're fat.
Or, rightfully so. It's going to affect you
economically, because you can't spend $10 a day
on fucking Chipotle. You can't do that.
Uh, you know, I mean,
that's true. Well, I'm saying you
probably should. Well, it's, it's, it's, it's
you could, you could make an argument, a sound argument.
That's a bad investment. And, like, like, the
perfect thing to do if you wanted to, even if you
want a delicious Chipotle burrito, if you
went to the grocery store, bought all the
ingredients, and cooked it yourself, it'll cost
you more time, for sure, but you'll definitely
save money by buying things in bulk and,
like, doing it that way. We're entering
a weird realm here, because I
don't think there's anybody
who is so broke
that they can't afford
to eat Chipotle every day, but
has enough money to smoke weed every
day. Like, I don't think this
person exists. Did you, I'm not saying
that they are literally incapable
of getting Chipotle every day.
I don't think they, they literally do not have the funds
to do so. I'm saying it's a smart
thing to do. I'm just saying, I'm just saying,
like, okay, in my case, for instance,
I could buy Chipotle every day
and it would do nothing to my bottom
line. Like, it, it is
inconsequential for me to spend that money
because I make way more money than
I can spend. Like, I
live such a small,
like, small life that has
nothing really behind it. I have a huge
savings, um, and
you know, every year a huge chunk of it gets taken
out for taxes and then it gets replaced. And
so, so, like,
for me, I could, yeah, I
could literally smoke weed or each chipotle
or do whatever the fuck I want every day
because, like, uh,
what is the reason not to do
that? You know, I, I, well, you know, I, most
people are not afforded. So, I'm speaking to the
audience. I mean, I think, I think what's
going on here is that you guys are talking
slightly about two different things, or at
least your, your emphasis is on two different aspects.
I think that's why there's a little bit of disagreement here.
I just feel like, if you,
I don't think there's anybody out there who like is
Smoking that amount of like nobody's smoking as much as I am if they can't afford it. It's what I'm saying like sure
Sure, I know multiple stoners that are constantly broke. Well, they're then they're fucking idiots
It's I would say that the weed is not their problem is the fact that they're fucking idiots that this their problem
I mean, you can make that point about spending their money on weed
Yeah, because they're I don't agree. I don't agree that they are also stupid. I do I they are stupid
I know is obviously not no, I would say any look literally
I'm trying if they can't afford it. That's the problem. Yeah, the thing is like there's people who do that
my fucking
My fiancee told me about someone she worked with who like her boyfriend had spent all his money on Pokemon plushies
Like he would literally get a paycheck and immediately drop it all on Pokemon plushies and be broke
She was like that too, yeah, I love you
People people literally just are bad with money because they don't understand it because probably their parents are bad with money
And just didn't teach them how to be good with it like the only reason I know anything about money is that my dad who was
Unbelievably bad with it and put himself in a massive amount of debt in his 30s
And then spent his 40s working his way out of all the debt and like learning everything about money and finances and taxes
He read literally the entire tax code. So I really should just get him to do my taxes fucking for me, but
So restraint because show restraint exactly
Like if you know how to show
Resuram show restaurant. Where's restaurant so overprotective of me
Like like basically if I if I stopped like if let's say my patreon took a dip to a point where I thought oh
Shit, I need to be worried about money now
We is the first thing that's got to go because it's what I spend the most frivolous money on like I know that it doesn't matter
How much I smoke I like I could smoke every fucking day and then the second I can't afford it anymore
It's fucking gone, you know
Well, I don't know if that's a proven fact that you could it's a very proven fact because I stopped drinking Mountain Dew
I stopped smoking cigarettes
I stopped doing all kinds of things that I was addicted to because well
I just thought that it was no longer appropriate cigarettes for like what like four months. I haven't smoked. I haven't smoked again since
Forever ago, I haven't smoked. Okay, you guys there. There is a difference here
You guys are basically talking past each other because there's two different things going on here
Munchie is talking about
Definitely positive possible negative things that could come from like being obsessed with weed and like the fact that there's addictive
Personalities like weed is just like like gambling we shouldn't like outlaw gambling but gambling can have negative consequences
Just by the nature of it existing but but digi here is focused on the positive that weed can do which I think we all agree
Exactly, I'm just saying that this this personality problem is not a result of any specific
Drug people will find a way to facilitate this personality problem
It goes way beyond like people talk about like gambling and weed and all that stuff because it's obvious
But like literally people will just blow their whole paychecks on fucking plushies like people will just spend their money
Badly because they're trying to fill a hole in their lives that they don't understand how to fill and they sure this is the way to do
It because they don't understand money. I
Completely agree. I don't disagree at all
But like last time so in the first cast we made fun people for making very getting fabulous commissions to spend all the American missions
Yeah, that's what I'm doing right here right now. I'm yeah, you should not do that. That's not yes
Do not spend all your money on weed if you cannot afford weed that's retarded
That might my main my main problem with the weed is is not the time or make a fucking budget
budget budget
Should I just to get into my big point get do it man. Let's do it. I'm ready
All right, all right when you can get high and feel good from just sitting on the couch like twiddling your clip playing the newest
Hottest like God of War two if you can do that
Dopamine for doing nothing your incentive to do like actually accomplish the things is diminished
You're not going to want to put in the hard work and do things that like really matter to me things that really matter to me
You're going to neglect other aspects of your life that make you feel good like social interaction work, etc
You can associate the dopamine rush that you get like from the high as rewards
You look at things that you've done or are doing currently and think wow good job. Like I'm so funny. I'm so much fun here and weed
I'm so smart. I bet no one would have thought of that Wow
When chances are it's either total bullshit and not good at all or the more like the scenario is it is good
But you just would have thought about it while you were sober and you're just more impressive than you otherwise would be
Hmm
So well, so basically you're making the case just like that that case kind of extends to just like something like video games as well
It's unearned indulgence. It's an indulgence and I don't I don't like the idea of pleasure for nothing
I mean, I agree
But the question like the question I think ultimately does come down to basically what we've been saying about like you've got to manage
That in your life because like weeds just out there and like weed or video games or any kind of drug or indulgence sex
Whatever it is not tell me that drugs are not more potent and easily well like literally released open mean in your brain
In the real world
You can you can get addicted to it like anything that that takes over your life because I don't
We don't even need to bring in anything else like the fact is that like weed as an example it
Alone it does do this, you know forget everything else forget drugs
It does do that and I can see why Munchie would see something like that and the effect it has on the on the world at
Large and think to himself well this you know, maybe there's some positives here
But I also see like a whole boatload of negatives coming along with it
I think that is understandable the the the idea that like you can take weed and then find like
The mundane stuff that you think to be like more impressive than it actually is
To be like that is literally our stereotype
Right now right now you constantly say that you're fun
You're on weed whenever I wait first of all, I don't even think I act what constantly was an overstatement
I don't think I even act any different whether I'm high or not. I don't think most people can tell
I don't think most people have any idea when it's the case
I mean, I hope well that it's been the case every single day since the year started
So if you just think I've acted literally different in every interaction
I've had with you since the beginning of the year than fair enough, but like you know
Well, it could be an overall sort of tonal shift, you know, I don't think that you're
Unrecognizable as did you bro, but I definitely I definitely like like notice a difference in your personality in general
I mean there is a difference in my personality, but it has nothing to do with weed it has like well
How would you know that though?
Because there's literally every single aspect of my life and my entire mindset has changed in the last
Okay, but that's that's hardly a scientific experiment though, you know, but also you started doing weed every day
So to say that I didn't know I think that my
Personality that I think yeah the changes to my demeanor that have been now. I don't know if this is what I'm trying to put you on trial
By the way, I'm just I'm just throwing I just want to say it
I don't I don't know if
Munchies time frame would align with other people's if he feels differently than than others who've expressed similar sentiments
however
Before the time where I started smoking like literally every day for the first like four or five months
I lived here. We were just smoked occasionally like maybe twice a week
Maybe it got up to like three times a week by the end of the year, you know
Because she was working a regular job
I was working doing shit all the time and I would talk about like weed in my videos
And I would make jokes about it in certain ones and in certain videos
I would say things like hey, you know, this is a high idea like this is an idea, but right
I had not actually been high and like any videos in that entire period until like a
Patron-exclusive like podcast release at the end of the year and people would say things like oh digi's so different when he's high
And I'm like, but I'm not high in any of the videos. I'm telling you about the experiences
I had while I was high. However, my personality is also different because I'm living a totally different lifestyle like I'm not a
Lonely weirdo in his room who feels bad all the time. I'm like, how do we get back to that? How do we get back to that?
I'm like a guy who's gonna go back to your roots, you know
Who's like having fun all the time and living well and and like just I
Just feel very different, you know from the way I did a year ago
And I think that what people don't understand and also the way I feel about weed is completely changed from that point because back then
Because we weren't smoking all the time. We did always get real high and we were like goofy and
Giggly and we'd watch a fucking Miyazaki movie and be like this is the greatest movie of all time
And then I'd watch a TV anime and be like all TV anime is garbage
I can't watch any of it like that's what it was like at the time
But I've completely desensitized myself to weed now like I'm high so often that it doesn't really have that much of an effect
it's more just like something that's fun to do and
It kind of lets me think a little faster and perceive things better like I've gotten better at following the plot of anime
I understood Ava way better when I've watched it high. Let me tell you that
Boy, it's just a lot easier for me to parse information because I've historically been terrible at following stories and shows like if you watch my critique
You'll you'll find that I rarely talk about like specific story elements because I literally don't remember a lot of the times
I can't even remember the main character's name. I just call him like the protagonist, you know
Yeah, I've gotten so much better at that just because I can slow down and like really take it all in so I
Prefer to watch anime high because I literally think I get it more and like I can also see things like I can tell the difference between the
Foreground and background better and I can judge them on different levels and things like that, you know, it's easier to
Identify each individual element of the production and that's an inarguable
Like how could I say like no you don't experience this better?
That's completely fine and valid way of thinking you like how you are better well high
But I'm saying for the general people
I don't like like like I don't want to condone or approve of that type of behavior
Because well, you might feel the same way that Digi does. There are also the many other various different
Things that I've said that I think are negatives about weed and also I can have my also own
Inarguable point that I just don't like people who are on weed. You can't say well, no, you just do people like people on weed
I just I just
Trying to like
Quell your argument that you don't like people on weed. That's completely fine
The only reason I'm arguing so strongly is that I'd want to encourage people to smoke weed because I see I
Think smoking weed will
Can make your life better if you are smart about it and you have someone guiding you and teaching you like how to do it
Well and to not
Digi, I don't even really disagree
It can make your life better if you use it in casual
Intervals if you use it it not every day if you can use it not regularly if you just use it as you know what workers really hard today
I haven't smoked and like, you know a little while. I'll just kick back tonight, you know, tonight's I just want to relax
I can't argue against that. I wouldn't want to argue against that. That's earned, you know, you've put it in work
You know, you've come home after work. I understand I get it. It's a casual
But what if I'm saying that like yeah, that's okay. If you're someone who's in a life situation where that is best
Yes, that I agree if you're someone who's in a life situation, however, like mine where getting high all the time will help you
Do it all the time and like, you know, use it in the way that's appropriate just like you would any other tool
That's what they're there for, you know, I
Mean, yeah, I totally agree that like all that there's there's no case that it should like be illegal or anything of that
It's just don't get it. I just I just don't get what it brings. It's never it's never like drugs or alcohol have never like improved
I've never felt good that I did them afterwards
Did you hear making his case, you know, that's
Would you consider your regular waking existence to be an utter nightmare. Yes
Proves that all from doing either of those substances temporarily, but I'm saying that afterwards
Like I can temporarily forget about what is my existence that that's actually brilliant
After you know, sorry bad. Sorry. I was saying but but but afterwards looking back. It's not better
Yeah, I don't feel better because I did it did you do you agree with him what Ben just said
Do you share that sentiment that your life existence is a waking nightmare? Etc. Etc. I would say I
Would not say that
however
How would I put this I I think that I have a tendency to get lost in thought
You know like and if I don't have anything to sort of guide me and focus me
Then I'm not gonna go into a good place, you know, and there's there's multiple ways to go about making sure that doesn't happen
Interact with somebody that will protect you from thinking, you know
Watch something consume something analyze something create something, you know get absorbed in your creation
Do something basically, it's what I'm saying if you're not doing anything then life is misery. However
Yeah, if you are in a situation like the one that I was in like this is more about
drinking really for me than than weed because I handled them kind of differently, but when I was a
Before before moving out and all I was drinking all the fucking time you guys remember I've had a historically
People used to constantly
Intervention me about how they thought I was drinking too much and I would go no
It's not like that because if you look up what actual alcoholism is
It's fucking terrifying and it's nothing like what I do
But but I did drink a fair amount and the reason is that sometimes I would be in a position where there was just nothing
I could do like no one was around for me to hang out with there was nowhere to go because it's too late at night
My sleep schedule is fucked up. I like either don't have a project or I'm stuck on the project and I just was like well
Nothing's happening. I feel like shit. I don't know how to continue the rest of the night
Like I don't know what I can change
Other than I can make my mind feel different by consuming this beverage that changes the way my mind feels and I can't predict
What's gonna come out of that? Maybe it's gonna make me feel even worse
Maybe it's gonna make me feel better. Maybe I'll feel productive
Maybe I'll put on the dick show and have three beers. It'll be a great night
You know, I'll rewatch something I love and just imbibe and and and take a step back
And that's why I drank so much at the time. The reason and I smoke so much now
Is more that I am living a an intense existence. I am doing
Everything all the time. I've got
Thousands of people who are talking to me all the time and I decided like at the end of last year
I had briefly decided to hole up and just be like no, I'm abandoning discord. I'm abandoning Twitter
I'm closing my comments and then I decided fuck it. I'm gonna go back into battle
And so I opened it all back up and now I'm constantly talking to people. I'm collabing with everybody
I'm paying everyone to do stuff for me. I've got a million things going on. I've got a thousand anime to watch
I'm you know with somebody all the time
You know much more physically active than before as a result. So
Yeah, I'm wearing myself out is basically what I'm saying and to keep all that together to hold it all together
Requires it just constant stream of like mind-altering
Substances that will change the way I feel in a subtle way throughout the course of the day that makes it feel like I
Reset again. I've got energy again. You know, it's like oh, I took I got high again
Now I can edit the rest of this video. Oh, I drank another beer now
I can do this and like because
Getting high is like I'm just way more potent effect than drinking is like you can get way higher way faster than you can get drunk
So it's just a really effective way to constantly shake things up and reset your sort of mental clock and you know
That's why I smoke all the time
I don't really think it changes the actual products that I create that much
Because the reason that the stuff I make has changed so much has nothing to do with the weed
It has to do with just that I started watching lots of really good stuff while I was smoking weed
And I took a lot away from it, you know and decided that I thought my content was just shit
Like my content was something I couldn't watch high because it's boring. So like let's make it interesting, you know
Well at that right there, you're showing that we is affected what you like how you perceive things
It's affected watch your it affected how I perceive things is that it made me a
Elitist who did not want to watch anything bad like all I watched when we started smoking weed like all I could watch was
Hiyami Izaki and like Jesse's videos and I got I got I had a total ego death watching demos
Like last three videos that he made that were like astonishingly good and I couldn't believe I'd ever said I was better than him
You know like but then I watched the rest of his videos and I decided I was better than him
But like you know those three videos are godly and well, okay, okay?
That was an interesting an interesting thing, but here comes neurotypical Nate to neurotypical explain
All your bullshit away. So that was very interesting. My Michelle calls me neurotypical Nate's a very
So it's it's pretty good. She's literally shaming my normal brain
But that's that's what's interesting about this because the way that you're approaching it is
PCP fan because like the idea of like calling people
Neurally atypical is like a meme that I do and oh, yeah, nobody's caught on except I guess her now
Yeah, she's figuring this shit out. So like we start I started by asking and Ben described the existence as a nightmare
I mean you didn't quite agree with that, but basically you said that you use, you know drugs use use alcohol use
You know weed now to like modify your existence
Which is exactly what drug is for so that you can like achieve the things you want to achieve now that I would never tell anybody
They can't do that and that's all fine
But I would say that personally like the hardware and software that I'm running in my body makes me say
definitively existence isn't is far from a nightmare
I I am at my most happy when I am sober and working on stuff, you know, I don't feel I agree
I would say that the drug life is the wrong life and this is not how I want to raise my kids
Like that's my point. Yeah
But because I'm not raising kids right now, you know, he's free
He's not only am I not raising kids
But like our audience are adults now and they're already fucked like their parents already fucked up
Like you're listening to the PCP your parents fucked up bad like
Normie life is over. First of all first of all your life is definitely hard because you're trans and everything
And
You kind of need this
Donate to our patron if you're neurotypical
Do I turn patron if your dad failed you don't take our patron if your dad ran away from home
Don't don't do our patron if you didn't grow up with the father figure. Well, so so this now this is cool
Like what it comes down to is like if you need okay, like this this would be my ideal scenario
I don't know if this is realistic. I don't know if this is even possible
But like I was a broken terrible human being when I was young and somewhere along the line
I developed the capacity to work really hard and put in a lot of hours to do things I want
I don't know exactly when that came where that came from
It started sometime after I started doing like t-bap stuff and was able to talk to women
Okay, at some point something changed in me and what I personally would ideally want definitely not realistic
But I would prefer if people could somehow
Make this change in themselves that simply doesn't rely on a substance to be that way
And so that they're they're happy all the time and I know that like I take caffeine
So it's it's kind of hypocritical to say that because I do consume caffeine. It is a drug
It you know makes me more energetic sometimes when it and it's helpful
So even I am not like the perfect ideal, but like that that's like my my platonic
Form like there's a human being who just goes through his life
And he doesn't need any substances outside of what he wakes up in the morning with he eats right he exercises
That's why I guess that's why I wish that I could say it was straight edge. I wish that I was yeah
You know like I think I was a I think if I was a better person
I wouldn't indulge
It's Jesse we're here he'd be going hard on the loving the straight edge the lifestyle the normal life
Jesse we're still with us today
I mean coping sounds judgmental and I'm not
I don't know if you can necessarily solve the problem because like doing what Nate does
Requires constant maintenance. You just have to learn to love that
Like you have to like you have to feel that your body is like it's worth it
It's worth the upkeep because it you know makes you feel so good
And by the way like the thing I love doing of like coming home making videos that I devote all my time to like even I didn't like
Work hard to discover that I just I committed to doing some videos with Ben and somewhere along the way
My body just awoke to the fact that it simply enjoyed doing this like I didn't like achieve anything
I just like my body just enjoys doing this kind of online work
So I don't even really give myself credit for that. It's just I feel like this is a really
I'm just so happy about life and everything feels great
That's what everybody said to have that well big part of why like not more people go down this route that you're that you've gone
Down is that for people who've never really been healthy
It's difficult to relate to that sentiment of like the idea that you just feel better because like again
I grew up on like shit food my whole life and yeah
When I like discovered what healthy food was and like that feeling of like cuz I've tried to do the health-kick thing for a while
And like yeah, it makes you feel fucking like
Weirdly amazing like you get a lot of energy
That's what humans are supposed to feel like. Yeah, what the fuck is this?
Like how is like I didn't know like it's just you don't really understand what food is supposed to be because you've never been fed it before
It's like how yeah, yeah, but guys I
Know I literally don't eat sugar everyone. I'm going off sugar for I'm throwing in on the trash
No sugar for a fucking week till the next PCP. I'm making a commitment right now. I'm not doing it. Everyone. Let's be healthy
Let's live. Let's truly live everyone. Fuck. Yeah, there's a while there
I've sadly fallen off the wagon and it's really disappointing and you know what day I'm gonna join you
I'm not going to drink any soda or energy drinks. Yes. That's what I'm talking about
For a while for a while there
I wasn't drinking any soda for like like like from like August up until like like December or something or like around there
But I remember there's one moment
There's one fucking moment where I was at it was at it was at your house and I think you saw saw this happen
Where we were leaving Wingstop and like there's just some sort of like impulse in my mind
There was some sort of like weird like like phantom of sodas past and yeah
I was pouring out my drink and then like I didn't like it was so fast
I like my body acted on I didn't even cognitively think about it
I just like got a little like like a tiny sip of
Orange of orange juice like no
Chugged it as fast as I could and then I was like, what did I just do?
What just happened?
Remember that yeah
Yeah, um, it was you know, it was sad. It was like it was like that episode of the Simpsons where um
Where Homer and Barney get picked for the space program and Barney excels
He gives up alcohol and he gets really healthy
And then like he he makes it to the end of the program and he's going into space
And then they celebrate with a beer and once a beer his eyes go all crazy and he says oh god
It starts and he goes nuts and he and he runs and he runs out jumps out the window and the scientist says I don't understand it
That was non-alcoholic beer, but it's just the idea. There was a seed in his brain
You know like it wasn't the beer itself, you know, it was the the addiction or the dopamine or the or the I don't know
The headspace to put him in or something. Yeah
We gotta fight we gotta fight our weak biology
We have to break our body man is both the sculptor and the sculpture every change will will will wreak agony upon your whole body
But that's how you make yourself into a better human being and a more perfect form. You have to carve yourself everybody
That's a well that's a well-known old adage
Yeah, there was a guy coming down the alleyway and he was a skinhead Yobo sort of lad
He looked at me and he smirked and he said do you want some weed and I looked down on my feet
And I looked in like glancing his eyes. I looked away and said no
Thank you and then he scoffed and they walked away and I felt bad. I felt emasculated
And that's that's my weed story everybody. Is that true?
Yeah, oh cool
I was in an alleyway and a guy was gonna offer me weed and he was a young man
He looked like he was bigger than me and he was a fucking freak and and and I had my stupid hair
And I was like, I don't know. Yeah, I don't know if I would trust no, thank you, sir. You know, yeah
Yeah, I don't want my weed from an alley. Yeah, I trust alley
OOP
Get give give what's alley OOP stance on the weed
She doesn't have a mouth so it doesn't really
So she's injecting
That's why she's white
She's just bleached pale from all the bleach. She's injected into your hands. You inject cocaine, right? Yes
Okay, where are we going with this? Are we?
I just want to I want to give my yeah, I'll give my big my last thing
I want to say word because Nate your lifestyle
Your lifestyle of healthiness like I really look up to it and I want to capture it
Like I want to be that guy not necessarily the beans shit, but like
The thing is my dad is somebody who in
When I was like a kid and he was in like his early 30s
He got real fat and like he was balding and he just kind of looked like shit for a little while
And he had been like a real handsome dude like he if you look at him pictures of him. He was young
He was fucking beautiful. He looked like Tom Cruise and like he he got fat and old as you do and then he like
Fucking was like this is bullshit. Like I'm not gonna be like this anymore. So like at age 35
He got like
Unbelievably shredded like he looked amazing. He was like, you know fucking bench pressing over 300 pounds and shit at age
35, you know, and like I don't know what it is
But there's something about the like 30s to 40s range where guys just seem to develop the will it's because your body
Starts giving out. That's why that's yeah because yeah
I know it's coming because the reason my dad every single time my dad's quit something
It's because he was told he had to like he used to drink real bad and as a result of drinking
He would smoke and he literally be developed an allergy to alcohol and couldn't drink anymore because it would give him like really bad
Anxiety attacks. So like but now that he quit like he's healthier than he was before
He quit smoking now. He's a vegan and it's like you you have time you always have a chance
You just but you you got to know that you can do it because if you let yourself get used to being like a fucking fat ass
And you just never learn how to fucking be healthy
You're not gonna be able to suddenly save yourself at age 40
But like you got develop that discipline the way I see it my my current plan is like just we're about to move to Boston
I'm gonna spend the next three years like slimming. I'm gonna lose like 30 pounds and just keep it off
I'm not gonna stop doing any drugs or anything like that. Then I'm gonna have kids then I'm gonna probably stop doing drugs learn Japanese
After we've established PCP HQ and it's like taken off then I'm gonna go establish the Japan branch of PCP PCP
The Boston branch and I'll go to the Japanese yeah, that sounds great
Yeah, this is my 10-year plan and once I'm in Japan because of the fact that you don't like drive anywhere
You just run. I'll just fucking run everywhere. You just run. Everyone in Japan is sprinting
Oh, we know now they're doing the devil man dash. Yeah
Like bullet trains are actually on Flintstones technology, sir
You have just like run with yeah, like like there's there's really fast actually since since devil man crybaby came out
There's been a massive stratification in society between the narrator runners and the devil man dashers
It's pretty massive racial and social tension right now. Do you guys know about the Brazilian Naruto run?
No, okay. There's a national event in Brazil
We're like 40,000 people fill the streets and Naruto run for like miles be ours. What the hell are they doing down there?
It's real and there's YouTube videos of it. So show credible get that shit. That's not even a good way to run
Yes come to Brazil
Okay, my final word to the will of the deceased is this
There are other ways to feel good. There are other ways to have that dopamine rush and I because I'm me
Value hard work. I value social connection. I value going outside. I value taking up a hobby
I value learning an instrument
I value things like that as opposed to doing nothing and sitting on your ass a smoking weed in your bedroom
And I value productive
you know aspects of society and that's the kind of people who I want to surround myself by because that's what I respect and
That's what I admire
So I don't want to be your friend if you're a stoner who wastes all of your money on weed and then just sits on you know
His ass I watching you know anime or you know fucking playing video game
I don't care about that. I don't care about any of that shit
I want to be around people who I like people who I like aren't so this is like completely side-side like this is just like the
The arguments that I can argue. I can't argue
I just don't like being around stoners because I don't like the way they smell or like the stereotype of a stoner
Which is real and I've encountered them. I don't like and I think they're annoying. I can't really argue that I can't argue
Dopamine rush incentives reward, whatever the fuck. I'm sure yeah. Well, you can make your case
I agree with that stance. I think you you should definitely not get shallow rewards
Chase the big I'd say because there's more rules say anybody who likes dark souls. You already fucking know
You already know approach your life like dark souls. It'll be just a satisfying
That's the best thing I've ever heard
Here's here's my okay. I've got I've got a life rule to go by for this
So I of course I feel a lot of empathy for the guys that like did you mentioned about like like if you live in like a fucking ghetto
There's nothing going like you don't know about you can't work on your entrepreneurial internet YouTube career or whatever
You've got nothing going on. I that's just an example
It's just an example
And it like it if you've got if you if your life is hell and the weed is your one escape and it is I get it
No matter what no matter who you are then then I get then who the fuck am I to criticize how you do
But I would always say have a have your goals in mind
You know, maybe your life is complete hell and there's no chance that I'm like well fair enough get high every single day
I mean, what do you gotta do? But I don't believe that's the case for almost everyone
So try to work on a plan to get yourself where you want to be I think most people just don't have like any
Ambitions they don't they need to be reminded that they can achieve something with their life
Ambitions, but they should yeah, I look for it. Yeah. Yeah
Well a a a lot of people don't have ambitions, but they should but be a lot of people don't like
Understand that they can achieve things
Mm-hmm, you know like I didn't feel like I could achieve anything until maybe a couple years ago sure
I'm sure like everyone is like that's the only reason to become an adult. Yeah, but my mind
What are you gonna do like how?
Well, I don't know. I don't know. I will I will I will say that what I believe that stuff
That's all do that I I will give people a vision of a better future for themselves by not being just a stoner and nothing else
I'd like I think that's sincere fucking you can make something yourself
You can you can achieve you can achieve great things if you put your mind to it like anyone can I believe it
And if you use weed just to relax every once in a while and you're still a productive guy
Then what the fuck just do whatever the fuck you want man. Like who cares it's fine. It's yeah
More power to you. I just think that like like
This is one of those things where it's like the act unit of self. I don't like but you could say well, you know
It's not that bad, you know, you know, he's just he's just having fun on the couch
You know, whatever the hell but I think this this happens a lot where doing an action is
Like indicative of the kind of person you are and your morals and beliefs
We're sure I feel like you have to be a certain type of person to even want to become a stoner
Who does weed all the time and just sits on the couch? I think you
Things about you. I think yeah about you if that's the way that you use the drug
Like if you are that type of stoner and yet you're a fucking like you deserve the stereotype because
Like it is a bad thing to be, you know, you know, I just just to go way back a little bit
When I find casually the last time that I did weed I was visiting friends in around Seattle in Redmond, Washington and
Like we did weed it was fine
Like there's a guy who's a big weed guy and like what what happened to me was that I just we were watching Tim and Eric and
It was an episode I had seen many times and just this time
I found it a thousand times funnier than I ever had before and don't get me wrong
That was an enjoyable experience except I became very self-conscious
About how it wasn't as funny to everyone else as it was to me and that to me was embarrassing because I have this
That feel like you get embarrassed that you're enjoying yourself and you know that it's because of the weed and it's like oh no
This is so uncomfortable
Like I want to observe the world as closely to objectively as possible because that's just like the way you can make a
Change and sculpt the world you want, but you know what that's just a fun story. That's fine
I it wasn't a crazy thing wasn't a big deal, but here's a life rule everybody
This is my this is Nate's hot tip for drug use
Never be the biggest stoner in your friend group. That's my life tip and if you follow that one simple rule
I think yeah things will go. I mean that would just lead you to going into groups with bigger stoners
Oh, no, it's gonna start an arms race. It's a big stoner and a small bitch
I like to think that it'll it'll just make everybody move away. Alright, I want to get us into a to the questions now
Let's do it. Let's do it. Oh, yeah
Okay, shoot shoot shoot. I get
More high from taking a chunky bite out of a soft white like spongy
crusty bread, okay, then I do in any amount of alcohol
Use yeast for bread not beer
Hashtag save the yeast everybody. Okay question one is from Mozilla fennec and zero who asks
Do you have to prepare yourself to record a script or a podcast in any way? Yeah, dude. I got a smoke a huge
Bubbly bubbly bubbly ball. I have to turn off my real self. There it is any podcast
You have never seen me as my real self and unless we're in person
Even I don't I don't generally like write scripts or take notes about things but like
I don't know if it counts as prep
But the times that I've recorded like a rant like a rant video or like a you know like a ramble video
I will yeah, I don't like prep for it
So I mean or maybe a little bit but mostly I just I start recording and then I'll just stop
I'll just redo it a bunch of times like until I'm sure
Yeah, yeah
In the show notes, you will find my my notes for this very podcast you listen to right now. Oh
Nice nice check that out
I I used to prepare notes for the PCP, but I've just found that I'm just so good
I don't need to that's that's my real thoughts on the matter though for like every other video
I I don't think they meant like notes wise like just prepare yourself to record a script or podcasted
Yeah, more like you know what I get in the mood
You know what I do. Yeah, this is the thing I always do
I never drink like milk or orange juice or anything like that before a podcast because it fucks up your throat
You gotta be able to the only good thing drink water tea. Yeah tea is good water water doesn't help me water makes me like
Some reason doesn't work. He does though. I don't know. Maybe it's just because it's warm, but that helps
Yeah, that helps I've actually meditated on this a little bit cuz for a long time. I I was thinking I was meditating on the issue
Why am I better on arm shield than I am on the PCP?
Why am I more likeable on arm shield than I am on the PCP and on and all of the many reasons I've come back with this as
Well, it's later in the day
It's like at night we record like at night
And so if I had more times like go throughout the day and you'll get all my groggy the sound get on my drowsiness out
And I've been able to like you know, you know
Get a whole bunch of water and by get hydrated and shit
I've been able to you know get some energy and I've been able to expend that on the podcast as opposed to the PCP where I woke up
Before just like like an hour for the podcast and I still feel like I want to die
It's interesting you say that because I think the opposite is true for me of the PCP that part of why I'm able to have so much
On arm retrieval what no I'm just saying that like I just meant that like the opposite is true for me in terms of
What time of day is more convenient to record a podcast because like if I record the PCP relatively early
It's like I haven't had the time to exhaust all my ideas yet today
So I'm like excited to talk because that's what I like doing is talking
Yeah, and by the end of the day like sometimes when I do the pub crawl because it's at 11 p.m
On Mondays and almost always by that point on Monday
I've already made a bunch of shit and like talked about most of the things I had to say or I have to do another like
I'm about to do a patreon podcast after it or something like that
So I don't want to say too much because then I have to have more to say on that it's just like as the day wears on
You know each new podcast it's gonna be more exhausted because I've already been talking all day because even if I don't record anything
I was definitely talking all day, you know
Fair enough I got I got nothing else to say on that
Yo, let's check out. Yeah, you've got a question
Yeah, I'm gonna check right now
But hold on I'm checking the patreon lounge right now just like just like the at like like actual real patreon lounge chat
Yeah, what I have found right here. This is a this is a straw pole. This is a
Which member of the PCP do you look up to the most? I'm gonna check the results right now. Oh shit
Oh, dude, I mean you are tied Nate mean you are tied. We are both tied with eight votes
Oh, I like the best Nate ever munchie wears tiny bells screaming best like who was the audience of this
This is just a bonus. Wait, I want to see I want to see it's linked to the same. I see okay
These are funny. This is cool. I'm gonna vote
for
Me well, all right, this is fine. This is not up to your self
I'm gonna put this in the description guys vote in this well sure that yeah, that's fine
Though this it'll be a will it even still be voteable in a week when it I am I am dissapointed in my performance
All right. Hey quick quick quick aside quick aside
Did you I don't know if you saw this but I just saw that demolition D retweeted PA work saying they're making a sureobako movie and
I see main character girl standing in the Gainax pose. What is this implying?
What does this mean and maybe that maybe they'll fucking have a Gainax reference in there or something?
I mean, I know it was in the goddamn TV show, so
Okay, sorry, I just saw that and it was weird. So okay moving on moving I would like to see that is what I'm
I'll have to watch the show and then do that. Yes. That has to be in the show notes now, so
Well, everyone will have seen it. That's true
Question give I mean
Okay, well here I'll go to the fucking Twitter here we go here is our pity question
Uh
What oh no god, these are shit. These are all bad questions. These are okay. Here we go
I do about two asks will thought be an official member
He's an honorary member for sure. He'll be a guest. He'll be a frequent guest and friend of the show thought
Yeah, I agree. That's I love both. I love him. He's our boy. All right. Here's our boy
Here's a quiz a question. Okay, like Cappy from the patron lounge
What is your favorite thing on the internet? This is very much like like what is a recent internet going on?
I believe they're saying oh
What is really there's an okay? Yeah, go ahead. There is a podcast came out by my hero and idol
Yon Renkowski aka 91. It's called radio pro seconds on whiz dumb gun
I'll look in the description obviously and it is an absolute experience
I've fallen in love with yon all over again his wit and humor and just on the fly like rants and promos
That he cuts just just on like like stoners and like juggalos and cyber vermin are just an utter fucking treat
And I'm so happy. I was really worried. This is gonna be like. Hello. It's me yon renkowski
I made a thing in the past and now I'm a wash-up internet creator
This is my life and I'm just going to sell to you Brit landly because I have a podcast show
That's what everyone does now, right? But no yon is not he is
Ceaseless and it's advancement in performance artistry. He has so many weird fucking unique gimmets like in the first episode
He he has like he sets up an interview with a crisis actor
Who who like like was one of the people who acted on the set of the Syrian Civil War?
What interviews him about about how the series war was staged wait
The whole thing it's fucking incredible. Yeah, it got damn radio Prozac absolutely incredible
I love it dearly and it just reminds me how much Barry Collin to be and it's really inspires me to be a better person
That's fantastic. Oh also. What was the question that inspired that answer?
Uh, it was what is your favorite thing on the internet at this very moment?
Okay, I have an answer. Yeah shoot. Um, it's the fucking it's the fucking rowdy fuckers juvenile detention
The slime economy should be coming online today or tomorrow. Yeah, the slime economy will be live
We have been workshopping it. We have been I we I watched I watched the economy crash and burn
I watched slime credits worth fall to zero as people lost faith in their society
They had to be replaced with a new with a new currency, but we are we're yes
It's it lives the world lives munchie
It's a living breathing place
How's it feel to be a whole four mega slimes behind me at this point? What the hell is going on?
What happened to the cop killers? It's embarrassed. Yeah, the the shit the cop killers were on top of their game
But then like the rowdies have just the rowdies have just have just embraced bots and just basic
Cowards. Yeah, well, there's no rule
You can easily kill a body could easily kill one, but the
The fucking killers were just so lazy and incompetent that they just couldn't foresee what the rise we're doing the cop killers
Look the cop killers don't employ cowardly tactics, but I tell you what they do employ
massive economic stratagems and when
They do and who else what was was like the first real bot then B dash Evan the fucking notorious killer
So don't give me that shit you fucking cock. I'll kill you. I'll kill you
You're done off to the combat zone right now first
I'm gonna kill you and then I'm gonna I'm gonna suicide and then I'm gonna go kill the Lord of Ghosts just to make a point
I kill them once and I can kill them again
I'll tell you I this is a small thing my favorite thing on the internet at this very moment
Legibly the first thing that comes to mind is the gaming Brits new video on the new God of War
I liked it a lot way to go chas you're killing it. That's it. That's my whole answer
It was good also in case you're not aware he like has a history like
Action games are like his wheelhouse and he made a video that was real famous of the first like the trailer for this
And I've both had famous videos about the trailer of God of War that's that said almost the same thing
But his was like a proper video and mine was me doing the Gilbert Godfrey depression for half an hour
The game in Britain is making me feel bad about like how good his content is and I got a
Right away does he like the game or not because I've been hearing it's actually great
The summary of spoiling your video chat. Sorry about that
But like every it's been a week by the time it's been out now
He just says that like
Everyone's like been telling him and commenting on his video like you were wrong
The video is getting 10 of 10s across the board every journalist loves it
Meanwhile, his point was journalists will love this game excessively
So like he's just like yeah, like of course it's getting 10 of 10s from these journalists
The game is exactly as not great as I as I feared it would be and it's boring and like yeah
It's not it's not it's not the DMC that he would wish you know it to be or whatever
So, of course. Yep. It's what it's basically what he predicted. You killed it boy. You killed it
Well, um, I've my favorite thing to come out recently was fucking mania madness
From our good friend endless Jess who fucking covered. Yeah, that was great
And it was like it he ended up turning it into unintentionally this like epic
Fucking weekend spanning event just like mania itself because I guess he recorded like a five-hour podcast and released it in 30 minute
Chunks that he was releasing over the course of days. I love that. I loved it
It was so good. I think I should check it out
It should watch the whole thing start to finish like I'll tell you because back in the day
Jesse had the drowning and kayfabe channel and that's how I got in any interest in wrestling at all was I would listen to these hours
long wrestling podcast and even though it was just like Jesse on a couch in front of a camera and like
rambling like you know
Like constantly undercutting himself and stopping to talk about how he has no idea he's talked about and stuff like that
You know that was like the first true rambling vlog
I ever enjoyed where I was like wow like he's just such a good storyteller that I don't even care that this is just a guy sitting
On a couch like rambling at me because this is fucking fascinating stuff
And I want to hear about it. So now he's doing it again
And I haven't cared about wrestling in the last year and a half because he hasn't been able to fucking talk about it
So I haven't heard anything about it
Learned all the new stories. It's like three hours of fucking it feels like watching a TV show because it's 30 minute chunks and like
If you watch them over the course of days
It's like you're slowly marathoning through this epic series that has like this amazing
Climax to it and everything all these huge moments because it's like the most exciting WrestleMania of all time and
He cut out like it's highly edited instead of being him in front of a camera
There's like it's just like images on screen like a long time, but like the audio is highly edited
I mean to let you know
It gives you exactly what you need and like in order to understand if you would watch this WrestleMania
Like you would need someone like Jesse there explaining everything happening. Yeah, why yeah, so just having it presented this way
For for guys like us. I think is like the best way to do it. Oh, yeah
Like literally watching everything you just watching the good part of wrestling
Exactly all you gotta do is then just go watch a YouTube video of the actual fight
So you can see the moves and like I mean he puts half of them on screen
I didn't even feel like I had to watch any of this shit. I was just like, yeah, there you go
I got the whole WrestleMania experience and it was way better than it would have been if I'd actually watched WrestleMania
So yeah, yeah, I had a really great time with that series
Sincerely hope it continues to be a yearly tradition from and you know
So do I and every basically every year
I think we missed one like two years ago
But the PCP boys will gather when Jesse sends us a link to watch the Royal Rumble and it's one of my favorite
We did it like a month or two ago and it's one of my favorite things to do. Yeah, you weren't there tragically
But I think me Jesse and Gib were all hanging out
Munchy to munchy, that's right. It was a great time. It's a great time
Yeah, wait, I've actually got I've got one
I want to know what hippo and Ben think are the the best thing that's out right now. Oh, yeah. Yeah, wait
I did I thought I said it was it's the rowdy fuckers juvenile detention
Well, hippo, what do you think is the best thing out. I mean, I like stuff. I
Don't love stuff though. I don't know whether I have like a like
Dude like it like if I was I had an older brother that I was gonna run and try and show him how cool
I am for knowing this well, I mean there's this I can't think of there's this one character
I really like that you might have heard about the Lord of Ghosts who's really being interesting to me online right now
I really like seeing what's going on with that guy really interesting
Yes, I honestly though like the stream you guys did of the ratty fuckers cop killer stuff like doing the lore contest and stuff
That was like I loved that. Yeah, I watched basically the whole thing and I the lore is rich and deep
And if you only you guys monetized it better, I would actually think it was a cool thing to spend your time on if only if only
I want to go the fuck do we do that?
I don't know before I find out it's $1 per slide before I even shut up about the the mania madness thing
I also have to mention that like since Jesse's come back. He always writes these
unbelievably long patreon posts for his videos that are literally a second video often with more context than the video that you
Watched so also those have been a great fun to read
It's like I just read them out loud to to May and that's like it's like I'm just getting another video out of it
Basically, well, that's cool dope. Oh wait. I have thing I have thing that I am in I'm doing currently
I asked for anime recommendations. Yeah, and she won it because I heard munchies say he wanted anime recommendations
I was like, you know what? I should get an anime recommend
I went to Twitter and did you said something you said Gundam?
I suggested Gundam goddamn it. That was me. No, he he said. Oh, I don't know
I said it first that people I know I told him to watch double 80 it's just because it was sure
Oh in the pocket and I've been watching it like one episode a day
Which is like a really good way to watch something like that and it feels like it's it's great
It's like a movie that's like gots. It's like a it's a good like action
Compared to like a BBC show just like a six episode tight compact drama, you know
Yeah, you're watching anime. It's it's it's it's an anime that does not feel like an anime. Oh, thank God
Thank God
Hippo, are you gonna try and become an anime boy too because that's what I'm well
I'm trying to become an anime boy, but I'm definitely trying to watch more anime. That's a definitely direction
We have to go back
I'm trying to be like like an anime boy before anime became anime
Yeah, like the 90s and the old all the old stuff. That's kind of like
Like a very very heavily influenced by actually good things
Like all the not the incestuous slurry of anime as it exists today, of course
Yeah, like if I see a picture of like a modern anime, I'm like, well that does just
I
Anybody who hasn't seen a Gundam double 80 war in the pocket by the way anime fans get out get on it
It's it's a it's a I consider it the best access point to Gundam simply because that's what I'm looking for
It's only six episodes
It's mostly standalone like there's a little bit of dialogue in the first episode that might go over your head if you don't know
The show but like the story but it doesn't matter. It's inconsequential to the it's yeah
I've been engrossed the characters are really well done in in terms of like having like quirks that I'm like
Ah, yeah, I could imagine him doing that as like as I just want to say human being my personal consultant
Ukrainian Zagok or however, it's pronounced. Yes, please at me on Twitter telling me if that assessment of this anime is correct
Cuz I trust you more than anyone when it comes to anime for some reason. Tell me if this stuff is good
He doesn't seem to have patrician taste this guy knows
This entirely on his avatar, I'm just gonna tell you that if somebody told me they thought Gundam double 80 was not good
I would not trust anything they said after that. Okay
We should have a podcast where we watch anime together that we want to know called the week of the plebe and the plebe
Yeah, let's actually do that
Hey, hey, listen to that me too. Yo, uh, here's an axle leader
That's a pretty good show pretty good show. That is 50 episodes long just let me know
Yeah, it is it is ooh, but stop after 25. I'll just watch all 50 at once
Also, the manga is better. So if you want to read the manga instead, there's also that option the ending
It looks really good. I'm like all anime which looks really bad
Basically, okay. Hey, there's a question here from
This is a Twitter question
Directors done looks just as good, but you know, we can get into that another day
Yeah, that's what I when you when you guys reach the stage where you want to get woke just come to me and I'll
I'll give you the dark side of the moon is what I'll give you
Digi literally what should happen is you should write like like it should be the plebe the plebe and the weeb
Yeah, me and hippo get into like an entry-level anime and then we're like this is not a bad idea
I like it and did you like
That actually happened recently like what I did like I can't get over that we brought that up last show, right?
I mean the Japs are real sympathetic to the fucking to the fucking croutes, you know, but whatever
Yeah, that should happen
Listen listen to this question here. This is from at at not you who three
It's weird. Okay. Here's the thing. Are you aware of the reach of your lectures?
I have presented two of them for my students to teach how to do lectures
Regardless of the subjects. Well, also that munchie one so spicy. That's a little common. Which one?
Um, well the new one of course the new one. I have a I have a I have a story
I got I'm retweeting. I'm replying to this guy right now asking which one so maybe he'll get back to us
I actually okay, so I have been
Recognized in public like relatively a lot recently like really yeah
I was hanging out with econ and
We went to this a magic we went to like a magic night and a guy there knew me
But that's not that surprising because he knew econ
Okay, but like he wasn't expecting to see me or anything
But then the other day we had a party me and Jackie had a party at our house and like a guy was just there
I might have even run into him before and he just at some point in the night asked me like hey
You're Ben, right? I was like yeah, I was like Ben St. And I and then he could see in my fucking
Sonichu lecture pulls out his little patreon subscription. I mean that's like a million fucking views right like yeah
Like half a million. Yeah, that's fucking nice. That's a lot of views. Every single day that I wake up
remembering that it would have been St. Patron it feels me with such glee
Such malicious glee and how I'm ruining the world for my fellow man. I love it
It fills it fills me with glee too, man. Also. I finished I finished signing the books. They're shipping probably
Yeah, but but in regards to this question people like
Disproportionately tell me how much they love I mean with when it comes to my content people say they love the gurren login videos
Like the galco video which was just like successful in terms of numbers
But then the the one that's even more discussed than that is the Kingdom Hearts lecture
Got a lot of buzz and people just are like, yeah, dude. That's like your best like it's incredible
The the lecture formula is such an overwhelming success
Yeah, and I got on the dick show again because I made a lecture, you know, I'm right
I mean if I hadn't even ever been on there before I probably could have got not like I I knew as soon as I made it
That I was like this will get me on that show like
And I by the way, it was my idea just throwing that out. Yeah, that's true
That passion and raw like like knowledge. Yeah, and you're like otherworldly like like if you have a lot if you're doing a lecture
That's something you care deeply about and you have a lot to say. Yeah, so it's you just dumping your best shit in the entire world
Which is why does anybody want to hype like any lectures?
They have planned because like we've never announced any I think before like way ahead of time
That's like the guilty gear one
But I think the guilty gear one got like hype by being mentioned beforehand and I that one did for sure
I'm gonna go ahead and say this mine because I want to encourage everybody to go listen to this music in the meantime
So that it'll be extra rewarding when I explain it
I want to do a lecture on the entire lore of the first five Coheed and Cambria albums
So that's a good one if you want to go listen to Coheed and get into their music and maybe learn a little bit about the lore
Before I fucking open it up and make you realize how fucking insane it is
Yeah, there you go
Well, I I mean I still want to hype I want to hype tails gets trolled. That's coming out real soon. Oh, yeah
It's almost done. It's almost but the time you hear this. Maybe it'll be out
It might be out by the time this is out. Maybe mm-hmm
Other than that, I don't know what else I want to do like lecture
I really wanted to do a lecture on the Digi clips
But when I went to go and like look up the that's the thing where where the people thought that the Digimon world was becoming real
Right, but when I went and I looked into it
Could not like find
Like I just could not find like the info that I remembered reading about it before so I couldn't confirm any of the stuff
I remembered about it, you know, I bet you should you should spend some deep dive time
Try to see if you can pull that up because hey anything that means like you've told me much about that like it's
I remember so much, but like when I went to go find it. I was like, where did it all go?
There was so much there was it's it's got it might be somewhere it might be buried in like a something awful thread somewhere is my best guess
I just hope it still exists like I pray. Yeah
And if you can if you can capture it in lecture form it'll exist for all time so that would be great just for historical
For me to do would be home stuck and I do do that, but I feel like yawn
Chief was already there. I don't need you that but I just came with us just now
Hmm. I like like what I like to do about lectures is stuff that is like influenced me and like you know
Wasn't my childhood and that like stuck with me and like it like made me feel a certain way or yeah
I'm part of my mythos human history lecture until nation. Obviously, so what I could do is like an explain
Like tf2 because you have to like like not like the yeah
Like like like the meta lore of tf2 it's descent into fucking retardation
And how was the greatest game of all time? That's uh, maybe that's a pretty good idea
It's interesting because I because I have like almost like three thousand hours. Are there like human characters you can mention in this
Okay, good. Yeah, yeah, gay banool
Yo, I actually I have literally already put together a list of future lecture ideas with with various degrees of
Their viability and how much research needs to be done for each one
I I'm not gonna share any specific ones right now because I really like to keep things secret before I release them
But what I will say is that people have put a lot of suggestions in like the Kingdom Hearts and the like the new final fantasy one
Which is doing very well. Thanks. Everybody go watch that
And and I'll just say that I have been taking note of the suggestions Metal Gear Solid
That that that's one that has been suggested that is true
That was that was just a guess that actually yeah, that wouldn't people suggest that went a bunch
Historically, but yep, you know, just just more will come in the future at some point everybody. So stay tuned for the radcon four. I
Want to try one radcon four literally with literally no
I want I want to try one
But the the things I have are like massive undertakings
Yeah, one of them is like an entire medium and I'm not sure whether I should follow an artist in the medium or like describe the
Oh shit, what about like here's just a thought like the history of the ps1 just like start to finish
Well, I don't know that that much. Oh, okay. That's just like I wrote over the ps2. I mean sure
It's just I don't know like I don't know what to do
You got to take some time and really think about like I think like for me the most fun is when it's something that's like
That no one else would have thought about it all like yeah
All the lectures have kind of been like like you wouldn't even imagine somebody would do this except for maybe
Well, even something like a final
Fancy would have made a no writer video about then it's not interesting. I mean that's definitely true
But like what makes in my mind the final fantasy and the Kingdom Hearts lectures so
Like like actually good is the fact that like very few people actually know all the details and all these learning about final fantasy, too
Hey, I don't know if you know this but like literally
Right after radcon may and I played through I played the final fantasy 10 and she played the final fantasy 2
And she really I know yeah, just she played through to just on the basis of me
Describing to her what you had described to me that night
Yeah
Emperor and she beat the whole game. I beat 10 finally the first final fantasy game
I ever fucking beat I want to write a whole book about it. There's a lot
Congratulations. Oh dude. I actually the first here's just a little tip it the first serious con panel
I ever went to was a hardcore analysis of Titus in final fantasy 10 as the like literary
Ubermench was the first panel I ever went to
That was right before the hardcore hentai panel at midnight, but go on sorry much this comment on my lecture
Okay, this was too packed with jokes like calm down munchie seriously
Look this is cool at all, but like please tell me more about thoats personality
Give me the real poop point. Yeah. Yeah a little bit a little bit
Hashtag where the means can we now I'm done that was actually a good question on the Twitter
So so way to go my dude way to go pretty great
I asked her better questions in the in the patron lounge and here the two that I got do not answer these
I I got from Miss Olafidekin who gives the worst head in the PC
Is playing with toys as an adult sad in all caps wait
Are you not gonna shake are you gonna say who their names are just give them the credit
They so richly deserve. Yeah deep lorms a little finicky. I said, oh, oh shit
There was one I'm scrolling for right now, but there's one amazing question in there
We also don't answer it, but it was what would you rather have a 20 inch thick two inch long cock?
No, no, sorry. It's a 10 to 10 inch
Who would choose the 10 inch wide cock
Not good. All right. It's not even penis at that point. Oh, I gotta give this guy credit. Fuck. Where was it?
No, God is near the top because we were near the top. It was near the top. I can't I
Damn it. What the fuck is it?
autumn in
Gain maybe
Yeah, and I mean was that it get a me yeah, perhaps it was their question. Yes. Okay. There you go. That's it
Okay, thank you. Sorry for the delay everybody. Okay. We're done. Thanks for listening everybody
Hey patreon.com
Slash the procrastinators give us $1. You're in the patron lounge. We get questions. They are mostly so there you go
Guys, you know, you know, this was a good episode
How's that because the tying flew because we were so like like like in the shit
We are so in the raw shit token up straight up spiritually. Wait. Yeah two hours. I didn't even realize are we still recording?
Is this is this in the show? Yeah, we haven't said goodbye. Okay. Let's start. All right
$5
exclusive videos
We need you to buy our shit watch the episodes. There's 13 of them. I think watch them. They're good
I think there's a new one. No, maybe not whatever. Anyway, thanks for listening everybody. We'll see you later
We'd
Right
Don't wanna do