I want to bless that guy. That son of a-
That son of a-
Son of a-
Hello everybody. We've passed the 333 milestone without any fanfare at all.
We didn't notice.
That's just the way we like it here on the pro-crastinators podcast.
How's everyone doing? We got Never Paint here.
Hello.
Ben Saint and Gibbontake and Never Paint. Just fucking around.
Oh shit.
Oh shit. Can't say profanity in the first minute.
Yeah, you swear. Now everything's gonna go to ruin.
Just replace it with an even worse curse.
I-
I used-
I censored my more extreme profanity
in the Mega Man lecture which I announced.
Ooh.
Twitter posted I have revealed the secret project
was the Mega Man lecture all along.
It is gonna-
It is rendering right now,
but it will be rendering for the next like 4 days.
How the fuck?
I think my computer is just starting to show its age a little bit.
I don't think it should take this long.
It should maybe take half that long. I mean it's an eight hour video.
It's got lots of like, you know,
filters on the-
color filters on the-
on the footage and all that.
It's got like 19 filters.
To look as fucked up as possible.
I just boosted the color contrast and whatever a little bit.
And it's kind of a high-res video.
It's not in 4K.
250, 2560 by 1440.
So, you know, it's a pretty high resolution.
Eight hour video.
So a serious render period is not unexpected.
Although I was hoping-
I was hoping it would be less than a hundred hours,
but oh well.
What can you do?
I'm just over 24 hours into the render now,
and it is just past the 20% mark.
21%?
Yes, we are at 21% mark.
A running commentary.
You should do a stream of the running commentary of the fucking render.
It will be out when this episode comes out.
Unless-
Unless some-
The upload also takes four days.
The upload will definitely not take as long as the render.
The upload will probably only take a few hours.
The only reason it would not be out is if I discover that like,
there was some fuck up
in the footage that I need to like,
oops, I have to render it all over again.
Which I-
I pray to God is not the case,
but you know,
you never know.
There's the naked filter, and you've accidentally
put that on your footage.
Now you're naked.
Uh,
I-
I have a low-
I have a low resolution render that I did beforehand,
I might like, watch it through at some point again.
I already watched it through
basically one time to catch anything
uh, before I made my final corrections.
But what if I fucked something else up during my final corrections?
So now I gotta watch it through again.
How do anybody make big video?
Surely they have secret technology.
Um...
They make many small videos and put them together in the end.
I mean, that's kind of a possible way to do it.
Like, if you've got like, heavily edited things,
it takes longer to render that with the filters on
than it does to stitch two fully rendered video files together
in a video editor.
Ebola, spreading on Twitter, suggested that I render it in chunks
and then stitch them together in Handbrake.
But I looked it up and like, and you can't do that.
Handbrake doesn't do that.
Uh, is there some other program you would use to
like, stitch videos together?
Wouldn't you just have to put them into
in a Vegas timeline and render them?
Take a sewing needle and some thread and then you go.
No, thank you.
Well, I guess we can't talk about the contents
because neither, uh, me or Never Paint have had time to see it.
Oh.
Because it's not existing.
Oh, well, that's okay.
I'll just send you, I'll send it to you right now
and you can watch it real quick.
And then we can reconvene.
Eight-hour episode.
Life reaction.
Eight-hour episode of a reaction to the lecture.
Bonus, is that a, do I smell a bonus episode?
Oh, no.
More like four bonus episodes.
Yeah.
So, I don't know, that's pretty exciting.
Then remember monthly bonus episodes?
That was the time.
It was a thing.
Okay, we don't do them every month anymore.
But, uh, do them sometimes.
Is the Patreon description like updated to that
or does it still say that?
No, I have not really, uh, edited anything on the Patreon.
I think, I think it probably still says that you want to,
like, make PCPHQ real and all that.
Oh god, yeah, it probably does.
That's probably still there.
It probably does.
I don't.
Can't wait.
You can't wait.
It's going to be so much great content.
Oh my god.
It's coming any day now.
It's still coming any day now.
The PCPHQ is now going to be in the metaverse,
so we don't even have to be in the same place.
We can have legs now.
Legs are coming.
Leg.
Why did they not have legs?
Like, that's so weird.
I think the, the technical reason is that they use the cameras
in the headset to track the face
and the arms around it.
The torso doesn't really move that much,
so they don't animate that,
but it can't check your legs,
but I don't know why they can't just add,
like, little fake legs that do an animation.
Like every video game does.
It's sort of baffling why that's a problem.
How is this costing, like, billions upon billions of dollars?
I really don't understand that part of it.
I don't really, um, I mean, I think it looked fine without legs.
I didn't, I didn't miss the legs,
and then they announced legs.
Like, okay, I guess you can add legs if you, if you need to.
It's just sort of like, yeah,
the metaverse being like a new thing that's trying to be made is like whatever.
I'm not that, like, I'm not shocked and appalled by it.
It's just sort of the money.
I'm a little shocked and appalled.
Like, how is he spending all of his money
on something that is VR,
that already exists quite, like, well?
I'm, I'm a little shocked and appalled just because I know that what's on the surface,
it's ha ha, it's stupid.
We already have Second Life.
But underneath, I know that what it is, is like this massive corporation,
this, this billions, like hundreds of billions of dollars valued company
is going to try to throw its weight around to, uh, what's, what's the word?
Uh, to, to basically, um, to like, to like privatize,
like commerce in the metaverse form,
to like take as much of society under its own ownership in the under,
with this Trojan horse of this,
Yeah, the whole, the whole stuff would like,
oh, you can purchase a property on the metaverse,
get yours today.
It's very, it's very, it's actually extremely sinister.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
All I can hope is that I'm not forced to do it.
Yeah.
Cause I don't want to.
It's just some video about how like unsuccessful it is that there's only like a few hundred people online
in the biggest hubs at the time.
And it's a very, it's a very small community that is not,
that's not really happening anything in there.
I mean, I just, I hope it stays that way.
Um, I can see it being like, oh, we're a big stupid business
and we are stupid business people.
So we've got the, the, we've got so much money.
So we're going to buy like the biggest, most state of the art meeting rooms,
uh, possibilities so we can have meetings from multiple locations
and they buy the metaverse VR headsets
and they have a meeting room where people put the headsets on.
I could see like one.
That's about like the extent of like the user base for the metaverse.
I can understand one like gullible tech bro, like convincing another.
You know, like, no, this is the future, man.
This is the future.
And it's like, yeah, yeah, the future.
Uh, uh, like a, like a mind virus spreading from one, uh, from one dweeb to another.
And like maybe one of those dweebs happens to be like the boss of some Fortune 500 company or something.
But like putting on your VR headset to fucking do commerce is just not,
nobody wants to do that.
So it's not a significant benefit.
Like more so than like zoom.
Like the ability to talk to people across the world with video is already like most of the job.
Yeah, it really does.
Now they should focus on hologram technology and have like this thing that they have in a Star Wars pre-quest
where they have the conference room and then as some people as hologram sitting in their chairs.
That's way techier and prettier.
Let's try that.
VR is, VR is fine.
I don't really use it because it's like clunky.
Like they have the Oculus Rift.
I played a little bit with it.
I haven't touched it in a long time because like, I don't need to set up a whole like room space for it or whatever.
Uh, it takes a lot of,
Wasn't like a Kickstarter goal at some point?
Yeah, for the, I think it was for the Vapors 2 Kickstarter.
No, it was one of the Vapors Kickstarter.
There was a stretch goal because I just needed an extra stretch goal.
I was like, uh, uh, if I hit this goal, I'll buy an Oculus Rift and then I did.
It has nothing to do with anything, but like, it would be nice to have one.
We did play it at Radcon 3 though.
No, for Radcon 3.
It was a misanthropony meme, wasn't it?
The Oculus Rift.
Yes, yes, that's right.
It was because he said at the time I was making like 300 something dollars on Patreon.
Which is enough to buy an Oculus Rift every month.
It's right.
It's very funny that like, that's how you conceptualize value.
Um, just like, I guess, I guess he looked at that number and like the first thing he thought of that costs about that much is a VR headset.
As far as we thought the switch came on.
Oh yeah.
Damn.
Um, yeah, it feels like the switch just came out.
I can't believe it's been like, it's been like four years.
Seven years.
Seven?
Shut up.
I think it's true.
Don't scare me like.
It's not.
Unless it is, because I don't know.
Did it come out in 2017 or something?
No.
I think so.
When?
17 or 18.
I mean, it feels about that old.
Like, um, what came out initially.
There was arms and like the, the weird like, oh, it's got the controllers have like motion sensor in them.
So you can sort of feel like haptic feedback.
You can feel a little ball bearing moving around.
There's like a little game.
You're right.
2017.
Yeah.
And that was all it had.
And then like Labo was later.
Okay.
Five years.
Yeah.
So that lecture video that is coming out, is that accessible for people who know nothing
about Mega Man?
Is that like complete beginner's guide?
The, the, the goal of it is explains, um, it explains the, the lore.
Like as it is, as it is expressed in the games themselves.
It's like how it's like what's what lore is there in every individual game in the whole
series.
So if you, if you just want to know like what's in the Mega Man games stories, it explains
it to you, it doesn't cover like, okay, it doesn't cover like, uh, alternate tellings.
Like, like there's like cartoons and manga and stuff.
And they're all like kind of similar to the games, but they're all a little bit different.
So I had to, I was like, I don't talk about any of that.
I'm just focusing on like the games themselves.
Uh, yeah.
And that was enough to talk about.
For eight hours.
Yes.
Um, uh, you know, I, uh, I was thinking, I was thinking, um, I, the, the, we were on
the subject of that, I don't want, uh, I guess we're only 15 minutes into the episode.
I'm not monopolizing it yet.
But, um, I did want to say that I have, um, you know, I bought a lot of stuff to make this
lecture.
I had to buy a new microphone.
I had to buy a bunch of like lights.
Uh, I had to buy like, like, uh, tripods and like light stands and stuff.
So I like, I like invested.
I like invested some money into like setting up my, the ability to like produce a lecture
like this because I could not have done it with just stuff I had lying around.
Uh, uh, my, my, I was, I was rewriting my Patreon.
Like yesterday and then this morning because I am sort of, um, hoping, I say so at the
end of the lecture, I say like, I'm, I'm hoping that like I can sort of make lecture making
kind of like a pillar of my, uh, uh, online presence going forward.
I kind of want to, I kind of want to structure it around like, okay, I have like patron goals.
I'm going to, I'm going to, it's now that I have the stuff to make it, I'm going to be
like using my Patreon money to like hire an editor.
This one I edited all by myself and it was a nightmare.
So if I make another one in the future, which I hope I will, uh, I'm going to, I'm going
to like pay an editor to do like some of the, of the grunt like, like rough editing for me.
Uh, and stuff like that.
And I'm going to, um, what's the other thing?
Oh yeah, I'm going to have, um, like patron goals.
I decided that if I, if I get a hundred patrons, I'm going to like do a poll and I'm going to
like vote on a, on a topic for me, whatever they want.
Uh, that'll be funny.
And, uh, I'm, I'm, I'm really hopeful.
I'm really hopeful that the video does well, uh, because, uh, I've sort of like, I don't know,
I guess I've kind of staked, I guess I've kind of staked my, my plan for like the future
of my self as a content creator on like doing, doing more stuff like this.
So if it doesn't work out, that's a little bit of a sunk cost.
Uh, that's all I have to say.
The eight hour tag definitely is appealing to people, I think.
Like that makes it stand out a lot.
To some, yeah.
I mean, for, for me, I would see that and I'd be like, hell yeah.
Yeah.
I know it's not everybody's cup of tea, but, uh,
I think it's plenty of people's cup of tea because it's so popular and so lucrative for
everyone who does it.
Fucking, um, Wendigoon and like Quentin reviews put out like six hour videos and everybody
loves it.
So everybody knows Shea Mei is a seven hour, uh, Omega Ruby.
Yeah.
Video.
When I first heard about that, that was a big deal that like people talked about that.
It just came kind of, I was actually relieved.
I was relieved that I hit eight hours instead of seven so I could be longer than Shea Mei's
now.
It has to get longer and longer every time you do one of these.
I'd be more and more impressive.
I would not necessarily have to make them all eight hours long.
Uh, but I also have no idea.
I don't know what my next one would be.
Like say, say like the video does well, but I don't do,
but I don't immediately reach like a get a hundred new patrons.
Like that's fine.
I'd still do another one.
I would just pick the topic myself, but I have absolutely no clue what it would be about.
Uh, um, that's it.
That's all I have to say.
I will, I'd think of something.
Make a lecture about making gummies.
Just doing your kitchen.
That doesn't need to be a lecture.
That doesn't need to be a lecture actually.
I feel like you've talked about that for like two years on the PCB.
Can't squeeze an eight hour video out of that.
Uh, no.
Too bad.
Uh, I don't think so.
Uh, I could just read it reading all my old notes about like failed failed.
Then tie a lore.
It would be so boring.
Oh my God.
So first I did it like this and then it was bad.
So then I did it like this and it was a little bit better,
but it was still bad and then I did it like this.
First I did sheet gelatin and then I tried four sheets,
but then I tried three sheets, but then I tried four sheets again,
but with less water, but then I tried three sheets,
but with more water, then I switched to powdered gelatin.
Oh, what a twist.
Everyone's like, oh my God.
He switched to powdered gelatin.
That's my secret ingredient.
What?
The whole arc started with rejecting powdered gelatin and going all fancy.
And I thought I was so clever.
Switching to sheet gelatin turned out no.
Powder was the way to go all along.
Surprise twist ending.
You see, if you do that for eight hours, that would be really funny.
Even if I wouldn't want it.
They could go on for more than 40 minutes.
Yeah, yeah.
My hope is that the Mega Man lecture will be interesting all the way through
and not something like that.
The gummy lecture would be, which is just me bad.
And then Mega Man went here and he saw Dr. Light.
Dr. Light said Mega Man died.
That's pretty much the story.
The first eight games, it kind of is just like,
I go through them pretty fast because a lot of them are just like,
the story of this game is Wiley built eight robots and you have to fight them
and then you do.
Okay, that's the story of this one.
And then the next one is a different guy comes in and he made eight robots
and you fight him, but then it was actually Wiley all along
and then you fight him.
Okay, that's the sort of thing.
Anyway, the next game.
Anyway, the next game is powdered Mega Man.
It's got more surface area than the other ones.
So he feels more pain per square inch.
There are some, there are a couple of really wacky things.
Quint, Quint and Rockman Shadow are a really bizarre piece of Mega Man lore
that I'm excited for people to maybe find out about.
I think maybe most people don't know about those too.
There's a part, I'll be honest.
This is embarrassing.
There's a part where I'm describing the story of Mega Man 04
and I literally like almost start crying.
No, that's good.
It's great.
Okay, I'm not like audibly like about to like cry or anything,
but like at the time I remember it be like I could feel like some emotion
and I had to be like, no, I got to calm down.
I can't.
That would be a great thumbnail image.
I kind of remember talking about Mega Man's lore on this board.
I just love the zero games so much.
There's so much better than the rest of them.
I wonder if that's a hot take.
I'm not sure.
I don't think so.
Probably that is Mega Man at the moment.
I feel like I see people talking about Mega Man recently more
than I used to.
You know, this year is the 35th anniversary.
So I think people are saying, people are talking about X9.
Like when is X9 getting announced?
I think people are expecting it.
I don't know if it's actually happening anytime soon.
It's what you should call your video.
Call it like X9 announcement trailer Mega Man.
So people take on it.
I think I'm going to call it something like Mega Man.
Every game's lore exhaustively explained or something like that.
Thoroughly analyzing Mega Man.
Or what is it like frantically rambling for eight hours
about the story of every Mega Man game or something like that.
Type it like a Jane and Niggason video and just call it like Mega Man.
Lower cast.
The Mega Man video.
I guess the audience will know.
The three videos that inspired it were
it was Jenny Nicholson's The Vampire Diaries video.
It was Mike's Unappropriately Unhinged Recap of Pretty Little Liars.
And then it was, what was your name?
Carrie Ken reads Desperately Explaining the Plot of Crescent City
so you don't have to read all 800 pages.
There's a title of that one.
So, you know, a title that communicates desperation, unhingedness, deranged.
It's always very poor.
A sick mindset.
Mental, it meant the themes of mental illness.
You know what you want to see on YouTube.
Yeah.
Well, that was a lot of my week.
You know what else I did this week?
The other big thing this week?
I played Inscription.
What did you think?
I loved it.
Solaru had a Steam key and gave me a free Steam key for it, which was great.
So I played it and it was amazing.
What can I say?
I can't say that much about it.
I can't say everything I would say about it because it's very spoiler sensitive.
But I will say that I knew there would be twists.
But the twists were not what I expected them to be.
And they just kept coming.
And they surprised and delighted me.
Yeah.
Have you talked about this game before?
Because I don't really remember what it was.
Someone in a voicemail I think told me I should play it.
I think.
I had other people recommended it to me before.
So, yeah.
It's funny that you play the game and you have the same response as everyone.
Being like, oh, I can't say anything about it, but it's good.
You really can't.
You've seen the footage.
It's like a card game.
But it's set in a room that you can walk around and explore the room that you're in.
You've seen that.
Is it like Undertale?
Hmm.
I could point out some surface similarities.
But no, not really.
Is there sand?
Yes.
That's the surface similarity I was talking about.
Hell yeah.
I guess it's like I could say.
I mean, the game's, there's a lot more to it.
There's a lot more to it than you think.
Like Frog Fractions?
A little bit.
Yeah, a little bit.
It's almost a little bit spoilery to make the comparison, but a little bit.
Because it's like, if the game is a card game and that's the game,
I generally don't like card games unless they're easy because I always feel stupid and unlucky when I play a card game like that,
where you draw a card and sometimes it sucks.
Well, there's the card game and then there's the room that you're playing the card game in.
And they're both like part of the real game.
Yeah.
The card game part of it, I've played enough, I played a lot of it this week.
I'm still not like, I can't beat it like 100% of the time, but I've definitely gotten better at it.
And, you know, I think it's like, if you, once you learn the game,
you know that there are ways to mitigate randomness.
Before you learn the game, you don't know that.
And then the fact that you have failed to mitigate that randomness means that you get draw a bad hand because you set yourself up to draw a bad hand.
And then you go, oh, well, it's all luck of the draw.
It's a RNG.
But it's not actually.
Hmm.
It sounds interesting.
It's just one of those things, isn't it?
Like a game that is like, oh, it's got so many twists, so many interesting things, you got to play it.
Yeah.
Telling me that already is sort of spoilering the experience of playing the game and finding that stuff out because now I'm going to be waiting until it does something insane.
I mean, I knew there were twists.
I was still surprised.
But you wouldn't be interested in the game if you didn't know that there would be twists, right?
Like it's just a random card game simulator.
It's, I don't know.
Like with a game that has like more to it, if you can sell somebody on like the initial premise of the game to get them interested in playing that and then not telling them about anything special that might happen.
Like I remember when I pitched Outer Wilds to you, Ben, I did not at all mention the time thing.
I just mentioned that it was a cool space game where you explore.
Yeah.
And like all of the things that you learn and left out and I felt like that was it was a pretty good pitch and it got you interested.
Yeah, it was when it was when you said that you have to like adjust your like speed to like match the like celestial body you want to land on.
I was like, oh, what, what kind of game, what kind of game makes you do that?
What the fuck?
So that was that was interesting.
On the surface, Outer Worlds is like really fun just because of the things on the surface.
But then there's the stuff under the surface where it's like, oh, cool.
Oh, interest.
Oh, intrigue.
I'm thinking is this inscription game like the card games really fun once you get the hang of it?
I'll say.
And then also there's weird stuff, but we won't tell you about that until you're playing.
The I have I have actually been playing the like sort of like challenge mode.
Like it's called it's called Casey's Mod, which is which is pretty much just the card game and but with like a slightly different like set of cards and slightly different rules.
I have been playing that which is just the card game and I like it.
It's fun.
What else? What else can I even say about it?
I do I do I do.
Yeah, like like the core the core of the game is the card mechanics and the card game and like it is it is a fun.
In my opinion, it is a fun card game.
I'm not usually into like deck building games.
I guess there's a lot of games that are deck builders and usually when I hear someone describe a game that way it turns me off.
But I enjoyed it in inscription.
So maybe I should be a little more open minded to it in the future.
I prefer dick building games like Minecraft.
You know, you know, I the thing about thing about it, I at some point I realized that oh, actually more cards is bad.
Actually, you kind of want less cards.
Actually, like my decks are like much better when like I try not to get any of the new cards that they offer me when I like deliberately avoid them.
My deck is more consistent and it's better like almost all the time, which is a very sort of funny real realization to have.
I think I learned that quite young when I had like Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
Sure.
I thought if I combined all of these boosters together and I have a huge deck, then there's no way I could lose.
I know that like, yeah, in like Magic the Gathering, you don't want to have like more cards than the like minimum deck size.
It's like it's not good.
I don't know.
I guess I just hadn't didn't I didn't go into like a game like this assuming that that would necessarily still be true.
But it's totally it's still true.
Yeah.
Anyway, thanks Salaru for the for the Steam key.
Yeah, I trying to think of what's what's how it what's what's the what's the what's the most I can say about it to recommend it without without blowing it.
I don't know.
It's like among us.
Elder Scrolls Online.
That's right.
No, I've said no, I've said enough.
I've said I've said too much.
Anyway, that was my week.
That was my week was finishing my video and playing inscription.
Tomorrow's Halloween.
Happy Halloween from the past coming out after right when this comes out.
It's already Christmas almost Thanksgiving Christmas.
Oh, well, you guys don't have Thanksgiving.
No, we don't thank anybody.
No.
So this week I will actually just yesterday I did the gig.
I did the thing I talked about.
Yes.
Playing the music.
The zone.
The game.
The big game.
Big game.
I played.
Wish you were here.
I did the acoustic guitar on that.
I did dig a pony.
The Beatles.
I played George Harrison lead guitar.
Wish you were here.
Is that Oasis or is that the Beatles?
That's Pink Floyd.
Oh.
You fuck.
You fool.
There's an Oasis.
No, there's an Incubus song where the chorus goes, I wish you were here.
And I always when everyone says wish you were here, I think of that song.
But that song, I don't even think that song is called wish you were here.
It's just the line in the chorus.
I wish you were here drinking a beer.
Is that the original?
I hope so.
No.
And then I played a fucking black magic woman.
It's the rhythm guitar for that.
And then.
You couldn't make that song today.
Huh?
You couldn't write that song today.
What?
Cancel culture being how it's like and all.
No, no.
Elon saved us.
I don't even understand.
Huh?
Elon saved us.
Didn't you hear?
We can say such things now on Twitter.
And make songs about it.
Oh, right.
Yes.
You can say black magic now.
I can sing black magic woman.
Yeah.
Finally.
And then I played sympathy for the devil.
And I played the bongos and then the guitar as well.
Bass, bass, bass.
And it was, I was very nervous the whole week leading up to it.
I was shivering.
I was shaking.
Epic.
I was cold sweats adrenaline.
I was like, oh, gee, I hope I don't mess up one note.
I did mess up a note or two, but it doesn't matter.
Once you're on stage, it's fine.
Once you're on stage and the light is blinding you and you're just looking at your guitar
and you're just sort of like doing your thing.
You're like, yeah, I'm here.
I'm just playing.
That's right.
It's fine.
It's the, it's the having to wait and set up all the equipment and then wait for a few
hours.
And it's, oh, it was dreadful.
I couldn't even get drunk because I was, I was afraid that if I got a little bit too
drunk, I would need to piss my pants on stage.
And that's not what I wanted.
So I didn't drink or be anything.
It would probably negatively affect your ability to perform.
I also would probably like chill me out, but yeah, I mean, everyone else is drinking.
Yeah.
Sure.
But yeah, it was a great, it was a great little performance.
I may upload it somewhere.
My mom was there recording a bit on her phone.
So it might have something to put on the give and take channel.
What did you end up wearing?
Clothes.
Oh yeah.
Cause I was wondering about that.
Yeah.
I didn't want to go like, I didn't want to be like drawing attention to myself.
I just wore like a, yeah, just like a shirt, a low cut, like woman's style like t-shirt.
I don't know.
It's just sort of like clothing.
I understand.
Just sort of clothing.
Everyone was wearing clothing.
Just a public shirt with no honor.
It wasn't like a, it wasn't like a big venue with like a lighting guy.
It was like the basement of a pub, but it was a really nice pub.
And they had like old oak tables and like miscellaneous chairs from various sort of eras,
just sort of all in the same place.
That's cool.
And they had good beer and it was nice.
It got very hot.
But now that's done and I'm no longer ever going to go play music.
Except until the next time.
Yeah.
Good riddance.
Thank you to everybody who donated.
I know at least two or three people went to the site.
I think you can still do it.
So I guess we'll put the thing in the description.
But yeah, we raised I think over two grand.
What's it for?
Did you say it's for Alzheimer's?
Parkinson's.
Excuse me.
Parkinson's charity event thing.
Mmm.
And yeah, it was a really, really good night.
The band was great.
I was good as well.
And I feel good about it.
Hell yeah.
God damn it.
Yes, queen.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
Thank you everybody.
Slay.
I did slay.
Nice.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Red.
Oh and I just got done before.
I wish I could have gone.
Yeah.
Maybe next time.
And I guess the only other thing is Halloween decoration.
I just carved the pumpkin.
I carved the pumpkin and I gave it big eyelashes.
Like my new impsona that I made.
Oh, I saw that.
Oh, I saw it.
I did see that.
I think I didn't see that.
I don't know.
Have you heard or watched Hell of a Boss?
No.
It's by Vivian Medrano, the person behind Has Been Hotel.
I've watched that.
Has Been Hotel.
Isn't it said in the same world as Has Been Hotel?
Yeah.
Has Been Hotel is a show that has been like, I don't know, more professionally funded
to be put on more professional like distributors, like something Netflix.
I don't even remember.
But Hell of a Boss was a more independently funded by Merch Sales show set in the same
universe with different characters.
And I love it.
And it's in season two right now.
And it's great.
And I just decided to make an impsona.
Let me get that tweet.
I found it.
It's good.
I like the horns a lot.
Yeah.
It's basically like Homestuck.
But you know, they're cooler looking.
They're cooler looking designs than Homestuck trolls.
I'll say it.
Impossible.
I really like the black and white stripes that is very imputing to me in any animal or
creature or whatever.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
We don't see it.
It's like a theme park close to where I live, where they made a spooky forest and all they
did basically was put up like a bunch of gravestones and also paint all the trees and like black
and white stripes like this.
And it's actually very spooky in that.
Yeah.
That's cool and all.
But let's talk about reploids instead.
No.
Let's talk about it.
Let's talk about reploids and how they just got genocided.
What?
Let's just talk.
Let's talk about how they did a robot genocide in Mega Man Zero.
Did I miss something on the news?
Did something happen?
Did they storm a robot factory?
No.
No, no, no.
Unfortunately, not yet.
Okay.
What are we talking about?
I don't know.
Just sort of the things I've done this week is practicing for the gig, which is now done.
I feel great having done that and Halloween's coming up.
Oh, Clarissa is getting close.
Here's my Clarissa update.
Give us the Clarissa update.
So I was struggling getting stuff done, but I forced myself to work harder.
And I was doing like a work day.
Like I was waking up and being like, okay, no distractions, nothing, no things, nothing.
That's pretty good.
Just not even like a podcast in the background.
I know that this is like a sense that, oh, you can focus with music or a podcast.
No, you really can't.
Not when you're trying to create things.
When you're doing monotonous work, yes, you can.
But when you're trying to come up with a solution to a creative problem,
like how does this character move from this panel so that they're in this panel and like this?
Or what do they say here that's not cringe?
You can't listen to anything.
So I had no distractions at all.
I agree.
I'm fine with everything that is like, whenever I work on something that doesn't involve language,
I'm fine with listening to anything, but as soon as I have to write anything.
Oh, yeah.
As I was going for like the page layout is what I'm getting to the very, very near end of.
I've been like sort of like scribbling down a rectangle of some very like random size
and being like, okay, so in this page, this thing has to happen.
This character's here.
I guess I'll draw them from below because like they're imposing right now and they've got a speech bubble.
I need to fit a speech bubble in there for them to say something.
What do they say?
I have to think of something because if I end up sketching the page and not knowing what they say,
I'll have to fill it with something that sucks.
So I want to make sure I have something that's kind of good and that I can like tweak and make better.
So I have to fill in the speech bubbles as I go and like sound effects and stuff.
And I'm like, ah, speed lines here.
And I'm at the point now where it is at the very final part of the showdown where the winner is determined.
There's only a few pages left and then it's like the epilogue.
What happens after?
I've been waiting for quite a while to see.
I mean, I assume it's Clarissa versus what's the guy with the big hat's name?
The Bandit King?
Yes.
I've been waiting to see how their confrontation would shake out.
So I'm happy to know that that's coming.
It is.
Is that going to be concluding the Clarissa story or do you want to do more with her?
Oh, of course.
I'm going to do more of that.
This is, I mean, initially this was supposed to be, it was supposed to be a short story for the competition,
the physical awards, the manga competition.
And I wrote a story that went far beyond what I could fit into like the 50 page limit.
And so it's going to be probably like 150 to 200 pages at the end of the day, maybe.
I know.
You won't have seen it yet.
So this is a spoiler for you.
But I wore the Lord of Ghosts pin in the lecture and I shouted you out.
I shouted out your website.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's pretty, it's pretty epic.
Hell yeah.
Very spooky.
For just in time for Halloween.
Yes.
Just in time for Halloween.
Very good.
You know, it's funny.
I haven't drawn anything spooky this month.
Yeah, you have so many spooky characters.
I guess you have your two vampire girls.
Yes, I did.
Yeah, you're always wrong.
You're always wrong.
It's hot.
It's every day.
Every day is Halloween for me.
Like, yeah.
She's like a puppy by Christmas.
It's not just for Halloween.
Punk is forever.
You did have the punk profile picture.
Except Halloween or something.
She's a culture, not a costume.
Yes.
Exactly.
Very good.
Yeah.
I don't feel like it's like more punk of a month than it normally is.
So I haven't really thought about like Halloween drawings.
I should draw a little bit, just in my own time, just for fun.
I'm actually working on a kind of Halloweeny character right now.
Oh, yeah.
I want to finish that before tomorrow so I can post it and be in the season.
Like a week ago, I came up with this character that is kind of a zombie girl.
But she has a wasp lava living in her brain.
That is the actual person.
And the girl is just like the suit, the body that the little lava pilots.
That's hideous.
Yes.
No, but it's like in a cute way though.
In a cute way.
He's got a cute kind of brain parasite.
Yes.
Yes, exactly.
Oh my god.
Have you seen a little brain slug?
Have you seen that it's like a slug or a snail that has a worm?
No, I hate that image.
I hate that.
I hate it.
With it like pulsating inside of its like eye stalks?
Yeah, that's the worst.
That's the worst.
I love that stuff.
It's kind of cool looking, but like what I actually think about it, it's like, yeah,
it's like the most horrifying thing I've ever seen.
It's the most existential sort of horrifying like it's using the slug as a suit to perform
like acts of gaslighting of other bugs or whatever it was doing.
What was it doing?
It was like pretending to be a type of thing so that something would come over to it.
And so it could grasp them or poison them or something.
I didn't want to look at it any longer.
I left immediately.
I don't even remember.
I thought it was just like eating it from the inside.
It like moves the snail to someplace where like a nutrient rich place to die or something.
Well, the caption was something like using like the slug to mimic something, mimic some
action.
The slug or snail could perform or some, I don't know, it was doing something that was
like gaslighting the birds to come and eat it so that they could kill the birds.
I don't like it.
I didn't like it.
Gross.
Is it like the hope is that the bird will eat it and then the parasite will be inside
the bird?
I don't know.
I didn't read it properly.
Some intrepid explorer can go find that post and puke and then read it.
I just posted Maggie.
That's her name.
That's a good name for that.
The idea was that like Maggie is just like an open cranium.
You know, it's just like a door.
She can open that if she has to leave the body for maintenance or something.
Okay.
I see.
So this is more like a flesh mech.
Yeah.
Than it is a person.
It's ratatouille.
It's gross.
It's actually cheesy, I think commented that.
It's more realistic.
What if ratatouille was real?
It's mega-goody.
Mega-goody.
I was also kind of thinking of attack on Titan when I drew it.
Like big flesh monsters that they sit in.
Why are they so gross?
Do you know about like wasp lava and what they do to caterpillars and stuff?
Jesus.
They fuck them up.
I know some things about that.
I know that like, you know, they put a fucking worm in their body and it eats them from the inside
and pilots them like a mech or whatever.
Yeah.
Yeah, more or less.
Like they, I don't know, they release some kind of chemical in them that like makes them
behave in a certain way and let them growl to a space.
And then the lava that are inside tell the caterpillar to make one of its cocoons to
protect the lava.
So it's literally like brain controlled to protect the offspring of this wasp.
And then the wasp lava feed on the caterpillar and leave it behind.
Makes the cocoon, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
You know, I wonder if like, like insects have, because they're so small, their brains are
like very simple, like electronic pulses.
They have like five buttons and the little maggots can push the little buttons.
It's like turn left, turn right.
Very simple to operate.
If they try to take over a human, they'll be like, ah, fuck, this is too complicated.
Well, they made a whole book series about that.
It's called The Animorphs.
Perhaps you've heard of it.
I haven't.
Only there was a lecture or something to watch.
If only someone could explain in painstaking detail what happens in The Animorphs.
Wait, I was going to say, did you know, I learned this recently that like figs exist because
like wasps like lay larvae in them?
Like a fig, like a fig fruit has to have like a wasp egg laid in it.
It has to like hatch like a clutch of wasps.
What?
Yeah.
It's like, I read this somewhere.
I think it was real.
They have like a symbiotic relationship with wasps.
I basically know what you're talking about.
I thought it was like the wasp goes to fertilize the plant and then it gets trapped inside and
the plant eats the wasp and then the wasp is part of the plant.
When you eat a fig, you're eating a dead wasp or something.
I don't think so.
I don't think figs would be a kind of a response.
If they're cannibal plants or meat eating figs.
Everything's so fucking gross.
Well, here's an image that supports to explain it.
Yeah, I think this is just part of like the life cycle of the fig, which is like wasps basically like pollinated.
That was kind of right.
Yeah.
The pollen laden wasp enters the circuitous root of the fig, lays eggs inside fig and
then flower ovaries contain wasp larvae.
So that's kind of just any pollination of a plant, but with the extra step that the
insect also leaves its larvae in there.
That's neat.
Oh, so it is.
No, I was kind of right.
The babies, they hatch, but they try to dig out and they can't get out and they die.
Yeah.
Like the like they're still sort of in there or like their bodies kind of like become like
part of the fruit or something.
This is why I do not eat fruits.
I know I have.
I've eaten a fig like once.
I've eaten a fruit once.
I've eaten a fruit, I swear.
You ever eat a, you ever eat a, you ever eat a pomelo?
Oh, I love pomelo.
What?
Fuck you.
Yeah.
No, they're great.
They're amazing.
No, they're not.
You're stupid.
Okay.
Pomelos are just, pomelos are just worse grapefruits.
So like you hate tomatoes and you hate pomelos.
I'm sorry.
I don't hate, I don't hate tomatoes, but I wouldn't eat, I wouldn't just eat a tomato
whole.
I wouldn't just like eat one by itself.
I would.
I love tomatoes.
They're not bad.
I had a tomato salad like basil and mozzarella.
With like mozzarella cheese.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's basically eating whole tomatoes.
But then you have the, you have the mild, the mild flavor of the mozzarella, you know,
kind of cutting against these sort of like acidity of the tomato.
And that's good.
But like, I don't know.
I know some people will just eat a tomato and.
Yeah, I want one of those.
I like that.
Oh, some pomelo is great because it's one of these fruits that really gives you something
for your money.
Like it's.
A pomelo?
Yeah, because they're giant and you can feel like an entire lunchbox.
You are a pretender.
You've never eaten a pomelo because if you did, you would know that it's all rind.
You open up the pomelo and it's just like all white, fluffy rind.
There's a little bit of fruit in the middle.
I think there might be different kinds of tomatoes and you might have like had a bad
one.
No, they're all like that.
Shit, American pomelos.
No, my American pomelos are the best in the world, even though I hate them.
There is a lot of the white stuff in them, but there's still like a lot of flesh, too.
Okay.
These pictures that I'm finding do have significantly less rind than I remember.
Oh, pomelo is a fucking app.
You piece of shit.
Stop making apps named after things.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Pomelos.
Pomelos are just to me.
They're just a grapefruit, but they don't taste like anything.
They have less flesh and they don't taste.
They're like sour, bitter, sweet.
I guess.
Sometimes they're bad, but most of them they're not.
In my opinion, they just straight up improved the pomelo by crossbreeding it to create the
grapefruit.
The grapefruit is perhaps my favorite fruit, and so I owe the pomelo a great debt for
being a part of its genesis.
However, now that it's done me that favor, it can fuck off forever and die.
I never want to see one again.
There is a lot of rind in the picture.
It's superior descendants.
Yeah, that's a bit much.
Okay, well, get off my podcast.
I think citrus fruits are weirdly inconsistent in taste.
That's why I don't like buying them usually.
Sometimes they get the same bag of oranges and they're great, and next time they're bad.
Sometimes when they eat a mango, certain mangoes, occasionally like one bite of the mango,
will have a weird pine tree floral flavor to it.
Interesting.
It's not the whole mango.
It's just one little bits here and there, and it's just not every mango.
It's just certain mangoes.
Why did I get on this subject?
You know what?
I said pomelo.
I didn't even mean to say pomelo.
I meant to say persimmon.
What is that?
It looks like a tomato, but it doesn't taste like one, and you eat it with a spoon.
Is it?
Are these those black tomatoes?
No, no, here.
They look like this.
Oh, actually, we call them khaki.
I don't know why, but we do.
They're more fushy.
They're sweet.
They're sweet like, I don't know what they taste like.
They don't taste like a tomato.
I don't know.
I had one once and it was okay.
My favorite tomato is the beef tomato or whatever the fuck that is.
Beef steak?
The big beefy ones that you can...
Yeah, with all flesh.
With more flesh and less juice.
I guess that's what they are.
Yeah, a beef steak tomato or a good beef steak tomato, it's like a regular tomato.
You cut it open and it's got these chambers inside that are full of beef.
A beef steak tomato doesn't really have much of that.
So it's ideal for slicing and putting on a steak.
That's also my favorite kind of tomato, because the only context I really particularly like tomatoes is the slice of them.
What about sweet cherry tomatoes?
I don't like them.
Cherry tomatoes are pretty good in a tomato sauce with a bunch of other stuff.
I don't like raw, cold cherry tomatoes just because it's too much moisture.
If I wanted a drink, I would have a drink, you know what I mean?
No, I could eat like a whole cucumber just because of drinking glass of water.
I knew my family would eat cherry tomatoes.
It would snack on cherry tomatoes and I just thought they were gross.
I don't like them.
There was this?
It's very, very simple Italian recipe of beef tomatoes in olive oil and that's it.
You just eat beef tomatoes with olive oil and it's great, actually.
You don't need to do anything.
Maybe a bit of seasoning, a bit of salt, but I had that one.
So it's like, how does this not a normal thing we do all the time?
When you're talking about like, oh, I'm too lazy to cook a good meal.
Just get a tomato and cut it up, put it oil on it.
I'm not too lazy to cook a good meal.
I am.
Depends on the meal, I guess.
I discovered, wait, I discovered a new food that I love, but I like it too much so I can't get it anymore
because if I get it, I will just eat all of it and it's unacceptable.
The last time this happened, it was nuts.
I decided I can't eat nuts anymore because I will just eat the whole bag.
The new one is Wegman's bacon rise pizzas.
Wegman's bacon rise frozen pizzas.
You know, nuts were a better idea.
Nuts will damage your colon.
I guess if you eat a whole bag, yeah.
Wegman's bacon rise frozen pizzas, they're just, they're huge.
They're giant.
They cost $4 and I can't buy them.
Yeah, they're like $4.99.
Oh, bake and friends, I see.
I was trying to think what the bacon.
Not bacon, not bacon rise.
No, no, no, no.
But it's like more than a whole day's calories for $4.99, which is good.
It's like a whole day's calories for a family of five and you have seven of them every day.
But it's not good.
It's good for the money, but it's not good for me because I don't want to eat that many calories in a day.
So it's a, here's what I should do.
Here's what I should do to be scrupulous.
I should like under eat one day and then use those calories surplus that I saved up
and use them on the next day so I can eat more the next day so I can make a Wegman's bacon rise pizza.
And that can be my food for that day.
Go on a diet for like a month and then eat pizza for a month.
I'll go on a diet for a whole month and then I'll spend the next month.
I'll eat nothing but bacon rise pizzas every day.
It's genius.
It's calories in, calories out.
The math checks out.
I'm sorry.
You'll probably be sick of it and you never have to do it again.
You know what?
You could take this further.
You could say the first half of my life.
I will not eat anything.
And the second half I will gorge myself constantly.
Yeah.
You know, the first part of your life is not like you don't need much food in there.
Like you're small.
You just stay small.
Get that sun.
Get that sun in you.
Drink some water and then eat when you're like 40.
That's right.
It's the circle of life, baby.
That's how I'm going to raise my kid.
So that one.
Speaking of pizza.
I left my favorite pizza behind in Canada because I came back and favorite pizza.
Yeah.
In Canada.
It was in Canada actually like in downtown right under the CN tower.
Like there's a little pizza place.
I think it's called scatter bush or something.
And they have, they have these pizzas that like, of course, like, I mean, it's, it's like
a kind of nice Italian bar restaurant thing.
And have these pizzas that are very properly baked, but they have like handmade, freshly
made mozzarella on them.
So there's a guy in a bag.
You can see how he like, like twists and like pulls the mozzarella and turns into balls
and stuff.
Pretty nice.
That was great.
His name was Remy.
We got told that his name so that we know that he's the Red from Rutter 2 actually.
And, and it was just like a very like kind of simple like mozzarella cheese pizza, but
it had like sun dried tomato bits on it.
And an olive like in basil oil over it.
Like just a few sprinkles.
That was so delicious.
I know we went there like, like three times in the three months I was in Canada.
And I, I don't know, I don't know when I'm ever going to go back.
There was, um, there's a pretty good, there's a pretty good, like slightly, it's not like
super fancy, but it's a little, it's a little bit fancy pizzeria kind of near me.
And I've had the other pizza like twice and it's very good, but they were the, you know,
at, um, at Radcon three, we got a bunch of pizzas and somebody, some, it might have been
my suggestion actually, I might be an idiot because someone suggested pineapple and ham.
And I didn't like it.
Uh, but this, this place, I got, uh, I got a pineapple and pepperoni pizza at this fancy
place and it was actually really great.
And I really liked the pineapple.
The difference was that it was cooked better.
It was cooked more thoroughly and the pineapple sort of like kind of melted and caramelized
a little bit into the cheese and it made it so much better.
The Domino's fucking, fucking raw, raw pineapple chunks on top of your pizza.
Nightmare.
Um, these other guys know how to do it.
Yeah.
I don't really eat frozen pizza or like cheap, uh, fast food pizza anymore if I can avoid
it.
Like even a restaurant or like handmade, we do that in our apartment sometimes, like
handmade, make the dough and, uh, sauce and stuff.
That's also good.
We have a pizza stone in the oven.
My dad used to sometimes make pizza and it's, it's funny in hindsight because like, I don't
know, it was so, I didn't really understand like why it was so different.
Like it had, it bore almost no resemblance to like, you know, pizza you would buy from
a pizzeria.
And now I've watched, you know, I've watched some cooking videos.
I've watched like, uh, Adam Raguse is like how to make, uh, you know, a New York style
pizza.
And now I understand, oh, there's actually a lot of like very specific processes that
go into making the kind of pizza you get from like a pizzeria.
Uh, you can't, you kind of can't just like fuck around in your kitchen and make it.
Uh, so no wonder.
I mean, it was still good.
I still liked pizza night.
There's very different kinds of dough.
I think, isn't it like mostly the oven?
That's the hard part to get right.
Like the immense heat that you need to get like the right, crispy, uh, the blackening
of the bread or whatever.
Yeah, that's, that's a big part of it.
Also the kind, the kind of cheese, the whole, the whole, uh, fat mozzarella is like kind
of hard to find.
Uh, although the pizza stone makes it a little easier because it's like, it gets really hot
and burns it from under.
Oh yeah.
And a pizza stone or a paddle, right?
Like you can't, you know, if you could, if you just cook it on a baking sheet like my
dad did, you know, it's not going to cook the same way.
Yeah.
But it's fine.
No, I'm not complaining.
I'm still.
No, I'm hungry.
Sorry, dad.
Listen.
Uh, this is the food cast for some reason.
Um, did I mention that I'm making, I'm making Halloween gummies.
I'm making Halloween gummy worms.
Oh, you haven't.
I'm making some orange.
Oh yeah.
I have, I have them, I have them laying out on a paper towel right now to sort of like
dry out so I can put them into a cup together and they won't all become glued together.
Uh, I tried to make orange and black ones.
I didn't have like enough food coloring to make them like black black.
So the black one just came out brown, but you know what?
It's fine.
This, they look good with the orange.
So it's all right.
Uh, it's spooky.
I don't know.
It's spooky.
It's worms, but they're pumpkin worms.
Worms like what will devour you in the gray food.
Are you two doing anything for Halloween?
Going to a party?
I think I'm treating.
I think, I think people might be, I think people are hanging out at Munchie's house for some
kind of Halloween thing.
I think I'll probably be there most likely.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm going to go see someone a friend and at home we're going to decorate and stuff.
I don't really do like parties anyway.
So it's just going to be a chill.
No scary tonight.
Just, just a bit of stuff.
I guess I'm going to wear my gulf get up.
I'm going to wear my full gulf get up that I have now with the corset and everything.
I just remembered.
I think, yeah, I think the, the, the Munchie place, I think they're doing like scary movies
and I hate scary movies.
That's not true.
Sometimes I like them, but I think I'm, I think more that more often I don't like them.
I like them except when I'm alone and I'm all alone in my apartment this whole weekend,
including Halloween.
And I'm like, I, this is your Netflix show.
Um, like you know, the Toros, uh, cabinet of curiosities or something.
It's like an oral anthology and I watched the first episode and was pretty good.
And I want to watch more, but then I was alone.
I'm like, um, that's exactly.
Yeah.
Maybe I watch it when everyone's back in Halloween's over.
Yes.
I liked the witch.
I did not like Midsommar.
I did not like drag me to hell.
Like, you didn't like it or were you like grossed out or too horrified to enjoy it?
I just, I thought it was extremely well, those are all, those are three very well made
movies that I, two of them I just didn't enjoy.
They, they, they, they, they gave me, I had the experience that the director wanted me to have
and it was not an experience that I appreciated having.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Okay.
I guess I get it.
I, I like the feeling of being like scared or tense when in a scene in a film, but like,
I don't really like sitting down knowing that I'm about to feel tense.
I like, I don't sit, I don't put on a scary movie for that experience.
I find video games are way better because like it's, it's not just that something's going to happen.
Something's going to go boo at you.
It's that something's going to go boo at you if you turn the corner and you have to be the one to turn
the corner and then you'll scream loudly and you throw the control across the room.
Like that, that feels fun.
And, and I don't know, watching a film and I'm just sort of like, yeah, I'll pause it.
I'll leave.
I mean, I don't need to finish it.
Yeah.
Have you guys seen like the, wait, what's he called Jacob Geller YouTube videos?
Video essays?
I, I hate that guy.
I think I know.
You hate that guy?
No, I don't really hate him, but I don't, I don't like his speech pattern.
Did he, did he have that one video where it's like the thumbnail was, they weren't disabled and then it was like.
No, that's, um, no, not, not Patrick Willem.
Uh, that's, uh, and shit.
I know who you're talking about.
Yeah.
I never clicked on it.
I remember that video, but I don't know who it was.
It's the guy, it's the guy who did, he did that video about Harry Potter and the Cursed Child.
Everybody did that.
Oh.
There's so many video essays on everything.
Everybody, everybody and anybody who's done everything.
Yeah, that guy's not really interesting.
Um, but Jacob Geller, um, I've been watching his videos for the past two days because they're kind of spooky.
I don't know.
They have a, they have a weird atmosphere and he keeps talking about horrifying existential things.
Um, he released a new video about like deep sea creatures and like the stories that people tell about like crackings and horrifying things.
And he often combines that, uh, like little, um, snippets about indie video games about horrifying things.
And that's cool.
I like that he includes or he always includes like literature and video games and, um, different kinds of art and all kinds of mediums in the stories.
Oh, I know this.
Yeah, I watched the one he did about the Simpsons intro.
Oh yeah, that one's also good.
Um, yeah, he's all right.
It's just sort of like, yeah, it is that is Austin McConnell.
Austin McConnell is the very disabled guy.
But yeah, this guy, Jacob Geller, there's something about like, I don't know, heady topics in a thumbnail that I'm like, oh my God, this is going to be like, this is going to be so like epic.
And I'm like, well, that's why I don't want to click on it.
Like, it's like, oh, the, you know, the big, the big talk about the big thing, very serious.
I'm like, oh, God, you know what?
Fuck this.
I'm going back to German.
Um, Jacob Geller's cadence speaking is like, it's almost like he's doing like a spoken word poem in the way that he's like so modeling in his delivery and I find it really annoying.
I have no, I have no hate towards this sort of style.
It's just sort of, I don't know.
I feel like I've gone past.
I've grown out of enjoying taking, taking, taking videos seriously.
I kind of, I kind of get what you mean.
I think I get it.
Yeah, I don't really, I don't really like religiously follow any like YouTuber anymore.
I don't mean to, I don't mean to shit on your YouTube choices.
I watched lots of stupid crap that I'm ashamed of.
Yeah.
No, no, no, no hate.
Um, what's, what's the worst, what's the worst thing I watched?
The Mega Man lecture.
That's, that's, I didn't even have one frame.
I wonder, I wonder, I wonder if, I wonder if, I wonder if my, what's the word?
My divisive lefty politics will, will, will enrage the existing Mega Man YouTuber community.
I wonder, I wonder if Twitter, I wonder if Reploid Revo will be mad that I, that I'm against the cops.
I doubt it, but that would be really funny.
There's, there's, there's a, there's a guy, there's a guy who has a channel called Reploid Revo and he just, he makes Mega Man videos and uh, he's, he's fine and all, but uh, I don't know.
He's probably, he's a libertarian, he's gotta be a libertarian and I know that because his, his OC is yellow and black, just like the Gadsden flag.
So that's the tell.
I'm joking.
Um, yeah, just yellow is just a sus color, just a sus color, I'm sorry.
I'm trying to think of any yellow characters.
There aren't any, there aren't any, I'm sorry.
Uh, April O'Neill.
Bumblebee.
Pikachu.
Pedophiles, all of them.
What?
I missed what you said.
I said they're, I said they're all pedophiles.
Oh no, Pikachu.
Pikachu, how could you?
That's why it's been with Ash.
It was too much power.
He had too much, he had too much, he had too much unchecked power and too much access to kids.
You know what, it's a, it's not a good combination.
You know, we should have, we should have done something.
I mean, Ash has been a kid for like 20 years, so.
Yeah.
And who do you think kept him that way?
It was kids.
Yeah.
You know what, it makes a lot of sense when you think about it.
Uh, um, who boy?
He's, there's only, I saw another Mega Man video, it was posted like a couple weeks ago, and it was like every Mega Man game, but it was only an hour,
pitifully the video was only an hour long, and it only covered the regular Mega Man games, like one through 11.
So like, that's not even that many games, bro.
Why, why would you, why would you even bother?
Was, I don't forget who, I forget who posted that one.
But I saw that.
I started listening to it, and I was like, oh no.
Oh no, he's saying some of the things that I said.
Oh no, some of the facts that he's repeating are the same facts that I repeated.
Oh fuck.
I couldn't keep, I couldn't keep going.
I was going to be sick.
Turn it off, I couldn't take it.
That feel when somebody has also talked about media that was public.
What are you, could have been seen.
You can't review this, this game.
Uh, I was going to, I already made a review of that game on my side, on my part of the channel, on my...
Don't do it, Critic, it's too bad.
Don't do it.
No, you'll, you'll, you'll cause a time paradox.
It's called, the one I saw, it's called The Journey Through the Entire Mega Man Classic Series by Gilly the Kid.
Beat me to the punch by two weeks, but it's okay, cause mine's bigger.
Yeah, somebody asked me recently if I wanted to like make a podcast or something about the new Tolkien show.
Uh, and I felt similarly that, like, this has been so thoroughly covered by now.
Like, everyone's made a podcast about this.
Do I have anything to say about this that other people haven't said better?
It is just sort of like, the quality and quantity of stuff talking about media on YouTube is quite high.
So, like, yeah, if somebody has talked about it, there's a chance that, like, many people have talked about it
and somebody has done a lot of work and put a lot of effort to make a really good video.
And it's like, well, I mean, fuck, what the hell can I add to this?
Oh, I would say that, like, the thing that would drive me to say, yes, you should definitely do a podcast about it,
is if, like, you were, you were hearing what people were saying about the show and you, like, disagreed with it,
or you thought that, like, the discourse was lacking.
Hmm. Or just, yeah.
Maybe it's also, like, retapping the discourse, maybe, like, going back and showing a different side.
Oh, my God. Just like, just like the Gibb and take a weekly analysis roundup.
What were they called?
Analysis assemblage.
Analysis assemblage, yes. You got to do that, but for Tolkien podcasters.
Oh, God.
Rings of power.
Oh, no. I really don't have time for that.
No, no, no, no.
I stopped doing that because I had to, like, watch people's reviews.
And I was like, you know what? This sucks.
I don't want to do this.
I don't want to go onto the My Little Pony, Brony fucking reviewer subreddit and find all of the Brony reviews of the episode
and look through all of them and being like, did anybody have anything interesting to say?
I guess this person did. Fuck.
But isn't that what you had to do to make those videos is find the reviews and watch them? Yeah.
I had to find them because, like, that's, yeah, it was just the easiest place because everyone was posting there.
Well, I just came across too many people who were very boring.
I think there was a person who did that with the, like, entire anime tube,
like, like watching all anime analysis videos that would come out in a week and making a video about that.
Oh, are you talking about Koon something?
Is it Caribou Koon? Yeah. I remember watching that years ago, maybe.
I think he's still doing it.
I don't know. There aren't any anime YouTubers left.
Like, that I watch. Are you? I used to watch that.
That you watch, that you watch. Okay. No, sure. Yeah.
I mean, I think Jeff is still around and does his thing.
Isn't Giga around? Giga is around and Giga is part of the podcast that they do.
Does he still make, like, anime videos? Probably.
I've never watched Giga ever, so I don't know.
I liked his comedy a few years ago. They were pretty funny, but also a little stupid.
Sure. That's comedy sometimes is.
Fuck, were we talking about? How did we get on this?
We could talk about tomatoes. Let's go back.
That's the most important topic.
Wait, I could talk about...
What if he carved a tomato for Halloween? How difficult would that be?
If it's one of these big meaty beefy ones, that would work.
You put a little candle in it.
You just put some gasoline in it, set it up light, fire, like, billows out the top.
I'll turn my house into a jack-o'-lantern by just lighting a fire in the middle of it.
Wait, isn't it already a jack-o'-lantern? It's like a hollow thing with holes and light inside.
When you think about it.
The doors, the mouth.
And when you think about it, all of us are jack-o'-lanterns because we ourselves are all hollow things.
Wait, are you glowing from inside?
Lit from the inside by the light of the Holy Spirit.
Talk about yourself. I don't have a Holy Spirit.
If you swallow a torch or your phone when your torch is on, then you'll have a light from inside.
The Holy Spirit is based. It gives you buffs if you're an apostle.
What if you're not an apostle? What if you're a Sylvester?
Why would you not want to be an apostle?
I don't know.
Wait a minute. I'm sorry.
I just looked it up.
I just went to Google and I went to the Wikipedia page for Pentecost.
It starts with Pentecost, also called Wit Sunday.
But I dyslexia, spoonerismed reading it, and I read it as Pentecost, also called Shit Wednesday.
I love Shit Wednesday.
Is it Wit Sunday or it's counterpart Shit Wednesday?
We call it Kingston.
And they have a week off at Kingston, which is nice.
Really?
Yeah.
A week off for fucking Pentecost?
Yeah, for university.
They say it's like for school trips and stuff, but then I went on a school trip one year,
and it wasn't that week, and I missed a week off school.
Why did you do this?
Why did you not put it in that week that we have off anyways?
Listen, listen, listen.
Okay, okay.
In Acts 2-1, the events that are celebrated at Pentecost, listen.
Here's what happened.
Be amazed by the power of the Holy Spirit.
There is a mighty rushing wind, and tongues as of fire appear.
The gathered disciples were filled with the Holy Spirit and began to speak in other tongues
as the Spirit gave them utterance.
What else, what else, what else?
When you speak in tongues, is it like the Tasmanian Devil?
Yes.
Yes, if the Holy Spirit, it will give you buffs, it will give you flame fiery tongues,
and you can talk different languages.
So, beat that.
You can't.
What languages?
Just other ones.
Just the normal one.
Probably like Aramaic, I guess, right?
It was what Jesus spoke.
So, yeah.
Maybe they started speaking English.
They started speaking Christian, a.k.a. modern American English,
and they wrote the new version of the Bible called?
Envy?
No, no, no, like the Envy...
Adams.
No, shut up.
Shut up.
The new international version.
They wrote the new international version.
This was, yeah, they skipped the Greek.
That's all, that's all fake.
Hebrew, fake.
Aramaic, fake.
Okay, that's all.
That's my joke.
Good job, man.
Let's move on.
Let's move on really, really fast.
But I can't, because I didn't do anything else this week, so...
I could talk about what my life's been recently,
which is distressing.
Go for it.
Oh, dear.
It's the world.
No, it's not that bad.
It's just, you know, new semester starts,
and I'm full of ambition.
I want to do so many things,
but I also get so many new homeworks and projects from school
that it's those first few weeks where I don't have that much to do,
but I want to do so many things,
and it's a bit overwhelming,
and I don't know where to start,
but also it's cool, I don't know.
What are you working on?
Yeah, for example, for example.
I have, well, just in general,
I have a bunch of presentations I have to do
in different classes on English things,
like cover, bebop,
and also I have an art project that I have to do this semester.
I already did one last semester of the kind where I have to have an exhibition at the end.
We do a big group exhibition in a gallery as a course,
and we kind of have a completely free range on what we want to do there,
and that's neat.
Yeah, but last semester I kind of overdid it,
and I did like six big full-detailed background illustrations
that took me way too long,
and I neglected my other courses,
and that shouldn't happen again.
So at the end, I was like,
okay, I have to do this course again next semester,
but next time I will only do one drawing, that's enough.
Some people only did one painting, it's fine.
I really don't have to do that much.
But then the semester starts,
and I'm like, what if I made a whole comic?
What if I made a whole short animation film?
So you're sure overloading yourself?
Yeah, I'm fighting against it.
Is the goal to get a good grade,
or is the goal to make something that you want to make?
Yeah, it's really doing something that I'm happy with,
and also that it doesn't take too much time away
from other things that I have to do.
I have like four different presentations,
and one exam, and this art project,
and I also want to do my private art, of course,
and maybe commissions.
By the way, commission me, I need money, help me.
And it's kind of crazy.
One of the other things that I want to do
is I want to finally get into making comics properly.
I tried it before, I made, I mean,
it's not that I tried it, I made comics.
I made like a whole chapter of my comic never forest,
but that was like two years ago, and it sucks now.
I look at it and I hate it,
and it don't want to touch it again.
That's how it goes.
It's just, I was really proud of it back then,
and now I look at the faces and I'm like,
ah, no.
Yeah, well, that's, what do you call it?
That's a...
Improvement?
Yeah, I guess so.
That's artistic growth for you.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I mean,
I mean, I don't know, if you wanted to do a second chapter,
there's nothing wrong with like the first pilot episode
looking rough or whatever.
Yeah.
But, you know, I mean...
I was actually thinking...
Yeah, I was thinking of like,
maybe reusing that idea in the future
and making something different with it,
because the story also wasn't that special or great.
I found a lot of like long running web comics
start as an obvious, like,
this is not supposed to be a long-term project.
I'm just drawing, you know, whatever.
And then they slowly realize that this can become bigger
and they start to improve the art and become more serious.
And so chapter one looks completely different from like chapter 50.
Yeah.
And that's fine, because, you know,
the only reason comics were so, like, rigidly,
like, you know, well done from the first chapters
because there's a rigorous, like, approval process
before anything gets published in like physical print media.
And on web comics, you can just make something
and throw it out there.
Yeah.
So there's no problem.
I mean, the beginning of Clarissa
is gonna look a lot worse than the ending,
based on just the two years it's been since I drew that,
I guess, almost two years.
Yeah.
And that's okay.
It's just, you know, it just sucks when a starting point,
when you want to send someone the beginning of your comic,
but that part is like the worst part.
It's like, you know, I don't know.
I wish I could, I wish I could start with a bang.
But, well, whatever.
It's better to make it finished
and then figure out how to do that
than it is to not, you know, continue.
I mean, unless you really don't want to,
but like...
I worked on other ideas.
I feel like the problem of people coming to chapter one
and being like, oh, this doesn't look very good,
is a lesser problem than not finishing things.
That's the challenge.
I haven't really...
Okay, I worked on three comics, I guess, so far.
I made Never Forest, just like the pilot pilot
that had no planning
and was just like 10 pages long
and it sucked and I threw it away.
Then I put more planning into Never Forest proper
and that was like 30, 40 pages
took me quite a while to draw
and I don't really like it anymore.
And then I have Midnight Mermaid,
which is still ongoing, I guess.
It's a comic I made with Asha.
I wrote and she drew the characters
and I drew backgrounds in the second chapter.
But that one, I haven't really gotten to it.
We published the first chapter, I think, in 2020
and the second chapter more than a year later
and I don't know when the third chapter is going to be.
It's going to take too long.
That's the problem, I don't know.
You know, I've been having quite randomly
without really meaning to.
I've been having some champion-related
world-building ideas lately.
Thank you, I'm glad that's exciting for you.
I was like, it's cool that you want to make more lectures in videos
but I'm like, I like your comics, go make more comics too, please.
Well, check out my newly up, my new Patreon page
or I'll just tell you what it says.
As I say on there, I do want to make more lectures
but I'm not going to stop doing comics and stuff.
I don't know if I'm...
I don't know, my hope is that,
okay, the lectures are kind of a hit, people like them.
So if I can split my time between do those sometimes
and then as my sort of side thing do comics and stuff,
that would be fine and great.
But the...
What was I saying?
Shit.
Fuck.
Champion idea.
I guess I didn't really have anything else.
I don't want to go into details about them.
I don't know when I'll actually get around to drawing it
but I've just had some thoughts across my mind about
what if it was like that?
What if that was going on?
I wrote down some notes about it.
I feel very inexperienced in storytelling
and so it's pretty hard for me to go back
to something I wrote years ago
and I'm like, this all sucks, this is all boring,
why did I do this?
Yeah, it's hard.
I was listing...
In the intro paragraph to the new Patreon,
I was listing projects I've done in the past
and I left the champion off
because I only listed things that I completed.
So I didn't list the Winnie the Pooh videos or anything.
I didn't list...
I didn't list Biscopades.
You can set up Vapors finished.
Vapors was never going to be...
It was always just going to be vignettes
and I did three complete vignettes.
So yeah, I would consider each Vapors story
to be sort of its own complete thing.
Yeah.
Still need the physical release of the third one, though.
Yeah, at some point, I guess I might as well.
Although now that I'm basically done working on
the Mega Man lecture,
it means I have to get back to finishing up the...
I have to go back to the Nightmare
that was sorting out the Slime and Punishment Bookcake Starter.
So I have to stop playing Inscription and start...
I have to finish drawing the cover.
I never finished drawing the cover.
Ugh, yeah.
There's just so much stuff.
Yeah, that's what...
I literally had kind of a crisis yesterday
because there's so much stuff I want to do.
I also have this completely different project
that I came up with this year
that was my last big art project
for the exhibition in the summer.
And it's the Draconic Drug Store
I posted these illustrations on Twitter.
Yes, with the Spider Man.
Is he a guy? Man?
Or is he a girl? I don't remember.
Non-binary, more or less.
Yeah, you know what? That makes sense.
Yeah, their name is Jitter.
And it's supposed to be this goofy, wacky cast
of monster characters
that live in this drug store
where they cure horrible, fantastic diseases.
And it's supposed to be this mash-up of fantasy
and modern life and aesthetics.
And also the thing that I specifically like,
is getting fantasy creatures
and designing them with natural animals in mind
or different natural aesthetics.
I think that's neat.
So Jitter is specifically designed
after the African social spider,
which is a spider that lives in giant colonies
and makes big web constructions.
Are spiders living in a social group?
Let's make them hive mind
and have them inhabit a puppet.
And yeah.
Okay, I saw something on Twitter the other day
and it was about a spider that builds an effigy of itself.
A what?
It builds a statue of a spider
out of debris.
Yeah.
If you could link that, that sounds amazing.
Why would it do this?
Is it lonely?
Nobody knows.
Is it like a body pillow?
What?
Yeah.
It's lonely for a spider.
Well, this was the tweet that I saw
and I get all my science facts from Twitter users
who I don't recognize.
The best source.
Yeah, even though my internet is perfectly fine
to handle this call,
Discord is having a really hard time
sending a text-based Twitter link.
It's really struggling with all those bits,
so you're just going to have to wait.
That sounds awesome.
Oh, there it goes.
Nobody knows why the spider in the Philippines does this.
Maybe it's like a scarecrow
in the same way that you would put a scarecrow to scare crows away.
It's like a spider.
What's a track fly?
Exactly.
What's a track thing to its web?
It wants to find masochist flies.
Oh, God.
Maybe there's spiders who steal webs
and he's like, this is mine.
There's already a spider here, so you can't take my web.
I'm going to go for a walk.
It might be some partner attraction thingy.
Oh, the person who owns this web is huge.
Look at that spider.
I'm going to go say hello.
That might actually be it.
If male spiders look for specifically the largest female spiders
because they are the healthiest or something,
maybe smaller female spiders will create this big fake spider
to attract males or something like that.
I don't know why it's so fascinating to me,
but they've got the number of legs correct.
Spiders can count.
That's what I looked at, too.
I was like, wait, does it know how many legs a spider had?
And I counted.
Like, yes, it has eight legs.
You know how many legs you have.
I'm a human.
I can count to two.
And also, I mean, I guess it must be an instinctual thing.
It's just so funny.
It's humanizing the spider to me.
It's like a little sculptor.
I'm sorry.
I know what a spider looks like from above.
Absolutely fascinating.
And I will probably incorporate that into Jidder's personality.
Maybe Jidder can make a decoy spider or like doubles of themselves.
In one of the tweets below it, they linked to like an article
and I'm embarrassed to admit that I did a double take
at the name of the island that the spider lives on.
I'm really sorry.
It's OK.
It's just a kind of...
Forgive me.
It's just a kind of like Spanish or something.
Exactly, exactly.
Anyway, I just thought this was really weird.
Yeah, that was the first thing I was like.
Because someone replied like, oh my God, the spider knows what it looks like.
Yeah, it has a sense of self.
Like, that's crazy.
Just a little guy.
You know, they train elephants to paint pictures of themselves,
but the elephant doesn't know that it's painting itself.
They train the elephant to do like a series of brushstrokes
that sort of end up looking like an elephant.
The elephant is not consciously being like,
this is what I look like and I'm going to paint myself.
But this is like...
The spider doesn't either.
You don't think so?
No, it's probably just like with anything.
I mean, spiders are able to build beautiful webs
that look super symmetric and accurate.
Yeah.
And there's like, I don't know,
paradise birds who make weird, interesting patterns in the sand
for their mates.
Well, that's sort of an instinctual...
Yeah.
But like, I don't know why a spider would instinctually know
that if they wanted to build a facsimile of themselves,
they would do four legs, eight legs with a circle.
What if that's a bit of a coincidence or something?
I mean...
What if they just follow their web pattern
because it looks like it's in the middle of their web
and the legs might just be placed on...
There's probably more than eight strokes.
The web is...
I don't think, yeah, the web is not...
Yeah.
I mean, it could be...
I'm just wondering if we're over-interpreting this
and we see a spider,
but to the spider, it's just a badge with a bunch of lines around it.
What a...
Yeah, I mean, I wonder if maybe if we looked at more of these,
if they don't all look so clean and spider-like.
Yeah.
I suppose.
I like the idea that spiders, for some reason, know what they look like.
I would like to know...
Yeah, I would like to know why it does this.
Like, what is the purpose of this construction?
I mean, spiders know what they look like
in the sense that any animal can recognize their mates
because they have to.
Yeah.
The spider knows when they meet another one of their own species.
It's just like a bear couldn't build a crude statue of a bear.
Well, bears don't build things anyway.
That's true.
A beaver, then.
A beaver wouldn't shape its dam to look like another beaver.
I hope he's sick, though.
It's just like an intimidation tactic.
Like, there's a huge beaver here.
Don't do not come close.
That's so scary.
Cool.
Pretty cool.
But like, this is a view of a spider from above, essentially.
And spiders, I imagine, meet each other on the same plane.
They can see each other.
They can't see that far in the, like, ahead of them.
Yeah, I'm not even sure how well it sees.
They might just sense themselves in different ways.
Because they could probably use their legs to rub against their other legs
and be like, yeah, I got one leg there.
Another leg there.
And there's a big smell.
Well, you know, bees can do multiplication.
Yeah, but bees also have a language like they dance for each other
to communicate how far the flower is away.
Yeah, I saw a movie.
There was a, I read about an experiment where they did,
they would put out, they had took a beehive
and they put out, like, sugar water or, you know, pollen or whatever
for these bees to, like, eat.
And they moved the location of the pollen.
Like, they tried moving it, like, you know, 10 feet away.
And then the next day it would be, like, 20 feet away.
And the next day it'd be, like, 30 feet away.
And the bees eventually figured out the pattern
and they would predict they knew where it was going to be.
And then they even tried it with a multiplication.
They would put it, like, 2 feet away and then 4 feet away
and then 8 feet away.
And the bees were able to figure out that pattern too.
They were like, oh, every day it's twice as far.
So they would, like, be there already.
They would be there already.
So they would be 16 feet away being like, where's the pollen?
Where is it?
Exactly.
And me dancing is interesting because it's kind of fucking
with one of the definitions of what, like, human language means.
I learned about this in the first semester, I think,
that, like, human language has the feature of displacement.
So we can talk about things that aren't true.
We can make things up.
And we can talk about things that aren't
in, like, our immediate surroundings.
We can tell stories about things that we can't see.
And most animals can't do that,
even though they can communicate, like, dogs talk to each other, basically.
But they can never talk about something that's not true
or that's not there.
But bees actually have a form of displacement
because they can do that.
They can talk about, they can tell their people about, like,
a flower that is, like, kilometers away.
And that's pretty crazy.
I don't think they could make up stories about flowers,
though I'm not sure if that's a thing.
But that would be fascinating.
Yeah, maybe more moral than humans.
I would be surprised if bees have, like, a sense of, like, narrative.
No, probably not.
Probably not.
Yeah.
But, I mean, there's other animals, like, dolphins, for example,
that have, like, very complex languages
that people wonder if that maybe there's more to it.
Maybe they can actually be, like, playful or creative.
If we made, we've designed a new special iPad
that dolphins can use underwater.
They boop the thing with their nose.
And we've discovered they've invented their own form of mean.
And they send it to each other.
You ever see a video of, like, a monkey reacting to, like, a magic trick?
Yeah, I've seen some of those.
Some of them are fake.
I don't like the fake ones.
I don't know if the one I'm thinking of is fake or not.
There's a few that are, like, CGI.
And I'm like, you fuck.
It's easy enough to make a monkey be, like, what?
Where'd it go?
That's fun.
That's all you need.
Well, I saw one where, like, someone does a little, like,
makes, like, a handkerchief disappear or something.
And the monkey, like, kind of, like, sort of, like, opened its mouth,
kind of, like, put its hands to its face, kind of, like, was, like, looking around
and sort of, like, started, like, jumping and, like, looking back at, like, where it was.
It seemed real enough, I don't know.
Yeah, they're subtle.
The fake ones.
There was one that, I mean, I'm not entirely sure.
It's just sort of, like, I couldn't tell how it could have been done.
But there was a guy who put a playing card up against the glass.
And he pushed it through the glass.
And it was on the other side of the glass, inside the orangutan enclosure.
And the orangutan, like, looked at it and tapped it and picked it up.
And that was fake.
And then he tried to push the thing back through the glass and he tapped it with a stick.
Because he thought, like, oh, I can push it through too.
And I thought that was real.
But then I was like, how the fuck did he put the thing through the glass in the first place?
That is, yeah.
That seems like more of a camera trick than it was a magic trick.
Well, I mean, I guess magic tricks and camera tricks are the same thing, but you know what I mean.
No, a camera trick is not a magic trick.
Like the monkeys, the orangutan seemed a little confused, but I don't know.
You know, magic is just technology that we don't understand.
Like cameras, I don't understand them.
Magic tricks are not the same as camera tricks, but, like, a lot of magic is about, like,
making you look in the place so that they can do a special thing.
Yeah, sure.
And so, like, you can not edit the footage, but still use camera trickery
to make it hard for you to notice something happening.
Yeah, okay, that's fair.
But I feel like that one particular was just CGA and there was already a card on the other side of the glass.
Well, wait, just to finish about the Draconic Dragstore.
Yes.
So I came up with an idea because I want to have, like, characters that have a world
that I can tell stories about, that I can make narrative illustrations about,
and explore that whole thing.
And then I made that big project for school and, like, explore that entire house.
By the way, I built the entire house in Minecraft to have reference pictures.
Nice.
Like, in a bigger scale to, like, get all the angles right.
So, yeah, that was fun.
But after that, I was kind of burned out on the project.
And I was like, I need to get back to it.
I want to make a comic about them.
I want to make a comic with my, like, five people cast of wacky creatures.
And it's, like, it's hard to think where to start.
It's, like, having a complex cast of characters is really overwhelming.
Yeah.
I have had, like, a big project in mind for a long time.
I don't really want to spoil too much.
But essentially, I think I've mentioned this part before,
is that comics that I make eventually will coincide.
So, like, Clarissa will meet Pumk at some point.
The Lord of Ghosts characters will meet everyone else.
And then there's a bunch of other comics with characters I haven't made yet,
which will also be part of, like, this big, super cinematic universe thing.
Going to make your own end game.
Yeah.
But, like, better.
Because I don't like Marvel.
But actually good, though.
Because it's got my characters in it.
I haven't seen that game.
Maybe it's great.
Maybe it's a masterpiece.
That's probably good.
I haven't seen anything beyond the first Avengers.
So, like, that...
It's a huge idea.
And, like, it's kind of stupid.
But I've sort of...
I've not, like, focused too heavily on, like, making it perfect.
Like, making everything fit perfectly and then having, you know,
parts of one comic, like, foreshadow other things
and having everything perfectly planned out.
Because I realized that planning everything out on such a large scale
would mean that I would be planning my comic career
for the next 20 years and then not post anything.
So, instead, I'm just going to work on Clarissa.
I'm going to make that.
Then I'm going to...
Maybe I'm going to finish the Lord of Ghosts.
Then there's some other things to do.
Bail Jape, too.
Punk will have to return at some point.
I don't even know how.
Zuggling many balls.
Yeah.
But, like, the point, I think, is to have this cool, huge story
and then to not think about it too hard.
And then do, like, the individual parts.
Yeah, do the individual parts.
Start it.
I don't even know what it would be called.
My problem was also a bit that, like, in that big project
about, like, the different rooms of the Draconic drugstore,
I essentially spent, like, three, four months
just drawing these rooms and planning them out
and thinking about how this house works.
And that's all cool, but it doesn't really tell a story.
Like, I don't really make people care about these characters
by planning out this house in much detail.
Oh, yeah.
It's fun, but, like...
It's extremely fun to flesh out the lore.
Like, I've got, like, a origin of, like, the universe,
sort of lore part.
Like, why roll these things the way they are?
Well, you see, millions of years ago,
and I'm like, I wrote a little thing, and I'm like,
oh, this is so fucking sick.
I can't wait for one of the comic characters far in the future
to be, like, millions of years ago,
and they just say the lore that I came up with.
And they just say it.
It would be fucking so cool.
I can't wait until the dramatic conclusion
wherein Clarissa and the Lord of Ghosts
and Pump are all unicorn jelly-style,
billions of years in the future,
existing as, like, abstract mathematical symbols
in a space beyond time.
Yes.
That's what I'm looking forward to.
I forgot what I was gonna...
What was I getting at?
So you were talking about a character in the future,
like, bringing up the origin of the universe?
Oh, no, not that.
Just sort of...
Yeah, it's fun to obsess over the lore
and get it all right.
And I would say every time you have a cool new idea,
write it down immediately,
and then figure out how you're gonna fit it in later.
I started off that recently.
I started actually using, like, one note
and making folders for ideas
and, like, putting them all down.
You can figure out the details
the minutiae later,
but it's fun to write it down when you think of it.
But a great example
of a naturally-evolving set of lore
and characters
is a Batman and Spider-Man,
the animated series on YouTube.
Have you ever seen Batman and Spider-Man?
A little bit, a little bit.
It sort of...
It starts out as, like, a goofy-looking Batman character
and a Spider-Man,
and they say,
I'm Batman.
I'm Spider-Man.
We come over to the house.
Sounds like a PSP voicemail.
We are best friends,
and they're just, like, Batman and Spider-Man.
They're just hanging out in the house,
and it's, like, really, like, dumb and fun and cute.
Yeah.
And over time, like, they introduce characters,
and then the characters have wacky adventures
because they live in a world where anything could happen.
It's kind of like adventure time.
It's just sort of...
Because anything could happen,
anything does happen,
and then things that happen remain
in the lore of the show,
so another episode can happen,
and the characters from before can still exist to there,
and there's sort of...
It just sort of builds.
It's really fun to watch.
I would very much recommend watching all of that
because it's not that long.
There's definitely stories where they feel so free-flowing
that I feel like would be easier to write for them.
Like, I'm not...
I'm thinking about Calvary Beaver a lot recently.
Like, every episode is kind of just something completely new,
and they...
It's the same premise,
but they do something new with it
on a different planet,
in a different set of supporting characters,
and it's very appealing to me.
And I mean,
my favorite example of someone who just started writing
and then figured things out is Tolkien himself,
because he's a weird freak of nature,
and the way he wrote was,
oh yes, I'm gonna start at Bilbo's birthday
and then I'm gonna send them on an adventure,
and whenever something happened in the story,
he was like, huh, what does this mean?
What are the larger implications of this?
Let's find out.
Like, he didn't really plan much ahead,
and that's why...
I don't know how he did it,
but like, it somehow in the end all fit into a larger narrative,
but he just went along.
He changed a few bits, like in retrospect,
I think like Aragorn when he first meets the Hobbits.
In the original script,
he used to be a Hobbit himself too.
Instead of Strider, he was called Trotter.
I mean, Frodo's name was also Bingo at that time.
Bingo. Bingo.
Bingo and Bilbo sounds like a monkey.
Yeah, they should have kept that.
But at some point, he was just like,
huh, this Trotter guy, he seems not that Hobbit-y.
He might be a human.
What kind of human would he be?
And as he was writing it, he was developing this backstory,
and I'm like, it's like, he just started.
He just started and went off in a crazy, creative direction
and made a masterpiece.
I really shouldn't spend years planning houses or whatever.
That sounds like the way to do it.
Yeah, I mean, for sure, he went back and iterated
and like, changed a few things.
The first draft is never the best draft,
but once you have a first draft,
it's so much easier to write a compelling story
because you have a story that already exists
and you're like, yeah, I mean,
this part would be better if it was like this, actually.
So you just change it and then you have, you know,
a story that had a good foundation
and then you made it better by tweaking a few things later.
So it's always good to get a first draft out,
even if you don't release it immediately.
Yeah, or draw it when it's a comic.
Yeah, I mean, that's definitely a thing.
I always write the comics before I draw them.
Yeah, I would think drawing takes,
I mean, it takes me much longer than to write something.
But even for me, it's like, when I'm sketching something,
I'm like, you know, I'm reading this the way I'm turning the pages
and I'm like, something sucks about this.
I've got to change something.
You can go back and change it.
And because I had all of those sketches,
I could read it and figure out that something was needed.
So it's always better to have something to work with
rather than planning it out
and then hoping that your plan will work,
because it most likely will not.
Yeah.
Just because of the lack of information you have
while you're making the plan, you have zero information.
You're making it from scratch.
And so seeing the finished product,
if it's perfectly to the plan
and you didn't change anything as you were going,
you might at the very end realize that the plan was flawed
and you're like, dang.
Fuck.
That's why it's good to iterate as you go.
Yeah.
I was thinking that I might focus on telling mini stories first
just to get myself writing and practicing
and getting to know the characters a bit
without having the pressure of having everything
to be canonical and important for an overarching story.
Yeah.
Honestly, I should do that as well.
Just like short stories with punk or whatever.
Mini comics.
We already have the mini red man comics.
By the way, I celebrated his return.
It was great.
The singular post of return where he has goofy teeth now.
Yes.
Very spooky, too.
I like to think he got inspired by the mouse.
Oh, the mouse vampire?
Yes.
And the red man was like, oh, that's spooky now,
having cute mouse teeth.
Yeah.
They got the same teeth.
They got to be the same teeth.
It's exactly the same.
I don't know what he got into.
Maybe red man killed her and is using her teeth for real.
He thought, oh, it's a vampire.
She must be full of blood.
So he ate her, but he's like, oh, there's just cheese.
It's disgusting.
Oh, but at least I got all the sweet teeth.
Red man is a vampire, right?
Like a vampire in its purest form.
Um, I don't, I mean, how would you describe it?
He's not like magical.
He just eats a lot of blood.
That's true, but vampire bats aren't magical either.
It's the vampire.
Sure.
I mean, what do you mean when you say vampire?
Do you mean drink the blood?
I don't know.
I was just like, yeah, he drinks blood.
Yeah, that's the thing.
That's it.
That's all.
Well, hell, I could be a vampire.
Every time I cut my lips and I suck the blood out,
I'm a vampire.
Eat a delicious black pudding.
No.
If you think that's delicious, yes, you are a vampire.
I do.
I do like black pudding, actually.
It's good, actually.
Everyone who doesn't like it is just a hater.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's just sort of like a little meaty something or other.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Ew, gross.
Ew, haggis or whatever.
Are you telling me that food is made of parts of a dead animal?
Well, let me tell you.
Let me tell you something, buddy.
There's more where that came from.
I don't like that.
Chicken nuggets are more gross than black pudding,
but they taste better.
So, yeah.
Who's the real winner?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I'm not saying they're as good as chicken nuggets.
Just that it's good is all.
Did you hear that?
Sauron's straight.
Was he not straight originally?
Well, well, not very.
I mean, not very.
There's a lot of queer readings on Sauron specifically
because he is...
Sauron takes on a fair form to seduce the man of Middle Earth
and seduce the elves to make rings and stuff like that.
And there's a lot of people who say...
I mean, it's a classic...
Okay.
I guess you could read it that way.
It is a classic boomer thing to make your villain
of your thing that you're writing gay-coded
because gays are evil.
And it's just sort of become like a popular thing in media
from then.
Is there something to it?
Because it sounds like you're just deliberately
misunderstanding the words seduce there.
Well, it's complicated, but...
You have to point to some clear sexual tension
between him and a person.
I think there's people who say,
researchers have said that queerness goes beyond that.
It's just a rejection of societal norms in a certain way.
What the fuck are you talking about?
There's a bit more to queer theory than just being gay.
I don't know too much about it, but the point...
Okay, so your argument is...
Yes, Sauron was never attracted to any men,
but he's gay-coded and that counts.
That's what you're saying.
He's just got gay vibes.
That is a very popular interpretation of Sauron.
That sucks.
I mean, look up Sauron Melkor and see all the hot fan arts
that there are.
The big deal about this show is that
it's about the making of the Rings of Power.
And Kelly Brimbo, who made the Rings of Power,
is very popularly shipped with Sauron
because Sauron seduced him and worked with him
on these great pieces of art and betrayed him in the end.
And murdered him in a horrific way.
A very homosexual thing to do.
Betraying and murdering.
Well, I didn't come up with it,
but there's a lot of people who are really invested in that dynamic
in that way.
In the show, what they did instead was
that they have Sauron paired with Galadriel
and make him instead of him being this ethereal,
beautiful, kind of elvish creature.
Evil fanboy.
Yeah, like evil.
Instead of making him an evil fanboy,
they made him like kind of a scruffy, aragorn type looking dude.
Yeah, because unlike back in the day
where you would code your villains to be gay, like queer,
nowadays it's queer to be straight.
And so the straighter and more masculine typical is like,
oh, that sucks, that's evil.
So now we make Sauron the straightest guy of all time.
Yeah, it definitely makes sense.
It feels a bit that way.
And I think they tried to misdirect the audience who were expecting,
especially talking fans who were expecting a certain tag on Sauron
and haven't been kind of the opposite.
But I've also seen a lot of people being really mad about that.
And I was like, I can understand that because, I mean,
it would be like one opportunity to have kind of a complex
or maybe queer relationship between two male characters in big fantasy show.
And for many people, that's been the text that they've been interpreting for decades.
And then like Amazon comes around and like makes it the most
just like, I don't know, boilerplate, kind of heterosexual ship.
That's like, yeah.
Yeah, I think he would have been cooler if he was gay
and it's super flamboyant as well.
Because like, they might still go there,
but they're like, yeah, I don't know.
Didn't do so in the first season.
He's gonna turn gay because of the power of the ring.
Well, he's a shape shifter.
So like he could take on a different form in the next season
to do different things, which could be fun.
But yeah, there's been a lot of criticism of the show because of that.
They like, it's funny, like on the one side,
like all the conservative rage troopers like calling the show woke
and the most horrible thing, the conspiracy, the message, everything.
And on the other side, the woke people are also not really happy with it
because it isn't like, it isn't actually like, it's still pretty conservative in that sense.
And yeah, it kind of, those show, I feel like it made most people
on both sides not quite happy.
And that's kind of, that's pretty unfortunate.
But it's the show good.
It's all right.
And that's the worst thing about it.
All right.
It's a lot of her rings.
It should be amazing.
But I think it was enjoyable enough.
That's good acting.
Is there going to be a second season?
There's actually five seasons.
They contracted five seasons from the beginning.
As a disease?
Yeah.
There's a contract or contract.
Contracting a disease.
No, that's correct.
I was actually.
I have to pee.
I will be right back.
Okay, bye-bye.
Have a good pee.
Ah, now that show has been occupying my brain for two months.
And yeah, it's a big deal for me.
I caught like the end or not the end.
It's sort of a middle of an episode.
And I was just sort of seeing if it was interesting.
And then it was a lot of dramatic talking between characters.
Obviously, I didn't know the characters because I hadn't watched from the first episode.
I was just catching it.
How are you catching it?
It was no TV.
My brother was watching and I walked in the room.
I was like, okay.
And there was scary people and they burned a forest.
And the hobbits were like, this sucks.
The forest is burnt.
And then there was a Jesus guy.
And so someone gave him an apple.
And then they were in the Mines of Moria or whatever.
That's actually right.
Yeah, I figured because at the end, the Balrog was at the bottom.
Yeah.
They threw like a stone.
They got a hole and it's like, wow, look down there.
It's like a cavern, cool.
And then the guy said to his father, fuck you, dad.
And the dad said, fuck you, son.
Get out.
They're gonna explore that.
They're gonna explore the backstory of Khazadum.
And they showed it at its glory basically and that was pretty neat.
Yeah.
The part of the episode I sort of watched didn't have anything that hooked me in terms of intrigue.
It was just sort of like characters despondently talking to each other about how bad things are.
And that, don't worry, we'll get through this.
Come on, we can do it.
Oh no.
And I'm like, that's not really the vibe of Lord of the Rings.
It is for like a few scenes at a time.
But like the swelling music and the adventure is what I think of.
The climbing of the mountains and the, I guess it's just sort of a film sized film.
It's better to get your pumped about what's happening.
Well, come back.
Yeah, they always just like get caught a bit of an episode and wasn't satisfied with the vibe.
And I get that because it's like the dialogue is well written,
but it's missing, it's certainly missing some of the drive that like a self-contained adventure would have like the Hobbit or Lord of the Rings.
Like we have a clear quest and instead we have like three or four plot lines that go into different directions and it's not really clear where or when.
Yeah.
Is there like an inciting incident that you can point to in the show?
Well, it's...
The set things in motion or is it just sort of like, let's have a view of the way the world is and then we'll build to something happen.
It's basically building towards anticipating that Sauron will come back and wondering where is Sauron, who is Sauron and what can we do to prepare against him.
And there's like resurgence of evil in the world and stuff like that.
But yeah, it doesn't have like Gandalf coming up, take this ring, go on, adventure now.
It doesn't have that at all and it has a few interesting plot elements that just kind of...
They don't have enough drive to like make that season very exciting.
It was very exciting for me because I'm a big Tolkien fan and I'm glad when they showed something from the Silmaroo and I'm like,
Wow, that's like the helm of Turin that you wore to slay Glauron.
Neat, they have that in the background.
Soy.
Yes.
Is that Baron Lufian on that painting?
You know what?
It's reasonable.
I like that.
And I...
Yeah.
The other big thing is that they completely rely on mystery boxes to keep the show going at least in the first season.
So like, there's like...
There's the stranger.
The stranger, nobody knows who he is.
He came to Middle Earth in a meteor and got found by a hobbit.
He's a weird bearded man who has weird powers and who could he be?
Could he be a wizard?
Could he be Sauron?
Could he be a Maia or a Balrog or something like that?
Could he be...
And they just don't answer it.
It keeps going on and we like find out bits and pieces.
And he may be a young Gandalf.
He may be a blue wizard.
I don't know.
And it's just like his story himself is not satisfying enough.
It's just about figuring out who he could be.
Yeah.
And same thing with the guy who turns out to be actually Sauron.
That guy, that story works out better because we actually learn that he's Sauron.
But yeah.
That's sort of a thing with TV.
I don't know like the sort of make the audience ask questions so that they'll watch the new episode,
but like never fulfill on the answer.
It feels cheap.
Did you see the latest Doctor Who special?
The last.
Do you watch Doctor Who?
I forget.
You don't.
Okay.
Well, I'll just say Chris Chibnall, the current showrunner.
He has a problem with having the illusion of complexity, but it just results in me asking,
what does any of this have to do with anything for like 90% of the episode?
And then at the end it's like, haha, they were all intertwined magic perfectly.
And I'm like, oh, that's not clever though.
You just didn't give me the information I needed to know that.
It's not like a twist.
It's just sort of like, finally you've revealed the plot right at the end.
I'm sure you can do it in a satisfying way, but it's complicated to pull it out of, I think.
It was just sort of like, this isn't good writing.
This is annoying.
I hate you.
I'm just glad that we know who Sauron is now so that in the following seasons we don't
have to wonder anymore who he could be.
It's like, that's just not a...
I want him to get to the plot.
I want him to get to the War of the Elves and Sauron.
And I want him to get to the Fall of Nmenor and all of that.
But they just, you know, feels like they were dragging and they wanted to fill a season.
They said, I think the showrunner said, it's like, no, it's so that you can learn to care about
all of these characters and know what's at stake when the war is coming.
That's fine, but in the end, it's mostly just about the mysteries.
I mean, you can care about Frodo even though you don't know anything really about his life.
That's true.
Yeah, we don't bear anything about his life for the first 50 years.
You get a brief like, oh, he lives in this nice place that's green and lush and people are happy.
His parents died, he got adopted, that's it.
Well, you don't even know that in the film.
I'm just thinking the way the film shows him.
He's just a guy who lives in a place and his uncle Bilbo has a ring and you learn about Frodo as he's on his adventure.
So while the exciting stuff is happening, you're also caring about Frodo more because of all the stuff that the way he reacts to things.
It's like, you don't need to do like a pre prologue so that you know Frodo's entire life story,
which is probably boring because he's not on the adventure.
That's right.
I agree.
He just lived in a house.
One day he had a lovely block of cheese.
What do hobbits do?
They fish, they have like Morris dancing, they smoke pipe weed.
Frodo was kind of a bookworm and was like meeting with the elves in the forest.
Did you say he was kind of a worm?
No, a bookworm.
I thought you was like, would you still love me if I was a worm?
I think Frodo was a worm.
Would the ring still fit him if he was a worm?
Yes, actually.
The ring changes in size.
Master Frodo, Master Frodo, would you still like me if I was a worm, Master Frodo?
Go back to bed, Sam, shut the hell up.
Yes.
Yes, actually.
He would.
Yeah, I think so.
A worm couldn't carry Mr. Frodo into the fire's amount dune.
Sadly.
Like worms, Sam would say, I can't carry the ring.
I also can't carry you.
I guess you're on your own.
I think the most interesting show, the most interesting thing the show did was that they
tried to do more with the orcs and having the orcs not be pure evil.
And they have a character who is like a deformed elf and he calls himself an orc, but he clearly
doesn't look like an orc yet.
He just kind of looks like a dark elf.
And supposedly he was one of the first elves that got caught by Morgoth and he like farbored
a lot of the orcs.
Oh, they made babies?
I thought they were all tortured, the orcs.
Oh, no, they procreate.
They procreate in the same way that elves and humans do.
You mean there's orc bitches out there?
Yes.
Well, don't they get like spawned out of like a pit?
No, that's Peter Jackson.
That's the movie version.
Oh, that's just the movie?
Yes.
I see.
It was cool though.
And yeah, I like that effect too.
I just imagined that they had sex down there and then just like they grow up and then the
babies come out of the mud pool.
They fuck the mud.
I don't know.
Or just under the mud.
But they have this like orc elf character.
It's like the Homestuck alternative mother grub.
Only instead of like a big grub that's like spitting out babies down at the core of the
planet, it's down in the pit.
There's just all these like orcs fucking down like a hole that you can't see and just
sometimes like fully formed like adult babies just crawl out from the hole.
Down, down in the pit.
It's the incestuous slurry.
The incestuous slurry.
That's right.
They still have that.
And they go in a direction where the orc guy just kind of wants to make a home for his
people.
I just like want to walk right?
Big mistake.
Have them be a place to live.
And I think that's very interesting because that's something that Tolkien never was sure
about or made a decision on because on the one side he was like, so orcs, yeah, they
they procreate.
They are like, they, they are like fighting, but they also have personalities.
They have some extent of free will.
But at the same time was like, but no, they're created by the evil.
So they can't have that.
So like, like his idea was like evil can't create anything new.
It can only corrupt things and make them bad.
And, and he was like, he can't give the orcs free will because then that would mean like,
Oh, after they're dead, I guess because they spawned out of else, they would go to the
west and live in peace there.
That's weird.
They did evil things.
That's not how it should work.
And I think in early versions, orcs were actually just like golems, like mindless, like fighting
robots that just did the bidding of the Dark Lord.
But while writing Lord of the Rings, I think it just had too much fun with the orcs and
there are scenes in Lord of the Rings where orcs talk to each other without like supervision
and they talk about after the war's over, we're going to go and open our own little company
somewhere else with a few, with a few good boys and we're going to do our own thing.
And at that point, orcs just become like their own like people that clearly aren't like, like
tied to forever just doing the evil spitting.
And, and, and talking never really made a like final decision on that.
Like, are they can, can orcs be redeemed?
Because at the end of the Lord of the Rings book, Aragorn like goes and genocides all of the orcs.
That's like, that's like,
when you think about them as people that had other ambitions than just being evil, that's really fucked up.
Sad, yeah, yeah.
That's too bad.
And I'm just, and at least they're doing something with it.
They're like, like Galadriel tells like the evil orc guy, oh, I will hunt you all down and kill your last kin.
And he's like, that sounds pretty evil, dude.
Like, that sounds pretty, that sounds pretty morgopy what you're saying.
Yeah.
That's, that's pretty good though, that they found a little bit of like space in the, in the lore that like Tolcan never really filled in.
And they're like, what, what's, what do we think is there?
But what the big question mark is, what are they going to do about it?
Because at the end of the show, there's still going to be a giant war between the orcs and the elves.
And like, the elves have to come out as the good guys there.
What's going to happen?
Yeah.
In short, maybe they're going to do something where they, perhaps they show some orc, orc characters that are more morally ambiguous.
And maybe they get like, they, they stand up against their like other orcs and maybe they get like granted lands in the end somewhere else,
like being forgiven by crimes or something.
And they need to, they need to do something now.
I would imagine that the way they could get around that is having like the sympathetic orcs who want peace killed by more bloodthirsty orcs that like the idea of fighting and killing.
Yeah.
So like the bad orcs are now the orcs that they do go to war with.
Or that they get tricked in some way, like, or like, there's some kind of scheme to make all the orcs forever turn against the elves or something like that.
They, they opened the door and the implications are pretty complicated.
And I'm curious what they're going to do with it.
Rose.
We're at 23%.
We are at 23% rendered.
We have gone up to almost 2%.
Yo.
That's like, it's a red, it's a red letter day.
How many minutes is that of the video?
Like two?
That's probably about half an hour.
Wait, no.
No, that's not right.
No, that's no way.
That could be it, right?
I can't do much.
Eight hours times 60 is 480 minutes.
So 1% of that is 4.8 minutes.
So yeah, 2% of it's almost 10 minutes, almost nine, nine ish minutes.
Shit.
Hell yeah.
We're, we're going to make it.
We're GMI.
Running commentary.
I would be so, yeah, I'd be so scared because like,
Oh, I'm terrified.
I've had like renders that, I don't know.
They just, they just fuck up like, like 70% of the way through,
like a multi-hour thing.
Like when I was editing the podcast a couple times,
I happened with the, the animations I did,
which I guess makes sense, but like still fucking sucks.
Having to redo it.
And sometimes it just doesn't make sense why it broke.
It could fail.
Something could go wrong.
But I mean, what can, what can I do other than just let it go and hope it all works out?
True.
Yeah.
Still, it is, it is a little nerve wracking.
I, you know, I try, I set, I tried setting in the control,
I'll delete menu.
I tried setting Vegas to high priority to allocate more CPU space for it.
And it does actually speed it up a little bit.
If I set it to above normal priority,
and it kind of slows down everything else.
But if I set it to high priority,
it slows down everything else so much that like,
I can't even like use the mouse or like do anything.
Like the computer, like it does not function when it's,
so like, if I set it to high priority, everything's fucked.
I literally have to like restart the computer.
Would, well, okay.
Hypothetically, if you were okay with not using the computer,
could you turn it to high priority to speed it up?
And then when it's finished,
then your computer will be usable again.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I haven't, uh, haven't tested it.
Hmm.
In theory, like maybe when the render completed,
it would like ping and then it would stop taking up all the CPU
and then the computer would go back to working normally again.
But I don't know because I didn't try it.
I started like the 120 hour render and then I set it to high priority
and then it was like, well, now your computer doesn't work.
And like the menus don't pop up when you try to click.
It just doesn't work.
So I was like, well, I can't not use my computer for 100 hours.
So I'll just have to start over.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
It's, it's, I'm, I'm thinking of like, what is it?
Like animated CG films, like finding Nemo or whatever.
They take, they take like, like an entire arrays of computers
to render, um, like a single frame and they have so many frames.
It takes weeks.
At least back then.
Is it still that much?
I think so.
Just because of like the, like the fidelity is increased.
I mean, the fidelity has increased, but the computer,
computing power has also increased and also the like efficiency of the.
Maybe, maybe it's different.
I still feel like they would still have their like arrays of rendering computers
that are just there to render.
I mean, I'm sure the files are huge.
Oh yeah.
Cause like they want blu-ray quality of like a feature length animated film.
Every frame has to be rendered.
Like every, every frame.
If you've ever like worked with, uh, with, um, like a blender or whatever
where you're like rendering like a little thing and it takes, I don't know,
20 minutes to make an image that has like the, the right lighting.
Like lighting takes so much more than like rendering in a video game
because it's like dynamically like figuring out how everything is going to reflect.
And so to do that for a high fidelity, like 4k blu-ray quality image of,
and then more than one of them.
It's just like an, I still, I feel like it must still take weeks for the final render.
I think if there's, it would be cool if there would be like a library or something
where they just had powerful computers.
They do.
Pay a little, pay a little bit and render your video there.
Another thing.
Uh, I don't know about library.
I mean, like, um, in Pixar, they have like the, the, the rendering room,
or at least they did where they just like tons of computers all linked together
to render these frames and they have backups just in case, but yeah.
Would be cool if that was like a public service people could use.
Like, so not everyone has to buy a more expensive big computer or two of them.
When I did like animation, uh, uni, I had to do some, some 3D rendering.
I only had the one computer and you were allowed to leave it running overnight.
And you could go home and you had, they had the computer room had like a lock
and you knew the passcode or your student ID badge was like a card things.
You could swipe that and get in.
I'm going to miss my student ID badge so much.
I still keep buying around.
I don't know why.
It's sort of like, oh, that's what I used to look like.
Oh, I remember putting this around my neck every fucking day.
Did you wear the transportation?
I wore my college lanyard everywhere and everyone made fun of me and I was a big loser.
We just have like a tiny card.
I wore it around my, I wore it around my neck.
What's a lanyard?
You know, like the like rope, the like the rope around your neck that housed like your keys and stuff on it.
I wouldn't, I didn't put my keys, but I know what you mean.
Like they'll like,
Or your ID card or whatever.
Yeah.
It would have like a little plastic thing.
You would snap your ID card in there.
Yes, exactly.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's such an old memory now having to do that.
My student ID gives me free public transportation and then entire like state.
That's really nice.
Wow.
That's a good deal.
I mean, that's most of the cost of going to university here.
It's just like, yeah, I pay like.
Fuck off.
I pay 300 bucks so that I get that card.
So I have free public transportation and I was allowed to go to school.
Geez, don't, don't break, don't break the bank.
Oh God, don't break the bank paying for bus fare for your college education.
Yeah, it's nice.
I was born in the right country.
I can't.
I can't complain.
My student loans are all paid off.
You're still allowed to complain.
I'll never, I'll never stop griping.
No, no, no.
I'm going to keep griping about it.
I'll never let that grudge go.
Severely horrible.
I'll let it, I'll let it drive a wedge between me and my, and foreigners.
You know what?
Maybe we should build the wall, actually.
To keep fucking...
We don't have an ocean between us men.
It's not right across the Atlantic Ocean.
Yeah.
Get that, that, that Saudi, the line project.
Put it in the ocean.
Why?
What?
Okay.
I saw that post that was like, this is terrifying.
Like, why is it terrifying?
Like, yeah, I get that it like, it's sci-fi and it's probably never going to happen.
But like, what would, what's, what's bad?
What's scary about it?
I think it looks cool.
Well, okay.
It doesn't look cool.
It looks gross.
On the one side it's scary.
It looks like, it looks like a cyberpunk video game city.
Yeah.
I don't like that.
I like that.
Okay.
I think like, one of the gross things or scary things about it is just like, it's Dubai
and Dubai literally uses slaves and like labor.
Shit.
Is Dubai in Saudi Arabia?
No.
Where is Dubai?
No, wait.
Is it?
It's like, ah, fuck.
I don't know.
Hang on.
I'm embarrassed.
I should know.
I used to think it was in India.
I'm not sure.
No, it's in the UAE.
It's in the Emirates, right?
It's in the, yeah.
It's in the Emirates.
Yeah.
Which is like next to Saudi Arabia, right?
It's under.
Close, close by, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
And they have like horrible human rights violations and stuff going on there.
I mean, okay, sure.
Exploit horribly.
And like they do these like crazy stunts like projects that are like just for tourism,
I guess, and status.
I had, I had, I'm just saying, sure, like maybe the country's bad, maybe the government's
bad, whatever.
But I just saw the tweet of the, this is terrifying with the video showing the 3D CG render of
the lion city.
And I genuinely did not understand what was supposed to be scary about it.
I think they might have been like talking about like the stacked nature of like the city being
like, I don't know.
It's, it's all in a line and it's all really tall and cramped together.
Yeah.
I feel like it could feel kind of claustrophobic living in a place where the only like, I mean,
it's, it's a terrible idea for very many reasons.
But like, I just think I'm not terrified by it.
Why, why, why is it a terrible idea?
Isn't, isn't the idea that it's just like a really efficient way to like.
But it, but it can't be though.
Organize an urban space.
Stretch it out as far as you can literally.
It's like the least efficient thing.
Like a good urban space is like a small and condensed like network.
A circle.
A circle would be better.
Well, I thought that's just the main thing.
I thought the, I mean, it's in the, it's in the desert.
Like it's not like, it's, it's like.
No, for like, all right.
They, they, here's the one of the main things, the public transport.
They say you can go seven kilometers in 20 minutes.
But it needs to stop at all the stations along the way.
So it's not going to take 20 minutes because no train is going to not stop at any of the stops.
Okay.
And it's just sort of, it's, it's all packed so tightly together that you can't expand if.
I mean, I don't know.
Yeah, that's also the thing.
Like cities grow and change and this thing can grow and change.
It's a sprawling, a sprawling city coming outwards, having like, like a single district being connected to four districts, five districts around it, as opposed to a line where you can only be connected to what's ahead or behind you.
And you can't build it taller.
It's a cute idea, I guess, but it has no real practicality making a city in that shape, except for making a cool CG render that's like, wow, the future.
It's stupid.
I've seen enough videos to know that it doesn't make sense architecturally.
I thought that the point of it was that the fact that it's like thin and condensed into a line means that you can like get anywhere in that line in like a relatively short amount of time.
Instead of relying on like a sprawling network of like public transportation and buses.
That's what they say, but the problem is that it wouldn't work that way, probably.
I mean, I don't know what they have in store if they have a solution to those problems, but they have not addressed them, which is the sort of the red flags.
They haven't addressed issues that are so obvious with the design of a line.
They just said, we're going to do it.
And I'm like, OK, well, I mean, your track record of Saudi Arabia is very poor.
You've built like so many lush, amazing things that you've abandoned because you did it for like publicity, tourism, or just showing off your wealth.
Most of Saudi Arabia is in like disrepair.
There's so many slums, there's so many poor places that are not kept up.
And the billionaires spend all of this money on these big, luscious, like mostly ego driven projects more than anything else.
They want to be the coolest guys doing the coolest things.
Stuff like the palm tree islands that are absolutely ridiculous where they like where they have to like dig up sand from the ocean to like destroy coral reefs and everything around it to make these islands
so that they can look like palm trees and then have like a normal like suburb on it and a highway.
Saudi princes are basically Elon Musk's.
That's the easiest way to describe.
Yeah, I, I, OK, I get that it looks like it's not actually there.
Like they're not actually going to do it.
I think they started, I think they actually started digging a hole for it.
Yeah, they've started doing something, but like.
Not a hole, a line.
Well, it's a line shaped hole.
It's a trench.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, it's just a fancy, it's just a fancy word for a line shaped hole.
I also just think it looks shit.
It looks bad on a map.
It's just a line.
I think it looks, I think it looks neat.
I think it looks cool.
All right.
One thing I don't like about like the aesthetic of it is the mirror on the outside.
I don't know what the benefit of the mirror is other than like blinding you with like the sun's rays if you're anywhere outside the line.
It's like, if you try to approach the line, we will blast you with these solar power.
I assumed that they were like solar panels on the.
I think it's just so that the desert, so that it looks kind of invisible in the desert that like the landscape doesn't get ruined.
I think that's the point.
Which is stupid because the landscape, like no one's going to be out there.
Yeah.
The only thing that might happen is birds will fly into it and the sun will like bake the land around the line, which could cause problems for the any, any living thing outside of it.
You know, Ben, I think my aesthetic problem with the line is like a cultural thing because like you Americans are used to like straight lines and borders and straight streets everywhere.
And like that's not some places.
Yeah, but it's just not how like the world that I grew up in.
Yeah.
I was kind of like terrified by Toronto where it's been like a month and a half just because like I look into one direction and I can see the horizon.
I look in the other direction.
I can also see a horizon.
It's like one street that goes from one end of the world to the other.
And it's so far and I need a car to get anywhere.
Sucks.
Boston is not really like that.
New York is like that.
And then that's yeah.
When I look at the line, it's like what?
It just looks like one huge strip of downtown New York.
It looks, it looks fine.
Yeah.
I don't.
I don't like New York.
Well, fair enough, I guess.
I like, I prefer a bus.
I like a curvy city.
I like roads that are weird and wacky and unique because they didn't know how to build roads back then.
That's what I like.
I like.
Stupid roads.
Actually, they knew it better because they are made for like people who can walk and not constructed for car traffic.
They would build it around the hill instead of destroying the hill to flatten it to make a cube.
And they would build it like towards like like city centers, marketplaces where the shops are and people gather and like making a spread from there instead of making just a grid over like a suburban like place for people to live.
Yeah.
I think when it comes to like, because I can say that one of the things they say about the line is like, it's walkable.
You're in your little pod and you can walk to the nearby grocery cube and you can go to the park area and it's like, you know, conceptually, not like terrible.
Like I like that they're trying to make it walkable.
They're trying to put trees in it.
I just, it's sort of the aesthetic of the future with the, the gray squares and the concrete this and that.
Don't you have like a rich history of architecture?
Put some like cool Saudi Arabian like architecture with like stone things and make it look like a marketplace from Aladdin.
Or you're just being a sentimental.
I'm just, I'm just being a fucking, I'm just being kind of racist, but I like old buildings.
I like old buildings in the, in the.
The line's cool, but can you make it look like Aladdin though?
I hate that.
I would prefer that though.
Not, not a single onion dome in sight.
Like are you, are you joking me?
What's the point?
Could you use like wooden planks instead of like concrete slabs?
I like wood.
Wood is cool.
Could you get some cloth?
I'm okay with squares.
I'm okay with concrete.
Like you can walk in, you can walk in your little pod section and like there's only so many things you can walk to.
Just this one thing and then you walk further and then that's the next pod section and it probably looks similar because like to be.
Yeah, that's what a city is.
Not necessarily cities have different areas that feel different and have like different focuses of like culture and like things you can buy there and like things you can do there.
Think of a video game.
Imagine if you're playing Dark Souls and every place in Dark Souls is the same place.
You go from one place to the other place and it's a new place.
There's new enemies, but it's the same architecture every single time.
It would get boring.
It would get dull.
It would be like, where's, where's anything new?
Where's variety?
That was a joke by the way.
It's not like that.
Just a little bit.
They reuse a lot of enemies and ruins and stuff.
It's like the same kind of ruin everywhere.
Okay.
Imagine this.
It's Dark Souls, but it's set in the line and because you can always see the horizon.
You can always see the point that like the lines converge on and you have to go in that direction and you have to fight through a gauntlet of big armor dudes that come out of the big concrete squares.
This is Final Fantasy 13.
Shoot machine guns at you.
15?
13.
The one where it's like notorious for being a hallway.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Hallway is right.
Okay.
Well, good.
No, not good.
You know?
Sounds cool actually.
I like, here's my favorite aesthetic is like a seaside town in the Mediterranean with
those like bright white, I don't know what they're made of like clay houses with like stuff.
That's what I like.
The ones like set into like a cliff?
Yeah, set into the side of the hills and sort of.
Are those called adobes?
I don't know if it's a specific type of building.
It's just sort of like, I like when there's a Mediterranean, it's like a hot climate and they have like colorful roofs, all the same color.
Or maybe it's like, there's a few red ones here, some yellow ones here.
And then there's like white walls or like peach walls and little cobbled streets and small little alleyways.
And it's all going down to the ocean where there's the harbor and there's the ships.
That's what I like.
That's my favorite sort of location.
I have a city in mind that is exactly like you described and one of my favorite places to be at wait.
What's it called?
Damn it.
I have to look on Google Maps.
Oh, Bonifacio on course.
Bonifacio?
Bonifacio.
It's like that kind of like Mediterranean city that is like built on a cliff, on a seaside cliff and it looks like it's almost falling in.
Is it the one that you can see in the background of the skybox in Mario 64?
I really don't know.
This is nice.
Show me.
I'm uploading it right now.
Got a bit of a long exposure.
It's more orange than it would be, but that's a cool little place.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I said basically exactly there where you can see this.
Yes.
It's the higgledy-piggledy unregimented placement of the buildings, the different sizes, different slants of the roofs, different colors.
It's so tall and like so thin and built so funnily over the cliff.
They're going to fall over?
How many kids spit off the end of that cliff?
You can see the giant rocks that have fallen in the past thousands of years and so like, yeah, one day the rest is going to fall.
It's neat.
Finally, I like in movies about Jesus in Judea or whatever, people just live in holes carved into the wall.
In places in the Roman Empire, peasants would just live in freaking holes carved into the side of a silver rock wall.
It was great.
Everyone loved it.
I have to go back.
Another thing about the line, I think I would hate to be anywhere near the bottom just because of the sheer tallness of everything around me.
I would want to be at the top all the time.
I don't know whether I'd be allowed at the top because it's probably more expensive.
Would you feel claustrophobic to be kind of like at the bottom of it with the walls rising up on both sides of you?
Yeah.
Both sides and floor.
Maybe.
People are going to throw trash down there probably from the walkways.
I like a big open sky.
I like a big open flatter sort of area.
I kind of think it's cool.
The idea is that there'd be buildings on the wall going up both sides.
The buildings would be built into the wall.
They wouldn't be rooted on the ground rising up from it.
I think that sounds neat.
I think it sounds neat as hell, honestly.
But isn't that just houses with many stories?
Isn't that already the same thing?
Well, it would mean that in theory it would mean that I think it would change the considerations for how you built buildings.
I don't know.
I just can't get a sense of how the lights would get into that place.
I feel like it would be dark all the time.
I think it would just need to be wide enough.
I just think if you make it wide enough that the street down the middle of it is broad enough that the daylight can come in through the top.
I thought the daylight comes in through the mirror walls.
I thought it's like a one-sided mirror or something.
The outside walls.
I think the buildings are on the wall.
Yeah, buildings would stop.
I mean, maybe those walls look really thick from these images.
They would have to be.
Yeah.
I'm assuming the walls are opaque and extremely rigid.
I'm thinking of it like the same way in an airport they have big windows,
the roof is always above them and shading everything.
If the sun isn't shooting through the window, it's dark, even though you can see outside.
I feel like that's how it would feel.
You would be in the shade looking out at the desert, and that's all.
I'm like, ah, jeez.
I shouldn't have made that left-turned-out bookway key.
I would go check it out.
I'd go check out the line.
I probably couldn't afford to live there.
No, no, no.
Well, that's all I got to say about that.
Yeah, I don't know if they're going to make it like a bridge people place,
because it doesn't even have a street.
Like, bridge people need a place to drive their expensive cars.
If it's just public transportation.
They'll have an airport at the top.
You can land your private jet.
I could actually imagine that they put just a highway on top.
You cover everything with a highway?
Yes, just on top and all under the highway.
And then the smoke would fall down into and suffocate everyone inside.
And then they also have to build parking lots next to the line,
just giant parking lot buildings.
No more cars.
Shoot the tires.
Shoot them.
I'm tired of tires.
Americans need cars to drive across the big desert in the middle of the country.
Yeah.
That nobody wants to be in.
You do that all the time, like, every two weeks.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
Yeah, of course.
Some people do for some reason.
You know what would be a cooler line is a vertical one.
If they build like a line straight up.
Cut the skyscraper.
No, no, no.
I mean, like a seven kilometer like into space,
like you can take an elevator to get to space.
And then you could jump and land on the moon.
You just jump like five feet as it flies past.
He's like, here it comes.
And then you go, whoop, splat and you're on the moon.
I think space elevator is something I've heard before.
Like, I think people tried that.
Or like, at least different plans.
The Apple Seed Manga.
Yeah, it's in Mega Man X8.
The Jacob Project for the Orbital Elevator.
Because obviously they can't build space travel
not after the Eurasia incident, obviously.
We don't talk about the Eurasia incident.
What happened to Eurasia?
The space colony Eurasia, idiot.
Not the sub, not the continent, not the continent group.
Obviously, listen, you don't know your history.
Is there a planet or a planet called Eurasia?
That'll explain everything, huh?
Is there a real planet called Eurasia or something?
Because there's a moon called Europe.
Europa?
Oh, no.
In Mega Man X5, there is an orbital.
It's like a space colony in orbit around the Earth
called Space Colony Eurasia.
Like an artificial satellite.
I was just freaked out for a second because, like,
holy shit, you call the moon Europa
because that's what we call Europe.
They just have the same name in my language.
I think there's...
It's like one of Jupiter's moons or something.
Jupiter or Saturn.
Yeah, something like that.
One of those stupid planets with, like, 18 moons
that nobody gives a fuck about.
I think that one's interesting because it's, like,
covered with water ice and liquid under the ice or something.
And people say there could be aliens on there.
There could be water aliens in the ice.
True, true.
It's not an apple seed.
It's Battle Angel Elite Manga
has, like, this cool concept for a floating city
that is suspended in the air
by there being an out-of-orbit other floating city
that it's connected to.
And, like, the out-of-orbit one is, like,
pulling the other one up.
And it's, like, attached with, like, these trash...
It's attached with a large, long, like, tube of stuff.
That's what I'm thinking of.
Yeah, they're, like, tubes of where they throw trash down
going down and under the floating city
where the second trash city where the story takes place.
Oh, yeah, yeah. That's where Battle Angel Elite lives
and she has, like, adventures.
I gotta read the rest of this,
because I remember reading, like, the first volume
at the Life Actions once.
I only watched the Life Action movie, and it was actually...
Oh, no, it's...
No, it was good. I liked the movie.
Oh, I mean, I didn't see the movie, but, like, the manga is amazing.
Yeah, I'm sure it is. It looks really good.
But the movie also looked really good.
It was really fun. I saw it, like, three times in the cinema.
And then I went back just for fun of it, because it was cheap.
I read the first volume of that manga,
and it freaked me out when that guy ate that lady's brain.
That was fucked up.
That's also in the film, I think.
Really?
Oh, at least there's a scene where they, like,
dissect, like, a lady who's just a character
and she's just a brain and a jaw,
and, like, eyes, like, next to it or something.
It's fun.
Yish. Yish.
I always want to...
I want these as physical copies,
because I don't like reading manga online that much,
at least not when it's long.
I like it either. Yeah.
But, like, I always see them in the bookstores,
and they're, like, 20 to 30 bucks a volume.
It's, like, so many of them.
Well, how many chapters is a volume?
I don't know how many chapters,
but there's at least, like, six volumes, so it's, like...
Yeah.
I could buy food for that.
Hmm. Hmm.
What do we think about voicemails?
Think it's about that time?
I think they suck.
Oh, I mean, should we do them? Yes, let's do them.
Yeah, okay. I agree on both counts.
Okay, let's see. I got them here.
Okay, I've never done this before, last time I was here.
We didn't have voicemails.
Well, I'll post them as attachments in the general.
Okay. Let's be listened to.
Let me just find the first one.
The first one from today is called...
It's called Very Talented.
Ooh, my neck just cracked.
Okay, here it is.
Three, two, one, go.
I can make Shadows, you know, the Pokemon.
Could you understand that?
He can make something, you know, the Pokemon,
and then he made a funny sound.
I think he imitated a Pokemon?
Or they imitated a Pokemon? I don't know.
Wait.
Bye-bye.
Saw.
I can't understand it.
The next one is Paramount.
Well, it's called Paramount.
There's a voicemail attached.
There's also a link.
Here's the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
And you have to look at this.
I said that s-p-c-p, hashtag,
but I guess you just used it the wrong time
because we couldn't voicemail.
I don't know.
He's saying you used the s-p-c-p.
Yeah, I guess we don't check it.
Oh, the hashtag.
I only check it when I make a tweet that's like,
hey, we're doing it by voice.
Yeah, I mean, I don't check the hashtag unless I announce it.
Okay, this gamma girl.itch.io.
This is like a claymation game called Gob.
This looks cool.
It does look cool, actually.
That's got just the right amount of grunge.
Yeah, I mean, I think of Hilux when I see it, obviously.
So dirty.
I love this PDA they're holding.
It looks like the curved plastic of the 2000s.
Yeah, it's just like a...
Okay, it's a point-and-click adventure.
Point-and-click mechanics without the pointing and clicking, it says.
Wordless design. What does it even have?
No pointing, clicking, and no words.
I mean, seems neat. Seems nifty.
Gob, huh? Okay.
Cool.
Next voicemail. Where did I put that?
The next one is... Oh, there's an image link here.
Let's see what's in it.
Big Mac. Big Mac, call the doctor quick.
Applejack just did the blackout challenge for her TikTok.
Oh, no. What the hell's that?
I don't want to...
Isn't that like when you put the black square on your social media
in solidarity with Black Lives Matter?
I think a big blackout challenge.
I guess that's not it.
I would imagine it could be like a blackface that TikTok is like doing.
Well, she's like throwing up, so...
Oh, the blackout challenge is resurfaced on TikTok,
and it's just as still as dangerous as it was 16 years ago.
Oh, it's just hold your breath until you pass out.
God.
Awesome.
Oh, yeah, somebody died doing it.
It has resulted in more than 80 deaths according to the CDC.
80? Oh, my God.
TikTok is extremely popular, so fuck.
So is death.
Okay, well, I get it.
Why? Apple Bloom, why?
Well, for the clout. For clout.
Same reason to do everything for clout.
She got the blackout challenge cutie mark at last.
More like blackout, more like black clout.
Nah, not really, though. Not if you die.
Next one is called Wiggler...
No, Wiggler Diggy.
Wait, don't play that one. That one's mine.
I can just say what I said. That's stupid.
Are you sure?
Yes, I know.
I recorded that yesterday before deciding that I want to be honest.
Remember that voice mail last week about the person who said
that the new Pokemon game is going to have a regional type that's not a regional type?
That's like Wiggler?
Yeah.
Yeah, the Worm Diglet thing.
So what they said is that it's not a regional variant
because regional variants can't change their biology or something like that.
That's why there's never been a regional variant that's a bug type
because a bug type is more fundamental to their biology
and it's not just attaching a different element to an animal.
So, okay, Bullpix for example.
That's like a fire fox, right?
And the variant is just an ice fox.
But you couldn't easily make it a bug type because what's a bug fox?
That's gonna be completely different.
Just give it a big ice.
Multiple ice.
Okay.
Wigglet is not a mammal or a mole kind of creature.
It's an eel. It's a fish.
So it's not...
And that's why it's specifically not a regional variant
and they said that when they announced that Pokemon.
So they're doing something new?
I guess so.
It's just sort of confusing because Pokemon biology doesn't necessarily correlate
to the way that we have genuses and subspecies in real life
and evolution the actual way it is.
I feel like whether it is or isn't a regional variant is sort of like a semantic difference.
Like a regional variants are still a distinct creature.
In Pokemon, yeah.
I guess the idea is regional variants in the real world are like,
oh, it's like the same species.
But a different kind of food or something.
I know, but that Pokemon doesn't follow a real world.
Well, that's what I mean.
It's like if the regional variants and this new thing are following real life rules
and naming conventions, then I guess they're not regional variants.
It's just kind of the difference between like a white bunny and a dark brown body
that's bigger and like a horse and a sea horse.
They're trying something there.
I mean, to me, it's like...
This is sort of like, I don't know, like a patcherisu.
A patcherisu is not Pikachu, but it's sort of a similar creature inspired by the other thing.
And that's not a variant of Pikachu.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like there's like a lowland, right?
There's an lowland right you, yeah.
That's kind of just different color than psychic type or something.
And that's...
I don't know.
I think it's neat when they try new things.
I mean...
I still don't think there's like a rule that says you can't have a bug variant of a region.
It just hasn't happened yet.
I mean, you could easily have like a regional variant of like Butterfree that's like bug ghost type or something.
And it just like is purple, I don't know.
It's a dead bug.
Yeah, when the butterflies go to this region, they will die.
It has like a needle in it that's like on styrofoam.
Like it's been preserved.
Very nice.
Yeah, I like it.
Yeah, I mean, I guess I get what you're saying, that like it would be weird if something were a bug.
That's a good quote.
I mean, they could make like, what if they made like a regional variant of Krabby that was like a land crab.
And it was like bug rock or bug round or something.
Yeah.
Something like that.
I guess it's still like the same...
It's still the same like basic species kind of.
Crabs are just sea bugs.
So fucked up that it's just pure water type.
I mean, bug is not a scientific term.
If there's a rule that says mammals have to be mammals and they can't be bugs, then I don't want to live in that world.
I mean, we don't have a bug evolution.
Not yet.
They'll have to do it at some point.
I don't think they're ever gonna add a new one.
What do you mean they don't have a bug evolution?
Oh, for Eevee?
Oh, yeah.
You don't think they'll add more Eeveelutions?
I mean, the last time was like three games ago or something.
I feel like they might add another one.
I mean, I don't know why they wouldn't.
I see no reason not to add a new one every now and then.
Like what is left?
Dragon, bug, round, rock, fighting.
Do they not have a ground or a rock?
No, I don't think so.
No.
Those are obvious ones.
You gotta have a rock.
Yeah.
It just feels like there's so many obvious ones that it's weird that they haven't done any
for Thunderborn and Sword and Shield.
I agree.
Why stop with Fairy?
Why stop at, you know, what do they got?
Like eight or something?
They didn't even stop just with the normal elemental things.
No, they did Dark and Psychic.
Elemental ones missing.
Yeah, they did Dark and Psychic, which are weird.
It feels random.
They could totally do.
They could totally do a whole bunch more.
I don't know why they wouldn't.
Got an order and chaos.
Maybe.
I mean, with the bug one, like what would be like a weird bug cat?
Like just a cat that has like a segmented, like off body.
Yeah, I feel like it would be like a fluffy sort of like moth, like like a neck fruff.
And maybe you would have little little bug wings.
Maybe you could just have compound eyes, maybe.
I think it would be cool.
I think they could do a cool, a cool one.
You know, I was, I was shocked to see that they made a frickin.
What are they called?
Oh God, what are they called?
The golems with the dots on them.
No.
Oh, no.
I was shocked to make this.
They made a frickin dragon Reggie.
Like what the fuck is that?
I forgot about this game.
I think it looks cool though.
It looks cool, but like.
That one looks better than the other Reggie's.
It looks, I mean, it's, it's weird that like what it's like made of like, it's made of dragon.
Like what the fuck?
What the fuck?
But I mean, if they'll do that.
I mean, what are, what are all any of the Reggie's?
I mean, it's, it's pretty clear that like the first three are, or the first four are like creatures that are made of stuff.
And the, you know, they're like a golem made of ice, a golem made of rock, a golem made of steel, a golem made of, I don't know, nothing for his Reggie Giggis.
Made of normal stuff.
And, and then, oh yeah, how about a golem that's made of electricity?
How about a golem that's made of the concept of being a dragon?
Do they even have a Reggie water?
I, I think it's just those six.
I mean, that's an ice.
Yeah, Reggie.
Yeah.
Well, that was, it was, it was ice rock steel, and then they, and Giggis, and then they added, they added electric and dragon and that's right.
They just added the two.
I don't even know.
They do have an electric one.
I still like his design.
He's just, he's just a guy.
He's just an orb with little feet.
Which one?
A Reggie dragon.
Let's put him in the description.
Look at it.
It's, he's like the uvula of a dragon or a tongue.
He's like the tongue of a dragon.
I imagine it's like some kind of species that lives inside of dragon skulls, like a hermit crab or something like that.
That gets bore or like.
Like what the, like what the fuck is that?
It's a llama.
I'm sorry.
This one honestly, this one actually kind of bugs me a little bit because like what the fuck is it?
There's lots of book.
It's a, it's a sphere of dragon meat with a skull of itself.
It looks mysterious.
Like what is it made of?
Dragon.
Sure.
I get.
You know in Elton Ring you get a sword when you kill the big dragon guy and it's made out of dragon.
Just a dragon piece.
Makes sense.
Like if there was some like rule for the Reggies being like imbued with an essence of something.
Then I guess if you shove a dragon in there it could make a dragon guy.
Just shove it, just shove a dragon in there and see what comes out.
If you put a ferret in there that could be like a Reggie ferret.
The thing is like the concept of being a dragon is so loose too.
Like it makes sense if something is like electric because it has electric power.
But what does it even mean to have a dragon?
It's really, it's even, yeah.
It's just a social construct.
Kind of like bug.
Yeah.
There's no, there's no such thing as a bug.
There's a bit more to bug.
There's a bit more biology to bug.
Like they're all like off reports.
Right.
But I mean like Krabby is not a bug even though it's also an arthropod.
Yeah.
There's always weird exceptions.
I mean.
Yeah, but it'd be a dragon that's even more like.
What's the name of the fire?
What about the starter fire dragon?
I forgot his name.
Fuck.
Charizard.
He's the dragon type evil, right?
How would you forget Charizard?
I, well, first of all, I didn't grow up with Pokemon.
I played my first Pokemon game like three years ago.
And also I know the German names.
It's Grumanda.
Grumanda?
Grumanda.
Like, like glued.
Like glooming, no, embers.
It's like, it's named after embers basically.
Hmm.
Neat.
Well, you know, they made him, he has the dragon type mega evolution, but like whatever.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Grumanda.
He's clearly a dragon, but they didn't make him one because I don't know, for balancing
reasons, I guess?
I guess because the dragon type was too good in gen one.
I think that, I think that's probably why.
Yeah, it's just funny that's the most iconic looking dragon just looks like a normal European
idea of a dragon more than anyone else.
I really liked, I really liked Drampa.
I thought Drampa was really cool.
You know him from, I think he's from, I think he's from X and Y.
No, he might be from Alola.
What one was that?
The one that sort of, it sort of looks like a Chinese dragon.
Oh yeah, no, that's from, that's from Alola.
Okay.
Yeah.
That looks kind of watery.
Yes.
It's like the white, the white like furry tail and stuff.
Yeah, that's neat.
I like him a lot.
Yeah.
There's a lot of cool dragons.
I like dragon.
They should just make Pokemon but just with dragon.
Hey, was Temtem any good?
Anyone play Temtem?
No idea.
You know, they made some indie devs made like a Pokemon MMO called Temtem.
I mean, it wasn't officially Pokemon.
And then I heard a lot of buzz around it when it came out and then I haven't really really heard anything about it in a while.
I mean, I think I got like wins or falls of the monster designs, right?
Like they got to be really good to like be a competitor.
Yeah.
I was like, I don't really remember.
I didn't really see that many of them.
So I don't know if they were any good or not.
They look all right.
Some of them look a bit too much like Pokemon and some of them don't really look too much like anything.
Here's a picture of their poster, I guess.
Okay.
All right.
They look like fun creatures, but I don't know if they probably don't have the same degree of iconosism as Pokemon signs have.
When I, when I heard about it, I was really excited about it because I'd always thought a Pokemon MMO would be super cool.
So I kind of in the back of my mind said I should play that.
But like, yeah, I haven't heard, haven't heard much about it for a while now.
So I don't know.
I wonder if it was any, I wonder if it was any good.
I think people overlook the marketing of the original Pokemon games and how it's just sort of like aesthetically pleasing to have like a blue Pokemon and a red Pokemon and a green Pokemon and choose.
Yeah, these are immediately two complex, I think.
Yeah, there's no like a theme.
I couldn't tell which one's the starters.
With the color design.
Who's the starters?
It's just sort of like, what if they were cool monster designs?
I was like, yeah, I'm sure.
But like, who's your mascot?
I don't know who Temtemon's mascot is.
That's why they keep the Gen 1 Pokemon and every Pokemon game almost like to like, yeah, these are so iconic and get rid of them.
There's a an old Tim Rogers video for Kotaku where he talks about Pokemon.
Yeah, and he says that like the marketing of Pokemon with like the red and blue, like it's like layers and layers of like making you make decisions about it.
Like before you even play the game, you have to choose red or blue and you're already invested.
And even before that, like even when you hear about Pokemon, you have to choose like, which one would you play, red or blue?
And then it's like, well, you have to pick one or the other or like, or else you have to make the conscious decision not to play it.
Like in order to not play it, you have to make a conscious decision not to do that.
Yeah.
It's, it's pretty genius actually.
It's like immediately presenting you with this binary set of options and it's like, well, you're all you're already playing the game much like Undertale.
You're already playing the game, whether you want to or not.
I'm probably going to play the new one.
I don't have a switch, but my, I'm sometimes babysitting my little cousin and he has a switch.
So I can just like, when he goes to bed, I can just play on switch and it usually gets a new Pokemon games and stuff.
Mercifully, I do not have a switch.
Wait, didn't you play Animal Crossing?
I played it on my roommate switch.
Yeah.
The roommate's gone now.
So I guess I'll, I guess I'll never go.
I guess I'll never go back to Yakitori Island.
What about your roses?
Make like a billion black roses.
Yeah.
All those roses are gone.
Damn.
Oh well.
That actually makes me a little sad.
It passed, it passed the time.
I was going to.
It's like a whole arc.
Yeah.
That's true.
I was, I was going to build a, I sort of had built up sort of a little piece of the island.
I was going to make a little like industrial city complex, like in one corner.
That was the goal anyway.
It ended up, I kind of ended up sort of like, sort of struggling with like what my options were and like how I could even make that really happen.
So, I don't know.
It's okay.
Is the, is the new leaf?
Am I crossing?
Is that good?
Because I have it.
On the DS?
Yeah.
I think it's for the 2DS, 3DS.
I, I think I played it a bit.
I don't know if I, I didn't play, I definitely didn't play it as much as New Horizons.
I mean, I think it's gotten most of what New Horizons has.
Oh.
Well.
Maybe not, maybe not as much item variety as that, but.
Anyway, where was I?
We were on the next, the next voicemail.
The next voicemail was.
By the way, I may need to go in like 40 minutes.
Then I'll stretch for 10.
Well, let's try and get through these.
The next one is called Week of 10, 29, 22.
I think this is Vinny's stuff.
It's a, it's an album.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's an album.
Why is the, why is the, the thumbnail of a fat molecule?
We'll find out in context.
Co-worker saw me doodling.
They're making it harder to, they're making it harder to stay sane at work.
I couldn't draw as much as I'd like to.
Co-worker saw me doodling and asked if I could do a dragon.
So I did.
Good dragon.
Then Saint.
God, I hope he didn't see you drawing Ben Saint's stand slime time and ask like, hey,
what are you drawing?
Like, hey, what's.
The first figure closest to him is Lipid, the, then Uwupadi, then to the right is Toxicity.
Toxicity is Ben's bile and expulsions compressed into a dense structure to make its touch lethal.
Then Saint is filth and fury down to the bone.
So what's Lipid?
Is it my fat?
Is it my keto?
Yeah, I guess.
I think it's your fat, your slime and your bile.
Great.
Buffalo Uwupadi is very distracting, very scary.
I'm checking my phone somehow one sec.
One sec.
Checking Twitter.
Lol, take your time.
I know what you're doing.
Wait, do I have another guitar there?
Is it like a little ukulele case?
Yes.
So what's in the smaller guitar case?
I know you play the one.
Oh, this.
It's actually a gift.
I was given.
I was given for you.
Isomoto Ligo Sakura.
Oh, shit.
Holy shit.
Yep.
I can't believe it.
Why would I carry it in a little ukulele case?
It's like a Breaking Bad Blue Crystal Man.
The fat molecule.
This is what Ben Saint stands original shape is.
What?
These are Lipid.
I know what these are.
These are Lipids.
That's fats, right?
Yeah.
This is just a diagram of variations.
I was looking for designing the stand for Ben Saint.
Wait, I'm looking at...
Oh, the shape of the head is like a molecule.
I think that's very strange.
I get so many stands.
I'm just a wash with stands.
Very cool.
Thanks, Vinny.
I just feel like that they added the dragon.
That's very...
Here's a dragon.
I want to see all the dragons.
Please draw more dragons.
More dragons.
Next one is...
And dragon types.
An untitled album.
We finally...
We finally found it.
A mammoth.
It's Poptropica Lego.
Oh, it's a...
Poptropica.
It's a Lego mammoth.
Cool and white.
She said I don't even know what I said.
Pretty cool.
This little custom bespoke piece for a mammoth trapped in an ice block.
Yeah.
Very, very nifty.
I actually had a Playmobil, like, Playworld that was the same thing,
but with dinosaurs trapped in ice cubes and stuff.
And like...
Do you know Playmobil?
Is there a thing over there?
Oh, yeah, I know.
Yeah, I never had it.
But I know...
Is it like Duplo?
It's not building blocks.
But it's still kind of like...
The similarity is the little people have removable hair
and they can put little things in their Lego mittens.
Yeah, and they're still kind of made of different segments
that you can build in different ways.
But it's not as...
It's not tiny pieces.
It's bigger segments.
And it's way cheaper than Lego.
It's definitely way cheaper than Lego and they just make better sets for your money.
But like...
Yeah.
Plastic is used more efficiently.
I always liked it with Playmobil.
You could take their hair off and replace it with different hair.
But inside their head is like a...
It's just a hollow little sphere.
So if you take their hair off and you misplace it,
they are now like an open skull.
They're Maggie.
They're Maggie from me.
Put a little maggot inside.
Oh, right, right, right.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, then next one is called Wild Tails.
Use Streamio.
Shish piracy.
Three, two, one, go.
Very cool, very interesting.
Argentinian movie.
Wild Tails.
I think Ben would really like it.
It's like human.
Human thesis, human dissertation.
Inspire me for a lot of stuff.
What did he say?
Ben would like it.
It's like...
There's a human thesis in it.
Human thesis?
Yeah.
Yeah, like a thesis on human condition or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is that all he said about it?
I think so.
Six short stories that explore the extremities of human behavior
involving people in distress.
I love people in distress.
True, true.
I mean, I like...
I'm down for vignettes, I guess.
I don't know, it could be good.
All right, next one is called Ben St.
More Like Ben Stupid.
I'm on it.
That's just mean, that's just uncalled for.
Three, two, one, go.
The late China QOCs.
Is that what China QOCs?
Literally 20 years plus of using the internet
and you don't know what Sonic OCs look like.
Wow, Ben St.
I thought you were the smart one.
Yes, I do.
What is he talking about?
You made a brief goof
where you thought something was a Sonic QOC
rather than just a Sonic OC.
Right, right, right, right.
Oh, that's right, that's right, that's right.
My mind just went...
I just think...
I'm sorry, I'm literally more familiar with Sonic Q
than I am with Sonic the Hedgehog.
I have consumed more Sonic 2 media, so...
Terrifying.
It's just where my mind goes.
I'm sorry, I've never played a Sonic game and I never will.
Incredible, even I've played a Sonic game.
I mean, I've played a little bit of like
and knuckles on like my friend's Genesis
when I was like a little kid.
Next one is called...
Ben St. More Like Ben's Stupid 2.
The sequel, okay.
Wait, sorry, I'm posting it now.
There it is.
3, 2, 1, go.
An addendum to that last one.
Like, literally, you were a Brony Ben St.
You were Brony St.
Phantom Horn.
Did you forget that?
No.
Have you literally forgotten?
Like the Pony O'Sauce?
What do you mean Pony O'Sauce?
Like fucking wow.
Gotcha.
What did I do to deserve this?
This guy's really pissed off.
He was really offensive.
He had his feelings.
Yeah.
Next one is called...
Is This Cannon?
Gwib?
I think it's meant to say Gib.
There it is, it's an Imgur album.
British people having sex be like...
Scrumptious.
It's Tuesday in it.
Why would you say it's Tuesday?
You're in a sex.
That's got nothing to do with it.
Oh, Eleazar, don't link this one
because it gives you the mature content
warning like RU18+.
Yeah, well last time when we linked Vinny's album
even though there was nothing bad in it
because it asked RU18+,
it gave us a freaking content strike
so Eleazar, do not link this album
please, although I'm pretty sure
you can show the image.
Yes, it's true.
It is always Tuesday
when British people have sex.
It's always Tuesday,
but I'm waiting for shit Wednesday.
That's after.
When the Holy Spirit will give me my tongues.
There's only one more,
only one more of these damnable things.
It is...
Wait, I found it.
It's called I Scream Halloween
into my mic for 40 seconds.
Oh, no.
Okay, let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
Boys and girls of every age
wouldn't you like to see something strange?
Come with us and you will see
this entire town of Halloween.
This is Halloween.
This is not what he said it would be.
Everybody make a scene.
We're going to get a copyright.
We're gonna get a copyrighted idea
for the movie song.
We go home, everybody
heads to the pumpkin song.
Nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya.
That's what I thought it would be.
Yeah, I was hoping for him to scream
Scream the word
That's what he advertised so I feel I feel disappointed. Yeah, I feel like I was misled
does remind me of of the
the
Nalaka calm version the endless war version that everybody did. Oh, that's why I know the song from
That I mean first I got us just yes, that was that was so great
But what do you mean you would you don't know the original? I don't think so
It's the nightmare before Christmas Tim Burton film skeleton guy. That's so funny. Oh god. I actually haven't seen you in the Nalaka calm version
Haven't seen it yet. Well, I
Was I mean I said I was I was I was too scared to watch it as a kid. I thought it looked spooky
Maybe I should watch it was spooky, but I did watch it and I was scared by the bugs coming from the big guy
That sounds great. I should watch it. Oh
Yeah, there's a guy who's filled with bugs and it is disturbing
We're done we fulfilled our obligations hooray. Oh god. We did was three and a half hours. Oh my god
Where does the time go? I'm really hungry and it's really dark
I'm sleepy. I might like I don't like go to bed or I say I was up all night
I fucked up my sleep schedule the night is start of the render because nothing matters anymore
Okay, well any last words before we walk the plank
Twitter.com slash never paint. Please commission me. I draw you
Never paint will draw anything except if it's like bad
I
Draw things that are bad. You know me if you have a bad idea like if you want to draw like Nazi propaganda keep will draw
Good ideas to never paint bad ideas to give that's that's how we're doing the division of labor here
Check out my mega man lecture on my channel unless some unless something went wrong and for some
tragic unforeseen reason
It was not able to happen unless I had a power outage at some point in the next
89 hours and my render fails or something like that
Right now. Oh do we have 24?
We're at 24, baby. We're getting there 24 percent. That's almost a quarter
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators in case you haven't heard all the bonus content
Help make PCP HQ real help make PCP HQ real. We are so close. We are we are
We are getting closer every day
Every pluge gets us closer
That's true
It's true. It's true. Um, I
Guess I think that's everything. I think that's all oh
Speak about comm slash PCV voicemail if you want to leave us a voicemail for next week and that's gonna do it. I think
Goodbye for now
everybody
Good morning, Australia or whoever somebody's in Australia
Are they though? I hope not. I hope we don't have any listeners in Australia
We have at least one
Don't tell me that