Come on everyone sit down at this end, so that you can procrastinate along with me. You know I'm supposed to be working, but instead I'm watching PC.
Let's make this the mean cast. Let's get mean this episode.
No, I know.
Let's bully Mage.
Munchy, what are you fucking dissenting? You want to be the next bullied? You want to be bullied?
You want to be on the end of my Roth?
You're Roth.
I'm fucking Roth Munchy. I am fucking Roth and you're gonna know about it.
There's that movie 7 with Brad Pitt and Morgan Freeman.
Yeah, I don't like it.
Remember at the end how Brad Pitt became Roth? That was pretty cool.
Oh yeah.
That's Ben.
Yeah.
Munchy killed his wife and put his wife's head in a box.
I became Roth by being Roth.
I really love the word Roth by the way.
Is it different from Roth?
Yeah, it's like the adjective.
Oh yeah.
If you have Roth then you are Roth.
I've always had an issue with the end of that movie but I'll save it for the podcast.
Okay, let's get into it.
Here we go. The 7 casts.
Oh, I'm interested. I just watched that the other day. It's a great movie.
God damn it.
Now we're waiting for Mage to get her shit together.
This is why Penalty. Bam.
Munchy opened the floodgates by informing her that we hadn't started yet.
This is why I was opposed to saying I think the penalty should have been we just don't inform her that we're all here.
You know she's not even going to say anything. She's going to be a typical Mage, typical Tom.
She's going to get in here.
That's why we shouldn't have said anything.
She's going to get in.
God damn it.
I mean we should just penalize people that don't talk.
That opens the floodgates to some complicated stuff.
What is the line between not talking enough and where is the line drawn there?
We just got to feel it out.
Okay, here's the thing.
If someone's there and they're present and they're engaged but they happen to be someone who doesn't talk that much
like Hippo sometimes is.
Mage literally sits and draws during the podcast.
Okay, see the thing like drawing or I think on occasion like Tom has like been programming
well that right there is not a full commitment to being on the episode.
I don't think that's cool.
I don't want to pick on the guy. God rest his soul because of the current complications
but there's been numerous times where Tom like has said literally nothing on a podcast.
Well again if he's there and he just doesn't have anything to say.
He's just showing up to siphon off some PCP panties.
Frankly, frankly, I think the quote-unquote flugger.
Not every time.
Not every time but there's been a few times.
Of course not.
Some of us talk more than others obviously but I can't believe someone.
What it really comes down to is
Hippo is fully engaged.
We need to decide is this a friendship cast or is this a like produce the best podcast possible cast?
Because you know there's a difference there.
Well I don't think there's a difference.
I don't think that makes a difference.
I think there's a balance there.
It can be a clusterfuck but obviously we all want it to be good.
Yes, I mean that's totally true.
But like if Mage, let's just say for example,
introduce yourself at the beginning and then just for example,
literally said nothing the whole episode and at the end said,
look what I draw while you guys were doing the podcast essentially.
It'd be like well how is that fair that this is like an equal share of the work?
Because it's clearly not.
Okay, I don't disagree there.
I just wouldn't use the same language.
I mean it's never been to that extent.
Well that's true.
So it's a bit of a dare I call that a straw man argument.
But if we started docking pay for people who aren't talking enough,
that would encourage more of a clusterfuck to like interrupt and stuff?
Yeah, and I don't know about all that.
Well I think people should be interrupting each other.
It's fine.
It's fine for people to interrupt each other.
No, interrupting is to an extent.
Interrupting sucks.
Yeah, to an extent.
It's bad for the podcast.
Hey Mage, we have not started yet.
Well actually we are technically recording and I encourage you to start doing so as well.
I am not recording.
But we will not actually start.
Okay, sick.
So here's a thought.
What we could do is just take this audio and just make it like a secret link on the thing.
It's like the secret precast cast or something.
But that would require extra work maybe.
Hold on.
I don't have any reservations.
I have no reservations.
That's fine.
Yeah, I don't know.
Me neither.
Well I guess we're all here now.
We can sync at this point and then start.
Wait, should we talk about what we were talking about before?
I mean, I don't think we have much to say.
Mage, we are currently riffing and raffin on the subject of how first of all, like is
it fair to dock someone's pay if the episode has not yet begun but like they show up before
the recording starts or they are late past the 10 minute thing.
Okay.
You know what?
I've actually revised my position because I think in the past we've said that like
technically there's a quality.
I think technically they qualify for a penalty but I think in the past we've said, okay,
we didn't actually start yet so it doesn't matter.
I basically agree with that personally.
Absolutely agree.
All right.
Yeah.
I've changed my mind.
The reason to have a penalty is so that like you did not contribute as much as the others.
That's how I think about it as well.
And I mean, like the greatest penalty of all I think should be if the others are organized
and they start the episode on time then you just don't get to join or if you do you're late.
I mean, I think that it's worth letting people join late as long as they know what they're
doing.
I actually kind of like when people join.
I just think, you know, if you weren't there when you were supposed to be and you joined
late, you know, you shouldn't get the full PC penny load for it.
I agree.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, on the larger subject of like divvying up pay based on contributions, that's a whole
can of worms.
That is a whole can of worms.
Yeah.
So I'm not even prepared to get into that in a serious way here.
Although, Mage, do you feel that sometimes, I'm curious what your opinion would be on
this.
There have been occasions where you, you know, you generally don't talk as much as other
people in the podcast sometimes.
You and Tom.
You and Tom are the offenders.
And then at the end, you in particular have done this where you just, hey, like, hey guys,
look at the picture I drew, which kind of implies as opposed to being engaged in the
podcast.
Now I don't find this hugely offensive or anything, but it's like, it shows a distraction
and a deep prioritization of, you know, contributing to the show.
No, that's not how I do it.
I usually draw things to keep myself focused.
I do, I do listen to what you guys say is just sometimes I don't have anything to say
or it's hard to interject, especially when you guys are very...
There is a lot, there is a lot as, I noticed this editing, there is a lot of Mage trying
to interject and getting cut off and...
Okay.
Well, that's fair.
I got two, I got two things to say about that.
One, I don't think the fact that you're drawing is necessarily a problem as long as you're
engaged.
Yeah.
You do try to interject.
I've seen this criticism in the comments and I'm going to echo it.
Instead of trying to interject with a, let me like, hey, I have something to say.
Just interject with the thing you have to say.
Then it won't be heard though.
Yes.
If you do it loud enough.
Just keep doing it.
Don't fucking take no for an answer.
I mean, I'd have to agree that that would be better, but you know, I get it.
I get it.
This is a sort of like social Darwinism, but I will say it's absolutely terrible when you're
like speaking and then someone like interrupts you and then like the conversation is completely
unsalvageable.
Yeah.
We've all got to deal with that.
It is like a Darwin.
It's like that.
It happens to everyone.
When you're talking and someone else is talking and you know that one of you has to give up
and stop talking and it's like a battle of wills for a little while.
Yeah.
I think once in a while, two people will be like so dead set on saying whatever they're
saying that they both talking and they can both clearly hear the other person talking,
but they're just going to keep going because it's like, no, fuck that.
And when that happens, like it's up to the editor to decide who is more important to
the conversation.
I don't think so.
I mean, if I'm the editor of that, just leave them both in.
That's the honest truth.
That's what happens.
Or at least cut it so that like it's one after the other.
I do a lot of like, I do a lot of fucking editing to make the podcast less terrible.
I don't.
I mean, yeah.
Fuck that.
It's not just about recapturing it.
It is like a product we're producing here.
So if you can make it like improved by spacing that, I think that's all fine and well.
I mean, I guess.
I think it legitimately impacts the like the quality of the show to have constant interruptions
and to have it be like talking over one another.
You can't really tell what's happening.
I don't think it's that bad.
I don't think it's where that talking over each other.
I mean, you see people complain about it, but every voice.
That's the main thing about the show.
It's core.
It's core to the show.
That happens every episode.
Wait, what's core?
Talking over other people?
Yeah.
Talking over each other.
Well, it's core to the show, but like, I mean, I'm really thinking that this is a product
if it can be improved by like de-overlapping people.
The product.
It's like a good thing to do.
I don't know.
To me, the product is we record ourselves talking for two hours.
It's not.
I mean.
There's probably an artistry there between balancing like friendly banter and then like
listenability.
I think there is something to be, there is probably a reason.
I don't know what the fuck I'm fucking going to say.
Because like if we were talking in person.
This is all going to the show.
If we were talking.
Yeah, this is all going to the show.
If we were all in a room together talking in person, there would be less interrupting
and the conversation would flow better.
That's true.
That's definitely true.
So talking over discord, a little lag in the interrupting that comes with this, there
has to be some kind of editing to sort of fix it to where it would be if we were actually
in a room together.
Hey, here's a question.
This is a phenomenon.
It seems like Jesse gets talked over more than anyone else.
And I've yet to figure out exactly why I might be, I mean, it might be because of lag because
he doesn't have like the worst connection.
Well, let me, let me, let me propose, let me propose a reversal of causality and cause
or causation cause and effect here.
Maybe he gets talked over more because he tries to interrupt more.
Could that be the case?
He went robo.
I'm not.
I'm not calling Jesse an interrupting mean man or anything, but maybe he could be getting
talked over more because he's attempting to interrupt more.
I don't, I suppose it's possible.
I mean, I feel like I, if two people are talking about something, I try to stay out of it unless
I really have something.
I don't think I interrupt more than anyone else.
Again, that's not me saying Jesse, stop interrupting.
I don't think that's a problem at all.
I don't know.
But I do, and if I am interrupting, then I do hate myself and I will lash myself with
the fucking cat and nine tails.
Maybe it's that you're more courteous than like someone like me where I will just, I
don't give a fuck and I'll keep going, but you're like, well, I'm going to let this person
speak and I'll let them go first.
Maybe you're just nicer in conversation.
That's possible.
I don't know.
I'm a little known badass.
You might call me a badass.
That's what I am.
Can I get the Urban Dictionary definition of a conversation, please?
Let me pull that up.
I feel kind of lost right now.
Should we start recording?
Oh my God, Ben!
You motherfucker!
No, no, no, no, no.
I didn't mean recording.
I mean, like, start the actual episode.
I mean, this is, we should put this in.
We should, we just haven't synced yet.
Oh, is this going in?
Oh, this is going in.
Yeah.
Let's fucking put it in.
Hey, here's the thing.
Okay.
Conversation, Urban Dictionary.
We're doing it, people.
The act of hooking up with one, usually in a sexual fashion.
That's the definition of a conversation.
Whoa, wait.
What the fuck?
That's what we're just doing this whole time?
Oh, no!
No!
Listen to these examples.
One, man, did I get some good conversation last night?
And then, leave us alone.
We're having a deep conversation, Nate says, as Munchy burst into his sex dungeon.
Gross.
I think the ideal podcast format is where people can have a thought and then say that
thought to completion and then have it be discussed instead of saying like a quarter
of the thought, having people interrupt and then say another quarter of the thought.
And then the conversation completely derail and you go into another topic before the
other one can even be finished.
I think that interruptions are not a great thing in general, but when two people are
clashing and they're trying to argue each other and shouting over each other, I think
that that, you know, in a way, I almost see it as like a historical record.
That sounds a little grandiose, but it's like this is a record of what the conversation
was and how it happened.
Yeah, but it does get hard to listen to.
When people are talking to each other and like stuttering and like trying to interjecting
and failing, like all that stuff I think should, some effort should be put into having it all
cut out.
And that's one of the things that we should be looking for in an editor is that kind
of audio engineering, making it all so unclean and, you know, making sure that we don't sound
like inarticulate fucking baboons.
What I think is really interesting learning like, like, like, like, like, like, like,
like, for example, when you start a sentence and you have to say the same word over and
over again because you don't know what the fuck your brain is doing yet.
Like when you do that, you just, I would like cut all the likes prior to the first to the
end like, you know what I'm saying, that's high level shit there.
Make it sound like I'm not stuttering like an electrocuted retard.
I might have a slightly lower threshold of stuff I'd cut with something like that, but
I get the idea.
It's all about, you know, what you want to do with it and how you want it to come out
in the end.
Other podcasts record for so fucking long and it's really strange.
I recorded a podcast with this guy low art on YouTube.
I recorded that like maybe two months ago and the guy is still like, I mean, yeah,
looking on it.
Other people, other people like edit their podcasts and like, I don't, I kind of don't
get it.
No, that's good.
Okay.
Other people who report podcasts for like a living.
Well, no, no, no.
For so long.
I listened to the Penny Arcade DLC podcast and they don't edit that at all.
Just a conversation between them and it's fine.
Like there's no pauses.
There's no gaps.
Are you sure though that there's literally no improvements made in the editing process?
I guess I can't be a hundred percent sure because I know that like, for example, Sam
Harris and his waking up podcast, like he treats it like a product that they like curate
to like make better and remove like to try to keep all the content.
Some podcasts are highly like there's one called the relentless picnic that it has like
musical interludes that are definitely like points where they like broke the conversation
and restarted and stuff.
And others just, I don't know, others just aren't like that.
And we are far on the other end of the spectrum.
You know, Ben, when you and I did T-Bap originally, like that was something that I went through
and I did like improve the audio by cutting out like ums and us and pauses to make it
into like, but that was essentially podcast format.
We just would put the animation.
Okay.
So guys would be shocked if you saw like my biggest timeline of like how I, cause I mean
it takes me in probably Thursday night to finish these things.
And I fully admit, it probably takes me too long.
Like if we were paying an editor and they did it the way I do it, we wouldn't be paying
them enough and we would never pay them enough and I would never want to.
Who's working too hard?
I don't win T-Bap, but like I'm proud of it.
Like when I'm done, even if it takes me all week to make it how I want it to sound, I'm
proud of it at the end.
But it's, it's a weird thing because we're looking for an editor.
It's a weird thing to say like, I want you to edit it good.
And if it's not good enough, I'll fucking kill you.
But don't think that we're paying you more if you edit it good because we're too cheap
to do that.
Well, you know what I mean?
We want them to take pride in their work, you know.
I want to say, I want to say about T-Bap, about T-Bap.
I want to say good, but the better it is the more we have to pay them.
We would break T-Bap up with like scripted segments.
Like we would, we would come up with jokes as we were going to be like, hold on, stop
the recording and then let's, let's, let's read these lines to make a joke in the middle
of it.
Or whatever.
We did it in a good way.
So it was okay.
Fair enough.
I think a lot of the time, good podcasting is a lot like good writing where most of
it is like recording for like hours on end and then in the editing room just cutting
out swabs of other interesting motion.
It's made in the editing.
We got to, we got to find the podcast in the editing guys.
You know, I agree.
This is, this is, you know, when I'm working with like Digi on like our Shearles, Shield
Hero podcast or whatever, Digi's a guy who I, I have a lot of admiration for this aspect
that he just doesn't give a fuck.
He just throws in the editing bay, puts one image, it's done.
And frankly, he does it in an unbelievably short amount of time and I'm huge, I have
a small degree of admiration for that, but mostly fear and disgust of that.
That's fair.
Wait, fear of what?
The jealousy of what now?
Fear of Digi not giving a fuck what goes up.
Like his output, his output rate is like can, can absolutely be through the roof and on
something like that.
Like the other day I finished recording, I walk in to like see Michelle, I'm like, Hey,
just finish this Shield Hero.
And like before I said like one fucking word, the podcast was up and we're like, what the
Digi, how did you do it?
Well, I mean, if the conversation doesn't have like a bunch of breaks and things you
have to edit around, then you don't have to edit it.
You just put it on the video and render it and put it on the internet.
Well, any of them can be improved if you like wanted, like there's gonna be one bad breath
that you could cut out to like, you know, make it a little bit better.
Oh, I don't know.
That's, that's sort of persnickety.
That's so persnickety.
Like I, I mean, I don't know if it's better, it's better.
I listen.
I, I mean, I'll just, I'll just say it.
I did not do hardly any like audio editing person other than like getting the volume
equal on what I, on the episodes that I edited.
And I don't think they were that worse for it.
I don't think they were that worth it for it.
What's that?
Say to Jesse.
Well, Ben's episodes look good at least cause he can draw.
I did do it.
I did do.
Man, I really like the, I really like the outline sort of what you've been doing on
the recent ones, like the light sort of wire frame versions of us.
I don't know what you, you, you, you mean like with the mouths moving and everything?
Yeah.
Just like the different colored outline.
I thought those looked pretty cool.
And I got to say, like I knew, okay, after a while, after I'd done a few of those, I
knew how to get the mouths moving.
And it was, it was a long process to like figure out the method to do it.
Once I figured it out, it was not that hard, but it was extremely like, it was extremely
time intensive because I would have to render each individual mouth with its own video track
overlaid over the thing.
And then I would have to put them all in and then render it in, not in Vegas, but I would
have to render each one as like a fucking high res, like not an MP4, like a T2F or whatever.
And like something, something would always go wrong.
And it would always take me like days and days of rendering, seeing a what fucked up
this time.
Okay.
Got to do it again.
It would like, like I could explain how to do the mouth matching up thing pretty simply.
It's not, there's not that many steps to it.
It would just take forever, every time I would be enraged every single time.
I was like, oh, I should be done by now.
I'm getting flustered just thinking about making those.
And there that's what I have to say about that.
Fair enough.
Hey, how about we sync?
Why don't we sync?
Oh yeah.
Let's sync on the count of three.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is Hippo joining?
He's in the call.
No, he said now he'll just listen.
All right.
Okay.
On the count of three, let's say sync.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Sync.
One more time.
One, two, three.
Sync.
I remember.
I don't know if we're going to cut this part out or should we, I think we should just upload
the whole thing of this.
Yeah.
This has to be the first part of the podcast.
Have it cold open for us.
I'm working to save up podcasts.
Well, there's a point of the pre-rambled.
Well, the point was it was a candid conversation that was relatively entertaining.
Hey, if you like what you heard so far, give us $5 on procrastinators.com slash Patreon
to hear the bonus episode where we do the same thing.
Yeah, that's true.
Donate to our PayPal.
Appropriate plug.
I remember.
I had a sort of digi-style editing process when I, back when I did Armory Triple and
stuff like that and like Jimmy Blockets and stuff, where like most of the editing was
creating the image that would be on the screen.
And then basically like that was it, like for Armory Triple editing, here's like all
I did, like for like the audio editing and stuff like that was I sunk up everyone and
then I like I compressed the IA levels, but I probably didn't even do that right.
I just did it like to ear and then I exported it all in one big audio file, put that like
I did that on audacity, then I just put it into like a video editing thing.
And then I spent like two hours making an image and then just put that in there and
then it was done.
Like that's all I did.
Like the actual like assembly and everything took maybe five minutes, maybe.
That's me.
That's me editing.
Yeah, that's good.
That's good.
Hey, speaking of editing that took forever, you want to talk about 10 paces?
Hell yeah.
Do you want to chat about 10 paces?
Because I do it.
It was a lot of fun.
Was chipping away on that for like months.
It came out.
It was good.
You know what?
Okay.
I want to say it was good.
Yeah, we all know that.
But I want to say how it was.
Red country!
But it was pretty good.
But.
Okay.
No, no, no.
That's actually the opposite.
I'm actually just saying it was pretty good and more on top of that, actually.
It was actually fantastic and way better than what we recorded, I feel.
This was the Star Wars of our generation.
This made it funny, something that wasn't really funny and kind of a cluster.
When?
Okay.
It really came off to me.
It felt like a real, like a TV show almost.
That's, yeah.
For sure.
When?
Okay.
I like the digi in the background when you guys were talking.
Just slinking into the fridge and then slinking back.
There's a bunch of us, other people lurking in the background because we were all just
in the same room all the time.
Okay.
Munchy, you and I both came up with the idea, right, Munchy?
Of course.
Yeah.
We like.
I approached you with an idea for a draw cast where we fought each other.
It was like a round-based thing where it's like a companion tournament thing.
Yeah.
And then me and you just spent the first couple days of Recon 3 being like, what if, like,
what if, like, dude, like, what if, and then they just sprouted out of that.
Good times.
Yeah.
I remember when we were thinking of it, I wanted it to be, I just, I wanted it to be
like strip search.
I just, I wanted, I wish so hard that I could have been in strip search that I just had.
Strip search came up many times in the conversation.
That I just, I had to make my own strip search, but with me in it.
So I was thinking like, how, how could I make this like look and feel like strip search
felt?
And, and the answer was like, spend a ton of effort like trying to edit it as professionally
as possible.
Like I learned, I learned the master class technique of the, letting the audio lead the
cut.
I learned.
That's Ben.
That's the thing I've wanted to do.
I've never actually done that.
And I was very impressed that you use that.
It's a pretty basic technique, but I was like, there he goes, being a real edit boy.
I learned that from a, oh God, in not innuendo studios, um, uh, oh fuck.
Who's that?
Dan Olson.
No, fuck.
There's some guy.
Acroid?
No.
There's some fucking guy on YouTube whose videos I watch and he talks about editing
somewhat, um, uh, folding ideas, folding ideas, talked about letting the,
Oh yes.
Three arrows?
No.
The German alt left YouTuber?
But he's cool too.
Um, anyway.
Yeah.
So that was, yeah, that's, that's just like one weird trick.
That's like letting the audio leave the cut is like one weird trick that I completely abused
in like so many shots.
I just did the same thing over and over again.
I learned one weird old trick to obliterate the YouTube algorithm and shoot to the top
of the charts.
I'm Google searching like hot tips and tricks, how to make sexy YouTube video right now.
Give me 10 tips right now.
Let the audio leave the cut.
Um, you know what's embarrassing?
That's nothing else.
That's all you got.
You know what I just figured out about editing?
It's really embarrassing that it took me this many years of editing professionally to realize
this.
But, uh, when the, when the sound peaks and it has the red number, like the, the red
decimal number, that the decimal number is exactly as many decimals as you have to turn
it down to make it not peak anymore.
I had no idea.
I'm glad that, that other people besides me hadn't figured that out yet.
I don't know.
I know when it's red, you got to lower it to make it not peak, but.
I knew that when it's red, you have to lower it, but I always like just kind of did it
like blindly like an idiot.
Wait, are you talking about it in Vegas?
Yeah, in Vegas.
Huh.
Like I would always, like my whole career, I've been like, ah, it's red.
I got to turn it down some, you know, it was always turn it down some, but like I actually
looked at it one day and I'm like, wait a minute.
There's a, there's a decimal number there.
I wonder if I turn it down exactly to that amount of decimal and like sure enough, it
tells you exactly how much you need to turn it down.
Maybe, maybe, maybe we're all dumb as fuck for not noticing that earlier, but.
I noticed the numbers.
I just also didn't, you know, didn't put two and two together.
That's so weird.
I want to continue going up to bat for, for fucking 10 bases and draw by last week.
Yeah.
I wanted to keep coveching about how much work it was.
Okay.
That, that right there.
Like sure, we can all like joke like, ha ha, it took so long, but like the actual editing
of it, I feel was most likely well-spent, you know.
It was straight up professional level editing, basically, um, unironically.
It's not, okay, it's not as though Ben was working on 10 paces draw for a year in the
sense that every day would clock in.
No.
Sure.
How long would you say it was of actual work time?
Um, like combined actual work time?
Yeah, it might have been a hundred, a hundred, I don't know, somewhere in that ballpark.
Yeah, right.
All right.
I put it, I put it all, I put off even starting it for a long time.
Right.
That's the main thing right there.
I think a lot of people in the audience and just abroad may not realize this about like
being like an online, you know, free flowing, free form kind of guy that projects are extremely
fluid and you can, you can like be working on something for a really long time and not
drop it.
Just have more things take up the priority queue of your mind and therefore, and when
you come back to it in like two months after where people have like forgot about or think
you're not releasing it, but it's just you're doing other things and like, are you supposed
to make a Twitter post that like, hey guys, switch over to this also in the next day and
then I switch over to this and then I switch over to this and then, and then I came back
to this for a little while, you know, it's a slow grind to do some of these long, you
know, effortless projects.
Yeah.
A lot of the time people will say like, oh, I've been working on this for years and
like, you know, a lot of the time it's like, well, you weren't, you weren't literally working
on it for years.
You like, maybe you started it years ago or you had the idea years ago and maybe you
worked on it some of the time and then other times you had other things that had to take
priority over it.
That being said, I just came out of a particularly grueling process making something for endless
war, which will be out by the time, I mean, it'll be out like, oh, was it, was it World
Famous Comic Nuts the beginning?
Yes, it was actually.
Did you like it?
I made it, I made it for you.
I didn't, I was very, I wasn't very impressed.
It was kind of fucked up that you put that on the Patreon actually, it kind of fucked
up that you put that on your Patreon.
Yeah, I don't, I mean, I just thought my patrons might appreciate your hard work on that one.
But that's the same, that's similar because, because someone, someone made, or I made the
joke like a month ago or more about the whole like, the difference between the timelines
is that real Ben St. likes salted almonds and cop, and the cop killer likes unsalted
cashews.
And I was like, that'd be really funny to turn into a comic where that's the joke.
Oh, that was the genesis, okay.
And so I started it like back then, and then I did a bit of it, had dropped it for some
other stuff, forgot about it a little bit until someone brought it.
And I was like, I got to finish that.
And then I stayed up for like two days, like a day and a half straight, like yesterday,
I didn't sleep, just like worked on it for the whole time, because I was, I was like,
I'm so close.
I'm so close to it.
I just got to keep going.
And I did, and I banged it out, and I made sweet gifts, and the art is rad at point.
Sometimes it's terrible, and other times it's great.
And I was like, job well done, and it felt good.
I have just gotten out of creating an update, which is fairly big.
I mean, there's no reason to be candid about it since they will know.
You mean a code update?
Yeah, a code update to Endless War.
It took such a frankly, like embarrassing time, it took maybe like four, no, three weeks
of making where I added a ton of shit, not most interesting of which, the fairy in three
new districts, and rebalancing and adding a lot of new flavor text for whatever, doesn't
matter.
Specifics.
I'm saying, is that-
Finally, the coveted fairy.
All that is good.
Finally, the fairy is running.
That is good.
It's been out of commission for so long.
But, okay, and the most weird thing about it is that I was working on it, like every
single day, this update ruined my latest trip to Boston, which we'll get into later.
Every single day, I was sick trying to work on this, just plowing through fucking dozens
upon dozens of flavor texts, which I didn't need to do.
This is the thing.
I was working hard, but I wasn't being productive.
What I was doing didn't fucking matter at all.
I'm sure people will go around the district, collect on the new flavor texts, and they'll
be like, ha, ha, cool, does not matter at all, did not need to happen.
I made the actual code for everything, like first couple days, changed a little bit of
it here and there.
But actually, making the majority of every fucking, for the past five days, since I got
back, since I fucking got back on the 12th, literally every single day, I would get up,
just like work literally all day, and then turn in at night, just constantly rewriting
fucking, yeah, like literally five days.
It's only five days.
Well, what?
Well, okay, I'll tell you what.
That's a long time.
In my mind.
This is very interesting, because I just...
That's a long time to be on like a 12 hour a day work schedule.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, okay, that's interesting that you say, because I actually too, just finished.
It's coming out at 5 p.m. the day of recording.
This is my longest edited video ever that's not a lecture, and it's the Kingdom Hearts
3 Weagawa, and I put in such an absolutely unnecessary amount of effort and work into
it.
And the reason was because in my mind, it was easier to just go along with the tide
of like, look, it's already there, just like add stuff here, make a little edit there.
And no way was I fighting against my just desire to just add things to it.
For the common sense approach of like, Nate, you do not need to do all this.
Just make a shorter video and get it out, talk about less things.
It's fine.
You can make another video later.
You will make more money.
You will get more views.
People will like that better.
No one or less people will sit through a long video anyway, probably.
So just do all these good things.
And I even made a fucking trailer for it, which was just for fun and was dope.
But what it is, it was the capstone to the Nate Power Creep arc when it comes to Weagawa,
as I was saying before the show.
So you leaned into the power, wait, you mean feature creep?
Well, both.
It's both the power creep and feature creep arc.
The power level has never been higher, but it needs to go back down because the bosses
are, we're in Dragon Ball Z levels, we're like, okay, we already know they can blow
up a planet.
How much more visually can you convey that this guy's way double, triple stronger than
the last guy was?
That's what Weagawa's become.
Okay, so I know what a power creep is.
What's that other creep?
Feature creep.
It's in a game when like, it's when development just goes, just balloons out to be longer
and longer and longer because they just keep adding stuff, bells and whistles.
So you played Terraria, right?
You played Terraria, right, Mage?
Uh, a little bit, not much.
Everything after hard mode is feature creep.
People will understand that.
I haven't played that much, but yeah.
Well, okay, hey, okay.
On the subject of Nate's power creep arc, let me just say that since, you know, this
is where people come and make fun of me for, you know, saying it's going to be done and
I fail.
I want everyone to know that I'm always telling the truth that I think that it will be done
at a certain time.
I'm just so fucking bad at it.
I'm unbelievably terrible at judging time and distance and I'm so sorry, everyone.
But the good news is, the good news is, this is the end of the feature creep arc of Weagua.
I have a new plan.
It will begin shortly and it will be, it's actually going to be bi-weekly videos is the
plan, not actually weekly.
So they'll continue to roast me for that.
But that's fine.
The point is, regular content, not like this, uh, Radcom pre-stuff, Weagabwa, but that just
doesn't sound as good.
I'll, maybe I'll make like a meme at it where I just put like a B before the W or something.
I don't know.
Weagabwa.
All right.
Not bad.
You know, I have a criticism about the 10 paces and draw and I brought this up in the
chat, but I guess I'll bring it up on the show so people can hear it and weigh in on
it or whatever the fuck.
And I can, I can criticize it because I wasn't in the video, so it's worthless to me indeed.
And this is a direct result of how well it's edited.
Um, I noticed that when you have it, please don't say the music's too loud, please don't
say the music's too loud.
The music was a bit loud there, Ben.
Wait, was it actually though?
It was a little bit.
A little bit.
I tried to watch it on my phone, but I couldn't hear it.
I don't get it.
I don't fucking get it.
It does not sound too loud to me at all.
And some, what did you use to, Ben, what were you listening to when you listened to it
on headphones and on speakers, both?
You might have bad headphones.
Also, your, your judgment might have been off because you were like in it and you weren't
seeing it from the perspective of a, I mean, I tried turning the volume down and like,
I didn't want it to be too quiet because if it's too quiet, then it doesn't contribute
to the atmosphere.
Like the point of the music is to build atmosphere.
I know the struggle, Ben.
I know the struggle.
I understand.
But anyway, we interrupted Jesse, but yeah, please continue.
My actual criticism was is that because you have a show with the, the really good lighting,
the really good house set that we had, Victor's camera work, everything looks great and the
editing was so professional.
Oh, I think I know what you're going to say.
And it looked like a real show and because everything about it was so good and clean
and nice looking, it only makes it all the more jarring that half the cast is dressed
like complete slobs in bathrooms and pajamas.
I'm wearing pajama pants, Digi's in his like robe.
I mean, Nate looks fine.
Ben, did you see?
I think the pajamas.
The pajamas and bathrobe arc needs to end for the PCP.
Oh, I want to quickly say, I liked, I liked, I liked Hippo's sweater so much, I forgot
to comment, but I liked his sweater so much, he's such a cute sweater.
Hippo looked fine.
Well, okay.
Tom looked fine.
Nate looked okay.
Everyone else.
I was looking good.
I was, I was in my, Ben, were you?
Are you aware?
Come on.
Okay.
That's iconic.
Everyone loves that.
Are you aware of the emergence of the dye, like the diverged timeline character that
is the, the, the earth shattering meta rebalancing character that is fat Ben.
The people love fat Ben, they want fat Ben from sea to shining sea.
And frankly, we want this current Ben out the window, we want fat Ben back.
I fucking killed fat Ben.
I look so, I hate how I look in that video so bad.
I'm so fat.
My hair is like, my hair looks shit and only accentuates my giant forehead to an embarrassing
degree.
I've got like, I've got jowls.
I'm like, I'm not clean, I'm not clean shaven, but I don't have the beard.
So I just, my face just looks like, I look like pale and like jaundiced and just, just
scruffy, but not in a cool, scruffy way.
I don't remember why I clicked on it, but the other day I happened to be watching the,
the old, uh, TBAP Q and A video.
Oh, the, where were you?
That was great.
What a beautiful voice.
And I was just thinking, who is this beautiful man?
Yeah.
And where did his beard go?
When was he killed and replaced by the monster Ben saint?
TBAP, TBAP, TBAP Q and A Ben, he's coming back.
I'm actually better.
He's actually, he's coming back, but better cause now I look, I look handsome, but I also
look like a freak now.
Oh yeah.
I was going to ask about the haircut.
Yeah.
It has the hair grown in a little bit.
It's, yeah.
I mean, it's still short on the side, but it's not like, you look older now.
You look older and less like an adult paradoxically now.
That's, you know.
Well, you mean in the, in the, in the 10 paces?
Uh, no, now.
Just in general.
Just in older and let, yeah.
Okay.
I'll take that.
I mean, that was funny.
Oh my God.
I take it back.
Your beard is so full and your hair is so kimp and you're wearing that plaid.
Isn't he a handsome boy though?
Yeah.
My beard is not back.
It's not as long as it was in that one, but it's, it's getting there.
I straight up think.
Ben and I will look back.
Uh, and I mean, you can right now, that Q and A video is what changed everything for
us.
If we had not made that one video, we probably never would have met like the rest of you
guys.
It changed everything.
It did.
It straight up changed everything.
And you know what it comes down to?
It's the fact that we were hot guys, work on your parents, it matters.
Being attractive goes so far in life.
Don't give up on yourself.
Look how far we've all fallen.
I know.
Look how I used to look.
I love myself.
I love myself too, but I'm back on track now.
I'm back right before I came on this podcast.
I was at, I've got a new gym membership, 10 minutes down the street from my current apartment.
I was there and because I worked out first thing in the morning, this is the secret
to life because I worked out before I did anything else.
I come home and I'm like, well, I'm not wasting this.
This day is going to be perfect.
So I get my fuel.
I get my protein powder.
I'm going to go have a fucking salad when we're done here.
Start your day off right people and you'll do no wrong.
Hey, I'm eating a salad right now.
You can probably hear me munching on this fucking rabbit food in an American phone.
Hell yeah.
I just, that's what I like to hear.
I feel good.
I feel good knowing.
I'm very confident in this that like you look at T-Bab Q&A Ben, you look at Radcon 3
Ben, basically a complete 180.
Fat Ben.
Please call him by his proper name.
Yeah.
Well, you know, I'm, I'm, I'm happy to say.
Old Fish Ben.
Present Ben.
Modern Day Ben.
Current Ben that sits before you right now is much closer to T-Bab Q&A Ben than to Fat
Ben.
That's pretty cool.
T-Bab Q&A aesthetic is what I want for 10 paces in draw and all future professional
production.
I actually, I actually fit into that shirt once more.
Finally.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
God yeah.
It is, it is so emotionally painful for me to watch videos of myself from like 2012
or like 2011 and just seeing like, like I watch videos of me from that time period and think
I have never seen a more handsome man in my fucking life.
Where did he go?
What happened?
That's how I felt.
That's how I felt looking at T-Bab Q&A Ben.
And I know what happened.
I met you guys.
The PCP was created.
This, this coalition came together and sucked the life out of every one of us individually
to add to the hideous collective like an Akira blob destroying all in its path growing more
and more grotesque by the minute.
Can I just make a quick point?
I've reversed the trend.
Ben's.
I just want to point out the shirt that I'm wearing into T-Bab Q&A is the same shirt that
I'm wearing in 10 paces in draw though like gray and black striped horizontal stripes.
It's the same shirt.
Glowing, aren't you?
I'm, I'm a perfect man.
That's my point.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Oh, speaking, speaking of you, in my enemy group, we watched Zambieland Saga.
We finished Zambieland Saga and we, we, we, we, we dubbed, yeah, we, we dubbed that guy
Anonite because it's literally just you.
You should watch it.
Haven't watched it?
I, I, I certainly intend to.
I certainly intend to.
I just haven't gotten around to it yet.
We love that guy.
He's a good guy.
He's better than you.
But it is you.
So it's like.
Doubtful.
Oh, is he the guy in like the suit?
Yeah, he wears like the glasses and shit.
I mean, I haven't seen Zambieland Saga, but I think I've seen the character posted with
Nate comparisons.
Yes.
Um, yeah.
Um, I wish I watched television shows.
I only watch YouTube videos now.
I've been thinking.
Oh, you're missing out.
TV rules.
I've been thinking about this.
I've been thinking about that.
And yeah, for, sometimes I think, man, I don't watch Netflix.
I don't watch Marvel movies.
I don't watch Disney movies.
I don't, I'm like, I'm like a, I like, I like, don't participate in the culture and
it's hamstringing my social life.
But then I was like, wait, maybe I should just lean into it and be like, I don't watch
Disney shit because corporations control our lives and I won't fucking be subject to
their, to their whims.
I won't fucking let them.
I want to think that hard about the Shiki Watch though.
But well, I mean, it's okay because I'm not naturally inclined to watch any of these things.
So maybe I should just lean into, maybe I should just lean into that tendency.
Disney's going to own every entertainment property before too long because that's straight
up the way they're going.
There's just absorbing everything.
Yeah.
I mean, there's a, there's a couple others that they get their, that they get their
mitts on will be the procrastinators and the whole thing that they'll never get their
hands on.
We will stand against the, we will be David fighting against that Goliath.
And in that day, our one ally will be the one podcast that cannot be found, the pizza
party podcast.
And if we will be able to fall, we'll be unwilling allies.
Where's the podcast?
Cause we need to team up.
We need to find them and team up against Disney.
Exactly.
We need, we need allies.
Ben, I want to team up this weird meme is going to end with Ben loving the pizza party
podcast.
If only I could find them, maybe I would love them.
Who knows.
I was saying that I want to watch more like topical shows and get on that rich deep fandom.
I just meant that, uh, anime is, you know, honestly through through my travels with Chibi
Baka's, you know, they're actually, it's, it means kind of good, you know, you're a
guy, you're a guy that I think I'm in the generally the same category of maybe a little
bit less these days, but like, uh, there's like most anime is trash.
So just watch the good ones and people will tell you what the good ones are.
And that's what Chibi Baka should be in, you know, I mean, that's what I've been doing
for years.
Classics.
Yeah.
I've never seen cowboy bbop.
I've never seen.
It's worth it.
Efficio.
Or it's sequel cowboy rock study.
Yeah.
Woo.
That's for the, that's for the, that's for the millennial.
Oh, no, no.
I mean, Nate's not millennial.
He doesn't seem Doug.
He doesn't know about Bluffington.
I know Doug and I know Bluffington.
No.
Well, obviously not.
Cause you're about Don Tello.
Don Tello.
Look, I'm crazy for this fucking pizza.
Hey, hey, let me just take a moment to wish everybody a happy St. Patrick's Day.
Happy St. Patrick's Day, everybody.
Today's St. Patrick's Day.
Today, the day of recording is St. Patrick's Day.
Oh yeah.
For us, for people, it's been like a week now.
Does England care about St. Patrick at all?
Or is he an Irish rebel?
It's a bad man.
I don't know.
I stay at home every day.
They do.
What do I must say?
Well, hey, let me tell you a story.
I was in, I was in Ireland for St. Patrick's Day.
Oh shit.
God, maybe like.
Don't they turn the rivers green?
Oh wait, that's Boston.
Like six years ago or something?
I don't know.
It was however many years ago I was over there.
You know, it's different.
The funny thing about St. Patrick's Day in Ireland is it's a much more, it's more, well,
it's kind of split in two.
The natives.
It's spiritual or something.
It's more laid back and it's more of like a religious holiday.
I mean, it's not like super, but somewhat.
And like the natives, you know, they'll go out to a bar, they'll be with their friends
and family.
The tourists, the tourists in fucking Dublin in like the tourist section of, did you know
that like the like quote unquote like historical district of Dublin is like a construction.
Like it was built like relatively recently, but built in like an old timey looking cobblestone
way to like look like what people imagine when they think of like jolly old Dublin or whatever.
I was unaware of that.
It's like a tourist construction.
Ireland is like, it's driven by the tourism industry.
They got like fucking tour buses running around.
They got with leprechauns on the side.
Everything's owned by Guinness confirms in the chat that St. Patrick's Day is a quirky
thing in England.
But everyone likes bear.
Okay.
So there you go.
It's the English perspective.
Yeah.
It's it's it's not like in America.
I think it's bigger in America.
Isn't it?
People go nuts.
Well, I mean, it's more of like, I mean, it's like a party holiday for adults.
It's like a party holiday in America.
Yeah.
See, I don't, I don't drink alcohol.
So it's not a, it's not a big deal for me.
Yeah.
That's, that's, that's, that's how we do it.
I do like a raucous atmosphere, though.
I like people having a good time.
I do too.
I feel like a raucous caucus.
Yeah.
That's why we're going to the Capitol, baby.
Gonna shoot up the Senate.
Wait.
Whoa.
That's not what I meant to say.
Head on over to the PCP store.
Buy your I'm the reason people are dying shirt.
Link links below.
No math shootings.
That's not what I actually meant to say.
I meant to say, well, I go have fun with the Senate.
I love my elected representatives.
No one's going to believe that you were trying to say,
let's have fun with the Senate.
But you said, let's shoot up the Capitol.
Those are not the same thing.
People are on edge these days.
It's like one letters difference.
Take Donald Trump on a night out.
I'd, I'd chill with Donald Trump.
I'd get blasted on ghetto blasters with the DT boy.
This is a perfect segue.
Because.
Yeah.
And then I'll segue.
Okay.
Just real quick.
Cause I don't want to ruin your segue.
Just ruin my fucking segue.
I'll stop between two worlds, a world of darkness and light.
And I'm calm between my ethnic father and my peer,
Boston Irish mother.
So whenever she, if I'm around,
she flips on the Irish accent and incredibly raciously and pretends
that we are Irish even though,
is that true?
Yeah.
Okay, listen, we are Irish,
but that does not matter.
And Irish people aren't distinct or like,
Or like different in real life. So like like guys, we're so fucking Irish. Let's go to the pub
Let's go in Irish. Let's get some corned beef and cabbage. That's that's the American way to do it
I don't know if Irish people aren't distinctive enough
Maybe you're just not Irish. I mean cuz my family is pretty stereotypically Irish in every conceivable way
Well, what do you got you got drunkenness?
You got I don't know. I have blue collar. I don't know. I have ten aunts and uncles. They're all alcoholics
They're all rage-fueled maniacs. Most of them are deeply religious so far so good in in in Ireland. I I
Was at a pub. I was in an Irish pub and I talked to a girl
and
She was a native and I remember asking her if she spoke Irish and she said no and she seemed annoyed
I think she seemed annoyed by the question like maybe there's Irish isn't a fucking language
It is a fucking language. Yeah, then there's the Celtic that there's Celtic
I think you're supposed to call it Irish called Gaelic
But it's there's that'd be fucking gay though
When I was there people told me don't call it, you know Celtic or Gaelic just call it Irish
Yeah, and I so I was like, okay
And I asked someone if they spoke Irish and she said no and I think she was annoyed
I didn't mean to imply this but I think maybe she thought that it was like sort of derogatory to even ask the question because the answer
Is no because it was like implicitly saying like oh, you're not real Irish
I wasn't trying to imply that at all, but I think she was annoyed by it anyway
Fair enough. It might also be because she gets asked the question a lot, and it's just annoying after a while
Maybe yeah, maybe probably or it could be that right after that you asked her where she keeps her lucky charms
I'm always after those lucky charms
So I'm entitled to a quarter of the pot the Welsh and the Irish make you so fucking upset trying to pretend like England like
Isn't there like their hegemon and trying to pretend like they're their own distinct countries?
I know I know listen the troubles are coming back, and I'm clearly on the fucking Union inside right fucking
Okay, so here's so I'm imagining that like in England
You probably you got you got Wales you got Scotland you got I don't know fucking Denmark or whatever the fuck else they got
And and like every single one of those is their Texas like always like griping and
They're gonna see one of these days. Oh my god. That's okay. I really like England for England. Just has like four Texas's
Ireland has enough to that I get it that they you know don't want to be in the best you know empire in the world for some reason
Wait, wait, but Ireland actually is Ireland is its own country. No, yeah, I know Northern Ireland is part of the UK
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right anyway, but the Welsh have no excuse and it makes me so fucking mad
And pretend like they're different they try they are different goddamn, but they've got a dude
They've got a Welsh accent. It's totally unique and different and I don't know
They were literally part of England for like like like like hundreds of years
They were literally okay
Listen to this though the best thing that ever happened for the Welsh identity was in Xenoblade Chronicles 2
many of the characters have Welsh accents specifically and
Minj posting minj posting will save the Welsh identity and what Minj posting is
There is a character named Nia in Xenoblade Chronicles 2 who is a cat girl with a Welsh accent as many of the characters do but especially her and
In one of her costumes. She has okay
Stick with me here
She's wearing a pretty revealing outfit. Does she have the dragon? Does she have the Welsh dragon on our no what she has?
What she has is a it's a patch of like it's like mesh or something
Directly above her crotch where you can like you can see her belly button
So you know it's flesh and you can see her skin and you can see the like lack of pubic hair
And this is what's known as minj posting to draw attention to the fact that you can see so closely
To where her pubic hair would be visible and you can almost get a glimpse of that minj
So I'm just saying this horrible work has saved the Welsh identity for generations to come
I need to clarify something I need to clarify something
This is not me saying that all like European or like English-speaking Europeans are the same
I'm just saying that England is the best one. So you should try and gravitate towards it culturally
Okay, listen, all right, okay
I take back what I originally I take back what I originally said the troubles not coming back, you know, Ireland sure
I just hate the Welsh is what I'm trying to say
Cuz they fucking don't cuz they fucking don't not trying to say anything controversial here. I just fuck fuck those guys
Can we get some Welsh voice mails, please? I want to hear the where Welsh defend their I don't know ethnic or cultural
Identity they have language well Welsh like is a language and it's fucking
It's literally stupid
This I mean I mean last episode we had maids tell those hateful bigoted jokes and this
Luckily at the same time a Jesse clarified that racism is in fact over so there's no need to worry about it anymore
The list of countries and people who I hate unequivocally and you can't become cool if you're from them
If you're if you're Welsh or if you're Spanish, I will fucking obliterate you your countries are shit
And I hate them Mexico cool Spain toilet. Yeah
That's yeah
But what about what about Catalonia, what about Barcelona that place is cool
I want to mix in with the local color the ruffians and the rowdies, you know, it's it's rowdy central in Barcelona
That's not true
By the way
Yeah, okay, go on I'm saying is that your Welsh go back to Argentina
Fair and as always munchy so
Okay, back to my perfect segue an hour ago. Wait. Let me first before you say it
Yeah, we've got new t-shirts people buy the group piss t-shirt because it's dope is I made I made the group this t-shirt because I need more
This was a you know, I mean I made I made the group piss image for a banner and I thought I'd make a pretty dope shirt
And I was right. He was so right. We all love it. I want one
I might get one. I know what people should do
I have a p.o. Box open people buy me the group piss shirt and send it to my p.o. Box
I'd really appreciate what size shirt you wear medium medium. Yeah, yeah
There you go. I actually made a shirt
I made a shirt. I'm not selling it because I would have felt weird selling it
But I made a shirt to celebrate my new meme
And my new meme is yang gang. I am yang gang now
Yeah, no, I own it listen that invented
Yang is stealing other people's jokes and memes for his t-shirt scam. Yeah
Yang yang is my new keto is what I'm saying
This is my new thing that I will talk interminably about and ruin everyone's good time
Okay, I'm about to start a fucking wildfire right now because I'm literally gonna ask this question
I mean like I literally don't know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah is Andrew. Yeah
You don't even want to know
I was I was waiting for I've been waiting for this
Can I just say can I just say I knew you were gonna bring this up and in preparation
I went and listened excuse me to large segments of the Joe Rogan podcast with Andrew Yang
In preparation to discuss this topic. Okay. Okay. I I listen to that. I listen to that podcast
I listen to I spent literally hours. I spent out. I was like all night. I had like yang shit on in the
I had yang shit playing in the back. I listen intently. I'm a yang scholar now
Okay, Benza yang man. Benza
I am a yang man hashtag. Yeah, I'm I'm with I mean I'm a yang man in the yang gang. Okay, please start like that
I don't know anything about I could not I could could not possibly have wished for for more
Well, he's a he's an entrepreneur
He he worked with the Obama
He was recognized, okay, he was recognized by the Obama administration
He wasn't like a cabinet member, but he was like involved with with the the
Advisor, I think yeah, he was he was named like a an ambassador like a technology or an entrepreneurial ambassador or something like that
So well his yeah, well his thing is automation his he like he's he's with like Zuckerberg and Elon Musk and
Other technocrats and saying that like automation is like it's you know, it's replacing the need for work
It's replacing the need for workers. It's taking jobs
And the solution to it the solution to automation taking jobs is
What he calls the freedom dividend or a universal basic income for American citizens
So this is the meme everyone ever if he's president every American regardless of how rich or poor you are will get a thousand dollars
Every month and the way that it's paid for is with it with something called a value-added tax
Which like most country including all of the EU already have a value-added tax and we don't
And by their cucks and by and by the way
Amazon paid zero dollars in taxes last year Amazon made 11 billion dollars and paid nothing in taxes
But do you know why that is because they're criminals?
What incorrect then because yeah, yeah, I know it's legal
I know it's legal, but that means but that means that the law but I know it's legal, but that means the laws are broken
But if you if you start if you start a political debate, I'll start talking about dreams and I ain't gonna stop
Hey, I solved politics on the last episode
I just I just want to get to the end I want to get to the end of it
So the idea is that like automation and stuff takes you know, it's taking a lot of jobs
It's generating huge amount of wealth for people like
Bezos for example, so those corporations that are benefiting from
Automation they'll pay a value-added tax less than what Europe charges for a similar thing like half of what Europe already imposes
But that will pay for this freedom dividend
So as these like, you know technocrats and tech companies are making huge amounts of money
They'll be taxed on their profits derived largely from automation and it'll be shared with you know
The American people including workers that are displaced by said animation and the idea is that automation should like make life better
For everyone so like as automation is is implemented, you know
The need for work decreases because robots are fucking taking on the workload
So everyone, you know shares in the benefits that automation brings to our lives and so
One second one second. So wait
What the only proposed way to
Pay for this universal basic income is to add more taxes and not to remove anything else. It's about well
I don't recommend it's not replacing any like current social welfare systems
But like people shut up
But like people that are already getting like welfare and stuff like they won't they won't get a thousand dollars on top of what they're
Already getting it'll be like you can get the thousand dollars or you can get what you're currently getting from welfare system
So just that that's true Ben
But I because I just listened to it as well. It is actually it's true that he he doesn't think this should
I don't believe he thinks that just that is enough to cover the entire okay, so he said right so right now
There's three hundred million so that makes the basically if you just round off the extra people or whatever the UBI total payment per year
Would be three trillion dollars, but not really
That was it's actually more like so much money. It's 1.8 trillion would be the cost
Oh, I remember him saying 1.5. So so fair enough and that's because munchie. What he was saying was that like
Every every the we currently pay about 1.5 trillion is what I heard
Maybe it's less or whatever in current like subsidies for like welfare and I don't know like food stamps like that that kind of stuff
Yeah, so that the unemployment all that stuff. So so that's fair
And so it's all about you got to make up that oh right and so as Ben was saying if you currently get benefits that are that exceed or
Equal the thousand dollars if this is implemented and you just keep those you're currently if you're currently getting 500 a month from benefits
Then you can get an extra 500 to make up the different like like the floor is a thousand
And you you can get more if you're currently getting more then they'll just leave it at that is what he said
So the idea is not it's yeah
It's it's not as expensive as it seems on the face
But because not because lots of people are already getting benefits
So like the the actual cost for it will be about the I heard him quote like it's somewhere between
Sometimes he said like less than two sometimes it's one and one and a half
I think it's somewhere around 1.8 trillion to be the total cost current American like the the spending of America per year is like
20 trillion so this is not like
Outlandish increase, but like the difference is gonna get made up in this value added tax is the now
Let me say this Ben
Because I think you'll find me more warm to this idea than that then people might have expected
Yeah, cuz UBI has a lot of benefits and when I really think about
Okay, okay, so like automation is coming and the the predictors that like many many people are doing because Yang seems to be correct about this
That's in I believe they said by 2030
This number varies a lot, but the kind of jobs that like 50% of Americans do will be gone
Yeah, by 2030 like like I mean he has like a list that he goes through. It's like truckers
food service workers
Retail workers like just just for the sake of people call center worker call center workers
Yeah, like these like 15% of jobs in America are automatable and they might just go away anytime for people to
latch on to in 29 states in America being a trucker is the most common job and those when we
Automated I know it's shocking isn't that insane, but by the time
And when those all get automated automated away those people will be out of luck and they'll be out of jobs and people
Like to lean into the whole retraining thing. Yeah, that is that is a very low success rate
It has been it's a low success rate and people say learn to code like all these truckers are gonna get they're just gonna
You know become software programmers like only only 8% of job
I'm just quoting a lot of shit that he says in interviews
He repeats a lot of these talking points a lot as any politician has to it's like
8% of the jobs in America are like in STEM fields and like so you can't you can't re-educate
92% of
Americans to do what 8% of Americans are currently have it's like it just does and where were those jobs even come from
You don't really got to learn to code you can just write it in the back of your hand up up down down left right left
Yang will give every American 30 extra lives
I'll find this meme and I'll post it
But there's a good meme of the guy with his girl looking over his shoulder at another girl
And it's he's with his girl that's Donald Trump face and it says America going to shit looking over a shoulder at hot girl
With Yang's face that says America going to shit. I'm conflicted plus one thousand dollars these memes now
Comparing Yang with Trump. He's really no similarity or almost actually so there's a couple with like their arbitrary like yeah
They're both entrepreneurs. I guess okay
Well, the reason why this is here is the like how I first heard about Yang
Yeah, okay first time on Joe Rogan
but the Yang meme has been popularized by people on the far right who believed in Donald Trump and
Currently think that the world is going to shit. Maybe not even a far right. I don't whatever people can speak for themselves
it seems to be a right-wing thing though and
They think that the world is going to shit Trump has not solved the issue that they hoped would solve and so imagine that and
So so they say Yang obviously he's the opposite of Trump in a lot of ways
So they it's accelerationism. They want to vote for Yang
I just fuck up America so we can just get this whole like that makes me so
Mad by the way that that acceleration is so funny Ben. It's so funny laugh every time accelerationists are I
There's I mean, they're the ultimate black pill. It's so fucking. It's such like fucking high school nihilism bullshit
I mean, we don't need to get into this too much
But that black like accelerationism was absolutely the motivation of the New Zealand shooter guy. It's that kind of thought process
That's why it makes me fucking mad
Sorry, so accelerationists. Yeah
It's the idea that like the world is fucked so we need to fuck it more
We need to fuck it as much as possible and faster to lead to like the cataclysm that will like just lead to be rebuilding
Everything from the ground up. Yeah. Yeah, and so people like the people who are on the on the right or whatever
They think that the world is drifting hopelessly into like a spiral of leftism whether you believe they're not whatever like
Let's just make that happen really fast because they believe the world will collapse under that and then they can rebuild
You know, maybe some right-wing conservative or objectivist utopia. Whatever. I want to say one more thing about the UBI Alaska already does it
Did you hear that?
Yeah, because they've got those oil riches
But you know what citizens in Alaska already get free money, okay
Here's the government for the the oil that they're coming so like the idea. It's like we are we're already doing it to a second
I haven't a collusion about this. Okay, and here's what it is. Look. I still unironically think taxationist theft
I just we should do it anyway. We should do it anyway
All right, and I guess I agree. I'm on your side. Okay. Here's that well
Here's the thing. I'm on your side when it comes to this automation issue
I see no alternative, but to basically do what Yang's proposing. Yeah, but the caveats I have are I
Don't think we should okay
I need I need real facts and logic to show me that like the rates that we're talking about now like
To have it in 2030 when we're in that world that makes a lot of sense to do it at that
But we don't but it's already happening like people we should ease into it just as it's people are already
I mean we might we might do more we'll probably have to do more in the future
But like it's already happening. So why do we not all right? We should all right? We should start correcting for it now
Okay
Well, that's if we do it too late then like that's terrible. I'm with you
I'm with you
We should probably lean a little bit more into doing it than to not and just like let the people suffer because I think that could
Cause serious fucking collapse of so this guy's like 50% of America had no job
We so this guy is like the opposite of Trump is what you're saying. Yeah
So in a sense this is made you in a sense Donald Trump is the yin to his yang
Damn damn. That's good. Um, have you seen the meme? This is my I like
Have mixed feelings about the Trump comparisons
But there's a mean of like it's four panels and it's a guy in a met
It's the what's that like sad face guy, you know the one that I know
Yeah, it's feel it's feel guy
But like yeah, he's red and his eyes are bulging and he's crying angry tears
Yes, and he's got the MAGA hat on and in four panels
He just fades into his MAGA hat fades into the yang gang 2020 hat and he just just smiling gently
And then in the last panel, it's a little thousand dollar bill. It's like, yeah
That one makes me that one cracks me the fuck up. By the way, so I mean I made a shirt
I made it. I made a shirt
It's not I'm not selling it because I feel like that would be weird because it didn't make the design
But I took the I took the vaporwave aesthetic yang symbol and I put it on a purple t-shirt
And I just bought one for myself and I'm gonna wear that thing
Everywhere, that's cool. Okay. Here's the thing though. I have one commentary on this. Okay, so
the basically so yang's proposal is for like
Deplaced workers who will be excuse me out of a job due to automation or whatnot. Okay. Here's my thought on this Ben
I think it's fair to say you have a relatively
Parasitic attitude toward life. I think that's fair to say. I don't think that's fair to say you Ben you Ben are able body
I'm sure Ben would call it educated college graduates with no excuse to not get a job that puts you above
What these 50% of people who will be deplaced get there is no excuse
You know what for you to not do that. I'll answer this. I'll answer this. Okay. I mean, I've had
I've had quote-unquote real jobs in the past and
I just admit you want the thousand bucks Ben. Just tell me you want me nice. I mean, I won't lie
I do want it, but I was think I was I was literally I was anticipating this criticism
And I was thinking about it as I was taking a piss before the show and I thought about it
I decided that I can honestly say that I think I would support yang even if for whatever reason it was like everyone
But you gets it like I would still think it's a good thing like I still think it makes sense
I do want the thousand dollars. I won't lie. Of course. I
Mean I I mean I've worked real jobs before and you know, I hated them
I always felt like I was just wait it was just a waste of time for the most part like I was spent
I was spending like most of my time right going to this job at this job
I didn't even work anywhere close to the nine-to-five the nine-to-five is like a fake made-up arbitrary number that like some
Inherited boomer mentality says that we should all do regardless of whether or not it makes any sense
Nobody works eight hours a day at their nine-to-five. It doesn't happen. Everyone is like I mean
It's think about Dilbert everyone everyone relates to Dilbert Dilbert's all about people pretending to work people you go to your job
And you pretend to work for most of your nine-to-five. That's like that's like the experience
That's what that's so common. Well, I'm surprised you're supporting communism after saying all that. I'm it's not communism
By the way, yeah, this is I mean this is this is capitalism with a floor
Is no, no, no, I just didn't regard to see your previous statements in the previous part
That was sort of a meme. It's not literally communism
But well, but Ben I have a nine-to-five and while it's true. I don't necessarily okay. This is the
We approach this definitely from two perspectives. I lead basically my whole existence. I prioritize
it's my job to get myself through life and I don't even want to depend on anyone else now with the automation shit
I get that I'm not in that position right now. So like I haven't been replaced by a robot and
And I mean, okay, this this isn't even an argument
But it's like let's just say this happens this automation stuff happens and you know 50% of
All Americans and I suppose it'll probably mostly men, but I don't know whatever will be replaced with
Robots and they just will give them the freedom to end or whatever and they can do that. I worry massively
First of all that I think a lot of people derive much of their like life purpose and happiness
Yeah from their gainful employment and like their sense of like feeding their family and you know being in charge of their life
And you know it might be inevitable
But I have deep worries that just like they're being no place for people
Society's just gonna be like fuck. Well, I mean get depressed and do drugs and sure, but that's I mean
I mean are you criticizing Yang? No, that's not doing this Yang's not replacing the jobs with robots
He's he's I'm away. This is not a criticism of Yang stuff at all. I just it's just a general fear about automation
Okay, yeah, I agree
I mean, you know like a trucker probably derives a lot of his self identity and his pride in himself from his you know
His ability to provide for his family and from his sense of you know
Accomplishment and like this is this is what he does and that's who he is
But you know automation can make that job obsolete and I don't think it's right
I don't think it makes sense to be like well, we should protect that because that's to be in like anti-progress
I'm not in favor of anti-progress at all. I hate that shit. Yeah, like like I heard Tucker Colerson arguing against like
Like advancing automation to protect jobs. Yeah, I can't imagine anything
That's horrible. Let's talk. Yeah, let's not protect. No, although although if like let's just say theoretically what I'm talking about here
Is true then like we might literally doom the human race by just continuing the advancement of technology
It's not gonna do just take it to its logical conclusion where we're all like Wally
Literal it like technology just takes care of itself and we are just okay
You know, I mean obviously everyone's fat and gross and Wally so you don't want to be like that
But like of course the purpose like like automation replacing the need for workers. That should be a good thing
Right. We that should that should make us happy because suddenly I want star trek. He's hard. Yeah. Yeah, exactly
We were these hard and difficult things that are like dangerous and time-consuming and boring and like
Just labor they're just labor for humans and this and we can we can make those things obsolete
We can liberate people to like have control of their lives and do what they want to do and not be slaves to an economic system
That demands that they I don't know mine for shit in fucking dangerous conditions. I hear you Ben. Yeah, I hear you
It's just I'm just saying it's possible that humanity is not properly equipped to handle that lifestyle and that it will all just fall apart
That you might you I mean you're not necessarily wrong, but it's coming no matter what I agree
Yeah, I mean it depends on how fast it goes humanity might
Manage to adapt and you know what let me just say like when it comes
I mean you're right mage humanity might manage to adapt like they did in Star Trek
But frankly in Star Trek even like that show was originally made in the 60s and shit
They didn't even know the technology that we have right now. That's radically changed how humanity interacts and stuff
So frankly, we can't even use that as a great predictor to begin with
But like but I mean the idea behind
Star Trek we're like, you know, technology is sufficiently advanced scarcity is gone
Everyone is provided for you know easily. It's not even a challenge and like just true those concerns
Are just gone. We don't have to worry about providing for ourselves. We can we can worry about like, you know, real shit
I do like the idea of not having to worry about your own self-worth in towards society like
It's pretty good right if everyone else is like, you know, like you and you know, you're just sit there and get a thousand bucks
And it's like
It'll it'll definitely reduce the stress caused by like oh am I am I of worth to society?
Am I am I being a letdown? Am I useless? Well, you know, you guys can I mean you probably have some insight on this all of us here
Because you know for the most part we're all off the grid workers at least in one of our jobs
Or you know as like a youtuber online person or whatever
It's like, you know, don't isn't it? Don't you think sometimes it would be easy to just like kind of lean back and like let's say that
You know, you just get money and you know, you could be working on your next YouTube video
You could be working on your comic you could be working on your commission
But like, you know now you don't need to well
I mean you're gonna be fine for me
And so you maybe you can just lean back and not go to the gym today and you can just like watch that new you know
VR sex doll simulation thing that just got downloaded to the main frame and you know fucking
Sorry go on yeah, I can tell you for a fact that for me personally just me just speaking about myself
Things would not change at all
Yeah, yeah, yeah same the reason say that now, but
Wait, well mage talk and then I'll go after yeah
I am I am
fortunate enough to be living with my boyfriend and he takes care of the bills and what I'm doing is mostly as a hobby and I'm
Earning for my own expenses like you know, if I want to buy some shit for myself
I you know, I have to earn it so if I got a thousand bucks, you know
He doesn't gonna change except I'll be able to buy more shit
I guess okay, but now but now let's say he also gets the thousand bucks and I mean, okay the thing about a thousand bucks
It's not enough to like live baby. It's enough to live. It's enough to like survive
So I imagine a lot of people will try to do things beyond that to like, you know, keep
I want to I want to say that like data has been collected and tests have been done and it seems like
The results of tests with programs like this is not that work like work does not decrease
I think people would in general like to look at it as to work and give it their all
To make money
Almost for a complete 100% fact that things with him would probably not change either
I think people people are we all want to think that though
We all want to think listen. I don't want to get into details because his life is his own. I don't really sure you know
Like knowing him things would not change people. I mean, but eventually, you know, the robots will do all the jobs
Well, no, all right here and not everyone. Hey, the the the
Here's my problem with what you're recording. Yeah. Yeah, this little bit. I'm recording
You're looking at it from the perspective of like work being
Something that you have to do to make the money so that you can survive and if you don't have to work
Therefore you will never do anything but like
Not yeah, I mean what I mean will become pleasure. See everybody has a hobby on top of their work
I mean everybody like whether it be like something that doesn't really improve your life too much like collecting
You know a certain thing or whether it's a creative thing like like
animating or making music or just fucking around with stuff like I think
These things aren't always work and a lot of people don't do them for profit. Oh, you know a lot of the stuff
I do I don't do it with the expectation of making it big with the stuff
I'm doing I would just like to survive while doing it
So I think if I get the money to survive the only thing that's gonna change with me is that I won't have to worry as much
And I would continue to make the things that I make for the people that enjoy looking at them and myself
But you basically said everything I want to say
I just want to also add upon that that you bi doesn't mean that you won't work ever
That like humans want to work. I just fucking with humans motivations to do things. I've never tried it
No, we haven't tried well actually we have in a couple cases. There is there is a couple cases
That working in the traditional sense is not like also at Alaska has been doing it for 30 years
Humans are like a program to do
Natural level people want have the will and motivation to work people yeah to work and they will do it
Anyway, they can whether or not it's like literally like no not everybody guys
Okay, not everybody we have to think outside of our bubbles because not everybody in the fucking country in the world
Like is a patreon creator who is filled by motivation to go create stuff. Yes, it is you're talking about I'm like like collect the stamps
That that I'm talking about hobbies in general people are motivated. You can't this is literally people are motivated to mow their lawn
That's yeah, like what's your point my micro goals exist and people will work towards those goals everyone has goals
Outside their work. I don't see how getting an extra thousand dollars every month could possibly lower someone's motivation to do anything
I think people would be more motivated to follow their passions and their dreams and do shit
Okay, people are I mean this is a yanks to tell me it's not it he didn't make us up
But this is something he says all the time like like what is it like like
57 or 70 it's like a big portion of the population like like tons of the population is living paycheck to paycheck
Most people cannot afford a sudden
$500 bill and yeah, these people are trapped these people have no choice
But to do the work they're currently doing or they will be destroyed even if that work is something that is
They hate or it's something that is not contributing to society. This is my thing every job every job
I've ever had I've never gotten the feeling that I'm contributing to society
I've gotten the feeling that I am just lining the pocket of I'm lining I'm lining the pocket of someone richer than me for
No, actual benefit to anyone but that person. I don't like that framing, but I get your
I'm gonna say I'm gonna go on a limb and I think that's what most jobs are
Okay, I get your point
But let me even bolster your argument even more with personally my favorite argument here
Which is similar to yours, but it's that like a yang said I think he was talking to like some
Like a correctional officer or police officer who like proposed like he said like yo, yo my dude yang
Why don't we just straight up pay criminals to stay out of jail?
And if we did that we would save money and then people wouldn't be in jail
And that's because and we would literally be doing that because okay, that's one argument
Money but if you go to jail, you don't get it anymore
I mean, yeah, I'd be something like that seems reasonable and I'm totally not against that idea because if there's one thing I hate I
Realize this just the other day. I am fundamentally opposed to the idea of redemptive justice period
I only believe in correctional justice. You mean you mean you mean like just punishing someone out of like vengeance
Yes, even like if someone murders someone it is I don't think it is moral to just harm them because they harmed
I think the only moral thing to do is to correct their behavior
And if it can't be corrected then you got to put them away in some way
I agree that the point of the justice system should be a correction and
Imagine someone killed your son though. I know it's hard. Yeah
I know it's hard to like see that objectively and I don't I don't blame anyone for wanting murderers to be killed because they're bad
I mean, I get it. Yeah
Do you think that the that the guy who shot up that mosque shouldn't have just been shot in the fucking head?
immediately well, I mean, I would I think he does
Right now he's going to go sit comfy in a jail, which is exactly what he wanted and he's gonna sit there
Happy as a pig and shit basically getting away with it. He that's not true
He's gonna feel proud because he accomplished what he said out to so
Shouldn't he just instead have a fucking I'm going for the death penalty
I'm absolutely for the death penalty for guys like that. Yeah, kill that guy 100% for I mean
I mean, how does that jive with what you were just saying?
No, no, no, they did say it and he can't get it can be corrected
You know, but what if we could what if what if you we had a team of psychologists evaluate this guy and they came
They should be surprised not this guy's not completely insane and with like, you know
Maybe five years in the correctional facility and whatever treatment we can give him this guy could be
Rehabilitated and made a productive member of society. What if okay, you know what you're right. I contradict myself a little bit there
I didn't mean to do that. It's yeah, go and I'm torn. I'm honest. I'm torn about that
I mean, maybe the right thing to do is let that happen if it's possible
I don't know if you got rehabilitated
Do you not think that the guilt of what he felt did would weigh him down like severely?
I don't care about him like like I'm more concerned about like
The like he killed so many people a lot of people hate him
Like if we're talking about like yeah, you've mentioned in the past like overall like
happiness of like the the people like on a mean scale ever a general scale like
They would be a lot happier if he was put to death rather than rehabilitated and out in the world living when the people they love
Didn't have a chance for like a bunch of doctors to come around and fix them because they died and that was it
Yeah
Clarify what I meant is it's not that I am concerned about him and his welfare
I meant like if he did they get rehabilitated and
Then you know the realization of what he did hits him
He'll probably just go back to being mentally unstable because like that sort of guilt
I would imagine it would break
You can't so it would be willing to be pointless. I think that's my
Okay, I get what you're saying and you're probably right, but I'm positing what if we could reasonably rehabilitate this person
Should we do it right? No, right? I'm willing to be a little savage. Yeah, right here
Some people are monsters, you know like the like the great American patriot Rorschach once said men go to jail dogs get put down
We could turn this person into a real person again
Then people then other people will go and kill him because they hate him so much like well
I don't know about you guys that's their moral failing. That's their moral
Ignoring the premise of my thought experiment and it's annoying. I'm not you're not you're not Nate. I only you're one of the good ones
No, I'm not it's not black and white like I get that if somebody like acts in a crime of passion and like murders a person
Maybe that guy could be rehabilitated
But I mean when we're talking about this this recent mass killer
I mean I I watched the video it was really creepy and unsettling and kind of horrifying and it made me feel really bad
But like the dude gunned down 50 innocent fucking people
Because it was funny. He's a monster. I mean he deserves to be fucking killed. You're not you're just not accepting the premise
I'm saying just imagine a world where we have definitive proof that yes
We can fix this person and he will I think why would you want to fix them? We already have enough decent normal people why?
Either hippo or manchi said
People will come after him regardless if he's a normal human being now we then we should stop all right
He's been cured because it's not good to kill people period
and so people
Maybe justified in wanting to kill him if he if say he's really
Rehabilitated perfectly and he's just a good person now and
I suppose like the ideal is that when you go to jail and you serve your time
Then that's your time and when you get out then you're a free man and it shouldn't be a problem
Like so I get it. I guess I guess I'm just like in in my head
I'm like he's rehabilitated in like a month and then he's back out on the streets
I guess he would be also in jail for like 40 years or something
Even if this guy can be rehabilitated fucking. What's his name? Bobby fuck nuts. I'll call him
Mm-hmm. If like why does he deserve the chance to be rehabilitated?
Well, I okay
I don't think that this is the world we're living in I think he probably can't be fixed and this probably is a
Pointless thought experiment that doesn't reflect reality
But you know, yeah, Nate. I'm I mean I come kind of with you. I think I'm totally with you actually
I think that everything is deterministic
This guy is the way he is because this is the environment
He was born into and it made him into the monster that he is and I think that yeah
Like from just like a purely rational like theoretical perspective. Yeah, I think I would say if we could give into the motion
Emotional howling mobs
And I think that just from a baseline everyone deserves the the human right
This sound this sound I just want to say this sounds like I'm defending this person. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I get I get where you coming from, but I'm afraid people will interpret that's what we're saying
I think also I do I'm coming from is like
It's it's far more attractive
The idea of pre-habilitation like
To make them so that they didn't do it in the first place rather than fixing them afterwards
I feel like fixing them afterwards is
It like even if it's a good thing
It feels like it's a wasted effort because this person already did this horrible thing and these people are dead
And also like there's also never like like because he already did a thing who says he won't do it again
Even if he's repealed
Have a world where he was fully rehabilitated
Even so no not even so that's okay major's arguing just that you can't that it's impossible
I mean if I'm acknowledging. She's almost definitely right
Is that repentance is a privilege of the remorseful if you're what if he had
Genuine remorse he doesn't he doesn't have it now he killed for the people
Can we please just substitute forget the masher let's substitute with him Timmy who stole the cookie from the cookie jar
Can he be made to redeem himself? Can he be forgiven for his deeds?
He committed a sin what if we could fix him so he never steals another cookie from this cookie jar
I mean does he deserve another chance? I mean, yes, should we restore his cookie privileges?
I mean, yeah, if he feels bad about it. Yeah, but if you sit in there in the corner all smug like hey
Hey, I stole a fucking cookie. You can't do anything about it. Yeah, he never like you again return to the premise
What if he was fixed for real
Okay
But I'm
Talking about a mass killer. All right doesn't deserve the chance
I'll I'll I'll bite right the cookie jar
People the people other kids who would have got cookies. They're mad at this guy who's eaten all the cookies and he's been perfectly
Rehabilitated he's never gonna have another cookie again, and he's really sorry. He's like man. I can't believe what a shitbag
I was still I've deprived others of their cookies and it was wrong and I'm so yeah
So like I can never make up for what I've done, but I'll spend the rest of my life trying
Yeah, so like he's he's remorseful. He's in the playground all the other kids still remember I think like
The I I know what the problem is I know what the like like I
See like in the hypothetical situation where he is perfectly redeemed and in the future like you can only know through hindsight
But whether or not he steals a cookie again
So we have a future machine
But like overall people are more annoyed
I think if he like if he got like a face change and like a name change and you just like nobody even knew that he was the same guy
Then I guess yeah, it'll be a little different. Yeah, it's like well that cookie guy. I did it. That's it
It was all a trick. This was all a trick to get you to agree to let the mask off and I did it
Let me speak there is a difference though in here like in this situation this hypothetical
It's not equivalent because what the damage he did it can be sort of like
Repaired with the fact that you just get him by more cookies
But what you know what the guy did well, I'll never get those eyes back
Well, no, no, what I was thinking is like the cookies is
And the people who love them like family members and friends those the kids who are annoyed
That they cookie got eaten listen, okay
Here's the problem. The problem is that other the the problem actually in this instance
Let's say we can perfectly cure this person. So they know we like the we have a future machine
We know they would never do it again, but the problem is
Everyone else because everyone else we would have to cure them of their
Emotionality and their irrationality because they just won't accept or believe that this is true
Even if we know it's true people are too emotional. Yeah, so the problem actually lies outside that one person
It's with the rest of us human beings. What I don't I don't care if you're that
I don't think that his right to be rehabilitated this hypothetical person doesn't have to be a mass killer
But I don't think that a person's right to be rehabilitated outweighs the other people's right to live who died
You're just not doing any good at that point
You're only getting revenge is because it makes you feel better and this person, you know in this instance in this metaphor
They've been redeemed and they won't do it again
Resources wasted on like recalculating that guy and then like all the other people who want him dead
Now you're bringing in this whole deviation of resources. Let's say we're in the future and there's machines and we've got infinite
We're in the game at this point the hypothetical is so unrealistic that it's sort of it's no
He's never gonna be like I in a perfect situation
Yes, it is good to rehabilitate something if everything lines up and it's we got to me
We got we got hippo on board. We got on there. Yeah, but in reality, it's so much further from that than well. Yeah
Yeah, I don't think we should actually do this in reality
And that situation where everything is perfect and it lines up perfectly and you can rehabilitate a person with a snap of a button
Then this shit wouldn't even happen
Okay, well, hey, that's that's a fair but what if I guess but what if it but just in the I mean let's add to the metaphor
What if it did just one time?
Stupidly unrealistic
Okay, I guess my only point is that yeah
I think you know in an ideal world where we could do this if your goal was to do the best good for the maximum
Yeah, then then yeah, I think the right thing to do would be yes
Let's let's hit our rehabilitation button fix this person give him a face change give him a new name send him out somewhere to be a
Citizen no more problems ever happen. Yeah, that's probably what I would do
I don't like it because this person is a monster and deserves retribution or but red yet true
But retribution does not I'm not arguing from emotion here. I mean don't underestimate my true blackpilled apathy on all things
I'm not saying that killing him would make me feel better
I'm approaching this from a purely logical
Vulcan standpoint where the needs of the many outweigh the needs of the few or the one if you kill one person
Maybe you can be rehabilitated
But if you kill two people then I think that those two people's rate to live outweigh your right to be rehabilitated
And it exponentially grows the more people you kill so if you kill 50 people and that's so you're saying then that's like
50 times zero the zero is your right to be rehabilitated 50 times. Oh you're saying oh you go to
So you kill so you kill these people and then they get you in the in their chamber in their rehabilitation chamber and we like
We this person's fucked up
We should definitely press this button to fix him and make him good and send him out again
And you'd be you'd be there in the in the in the the department in the oh god
What do they call them in in in 1984 the the building like the Department of Love the Department of Plenty
But yeah, the fuck there's so it's not department, but whatever you're in there in the whatever of love and you're like
Okay, sir or madam madam president. Don't push that button. He does not deserve to have the button pushed
He deserves the death button push which is right next to us
We couldn't we shouldn't we shouldn't fix him that we should kill him. I'm saying everybody gets one
Okay, you get one murder one
You can be rehabilitated that's a life for a life if you murder more than one person then you then you're done. You're dead
We kill you
Hmm. I I don't I see where you're coming from. I see it
Yeah
I think as a as a young man as a yang man in the yang gang
I appreciate numbers and your numbers are adding up and making sense to him and watch out jessior. You'll see his yang fang
It's like christian when he said that you'll see my fangs. No, I gotta bear my fangs. Yeah
By the way, see my oh don't even we don't talk about the yang wang
First of all agree with Ben
second of all
What do you guys think is more cruel the death penalty or life in prison because I this could go either way
Um, I think I think death penalty is cruel. I think death penalty is cruel
I think life in prison if it were me. I would much prefer a life in prison to the death penalty, but that's just me
I'm just I'm just sitting here reflecting on the on the flawless perfect utopia that I just accidentally created in this argument because think about this
If you were only allowed to kill one person then you would only kill the people who really deserve it
You'd only kill someone you really hate. I guess so that's like Dave chappelle's bullet control argument
Yeah, like what if like what if each bullet cost $10,000 you would only use them if they really
That's right. Was that chris rock? Oh, I think you're racist. Yeah, I think you're right actually
Damn it. That's okay. You get one murder and you get one being racist
Okay
I'm in deep deep racism debt
Uh, yeah, all right. Well, I think we got a lot done here today. That was yeah, this is good
We were exacerbated. Well, wait. No, we've excised our demons not exacerbated them. Tommy Wayne sure has a funny name. That's what I learned today
Hey, hey guys. Do you want to change your topic very quickly to something else? Hell? Yeah, go for it
Did you know that there are pigs that are fluffy?
No, I knew that there are they make pig. Do they make pig? Do they make pig wool?
Whoa, no, but look at it. That's that's like um one of those images that like combines two things and with an outline
It's just it's just like human beings both a swine and a sheep
Hey, uh
Hell, yeah, I have I have one I have one thing to say. Uh, this is not directly F too much hip of saying this
I know this is this is not this is not directly this is not directly related to yang per se
But it's sort of in line with my whole, you know, my whole like radical
I guess am I a radical lefty now? I might be I'm not sure
Um, possibly but I was I was rewatching some videos and there was one that I thought was really great and really thought provoking
And uh, it's it's by this guy
I I found him because I was on the rfck twitter and I just saw a link to this guy called thought slime
And I thought that's a cool name and I thought and I followed him on the rfck
He's like one of the like four people that the rfck twitter follows because he has slime in his name
But he but he is like a radical anarcho communist. So he's like he's as bad as far left as you can get
Um, I see a video of his called all cops are bad. He sounds sounds balanced
He does have one called all cops are bad
He doesn't like the institution of the police and he thinks it should be like radically restructured is the idea
But he's got one video called um capitalist entitlement
And uh, and I think that one's really great
And I would encourage anyone to watch it and let me know what you think in the comment
Could you give me the general synopsis?
The general synopsis is that people say that like lefties are entitled because they want government benefits
They want you know, they don't even want to work for it
um
And his basically his argument is that like the like the way that capitalism allows certain individuals to amass
Insane wealth on the backs of like a system that they did not build themselves that was created communally by
You know americans and by people large and by workers, but like all like all the um
You know the the wealth and the talent and stuff like the the benefits of like the people
That they should be profiting from themselves get siphoned into the pockets of like, you know
Like the rich oligarchs and technocrats just based on how capitalism operates as intended
And and the idea is that like this is why capitalism is flawed and why it is like an inherently exploitative
System and anyway, I really like that video and I think it makes a lot of good points in a short time
And I don't want to just directly quote it all so I don't know
I thought maybe people should check it if you feel like it check that one out
And I don't know let me know what you think in the comments, uh, because I am a big fan of all that
Uh, yeah, I just wanted to I'll have to think okay. You know what I have to counter that uh go listen to
I don't know any video by rucka rucka ali. I don't fully agree with all his ideas
But he is the purest objectivist. I've ever seen um, and he really straight up believes in that stuff
And I am not a hundred percent on his side and all those things
But we overlap in the majority of our ideas
So I don't I don't have a specific video, but I'm just countering this leftist indoctrination that ben's attempting to do
It's not an indoctrination
I just think that maybe because like a lot of I don't know because like on youtube
You are way more likely to get recommended like anti sjw. Shit like you're like like
YouTube will send you down this fucking rabbit. I have to stop you there
YouTube will send you down this fucking rabbit hole of like of like sargon of a cod and like armoured skeptic and all this
And all this weird like crypto right wing youtube will send you down whatever passage is related videos
But which okay, but which one is more like there is which one happens to more people
Which rabbit hole do more people get sent down by the youtube algorithm. The answer to that question is left wing
Because tim cool just did a video on this. Okay. This was a couple weeks ago
I think where he summarized and he's on the left. So this is his team. I know people mean about him being
I mean, this sounds like one data point and an anecdotal argument that's coming up
Okay, he cited a study and I don't know how comprehensive it was but but the the gist of that was
I'm just saying there was some evidence to the contrary that was a study
And I don't know what video it was but he references a couple times
Uh, so I'm just saying I've heard points and this wasn't just him making it up
He was citing a study by I don't even remember who but it was real and I saw the chart and it's out there somewhere
So I just think it's more of an open question. Well, that's interesting. That's interesting. Okay. I guess my only point
Oh, I'm trying to say is I think that probably our audience just from what I've observed probably skews a little bit in the anti
SJW
Direction and you know, I wonder about that. I really do. I mean, I don't know. I don't know it. I don't know for sure
I guess we do
Like digi's audience would be like, you know
Lefty guys because digi dabbles a lot and like lgbtq stuff and uh, I don't know
I mean a little bit the anime culture to me seems more lefty in general
I um
I'm not sure about that. I think digi was just a source of a lot of viewership
I get a mix of both. I don't know. I mean time to time because I listen to
Well, what is it?
Every viewer of ours is transsexual and also gay or something like that. I mean transgender. I think right
It seems to me that a good 90% of our audience or if there is a difference of our audience girls with dicks
Um, I don't know but I don't know. I just want to point this out because thought slime is not a huge channel
I think he's only got like less than 100k. Oh, he's got less than me. Oh, thank god. I don't pay attention
Thank god, I think
Specifically the stuff he says in the video called capitalist entitlement is not
Stuff that I've heard repeated a lot around and I think it's interesting. So that's my recommendation
Ben, I suspect put it in the show notes. Okay. Would you willingly call yourself?
Someone like a leftist like someone on the left. I would call myself a leftist. Yeah
I would call it. I would definitely call myself left leaning for sure if it is anyone that would consider themselves
on the right here
In terms of economics, I definitely am on the right. That's specifically economics people
I definitely lean left in terms of like a social policy. So
Just saying I don't think I'm not sure any of us would call ourselves right leaning
But I mean, I think maybe some of our audience think we are
I think that's very because I wouldn't because we've said the n-word
All I know is that I'm real right and I don't believe in it
Left and right is totally arbitrary. Okay. Well, again, you need the four quadrant spectrum
You need the four point of liberal uh and authoritarian versus, you know, uh, not leftist and rightist, but you know
That's a concern. I'm definitely in a flushed quadrant. Yeah, whatever
So, I mean, I think most of us if not all are pretty much very high on the like liberal side as opposed to authoritarian
I mean to me, that's the most important one. I mean, I'm not sure. I I generally don't know
I struggle every single day with looking myself in the mirror and not being the perfect
Centrist god that I know I want to be and I'll pretend to be
But knowing that I just have that smidge of devil that smidge of left-wing politics in me
Makes me so genuinely upset that I can't fucking like grapple with it. You should embrace it
You should embrace your devil munchie. No, I shouldn't it's not fucking right. It's it's so fucking
It's not right. It's it's not right. It's left. It's so disgusting to lean in to be on the left or on the right
It's fucking like that's horrible. It's really important. It's I I don't I I'm are you serious?
I really hate that attitude. You know why you say that
No, I really I really really hate the attitude that you have to be on like the far-flung edges of society
I didn't say that. I just think I think centrism is like a non-position a lot of the time
I hate when people say that that makes absolutely no fucking sense
You one should never okay
You should never come into life thinking I'm going to be a leftist or I'm going to be on the right
You should obviously like think about the arguments one by one
And then as a result of those positions on arguments the rest of the world will conclude in response to them
They find you on the left. I'm not saying you should pick a side and then and then align yourself with whatever that side believes
I know I'm just I'm just and I understand how someone could have a mix of opinions that brings
Here's why this conversation
Here's why it's totally circular and worthless. Sure. The term centrist is a fucking straw man
There is no such fucking thing as a centrist
And when people try to like shame centrist like oh centrist are just fence sitters. No, they're not
Nobody is exactly in the middle on everything
Everybody feels one way about one thing and another way about another thing and that's how you should fucking be
You should tackle problems in your own brain on an individual fucking basis not according to what your fucking team is
Okay, okay. Okay. I don't think ben was arguing. I agree. Okay, but what munchie is saying is that he wishes
He were a centrist and what is that if not picking an alignment and trying to align your values with that? That's what i'm saying
I don't know that was munchie
That seems like exactly what you're arguing against what what what i'm saying is okay
I I believe what jesse said that everyone has opinions. I don't think anyone is actually going
I'm gonna be a centrist and i'm gonna be in the center of all positions. I think they are
What about boogie boogie is literally that
Well, I think he's trying to fucking have empathy and dismiss and denounce people who won't be on the extremes
I'm sorry
When I say I want to be more of a centrist
I mean that I think that I easily dismiss people
Of more often than not like a right-wing perspective
And I wish that I were not so biased in that way and I wish that I was able to more
Accurately engage with them and and I wish that I had more of a balanced perspective in life and in politics
I feel it's too easy for me to just completely like align a lot
Well, that doesn't that doesn't make any sense if you if you okay if you feel a way about the issues
How does it make sense? That's not what i'm saying. I'm sorry. I'm saying that I
wish that I could
Not not I'm not saying that I want to have different opinions than what I have
I'm saying I want to be able to engage with people who have different opinions
In a more balanced way than I currently do where it's it's easy for me to dismiss people out of hand
I mean you could
Well, I mean you can engage with someone with right-leaning opinions even if you don't share them right or left or whatever
Well, that's what i'm saying
Well, okay guys on the same thing as being a centrist and we can all agree that whether you want
The acceleration of the degeneracy of the world to happen or you're a communist hack
We are all in the yang gang and we can all be united on this point, you know
And we could move forward. I feel I feel conflicted. You know, I think the yang gang is funny
But I also feel weird like am I undermining it by by leaning into the meme of it. I wonder what but
I mean all you're doing is saying the word yang gang. That's not all I'm saying is saying the word yang gang
But other people are out there making memes that are really like, you know, you know
Like yang is the new trump and yang is uh, is uh, yo listen to this
I saw a tweet from uh, okay. I hate doing this, but like, okay. I saw um
Contra points make a tweet that was just it was the shooter from the new zealand thing and he was doing the okay sign
Which we all know has the right wing dog whistle
Okay, that yes, that's the thing but but just in response to this
Yeah, the the the conclusion found by contra points was we got him all along
Everyone who's been doing the okay sign has in fact been a right wing evil racist monster
And I just thought that seems unreasonable a position to take you can't that's a bit of a that's a bit of a jump
There's so many people we're like we're on board. We we agree
I don't I don't think the right thing to do is crack down on the okay sign
Right and look it's fine
If you want to say that like I don't know if you see a person who seems spouting a lot of right wing things
And they're doing the okay sign
I think it's reasonable to develop a conclusion that looks like this person's leaning into this possibly racist meme
And sure enjoying it, but just what do you get from that?
I don't think that gives you anything. Hold on the okay symbol is like a racist thing. I thought it was like
Someone unfortunate. I thought it meant okay much
That's the thing a lot of people don't even know that it but yeah, like it is kind of it's sort of like pepe
You know like like pepe is some people use it as like a right wing dog whistle thing
Like like that's what I'm here to sound pepe back. It doesn't really mean that to everyone as a as a should post in 4chan
Let me just clarify the okay symbol
This is a fact the okay symbol was co-op if you make your fingers in a circle with the three
Whatever fingers up and you hold it upside down
It looks kind of like a w and a p which they say is white power
This was a made up thing on 4chan. They it was it's confirmed they made it up to confuse and like
Fuck people up because everyone uses the okay. I thought it was just because I thought it was just because trump does the okay sign
Sometimes they that may have been why they showed that it's such a tangled web
That the solution is just stop. This is the word renter stop caring
I just want to say a lot of people have made the okay
Yeah, I mean, I mean, that's the thing but yeah, they co-opted it
But that's why it's such a great weapon that so many people do it and of course they don't know that it's being
You know interpreted this way and like people that don't know about it might still do the okay sign
Um, with like and it's like oh the dog whistling even though they don't mean to on the other hand
I mean like even if it was like a fake made like like people that are in on the meme would do it like genuinely like
Yeah, I know I am right wing. I know we've co-opted this sign
I'm going to do it as like legitimately like
Exactly. It's just that you need more evidence than just the okay sign to conclude
Well, I mean I think I think we can conclude that about this guy
This shooter guy was definitely in on the the meme or whatever. I mean, I true
I mean, he also said subscribed to PewDiePie. I really think it's which I did immediately after that
There you go because he's trying and he said in his manifesto. That was a joke by the way trying to fuck up the world
Yeah, um and just he just did all the all the things and honestly, I can say I can just say like don't let him win
But that doesn't mean anything like how do we prevent him from winning?
The answer is there is no way because they're just fucking up speech and information
And uh, it is worrying and I am concerned about it. I'm really annoyed
Just then when Ben did the funny joke and then he had he felt the need to clarify that it was a joke
That he that he didn't actually subscribe. Oh, thank god. Ben would never subscribe
The subscribe to PewDiePie meme before that point was like one of the nicest things on the internet
That's why it's so fucked up with that guy. Look, obviously, okay, the worst thing to do is kill people obviously
I'm just saying to see people corrupt information like that. There's there's nothing that can be done
Honestly, I might have some eventually subscribed to PewDiePie and now I can't now I just can't bring myself to do it
I can't ring that bell
I would like to submit to the court that for some reason I had left a youtube video playing and then I have autoplay on
And I come back after this intense yang-gang
This this this mass shooting
Yang-gang bang you this yang-gang bang
This yang-gang bae I come back to minecraft new versus pro sky block in minecraft as much when am v shorts animation
Well, cool. That says a lot. Oh god. They're rat. They're radicalizing you
Look at look at this anime boy made just posted doing the the okay symbol. We've got another one. We bagged another one
I'll bet you boy though. He probably didn't even know I don't know. He's looking pretty white
Honestly, I look at this guy and I think this guy's definitely subscribed to PewDiePie
So fucked up would have okay, you know what let's just move past this let's get some voicemails guys
We gotta we gotta
Go on okay, but before we do voicemail voicemails
We have course have to check in with our dudes at the pizza party podcast quest. Oh, yeah
So just just give me one sec. We've got uh, we've got a thing here
Play the jingle play the jingle. I've got I've got okay. Here it is. Here it is. We've got a new jingle people
Um, let me fucking okay. Here it is. Here it is. Okay. Sorry, uh, uh
Jingle from what was it called? Oh, it's called pizza party shit song
sweater song
Okay, it's what it is. So
Go
All right, it's time to shit
Oh
Yay
Time to sit on the pizza party
Podcast if you want to find this podcast
Gotta find the podcast
Hey devil taxi, where's the podcast?
I can't find it on your god damn channel
Please give me all the links to every episode
Of the podcast
You stupid car
There you go. Yeah
Got him. Well done. Who wrote who wrote that? What was the name of uh, the name on it was just, um, uh,
Pizza party shit song sweater song. Okay. I think I read that right. Thank you. Pizza party shit song sweater song
Now we do have one
We do have one. Hold on. I would like to say something
That this just made me don't tell me you found the pizza party podcast that guys I
Someone just momo just deemed me over whatsapp giving me the coordinates to the pizza party challenge. Um, what?
Hey, well, what I was gonna say is
Back in the day
I would like know who the pcp fans are and this this may realize that like
Man, there's a lot of like creative people who's from the pcp who who who put in like voicemails and stuff like that
But I don't fucking know any of them
I don't know a goddamn because I because I was in the fan chat, you know, I was a fan back in the day
I knew who everyone's name was and I knew what their fucking deal was
But now like
Literally who watches the pcp? There's a few people in the patreon lounge who I hate and then that's it
Give us names. Give us names. I I couldn't I I could only like avatars. I don't even know their names
Is there is there people in the patreon lounge? Because is that a thing? I haven't been in there in like two years
Yeah, I mean this is a pop didn't briefly uh to
Post about 10 paces and draw and that was it. That was the last time I was there. I I I I lurk there and it just makes me upset
I'm there
Because they're all they're all just named digi heads. They're all just named digi
Oh god the lowest of the low all right fucking subscribe to pewdiepie if you're if you're a saint
If you're a saint head in the in the pcp patreon lounge make your presence known
Yeah, nades assemble nate heads
Nades are the are the that's like saying like white people assemble like we need to fight back
Yeah, it's it's literally the same
You're all fucking white except munchers. So you know
Why don't you hold hold a nade heads? Why don't you go hold a rose power rally?
Nate heads. Why don't you go fucking shoot up a mosque remove that from the podcast?
If you're an if you're an endless friend out there in the patron lounge
Make sure that you support the real shit by downvoting every episode in which we talk about politics at all
Yeah, I'd appreciate that and up voting every episode where we talk about video games and shit
Uh video games are the best everyone everyone in the pcp patreon is post yang memes, but only the good ones
Only the nice ones
There are some there's some black pilled ones out there. Okay. Well, hey, you know what I think
Maybe we should like take the patient lounge because we can be there
This is an unprecedented a lot of people do this where we have like the patron section
And then we just release like the discord like I have a general section for the public
That's how the uh, that's how the podcast one works and it's pretty great. It works. Well, do we not have do we not have that for the pc?
Wait, is the pcp discord only patron only patron only yes, there's no there's no non patron section. Yeah, that's correct
I mean there was there was a non patron pcp discord and it quickly devolved into shit
Well after we made the patron only one like that changed a lot
You know
Whatever like some of the people
Microwaved over and so it just kind of weathled out after a long time because the most devoted fans were mostly patrons
So they all left that one in uh, you know, you know, it's kind of a scary thought that like what I maybe like the
audience is like it has like changed to the point where like
I wouldn't resonate because like I think about like old pcp fans. I think about steve
I think about steel. I mean you were you were in the you were in that group at the time
Yeah, me and like I feel like I resonate with those people a lot to the point where it was like
I don't know like very fast friends
But I feel like maybe like I wouldn't like what if I don't resonate with the people who are like fans of the pcp now
That's just a really scary thought that I haven't really considered before
I think it's just that you were friends with them now and the you know, it's changed
So you just don't know and so you're comparing the good thing that you knew to the unknown thing
Yeah, might be bad and you know, yeah
I mean it's been going anywhere
I mean a lot of your a lot of your um
Let's do a lot of a lot of people you were friends with
In the pre you being on the pcp days
I mean a lot of those people are like pretty like people know their names now because you talk about them
That's true. So, I mean they're they're kind of a sort of
Click within the group, I guess. Hey guys, it's me the pizza party podcast. Oh my god
Let me tell you my opinions on the mass killer of the boss. Oh god. No. No
This is why I need to know a new voicemail new voicemail
Tell me about mr. Yang Wang tell me actually, you know, gladly mr. Pizza party, sir
It's great that you're here because we have a we have one looking for you on you
What are the merits of communism versus capitalism please enlighten me?
I've got a list here. Let's hear a question for you. All right. Well, not maybe not a question but a comment
It's called this is from uh ppp more like kkk. Let's see what he has to say
This one goes out to all the gamers out there
Present pizza. I'm criticizing you. Well, it's an inch of pcp on friday afternoon
Pizza, whatever did we do to make your podcast so bad?
Podcast where even is it? Where's the podcast? Good. Good effort. You should have been to make your podcast go away
Because you can't find it. Yeah, so uh, wouldn't it be more like to make it appear, you know, because it's you don't know where it is
What did we do and it's gone now. Oh, right. All right. Yeah, okay fair. If it was whatever can we do to make your podcast
Whatever have we done to oh, yeah
Well, they're okay. I mean, there's your wrap up on the pizza party podcast quest question. How many voicemails do we have?
I have a total um
I have 12
All right, that's well actually those two didn't count. I wasn't counting those. Okay. Okay, cool
Okay, let's let's get to it. Um, this first one of the actual ones. Oh good news ben. This is from ben and nate's father
He's finally after all those years going out to get cigarettes. He's checking back in. Oh, let's see what he's got for us dad go
Ben
Nate
This is your father help
Boys I've
I've tried to be supportive and everything that you've done
I tried to raise you well and and love you the best father is inaccurate
Ben when you
When you came out of the closet and said that you were gay
Well, it was difficult for me, but
I still love you
gross
Nate we
We knew you were gay the the minute you came out of the closet
It was
It was it was frankly fabulous and we weren't
Boys we weren't uh
Exactly thrilled when you stated your intention to get married to each other as well
Oh, right. That's Jewish brother on brother
marriage, but you know
We love y'all. You can't control me. You know, what are you gonna do?
Oh, what are you gonna do? I should be supportive of everything else. Mm-hmm, but your mother and I recently found this podcast
And it is it is just awful
Yeah, he's he's not wrong. So, uh, this christmas, um, just just don't come over
Nice, I'll save money on presents
All right, I respect that dad. Love you too dad. The ever-disappointed gold standard finally calls into the pcp
Gold standard that's deep lore
Uh, did people even know about gold standard? Do they know about gold standard and angel food?
Uh, they might if you have an angel food cake the tea vap
Well, I mean we'll we'll get into that. Well, they're not gonna be at it anymore because we've been disowned. Um, that well, that's fair
Yeah, sorry guys gold standard and angel food are out
Um, scrubbed from the workloads. Well, that was well, that was heartwarming. That was nice
We're ready to sour your
Attitude and drawers because we've got uh, the perfect digi bro impress impersonation. Wait impression impression. Let's let's hear it go
Hey, so I don't have anything really insightful to ask all I want to do is my digi bro impression. So, uh, uh, yeah
Here I go
Anime is a japanese colopilism for smoking dank weed
Disconnect that's all you get. Yeah, that's it. You're over. Yeah
That was terrible. Why did you put that in?
Because it's fucking funny is why dude. He said like weed. That's like not what you supposed to be. You're fucking fired
I really I'm I'm quite happy with the hatred for that man. That was immediately a risen
Nate that's cruel
Well, how was that cruel? That was just fucking funny
I liked it writing him to laugh at him and then
And I didn't I was laughing with you guys. Well, I'm curious
I like dumb voicemails. What do you want from me? Does the impression get more elaborate or is it just that basic all the way through? No
I think he mentions lollies, but like that's basically it
I put that in solely for the anime is a japanese colopilism about smoking weed
Jesus
His impression that's my impression that everybody stole
questionable
That's that was a questionable voicemail inclusion. Uh-oh my position is on the road
Someone else might have to do the extra unpaid work. We're gonna finding the voicemail
We're gonna impeach you four percent. You get four percent, Nate
Okay, I got paid the same amount before and after I started doing the voicemail. He didn't get any more administrative fees for the voicemail
And we appreciate it. You fucking hack. I thank you everyone. Okay. Uh, let's move on next one is from
Okay, this is from like f1m. I get I think is the name. Okay, uh, go friendship
So I listened to the pokemon podcast and I do not understand how people even took this long to talk about the pokemon match up
Communism versus capitalism when capitalism is just better pokemon
Now granted in all the high level replays of pokemon battles that you can watch
Communism always chaos capitalism
But that's only because communism uses the move self destruct. In fact, that's what makes communism such a weak pokemon
Because it only knows the attack self destruct
So even when capitalism is knocked out communism still dies on the other hand
Capitalism is a great pokemon with an extremely high attack stat and great bulk. There's only one big problem
It's only attacking move is false swipe
That means when your opponent sends out a pokemon mass starvation or widespread poverty
Capitalism can only be a large part of it, but we'll never KO them
But that is so much better than communism which can always kill its opponent
But will always kill itself and as stated by the official rule set of the pokemon vgc
Also known as lock theory of economics if the move explosion or self destruct leads to a double ko the move user will be declared the loser
Also a quick message to jesse. The reason why anarchy is banned is because it's a dragon type pokemon
That only knows a move outrage
It resists everything and we all know that the only good fairy type pokemon good virtues of the people
Has too low of a base attacks that fight it despite the type advantage
Leading to this boring ass meta where the only pokemon that can beat anarchy is another anarchy
Hell yeah, I appreciate that was smart
That was way too high brow
We are clearly lit. I think we're living in the brightest timeline right now
I'm trying to laugh about fucking dude smoking weed
Yeah, I know I love I love that like the meta, you know the meta is just so rich and so strategic
There's so many options that clever shit out of here
We're dumb dumb on this podcast. Well, okay. I've got good. I understood everything guys
I'm sure you did. I got all the references shut up boomer playing pokemon
Okay, you know if you want to dumb, I've got what you need because the next voicemail is from riddle my ass batman
Let's get going
Yeah, please
Batman I have every member of the pc carry ninjas above with tank of penis any worms
And so these riddles not or I shall assuredly get away with this crop
That's because there's so many but we're not very well
Riddle my ass batman who has a fifth degree and drinks on certain energy
Who steals heavy cream while you dream who has a key shaped like a toe
Who batman who?
Easy riddle a man who vapes ben saint
Yeah
Thank you. Thank you so much. Do you have any?
Whip cream
Here kid
You save you save one member of the pcp so far batman, but you're really
Ben saying it's saved a minor victory if one could call that
Well, batman's kind of intellect be enough to save members of the pcp
Through the next time to find out same pcp time same pcp channel
Oh my god, I'm in so much suspense. What's gonna happen? I demand more
Yeah, we're all dangling over this dick eating worm vat and only ben has been saying I guess mage is actually safe
Because what's the worst that could happen in this situation? Oh, yeah, you know, well, we all know the mage also has a dick
I don't know anything anymore
Well, thank you batman. Uh, fuck you, uh riddle my ass. Don't leave me
How did you deprive me of heavy cream?
That's his legal name riddle my ass batman
How is like I was like gonna vote for yang dangling over a vat of dick eating worms exactly exactly
Okay, uh
Next one from serf wax crastinators. Okay. Get it. You ready set it go
Yeah
Yeah, way to go dude. I love about dreams. I'll fucking let's fucking make that the opening. Yeah. Yeah new theme for the next episode. Yeah
Yeah, no, no, it's great
Especially the turn we get a cleaner recording tyranny of the majority
Uh mage is out there. I will definitely talk about dreams, son
No, do it. I'll fucking do it. I don't care. I'm an accelerationist. I just want to watch the world burn
Let me talk about by trying to keep me down. You guys have given me a power that no one can oppose
That's the super powers will just devour each other and we'll just we'll feast on the scraps
Okay, okay next one. This is from uh apparently you've forgot to eat your greens
How many more do we have a question? What's that? It's the sound of you forgetting to eat your greens
What the fuck is that?
Why does that sound like my chi?
It does sound like my chi. Oh, no. Yay
You've got to eat your greens
It doesn't have lyrics. You've got to, you've got to
I'll let my greens but I won't set it.
Fuckers
Guys, I've literally been eating my greens this entire duration of this podcast. Oh, yeah, the rapid food. I've been eating this
I've been eating with a fork just this giant plastic bin of lettuce and nothing else
There was like one tomato in it
But mostly just lettuce and I've just been just devouring it the whole time people come up to me and they're like
Nate, why don't you ever eat salad dressing on your salad and I'm like because it's gay, bro
I don't need that extra garbage. I just want to chow down. Nate on my name. What what salad dressings keto
Not not ranch dressing. It is. It's all fat
Well, okay, but I'm not on keto. So I don't I'd have to analyze whether or not that's keto
Like you know, just necessarily better
Is part of gang gang gang gang gang gang is part of keto eating things that are keto even if you're not hungry
Uh, no, not really. I mean not really. It depends. No, actually a lot of people fast on keto
Yeah, is there any benefit to keto if you're like underweight and you're trying to gain weight as some people are?
No, I don't think so. Okay. Just curious. All right. Uh, I'm not I'm not sure, but I don't think so
All right. All right. The next one's uh, the voicemail from chillin chocolate our old buddy. Uh, get get get it going get it going
Nate you
I took beans to school a can of beans like you recommend. Yeah, and I made fun of me
I told them the bean juice, you know the stuff in the can. It's delicious. It gives texture. Wait. No, it's weird
Why didn't you warn me about this chugging the bean juice?
What are you talking about? I specifically told you you have to drain the gunk from the can you don't eat it in the soup
That's pretty gross. That is gross. I think you're gross too and weird and you deserve to be rid of your bean juice
Um, do not drink your beans. I'm I'm imagining him just just scooping out the beans thrown away and just chugging it right out of the can
Just chug that juice if you if you like the texture with all its nasty beans all its nasty collected beans sediment at the bottom
And it is a problem
I can't help you with that my dude. This is on you. This is on you
Okay, you know what? I was gonna play this one that was this guy called in his gimmick was it was the pth
wsep
Which is the something like
podcast on someone else's podcast episode one, but you know what it wasn't that funny
Is it is it the is it the one about did you didn't did you mention a podcast where they review other podcasts?
And people and people in the comment I on the episode I was like I want to hear that and people in the comments said don't it's shit
Well, okay, I don't know if that was this or not
I I mentioned because I that guy I respect your effort, but it wasn't that funny. So I'm skipping it. So there you know
You've been addressed. Okay. I appreciate that. Yeah, I thought you would I thought you okay. So next one is from
Oh semi normie guy semi normie guy. Okay commence, please
Any day now
Is it I spelled I spelled play wrong I spelled
Pally as but Pally in the thing. I'm so sorry everyone. Okay
So a lot of young people struggling to find a purpose in life join the military because they think it's a good way to contribute to something
That's bigger than themselves
I'm 17 now and I've begun to consider doing the same
It's not that I don't think I can find purpose outside of the military
More that I recognize that it's the most apparent option for me to have the largest net benefit in the world
And because it's hard and I think it would make me a better person
What are y'all's thoughts and do you have any advice for me?
Don't first of all he sounds american right, so I'm uh some of that my connection died
Yeah, I missed a little I missed a little bit of the middle of it
So did I but I I think I'd get the gist of it and my advice is
Don't join the military to be part of something because that's a crack of shit
Join the military to have a comfy cushy job with benefits and a lot of pay
It sounds particularly get a job in the military that doesn't involve actual shooting and getting killed
It sounds like he thinks that the military would be good for him personally
Which you know a lot of people say because like it teaches discipline or whatever, uh, which I mean
Could be true. I mean it's work. It's it pays really well and it has tons of like benefits and stuff
So yeah everybody joined the military. I mean selfishly don't do it for anyone else. Don't do it for your country
No, no, no, no, no, no, no don't I mean because that's that's what he let he didn't say I'm trying to find a good paying job
He said I'm trying to join something like a movement or whatever
Uh, wait, did he because I missed the middle. So did he say just I I want to be part of something?
So yeah, that was just gist. Okay. Well, I don't I don't like I mean
unless you
Really passionately believe that like american foreign policy is great
And you want to like personally put your life on the line to enforce it because you believe in it that strongly
I guess in that case. Yeah, join the military to be part of something
But you know, I don't know what the reason I don't love the military particularly. I'm not I I'm very anti interventionist
But uh, like what what about someone who like like they they recognize that there's flaws with I mean you could argue massive flaws
I get it uh with the way the american military does stuff
What if you think that like I want to make a positive change to some degree in the military?
Yes, you have to take orders, but like if you're out into shit, perhaps you can you know
Make changes from within. I do you think is that uh, okay? Here's the thing
I mean, I think to do that you would need to be an officer and I think without a college education
You have a cap on how high you can rise. So like I mean, I I think if you join the military
They will at some point like pay you to go to college and get a degree which will probably allow you to advance
I think probably if you want to be a high-ranking like guy making decisions in the military
Your goal should be to go to college and then join the military and I mean, you know, there's different ways to do that
military and otherwise
But like just joining the military as like a you know a base recruit is probably not the way to do that
You know what this you know this brings to mind though the lack of community in I don't know America in general
And how I don't know with the death of religion nothing has replaced
I don't know what you mean by that the I mean, yeah, there are more
There are more people that are identifying as non-religious that number is growing
But the number of people that are identifying as like devoutly religious and evangelical christians is also growing
Okay, that's fine. That's fine. That's not really what I mean scary by the way
Well, I mean, I hate religion more than anyone in the world. So I'm totally it's not even just that it's religion
It's that it's evangelicals which are I mean, am I crazy? Are they scary? I think they're scary
Um, uh, well, I find religion pretty terrifying. These are these are the millets
These are the militant ones that are gaining traction
Well, okay. Okay, sure. That's we're becoming we're becoming more just like in politics
We're as a nation we're becoming more divided organizing more. Yeah more people are not
Centrist or not send more people are not moderate christians more people are either atheists or fucking
The pray the gay away ones. Okay fair and that's a that's an issue that should be addressed
However, I got on the subject of thinking about it fair enough on the subject though. Oh, I just pray the gay is not religious
Yeah
Indeed in in relation to this guy's comment though. I think the relevant thing to me is that uh, uh, I do feel that like as
Uh, a larger population a larger amount of the population gets less religious
Even if you know whatever they polarize more and some people get more like I do think that those people
Like there's a strength in a collective belief structure or whatever of like, you know christianity or judaism or you know
Whatever it is. Uh, and I do like this guy's saying he he he wants to be a part of something
And I think that is a very common thing that a lot of people are lacking
And I do not have an answer what I personally believe in I don't think is actually good enough
But it's this like starfleet like humanism
Kind of I mean, I guess we know we have a name for it
What's that? It's weird utilitarianism. Obviously. Oh, right. Yeah, of course weird utilitarian. Yeah, I forgot
Uh, uh, but like I the the problem with that
I think is that it's very impersonal
And I don't think human beings get much value out of particularly abstract concepts like that
Including me include like on a day to day. Do I feel more fulfilled?
Think about that
Not really because my actions aren't like if you're in a church group and you can go like hang out with your peeps
And you can go have a personal relationship with god as they lie and say is the thing that you're doing
That probably is very good. And you would appreciate that
um
I and I don't but good answer
But I mean form a community somehow you
I mean, I think you would agree that uh church is not the only way to get that sense of community
Uh, but you know what though? I think it's like in practical terms. I don't know
What your average like, uh
Non-religious person will replace the thing that is lost. How about uh, I mean, how about like a volunteer organization?
Yeah, how about competitive gaming, bro? Why not? Why not?
Sounds great. That sounds awesome. Well, that doesn't sound bad a fandom on tumblr. That was me
Sure
For you know what it become become a furry become a furry. You know what it is though. I become a fucking juggler whoop whoo
Yeah, they have a community tight. They have a community tight community
I don't know. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. He wants to be a part of something
Uh, join join rfck join join join join endless war
And sign up for the pc pyramid scheme. We'd appreciate that
Um, I don't know. Uh, okay. I'd say you got to form a community somehow. Um
Meet people with like-minded ideas in your community
Maybe join clubs in your area like being part of the anime club was actually helpful and good for me in college
And having something like that. It's just like a good thing to do. So I guess what we're saying is like, um
If you want it this guy wants to join the military things, it would be good for him
Do it
I think we are in agreement that it's not a good idea just to be just because he wants to be a part of something comma
Anything in all caps, you know on on a practical level
Like if someone's just desperate for meaning in their life and they don't have a solution
I I would never say this is like a great idea, but like if you really need something
I don't know. I mean, that's I think of worse ideas. I just don't want to leave him with like no
I don't know no answer. My answer is don't do it for that reason alone
Do it if you do it if you think it will benefit you in
Whatever that means like yeah learning discipline the fact
Yeah, just the fact that it's a secure job if you joining any group just for the practical benefits
That's like that's like being religious because like you're scared of hell. I mean, that's why most that's why most people join
Have jobs just for the practical benefits
Right. Uh, I mean job. Yeah, you know being in the military offers relatively like the you know, best pay most most security
Most benefits. Maybe it's just pragmatically the best thing to do. I don't know brotherhood. I mean if you're in like the marines
I don't know how the army's like, uh, I don't know that probably goes a long way to make you feel like you're part of something
I don't know. I don't know. I mean, it's tough. No, it's tough. It wouldn't be it wouldn't be my choice
I feel like
Yeah, work is work if you can make money doing something do it make your money and get out
Yeah, but he wants to but like belonging to joining the military. I mean, you know, that's gonna come with
You're gonna be you're gonna be the product of your circumstances. You're gonna
I don't know. I don't I'm not trying to shit on veterans. I'm not trying to shit on veterans
But there's like there's a military mindset like people have a
If you know, it changes what you believe it changes what you how you see the world that experience is gonna affect who you are
I don't know. I mean, so I have to think about like if you think I feel like I feel like I feel like
Military people they come out like they they tend to come out, you know, more nationalistic. Maybe more right wing. I don't know
Oh, well, okay. Is that necessarily bad? I can't claim it. It's necessarily bad. I think that's a generalization
It's not it's not my favorite, but whatever. I think you're the military people I know of
That's not everyone, but I think that's the trend and and like responsible people
So like if you're looking for something to make you a responsible adult being in the militaries
It seems to work a lot of the time. I haven't I haven't ever met a military man
Or woman who was like a slob and a lazy piece of shit. Sure
Actually, I mean, it's so there's some military my mom told me like so there was this guy
back in the thing. Yeah, he
Currently lives above my apartment and before he went to military. He was
Kind of rude and a bit disrespectful and he was a bit of a hassle
And he made a lot of noise and and was a bit of a slob, but then he went to military and when he returned
He he was like a completely changed person. He was more nicer to my mom than he
Discipline can be a valuable thing in life. Sure. Sure. He became more responsible, you know, I I have
Thought previously about joining the mill. I've never seriously entertained, but I have dabbled with like man, wouldn't that be
Nice to just go through a process might be really hard might be terrible
But you come out on the end like it just seems to happen that you like if you make it you're now like organized
You're more like goal oriented
It can give you like some companionship and I've met, you know, again, these are just the practical benefits. I don't
I'm not a military guy for sure
But I don't know so I've kind of thought along the same lines a little bit as this guy
Let's talk about the community more about just the practical better
There's nothing that can possibly be wrong about getting as much money as you can while you're young
That's fair. That's just don't be one of those
Just don't just don't become one of those fucking
Manga-loids who goes and does basic training and then washes out and comes home and struts around town with their fatigues on like
They think they're hot shit and everyone should bow down to them when they didn't do shit and they ain't shit and they never
Going to be shit. I don't like that guy. Agreed Jordan. I don't like I don't like my friend from high school Jordan
Specific person I'm talking about. I hate you. You cock-sucking piece of shit. I hope you're dead
Excellent, okay, let's let's switch it up and go from discipline to raw pleasure
Because let's check in with our boy center point who's reporting back from his he was in cancun
Last week and was asking us for advice on what to do and we all resoundingly told him
Fuck some island pussy my dude. Smash that shit wide open. I did uh, I did
And let's find out but mage did not fair
Okay, mage was the conscientious objector
Uh, I actually don't know where it is. No, it's in mexico, isn't it? Yeah, okay. I'm wrong. Oh, is it in mexico?
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right, but he was talking about being on the sea and enjoying the sun
So, okay, it's it's like I was actually imagining it was in spain, uh, but whatever. Oh, yeah
Okay, I thought I don't know why I thought I was not anyway. Let's hear center point. What do you got for us?
Go
Hey guys
I'm back from oh, yeah, cancun man and I gotta say I
Fucked some my soul for right on over
Oh god. All right, so no whores were involved in the story
Oh, okay. I didn't hear your advice. I don't limit our whores center point. He didn't hear it in time. I know morning
I went out and uh got myself on a fucking water jet pack and water jet packs are pretty like in mario sunshine
But they're also impossible to control and I may or may not have crashed directly into the water
Uh three times, uh, and by the time I heard
The podcast and this great sage advice that you've given me
Yeah, correct. I was in pain
Oh, so much pain
Uh, so I appreciate the advice, uh, sorry that I completely and totally failed
Hey, man. Yeah
Whoops, he didn't let us down. He won't you let god down that one if only we'd released it sooner
Well, you know, this is a great life lesson. Never trust a jet pack
When when he says jet pack does he mean like a fucking mario sunshine ass? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they got water jet packs
Wait, is that real? Yeah, they're real Ben. They're fucking real. I never heard of that. That's awesome
There's mario powell. I'm gonna go try it now and end up in a hospital bed next to that
No, that's fucking cool. What the fuck? Yeah, I'm fucking jealous. I'm gonna do that shit. That's dope as hell
I mean, I'm I'm very curious about the whole next podcast is gonna be live from the hospital
Live from ben sains funeral
He's doing special guests that guy from that vacation
Fuck well, uh, well center point
That's too bad and you gotta you gotta you gotta lead with your cock in life, dude
You gotta lead with it. So prioritize the puss. That's that's
Quote me on that put that on my grave prioritize not put the pussy on a pedestal
But just prioritize the puss. That's you know, yeah, it's about balancing life. Not not similar even
Okay, uh next voicemail how many how many left we have this one and one more okay, uh, and uh, okay
So this one is the real this okay. This is from the real pcp dating sim. Okay, the real one. Let's let's get into it
And low procrastinators ways is the real pcp dating sim those fake gay people with their infinite resources
Have not shown results since august. We are taking the mantle a full game coming march 30th
May only in seven days march check for updates at the real pcp dating sim at the
r e a l pcp dating sim
Don't confuse us with those israeli opposing communist people named pcp dating sim
ah
They left us
They left a second voicemail too, but it was basically the same information
Yeah, I checked this out on twitter at pcp dating is the original guys. This is at pcp dating sim
These are a separate organization
Wait, wait, didn't didn't he say it was at real pcp dating sim?
Well, i check it's at pcp dating sim is this guy is the new one. Oh, i'm looking at it right now
Yeah, it's real. They're like green instead of pink like the other one
So I guess there's two competing dating sims and this one's and this one's coming out a day earlier
Uh, two days. I think says march 30, right?
30 yeah, it's in march 30th. This one's coming out. Oh, okay. Yeah, the other one's coming up
Yeah, the first he also said this was made in seven days. Maybe there was a game jam or something that happened. Um, god damn. Well
I this is great. Now we get to compare and contrast. Mark has to always use competition. So I like this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I'm
I'm I'm titillated
I like that when you go to pcp dating and you look at the promo image pin tweet
There's a quote says the pcp dating sim is a fake project
Which isn't actually happening which is a quote from me which I still stand by and I don't believe will release on that day
I mean, we'll just see what happens. We'll see what happens on april fools day
I mean, it's a suspicious day to release your game, right? It gave me my
Did my doubts, but I talked to a lemon tart who's on the project and he assures me that it is real despite its
questionable launch date
Indeed indeed
Uh, okay voicemail from hard life voicemail from hard life is our is our 12th one. Let's uh, oh shit
Hang on. I didn't have this one ready. Okay, uh going over here going to the robot. Okay play
Now hard life commence bring us home. Why is my peepee heart?
Why is my poo poo heart?
But most importantly
Why is life so hard?
Oh
Hard life
Uh, don't worry his skull so hard so it didn't oh he's got the hard skull too
Well, thank god wasn't there one wasn't there one more
We do have we do have uh, wait that there was one more. I've just discovered this is from this is a mystery
I didn't even answer that question at all. It's just like, oh, no, he's dead. Well, I mean, what what more is there to say really?
I mean, he's right
He's right. He's right. That's all he's just he's just he's just right
That's all there to say
Agree on all counts
There there's oh, we have a secret 13th mail here. I think it's from a from a snake individual possibly
Yeah, okay. All right. Here we go. I'm gonna play it. Here we go. I'm getting ready one two three
Commence the plan has been set. Thanks to my dank rimes. You're in for a bad time
And I have devised the most cool
Even as I record this I have mobilized my many snake bodies into action
Oh my god
And you will never see it
Oh
Oh my god, wait, I am here in the flesh arch nemesis question mark
You've been you've been you've been surrounded in a pincer attack
It appears I've caught you with your pants down. I'd like to see you wriggle your fat way out of this one, munchy
I'm ready to reel them snakes
Get ready to be
Stop sucking that. You can't do that. Stop it. Get ready to be in ready to be in an animal slot
They should work out or on a snake proofing
You hold them. You hold them up on him. My urethra isn't snake proof. I didn't foresee this
Get him get him
Shed my soul you cannot possibly comprehend my existence
My scale is beyond your comprehension. Oh, wait. Wait. Use your plus 10 bonus to grapple checks
A real voice line so I can wait. Are you like a real? Are you like a bot? I am real and I oh my god
This is we're killing. Well, we're killing him. Well, he's well
This is just like
In new york city at the nintendo store back in like 2002 when you could go there
And charles marnay would be behind like a fucking wall and you could talk tomorrow
And he would say yahoo and then you'd be like wait mario. Are you actually there and he would say yeah
And then he would say like you're wearing a hat
That's red and then you would piss your pants and die them snakes
You got a little bit of a charles marnay red hat thing going on right here
We're not even swearing me
We're doing so much damage. I wear 600 pairs of sunglasses and still have my eyes to spare
You know, you know at them snakes, I think we can get along. Do you want do you want to do you want to hang out after this?
No, don't listen. No, don't listen
Today's thing saints patrick's day. I think that we could go to the pub. Listen
I know ben's gonna try and role play that catholic motherfucker. He idolizes so much as st. Patrick
You can try and drive them snakes out of ireland and I'm just gonna
I'm not gonna celebrate st. Patrick's day. I'm gonna keep the united kingdom together brexit where we're feeling it
We need open border open snake borders, please
We I want snake holes placed under the walls think about it ben st. Lurks in a cathedral
Who's the catholic none other than the pope? Who else is a catholic? I'm a progressive. I'm a progressive pope of the st. Ben's cathedral
We've got a progressive policy
We've got a progressive snake policy. Um, all right. That's that's my combo attack
That's my combo attack them snakes. We really did some massive damage here today
There is more damage to be done for I have written a diss track to be performed alive
Oh my god. Whoa. Whoa
Okay, I guess we're doing it. I guess we're fucking doing it. We are doing it 100 bpm
Are you ready?
I'm ready, baby. I hope you're ready. Is them snakes recording?
Yes, okay. Don't worry about it. Good. That snakes knows what's up. All right millions of tiny headsets
You're a diabolical diabetic you have non-diagetic pizza
Asphatic you're pathetic you need a medic when your heart stops because your blood clots and you can't stop eating fat
Slop, albola constrict your dick until it pops off get my rocks off and your socks off
And walk in your shoes if I had feet just can't be beaten like a beat in my meat freak
Damn
10,000 tiny mics
Oh my god, incredible. Did you say that you would walk in my shoes if you had feet is that was that one of the
Yes
Okay, don't analyze it. So that so that you would be like me if you were able to do so
I would be like you and then I would kill myself
How does it feel how does it feel to be savagely owned by a snake collective?
Like I say the arc that uh them snakes hates me uh and is my enemy has been well built up across the show
And I'm glad that we finally have some payoff to this uh character arc, which I knew was happening
High five high five me high five me them snakes with your snake goop hands
With my many tales
Yeah, there it is. All right. Thank you. Hi snake. Hi snake brother. All right. Hi snake
Hi snake and by snake. All right. All right combo combo. Thank you for being here. Um, uh get
Good
There he goes
There he goes. Well, everyone, let's just end it on a high note here patron.com slash the procrastinators podcast
Oh
No, don't fool him. Don't do that. Uh five dollars for the bonus episodes people. Um, it's gonna be a lot of fun
It's gonna be a lot of goofy stuff. It's gonna have you're gonna have a good time
There's like 23 or 24 or something of them now
At tpcrastinaires follow us
Follow some of these fucking
Gaming people at pcb dating sim at pcb dating. Who the fuck knows that's not us. We didn't do that
But they're doing it. That might be fun of you to look at. Um
And leave us a fucking more voicemails on the speak pipe people link in the description
Just have fun with it, you know, just be cool. By the way, the them snakes is canonically
Is canonically the the bunch of snakes from my webcomic bail jpe, which you can read on aksadventures.site
I've been animating during the podcast and I'm I'm getting I'm it's gonna be done. It's gonna be cool. It's gonna be cool
It's gonna be a real thing. Oh, is it ending? Are you finishing the finale? I'm I'm animating the finale and it's
I don't know when it'll be done. What's like the eta. Oh, okay. Okay. Eta is like april
The middle of april maybe that's only a month. It's only a month away. How exciting nice
Uh, I'm stoked. I'm fucking stoked. I got I gotta catch up or should I should I just wait until the finale and then binge the whole thing
I mean, maybe I'm tempted to do that. So you gotta finish soon so I can do that
You know, I don't know about you guys, but I feel like a great weight
Relatively speaking is off my shoulders. I've got a couple more that I'm gonna be finishing soon
I feel like I really am turning the page that I've unburdened myself of a lot of problems
I feel good
I feel like I've completed a bunch of projects and I'm almost down to the bunch more
And then I'm really gonna be launching into some new shit and doing good. Dude. I gotta say I feel the exact same way
You know, I finally finished that great bugbear
10 paces and draw and then just like a couple days later. I bang out
Nuts the beginning, which was pretty fun. I feel
Like I like a little bit before 10 paces. I posted a new vapor's page for the first time in a while. Yeah, I'm I'm with you
Uh, you know what? Let me just say on 10 paces. I think we all got a little bit of the rad con bug
Or the the bite just a little bit because I'm not gonna overburden myself again the same way that I was
With rad con 3 and stuff. But but and you know more than that watching rad con
Rather watching 10 bases and draw live
Which like the structure of that show was absolutely perfect for a premiere. There was an arc
There was a narrative like live as in like everyone in the chat for the premiere and stuff. Yeah, exactly
People were there was great. People were fucking dope and like like every round people were like screaming like who they were like
It's gonna be munchy. It's gonna be ben. No tom gang. Tom gang
Yeah, and people went nuts every time there was a there was an elimination
That was like the perfect show to be doing a premiere. Yeah, it was so good. It was the best
It was such a good time
So I don't know about you guys, but I'm feeling great about a lot of things going on with me and with the pcp and rad con 4 when
Uh, I I perpetually I perpetually feel like uh, I don't get to work on the projects that I want to and I'm bogged down
Do you know what you mean? I want to uh, and so I I've felt like that for half a year now and I continue to do
Yeah, yeah when you see any light at the end of that tunnel anytime soon. No
No, okay. I I was feeling that way for a long time like maybe the better part of a year
Um, but I mean, I guess I guess hindsight will tell if it's over or if this is a false light
But I'm trying you know, I want to capitalize on this feeling now. I feel like I finally have a chance to get to get back
To uh, you got to ride good vibes while you got it
Exactly and I've got I've got my big ass biggest we had whatever coming out in 43 minutes
And I'm pretty stoked about that. Oh my god, and I've got a video
I've got a big video coming out and it's gonna be fucking terrible
You guys ever you you're right a thing like a thing and then because you're editing it
You have to listen back to it and while you're listening back to it and editing it
You realize that you don't agree with yourself at all
And everything you say is fucking stupid and you're going to rightfully get crucified
And you're going to have to make alt accounts to crucify yourself because you fucking deserve it
It's that's justice to down go down vote. You're on video for that. Stay. I'm looking forward to it
We gotta protect this from getting into the algorithm. Were you saying something mage? No
No, my life my life my life is perpetually like that one terrible joke character from disney's the hunt back at
Notre Dame where he gets full. Oh, you mean the hush back of Notre Dame
He gets freed from his place like his like I don't even know what you call it
This is like old timey prison where you just like stand in the middle of town with your hands and your head
Locked inside a bar that he gets the stock the stockades right the stockade
And then he walks a little bit and then he gets trapped inside of another prison cell after rejoicing that he was free
That's what my life is continuously. Are you are you like I know what you mean?
Are you like sideshow bob in cape fear just stepping on rakes over and over again?
Just an infant just a whole field of rakes. You just keep stepping on them. Yeah, I I'm like, oh my god
I'm done with the district thing now. I can do all the way. I have to edit that show
Okay, you know guys, uh, I mean I I the reason I'm feeling good is because I've made some hard choices and I've cut certain things
I've come to conclusions about certain things and uh, it hasn't been easy
I've had to made some hard
Basically cuts of things I wanted to do
But I've just got a I've got to prioritize not even just the stuff that I want to do
But that the audience wants to see that will be good financially and you know what?
I don't know. I feel like I've arrived at a pretty good place with what I'm going to be doing next. So
Sick. We'll see fucking see. Yeah fucking sick
And I guess that's it. Are we have we come to the end?
Of this this is like a two and a half hour episode
Yeah, two hour 40. Awesome. Yeah, awesome. Oh god. It was good
It was solid good juicy stuff. Yeah guys. We did it. We fooled
We fooled them
We fooled them by the by the group piss shirt by the group piss shirt and show us pictures on twitter
Tweet at tbcrasnayers with a picture of any of these shirts. Yeah. Yeah retweet. Yeah, they're dope as hell
We've sold uh, I don't know. I want to say, you know a decent number of um
Of shirts and if you got a shirt, yeah fucking show us yourself
Yeah, we'll retweet pictures of people wearing the shirts preferably over your massive jugs
I would just love to see that that would be the perfect ideal
And if you're a man, please stuff your shirt so I can think it's jugs
Please fool Nate jugs. That's what I want to see your jugs of water that you keep next to your body to keep you
And let the and let the pizza party podcast know that we really want we're still looking and we really want to find it
So go tell them to ask them ask them where the podcast is
Just just ask so we can so we can ally
Send send the pizza party podcast our t-shirts with the question
With their p.o. Box if they do let's actually send our shirts to
That'd be pretty funny. Uh, if you pay for it ben, I'll do it
Deal
Just get those neat bucks from our boy yang. Uh, bam distribution done if yang gets elected
I will send the pizza party podcast the pit group piss t-shirts
There it is people hold them to it hold them to it that goes for perpetuity ben
This happens in 2040. I'll send them a pair of shirts every month
No, I just meant one like if he gets elected in 2040, you still have to send him a shirt
I'm gonna get on your case. All right. All right. All right. There you go. Good. You like your neat buck
So you should be able to whoo. All right, that's it people. Thanks for joining us. We'll see you next week
Have a beautiful day and a wonderful time
On the illegal drug
This drug is not a play thing. It's not a beer. It's not a marijuana cigarette
This is something so mind-altering that it will make you a countable or base
You