Feels like it was like two days ago that we recorded the last time.
Yeah, that's how I always feel. I'm like, where did my week go?
I only did like, I only got to spend like one and a half days doing the work I wanted to do.
Oh well.
Not doing the work I wanted to do today at all because I'm doing this fucking podcast.
All right. I'll get the voicemails.
Cyber Shell and Gamers Tavern, we're going to be on. Anyway, who's that? Gamers Tavern. Gamers Tavern.
Can you hear me now?
Hey, we can hear you. And there's Cyber Shell. There's number, what's number five? Yo!
I'm getting the voicemails.
Can you believe we have a full roster of people on this episode?
It's like a real podcast. Oh, we, my God, we qualify.
You thought it was going to be only four people.
Yeah, I saw your message and I was like, I'm going to ruin this guy's whole career.
Okay. Well, day ruins.
I only appear on this podcast to dab on Ben Saint and ruin his day.
That's the only reason any of us are here, right?
The only reason I even am here is to bait people into trying to dunk on me by being on.
To masturbate people.
No.
Voice mail, voicemails, voicemails.
There's not, there's not that many. There's like less than, there's a little less than usual,
so that's good. Fucking finally, yeah.
Only 90 minutes worth.
There's only just over one full page of them, usually there's a page and a half.
Yeah.
They're all going to be like, only just a, only just an hour.
If we only spend an hour on voicemails, I'll call that a win.
There's no winning. I'll take whatever, I'll take it and it whatever.
Maybe they're all just like really well thought out questions and they're all just very good.
It's possible, it's possible, like it's possible that the sun could simultaneously
go supernova right now. It's possible when the odds are possible.
We're all praying for it, but who knows if it's going to happen.
Yeah, yeah. Just like the heat death of the universe happening immediately.
A quantum event, an atom spontaneously transforming into another element.
I have yearned to witness such a rare event.
That's what the Dr. Manhattan says, right? That's like the...
Yeah, yeah. That's part of this little monologue, I believe.
About how humans are all special.
You know, I liked it better when Barney sang the song about how I'm special and I'm the only one.
I didn't like being condescended to by Dr. Manhattan. It just wasn't the same.
Yeah, his thing was kind of some bullshit, to be honest. It was like, oh,
now I realize the odds of this specific person existing, this specific sperm and egg,
like what are cosmic twins? Yeah, whatever. It's like bullshit.
You could point to literally anything that exists and be like, it's...
I can't believe this exists. I can't believe what's on Mars is this shape.
Right. That's basically what he was like. He went to Mars and was like, this is so cool.
That's what betrayed Dr. Manhattan, not as a super fucking genius scientist man,
but as a construct written by a normal comic book artist.
Yeah, he had to take this based character and turn him back into some cheesy fucking,
yeah, humanity's good kind of shit. Oof, big oof.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sad. Fuck you, Alan Moore, you hack.
They did a pretty good job of trying to write a character who loses all his humanity,
but I guess it would be a little too depressing if that was just the...
I mean, he does fuck off at the end of the story, but if he just was like,
nah, I'm not even going to fucking help a little bit during the climax,
that would have been a little too depressing.
I don't know. I think it would have been pretty sick.
People weren't ready for that yet. People were barely ready for Watchmen.
People are still like, they couldn't even conceptualize comics besides being just,
you know, cape shit, whatever the standard was in the 80s.
Fair enough.
I mean, I'm sure there were good comics before Watchmen and fucking Dark Knight Returns,
but I don't know. I'm not really a comics expert.
Um, there was, um, there was, uh, oh, who was that? I was just reading about...
He wasn't like a comic book character. He was like a radio serial character,
and he's the guy who Darkwing Duck is based on. I think he's called The Shadow.
I think he's like... Oh yeah, I know, I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, The Shadow's a real thing.
Yeah, I guess he was not a comic book character.
He was like a film noir guy, right?
It was before they invented drawing,
so they just had to tell stories about him on the radio, I think.
Oh, jeez. It was a long time ago.
It was like a big inspiration on Batman or something.
Yes, yes. I think so.
They like homage The Shadow in an episode of Batman the Animated Series
by making their own version of Shadow called The Great.
And what if The Shadow was a furry? That's Batman.
And Darkwing Duck is also, he's kind of like, he's more The Shadow,
but like, since The Shadow is like such a dated reference,
he was he was often more of like a Batman parody because like that was
contemporaneous.
Well, they're a duck man.
That's right, it's Darkwing Duck, isn't it?
No, I mean, like a guy who's got like a spandex, he's got like, you know,
suit, but then his signature moot aesthetic is that his mask is like a duck bill,
and he makes a duck quank.
I mean, ducks aren't that scary, but I mean, Goose Man, that could be scary.
I'm kind of scared of Gooses.
His signature move is ducking.
Yeah, you can't hit me if I'm if I'm going to duck under it.
That's good.
You could definitely get a really gross looking cartoon called Duck.
There is, there is a, does Donald get turned into a superhero by that one,
like Professor Duck?
No, no, it's not.
It's another character from Duck Towns.
I forgot his name.
Duck Dodgers?
No, is it?
Um, that's that's Daffy.
Is it?
Is it the who's the fucking the big duck, the big guy, uh, Launchpad?
Launchpad McQuack?
He does not become the it's like some scientist guy who works and like he
gets like the suit and he becomes so like he becomes a gizmo duck.
That's true.
I remember gizmo duck.
Yeah.
Learning a lot.
Universe is so extensive.
Why does it exist?
Such a, such a mystery.
You've got to find like the equivalent of the flan.
Fenton is his name.
Fenton becomes gizmo.
What do ducks do?
I guess they just honk.
Why are there so many ducks?
But they, uh, there was a duck.
Gizmo, gizmo, but gizmo duck is not the guy who gets, there's like a game.
There's like a video game about not technically it's Donald, but they don't
call him Donald and I think he's technically not the same character.
I know, I know what you mean.
Uh, I forgot the name, but it was a game on a super Nintendo and the Genesis.
We're learning so many things right now in a podcast.
There was a show in the late 90s about Donald duck becoming like a ninja.
Yeah.
The ninja one.
I think there was maybe a game grumps about it.
Maui Mallard?
Yeah, that's the one.
Yeah, maybe.
Maui Mallard.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I actually recognize this box art now.
I can't believe there was a Donald duck as a ninja game.
What the fuck?
It's actually weirder than kind of words.
Yeah, I rented that game years ago and it's, uh, it's kind of mediocre, honestly.
Maui Mallard is a medium boiled detective.
Oh, because of eggs.
Jesus Christ.
Wait, you can't medium boil out an egg.
Why is he medium boiled?
You can hard boil it and you can soft boil it.
I think she's not hardcore enough.
So it's just in between soft and hard boiled.
Okay.
Yeah.
This is not hard enough.
Lane.
There was a lot of demand for duck and Donald duck related media in the 90s.
It's huge in like parts of Europe.
Like in some European countries, duck stuff is like really big in culture.
Uh, in Germany, I went to, there was a like a celebration when I was there and there
were a bunch of, I saw people dressed as it's the goons.
It's like the evil goons that like try to steal Scrooge's fortune.
And like, I didn't even know what they were all the be the be the beagle boys.
Yes.
I saw people dressed as the beagle boys.
It's like, I don't even know if anyone would know what that is.
I'm looking at the list of fictional ducks on Wikipedia.
And I've got like the ducks from duck hunt in video game section.
If they remade duck tails, they would just replace them with Jeff Bezos, right?
No, they replaced, uh, one of the rich ducks in the duck tails remake with like basically
Mark Zuckerberg.
That makes sense.
There are a lot of ducks.
Social media fictional ducks, I mean.
There's so many ducks.
I mean, there's, I mean, the whole, the whole duck of verse is.
Are we just going to have the duck episode where it's like, all right.
We're not even recording.
This is completely wasted.
Donald Duck.
No, Craig's recording.
This is all the bonus episodes.
Thank fucking God.
Yeah.
This is going to be a really short episode.
I started recording.
I was saying.
I just throw out my audacity because I was like, this is too good.
I think ducks in other media.
And the second example is duck guy from don't hug me.
I'm scared.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I remember that.
The duck guy.
I don't know why it just cracks you up.
It doesn't have a name or anything.
Pretty fair.
Maybe we should just, maybe Ellie is, I should just put this in the main episode.
I'm not against it.
I started recording, but I don't have the, I don't have the beginning of the duck conversation.
I know Craig should have it, but.
Craig has, Craig has, I just.
You can have 15 minutes of an episode if we just include all of this.
I didn't even get to start off with my customary joke.
Well, we can have an official start and then the unofficial start, which is our duck conversation.
Let's, let's sync now while we've got the chance on the count of three, say sync.
One, two, three, saying.
Same.
Why?
Sorry, my headphones were off.
Fringe.
Okay, I'll do it again.
One, two, three, saying.
Same.
Okay, I'm gonna move my mic.
Ha, ha, ha.
Yeah.
Okay, there we go.
Um, ducks thumbs up.
Duck tails.
I didn't like, I feel like maybe I talked about this on another episode,
but I didn't like duck tails.
I thought that, I thought that cartoons with animal characters were baby shit.
I thought Disney cartoons were baby shit and I thought animals were baby shit.
You definitely weren't a furry.
No, no.
Sounds like an opinion edge lord contrarian fancy.
Yeah, a little.
I thought animal shows were baby shit until I grew up.
And then I got all into my little ponies.
Then I thought they were hot.
Take care.
Until I saw the quantities.
Well, after my sexual awakening, I realized that they, the ducks could be fucks as well.
I could fuck the ducks and now everything changed.
Things would never be the same after the Fire Nation attacks.
After the, ah, whatever.
Oh, after the Duck Nation attacks with the duck bending powers.
After everything changed after Duckburg attack.
Duckburg would never be the same.
My favorite duck show actually was Darkwing duck and not duck tails because
I liked the concept of a hero who sucks at everything
because that was basically the plot of the show.
Just so relatable.
No, he's, he's good when he, when he tries.
He's mostly incompetent.
I don't agree.
He's, he's not motivated.
He doesn't want to, he's unmotivated, but when he puts his mind to it, he's pretty good at crime fighting.
He mostly does it to become popular.
So it kind of reminds me of like a YouTuber that just does videos to become popular.
Like every YouTuber.
So he just wants to be a hero to be popular and he kind of sucks at it.
I just liked it because it was very, it was a very cynical show, even though it was a kid's show.
Yeah.
Now, now I'm thinking of like a YouTuber going around dressed up as a superhero,
going into alleyways and beating people up for views.
Yeah, that would be a good idea actually.
That probably exists to some degree.
That's like Phoenix Jones, right?
I was gonna say that.
He wasn't like a full-on YouTuber, but like that's basically what it is.
He had a, he had a big social media presence.
Yeah, he had a YouTube channel.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I guess he was a YouTuber.
I guess he could technically be considered one.
I just, I just, I watched that atrocity guy the other day.
Maybe that's an idea for the YID crew.
Ooh.
Which is gonna become crime fighters.
It's a new niche on YouTube.
I could definitely see that.
People would love that content.
Riley already has a cape.
That's true.
I mean, that could be the name, that could be the name of their like superhero team,
the branches of YID.
Dude, that is like a bad idea.
Um, did you guys see that May is pregnant?
Excuse me?
What?
I saw you celebrating the good news on Twitter.
He seems so happy about it.
Oh, you saw that?
Yeah.
She, she's, you know, I'm just, god, I'm glad someone is protecting the white race.
All right.
Because Biden sure as hell isn't doing a, doing a damn thing.
Um, what a night.
No, Maya, she, she tweeted like the, the census stats saying that like white people,
there are fewer white people and she said, oh, I'm so, this is a girl.
I'm so glad I'm having a baby now.
This is the now is the best time I need to be having babies now.
This is so weird.
Good for you.
Love it for you.
That's so strange.
It almost sounds like a coat.
It's totally.
It almost.
I don't even know whether she's happy about it or not.
I guess she is.
I, I can, I, yeah, I feel, yeah, I feel like I want to read it that way.
I guess I could, I could maybe see.
Oh, I mean, no, no, no, no, no, this is good.
This is good.
The white, white race needs this.
I, I should be happy about it.
Maybe, maybe.
Having children just sounds like a nightmare.
And so, yeah, it doesn't matter who is having children.
I'm always just like, no.
I mean, I don't want to, I'm not actually that caught up with my Ethan Ralph
Laura, but he didn't.
He just had like another child born to some other woman who's like.
Yeah, the last training order against him or some shit now.
So it's just like, you know, he's staying busy.
You got to respect the hustle, just constantly having new children.
The first won't share the first, the first marriage and immediate pregnancy,
and then divorce ended in like extra, it protracted, you know,
divorce proceedings and harassment lawsuits and all that.
But I'm sure this time it'll work out a lot different.
The best thing you can do is have a rock solid foundation.
Make it all content for social media and be posting that all the time.
So there's no way you can bite your in the ass when it goes wrong.
It's all going to work out.
And if it doesn't, hey, it's great.
It's going to make great content.
Yeah, it's good content either way.
God, I only have to be on the fucking show.
Going to the divorce, going to divorce court, going to divorce court
and just being like, hey guys, it's your boy vlogging you from,
from divorce court.
So big dance is going to be great.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I'm going to get married for content.
Get married.
Why not?
They're worse.
They're worse reasons.
Yeah, it's a fantastic idea.
So much, so many like donations coming in.
We'll be great.
This childbirth will be great content.
I bet, I bet somewhere.
I think there's already a, I think there's already an entire genre of YouTubers
that have done that before.
Yeah, I love the idea of someone like live streaming their whole wedding
and like right in the middle of the proceedings.
Like, yo, what's up?
Thanks, pussy fucker 69 for the $100 donation.
Really appreciate it.
That's definitely real.
That's, that's, it's definitely happened.
I know people have live streamed their weddings,
but I don't know if anyone's ever stopped for donuts.
That's not in the future.
That's the past.
Before the vows, can we just catch up on donuts quickly?
Do you take your fellow content creator to be your, your YouTube partner?
Uh, uh, uh, till, uh, till a copyright, copyright strikes.
What are you doing at this wedding?
The first streamer to get married in a chat.
They turn, they turn the wedding into a review of something.
Like, like this is the pretext, this like the beginning skit is the wedding.
And then they turn the camera and they start talking about fucking.
I'm here to review, I don't know.
Reviewing marriage.
You know, it started off like a, the plot of super paper Mario.
First, first wedding.
This is a good like a concept for like boomer reviews on YouTube.
Like, uh, today I'm reviewing my dumb bitch wife.
First of all, I hate my fucking wife.
The game feel, the game feel is, it leaves a lot to be desired.
The graphics are pretty, pretty realistic.
Um, you know, maybe a little too realistic.
There was a lot of false advertising for this game.
A lot of bull shots before the marriage started, but, uh,
now that it's released, definitely a visual downgrade.
The devs, not a lot of replay value patches.
The patches just starting to know what that would mean.
It's, it's, uh, it's, uh, it's a band and wear.
This marriage is a band and wear.
Now that I'm a few months into this marriage,
it's pretty obvious to me the economy is very pay to win.
Hahahahaha!
Yes!
This game is not fucking balanced.
This sucks.
Just gotta, you just gotta patch it, I don't know.
You just gotta, well, but at least it's good content.
At least I can stream it on Twitch.tv.
Uh, uh, I'm, I'm, yeah.
I'm what you could call the DSP of getting married.
Um, you know, I complain, you just edit the game.
You walk home and your fucking wife's cheating on you
and you're just like, wow, there was nothing I could do!
Just get good, oh my god, omega lull, just get good, marriage, just get good, and she wants you.
Get a cut to the chat, it's just omega lulling at you.
Compilations, guys, this is how you don't get married.
This is how you don't live your domestic life.
When people do mukbang, and I think people like livestream them sleeping, I don't even know if that's allowed.
You could do the entire, entire life challenge livestream, entire life livestreamed.
There's like, in real life streamers, you basically just stream their whole lives like, just incidentally, so I'm not surprised if someone out there is basically doing that right now.
Having a baby, so I can mount a fucking digital head camera to it, and then just livestream, it's POV 24, it's entire life.
You can basically do this, you know, you can like, have a kid and be like, on broadcasting it every day on social media.
You're basically making them have like, a little Truman show, and they got it sent to a channel.
We gotta monetize. Baby, you're not, this baby, I gotta feed and clothe it while it better pay for itself with content.
Wait, wait, wait, I need to write all these ideas down.
The Gamer's Tavern Empire is about to begin.
This is the next wave of content.
This is the rocketing to Twitch stardom.
Every time you sit down to have just dinner with your family, you like, have to set up all these like, mics.
They're like, Dad, we don't wanna do a podcast, we just wanna eat dinner.
It's like, shut up, we gotta do another podcast episode. This is the bonus episode.
Honey, did you wash your hands before the podcast?
Did you, uh, did you, uh, make, make sure you gotta clean your plate before we, before we, uh, sign off the podcast and ask everyone to like, comment, and subscribe?
It's like, uh, Dad, we're tired, we just wanna go to bed.
He's like, quiet, we only have a few more pages of voicemails, just be quiet.
Damn, this is, this is too real.
Uh, this, this is, this is just, damn, I can't believe we live in 1984 and the world is really like this now.
I mean, it's not even that far removed from like, celebrities, children being in the spotlight and having to like,
growing up, like, knowing to pose for cameras and doing photo shoots and being so disconnected from actual real life.
Man, this is just the modern, this is the modern version of that.
Like, uh, if I can, Jayden Smith or something.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, you know, it is kind of like Jayden Smith has said some infamously hilarious things, but like, I mean, you know,
Yeah, he actually had people paying attention like his Twitter account when he was like a tiny little kid, you know what I mean?
Like, of course he's gonna have all the dumb shit he said recorded.
It's, can you really hold that against him?
I probably said some pretty stupid shit as a kid, but luckily nobody cared.
I said some pretty stupid shit like last year.
Oh, we know, we know.
Just as embarrassing.
We didn't forget.
Um, it's like.
Got my wrist, it's ready to go.
Was it, was it the, was it the YMS review of the, that one movie with the Ursa?
Which fucking?
After Earth.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
There's the clips, there's the clips of like the, it's like Will Smith and his whole family on talk shows and sometimes like,
sometimes like they make jokes like at Jayden's expense and like they laugh at him and like his dad like laughs at him when he makes a fool of himself.
It's kind of funny, but it's also like, wow, that's bizarre.
There are a lot of interesting like things you can find from those just like behind the scenes, like touring and like promotional videos.
Like cause they record so much promotional bullshit.
Like that's something I appreciate.
Like YMS will like, nobody's doing like a Lion King review.
He'll like go through like all the fucking promotional red carpet shit just looking for the highlights of like cringe and just weird interpersonal moments like that.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's, it is like, I remember in that one, it does like the way Will Smith talks about the movie is like, yeah, I guess you can,
he had a certain attitude toward the production and it does kind of come across in the movie itself and like why it is the way it is, you know,
why is my son the star of this movie even though he's bad at playing this role?
Well, it was a little family project.
That movie had like weird Scientology undertones to it.
What kind of undertones?
Scientology, I don't know.
There's like a lot of weird parallels.
That movie was just weird because like they decided to have Will Smith be like calm and like not emote, which is like, that's not really the kind of acting he's the best at.
He just had a vehicle for his son.
So he had to take the backseat before.
Right.
It was a vehicle for his son, I guess, but nobody wanted that.
They just wanted to see Will Smith be Will Smith.
Not even Jaden Smith wanted it.
Right.
Is he still acting and stuff?
I mean, I assume it has to be, right?
The only thing I remember Jaden Smith being in was what was that fucking anime on Netflix?
Oh, right.
Right.
Oh, the one with the Tobleron?
Neo-Yokio.
That was it.
I only remember that image of the Tobleron.
Yeah, I think it was.
I think it was Neo-Yokio.
It was pretty funny.
Oh, no.
I'm real at it.
I only have disk space remaining for three hours and 14 minutes.
Oh, dear.
I got to clear some space.
That's pretty mad.
I guess.
I guess that means no voicemails this week.
Oh, no.
What a nightmare.
It's like four hours now, so.
There's five people on here.
I can see ourselves going four hours easy.
Since Cyber Shield is on this one, it's probably going to be five hours.
Well, we had to take, last time we had Laserbot.
That was like a historic moment.
That was a world historic event that'll be in history books.
That's true.
It's all been overshadowed.
It's all been overshadowed by the Chris Chan news.
It's such.
It is so funny the timing of that and how you had to rush to put out your Sonichu thing.
I mean, you didn't actually have to, but I agree that that was probably the best way
to do it.
I was better immediately than later, I think.
I wish I had just put it out a year ago.
Like you said, it's not like, if it was already out, it would still be getting a spike of
views.
All Chris Chan content was getting a spike.
Ideally, it would have been better if you just had put it out like a year ago or at
least six months ago.
Yeah.
I didn't gain anything by waiting.
I thought, I mean, I thought, I really thought that it was the end of Crystory and nothing
else of interest was ever going to happen.
Truly, it didn't matter if it came out.
Nothing had happened for like years.
It really seemed like it was sort of tucking in.
And now it's like, this is the most relevant Chris Chan will ever be.
I have to believe in my heart that there will never be another like more mainstream event
than this.
Like please, for God's sake.
Yeah.
I hope it never gets more, any more confidence.
As someone who has known about Chris Chan since like, I don't know, before 2010, watching
all of this was pretty surreal for me.
It's horrifying.
It's just, it's just horrifying.
I think I watched that Tucker segment on a voucher.
I didn't watch the segment.
The segment is weird because it's, he says like, you know, Baba Chris Chan, Baba biological
male, and then he moves on to like some other talking point.
He barely even, barely knows anything about.
He's literally just like, oh, we can say this is bad because of trans people.
I feel like it's not as like a pivotal turn.
I don't think it's a pivotal turning point that's like, Oh no, now loads more people
are going to think that trans people are just like this.
I think it was just like one in like just another.
Any, any same thing will realize there's like no connection.
It's just, it's just a talking point.
Yeah, I already have the same talking point.
Like you said, he barely, he barely mentions Chris Chan.
It's, it's, it's like you could just, just have a list just like any time a trans person
does a crime.
Just like talking was like, all right, time for the segment.
And he'll just read off the list.
This crime, this crime, this crime.
Okay, there we go.
Trans bad.
Someone pointed out that it was like, I think Tucker Carlson thought his name or thought
Christine's name was Chris Chan.
Like everybody thinks that.
But it's not.
I mean, that's not, that doesn't even make sense.
Like do people, I mean, okay, whatever.
I guess it makes even theoretically possible.
But like even people that should know, I've seen them writing it as two separate words,
Chris space, capital Chan.
And like, no, it's Chris dash Chan.
It's the Japanese diminutive.
Maybe I've just been too much online, but like that seems so obvious to me.
Like obviously it's short for something.
It's the Japanese diminutive.
It's the Japanese diminutive and it's short for Chandler, but it's not a name in and of
itself.
She's not Chris.
We have to forgive Tucker.
He's not very cultured.
Yeah.
He doesn't know deep internet lore, which is embarrassing.
You should watch Ben's lecture.
You should watch.
Ben, you should add him on Twitter.
We're still weird.
I got the inside scoop, Tuck.
You do.
Hey, Tuck.
It's weird how he picked Christian.
If he didn't really mention him much at all is like, why pick Christian out of like anybody
else?
Literally just because it was like trending on Twitter and it was like, oh, this is just
some easy thing I can say for like five seconds without having to like formulate an argument.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's just so weird to me how many people are like, I never even heard of CWC before this
week.
And I'm like, damn, you people aren't as online as me, I guess.
Yeah.
I guess.
It makes perfect sense to me.
It's kind of like a really weird internet thing that you have to have been using internet
for a long time to be fair.
It's like, I have a, it's hard for me to even understand like how quote unquote mainstream
it is.
But like, I don't expect everyone to have like a deep knowledge of Christianry, but I do
expect someone who's been online for a long time to have like heard of Sonichu.
It's a pretty like not seen one image with the medallion ever in their whole life.
Like it's a pretty widespread.
I remember only ever hearing about Christian and Sonichu from Ben, not from the lecture,
but from just talking.
I hadn't heard about it until that point.
People in my discord were telling me that I should, that I should call it, that I shouldn't
call it a Sonichu lecture, that I should call it a Chris Chan lecture because the name
Chris Chan is more recognizable than Sonichu.
And I thought that was so bizarre.
At this point now, that's probably true, but that didn't used to be true.
No, to me, Chris Chan is the creator of Sonichu.
Like that's, that's who they are first and foremost and everything else is like,
I like about those lectures that they are looking at it through the lens of Sonichu,
which is the only real reason you should be interested in Chris Chan.
You know what I mean?
Like you shouldn't be like, oh, I want to troll this person.
You should be like, oh, I want to see this weird thing they made.
You know what I mean?
People, people asked me in the, in the comments, like, are you going to do,
are you going to do a lecture, a 103?
And I'm like, what would I do it on?
I talked about the whole comic.
The comic is over.
Literally just bait them and be like, do Sonichu 103 and get those clicks.
And it's just like one, like a couple like minutes on the remainder of the special issues.
And then the rest is just summarizing slime and punishment.
Maybe you never know.
Maybe it might be Radcon 5, baby.
There might be more Sonichu coming out of prison.
Yeah, we don't technically know that Sonichu is over.
I saw some people saying like, oh, it's over at this point, but we don't know necessarily.
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, I'm not necessarily saying we're going to get more.
So we'll see.
We might get the prison arc.
I think this, this might be the most like a new and like more productive era.
You know, we had a Sonichu Dark Age for a while there.
There was no Sonichu.
Right.
Maybe now we'll get more than ever because Chris will just have like, what else is she going to do in?
I don't think she'll end up in prison.
I think she'll end up in an institution or something.
Even in an institution or you're in prison, they let you have crayons there apparently.
Those are some of the only things you're allowed to draw with because they don't want you having sharp things.
This is the long game.
Chris was preparing for this whole time.
It all comes back as full circle.
You start as a child when you're drawing with crayons and then you end as an adult in prison and you're only allowed to do that.
That's why she never got more advanced.
She knew.
Right.
This is going to happen eventually.
She knew.
She knew it was going to come back to this.
You saw her in her mind.
She used Future Sight.
Just like she used Future Sight to avoid being raped by her son, Sonichu.
In issue 13, she used Future Sight to see that this was going to happen.
Honestly, I mean, I don't know.
It's like part of me feels weird going back and trying to look at an old F-shoes of Sonichu and laugh at them,
but there's some things that are still so funny.
It's just like that one panel where he's like,
Begged your pardon, miss, but nice rack or whatever.
Oh, Blake.
It's so fucking funny.
Blake.
Yeah, Blake.
Confidential Christie.
Thanks, Blake.
Don't get any fucking ideas.
They all just want to fuck her.
Of course.
Wouldn't you?
It is one of those weird things where it's like,
God, just because of how obscenely, ridiculously documented every aspect of Christine's life was,
there are a million red flags in hindsight,
and there are a million, a million people have pointed out things like there.
You know, Chris is really weirdly affectionate with Barb.
It's like, hmm, yeah.
There was a, this was like months ago,
but there was a tweet she made that was like,
it was like apropos of nothing.
She made a tweet that was like,
Yes, I have slept in my mother's bed,
but only sleeping, only sleeping.
Have a good and safe day.
Lightning bolt, blue heart, lightning bolt.
Let's talk about a red flag.
I was like, hmm, yeah.
Like, hmm, my tweet about how I only slept and did nothing else in my mother's bed
is raising a lot of questions that were already answered by my tweet.
I don't, I don't see what the problem is.
Some people just have to take things out of context.
I know.
Yeah, sometimes it's better to take something out of context.
That's, I just, that was like months and months ago.
That was like earlier in the year.
It's, might genuinely have been unrelated.
Well, I can't, I can't say I'm too surprised,
honestly, knowing the history of Chris,
it's kind of par for the course, I guess.
This is what I said.
Not really.
I'm just saying by Ben, which is that.
It's a little stranger than anything that's happened before.
Yeah.
I would say.
I kind of thought Chris was over.
I thought we were entering the boring twilight years of just boring commissions
and all sorts of other weird, you know, nonsense.
And yeah, honestly, I don't want to get too into it,
because actually I'm on the same page as you, Ben,
which is I saw there's like more lore about some Chris being manipulated.
And I was like, I don't even want to, I don't want to read this.
It seems too, it seems too upsetting.
I just don't want to get into it.
I'll let everyone else take care of this.
I've seen a bunch of it.
And I'm like, I think it's like, yeah, that seems plausible.
Sure.
I believe Chris might be manipulated, but like.
It doesn't absolve responsibility or anything.
It's just like another factor.
Another thing that's going to be complicating this whole ordeal.
Chris has been, Chris has been manipulated into doing very,
very bizarre and like harmful things.
Hardly anyone could possibly be on the record as much as Christine
as like being easily manipulatable and like having just like on record
is doing like being tricked into doing all sorts of ridiculous things.
So I mean, again, I'm not saying absolves responsibility.
I'm just saying it's another thing to make it more complicated.
But blackmailed for thousands of dollars by someone telling her
that a laser on the moon was going to blow up quick bill.
It was literally a thing that happened.
So not nothing is off the table.
I don't understand.
Why do they think financially extorting was going to be the best option
for, you know, ruining Christine's life?
Like that's just a weird saga for me.
I think they just wanted money.
They were just like, hey, we can just get some money from this person.
Lol.
OK.
You could just get a job.
It's not an epic troll, guys.
You could spend months trolling this fucking weirdo
and manipulating them and gaslighting them until you can get their fucking
like PlayStation online gift cards or whatever.
Or you just get a fucking job.
It's like, OK, so these people really in their mind, the idea guys
and whatever this new chick is, they in their mind like,
I'm really owning Christine by spending hours and hours in my life,
literally like my life every day and feeding into her delusions
and just being, you know, it's like you're wasting your own life.
You know what I mean?
Like I've seen like chat logs leak and they're like, they're very long.
I mean, Christine just wants to talk about lots of bullshit.
So you have to do a lot of just entertaining.
I mean, if the rumors are to be believed, the new girl is just like a sadist
who just likes to torture people
and wanted Chris to kill herself eventually
and was playing the long game to get Chris to commit suicide just for fun.
There's a lot of psychos on the Internet.
It's a scary place to be honest.
And yeah, it's kind of sad that someone would target Christine
just because how famous she is.
Basically, I would assume that's the main reason just like, you know.
How famous and how famously vulnerable.
If you've been using the Internet as long as I have none of this is surprising.
Right.
Just the kinds of people that are out there.
Yeah, me and Gamer, we're old friends on.
We go back to the LP days and we just, we've seen it all.
We've seen it all.
We've seen all the horrible.
I mean, even like something like that exists out there.
It's just sort of, it's sort of stranger when you have like a face
or a name to an actual person who does that sort of stuff.
Like there's always this amorphous like, oh, the dark web,
the worst kinds are on there.
And then you see one in real life in some capacity and you're like, oh my God.
How does somebody end up like that?
It is different when it's like versus like, oh, there are creepy people on the net
versus like this, here's a specific person, all the weird fucked up shit they've done.
And it's like, damn, it's kind of harder to like, you know,
pretend they don't exist or whatever when, you know, I know what they are.
You know what I mean?
But I don't know.
Well, there was a time when the regular internet was basically the dark web
and the average forum was like a four-shand board, you know?
Yeah, the internet used to be a lot meaner in general to the point where,
I mean, there was this weirdly like lighthearted element to it all,
but I don't know, yeah, like the idea of harassing people and stuff.
I mean, a lot of this harassment to Chris Chan back in the day was like,
not even seen as that malicious.
I mean, there are obviously a few malicious actors,
but a lot of it was just people were like, lols, it's just trolling.
It's just trolling for the lols.
It's all been agglomerated onto like, you know, individual, like social media sites.
It's all been like collected into, you know, like private platforms, right?
Instead of the discourse being all spread out across like forums and message boards
and private servers and stuff.
Right. People in general are just less psycho on the internet now that people,
you know, a lot of people tie to real names and identities to their online identity,
whereas back in the day it was like everybody, you can't be using your real name online
or you're going to get kidnapped and killed.
So everyone has to do everything anonymously, you know what I mean?
And now everybody just willingly offers the government all their personal information.
Yeah, now they want to make it a crime to be anonymous on the internet.
There's like people like, we see these trolls hiding behind their anonymity,
like all the, you know, like the blue check marks on Twitter.
They're like, they shouldn't be allowed to be anonymous and not,
because they can make fun of me and my face, but it's like, I don't know.
I don't want anonymity to go away, but I do understand there's people who abuse it,
but I don't think the solution is making it so everyone has to use the real name all the time.
It's okay. The vaccine microchip will automatically be uploading your data to your Twitter account soon.
It will upload your DNA to your profile picture.
As soon as Bill Gates is going to wait until 99% vaccine saturation,
then he's going to push the big red upload button, and then the blue check marks will be safe.
The blue check marks are the only people who are going to be spared in like the post-apocalypse.
It's like every single other person is going to be purged.
Only the most valuable people recognized by their blue check mark will survive.
It's the mark of the beast. It's the mark of the beast.
Mark of the best, more like.
Yeah, exactly.
I got a pee. Sorry, I'll be back in a minute.
Excuse me. Pardon me, bad time.
All right, everybody, now we can finally shit-talk Ben, get all of our hot Ben takes out.
Hot Ben Saint takes out.
Can you believe that Ben Saint doesn't have 30 plus tabs open on his web browser at any given time?
What a dork. How does he even use the internet if he doesn't have that many tabs?
He's barely using it.
He needs at least that many.
My favorite thing about Ben Saint is his Twitter timeline.
It's basically just him listing all the people he hates.
Somebody has to dab on them.
I saw a series of tweets the other day where the entire day was just him tweeting,
I hate this guy and I hate this other guy and I hate that guy.
That's our Ben. He hates a lot of people.
There just wasn't enough negativity on the internet.
So Ben was like, you know, someone really needs to close the gap between the endless positivity on the web
and someone who's just solely focused on the negative.
There was too much discourse on Twitter.
There were too many people having conversations and someone needed to come in and be a little agitator,
a little disruptor and throw a wrench into the works and be like, you know what?
I'm going to say what nobody else is going to say, which is that some of these people online suck.
And you know what? He's a hero for saying it.
Here's a list of all the content creators I don't like.
And why I don't like them and how they can be better.
That's the, you know, people are afraid to tell it like it is.
They just want to sugarcoat everything.
They're too afraid to constantly be getting into arguments with everyone who approaches them on Twitter.
I think our boy does though.
Gamers Tavern was following it with silence because he loves everyone.
Yeah, exactly.
No, no, no, it's all good.
It's all good.
If you're listening to this episode right now, definitely do not bother Ben Saints on Twitter
because he will definitely listen to this part back and know what's happening.
Yep.
We're all fucked.
Nah, he'll never.
There's no way he'll ever listen to me say fuck Ben Saint, more like Duck Ben Saint, more like Duck Saint, more like Quack.
Eleazar, make sure that Ben Saint has been thoroughly dabbed on and that he never knows about this.
And if you ever find out about it, it's your fault.
There's so many fictional ducks. I'll never know them all. I'm actually upset looking at like the page of fictional ducks isn't that long, but there's still so many I've never even heard of before.
I actually know most of the video games.
I'm back and I just want you to know that you're all great chums and pals and I'm just glad to share my good times.
Share some positive vibes with all of you here on the Procrastinator's podcast.
I'm so glad you said that, Ben, because we weren't shit talking to you the whole time you were gone or anything like that.
I know. I assume so.
Yeah, we definitely weren't doing that at all.
What else? Why would I think anything differently?
What did I miss?
I don't know. We're back on the ducks.
We're like, I don't know. I think this happened before the episode started.
We accidentally pulled up a list of fictional ducks on Wikipedia and we can't stop.
Well, it was no accident. We deliberately wanted to talk about ducks.
It was a guided discussion towards ducks and Darkwing duck and a lot of ducks.
Doctor Quack from Sonic the Hedgehog.
Oh my God. I remember Doctor Quack. Jesus Christ.
I don't.
That's an interesting example because it's a non-game example.
Yeah, it was from...
I actually don't remember Doctor Quack.
That's from the Adventures of Sonic the Hedgehog, right?
Yeah.
I like, at the bottom of the page by the video game section, it has Bruce the Duck from the Atari 2600 video game Duck Attack.
I don't know why, just the image of this super low-poly duck.
It's just a duck.
It's a low-poly looking, but with the description, with the Wikipedia description,
something about that cracks me up here. I'm gonna post it in chat so people will understand what I'm talking about later.
Bruce the Duck is just a duck.
You know what they say, life comes at you fast like Sonic on a first date.
Exactly. Except Sonic doesn't date. He's an incel.
No, he's a vol-cell.
Sonic doesn't come in. He's a vol-cell.
He could get laid, but he would never.
He would never do that.
He would never dare do that to me.
He would never betray me like that.
Dating would mean slowing down in life, and we all know he would never do that.
He's too much of a shan to get laid.
That's the opposite of like, celibate the word.
Like, to have had sex in a celibate.
No, that's not it.
Just laid.
Based.
So like, vol-laid or inlaid?
In that one, in the Doom episode of Action Button, Tim Rogers is giving a bunch of lists of like,
how like everyone I knew in college had watched the animation for Nights of the Round from Final Fantasy VII,
and he says like, it doesn't matter if you were like, loser or Chad, virgin or laid.
So that's the dichotomy.
I see.
I don't think it's true that everybody watched that animation.
That seems a little strange.
He said that like, he would be like, hey, I'm playing, you've heard of Final Fantasy VII,
and they're like, yeah, I've seen that poster of Cloud on the motorcycle,
and they're like, okay, cool, we'll just, hey, look at this cool summon I can do.
Look at how these knights, and they go, wow.
It is a cool attack animation.
I'll give them some credit.
I appreciate when Tim Rogers tells me about video games in between monologuing about his life for three hours at a time.
Yeah.
He is a, what a windbag.
What a bitch.
He's one of those people where it's like, oh yeah, well, of course you can have an interesting YouTube channel
because you've done all these cool things in your life, like go to Japan and translate games.
What am I supposed to talk about?
Just being a fucking loser who makes YouTube videos and hasn't done those things?
I brought up Tim Rogers last, I think after the show last week, I brought him up and I showed,
and I mentioned him to Tom, and Tom looked up a picture of him,
and Tom was like, oh no, I don't like the look of this guy.
You know, sometimes you see a guy on the Internet,
and it's not fair to judge a book by its cover, but you just see him and you're just like, I don't like that guy.
Ben's immediate defense, and I will defer to his expertise since he's more familiar,
that it was not the most flattering quote though.
I had that reaction with pro Jared.
He might be a nice guy, I don't know, but I just don't like his fucking face,
which isn't very polite or nice to say, but I just have had that reaction.
I see him in a thumbnail and I'm like, I'm not clicking that video, you piece of shit.
How dare you ask me to click this video by making a thumbnail?
For whatever reason, the women seem to really like him.
Yeah, the only thing I know about pro Jared is that he got in that controversy.
I can't even remember how long ago that was.
They completely lost track of linear time.
That was before fucking COVID, wasn't it?
Yeah, it must have been.
So it must have been like early 2020 or like late 2019 or something?
I think it was like 2019 or 2018.
Oh my God, that shit was so funny.
That shit was so funny.
Bad things happen to people who aren't me.
I remember celebrating when I was watching his follower count drop.
I thought it was so funny.
Watching him go down from a million subs to 750k.
But then I ended up hating other people involved in that situation more than I hated him about it.
It wasn't like it was all him or whatever.
I think Bethead Bernie or something had a good video where it was like pro Jared.
It wasn't just being a creepy.
Some people lie to him and some other bullshit.
I don't really want to rehash it all and I don't remember it properly.
Just for the record, I'm not putting him on blast.
I literally do not hate the guy.
I just think he has a fucking weird face.
Bethead Bernie asked me for my input about that video.
One of my tweets is in that video.
It's in some point.
It's screen-shotted.
Your take on the Sitch.
That was the first thing that happened as soon as the fucking pro Jared drama dropped.
As soon as the Christian drama dropped, everyone was like,
what's Ben Sainz take on this?
It's the most important take to know about.
The only one.
All you need.
And that's all you need.
Pro Jared's face is like smoothed out grumbo.
Is there any way to describe it?
He's got kind of a smooth face, but it's lumpy as well.
What are you talking about?
The way he wins.
I don't know.
It's kind of wet, but in a dry way.
It's kind of like a bird-like snout.
No.
The skin is like, he takes care of his skin.
He takes care of his hair, but he's got a lumpy, weirdo face.
And bulging eyes.
He does kind of have bug eyes, yeah.
At least be thankful that you haven't seen his leaked nudes.
Oh, I think...
I think they saw the editor version.
It's not a pretty sight.
I might have seen his dick.
I saw a censored image.
I laughed.
If you're an internet content creator and you're like taking pictures of yourself like that,
you're basically asking for them to get leaked to the public.
Yeah, it's a time bomb.
I'll say.
It's a matter of a way.
You can do it.
I'm not saying you're not allowed to do that, but just be aware.
Knowing that it's going to happen, even.
Just make that your brand, if that happens.
Fuck it.
Yeah, just have an open door policy.
Just like, yep.
You have your video game review shown at the end.
Now for the cock of the week.
He should have leaned into it and been like, yeah.
I'm cool, progerited.
I'm going to have lots of sex with people now.
I'm going to be the sex game reviewer.
I'm going to be the sex YouTuber now.
I'm going to be the gaming YouTuber.
I'm opening up my secondary channel on porn hub.
So if you guys want to come check that out,
here's the link in the description.
I think he's still really popular and successful.
He's not like a top triple A tier YouTuber,
but he's pretty popular, pretty successful.
So I don't feel that bad making fun of him.
In the long run, it didn't really hurt him that much.
There's a lot of people getting these huge fucking controversies
and traumas and people are like, oh, he's ruined.
His channel is over, but no.
It takes a lot to really ruin your channel.
You'd have to be trying on purpose or something.
Unless you literally go to jail, usually it's okay.
Even then, sometimes these fucking Minecraft predators
will come back and then they'll just still start making videos
and their fan base is so young and stupid
that even if they lose 50% of their viewer base,
that's still enough for them.
There's two names that are coming up in my head
relating to this, Onision and Shane Dawson.
I don't know whether they're the same guy or very similar.
Are they both like sex freaks or is just one of them?
Wait, Shane Dawson isn't like a sex freak, is he?
He's not like a groom or anything.
He's just kind of an asshole, right?
Am I wrong?
I don't know.
He has a bunch of weird drama.
I'm not really sure about all the Shane Dawson drama,
honestly, I kind of miss both of that.
They strike me as like people who've been horrifically canceled
because of things they did absolutely,
and I don't know whether they've come back from that.
You can't cancel someone who's as big as Shane Dawson.
Right, you get to a certain point and it's really hard
to truly cancel someone.
Again, you can make them lose popularity or whatever.
That's fine, but to make them fully go away,
if they're determined to stick around, it's tough.
I've seen at least one popular YouTuber get...
They do look exactly the same.
Completely canceled.
There was Zero, the Smash Bros.
He used to be one of the best Smash players in the world
for Smash 4.
Right.
Oh yeah, yeah.
There's a lot of Smash community people who have gotten...
Oh, what's sorry about Leffen?
Are you talking about Hax and Leffen?
No, just a different guy who's been accused of...
I don't know if it was grooming or some shit, but...
I heard there was a lot of grooming going on
in the Smash community for a while.
It's ironic that there was so much grooming going on
because there was little to no self-grooming.
They never took showers.
Look at these freaks, they're exactly the same guy.
I do have that sort of...
I'm a YouTube pretty boy face bullshit going on.
I have no idea how they're both still around,
but I think it's...
I think younger Shane Dawson looks even more like Onision.
I think you could find even more similar pictures of these too.
Yeah, another thing about these guys,
I'm not really that much of an expert on them.
I think I've seen a couple YouTube documentary type videos on them,
but they've been around for ages.
When you've been on the platform for this long,
people will have these laundry lists of controversies.
They never end, so it's like,
is this latest thing going to be the thing to cancel them?
I don't think so.
At some point, your career just becomes like responding to
people making videos about how you are a monster
and need to be canceled.
But randomly, there's a lot of people who want to watch those
like apology videos.
There's always get lots of views,
so it's like profitable to be constantly apologizing.
There should be a chance where the first video is an apology video
and then every video after that is also an apology video.
I'm so sorry for never making a video up until right now.
There should be a gimmick.
There should be a fucking like priest YouTuber,
like a real priest who does like,
what is the thing, where you go in the box and you say,
oh, it's confessional.
Confession booth series YouTube show.
I'd watch that.
It doesn't look like a good gimmick.
It's hidden camera confessions where he just like records
everybody who comes in and confesses their sins
and then exposes them.
Completely goes against the idea of like the confession box,
like the secretive private thing.
Yeah, but it's for content though.
It's for content.
The church is running out of funding.
I gotta have a baby.
I gotta have a baby so that I can raise that baby to be a sinner
and then I can record my child in the confessional
confessing his sins to the priest and then upload it to YouTube
for content.
You just stream the confessional all day.
Yeah, I was gonna say Twitch.
And then in between people like coming and leaving,
it's like, all right, we're gonna fucking read some doughnos.
It's like America's funniest confessional.
Someone's like confessing in their booth,
like it's like, Father, I'm so sorry.
I hit someone with my car and the priest is like,
can we get some Monka S in chat?
This is not on open guys.
Can we get some Monka S?
Yeah, of course.
I like the idea that it's not like some third party,
put the secret camera there.
Like the priest is the Twitch streamer.
Exactly, exactly.
Like he's like pogging at the camera.
He's like, oh.
It's just like, you know, there's like two sides of the confessional.
There's a little sliding door that opens so you can talk to him.
Father, I'm sorry, I sinned.
He like closes it, turns on like the RGB lights and stuff.
It has like this fucking gamer setup and turns it back off
when it's back up, keeps talking.
He's like, I cheated on my girlfriend with her sister
and he goes like, oh, based.
Oh, like can we get, smash the like shit, like come and chat?
No, no, no.
Like the idea is that it's a secret.
Like he doesn't, he doesn't tell them he's live streaming
and when he pogs, he's like silently pogging,
but they can't see him through the thing.
He's like, pogging to chat.
The camera's on his side.
And then they're hearing all of like this, the confession.
He's like, oh, pog base.
Someone just realizes it's the perfect way to get content.
These people are just coming in and telling all these embarrassing stories.
Like where else are you going to get that?
This is all, it's all been, all these confessions before
they've all just been wasted content.
We're just, we're just leaving money on the table.
We have like thousands of years of wasted content
in terms of confessions.
If you think about it.
As rid of all these ideas are.
The problem is, I think this might be illegal.
If you think about it.
That's clearly never stopped the Catholic Church before.
If you think about it, all of human history
prior to the invention of like the written word
was just wasted content.
It really was, it really was.
Imagine having a life experience and not making content out of it.
What a waste.
I would rather not.
Imagine not having thousands of people watch you through your eyes
and get like advertised to.
Imagine that didn't happen.
I mentioned like, like 5,000 years ago, like around Stonehenge
they're like passing down their songs to a world tradition.
And one guy's just like, what's the point?
We're not even monetizing this.
We're not even getting any doughnuts.
We're not getting any doughnuts, bro.
Oh my God.
Imagine, what a great conversation with a friend.
No, no, no.
Imagine with like a great fucking Isekai show
that would be like a fucking streamer gets sent back in time
to like prehistoric days where there's no fucking content.
All he's doing is like, he's like,
he's like experiencing all these like fucking like historical events.
He's like, I can't fucking vlog any of this.
I would love for there to be like a Dr. Stone
where he's like trying to teach these cavemen.
Alright, so this is when we have to start a fake beef
and you're the heel which means you're the bad guy
and we're going to have to start a whole rap battle
that goes on between you guys
and then we're going to do a boxing match
and he's just like trying to explain the complicated
like setting up a huge beef or whatever.
Yeah, the first thing that comes back
is not like humanity infrastructure
like countries or like society.
It's vlogging.
That's the first thing that we need.
All those Islanders, like they're building the Moai statues
and there's like, I know these seem totally like pointless now
but like hundreds of years from now
they're going to invent this thing called the Internet
and then we can stream these
and then we can, then we can, we'll get doughnuts.
Like, stream like aesthetic statue, not moving.
Yes, yes, like this is for content.
This is for content.
These are, these are too many good ideas.
We need to pay people.
Yeah, Aliza, cut this all out.
We got to keep you close to the chest.
Listeners, if any of you do this, you owe us a cut.
Don't even think about inventing a time machine
and going back and inventing streaming.
If you even think about doing that.
Going back in time and inventing Stonehenge.
It's like, it's like those, those movies.
Livestreaming the building of Stonehenge.
Or like, oh, like the kid goes back in the past
and he's like, whoa, what the fuck?
There's horses and shit.
Where's the video games?
Then he teaches like the princess about,
I don't know, like skateboarding or whatever.
But like a modern version of that would be like
the kid going back in time
and then teaching them about like,
I don't know, Mario Kart.
I would love like a training montage.
Like this is how you make a pog face.
Or like practicing their pogs.
That's kind of all to this point.
Bill and Ted, but instead of a history report,
they go back to the live stream history
because they want to become streamers.
They've dropped out of school to become streamers
and this is how they're going to get the big scoop.
They go back to when Twitch was called JustinTV
and then they start an account.
Honestly.
I remember JustinTV.
Imagine if you could just go back to when the internet was new
and just upload the same videos that you make now.
You'd be huge.
It would be so fucking easy to go viral
like knowing everything you know today.
It would be literally like, you know, the sports almanac
from Back to the Future part two or you can win it every bet.
But you just can predict every YouTube trend
before it happens and you'd be making this worst clickbait garbage.
You would have such terrible tools to use, though.
Imagine having to do your shit in Windows Movie Maker
and just be like, oh, God, my fucking Pentium 4
is struggling to fucking edit this
and I can only upload in 360p.
Google's not good enough. I can't get all my footage.
I can't just rip it. There's no tools to use it yet.
It really was a fucking nightmare back then.
Now you bring your bad memories.
I go back to 1999 and I'm on Usenet forums
and I'm like, hey, bros, listen, years from now,
some person is going to put Sonic the Hedgehog
and this new thing called Pokemon.
They're going to combine them into one guy
and make a comic about it and you're really going to
and you're not going to believe what happens after that.
I love the idea of like a John Teeter
who just goes back to warn people about Sonichu
and nothing important.
No warnings about 9-11 or anything.
No, no, just because no one would listen.
No one would listen to that.
I miss like you have like a time machine,
like you give a kid a time machine and they're like, wow,
I can go at any point in history and they just go back
a couple of years to get YouTube famous.
That's the only thing they do with it.
What if you just did that now?
What if you just went on a fucking forum
and just said you were a time traveler and was like,
oh, this new content creator is going to show up.
It's going to be fucking ridiculous.
Then you just wait two years and then you start that account.
You start a prophecy about yourself?
Yeah, you just start like a prophecy about yourself
so you can like get that jumpstart to your career
and just be like, it was this guy predicted it
and now it's shown up, you know,
and you just spanned ignorance the rest of the time.
I love the idea.
Before you even start your streaming career,
people always ask my advice.
I was like, what should I do on YouTube?
I was like, okay, before you even start YouTube,
you need to spend five to 10 years foreshadowing
your channel before it even exists.
You need to be like dropping in some of your forums,
fakingarchive.org results about...
Organic growth doesn't exist anymore.
Therefore, you got to really fucking play the long game.
Right, you have to game the system
by doing the most crazy outlandish stunts possible
and like fake time travel.
That's the only way to get your attention.
And you also got to hope that nobody else
decides to be that person that is foreshadowed.
Oh yeah, nobody can like...
You have to have some specific thing,
otherwise someone can just swoop in and take all your glory.
That was why the John Theater stuff works,
there's so much hyper-specific bullshit
that never even happened,
but like, oh, it sounded legit.
But it can all happen if you're the one controlling it.
You can make sure everything comes true.
Don't even think about starting YouTube channel
if you don't have 10 years worth of deep lore plans.
Worth of prophecy.
Isn't that basically how you got your start cyber shell?
You've been doing this for quite a while.
Yeah, it was all prophesized back in the day.
That's exactly how I got my start.
I didn't want to be a guy who made videos
that sound like that.
Also, I love the idea...
I love the idea that John Theater,
you know, I dropped some clues here and there.
I love the idea that there's a prophecy,
the prophecy, the chosen one,
and then it's like,
it's like Link Carr in front of a couch.
Like, hey guys,
we were doing this on YouTube.
Oh, it was Doug, it was Doug.
Doug really is the chosen one.
He's like the main character of this timeline.
Yeah.
More like the awesome one.
I saw...
It was a YMS stream clip
about Doug reacting to criticism of the wall.
Oh, right.
I think I saw this.
He has a weirdly good and positive
and wholesome attitude about it.
He has a positive attitude,
but he also just completely
just talks around the actual criticism.
Oh yeah, he'll never engage
in the true substance of the criticisms.
He'll be like,
you know, I'm glad people are talking about it.
It's like, hey,
why did you make it so like confusing
and contradictory and like bad?
And he's like,
I'm just glad people are talking about it.
Right.
He said it in kind of a way like,
oh, I understand those criticisms,
and he sort of lumped that into like
one general thing.
And it's like,
people are always going to dislike
what you do on the internet.
I know that.
I've been on here for a long time.
And everyone's always disliked everything I've done,
so it was just haters.
He clearly doesn't realize
that there's a distinct like confusing aspect
of his video.
He just thinks people don't like it.
And that's just how it is sometimes.
It's just, you know,
no learning capability.
They're always going to have haters.
They're always dissecting the wall
because it was just,
they were haters.
They're just,
oh, of course,
there's going to be some people who don't like it.
It was like a fascinatingly bad piece of media.
I don't think I understand that.
Yeah.
Like it's not a normal level of criticism
that was being levied.
Like it is a uniquely,
it's like a uniquely bad cultural artifact.
And he's,
yeah,
it's a little disappointing that he's just like,
eh,
it just rolls right off me.
Like I said,
hey,
I still think he had a good positive attitude
about the whole thing.
There's guys like just going on right now,
like only plays have made a few like Linkara jokes.
And someone like asked Linkara
what he thought about it.
He's like, I don't like it.
I don't think it's funny.
They make their people are calling me the light bringer
and I don't like it.
But that's,
but that is funny.
I know it is funny.
It is funny when people call you the light bringer.
It is funny.
I mean,
I don't know.
Which not funny to him.
Again,
I don't,
just lean into it.
Yeah.
You literally have to lean into it when that's the case.
Like you should literally just be grateful
that people still care who he is after 10 plus years.
You know what I mean?
This is,
this is what I said.
Oh,
absolutely.
Like this is what I said.
I,
I saw,
I saw Nate the other day.
He just like happened to be in town
and like I hung out with him for a day
and we were talking about the PCP stuff
and the,
and the rad con stuff.
And I told him like, you know,
yeah,
the rad con stuff,
it's a year late and like the PCP has like,
you know,
I wouldn't,
I mean imploded is a strong word,
but you know what I mean?
Like it's all,
the whole landscape has changed
and it's really awkward to now just be like,
well,
here's these videos of a totally different PCP
from a completely bygone era.
And I'm just like,
I think that's funny.
It's just,
just lean into it.
Like,
yeah,
like here it is.
It's changed in just what,
18 months or whatever.
Yeah.
I mean,
it was funny seeing the reactions to the music video
when I would,
you mean the,
not the music,
the rap,
the rad lecture.
Yeah.
Cause like,
that one in particular was like,
that one was heavily steeped in PCP lore.
You know what I mean?
Like that one was,
yeah,
the OVA will be even more.
It's even more.
Oh my God.
It's going to be that times 10.
The OVA,
age,
like,
people are going to be like,
people don't even remember Brad Garlinghouse at this point.
No,
it was,
it was a,
the saga is over.
The Brad Garlinghouse saga was over when Radcon happened.
It had already been solved.
It was only like,
while the,
the,
the campaign was going,
that like,
it was a thing.
The OVA is going to be like,
it's going to be like,
like a,
a time capsule that you bury in the past and open the future.
And they're like,
Oh, remember that?
Except it was just late.
Only,
only you had to put $31,000 into it.
And the time capsule is a hard drive.
All the footage is on.
It was,
it was like,
it's like a gotcha game that you,
yeah,
you put $31,000 in and then a year and a half later,
you get some,
some videos out.
I can't wait to roll for the PCP dojin.
Oh, I got the OVA instead.
This is my favorite gotcha game.
Just got to keep rolling.
You just got to keep putting those PC pennies into the machine.
That's,
that's,
that's why you don't release it at all.
So even now that it's like post-apocalypse arc or whatever,
you can still tell people,
we still have nuggets of the pre-PCP,
the,
the good days.
We're like the brother gotcha game was on,
was on the,
the PCP discord channel.
It's like,
I'm going to fucking roll for,
for another lecture.
Ah,
branches of yig video again today.
Oh yeah.
The,
the bot was only uploading branches of yig videos for some
reason.
I don't know who,
I don't even know who made the bot.
Yeah.
I was trying to look into it.
I have no idea how to edit it.
Yeah.
I think I know.
Appropriate.
But yeah.
It's confused.
So I just,
An ancient long since gun PCP fan.
Hmm.
And I saw it was,
the,
the bot was going,
the bot was going crazy as a,
as,
as Trixie was surreptitiously,
uh,
like re-uploading stuff from the main channel to the side
channel.
And I like,
I see the feed and I'm like,
these are all,
I don't,
I don't need this.
Just get rid of this fucking channel.
We don't need,
we don't need to fucking see this bullshit.
Uh,
and that's what I did.
the,
anyway.
We don't even need a bot.
We didn't even make videos anymore.
I actually,
Yeah.
I have a,
uh,
a couple of,
of gamers at Tavern exclusive Trixie stories.
Uh,
What?
Oh,
what?
What's this?
Like, um,
How,
how is this possible?
Uh,
last,
last year when,
uh,
I came on and,
it looked like at first,
uh,
it was just going to be me and you recording me and you, Ben.
And then,
uh,
we were having a conversation about something
while we were waiting for people.
And,
uh,
I think I mentioned something about,
you were having a bunch of guests on and I was,
uh,
I made the point that
it's going to be pretty difficult for you to keep that streak up that you had at the time.
You had a,
this streak of like,
bunch of guests.
Yeah.
Maybe that was around the time
that the Frog Fractions guy
that lady who was running for sheriff were on
or something like that.
Yeah, but anyways,
uh,
Trixie came in,
during that conversation.
She was on that episode,
uh,
that we did.
Uh,
and,
uh,
she said something kind of funny
that I just wanted to bring up,
uh,
because of new information that,
I have now.
She said,
um,
I was saying you can't just keep having new guests forever.
You're going to run out of guests eventually.
And she says,
well,
I know,
uh,
the guy who books guests for the dick show.
And,
uh,
so,
you know,
he's pretty good at booking guests.
We can,
we can,
that's a big money connection.
That's what we call a big money connection.
So,
at the time,
I didn't know who she was talking about.
Uh,
so I would just like,
I would just like,
okay,
I guess,
but,
you know,
thinking back on that now
with everything that I know now,
I'm pretty sure she,
she met Riley.
Yeah,
she,
that's,
that's pretty,
I think that's retroactively pretty funny now.
I think,
I think so.
Uh,
hmm,
uh,
I don't like her at all.
I think she's bad.
I think,
I think people should stop supporting her on Patreon.com.
Uh,
that's what my opinion.
Before,
uh,
it was actually before this episode that we recorded,
but I,
um,
this is kind of embarrassing,
I guess,
but I actually paid for a couple of Trixie Rants
and she never,
you know,
back when she was-
No!
Digi Bro,
she never did them.
You're kidding.
You paid for a couple?
Yeah,
I paid,
I think,
for two.
Neither of them happened.
No Rants.
That face went,
no Rants.
Brutal,
I thought at least for sure,
I just sat down and like,
cranked out all the rest of them at once or something,
but you know,
it is what it is.
I thought that happened as well.
I thought I remembered that happening,
yeah,
but,
hmm,
I heard,
I'll get it right after the,
the Brony lecture goes up,
don't worry.
Yeah, of course.
She's got to release that Brony lecture.
It's the way to kickstart the Branches of Yig Channel.
It's the only way.
She's getting double digit views.
She needs,
she needs a shot in the arm.
It needs,
wait,
I forgot,
she's an anti-vaxxer,
so that's a bad metaphor.
So,
I can't say that,
never mind,
never mind.
It's okay.
I have no hard feelings over it,
because I don't,
I honestly don't really care,
but I have the right to,
to be angry.
I'm just going,
choosing not to exercise that right.
Hmm.
That's
big of you.
Fringe.
Yeah.
You know,
you know me,
you know I would never
pass up an opportunity
to get mad about something
on Twitter.com.
I can't think of any
reason.
I mean,
getting mad,
that's content.
That's good content.
That's good content, baby.
That's a good point.
Now, that's what I call calm.
I'm feeling an emotion.
Turn on the camera.
Oh, my God,
I'm having a feeling.
It must record.
It must,
must monetize.
I made
a content
that's good content.
That's good content, baby.
That's a good point.
Now, that's what I call calm.
Oh, I'm feeling an emotion.
Turn on the camera.
I made a comment.
I made a YouTube comment.
If you can believe it.
I made it.
I made a comment on.
This sounds bad already.
Yeah.
Well,
it's kind of funny.
I think,
I think this is W.
I think I'm going to call this W.
I made a comment on,
it's some other Chris Chan
YouTuber.
This guy's name is Dylan Thomas
and he's one of these weirdos who just
for years,
he just uploads like weekly, like
Chris Chan said something stupid
on Twitter.
Chris Chan thinks cartoons are real.
It's like this.
This is the level that he's at.
And he put out a video.
Like,
should we respect Chris's pronouns?
Short answer,
his answer is no.
And he gives all the usual,
like,
non-reasons that don't make any sense
for why he shouldn't.
So I just made one comment on the video.
That's like,
you know,
pretty pathetic.
You know,
not a lot of intellectual rigor on display.
Embarrassing.
You know,
you're irrational.
And I'm looking today and there's a whole,
like,
40 reply thread.
That's a win.
40 replies.
They're all like,
oh,
you're stupid.
You're thinking too hard about it.
You don't,
no,
you're stupid.
No,
you're a stupid one.
Seeing the amount of people to actually
unironically take that stance.
It's really fucking bizarre to me because
you can literally make the exact same argument.
Well,
you know,
I don't like using the n-word,
but I don't respect this black person.
Therefore,
I guess I should be allowed to use it, right?
I guess they should be racist.
Oh,
this imperative to be racist.
This black guy did a crime and you still,
you still don't think we should call him the n-word?
Not wanting to get called the n-word.
Like, bruh,
why are you defending his crime?
It is like the exact same,
like,
line of thought and there's no substantial difference
between the two in my opinion.
Like,
if you think one,
you necessarily should think the other.
You literally must think the other.
It's,
it's,
I mean,
it's embarrassing and this is,
this is a,
this is,
I mean,
this is the sad truth of,
like,
the,
the Chris,
the Chris-Chan community,
if you want to call it that,
like, the Chris-Chan fandom.
Like,
the devoted Chris-Chan fandom are all,
they're all idiots.
They're all Kiwi farmers.
They're all,
like,
weirdos
who are
embarrassing.
It's the,
the sad truth is that,
like, this is the audience that,
like,
I mean,
that's not the,
like,
the main audience that's like,
watch,
for instance,
my lecture.
Like,
I'm sure most people that watch the lecture are not,
like this,
but like,
some people were giving you the debt,
the debt,
releasing the lecture,
and they're like,
oh,
Ben was,
you know,
trying to capitalize on this.
But I mean,
I feel like there's a difference.
There's a big difference between releasing a lecture,
which was recorded
over a year prior,
versus making,
like,
daily.
I was going to say,
I was going to say weekly,
but literally,
lately,
they're exploding,
I see them all over the place,
but it's,
it's crazy to me that a few people,
like,
G.B.
and Dylan Thomas,
and,
like,
one or,
and a base shaman,
and like,
a few others,
their channels are just,
like,
how much is there to even talk about?
Like,
like,
Chris says the same,
insane fucking merge shit
on Twitter all the time.
How many times can you just like,
how wrong it is,
and how the,
there's no such thing as,
cartoons.
Guys,
you might have heard of this thing
called the Dimensional Merge.
Let me tell you why it's not real.
Let me break down
where the Dimensional Merge is not real,
with a 48 point list.
I can prove,
I can prove it,
actually,
and here's why.
Debunking the Dimensional Merge
with facts and logic.
It's like,
as I heard some shit
about the Dimensions Merging,
and I'm scared,
and I need someone to tell me,
it's all going to be okay.
Chris says that if I don't respect my OCs,
they're going to fucking kill me
when the merge happens.
There's a lot of content
that can be derived from Twitter feed.
Remember,
when Trump still had his Twitter,
and the mainstream media was just like
24-7 broadcasting all his tweets?
Yeah.
And there will always be like,
look how ridiculous this tweet is.
It's horrible.
Let's spend an entire segment
explaining why that is.
The amount of free advertising
that Trump got was unfathomable.
It's truly insane,
both before and after getting elected.
They were nonstop covering him.
It was honestly,
you have to appreciate that approach
to getting elected,
which is that have no qualifications.
Just get on the news
and have the news talk about you
all the time.
Yeah.
Yeah, it worked.
It worked.
What can you say about it?
It worked like a fucking dream, yeah.
Can't wait for the next time it works.
I'll never forget my favorite,
my favorite Trump tweet.
Coca-Cola company.
Not very happy with me.
That's okay.
I'll still drink that garbage.
Poetry.
And he made some of that.
Regardless of what you think about him.
Some funny tweets.
He was an eloquent Twitter user.
He was a powerful poster.
He made a lot of funny tweets.
He really did.
A lot of the things he would do
over and over again
are just like,
popular things people do now.
Like just saying an emotion
in capital letters at the end.
Sad.
Yeah.
Dude, his way of speaking straight up.
Well, first of all,
I guess like half the site,
all the conservatives like unironically
wanted to emulate it.
And then it's also funny as fuck.
So a lot of people just ironically
are doing shit like that.
And then he had to change the way
people spoke on Twitter.
It's very effective to just like,
just state very bluntly
what you're trying to say
and then say how you're supposed to
feel about it and then just repeat it.
Like that was a,
I watched a,
I think I watched a video
that was like about,
it was like a,
the channel was about like teaching
charisma or something.
It was about like teaching,
like how to be more persuasive
or charismatic person.
And they took like a video
about Trump and it's like,
how does Donald Trump speak
in a way that is so compelling to people?
And like one of his major tricks
is just that he repeats himself
over and over and over again.
And he'll just say the same thing twice in a row.
True.
So you don't forget it.
Yeah.
There's a funny scene in The Simpsons
where Marge is like,
this town is a part of us all,
a part of us all,
a part of us all.
Sorry to repeat myself,
I don't know if you remember.
Yeah.
And that actually works.
And Donald Trump literally got elected
on that advice.
So it works.
Donald Trump watched The Simpsons.
He got the idea of him running for president
from that Simpsons episode.
The Simpsons.
Yeah.
People always say The Simpsons predicted it.
Not enough people are giving Simpsons shit
for causing it.
They're the ones who cause all of this
in the first place.
Like he would,
he would make up little nicknames
for people like he would call Hillary.
He would call her,
like Lion Hillary, right?
I think that he called her like corrupt Hillary
or something.
Like crooked Hillary, wasn't she?
Crooked Hillary.
That was Lion Ted or some shit.
Right.
He gave everyone a little nickname
and that's funny because it's probably
the only reason he could keep track of them.
But it's like, you know,
that's people love that shit.
And it didn't even have to be like that.
Like crooked Hillary.
It didn't have to be clever or witty at all.
It's not exactly a joke,
but he just keeps saying it.
He just keeps saying,
yeah, crooked Hillary,
yeah, crooked,
and then he's thinking,
you're mine.
Oh yeah, crooked Hillary.
And then the media,
the news cry-ons are repeating that,
like crooked Hillary on CNN.
Yeah.
And quotation marks, you know what I mean?
Just say it enough.
Right.
That's why my next campaign
is just going to be walking around.
I'm just going to be walking around
and publicly saying,
I'm the president.
I am the president.
I'm just going to start walking around
and telling people that.
And eventually, I will be the president.
And then literally,
and then whatever people talk about,
they'd be like,
Cybershell, like,
who's that?
Like, oh, you know,
that guy who always says he's the president.
I guess he's the president.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, the president.
He just seems so presidential.
And then everyone's like,
oh, you mean the president guy?
Sounds like something off of it.
Well, the real world is something awful.
It just works.
Psychology is so simple.
It's the easiest thing in the world.
Nothing to it.
Not much to it, yeah.
Yeah.
I guess Trump is going to go down
as the best, worst president in history.
He will always be missed.
Well, from this point on,
there will be two histories.
And one of them,
people are going to say he's great.
And the other one,
people are going to say he's bad.
And then luckily in the future,
it'll continue to fracture out.
We need to come together as a nation
and reach across the aisle
and agree that Trump was a legendary Twitter poster.
That's the only way.
That's true.
It's the one thing that binds us all together.
I honestly feel like he probably was more upset
about losing his Twitter account
than like almost anything else,
than maybe even losing the presidency.
I would assume that Twitter account
gave him more power than the office of the president.
I don't understand.
I don't understand why it was like only then
did they take his Twitter
only when he lost the election.
They were like, well, now we have to take it away.
It was hilarious, the timing.
Like he lost it.
And then it was, I guess it was,
it was right after the whole capital rate riot bullshit.
So it was like, oh, we have to take it away.
Was that why?
Was it like,
That was the reason I'm pretty sure they're like,
he was inciting it by posting that video
where he was like standby or whatever.
I don't know.
Yeah.
We love you.
You're very special.
He's talking to them like fucking Barney.
It's funny.
It's so funny.
A lot of the platforms like Twitter,
they ban people based on like PR stuff,
whatever makes them look best at that moment.
Right.
That was absolutely PR move on Twitter's part.
There was no like,
any like reasoning they could have had,
they could have done it way earlier,
but they would have gotten so much shit from people
when he was president.
I mean, I would kind of respect the ballziness
to just be like,
we're just going to ban the standing president
in the middle of his term,
just because we don't like his politics.
We just don't want him on our platform.
Twitter literally wanted him there objectively
because of the traffic he brought to the site.
Yeah.
I wonder if they didn't want to like be,
I don't know,
accused of like forcing,
like silencing him.
I know it's not actually censorship.
People are already going to take that stance of like,
oh, you ban all conservatives.
Like you're censoring him
and therefore people won't vote for him.
You're basically like rigging the election.
It could have backfired
if they banned them at a bad time.
Like you're right about that.
Like people would have gotten upset.
I mean, it did back.
That's exactly what people said.
I know.
So it's weird.
I just wonder why they didn't do anything
up until that point.
You're right, Ben.
They literally could have just banned them
at like in 2018.
They could have done it way ages ago,
but you know,
like I said, his posts were too fucking funny.
They really were like, you know,
the presidency ones in particular,
there's a lot of really funny ones.
If we've got these fucking billionaire technocrats
running these big tech conglomerations
that literally own us all
and manipulate our data
and have us all in their pocket,
I would at least like them.
I would at least like my corporate masters
to show a little bit of moral consistency,
a little bit of backbone.
Is it too much to ask?
That is way too much to ask.
Yes, it's far too much to ask.
No, no, I see.
Well, I apologize.
I don't know.
Not until we do it.
I was kind of bummed out when he got banned
because I really liked reading his tweets.
They were, you know,
I always like when you read someone's tweets
and you can easily like read it in their voice.
You know what I mean?
Like a tweet that sounds like
there's a specific person talking
and his tweets always like sounded like,
you can easily imagine him saying it.
Hmm.
He was a great comedy.
He didn't, he didn't say,
say what you say what you will about the man.
But he didn't post like a boomer.
He just posted on a very like straight forward,
like wet normal.
Well, honestly, he just said what he wanted to say.
The more I think about it, the more sad I am.
We never got to see the post presidency
Trump Twitter meltdown and just the subsequent
daily Biden is a piece of shit.
Yeah, that would have been great.
I agree.
I'm not sure banning him did any good
for anyone really.
I mean, I don't think.
Yeah, I don't think.
I don't think you can really say that it stopped much harm.
I mean, come on, anyone.
No, I don't think that is.
You could have made that choice.
They decided to do it ages ago,
but they basically waited until yeah,
like you said, like right at the very end.
You know what?
It's just robbing us of content.
It's just it's just wasted content.
That's the name of this episode is wasted content.
It's all about bemoaning all the things
we'll never get to consume in his private life
that were wasted content that we don't get to see.
They weren't monetized.
Wasted content and wasted comedy.
Exactly.
I think he is.
Money on the table.
Is he banned on YouTube?
Because when he got banned on Twitter,
it was like a big, it wasn't just Twitter.
He got banned off a shitload of social media apps.
I think everybody banned him.
Yeah.
Because I'm thinking that like he like.
That's a shame.
It really is a shame.
Like I would love to watch the Donald Trump YouTube show.
That would be fucking funny.
I want to see the Donald Trump like
Twitch stream fortnight.
Yeah.
I wanted to see Donald Trump let's play.
Many of politicians have Twitch streams now,
like for realsies.
So it's not even all the possibilities.
Didn't AOC play Among Us?
Among Us.
Yeah.
With Ilan Omar.
So funny.
Yeah.
It was pretty.
I guess maybe it never materialized,
but I was hearing when the election happened,
I was hearing people talking about Trump was going
to start like Trump TV and like start a whole
like independent like media outlet.
I thought, well, originally back in 2016,
I thought Trump TV was the game plan.
Like I didn't even think he really was trying to be president.
That hard.
I thought it was just get an absurd amount of press for free
and then, you know, pivot into being a TV star.
But this is what I read.
It was like it was the plan at first,
but then he became president.
He's like, I guess we'll just roll with this now.
I guess we'll just be president.
Like, okay.
Then I can get back to my real job of being a TV star.
Making Trump TV.
Yeah.
I guess we'll just be president of the United States.
I heard about Trump TV,
but I haven't heard anything about it since.
I first heard about it.
Yeah.
I feel like I haven't.
I'm surprised he's been.
I don't want to say he's been like quiet since leaving office,
but like there's been a few like press statements by him or whatever,
which are hilarious because they really like tweets.
Press statements.
And I keep seeing people say that someone basically just made
like a new Twitter,
like specifically just so that he could be on.
I don't know what that is.
I don't think it's Parler.
Doesn't he just have a website?
He just has a website where he like makes blog posts about how
he just makes what are essentially tweets.
I think he has like it's an email list,
which is like probably the same.
He's going to old school.
Right.
I think I think that's the current grift is just have an email list with
literally like 50 million emails on it and send out like weekly begging
for money.
Because that's nobody outside.
That really takes me back.
Your fucking circle is going to see it.
Those mailing lists take me back to like 2002 or 2003.
That was like the first way to keep in touch with people on the web
was like getting in that web ring or whatever.
That's still a very effective method of marketing.
Yeah.
People still value that.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Marketers are right.
I always get people on your email list.
Yeah.
I feel like it went out of fashion for a while,
but then like two years ago or so,
there was a kick of people being like,
you know what,
you know,
social media is bad and it's owned by big Corpo and like it's more,
it's kind of more effective.
Yeah.
Just an old school.
Join my mailing list.
Join my mailing list because my Twitter could get banned
for any reason at any time, right?
Well,
I love that part of being on the modern web is,
which is that, you know,
oh, I have a YouTube channel,
which is I make money.
I could just get banned at any time for any reason
that I would have no recourse.
It could just get hacked by some,
the only thing you can do,
for instance,
Brad Garley knows.
Imagine if that happened.
How embarrassed.
So that's why it's good to diversify,
have a Twitter,
even if you don't like Twitter,
it's not bad to have one just,
you know,
as like a backup type situation.
You got to diversify across different sites nowadays.
Yeah.
Just like investing in crypto or stocks,
diversify your portfolio.
Yeah.
If you're a coward,
you just put everything into one stock
and then wait for it to pump
and then take it off.
I have a shameful,
I have a shameful confession to make.
You being a crypto boy again.
I bought some,
I bought some Bitcoin.
Why would you buy it now?
It's going up.
I don't have anything bad.
We're never going to get
another cheap video card again.
It was going up.
That's like a thing of the past.
People in like 60 years
are going to be laughing like,
oh my, people used to be able
to buy video cards?
What?
You have not looked.
No, it has,
it fell in a big way.
No, no, no.
It's been going up for like a month
or almost a month.
I've had like a bit of Ethereum
and a bit of Bitcoin for a while
and it was really low for a while.
And now it has been going up
but it's really slowed down.
I've just sold mine.
I feel like it's going to go back down again.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe.
If you notice it's going up,
you've already missed the window.
That's not,
that's not true.
That's not true.
I mean,
maybe next week when Ben's
complaining about crypto prices
dropping and getting mad again,
maybe I'm just saying people
earlier in the year were predicting
like Bitcoin hitting 100K.
Everybody says that has a vested
interest in Bitcoin hitting.
And that's what I thought too.
But then I thought,
then I thought like it fell off a cliff
after the big pump.
And I was like,
okay, it's down.
But it's when you buy,
if you actually want to get back in on this.
But it started steadily.
It started steadily.
It's like almost halfway back up
to where it was.
And I'm like,
I feel like there's a real possibility
that it goes even higher
than it did the first time.
And I'm like, well,
if it does that,
it would be ashamed if I miss out.
So I fucking was like,
okay, fuck it.
I'll gamble it.
I'll just buy a little bit of Bitcoin.
Just in case.
I don't know.
I don't think it's that stupid.
I feel like I'm watching it every day.
If you buy when it's like 50%.
Cool.
It's going up.
But I want to not make the mistake
I made before
and not sell at the peak.
I've sold and I've made a profit.
And I'm hesitant to like jump back in
because it does look like
the curve upwards is like flattening out
right now.
Like it's slowing down a lot more
than it was.
But I don't know.
By the time you,
the viewer are listening to this,
it's definitely too late for you.
Don't even fucking think about buying anything.
Yeah, that's true.
Look at, no, no.
Look, I mean,
look how it's,
we got a fucking show.
Look at this curve.
Guys, if you want to get rich,
just buy some Ripple XRP.
That's my advice.
Let's just all invest in Ripple.
This curve,
this pattern looks to me
and obviously I don't know,
but it looks to me there
like it is like starting a bullish trend.
Right.
And that line is like a month long.
It's been,
it's been,
I don't know.
Well, how much Bitcoin do you have?
I have like,
it's not,
not as much as I had before.
I just,
I don't want to say,
I don't want to give numbers,
but I have,
I mean a fraction of a Bitcoin,
like a small fraction of a Bitcoin.
Cause like,
let's say it goes all the way back up
to like 56 or 47, right?
That's like a 20% increase.
If you bought like $500
in Bitcoin,
a 20% increase is only like a hundred more dollars.
It's not going to be significant.
So I'll make a hundred dollars.
Yeah.
That's what I'm hoping to make a hundred dollars.
I guess.
What are you saying?
You're,
I don't understand.
You're like,
but Ben,
sure if it goes up,
you'll make money.
But if it goes down,
you'll lose money.
I know.
I'm saying the time to buy
was when it was like
way lower.
So you could have bought
$500 then.
This is so foolish.
You could have already opened up
so much more money.
We will see.
Yes.
Obviously.
Ben has bought his.
So we'll see what he wins.
Obviously it would have been better.
Obviously it would have been better to buy
when it was even lower.
But if it goes up from here,
it's still good to buy now.
Sure.
My bigger complaint
is that we've been down this road
like four times
and explained this to you four times
and you keep buying at the same time
instead of revising your strategy.
I don't think that's true.
I don't really feel like that's true,
actually.
I do promise that I won't make it
a big fucking thing.
This won't be the crypto cast again.
I can't believe that.
Okay.
Well.
I'm afraid we can't trust your assurances,
Ben.
Here's the thing.
If Ben loses money,
if Ben loses money,
it'll be like half a crypto cast.
If Ben gains a lot of money,
we're not going to hear the end of it.
He's going to rub it in my face.
He's going to rub it in our faces.
Everyone in chat.
No, that's a good point.
YouTube comments.
Be praying and emojis
for Ben to be losing money.
I think if I make a huge profits on crypto,
I think I'll be embarrassed
and I won't want to talk about it.
Oh, well, if it isn't the capitalist Ben St,
who loves cryptocurrency
and all sorts of other currencies.
See, this is why.
I'm feeling the shame.
I'm going to use all those profits
to buy carbon credits
to offset all the damage
you're doing to the environment.
Ben St.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, for our socialists,
you should enjoy capital.
You sure do enjoy having money, you hypocrite.
Yet you choose to participate
in this society of ours.
Why aren't you living in a commune
waiting for the second coming of Christ?
Like a good fucking commie.
God, I wish.
Jesus, love him.
Now, there was some...
the crucifixion of Christ?
Now, there was some fucking content.
They really milked the shit out of that one.
They're still talking about it.
That was...
I mean, that was not wasted content.
That one was...
Yeah, that one was milked.
That one was heavily monetized.
They started a Twitch stream
that you might have heard of.
It's called the Roman Catholic Church.
It's still good.
They have so many subs.
They get doughnose every fucking Sunday.
I would love to see a video that says...
They only stream once a week
and somehow they still make a fuck ton of money.
It's great.
I would love to see an apology video
from Judas Iscariot.
He's just sitting there like,
guys, I feel so shitty
about what I did to Jesus.
My apology.
Judas Iscariot makes an apology video.
It's like, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I gave Jesus to the Romans.
It's like, oh, he monetized the video.
He left ads on the video.
Judas Iscariot.
Ratted him out
to fucking Twitch staff
and then he got fucking banned for three days.
But then he came back
and was even bigger than before.
He made partner.
He made partner as a result.
You know, I know it was a joke,
but actual churches do have Twitch channels
and they do stream their services.
I've seen it before.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Do they get doughnose from Twitch chat?
I think they do.
They don't know as the substitute
for the passing the thing around.
How fucking great would it be
if the priest did get up
on the pulpit or whatever
and just be like,
all right, I've got to read up my doughnose
for the stream before we move on
with the actual mask.
He gives live shout-outs.
Interrupting the server
and just go, oh, Pog.
Omega Pog.
Check out that doughnose.
That's basically the reality we live in right now.
Subscribe at tier three.
You get an annulment.
It's like when you put a 20
into the collection plate,
it's like a soundboard
starts like air horn,
like...
lights light up behind him
on the pulpit or whatever.
Confetti is released.
Like the same confetti for weddings.
Church needs to start a vtuber of Jesus.
They've got to get their new image up there.
Dude, I would love to see a hot tub stream,
but it's all holy water
and they're just like,
you pay money to get your name written
on one of those little crackers.
A hot tub stream,
but it's like baptisms.
Yeah, baptizing people and shit.
There was a church near my house
where they had a big tank.
They had a big water tank,
and I guess the priest would bless the tank.
And they had a dispenser.
You could go up
and you could rinse your hands
on this little spout
out of this little plastic tank.
You could just dispense some holy water
into your hands, I guess,
if you wanted some.
The tank was there.
People have containers of holy water
they use for stuff around their house.
That was like a refill.
Yeah, I had...
What do you do with it?
I'm not sure.
What does he do to it
to make it holy water?
That's what I don't know.
Does he piss in it?
Do you spit in it?
I thought it was so cool.
I had a fancy,
like an old glass perfume bottle,
and I went and I filled it up with it.
I was like, oh my God,
I have this fancy red,
this like red stained glass bottle.
It's full of sacred water.
It's so fucking holy.
It's so ready to fight a vampire.
Exactly.
Yeah, exactly.
You use it on vampires and zombies.
That's what Castlevania taught me.
That's why they put it out.
It's like for a home,
it's for a defense.
It's important to have a lot of compartments in your house
with holy water and whips and crosses.
When the kids come around for trick or treat,
you just splash it in their faces,
and they throw it on demons.
The best way is to throw it like a grenade,
and then when it lands,
it explodes with a little fire effect.
Yep.
I just throw the bottle,
and it just clunks someone in the head
and gives them a concussion.
It strangely goes at a 45-degree angle,
no matter how you throw it.
It needs to shatter.
Yeah.
Now I'm second guessing
the sale of Bitcoin.
You can go all in,
and if you lose money,
I did make a profit.
Think of it this way.
If you don't own Bitcoin,
and then it goes up, you lose.
No, you don't.
Yes, you do.
I don't know.
Ben is right. Every single day of your life,
you are losing at casinos
and all sorts of games that you're choosing
not to take in.
Think of how much money you're losing
by not going to Vegas right now
and betting on your money.
Think of all the free V-Bucks I'm losing
by not buying and getting my bonus
on my purchases.
You're actively losing money every second.
That's how corporations
plan their profit margins.
Exactly.
Whenever it goes down,
that's not money they're losing.
That's money that they're not making.
If they're still making money,
but not...
Even if they're still making the same amount
of money as before,
that's terrible.
We should have been making even more than we used to make.
There's nothing wrong with
expanding exponential growth forever.
No, of course not.
Man, it would be really unfortunate
if the dominant business model
of the entire planet was growth
on a finite system like the planet Earth.
Man, that'd be pretty fucking shitty, guys.
I don't understand.
I think it'll all be worth it
as long as some specific shareholders
make a lot of profit.
We can always get another Earth.
Those guys can just go to Mars.
Right.
So what's the big deal?
There isn't a single motion right now
who owns an Amazon Prime subscription.
It's a completely untapped market.
You just have to become one of those guys.
If the existential Earth might fail on Earth,
but on Mars, it's going to be different.
Mars is half the size,
so the growth will be twice as fast.
A civilization of people who all watch
Rick and Morty. It would be so advanced.
There'd be no stopping them.
Yeah, that's true.
Is that what Mars is?
Yes, it's just going to be Elon Musk
and the rest of his Rick and Morty pals.
Did you see Elon Musk
and Grimes on Twitter?
These fucking freaks.
They're being all like,
Elon,
make me a cyborg body, please.
Yeah, they're cringe on Twitter,
which is truly the highest crime possible.
Why on Earth
are you paying attention?
Yeah, that was my question.
I saw someone else retweet a screenshot of it,
so I'm not following them,
but I saw it rebask.
Oh man, it just reminds me
of dislike these people a lot.
I so much hate things of many people.
I hate them. I so much hate them.
That's what I do.
I wake up and I look at a list of every
single famous person.
I hate that person.
That's how you wake up in the morning.
That guy's just a problem.
Ben, you should wake up in the morning
and think of all the things you love.
Done.
Now you've got to think of more.
You've got to start loving more things
than zero things.
Just think about how much money
you're going to make off of Bitcoin
and it's definitely not going to bite you in the ass
because it can only go up.
It will only eventually go up as long as you don't sell.
It literally can only go up.
You don't lose money until you've
sold it at a loss.
So if you never sell.
That was that thing we came up with.
If we do
the opposite,
then at least one of us will make money.
Ben keeps his Bitcoin
and I wait for it to crash before I put back in
if at all.
Then at least one of us
will be with the winner.
This is not a financial advice podcast,
but if you follow one of them,
you're guaranteed to make money
because we're covering possible outcomes.
Not having Bitcoin and having it.
If it bit you in the ass,
then it would be Bitcoin.
The name would be apps.
Aren't those the two genders?
Not having Bitcoin and having Bitcoin?
Sounds about right.
I think so. I've read that somewhere.
I still have Dogecoin though.
If everything goes way up,
I'll still have that Dogecoin.
Literally, way before I knew this Doge should happen,
like a year and a half or maybe two years ago,
I didn't do it. I fucking hate myself so much.
I almost bought a shitload of Dogecoin
just because I was like, that dog
is going to die pretty soon
and it's probably going to spike in value.
So I was just being very opportunistic about it.
Dogecoin is
well, it's almost back up to
30 cents.
It's doubled in the last...
It's interesting. You watch Ethereum,
Dogecoin and Bitcoin and their graphs
are almost all the way back then.
It's just people's faith.
It's not that it's not the specific ones,
but it's also...
It's almost like these coins are just
fucking investments and have no value
outside of people hyping them up.
I don't think I can agree with that.
Are you seriously discounting
the myriad of uses that you can have
for Bitcoins like buying drugs
online, buying
pornography online.
Those are the only two, but
those exist.
You're right.
AMC is going to start accepting Bitcoin
because they're a meme stock and they're leaning into it.
Unironic, that is true.
What could go wrong with a currency that can
rapidly devalue itself to half
in one day? There's no possible
way that could bite them in the ass.
What if you could leave your car idling
and it would generate
arcade tokens that you could
trade for heroin and that's what Bitcoin is?
It already does.
You can just hook up like a bag
to your car exhaust and then huff the fumes
and then get high off that and you can trade that for drugs.
Just put your mouth over
the environment.
Just deep-throat that...
That's a solution.
Just an illusion, yeah.
That's a solution to climate change.
Just put bags over your car exhaust
so it doesn't go into the atmosphere and sell it for drugs.
Just put a big garbage bag over the back
of your car and then when you're done
just bury the bag in your backyard
and then there's no problem.
Just put the carbon back in the ground
where we got it from.
Right, just burying it, grow a carbon tree.
A lot of good ideas
in this episode.
Dude, we're like solving all the world's problems.
Million-dollar ideas here.
They're all patented by the way.
We will sue the fuck out of you if anyone's
asking for any of these things.
Exactly.
If you could hook up a car engine...
You only pay me a bitcoin, by the way.
You know how
bitcoins always like, oh, we gotta get computers
or whatever to do it.
What if you could hook up mining bitcoin
to a car exhaust and then people
would drive to make bitcoin
and then that would be like so much bitcoin.
Sheet.
Infinite funds.
Never mind the greenhouse gases accelerating.
Someone gets a toshi on the line.
We gotta fucking figure this out.
A boat.
What if you build a sailboat and you just
attached a big fan to it
that would blow air into the sail
and then you would just push the boat
in a perpetual
motion machine?
What if you covered yourself in oil
and then you went out when it was raining
and then you started flying because oil is lighter than water?
I'm not sure if that would work.
You should live stream that.
You should live stream it.
Live stream perpetual motion machine
test number one.
Yes, please.
Do we think it's time to start listening
to voicemails?
An hour and a half, give or take.
Well, I've got one thing to talk about.
We haven't even talked about
anything.
Zero topics of discussion.
We've literally just been like, um,
for like an hour and a half.
Usually, by this point, I would have been like,
I would have been like, yeah.
Let's start the fucking show, guys.
Let's get down to business.
At least I even cut out everything that happened
before this point.
Let's cut the crap and get down to brass tax.
We've got business to attend to.
There was one thing I wanted to get on record.
Uh,
because I don't think people are aware of this,
but, uh,
I've been a fan of Cyber Shell
since around 2008 or so,
I think.
Wait, what? Before the PCP was even a
twinkle in anybody's eye.
Yeah, me and gamers have been
our old school LP heads
from when that was a brand new
and creative art form
just bursting onto the scene
and everybody was so excited about it
that they could have predicted how horrible it would become
and how awful modern twitch culture
will be. And it's definitely not my fault.
I didn't need to contribute to this at all.
Yeah, don't try and play me.
That's definitely true.
Uh, but I never,
I never thought I'd eventually
be talking to the great Sonic lore master himself.
This kind of just
happened, uh,
by mere happenstance
because I wasn't, uh, I didn't even know
what the PCP was until 2018
when I was, uh,
invited on by, uh,
I specifically remember that
because, you know, the PCP
used to be a very non-guest
type podcast, you know what I mean?
I was very surprised when I got asked to be on
because it was like, I was not the first guest ever
obviously, but like, I was like the first
guest in a long, like there was a,
it became guest time for quite a while after that
so I was like, what the fuck?
I had, I had literally never,
I had literally never even heard of
Cybershell. How dare you.
Not be a Sonic fan. Until someone
said, Ben,
Cybershell, reference your, your lecture
in a video and I looked
at my, my ad sense and like
I had made like more ad revenue
than usual in the last couple days.
You could actually see the runoff effect
of people going to that video from
my tale to get strolled video. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. That was, uh, really
surprising to me when I saw, uh,
that, uh, you were on
a PCP Cybershell and I heard somebody
mentioned that you, you were, uh,
a PCP fan.
So that, uh, surprised me even more.
I was like, whoa. I was, I didn't
believe, I still don't believe it.
I mean, I remember seeing, I remember
seeing Cybershell's like name
and, and, uh, avatar
like in comments of early PCP
or at least some, like
some amount of PCP episodes.
You can go back and find out. I had no idea you were a big
YouTuber. Well, I wasn't a big YouTuber
at the time, especially back then. It's like, if you
find my like 2016 comments, I was like,
um, well, I had my one
little let's play I did for something
awful back in the day and I had like, I don't know,
under 10K subs. I can't
remember the exact amount, but it was like some amount
of subs. And then it was just like
in 2017, all these people
were making videos and I was like, I guess I can
make a video. Making a video doesn't seem like it'd be that hard
to do, right? Because, um,
I just had this weird thing where I promised
I was going to do a Sonic 2 bonus video
back in 2008 and then I never did it.
So I had eight years worth
of just cheeky comments of people going, oh,
when's the Sonic 2 bonus video? So I
took all of those comments. I made a little
montage and I was like, fine, I'll make
the little video you guys wanted. Are you happy now?
And then I just made a couple more videos
and I don't know, you know, we make a couple videos
they do well. So you want to keep making
more ones, I guess. I don't know.
Yeah, I remember that. You do a little content.
You do a little content.
Yeah. Cyber show at one point
and maybe hard to believe this now was
an underdog
video maker on YouTube.
And I was following him since back
in those days.
But it's, um, it's just weird
how I never knew about
the PCP and now I'm,
you know, I'm on it and I'm a fan of it
and it just so happens that Cyber show
we both ended up on
the same episode because I had the same thing where I recognize
gamers taverns avatar
from like comments from like ages
and ages and ages ago. So I just, I don't know.
You just see people in the comments enough, you sort of like
start to just, you know, remember them or whatever.
I always just, for some reason
is his avatar of just gamers tavern
where it's like a shade of brown and then like
like a slightly different shade of brown
for some reason that always just stuck in my mind.
But that means I did
a pretty good job designing that logo
for not being an artist. It's minimalistic
but it works. It's
enough.
It's enough. At least it's not a fucking
anime avatar. Yeah.
Am I right? Not one of these sick
fucks. Anime people.
Those are pretty
terrible. Something else
that surprised me is to find out that
Shuga Conroy
is a big fan of yours
Cyber show.
Yeah. There are a few
like, you know,
bigger people who are like still doing
Let's Plays or whatever, you know, like Shuga Conroy
which is crazy to me that there are still
people out there making money and like continuing
to keep the Let's Play tradition alive.
And I mean, most of Let's Plays tradition
sort of exists now on like Twitch, you know what I mean?
And like live streaming which is fine
and is like good but it's sort of a separate thing,
you know, from like the
pre-recorded Let's Play days of old
Yeah, Shuga Conroy
was one of the original YouTube Let's
Players I think back from
2006 or something and I
started watching him on and off since around
that time. And
he's one of the pre-game grumps
appears and
it's pretty surprised that he knew
of you and is a fan of yours.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, I actually never
like talked to him that much back in the day.
I actually knew, he's part of a group called
The Runaway Guys with a guy called Proton
John and I knew Proton John from something
awful because, you know,
that's where all the cool kids were hanging out
back in 2007-2008, you know,
the hub of all cool
internet activity that sort of became a nasty
little seed which blossomed
into a million other parts of
modern internet culture of something awful,
you know what I mean?
Well, I figure since
Shuga Conroy is a fan of yours, maybe you should
you could pitch him my
LPs one day.
Oh yeah, I'll definitely
Yeah, you, you, you're also
making good Let's Plays, a very
I really like, I really like the
Gamer's Tavern, the Gamer's Tavern
collection of Let's Plays.
Nobody, nobody tries to be funny in their Let's Plays
everybody just thinks their stupid natural
personality was going to be enough
to cut like, you know, carry the
I just thought, I thought maybe he'd like
them because he's a, from what I hear
he's a big pun guy and
that's kind of my specialty.
I feel like he absolutely would like your videos, definitely
he's got that kind of very
you know, you know, humorous
sensibility, you know what I mean? Where it's just like
a lot of unrelenting punchlines after another
which is great. Nobody, nobody writes
material for their Let's Plays
It's a loss, a lost art.
It's ironic to like complain about that
Part of me does miss that, you know what I mean?
That's exactly why I chose to do it because
I figured nobody in their right mind
would do this.
That's how you know you have a good video
That's reason enough.
I agree.
It's funny because back in the day
people used to accuse Let's
players of scripting their videos
but actually
nobody ever did that because that would require
you know, effort.
To fully script out a video
yeah, that would be like a lot of work.
Usually I would just have like, you know
things I want to talk about that I try to
make sound natural.
If you thought that
the banter in a Let's Play
was so sharp that you were like
this can't be off the cuff
this has to have been like prescripted
and like written and produced
I was just like, wow
The news comes out, Aaron Hansen
has never played a video game.
It's all been scripted.
It really tells you a little bit about
the person that they can't imagine
having a funny conversation like that.
Some people are natural entertainers
it's kind of weird. Some people like Jerma
they can just flip a switch
and they're just like on, you know what I mean?
They can just be funny for like extended periods of time.
Yeah, that's definitely true
and I'm not one of those people
that's why I need a script.
Hey, there's nothing wrong with that
nothing wrong with a nice bit of scripted content.
Not everyone has to be a
Twitch streamer in my book
You're missing out on content though
as you've been saying.
Every second in your life is content
You should live stream
your script writing
We should live stream us
recording the episode
before we release the episode
You live stream the recording of the episode
then you have the episode premiere
and then you can have the post premiere
look back at the episode
the walking dead and the talking dead
look back at the PCP we just were on
Which then we live stream our
after like how do we feel about the reception
of this episode
That was a few bonus episodes where we just talk it over
a PCP
as if it was a mystery science
theatre in your old episodes
I think we haven't done another one in a while
Yeah, you were on the one
because we did your old episode
the first episode you were on
we did the re...
the PCP will never die
it'll be like a loop
it starts back at the beginning
now we're going to be commenting on the first episode again
We should just not even have those as bonus episodes
that should be the next
That's the next phase of the PCP
just redoing every old episode
commenting on the old ones
People love your old content
like all the people pitching about
the old days
They can give them what they want
the old episodes again
like the exact same episode
commentary tracks
We literally scripted it
we would get the transcript
and then say the things again
If somebody is not there
play your new person
I give you
we hire a bunch of actors
I give you a live
I'm imagining it at a local theatre
like on stage
in front of a curtain
just people standing there
with scripts doing a live reading
a live performance of
episode 4 of the program
they think it's just like a fucking podcast
or something but they don't understand
every single line has been prescripted
This is starting to become an actual good idea
It's kind of funny
the idea of doing commentary
has always been funny to me
let's play is already commentary
only you're not the director
so I did a video once that was commentary
on my first let's play video
and I was like this is my commentary on my thoughts
and then I immediately did a commentary on that video
and then I did a commentary on that video
I did that I was like I got 4 deep
and then I stopped
the commentary on a commentary
but on a podcast is like extra funny
because it's already pure audio
it would be so hard to tell
especially if it wasn't some of the same voices
it is hard
it's very confusing
what if we literally do that
and we get the transcript
the closed captions from a video
and we just re-record a re-performance of it
and we make it a bonus
we're doing it
we're fucking doing it
do we have that
on our channel
do we have to enable that
or is it just automatic
there's automatic captions
the captions are pretty decent now
the automatic ones
if you have some specific proper nouns
it might not get but for the most part it's pretty good
you don't even need to hire someone
you could but you can also just use
the AI text to speech has gotten pretty good
you can just synthesize new cast members
here's what we do
we replace everybody who's not here
on the podcast
just run their scripts through all the
Pony video audio generators
so we just have Twilight and Applejack
we're placing Trixie and Nate
and all the other stuff
that's the final stage of the podcast
is you actually talking to the Ponies
it's where we've been heading this whole time
speaking of Pony
have you seen the trailer
for the new movie
I did
I didn't actually watch it but I've been seeing images
from it
it looks like really
really lame
you wouldn't have expected much else
but it was just like
no jokes in the trailer landed
at all
I saw people saying that that one Pony looks like
she's the daughter of
Mordecai and Twilight
oh yeah with the blue hair or whatever
that meme is pretty funny
cutie mark even has like three little things
coming off it that looks like Mordecai's tail feathers
like it's a bit of a stretch
but it's like
it's not the biggest stretch
it just seems very generic
it seems like what you would have expected
G4 to be going into it I guess
yeah
back to the same old like corporate nothing
well now they have like a huge
fan base of like
there are obviously always been some my little Pony fans
but I feel nothing now they can make some generic shit
and it would still probably sell really well
so they're like hey let's just make some generic shit
it's got
they really reinvigorated the brand
with G4 they don't have to try that hard
all the people who have the content
they have to make the content
by reacting to the episodes
they'll drive up the engagement
people bitching about the Pony's and saying how ugly they are
and how bad they are and how not good they are
Dr. Wolf is making bank
Dr. Wolf's not wasting any of this content
he's monetizing his every thought
there's a lot of the bronies who really
stuck through it and they never once
even considered covering a different
show or something and they just
they're just gonna wait until the next fucking generation
of Pony shit comes out fucking
I know my niche
they've been doing it for 10 years
can you imagine being a content creator
that just stuck to one topic
and that was it
I mean
maybe I would have more money
were you gonna pivot to being a full time
sonichu channel now
me
no, full time Winnie the Pooper
oh yeah, hell yeah dude
if Chris was releasing
monthly updates I might
I don't know, no I wouldn't do
no, no I couldn't do it
I couldn't do it, I don't have it
it's one thing to do if there's actually something to talk about
it's one thing if you have to just make up shit
to get angry about it
read a new tweet that says the same thing
another deranged tweet that's exactly like all the ones
as he always makes
Ben just doesn't have it in him
to be too successful
no
oh you think you're too good to read tweets
just as a hardcore anti-capitalist
can't let yourself get too successful
otherwise you might get seduced
by the system
I gotta, you know it's like
that's why I love Bernie Sanders so much
he knew that like if he actually
won anything it would just defeat the whole
point so he has to
he's just there to give people hope
he's not actually there to fix it
controlled opposition
he had to do a classic
pratfall
pivot to, pivot crash and burn at the last
minute and you know he pulled it off
crash and burn
he's a comedian at heart
it really was like a perfect example of like a
sideshow bob stepping on a million rakes
and he was like he pulled it off with a plum
I'm much respected in it
you should never
seen anyone step on rakes
with such poise
such grace
also he wants to prove that he's legit
so if he actually won then you know he's
one of them
I'm glad he didn't win that we didn't have to get disappointed
by him winning and then not fixing everything
absolutely
nothing
that would have been great because then
once everybody realized that Bernie wasn't the answer
it would have taken up their pitchforks
that's why they couldn't let him win
they weren't afraid that he was going to fix everything
but they were afraid
it doesn't matter who we elect
it's never going to change
we can't let him
eat the carrot
we can't let him eat the carrot that we're dangling
because we only have one
carrot
you have to keep using the stick forever
I don't know I think you're
placing too much faith on people
people never seem to
learn
that idea
I don't actually think
they would learn a lesson from any
from anything that happened
I think you're probably right
history
is doomed to repeat itself
at least that means
we're going to get a few more good sonic games
before it's over
wait because Bernie's going to
well if history is going to repeat itself
we're going to get to go through the 90s again
oh
yeah I guess you're right
but the problem is it's not going to happen until
the 2000
ah god
I need to put myself in sort of Walt Disney
cryo storage or something
wasn't there a plague in like 1920
yes there was
and there was another one in 2020
there was also one in 1820
yeah the spanish window was like 100 years ago
yeah I heard about that one
yeah
anyway speaking of
speaking of elected officials
I have the lord of ghosts
the lord mayor of ghosts
is with me
the plush exists
and he's here right now
he's got his funny little hand
spent so much on shipping
he's on the podcast
oh god I gotta
I guess I've got her
wait you're not shipping them like now are you
changing my address in
this is just the
sample I've been waiting to see it
in person he looks great
and he's squishy
and he's like you can pick him up and throw him
no problem
that's important
that's what you want
he's adorable and now I have
something that I can like fashion a little
the little like ghost costume
it's going to be like the size
of a like a handkerchief
which is super adorable
I'm gonna have to figure out how to make those in bulk
but yeah
things are happening it's exciting
but also terrifying
yeah now you have to do it now you have all this responsibility
I have to keep track
of everybody who pledged
and how much they pledged and if anybody
wants like a plush
I haven't ordered them yet
and if they want one I can
maybe like accommodate
adding that to like
a thing that I'll figure it out
I need to like ask everybody before
I start buying stuff because
some people may have changed their minds I know Tom
wanted one so I have to like buy
an extra I couldn't believe this
I was looking at the battle gem ponies
Kickstarter
and I saw that there is apparently an
option to like add to
a Kickstarter tier
you can add like optional bonuses where
you can like hit a button and be like okay I want this tier
but I'll also add like five dollars
and I'll also get this add-on to it
or I'll add ten dollars and I'll get this other add-on
and like I had no idea
you could do that
on Kickstarter that was like exactly
the feature that like
it would have been really useful for me
with the vapors it would have been useful for you
with the Lord of Ghosts and adding the plush
like I've never seen it before
I guess I'm glad it's there but I wish I knew
about it
yeah it's pretty stupid that I didn't
like figure that out
it was right there
I was just like oh I don't want to do anything wrong
I'm not even gonna click on anything
as long as you don't forget
to fulfill any rent
that people paid for you'll be fine
nobody would ever want me
to rent about anything
that's impossible
who could think of such a thing
well we've been going we've been ranting
and raving for
almost
we're almost at two hours now
I'm trying to think was there anything that
I fucking had to
bring up this Wii anything I wanted
to mention
that I didn't already touch on
maybe maybe not
last week did I mention the funny thing
about
when May and Ethan Ralph
went to the arrest took a Christian
arrest
he says you know my friend Ben's name
did I mention that before?
I don't know if you mentioned it I saw that
you got fucking name dropped
I got name dropped
I didn't see that
I don't know
I just think that's really funny
that's really funny and bizarre
I guess she thought
your name is part of the
historical record
I'm getting arrested video
future historians
who was this mysterious Ben saint
that was the
that'll be the only artifact that exists of our civilization
that was the friend of
the holy lady
our lady
of pain
Pantsu party
the historical record
there's no better way
to get in Chris's good graces
than a woman who knows Ben saint
and see
what a treat
I guess other than that no I had
I didn't do anything
and I never will do anything ever again
what about the game Ben?
oh god I um
yeah I've been working
I have been working on the game
I made a
I added blood
I added animated blood effects
I've been like
I've been like splatter all over the world
it might be a little too much
I might dial it back and make it a little less
there's like a lot
it gets everywhere now
the game is no longer appropriate for children
I was going to make some children play it but now I can't
I might force some children
these kids in the park want to play this game
and they're like no
it's cool like body parts
this is important
and my little pony
spray out like a stream of blood
out of like the severed part
and like the blood like arcs across
like the floor and the wall and like splatters
and like patterns
it actually looks pretty cool
I mean it's a pretty basic but it's a
it's a funny effect
this is sounding kind of like a feature creep to me
you're right
but I've been this is a feature that I have been imagining
I've been thinking of adding it for a long time
and I finally sat down the other day
and I did it
there's only so many features that I actually need
there's only there's
there's no
I feel I feel okay
because this isn't like a new thing that I thought of
like yesterday or what the other day
when I was working I was like wait what if I did
this is a thing I'd already had like on a list
that I had I mean a mental list
but it was an old list
no no feature creep
never feature creep
um
maybe a little bit but not too much
just just the right amount of feature creep
just the right amount of crypto creep
yes
bitcoin is going to the moon
and you're all just jealous
you should add a slime coin idle game
oh like it's like oh
just in the middle of
in the middle of battle you can just open up your
your gel phone and just look at a little like
stock and just like trade stocks
like between attacks or whatever
it's like oh shit I gotta sell I gotta sell my
stock
you know what I'm like KFC no don't
it was a silly joke
you know what feature creep actually sounds kind of cool
actually it's a good thing
right it's like more features creeping and make
the game better yeah I like that
correct I like when the game get better
you can expect the release of this game in
no
I can't even believe that that year will pass
someday that doesn't make sense to me
I remember feeling that way about
2021 you know what I mean like back in
like 2016
media in like 2020 like that's so far in the future
I'm never gonna be there
I felt that way about the year 2000
now
well that's weird
I can't imagine living in
an era where there's a two on the end
of time imagine
how good the world's gonna be by then
yeah imagine how cool
a technologically advanced it'll be
we'll have flying cars and
how old were you in 2000
I was 12
or 11 or 12
okay
yeah it was 11
I think I was a little too young to even
anticipate like what even that
means for like the millennium
the year 2000
like huh what
I thought that shit was crazy
I'm going back to playing with
whatever
these fucking zoomers who have the privilege of
being born in the year 2000 so they always
know exactly how old they are because they can just
look at what year it is and like oh that's how old I am
yeah I was thinking about that the other day
that's really convenient
well I know how old I am because
I just google how old is the Simpsons
and I'm as old as the Simpsons is
so
on a separate note that's depressing
as fuck I was thinking about how like Homer
Simpson he's like supposed to be in his 30s
he's like there's not like a one
clear canon answer but he's been
portrayed as 32 and 36
I don't want to be as old as Homer
Simpson though I would prefer not to be dead
I think there was a tweet going around where they were saying like there's one of the recent episodes
of the Simpsons
portrayed Homer as like a young Rebellies
teenager in the 90s and I was like
well they have that sliding time scale
because I mean yeah he's like they're not getting older
but things are still
current events are still happening so
okay I'm pretty sure that he
was canonically 39
but then like at some point
they changed it to 40
I always thought of him as yeah closer to 40 to be honest
but yeah you can find shit that
say is he's like in his mid 30s
it's not like there's one canon answer
like I said it's
I remember there's an episode where there's a
his crisis is that he's literally
he's hit the like halfway point of like the average
age
he's literally like halfway through his life because he's
you know he thinks he's 38
and
but he's actually he forgets that he's actually
39 so he's actually more than half
I remember there's like a bit in there
I wouldn't be surprised
it probably does vary
at some point they must have made like
a decision but made probably early on they like
weren't 100% sure about it
I googled my
birth year and like what happened
in this year and
I'm scrolling through and there's a lot of like
you would never think to remember this
like oh Ben Johnson
is banned from athletics for life
I don't
I don't know what that is
who is that
the Indonesia earthquake
earthquake hits flora's Indonesia
2200 dead
that's how old I am
sorry I only know
the release dates of video games I don't know
years
such a useless list
not world historic events
like stuff happens in the year
and it's just a bunch of
boring news articles
and like war
lame
where's the real shit
what video games came out that's all that matters
I know in 1988
the year Ben was born
is when Mario 3 came out in Japan
Mario 3
wait really
yeah Mario 3 came out in US
in 1990 and in Japan
it came out in 88 I believe
I was playing the NES
as a kid thinking it was like new
hot shit I didn't even realize
that it was like old busted
bullshit technology
my parents probably got it at a
fucking bargain Ben at the library
I'm kind of grateful to have grown up
and been able to appreciate like the Super Nintendo
and Genesis just to have like been there
for that big jump into 3D
like whoa it's fucking
3D
quick facts from 1993
world's changing event
Intel introduced the Pentium family
of 32-bit microprocessors
the world was never the same after that
it's just so rememberable
I remember seeing
it wasn't like a commercial
for the Game Boy Advance
it was like a commercial for like
McDonald's
and McDonald's was doing like a Mario
tie-in
doing some kind of like tie-in promotion
with like Mario 64
or something
and they fucking
the commercial showed a Game Boy
color or maybe it was a Game Boy Advance
I think it was something like Mario 64 on the Game Boy color
I think I remember that commercial
and I remember being pissed off and like you can't do that
technology I wish I had that
like oh my god a handheld with 3D graphics
I can't even fucking believe this
if I could just have Mario 64
in a handheld I'd be so happy
that it happened on the fucking DS
and it was like whatever it's fine
I think one of the biggest
I played it in like a week because that was cool
look at this fucking this thing
the conversation Ted Danson
wore black place and used the N word
at girlfriend whoopee Goldberg's roast
at the Friars Club
this looks like it was like AI generated list
it says the most famous person in America
was probably
where did you find this list
I'm just googling place it like
pop culture all of facts and trivia
I remember the shipping news
by E. Annie Prowles
had the price of a Domino's Pizza
two toppings in 1993
it was a different time
back then you could wear black face
and say the N word it was okay in those days
it was a different time
it was charming
cool and epic as a matter of fact
Intel introduced a Pentium
there used to be a micro process
pretty good
okay I guess Dune came out
that's a pretty big release
is it the initial yeah 10th of December
like Ted Danson wore black face
and used the N word at girlfriend
whoopee Goldberg's roast
at the Friars Club
we gotta cancel Ted Danson what the fuck
is going on here we gotta dig up this roast
how old are you
remember when Ted Danson said the N word
you remember that
you remember the rascal Ted Danson
I'm trying to imagine like what the context
was that like maybe at the time
not everyone thought
that was like really
cringe to do
hmm
the 90s was a world before cringe existed
everybody just did everything genuinely
and nobody was embarrassed
by anything
there's only once YouTube and the internet existed
that cringe culture came into being
well it wasn't that long ago
that the PCP used to
say the N word quite often
we're just like Ted Danson
we're even better
we said it even more
than Ted Danson did
and later so for all you know
we were in black face the entire time
did you know
you can't prove that they weren't
did you know that behind the scenes
we all wore black face all up the first
entire year we were recording
and we never talked about it
we thought it just went without saying
we thought it was black face but it was actually
a bunch of soot like we were in Mary Poppins
and we were cleaning the chimneys
because well you see because
we had all been holding like we had all
collectively been holding a large cartoon
bomb that had like exploded at us
and you know covered us
and that's basically what it was like in the 90s
it was a lot like the early PCP episodes
in a roundabout sort of way
good times
those were the days
love that cartoon ball
celestine prophecy
classic a classic
game of the year
game of the year of the year of your birth
what do you got?
let's compare like year birth games
who's got the best gamer
we're pretty sure
I'm slightly miffed
I'm one year early to be Sonic the Hedgehog
so I have to say Super Mario World
that's a pretty good one
it is a good game
from the year I was born
I'm going to deal with ones that were released in America
Super Mario Bros. 2
was released in America
see I don't even need to do this because we have the same birth
so whatever your answer
let me just take it
Master Blaster
damn
I might win I've got Mega Man X
Monopoly on the Sega Master System
it's Mega Man X
the secret man of this doom
Disney's Aladdin on Genesis
Mega Man X kind of came out in 94
in US I think
in 93 in Japan
I didn't click on the thing
Zelda came out in 1988
so that's pretty good
that's pretty solid
I thought it was 1987
not according to computer gaming world magazine
why is it always got to be like you gotta check things
I typed in it in google and I have to go and check
what year it came out in what country
actually something that fascinated me is that
with some really old games
they actually don't know when they came out exactly
because they used to not keep track of that sort of thing as much
like there's a big debate
as to when the original Super Mario Bros. came out
some people say it was 1985
others say it was 1986
it was an actual year
package with the NES
with like Duck Hunt cartridge
well Nintendo officially lists it
as 1985
but the NES only had a limited release in the US in 1985
it was only released like in a couple of cities
and I think it wasn't until 1986
that the NES had a
a release across the entire country
okay riddle me this Nintendo
you say it's called the family computer
then why does it only play games for babies
explain that to me
where's the porn
where's the porn games
and a spreadsheet accounting software
for mommy and dad
the Famicom actually did have
a couple of antigames
I need my adult themes
and situations
and mature situations
I need to be titillated
I need the Famicom to do a fucking digital
striptease for me on my television set
you ever seen a Takeshi's challenge
I think it was called
I've seen the Jontron
video about it
it was popular before Jontron did a video on it
yeah but I'd never heard of it before that
I think maybe AVGN did a video on it first
but I'm not sure
maybe he did it after
wait what game
Takeshi's challenge
no I don't think AVGN did that
Jontron did that one
yes that's what I remember
uhhhh
are we still looking at
video game years
legend is all though
can you imagine being an old enough piece of shit
to play Atari games
and enjoy them
even though they suck
I watch this youtube channel
sometimes called Kim Justice
and Kim Justice talks
about
pre-NES games
in Britain
and Britain
they had the Zidic Spectrum
the Zidic Spectrum
UK didn't get games
from the rest of the world until
the NES
they had their own homebrew
they had a whole different video game scene
guys are there, they love Dizzy
the Ig, they love that guy
they have all sorts of weird shit they like
the second master system is not popular in the UK
I think
this is in the late 80s
that one where you're the little guy
Kim
there's like one of like a bunch of sequels
she's made a
sort of a documentary about the life of this like
kid who like made this game
where you're a guy running around like a hotel
and it was like a
huge fucking hit
it was like a massive success in the UK
and nowhere else and the guy was like
a fucking rockstar and he like
got into drugs and like burnt out
really young after making one sequel
and like he had like a whole
like rise and fall like celebrity
that's just so weird to me you're like a rockstar
video game dev but like in the fucking
late 80s when all the games sucked
basically again I'm not even trying to be mean
but like Atari games are just so primitive
that they're just like they're basically like
unplayable by today's standards again but it's just
weird to me like imagine video games don't even exist
like you don't even know I mean I guess Pong existed
and then like all of a sudden there's this new
thing called Atari you probably think it's pretty cool
but like it's impossible to show it to a
kid nowadays and have them actually be
interested in it
let me let me let me show you
there are probably some good Atari games
let me show you the game this guy made
this guy was um
was like living this rockstar lifestyle
off of it looked like it looked like
I'm gonna post a script this
it's called Jet Set Willy
this guy was like
because I remember hearing Jet Set in the titles
like what the fuck is going on but yeah just a weird ass game
is that the prequel of Jet Set Radio
that's what I thought but I don't think so
I think I think this is the sequel
this is number two I think
I've seen games that look like this before
but I forgot what it was called
but I played actually
a ZX Spectrum game once
in Donkey Kong 64
there's a mini game where you can play
a ZX
Jetpack, that's the one
you can play that
it's I think the real original
version of the game
Rareware got their start making ZX Spectrum games
so yeah you can
find a few of them on like the Rare
Replay or whatever
I actually thought Jetpack was pretty cool
even though it's a very simplistic
primitive game
I thought it was not so bad
it's kind of fun to play for a couple of minutes at a time
right yeah I
was sort of being comedic in how
overly harsh I am I know there are some good old
games it's just like they're rarer
and you find a lot of just bullshit that sucks
and you have to use your imagination
which is the last thing I want to be doing when I'm playing a video game
I play that to have
imagery force fed to me not so I can imagine
things
door fortress
I mean it's easy
to make fun but like I'm doing
some game dev shit and I have like software
that's specifically built for it
imagine trying to make this
you have to like program
it must be really hard to make games
like draw the sprite
you have to like I remember seeing
like
for Mario or whatever they have like
paper where they would draw
yeah they drew it on graph paper
like where the pixels would be and then they would have to
type up like okay this coordinate
here draw this pixel
and they would do that
and then that's how they would draw pixel art
so it was incredibly difficult for them
to make fine
tune changes to the levels
since they
they'd have to draw it on the graph paper
first and go back and
type in the code to change something
mm-hmm
yeah that
sounds about the size of it
I think also back then they had to use
like certain
ROM cartridges that would
only be erased
if you shined light into
the ship
add like a little hole for ultra
violet light
what
I don't even understand
that's wild
you mean like to
erase data
they had to like sack it
that is weird I was not aware of that
but it was just a feature
I completely had the weird arcade technology like that
it was like it was a read only
memory ship but you can erase
the data on it by
shining light into a little hole on the ship
you have to like manually do it
yeah I think they had to
manually do this kind of thing back then
it was pretty
inconvenient you know making games back then
was very difficult
that's why it's pretty impressive
I always had my mind blown
I had like small of like disk space
you know they had to work with those games
like in the original Super Mario Bros they had to reuse
like the fucking clouds as the bushes and shit
you know what I mean because just anywhere to save
a little bit of space
that's why a lot of the levels are kind of samey
but it's impressive
they were able to make a you know a pretty
playable game off of
the technology they had at the time
you ever watch those videos there's a guy
who does like sort of like how it works
like old gaming tech and he
there's one where he explains like
he explains why missing no looks the way it does
but in the course
is that the 8-bit guy
it's not the 8-bit guy
no that's a different guy
LGR
um
why missing no
I haven't seen that video specifically but
I think maybe I know you're talking about
I think it's called missing no
explained
I may have seen this video it's ringing some bells
but yeah it is interesting hearing just like
the exact minutiae of like
like why does it come out is this weird
garbled box like what exactly is it trying to do
you know what I mean
is it like explaining how
it like it's it decides
to be printed in that weird
pattern like we all know why
there's a glitch but like is he going into like
it's called it's called
the channel is called retro game mechanics
explained the video is called missing
those glitchy appearance explained
and it's basically I mean
he he he says he
explains why missing no has that sprite
and he and to do so he has to
explain the whole like process by which
Pokemon sprite data
this is a good video and then like
translated and compressed and stuff
I appreciate anyone who will go to like
I've seen lengths to like
like look at this the visualizations that he
does to like don't like
I need to explain to me very basically
you know what I mean so for me to understand
something of this like when he's pulling out the math
and shit I'm like okay oh this this is good
I want to watch this
this is a good video yeah I like I appreciate anyone
who's like oh did you know this
missing no is a thing that happens
right right right this is
just glitching this you know it's like a
why why is it like you know
missing no is a
a very mysterious thing to have discovered
as a kid
because it's kind of like the father
or mother of all glitches it's
it's quite amazing
yeah I remember it was really cool
it was like yeah it wasn't hard to do
but it was like you had to do these weird
esoteric steps which were easy to
explain luckily and it's so weird to
me how it could like fuck up your game it
like clone your items
it's accessible and you can do it
and it's fun how it
sort of works like it's sort of you can
sort of just use it as a pokemon
kind of and it like does things to your
game that are like it breaks your game
but like it doesn't break it's so bad that
like it doesn't work it doesn't like hard crash the game
it actually has like you can like put your master
ball or rare candy in a certain slot and get
infinite which is like incredibly useful I mean
sort of breaks a game and like makes it too easy
blah blah blah but you know as a kid I didn't
give a fuck about that I was just like whoa this is epic
it was a really easy glitch pull off
but it was just so
weird it didn't make sense how it
work and
as a kid I couldn't figure out if the developers
did this on an on purpose
or if it was
not on purpose it was just
it just didn't make sense until I got older
it was hard to imagine like yeah how could there be like
accidentally put a pokemon in the game with like
a unique name and sprite like how does
accidentally happen to like oh yeah exactly
these aren't on purpose these are like default error
messages basically like missing number
means like we couldn't find the fucking pokemon's name
just crazy that so much
comes up from just this one
uh tiny error
it is cool I like to think of how much like
people who are like inspired by missing know just
in terms of like glitch hunting and just people
make their own games so they're inspired probably
not directly but just like that kind of glitchy
shit is inspired like creepypasta to you know
just some degree which is actually I was gonna say that
inspired by other games missing know actually kind
of scared me a little bit as a kid because
it felt like a creepypasta
it is like it's basically
like a creepypasta that's what creepypastas are all like
they all have that start off it's like a missing
no shit well you have to go here and do all this obscure
shit that's like a reason why you know
no one else has found this hidden ghost
bullshit in the game it's interesting
as like when you're a kid you you think
that uh your game got
infected by a ghost
virus or something I was very
you know when I realized
that that it had corrupted my
I didn't realize until later that it would
corrupted my elite four data and I was
very bummed I was very bummed about that
the first time I got
like poisoned in Pokemon
I thought the game was glitching out because it
went you know does the whole
thing with it when you walk a few steps
it beeps and it flashes and I'm
like oh shit I did
I do something wrong oh no the game's gonna break
I'm gonna get in trouble
I was very scared very
upset I had no idea that's
what the poison was your first explosion of poison mechanic
yeah it's not it doesn't make sense and that is
why I mean it's not they don't explain it but like
it's easy to have it happen to you and not know
what's going on for the first time so
that's fine and eventually the Pokemon fainted
and I was like oh it's a thing that was going
on
I love that feeling when you think the game
is breaking and then you realize oh that's just a mechanic
yeah that's a great feeling
that's what
that's what eternal darkness does on purpose
you have the sanity mechanic
and as you lose sanity
the game tries to trick you into thinking
more games haven't ripped off the sanity meter
but I guess it's like a trick that doesn't you know
it only really works when it's novel
and fresh you know what I mean
I don't think many people remember eternal darkness
it's like mainstream
right you know I don't know what that is
not anymore
everyone's practically forgotten about it
now but it was a
pretty interesting mechanic
the end
so fucked up the end
thanks for listening
that's the end of the procrastinator's podcast
it's voicemails
do you have enough time left on your recording for voicemails
oh no I cleared some data
I cleared some data I'm good
I have space for 17 more hours
and I intend to go
alright we have a 17 hour episode baby
break out the record
I have space for 52 more hours
I don't know I can keep going
fuck
you just deleted all of his porn files
no I would never
Ben just deleted all of his game files
if anything I do placate it
let's see
here
alright the first voicemail
do I have this numbered correctly
let me make sure that I'm starting at the
at the beginning
first voicemail is called
lord of kickstarter trailers
let me find it
it is number 3528
there it is
putting it in
I'm in the wrong channel
I'm looking at the wrong channel
okay putting it in general
there sorry this is taking a second
okay lord of kickstarter trailers
let's go in 3, 2, 1, go
even though the lord of ghosts kickstarter
is already funded I keep coming back
to the page just to rewatch
the like trailer announcement video
thing because it's so good
it's so funny
it's evergreen even though it is
about a limited time event
the video alone
is worth the money that I pledged
thank you gib for making
for being epic
you're welcome
it's a funny video I love the
sports theme
I saw tim and eric live once they did it
sports live it was cute
I have not seen it just think it comes from
that reminds me of
when John and Aaron used to do
those videos advertising
when they're going to do
some kind of new content
and sometimes those videos were funnier
than the actual things they were doing
or advertising
yeah I used to like the skits
for like oh crunchyroll subscription
or a new t-shirt
and they that was
those were good
I definitely wanted that video to be
like I remember
the punk plush kickstarter where I
was just sort of explaining what it was
in front of a camera
and I don't think I think that was
kind of lame
I wanted this one to be like memorable and fun
and cool and people like oh
I'm excited about this now
I did it I think
better to do something that like
gets the energy across
than to do something that just like
explains what it is but without like
you know
an impact
yeah making the impact is the important
thing
explaining things in front of a camera that's a
very tricksy move
I mean it's normal
it's a normal thing
to do
ranting about
the lord of the ghost kickstarter
yes
the next voicemail
is called
another poem
oh my god my computer
it's called another poem for ben sains
2 1 go
as I open my eyes my mind
is set no more setbacks
no more regret it seems
I've come up with a perfect plan
I'll tie my artistic brand to Christian
I just can't stop
merging my comic is sure to get lots
of clicks I just can't stop
merging come watch my lecture
get your christery fix
I just can't stop merging
a canon end for this tale of strife
what am I doing with my life
hey
so
I enjoy it
I think we can all find that
relatable who among us hasn't
you just got merged on
in this kind of situation
who here hasn't done a lecture on chris
who here hasn't invariably
tied their brand to chris chan
at some point or another
who hasn't merged their canons
together
into a strange bizarre
crossover story of
things nobody has ever heard of
not I
okay
the next voicemail is called
an elegy for a fallen hero
an elegy
but the next one says ignore the previous one
but I'm not going to ignore the previous one
elegy for a fallen hero
3, 2, 1, go
it was a battle of the pcp
maybe you watch
what he took of me
no matter how I try
I could not break free
and he maybe eased his slasps
I think this is a resend
yeah maybe they accidentally
posted this one but it was good still
it's good
even the voicemails you accidentally resend
are getting played on the podcast
don't filter these
okay this one is called
oh god it's a minute long
this one is called ignore the last one
3, 2, 1, go
oh yeah I remember
how they told us
what they had been
and when they creamed
I do
that's what he did
3, 2, 1, go
that was lovely
that was incredible
that was
that was the first good voicemail to be over
one minute long
I think he did it
I think he did the impossible
it made a good long voicemail
you should redo the whole
of the wall
with pcp memes
definitely do that
please
if you can make something like this
why would you send it in as a voicemail
yeah
the juxtaposition of
putting an effort post into
a shitty voicemail
to get played 2 and a half hours deep
into some podcast
that's the appeal
that is its own reward
next voicemail
is called son of marowak
3, 2, 1, go
son of marowak
so I just got back from odicon
participated in the art show
people bid for items at an auction
online auction
the odicon
art stuff was asking for a lot of hentai
we only had about 10 pieces
this year
usually it's pretty small
but I'm determined
for the next year until the next odicon
I'm going to submit at least 20 to 40
pieces of hentai
it's going to be monster girls
I'll let you know how it goes
submit them for what
is it an art show
I don't understand
I thought he was talking about the vendor hall
was he talking about selling them
you can never have enough hentai
I do not know
the mechanics of odicon
I'm sorry
what they're being submitted for
but I mean good luck
if he's a son of marowak
he's a cubon
he's not just a cubon
he's a special cubon
I drew him on the radcon 4 poster
he's got a whole backstory
he wears a hoodie
he's a cubon with a hoodie
and he's got a special
you don't have to go on it
I was already sold on the hoodie
say no more
what if a cubon had a hoodie
also did you know that
Ethan Ralph was at odicon
I did
someone did say that
may drag Ethan Ralph to odicon
which sounds so awkward
I just can't imagine
I just
sounds like there's going to be some fights
sounds like there's going to get in fights
you missed a great opportunity
to go have a fist fight with Ethan Ralph
and upload the video to your channel
I could have done it
you missed out on some primo content
you left it on the table
I did
that's wasted content
the worst wasted content is the content
that never even happened
that could have been recorded
think of all the boxing matches
that aren't currently going on between YouTubers
think of everyone
in the world
who isn't punching someone right now
think of how many hundreds of boxing matches
that you're not participating in right now
you should be ashamed of yourself
it boggles
you need to get swollen
and start challenging
all the content creators to boxing matches
all the content creators you hate
I mean
that's one way to get my
revenge
on this world, on this bitch of an earth
the next voicemail
is called
Mordecai Saint
3, 2, 1, go
Ben Saint
is just Mordecai
from regular show
I will not be elaborating
cause he fucks horses
cause I, yeah
cause I fucked Twilight
child is in the new generation
is that a good show
regular show?
it looks like adventure time
but it doesn't have adventure in it
that's literally why I watched it
I was a big fan of adventure time
similar right? and I watched the first season or two
and it is good
but it's sort of a slice of life
shit happens
sometimes the funny shit happens
they had an episode making fun of Billy Mitchell
I've seen some pretty good shit
I like that it's just about some guys
working at a job
I really like the premise
and find them being groundskeepers
at a park
you ever see 4 in the ampm
the student film by the guy
he's good
he takes acid and he's tripping
he turns in the character from a regular show
that's just his regular voice
his Mordecai voice
J.G. Quendall
he's the creator of the show
cause you watch his new show
he's the exact same voice
yeah he's a new show on HBO Max
I think about being a dad guy
I hate it
we were bitching together about
Brad Neely's new show
I'm not gonna say it's bad
but just based on the trailer
it didn't look interesting
it's another family show
the last thing the world needs is another show
about being a parent
adult animation cartoon
that looks kind of like family guy
and it's about
the only reason
I'll give it a shot
because I like Brad Neely
he's made some amazing shit
I like China the way the show
but the funniest thing about it
is Professor Bros.
the YouTube videos are just better
I don't even want to be mean about it
but they're just so funny
I watched some of the show
and it was okay
it doesn't even need the animation
somehow it works perfectly
when it's just comic panels in sequence
somehow it just works perfectly with that style
bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad
bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad
oh my god
it's so weird
it's like baby cakes and the Professor Bros.
are just such memorable amazing characters
I don't know
they don't really come across
they don't really come across that
they still have their personality in the show
but I don't think they come across as well
it's just fundamentally
is different and feels different on
aspect of it being an actual show
And I'm not even like mad or anything, but just like a part of me. I can't help but prefer the original YouTube videos
Yeah, I don't know. It was a
Just just it's like Carson's
Carsonization like every every evolutionary line eventually
Takes on a crab-like form because it's just the most effective shape and similarly every
Eventually finds itself working on an adult animated cartoon about being a dad or whatever
So we desperately need more family animated shows obviously so funny like Simpsons and Family Guy are both still airing new episodes
Yeah, they are
They never stopped
Uh, okay next
Uh, was that the one we just listened to? Yeah, Mordecai. That's right. Um, next one is called
Oh, the next one is an image. So here's here's the image. I haven't looked at it
Oh, there it is
I hate the anti-christ
We've got you surrounded
That's it's the name of the Nerf gun
It's this name that I still don't really get it's the Nerf gun from the the the fucking ragcon three
arena ragcon three good attention
That's a nice deep cut. Azumi has one has one arm. So big crimp. Yeah, but that's okay
Oh
This is before the accident. She lost the irs. Oh, fuck back story confirmed. It was the irs
Right the irs chopped her arm off
Well, nobody like they'll do that in real life if you get behind on your payments
They will come cut your arm off like a samurai. Yeah. Yeah, I think that's true
Is the anti-christ in the rebel pixels like grain red
You know, well, I see it's got the irs highlighted. Oh, yeah, I noticed that I didn't realize but yeah
Yeah, you're right. That is like the that color schema
I don't know like
Yes, I guess I agree. I will say I guess I agree with this image. Tom is insane. I've definitely made
The repo time in my life just just today honestly
So that's pretty true
Relatable base to make a to be fair. I'm not a ton of debt. I'm just in student debt, but who is
Mmm smart people many you didn't get your student debt canceled. No
Biden Biden
Well rich people are in debt all the time rich people take on more debt
You can't make money without being in a shitload of debt
That's what sam sam hide told me that actually max out all your credit cards
Rich people just borrow just they just keep borrowing more and more money and never pay it back and like whatever
What are they gonna do?
The gold knife is just to make as much debt as you possibly can rack up as much debt as you can and then die and leave it all
to your kids
Wasn't there like a greek philosopher or someone who was constantly like in debt to everyone?
But he was like, yeah, it's great because when when you owe other people money
They're always trying to like hook you up with like connections that like will make you money
Making money and like they don't want to see you debt
They have a vested interest in you sticking around because yeah, you get in debt to everyone
And they're all like they're all like pulling for you and like like like on your team now because they need you to succeed
Well, I certainly certainly seems to work for the us because I think the us isn't like
27 trillion dollars insane amount of debt. That's like good though
National debt is like good for some reason right that's what they can't just nuke us because they have to collect
They're dead first
Yeah, they'll just repossess our country when we can't pay it
Oh, that's fine. I'll be dead by then the zoomers can deal with that
I'm already adopting the boomer mindset of just all okay. It's fine. I'm just ruin everything and die
They make so much more sense now that I'm getting older
Why solve the problems we create? Uh, it's too late to fix things might as well just not do anything
Yeah, just pass everything on to the next generation
The next voicemail is called
Um, it is called a worst idea ever. She they
three two one go
So when discussing how older games have soul while newer games often don't Nate said this on his gamer zone podcast
People argue about that word soul so often one day. I want to make a video defining
And it really struck me this is the quintessential example of something that is both the worst idea
He's ever had and also the most best guy ever idea
He's ever had and I finally fully grasp how those two things are directly correlated with each other
I see okay
You know, I I listened to that a gamer zone podcast and uh, I I left a comment
I really thought that everyone involved with that project was should just be ashamed of themselves
I uh, I feel like it's the new hot thing. I feel like the pcp
That's gonna be on the way out and everybody should drop and start pledging to the gamer zone podcast
Which doesn't or doesn't even exist doesn't even have a patreon. Um, what can I say? I never say no to a podcast appearance
I'm here now aren't I?
The standards are the bottom bottom floor
I uh, I don't worry. I'll I'll sneak in plenty of um, I'll be sneaking in plenty of pcp references that and like
I'll be mind fucking Nate's audience tricking them. It's coming back
Nate uh, like oh my god, I've never heard like have you
The Nate Nate fans will be blindsided to know that he was once on a podcast. What Nate podcast what?
um, um
So I don't know if this is the person I'm thinking of but I saw someone in the comments of the gamer zone making a comment about
Soul and being irritated that like Nate describes things as having soul
And being like that's so vague and it's literally just something you can say you like anything you like you can just say it has soul
Yeah, that's right. Everything I like is good wherever you want it and everything that's bad and new is soulless
That's just the way the world works and I like yeah
I guess yeah, it is. Um, I mean
I mean it's sort of an extension of just saying like if if it's good if if I like it then it's good
And if I don't like it basically yes, but like describing the words to that
To imply that there's more is that Nate could just make make a 50 minute video
That's just like like this is what it means to have a soul and first of all
Let's take a look at the first game to involve souls undertale. It's like a look here
They invented it
My take on soulfulness really quick is like I feel soul what it means is like you can tell the people working on the game
Like liked it and they tried they were trying to make a good game
They weren't just trying to make a quick book again. I know that's not something you can just quantify but like there's it's some
slight difference between
soul versus like me likey thing
It basically isn't there basically is no difference between that but like I think it's sort of it's like
Knowing that people are getting a sense at least that people cared about the product
They were making is a feeling that affects your opinion of the game in some way that is that the game itself
Doesn't really have anything to do with it's just sort of like right
You just feel happier thinking about the fact that people put their heart and soul
Into a product. I always thought it was less corporate therefore you like it more for no real reason
But I just thought a soul basically means personality when something has a lot of
Personality to it. I think it it definitely doesn't have like one set meaning
So this is sort of just what our takes on it are and I feel like both of those takes are pretty accurate in terms of just
As opposed to something that is a homogenized
Because like for example, you can you can look at the new super mario bros games that everybody hates
And uh, you can say those games kind of lack personality and therefore soul
But then you look at mario world and mario bros 3 and 2
And those games have a lot more personality
See the thing is it's not a very useful term to use and I I don't use it myself
When somebody does use it, I know what they're getting at
Generally speaking, it's a little bit of a fortune. It's kind of unquantifiable because it really does what uses it
It relies a lot on
Your perception and if you have nostalgia or not that
Influences whether you think there's soul in a product, right two examples of uh games
I think are soulful it's like sonic adventure is a soulful game
That's not necessarily always good, but it like it feels like they had fun making it and they were trying really hard
And they were like trying to make a good game. That's why it's like crammed full of ideas even if they don't all work
I feel like another example of a soulful game is earthbound because it was made by an auteur and it wasn't like
Yeah, I was gonna say trying to be
Earthbound is quirky and stuff, but it's not like trying to be a quirky in the rpg
It was just trying to be like itoy just made this game based off of like his life experiences and stuff
You know what I mean? Like it's I don't know it's hard to explain
It really is hard to explain and it's not something you can easily quantify and a lot of it just does come down
How do you personally feel about a game?
It's like if you if you look at uh a typical ubisoft like open world
Kind of shooting game you can kind of tell that that doesn't have much salt to it
It's almost easier to point to the soullessness than soulfulness. Yeah, it's just a pure corporate production
People just have to make it and they have to make a million of them
Okay, but I think it's possible for a corporate entity to make a game
Yeah feels like it does have soul
You're absolutely right like a shitload of art throughout human history has been commissioned, you know by like, you know
Not not not just corporations, but like, you know wealthy, you know patrons of the arts and like the
You know the renaissance and stuff like a lot of art
I wish art could just exist spontaneously
You know without having to be you know fit within the monetary framework of reality
But you know
It doesn't so yeah a lot of good art can come from a corporate shit too
But like there is still element of soullessness and homogeneity that you can see and identify
Well, a corporation has to hire artists and artists might care about the work they're doing
right
Yeah, it's really kind of a useless metric by wish to judge a game
um
Like it whether or not it's like you think it's has soul or it doesn't
The game is the same and if it's made corporately
Uh or like artistically the end product is the only thing you're experiencing
You don't really know and that can't possibly influence
Anything right like you know
It's just the the end product is the thing that you end up experiencing and the the soul is just added on on top of your own
Yeah, it's what you're extrapolating backwards based on what you think happened during game development
Which is again like you will have a different opinion of how soulful a game is if you were there for the entire process of making it
Which obviously, you know, you can't be for that's true
When you when you say it has soul you're saying that it feels as though someone put a lot of work and love into it
And maybe they did or maybe they didn't but like you don't you don't know at the end of the day
You're you're just saying it feels like they did and that's good at the end of the day
It is a nebulous term. It doesn't really have much
Or not narrative doesn't have much like analytical value because it's so unquantifiable
It's better to like if you feel like something has soul, it's better to kind of extrapolate
What about it is resonating with you that way emotionally you can you can be like I feel like it has soul
But you got to explain like what okay, what what about it makes you say
If it resonates with you and an emotional level like that and you're trying to make an analytical point or trying to like
Explain what that means you have to then extrapolate into something much more concrete
So someone else can understand why what you're coming from just defining soul
Will not solve the problem. You're defining your feelings. You could just double down on on the feeling aspect and just say
There's just something unquantifiable about this that I just really love and I don't
I don't think Nate would accept that if someone else. Yeah, that's that's what I was just saying either way like you can't
Either way it all comes down to the specific thing what like it was a specific game
I think it's all four or not it's hard to do this is in the abstract make a video
That's just about soul. You know what I mean like that would be really
I like to list specific examples like
In earthbound there's an enemy called mad duck and one of his attacks
I forget what it does, but one of his attacks is to spin something around
Which like confuses you or whatever and it doesn't tell you what he spins around
He just spins something around, you know the dialogue says that
So it's little things like that that are sprinkled throughout the game that I think
Adds personality and you could say it's uh, it's soul
I can I can imagine though a game where like the developer really cared about what they were making
And they really put a lot of themselves into it and they worked really hard and they poured love and time and energy into making
Exactly the product that they wanted to make
But like it's bad and it's something that you hate and you don't like it. Yeah
What what it's still
That can certainly happen
What it's was it is it still I guess that you'd still yeah, it's it's soulful, but it's not good
I I guess that would make I guess that can exist. It's gonna be pretty rare
You'd see people say shit like that, but I mean like I guess you're right
Actually, I think a good example of that is uh, what was that game called a deadly premonition? I think
Well, most of the time when you're saying, oh, it's soulful and you say why and then you oh, well, you know
Here's some here's a detail that I like here's a story
That's a that's a game that uh is kind of bad, but a lot of people loved it. Yeah, it's like a
game
It's people love it in spite of the fact that it's kind of a hotness
Hmm
Yeah, but that's because uh, it was clear the the developer put a lot of love into it even though it's kind of bad
I'm thinking of uh, I'm thinking of limbo of the lost
as a soul a soulful
Game with a lot of a personality that's just piece of shit
Game, yeah, you know, you know that one right the uh the one with uh
The one that's the box art, right?
The I don't know the box. It's the one that ends with the the king limbo song
Uh, oh, yeah, it's not the box. I'm thinking of it's uh, but yeah, um mandalore gaming had a good video on this
Which is how yeah, yeah, it's a good bad game. This is again. I had like lots of blood ledgerism and didn't it
Yeah
Stuff just in it. They just stole assets from skyrim
Uh, nothing nothing says soul more than stealing assets
Well, okay, they stole a lot of stuff
But the stuff that they did is original is very weird and very like unique. Um, I mean an a tour made this
I don't agree with some of the vision assets
But like that doesn't necessarily preclude something from being soulful like barkley shut up in jam
Guiding it has a lot of stolen assets, but like that's part of the joke like that's intentional. It's not like they're it was
That's uh, that's almost like a a rom hack from back in the days when people used to do rom hacks and
that kind of thing
Something useful about rom hacks in general just the way that it's like such a purely fan driven out of love
Not for a problem. A rom hack is uh, when you think about it, it's kind of like a fanfic
Just uh from a
Programming standpoint, right?
Basically every good programmer got their start like modding some other game, you know what I mean?
Well, not like every good programmer, but you know a lot of
I think that's uh, that's a case for a christian whitehead who made sonic mania
Yeah, a lot of the modern sonic mania team in particular is basically made up of fans from the rom hacking scene, which is pretty cool
Um
I think I think we can go to the next voicemail. Oh, yeah, I forgot that that was all just soul
So we basically made Nate's video for him. We just talked about it for 15 minutes about yeah
But he can't if he just clips our audio and makes that video. He's got to pay for it
Wouldn't be a very soulful explanation
This clip so it else's podcast here's my video
Then the next voicemail is called, uh, it's called nothing can stop me. No, there is nothing that can stop me now
Uh, sorry, it's it's loading
There it is. Okay, three two one go
None of you can stop my evil machinations from coming at your fruition. None of you can stop my
history plans
And underneath the table of justice. I reside
sticking
sticky six of gum
under the table and which I
I reside which I will reign supreme
Sir, you may lift the table up
But I will win as soon as the table turns you have flipped the tables yourself leaving me
That victor sure you can punch me in the face
But I have a face mask that can block exactly one punch
He thought of everything
What can you do? Why can't you say there is nothing that can't stop me now?
I like imagining that he recorded that under the table
Where he was sticking during class the tables sure have turned
Well, I'm intimidated sounds like he won and I feel like there's nothing we can do about it other than admit defeat a big
w for that guy who
Uh, I don't know. I don't remember being under the table guy under the table guy is uh, he's he's thought of everything
Uh, next voicemail is called
based based comments award show episode two 74
three two one go
Welcome to based comments award show for procrastinators podcast episode 274
Uh, the most based comment sounds like I gotta be by tectonic improv who says the most based guest ever
I'm inclined to agree. Thank you for your comment
Uh, tune in next time. I'm the just kidding. I'm never doing this again
Uh, wait, you didn't even say what guest it was, but I guess it's him
No, it was it was last, um episode
Uh, who was the guest? I don't even remember a single last week was crack
Yes, that's right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It was last week. He had exactly two guests. Uh, crack and tom
Uh, I'm I'm also inclined to good good good commenter. Good commenter that tectonic improv
Uh, next voicemail is called, uh, it is called order number us one underscore zero seven eight four six
four one
Hold on. Let me put it in the dang chat. Okay, there it is three two one go
Hello, how are you today? I am chewing gum in your ear. What? No, I am a real person
Can we continue? This is the asmr you ordered
I am a real person. Did you hear me okay?
This is a bar package was ordered by Nate on october 19th 2017
Yes, I'm a real person
There is a live person here. We're sorry for the delayed shipping. Who's the real person? I am a real person. Oh
I am a real person
God
Is that it?
Okay, that was good fine. Well, that was great whatever that was
We did they were a real person. They obviously
I mean that was never in question. That's what real people do is insist how real they are over and over again
I I am a real person
You see this is what is known as performance art
Your question about whether I'm real has already been answered by my statements
About that. I am real, uh, actually
Uh, next one is called one upping. Sorry. It's bad. Uh, she her
Here did I already put it in the yeah, there it is. Okay, three two one go
All right, so a little bit towards the end of the episode of last week
You guys were all, you know, kind of just going a little bit crazy over the fact that somebody had been watching
Um watching your pony videos since they were 11
And you know, I I thought that was a bit weird. Um, because I've been watching your videos
Since I was 11. Um, I got into the pcp
Like at the tail end of fifth grade
Um, I was
Looking for something to listen to while I got um got my work done. Um, it started ironically with, um
Monkey jones and the biggest problem in the universe and I'm no not the biggest problem in the universe. Whatever they're, uh
In sufferable social insufferable social media or whatever and off of that since they kept referencing the pcp
I ended up getting into it. So, um, I am currently 14 years of age
So I you know, I I just wanted to let you guys know
That that there are active young people in your audience currently and I'm sure that I'm not the only one
I can't terrify your band. Yeah. Yeah, this fair is banned. I'm sorry
We mark every episode as not suitable for children
Get the it fuck out of here
It kind of it kind of doesn't surprise me that much really that there would have been like kids like young kids that found
Us through the pony stuff because that's kid shit
It it's a little more surprising that like a kid would still find us in like a post pony era because like what's the
Through like monkey jones. I guess if you like monkey, are you an edgy 14 year old? Who is it?
Uh, if you're an edgy 14 year old you find us through monkey if you are a
Korean 14 year old you find us through
Uh, uh, all the rest of us through normal means everyone else. Yeah. Yeah. I'll you find us on reddit
Insufferable social media podcast is the gateway drug to pcp
It is it probably was I don't even remember them saying the pcp that much
I thought I felt felt like a very self-contained old show. I never actually never actually listened to it
So I I actually quite enjoyed it. It was probably my favorite thing. Mumki did
I remember the gimmick was that they were both saying outrageous shit
Like that was so obviously like, you know, just clearly like in character
You know what? I mean like the whole time like they're just trying to one up each other who could say the most ridiculous thing
Which I think is a pretty interesting premise. Also. It was like short for a podcast. It wasn't a long
It was like 20 minutes to 30 minutes
But that's uh, that's a good bit for back then but probably not. Oh, yeah nowadays. Um, yeah
It was some edgy shit edgy humor in general attracts 14 year olds
I'm not that surprised. It would get an audience of that. But um, yeah
Yeah, yeah, I don't know if you're a new pcp fan listening to this explain how and why and
Yeah, I guess I'm kind of curious the ultimate question tell we want to hear your pcp stories
We want to hear
From the audience like what the fuck are you doing and why and why are you still here?
I do I do find that kind of thing really interesting. Uh, whenever somebody
Mentioned that they are a fan of mine or whatever. I'm always interested or how did you find me?
Yeah, it is interesting. I've been running in hiding for so long
There's probably at least one person out there who found me through the pcp, which is funny
Yeah, actually, I got uh, I got two comments, uh
On my stuff saying they found you through the pcp. That's uh, that's kind of weird
That is weird
Why would they go to your channel? Thanks for letting me know, I guess
I don't know why they posted comments on on on comments. I left
Uh, and they were like, uh, hey, I know you from the pcp and I I found out about cybershell from the pcp too
There's a huge contingent of quadruple pcp fans. You guys are like just oh, let's just do another episode
Whatever, we'll there's like a millions of people out there. They're the silent majority. They're the silent majority just clamoring
Uh, uh, silently, of course
I would love if it was like like some foreign country like japan or a weirder one like iran
Like you have a huge fan base over there, but they never can interact with you
We're uh, afghanistan
There are a pretty sizable number of like, uh, south american
Listeners, I feel I feel like that's I feel like those that continent is fairly well represented among the really big
There's a lot of youtube and and social media stuff in like brazil and things
I see lots of like come to brazil comments. I think it's like a meme like they just yeah
We'll leave a big population. It makes sense that there's like a lot of people there, but you're big in south america
I know at least four or five people from south america actually
Um, not even in the same country just different countries. Yeah different countries, but all from those
Sorts, how can I tell youtube? I only want americans watching my content. Nobody else. No other countries should be allowed to access it
You can block
Maybe we should build a wall in youtube
We should build a fire
That you have to like play brick breaker to get through if you're from a different country. Yeah. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, it shouldn't be impossible to get over the wall just like a slight inconvenience
Just just to let you know that we really don't want you got to do a mario
Jump like triple jump over the wall. You got to do a triple wall. You have to backwards long jump through the videos to get
Yeah, yeah, you got a blj like like speed clip
You gotta you you have to yeah, you have to um you have to build up speed for 12 hours to clip into a qpu
In order to get over to get through the wall
actually
And if you hit a if you press a at all you're uh your bands, you know if that's how vpns worked
I would actually play one
If it was mario 64
You know if a vpn was mario 64 i might also play
Just like too confusing so they just have to build video games like into them so people can like get excited about them
You jump into a painting. It's like a video
You jump into the youtube painting like yeah, it's like it organizes the internet as the castle from mario 64
Opening up microsoft word. I'm like typing is boring. I wish I could type by playing mario 64
Like like yeah, I'm pounding the the keyboard. They did make a they did make a mario's typing game for the pc whatever it was called
Um, yeah, tom even fucking around with linux like how would you feel about if instead of the current graphic user interface?
They just replaced everything with mario 64. Would that be an improvement? It'd be better than linux. That's for sure
Hot take um next voicemail, I guess uh is called
Uh, oh wait, I didn't fucking I didn't put it in the chat. Sorry. Here it is. It's called. No, it's called one upping
It's bad she heard did I just play this one?
Or are you that's a title?
Oh, i'm stupid. No, no, no that sorry. Okay. Let's play the one that's number 35 40 at the end
It's called some dumb shit one. Okay, three two one go
Okay, so I got some dumb shit to say nice. Um
I was reading this thing on the pcp
subreddit, I think
And it mentions a couple things about gib
And it also mentions gib's real dead name. Maybe I don't know if you've changed your name yet gib, but
Apparently gib are you actually like a professionally trained guitarist? I thought you did some kind of like
Writing job
I'm not a professional. I mean I had it said something about you being a professional guitarist
and how is gib a musician
And somehow trixie is the one who thinks she's
A musician when she's the worst
Okay, well first first off
I have not changed my name
Um because I have no issues with it. So I don't mind
Uh, so my name's the same. Um
I'm not professionally trained. I don't know I I I've played guitar at a few gigs before
Um, and they weren't for money. They were just sort of like like at various events
And I was like, hey, do you want to play guitar the thing? I'm like, yeah, all right
I've played with my my dad and his band a couple times
But I'm not like a professional musician by any metric
Uh, and I do like hobbyist stuff. I have a band camp with some
Some good stuff and some shit stuff. I should get rid of some of the shit stuff
I haven't posted any music in a while
I haven't it's it's mostly just sort of a like I have a guitar and occasionally I just
Pick it up and play for like a few hours and then it's fun. It's like it is like a hobbyist sort of thing
I don't really intend to make music because making music involves like
Putting multiple instruments together or thinking of lyrics
And I just don't have the patience for that like recording and and like mastering anything. I'm just like fuck it
I don't care. I enjoy playing the guitar. I don't enjoy recording their guitar
Also, uh, I would need like a manager for all that
Also Trixie isn't a musician. She's a rapper. There is a difference
No, I mean
It's a subcategory. I guess she doesn't play an instrument. I think you have to be a
To play an instrument. I guess your voice your voice is an instrument
I think the the the term people use as artists rather than musician just like you create
You create some music, but you don't literally create the music you you rap over beats that other people make
Artists works just as a catch-all. Yeah
sure
Not only should you not be allowed to rap over other people's beats
You shouldn't even be allowed to play an instrument unless you built it yourself. That's the only you shouldn't even be allowed to rap
I built a guitar once
You're allowed to play it then
Yeah, you you you you're safe
You're safe for now
Okay, the next one is called dumb shit, uh, two. It's the next one. Okay three two one go
Uh, so
Tom's discussion about laptop hardware shit
Might be the hardest I have ever zoned out
Of any person speaking
About any subject I'll be honest that was I kind of zoned out as well the yellow light discussion
Um, I don't okay. It wasn't like you got that deep in the technical stuff
You basically had one point which is that you know modular laptops where you can take shit out is good
Instead of have anything be soldered to like the motherboard and shit, which is a perfectly fine take. Yeah, I think that's fine
It wasn't something I had a lot of
The yellow light thing literally took hours and derailed the entire
Yellow light thing was funny. Wait wait. What the yellow light thing took hours and derailed the episode
It came up multiple times
Throughout the episode there was a cutaway. I remember where Trixie had like a whole like live action vlog thing for a little bit talking about
It was a whole
Wait, what are you talking about?
We're talking about the like like five years ago the yellow light episode of the pcp
Where jesse had a meltdown because you guys accuse his videos of having warm light instead of cold light
I thought oh, you're comparing. Oh, you're come. I thought you were saying that this happened last episode
He was saying it was the worst thing since the yellow light
Uh, oh
Oh, I get it. I get it. I guess the yellow light thing was good though. I don't know why yeah, that was a great meme everybody
Love that except you this day. Literally the most memorable thing that ever happened on the pcp
He was still bringing it up like five years later. He just brought it up right now
The best thing that ever happened on the pcp is also the worst thing that ever happened
Uh, that sounds about right. It's the second worst thing talking about the framework laptop. Was it the worst?
Five years from now people are gonna be like this was worse than that time
Tom had to got dastic to talk about laptop talk about a modular laptop
See, this is this is why this product is necessary because all you fucking smooth brains out there are fine with throwing away your laptop every two years
Fucking yeah, laptops have never appealed to me basically because of that. You know, they're like such like a specific thing
Like I mean they have their uses. I mean nothing against it
But like I just like a computer because it's like a real thing you can upgrade and stuff
I'm a bit of a computer tech guy myself
So I really would appreciate if all laptops were designed in a modular manner. Do you want to talk about it for like 20 minutes?
Yeah, let's get into it. Let's just just piss this guy off because I mean come on
Why would you not want that? I mean at least if he didn't like the conversation
He at least should admit that you were right
But I just want to say I watched a youtube video about it recently by uh, what's that guy's name?
Linus. Yeah, Linus tech tips. Yeah, we mentioned it last week. It's really good
I watched the entire video was pretty interesting great idea
Unfortunately, I don't think it's gonna catch on. That's the pessimistic side of myself. Yeah
I just I just want them to exist as like a niche
enthusiast brand for for smart people
Like just even existing is like what we have to take at this point
Not that it's the industry standard that like it exists at all in any capacity is what we're taking as a w
That's that's that's capitalism for you. Yeah, that's that's that's basically where we at
Take what I can get I'll take what I can get
Uh next voicemail is called. I think it's on dumb shit number three
Yes, dumb shit three three two one go
This one time I tried to mess with chris chan
This was in like 08 or 09
And this girl I was hanging out with I got her really into chris chan stuff
And she wanted to send chris a picture of her boobs
But chris said no, thank you
So really
My point is a story
Fuck people who think that everyone who
Goes to the kiwi farms to think about chris
Wants chris to kill themselves like
Some of us just want chris to just not be a shithead
That's kind of where I've always been
Um, I saw some people getting upset at crack for saying like
Destroy kiwi farms at four chan
But like the point is like yes
No one thinks every single human being on kiwi farms is like a psycho a log wants chris to die
But like the fact is if you post there you're posting alongside people like that and the whole point of the site is that
They will not face repercussions for being like that. I I completely understand
Why you would be interested in the sorts of things they talk about on kiwi farms for like non malicious reasons
It's a gossip brag, right? I mean it's the human nature people love to gossip about shit
But I doesn't mean I think it's like a good place
The the thing that bothered me most about it is what you brought up a while ago
Ben saying which is that they loved a posture like oh, we're not transphobic
We just allow any kind of free speech
But if you go in and use the proper pronouns people have a bigger meltdown and they get upset
It's they get upset being not transphobic is like
Theoretically allowed, but you will you will start a fight?
You will start a fight if you do it just without even trying like you know what I mean?
It's like so I don't know so to it's a little disingenuous
Also, it's not an anti trans site because there's nothing in the rules that says you have to be anti trans or whatever
So I don't know paper. It's not on paper. They have no ideology of any kind
They're completely free of all of all bias or political
The idea is whatsoever
But you mean of course
The most the most political
The most ideological people are the ones that claim that they have no
Ideology it's a kind of a bad place, but it's a little bit too useful if you want to find out information about people
Yeah
I mean, that's why I sometimes look at it
So I'm like if I I mean if I want to know what like what is the gossip about someone's like
Yeah, if you want to find out all the terrible things ben saint has done or has ever said in his life
That's a place to go
Uh
No, you just go to my youtube channel. You just go to my twitter feed for that
See them
Yeah, you need to cut them out of the equation and do all your embarrassing shit publicly loudly on your twitter
So it's like nobody even needs to like go find a thread on you. You can just be an asshole in public
Well, that was that was that was chris chan's strategy is it's like, you know four cent garbage is posting all these lies about me
So I will flood out the lies with with with the honest truth
I think I'm pretty sure that worked. I think it works perfectly
Well, it it's sort of work. I mean it didn't have exactly the consequences
I think I think though. I think everything had a happy ending in the whole chris chan story. I haven't looked into it recently
I don't know about that
Yeah, I haven't looked at it in a while, but last I checked everything was just pretty much fine
Next voicemail is called let me put it here in the chat it is called um
The I it's called I I meant parasailing
three two one go
Hang gliding is scary
Yeah, sarah palin more like parasailing
That one got me
um
Hang
What's the difference uh
Hang gliding is all glide on the air parasailing is where you sail on the ocean
Parasailing seems less dangerous because if you fell you would just fall into the water
Yeah, Paris seems less scary than hang-hiding. Hang-hiding is like you jump off a cliff. You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah
If you played uh sonic 2 3 game gear you would uh, oh, yeah
This little hang glider item. There's most of my hang gliding and knowledge comes from pilo wings from that game
Hang gliding is just like elytra in minecraft if you get some fireworks and you set them off you can keep going
I I don't think I don't think I'm interested in doing any like
Any like extreme
I mean, that's not even that extreme. I mean like skydiving type stuff
I don't think I'm interested in doing any of that shit ever again because I'm I'm very very aware of like the
Frailness of my human body and just how easily you're not interested in paranoid about it
You're not interested in uh potentially putting your life at risk and dying
I would really know
Because I could see Ben saying jumping out of a suicidal. Oh, yeah, I was gonna say if you have nothing to live for
I was like I was like maybe when I'm older all I go skydiving and I don't care if I'm fucking live
I have the most to live for living in some fucking base living is so fucking awesome
I could see Ben saying like jumping out of a yes. Yes. That's exactly right. Give that's why I'm fucking miserable and terrified
I'm miserable and terrified of the idea that this great life that I'm living being scared all the time will come to an end
unironically true
I'm so sad that eventually this life where I spend every day every waking moment
Just thinking about what it would be like if my head got squished under a train. I don't want that to end
I don't want that to go on. Yeah, please more of this, please
You're excited about the potential for life, but you know what a great, uh
Other of the reality
You know what a great, uh philosopher once said life is a cage and death is a key
I heard that I heard that once. Oh, I wonder who said that one
It was it was give give said that that one time
I know you didn't have to spill it out
It was you actually that should be on a fucking shirt
You said that thing that time that should be on a shirt. Was that on the yellow episode?
No, that was way later than that
No, I don't I don't I don't actually know when it was but I
I remember mage being there. Would you be allowed to put that on a shirt now?
Uh
There is
Well, somebody should somebody should put it on a fucking shirt
Uh next if you sell a shirt you have to mail us money
Viewers, uh, don't you won't get away with it. Uh, next one is a next voicemail is an image
thankfully
Uh, okay, I this is a comparison from the last I guess we were not sure who it was
I mean, I thought it was munchy, but I think we did settle that it was munchy
Well was Ben behind I kind of remember the original image. They didn't so we thought it looked like doesn't matter
But we weren't sure if it was super much. They're bad, but I think this image thoroughly says
Like I guess it's I guess it was munchy
Whoops
Okay, well, uh next one is called
Put it in the chat right there three five four five. It is called a suggestion
three two one go
Hello there PCP
I was wondering why you still have Nate as a member of the pro crastonators podcast
He does not do anything
You cannot extract surplus value from him. He is dead
literally
Release him into the great beyond and also it would make some people very angry
Well
I don't I don't know why I decided to eat this left over wait. What do they want to say?
Kill me start eating. Yeah kill me
Uh, I remember uh when Nate posted the gamer zone thing on twitter
I tweeted at him like, uh, oh you're starting your own podcast, but won't be on the pcp. I see how it is
Yeah, I tweet got a lot of likes
I uh, I'm gonna try and convince him to come on but just because I want to dab on what's his face
Who's always like no, Nate no watch. I want him to post that on a video that has native it
You could never recover from a humiliation of that would be sshc
How was I forget the acronym it's s like schv videos
Right. I remember it was complicated enough that I wasn't gonna bother remembering it
shcw video
He's he's he's doggedly continued his fucking crusade and I again
I don't think he's watching the videos
So you can get him you can just get his ass you just when Nate comes back
You just got to make sure you don't I know you're gonna want to put it in the thumbnail and title
But don't because then you can get his ass and make him say no Nate no watch on a Nate video
And once he does that it doesn't matter what he posts after that because it'll have lost all credibility
The battle will have been why I mean if it's no, how does he say no Nate no watch if he doesn't watch
How does he know there's no I know that's the point he's it's a flaw in his system
His whole ideology is crumbling. It's been working on sills. It's on predictions. He'll trip up
We could make that happen. Okay, Nate will never come back. So maybe he'll accidentally watch it and then he'll be like no
I
Yes, I I did um because Nate hadn't been on an episode in a while
I did take him his channel off the like sidebar
With the expectation that like I could just put it back any time
And he got like kind of mad at me. He was like ben why why you'd message me sort of upset and I was like, jeez, dude
I don't know. I'll put it back
But like whatever it is kind of funny that he would care at all because yeah, I
Think a year I generally think he would care because like he has even at that point
He hadn't been on in like a year and it's just been even longer since
I will just agree with what you said ages ago ben which is why I agree to do game or so
And why I'm going to do this which is that doing a podcast is like a couple hours out of the week
It's not that much time to do. It's truly. It's truly a low commit. I don't understand why so many people seem to think it's like
I mean, Nate has the time clearly. He's doing another podcast. So
That's the funny part. It can't be the time thing. It's just kind of funny. He just doesn't love us anymore
Which really hurts. It hurts. It hurts, Nate
Well, I'm just um, I'm waiting until uh, I'm waiting until I get invited to the gamer zone because I mean I'm
I'm kind of the gamer's tavern
The gamers tavern is the zone is in the zone
Gamers tavern is one such zone. I was pushing we should just call the podcast gamers tavern
We should just steal that from you
That's funny. Yeah, I I made that suggestion in the comments, uh somewhere
I don't I don't understand the mindset of people that oh, let's say like
Sometimes people will say like once she's not for for instance, they'll say yeah, once she's not on the pzp anymore
He's gone on to do bigger and better things and like
I like it's it's fair to say like, okay
Maybe he is doing bigger and better things that might be true
But like the sort of implication that like he he he or or anyone you had to stop doing
You had to stop doing this podcast in order to do something else instead
As though it is not perfectly feasible to slot a three hour podcast into your weekly schedule somewhere
It's not usually also pursuing can do more than one podcast. Look at me for example. I'm on both of them
You're a slut. You're a podcast
You also don't have to uh, you don't have to be on every week either if you're busy on that time
You can just miss out
Yeah, that was the thing like if they just didn't want to be on every episode because that was the thing
He was on every episode for like a very long time. So like I kind of get that if you want to take a break
I mean he can do whatever he wants doesn't have to be on the show
If he doesn't want to be but I don't understand why he does he feel like he can't be on it
It's just I'm confused why people
It's it's it's really not all or nothing. It really doesn't have to be an all or nothing proposition
That's what I was thinking like just do it once a month if you aren't feeling it. It's fine or or not
I mean whatever you don't want to be in the show. That's fine. Yeah, that's what I was saying
I don't want to like bully like if he doesn't want to do it doesn't have to do it. It's just like kind of funny to me
it's
It's funny that it's it's just funny that it seems like it's it's such a
Never be on the show again
but also
Never say anything about why ever right like to like take a look what seems to be like a really hard line stance and then never
Refer to it. Yeah. Yeah. If I didn't know any better. It sounds almost like a jaunt run thing
I genuinely don't understand why he cared that I like took his his button off the sidebar
Well, I'm sorry. I didn't even notice it and did you message him saying I'm doing this
No, yeah, I I don't know how he noticed. Honestly. Yeah, it's such a small thing
I I was just like
If if you were on the show, I would just I could just put it back. I don't I am surprised that he noticed actually
um
anyway
Next one is called
to
Angry Nate head. Oh, this is to that guy
Who was mad at us for being for being?
Mean to his boy
Three two one go
So in response to that one guy who was so pissed at you guys for talking Nate just give him one of these
Click here to skip the bad
Hmm
Uh, maybe he means a timestamp
I
I take offense to this that he thinks you should even go to the trouble of time stamping any of this discussion
Is that what he's saying? I'm not sure. I don't know sure
Dev alchemist, I'm a little I'm a little confused about what you're suggesting. I'm sorry
But I think you should uh timestamp a timestamp the voicemail probably what he's saying
I think is
To the guy who got mad about the Nate
of uh
bullying
We should say hey guy
Here's a timestamp for when you can skip us talking about Nate
But I don't think but that's
I don't know if that would solve the problem. I uh, I don't think that's the problem
I don't think the problem was that he heard about it
I think he was indignant on Nate's behalf that how dare people
Discuss him on this podcast
Which he could easily come on and defend himself at any point if he wanted to that's what I'm saying
Well, he doesn't even have like not only then for permission. He can just literally just establish when we tried to remove him from the
podcast
Association he adamantly refused the thing. So like he's part of this what be brought by his own volition
If he ever wanted to say anything about the pcp, he has the perfect platform here on the show
Right like if he wanted to leave the pcp, he literally could but he doesn't want to
Yeah, but also doesn't ever want to be on
I don't get it
I generally don't understand but I just want the credit without putting in the work
I mean what what credit he's getting with such accolades. He's happy being the pcp accountant. I'm getting his small cut every month
He still does the he still does the the paypal
paperwork the paypal per work
This is still ironically his business
Yeah
Oh, yeah, I guess in a way he's your boss
Yeah, legally he worked for us legally. It's his it's his enterprise and we're all getting non-employee compensation
For our cuts at the work viewers ignore what ben says because he's definitely works for his brother
That's a sick burn. I said it's non-employee non-employee compensation. You're a contractor
You got no benefits. I have no benefits
I'm being exploited
Next next voicemail is called one cool dud
three two one go
I've been meaning to mention for a while now
That ben's uwu voice is just like top tier
Like not even joking it genuinely
Makes me feel so happy
and squishy
Whenever you do it
I was wondering if you could possibly use it to say
Uh, not so fast mister. I have a master's degree
That would be extremely choice
Um
Yeah, well, thank you
Um, let me see. What is my uh, I'll try I'll try to do it naturally
Um, I don't know if you do this sounds like uh, not so fast. Mr. I have a master's degree
Well, is that is that?
I think that's not quite it. I think it's just sort of the the high-pitched squeaky thing you do sometimes
When you say thank you and thank you
I have a master's degree. Wait, weren't you weren't you like doing an uwu voice with munchie like a while ago?
And you just kept doing it
I remember kezi talking about that like you would not stop doing the uwu voice and she got really upset or they got really upset
Whoops, I said it again. I fucking misgendered them some somebody somebody. Um
somebody uh, honestly like
When i'm trying to think of my uwu voice like i'm not exactly sure what voice it is like
I would need to hear like a clip and be like that voice when you do that
And then I could be like oh, I can do that you can't do it now because you're too self-conscious about trying to do it
You know what I mean? Now i'm i'm overthinking it. I'm overthinking it. I'm like, wait, like how high do I have to go?
How nasally I think you're just contributing. It's just like replacing all the vowels with w's or however
However, you do it you do it you do it. However, you
I don't know. I think you're you're contributing to this person's uh, joe material
Charge the crystal i'm charging their crystal
You're definitely helping charge that crystal
Next oh wait, uh, don't not this latest one do the one that's three five four eight
This one is george the bird
three two one go
Okay, so we're gonna hotel on the beach
And we have this little seagull
Who is either hurt
Or just a dumb baby and he cannot fly and he's been offended. I've named him george
Um, he doesn't like berries. He doesn't like crackers
But uh, I stole a piece of chilean sea bass that would have gone on a $40 plate from the restaurant
we have
and he likes that so
Seagulls are bougie little shits is my point. I don't know george is a cool guy though
I almost almost I almost just said
Wait seagulls eat fish
And I was like, what else do I think they that would have been embarrassing
All right, it's a good thing. You didn't say I guess they're just scavengers. I guess yeah, I guess they just eat anything
I thought they eat hot dogs. I thought they oh, yeah, like I think of them
Yeah, like trash, but like yeah, of course they eat meat
Like they live at the sea of course they eat fish fish are basically sea trash, so
Fuck fish, you know
Who needs it's like it's like thinking of like what pigeons actually eat if not like bread and and chips
Nobody knows
Yeah, before humans invented garbage
Uh, they didn't pigeons only exist because we invented them to eat our garbage
Because we needed something to clean up after us
And then we needed them to poop on our heads. Yeah, we definitely needed that
We we designed them specifically for all these purposes
Uh next voicemail is called breaking news
three two one go
The Taliban has assumed control of Afghanistan like a month after parking with a tour of the troops, so
That's pretty cool
Yeah
Did you see that picture of the Taliban recreating the Iwo Jima image with cat with captured american like
Uniforms and shit. It was epic
Uh, I saw a picture of a guy posing in front of a bunch of guns that they had gotten from like an abandoned american base
Just another one of those silly Taliban pranks. They're known for
one of their many gaffes and japes and
Uh, it's just classic
Uh, yeah
So, you know, that's cool
I think the Taliban's good, right? We like them. Yeah, that's great
Uh, I think they're the good guys. I can't remember. I remember watching a fake sound. I fucking uh Rambo bluey where they were uh pretty cool
The brave muhajine jine fighters or whatever
The Taliban is uh
Taliban is when you know, I don't know if those are related to each other or not
The Taliban is when you get banned from a forum, right?
Oh, yeah, you get tallyed. No, it's when it's when it's when uh
You you're banned from dating tally in mass effect. No a fate worse than death
Therefore they suck
Well, shit you piss off the Koreans you get tally band
I was I was on the tally band side, but now I have to reconsider
Yeah, I was on their side until I heard their thoughts on the specific mass effect romance and now I'm against them
This makes me reconsider everything I used to think about them
I mean if you fuck up the loyalty mention of mass effect you can't get out banned from for people
That's true. That's also killed
Everybody can die in that game. It's pretty fun. Yeah, you get the watching every single every single person die on the suicide mission
It's actually like hilarious. I don't know why this is like it's like every single thing that can go wrong goes wrong
Like the worst possible way
There's tally band and then there's weird al qaeda
That's a good one. That's solid solid work
Uh, thanks
Thank you
Next voicemail is called
A simple request and this is sent in by
Fattest nuts at hotmail.com
Son of a mention that I believe he means peanuts
I hope delicious keto too. Uh, three two one go
I'm gonna need you to do me a favor go to the gift tab of discord and search
Relax and take notes. I'm gonna give you a few seconds
Okay, so who's getting the best head
Oh, and also a hashtag lynch tommy j. Nobody loves him his voice sounds fucking awful. Oh
Come on the chipmunks
Um
Oh
I don't even know what the chipmunks names are
Alvin simon and theodore right theodore's the green one
Theodore is is like is like in nirvana right now
Yeah, it's the it's definitely theodore's eyes are closed. He's in like he's in like a zone theodore
Alvin is pogging alvin is just straight up
That's just a tuesday for alvin. This is a pog moment
He it's poggers, but he's he but he's still like aware. He's just like yeah, this is pretty cool. He's like consciously reacting
Simon seems to be in discomfort. Yeah, he's like scrunching his eyes
God damn it
That reminds me of that uh video where uh, everyone was
Chastising tom for using the gift thing on twitter. Oh, yeah, tom oliver cringe
The boomer
You you did
I always thought using gift tab was kind of cringe, but then I when I was
Watched that it made me think about can I put it into words? Why and then I was like I kind of can't honestly
So I guess you're uh, you're right
I think you won but you won the legal battle, but you lost in the court of public. I don't know the comments seem pretty
Heavily in my favor. I've I've grown into into enjoying the gift button
Recreationally not just as a meme like haha. I'm using the gift button. Just like
Uh, oh, there's a
I don't have like a folder of these sorts of things and I just want to
Show an image. There's probably a weirdo gift of whatever people are talking about right now
I just find it
I really like I think it's really cool that like if you type in endless war rfck. There is a there are lots of like
Endless war memes that's that show up in the gift tab
Because it just searches gifts. It's not like I yeah once I realized that it's not like a pre picked out boomer approved
List of memes you're allowed to share. It's just like it literally is just like it searches for gifts
Like I can't really be that upset of it then
That was which was the case I was making in the video. I'm glad I've been right retroactively justified and proven correct
Everybody will like uh the gift button sooner or later because everyone becomes a boomer eventually
Exactly. We're just aging into him just ahead of the curve. I think that
I think that
I think that using a gift as a reaction
I mean you can do it once in a while, but I think if you do it all the time
It's a little bit like it's a little bit like low effort
You do it all the time then sure but like I mean there's something inherently wrong with using as gift as a reply
Which is again a reason why I was inherently opposed to the gift button, but I was like well inherently wrong
But I think really wrong. I think it's easy to overdo it
I think it's easy to overdo it like like I typed in cyber show and I get this
Yeah, that's a clip from one of my videos
You can like do a cycle animation where you make Sonic do all his little do all the different animations
He can do in the game and it looks funny. It looks funny
Funny and that was uh back in the early days of cyber show
The early back in the LP days
Uh
I um
Yeah, I can't I should we do it with a whole podcast. It's just boomers bitching about the you know
Best boomers bitching about being old. Yeah two two bad two boomers bitching about
Can we just complain about tick tock and how I hate it?
I do hate tick tock. I can I I don't even want to hate tick
I don't even want to be that guy who's old and hates tick tock, but it's a very little video
Come on. You don't even give me a choice. What blows my mind is like I just I realized literally yesterday
That is like, oh, I need to use tick tock. You know, I hate it. Um, wait, why my because uh
The reach there is ridiculous. You're ignoring a separate youtube. It's not just like a couple zoomies on there. It's a huge ecosystem
Let me explain this to you my my friend my friend. Okay. She started a tick tock
yesterday
And uploaded a video of her a couple videos and like three parts of her unboxing this like uh my hero academia figure in
15 hours her video's got 400,000 views. She gained 2,000 followers and got 50,000 likes
This is where people are getting famous now
But where's the money I'm already a later. No, we're already too late. We're already stuck on youtube
I should do the algorithm. Um, but yeah, I mean it's not though because she just made her account like two days ago
And it's all and like got 2,000 followers right off the bat. Like but that's the same
Yeah
I don't what what could you put on there?
though the like anything
Anything it has a separate like me. I guess if there's anything then there's no no right probably
Have you uh, have any of you seen the youtube shorts thing?
Oh, yeah, the only shorts I watch are yours honestly
I haven't watched mine. Oh, do you do you post? Yeah, you want you post the little tips and tricks
Little tips and yeah, that's what I've been um, I've actually been experimenting with the youtube shorts thing because um
A fellow lp or that I know named karma jolt
He was doing the the shorts like uh sometime last year
And uh, he just exploded in popularity all of a sudden
Like he went from 700 subscribers to 20,000 subscribers in just a few months
YouTube was like pushing shorts really hard like it has like a separate virality thing like on the front page
There's like a tab for shorts and like if you're not making shorts, you're not even playing that part of the game
You know what I mean? You're missing
It sucks to be missing on I know just when you do youtube shorts, uh, the algorithm will push your video much more aggressively
Regardless of what size your channel is because they want to kill tick
Which is why they're pushing. I mean the nice thing is that like if you start using youtube shorts
You might as well just post them on tiktok. It's exactly right. That's sort of what I was like
I was like, I just don't really see them on my channel and then I was like
I'm just lazy but like I see I see in theory why they're doing it
It doesn't make sense like it is objectively algorithmically smart to be fucking around with those shorts. Yes
I don't I don't like engaging in social media that I don't
Actively watch and engage with myself. Yeah, I don't post that's the problem is that every time I've tried to like
Okay, let's see what this tiktok thing is about
I just hate it like I just
It doesn't connect with me at all because like I like sitting down and watching a youtube video that has like some feet on its bones
tiktok is just like
30 seconds of like bite size by design
It's it's like designed for like I don't even want to get too boomery about it
But like it's like we've been breeding attention spans smaller and smaller and we've basically gotten about as small as we can go
Or like 30 15 to 30 second videos are like the what people are aiming for you know
I mean that used to be like abnormal on youtube like I have a meme channel
I'll post 15 30 second videos on but not like that's not a real youtube video, you know
Yeah, I think it just because I like I'm so like focused on like the youtube format in terms of like if I was going to make
Video content. That's what I want to do that moving over to that
Like I don't even like know how it changed
My content to suit it. I wouldn't even know what to make that's really kind of the thing that why I haven't ever messed around with shorts either
It's like what can I
do
Right, you need a different style of content. You can't just yeah
Can't just go over with any type of content like if you have no idea what you're doing
Or why you're doing it. It's going to suffer
Compared to people who have like good ideas
Or passion behind like oh, I love tiktok and I love doing this stuff and they're gonna just
They're gonna have an audience that enjoys tiktok content and if you're right the kids will just be in tiktok audience
Yeah, you'll you'll be stuck doing those things. I mean, I guess you could do a short little like animation
Because I do like 3d model stuff feel a little short animation. Yeah, well that would be good for animation for sure
At least there's that you could have a little looping thing
I just try to I think of the stuff you already have would be really good
Actually, I try to think of the limitations of the the format and find some way to make it interesting to me and the viewers
So I um right that's I mean that's the best way to look at it
You know art comes from adversity like it's not like having a shorter amount of time
Doesn't necessarily mean you have to make worse videos. You just have to think harder
But I don't know I just have to change the what you're doing and I'm not sure
Exactly, right, but I totally get your point like I don't use tiktok. I'm not tuned into the things that go viral on tiktok
So like it's just gonna I'm gonna be at a disadvantage in either way
You know what I mean? I don't like start using it and I don't know if I want to go down that
Something about the way the site is like like so focused on like lip syncing is like abhorrent to me
I just hate everything about it. Basically. I think it's grown to be more because I just know the stats and like
It has more than twitter already
Right or downloads and all that. It's massive gargantuan ecosystem
And that's why I was like, yeah, it doesn't really make sense to completely ignore it
But I don't know. I'm just too lazy to make a tiktok
I think the short thing is uh good for like scripted content because normally when you script something
It takes a long time if you're doing like a long
Uh video and it takes forever to put out the video
But when you're just doing 30 seconds to a minute, right?
It allows you to script stuff and put videos out at a faster pace
Right and you're for your little series of like game tips and tricks and like cheats
Like I feel like a good like people want the videos to be short for those kinds of videos
You know what I mean? Like the shortness sort of works in its favor. You know what I mean?
Yeah, it just seems like the perfect uh combination
I
On the completely opposite side of like oh intentions getting shorter and shorter
Um, Noah called will jevaze. Oh, yeah, his resident evil video. Did you watch his resident?
I watched the seven hour resident evil video. I'm very close to the end
I'm on resident evil seven. He's seven hours. Yeah, it's he he's his videos are really good
They're often very very long very thorough very in-depth like great analysis
Uh, that's witty and not like stupid. Yeah, he doesn't get bogged down
It doesn't it's like a seven hour video that is packed full
With like literally he literally could have just he could have just like divided it up and be like here's my video on
Resident Evil 1 here's my video resident evil 2 like people wouldn't have even thought it was weird
But like it's just like he literally just chose to do it all in one video because you know, why not?
I can't I can't imagine
Scripting out a seven hour video that would take yeah, that would take months. The thing is like somebody will hear how many pages that is
He um, like you'll hear him like read stuff and somebody will hear him like make a little mistake or something in the video
And it's like whatever and pardon me was like, oh, that's kind of like unprofessional in a weird way
But then I was like, you know what at the end of the day
It was like literally who gives a fuck if I can hear him do a mouse click it doesn't
Know it's always been like that
He's always just like he just leaves his like miss his like miss words and like he'll stumble and he'll just leave it
It's just funny because like I would never do that to me
I would be like, oh god, I gotta re-record that, you know, but it's like at the end of the day
He made me realize like I don't even need to do that
You know what I mean? Like he doesn't care and like the end the audience doesn't care and I don't so yeah, it doesn't matter
Yeah, I had the same realization
Well, now there's no reason to you know, try to make videos
I sure ever but like there's no reason to overly get obsessed with your presentation to the point where it's like a problem
You know what I mean? Like I appreciate that sort of minimalistic
I would I would rather him make twice as many videos than half as many and I actually really appreciate all the little verbal
That his shit's not that flashy like his video like his page run credit to him
Just standing in front of the camera reading off a list, you know, I mean it's so long
It's him say for like 15 minutes just reading names
It's a half an hour at the end of the video
I agree with you like I who sits through that who doesn't just immediately turn the video off as soon as they get to that part
Like it's gotten to the point that I I can't like I understand the I totally get why he does that
He said in his thing. I'm if you give me a certain amount of money, I'll little read your name off
But like it's it's become cumbersome. It's become so long and almost
Unlike counterproductive. I don't know. I like that aspect. It's it doesn't hurt the video because you can just turn it off
Exactly. It's not like oh, he better stop doing that. Like I don't care in that for a second. It's just it's a very long at this point
It's not a very silent. It's not sometimes I'll hear like hear my friends names. The reason I brought him up though
um was
As a contrast to the tiktok stuff and it shows right because he's getting more
attention than he used to have like he was a lot smaller and
Niche and people are discovering his stuff and like it's so good and there's so much of it
That it's you're absolutely right. Give that like it's not just short videos. It gives me like hope that like
Like long form good stuff is not like going out of there's there's definitely a split here
There's a split here the the the shame a seven hour pokemon analysis did gangbusters. It's got like a million and a half views
I'm sure it's made like I'm sure it's made like $10,000
Becoming so long is like it becomes like the point of I have noticed that
A lot of uh longer form videos are getting popular
Which is why I thought well, what if I if I tried doing both of those
You know the short videos and a couple of long videos every I think the reason that they're both getting really successful
Is that like the short videos like shorts are just like people like actively watching a little bite-sized things
And then the long videos are like, oh, I gotta do something
I'll put this over to a new tab
And I'll just like do whatever I need to do play my game
Watch do my homework whatever while it's playing in the background
I would love if there was like an analytic to show how much of like like
Watch time is like actually looking at the video versus playing in the background because I guarantee you videos like that is like 90
We were talking about that like yes, so many people use youtube as like youtube videos as like podcasts
You know what I mean?
Either on a separate monitor or on a separate tab so they can't even literally can't even see it at all
Right, I mean like so and you're right
So if you could see this that's an image on the screen and then they have to tab over to check you have to look at the screen
You can't be this is a visual podcast now
But that's probably why it would be better to
Focus on the scripting more than everything else right that is honestly the most important part. Yeah
It's it's kind of weird that it is like if you if you could look at the stats
It would be some
Dishearteningly huge number like 50% of the people who watch your videos don't actually physically watch your videos
But like yeah, why does he care? He doesn't even like I mean sometimes he'll show relevant games
No, I was saying that's like smart for Noah Gervais to like his he does right
He doesn't have flash yet any he basically has relevant but not like super duper relevant videos of what's going on
You know, which is the smart way to do it honestly
But I like to you know people guys like me and you guys like Nate, you know
Get so obsessed with the visual editing in the visual language of it all which is like just you know
Not that it doesn't matter, but it's not as matter
It matters more for certain kinds of videos. You're right. It does depend a lot on the specific kind of video essays
Yeah, I feel like it mostly is about the audio
and
I mean if you're making like a 15 to 20 minute like dense video
You definitely want good
I think most people are probably or a good amount of people are going to watch that because it's short enough to like
I'm like
I know like when I was like Trixie all the time with like make food and then go downstairs and watch a YouTube video
Like actively engage with it while eating then be done and move on to whatever else they do
So like I'm sure like people find little chunks of time in their day to like watch a dense video like that
But I think if you're going for like an hour plus like
Just do the bare minimum for visuals. Yeah
Don't get too bogged down on every single like thing on screen being perfectly relevant to the sentence
You're saying especially for hour long because it takes so long to do good video visual editing on hour plus long videos
So it might take you to do it, but it's hard take years if you're going to do something seven hours long
Imagine working on one video for a couple of years
It's interesting like you can imagine trick people into thinking you have decent editing when you actually don't if you just cut
With like every like yeah, do it on the rhythm do it like so yeah
They're constantly seeing new things like just put be putting in new fucking images or cutting to things
As long as you cut with the speech rhythm it feels like there's actual editing even though you're just I had to realize that
Keep their neurons fired. I try not to be too cynical about it
But I was like, you know a lot of people watching videos are just like dumb sheep and they just want things to be flashing in front of their eyes
So don't let them get bored. You can't let them get bored
But like 100 it really is true though. Honestly like when you're thinking as an entertainer you really have to be like
Okay, don't you can't give them any debate or got to keep them visually interested or if not visually then you know
It depends on the kind of video
I guess we said that a few times one thing that really
annoys me a rubs me it makes me click off immediately is if there's like
You know a video about some subject or whatever and it starts with like an editing
Slash voiceover like comedy bit that doesn't land. I'm like, okay
Humor is definitely a mixed bag where it's like
If you're being funny, it just wasn't it was like it felt like a
If you're gonna lead with a joke it better not be annoying. That's why it became such a meme like so many bad reviewers
Like like jokes that are just they have the sound and sense and like
structure of like what a joke is but
I don't feel like they found it funny when they wrote it or decided to do it and they're like
Oh, we need to put in a joke here because when I watch reviews they put in for a joke time for a wacky edit
Something I really
Genuinely appreciated about like know what your face is that he doesn't feel the need to needlessly insert jokes
I'll have like one joke an hour, but it'll actually be a funny joke. You know what I mean?
Yeah, probably because he actually thought the joke was good and not because it
Right. Yeah, he doesn't he doesn't just put them in because he wants and they help him if he thinks if something comes up
It's not like you have to rid them
You know jokes are pretty difficult to do you can't just write something and it's good
You have to kind of workshop it and polish it and just doing one joke can take a very large amount of time
Right and it's sort of mean to say but some people just aren't fucking funny and if you're not funny
That's fine. Just don't try to be funny. Just make your video and don't
Be unfunny in it. I have
I remember many times for my own like hypocrite videos where I
Was writing and I'm like I gotta put some joke in there and I did just put it in there
And I didn't find it funny at the time. I still don't that and I'm like, oh this sucks
Oh, I'm such a fucking loser for doing that
Well, I think most of your jokes were pretty good if I remember people don't know though. Yeah, sometimes
it's it's fine and people don't recognize that because like
comedy
Senses of humor differ some people find everything funny
Some people have very strict like it needs to be like very funny for me to laugh
Doing good comedy is hard
It's it's different than when you're just doing a straight analysis where you can just
Write stuff and you don't have to think too hard about everything you're writing
But when you write a joke, you have to write one line and you really have to spend a lot of time on it
Just going over it and thinking, you know, is this really funny?
Maybe you have to tell it to someone and see if they react to it
You know, like one line takes forever
With a you know, with a joke or one like skit or one sketch you're gonna do
You gotta get your tight five. It's easy to like just pat out like an analytical video
It's way harder to like pat out just insert five minutes of like jokes, you know
I mean like I guess you can't do it, but it's harder for them to be good
It's harder for them to be good, you know, you can't pat out the comedy and have it still be funny
Right, but some people really feel like they need it like they they've watched they grew up watching videos of a certain way
You know like angry video game nerd nostalgia critic
They just they just in their mind a youtube video has of guy and standing in front of a camera making bad jokes
Like that's just like what it is in their mind's eye. They can't envision it without that
Which is not you gotta be thinking
The more you think about what you're doing the better it'll probably be probably
Nah
It is kind of funny that youtube and I don't know tick talking to social media in general
Does seem to want to like prioritize like don't be like thinking about your content
Just be filming everything just be pumping out vlogs, you know
You don't need to think about your content. You just need to make it as fast as you can
Right. Yeah, that's what works best for that because they make the most money. I do dislike that though
I I I prefer thoughtful content
I mean does it does it make
I guess it
Does it make more money if you're like a family
Channel and you can be putting out videos daily that get like
Does it mean more ads does the shorter less
Most people aren't watching youtube with an ad blocker
So if there's like a billion bad videos and you're looking for something to watch you have to click through 10 videos
That's 10 ads youtube gets to make instead of you landing on right video and that's sort of
That's sort of why youtube is like doing this thing where it's favoring really long content
Which can have tons and tons of ads shoved in or just lots of short content that will chain into each other
You know what I mean and be like, uh, well auto plays on by default. I think they keep on so yeah
They just love to have shit auto play from one video to the next to the next
Well, here's an idea. What if you just made a really long video and then you cut it up into a bunch of short videos
And you just upload everything
what
Couldn't if you guys were smart
You would be recording one podcast like this a month and then breaking up another 10 minute chunks, which are we should 10 ads
We should cut this podcast up into like like youtube short length
300 different youtube short seconds, then you're really going to be playing the algorithm
Do you think of all the ads?
Think of all the content
Oh my god
You should be ideally aiming for a one-to-one is wasted content
Exactly you should be aiming for a one-to-one ad to content ratio
You're spending half your time watching ads and half your time actually getting around to watch the content
It's dystopian
Um, just uh, just just
But it's like and then we can release a new tick tock size clip of the podcast like every fucking
Five minutes for like the next week and the algorithm will be like, oh, they're all everyone is watching so many of these videos
Like the algorithms exploding
It is stupid shit like that where it's like that would be an increase in like views to the channel
Technically probably just because of how many videos you'd be pumping out. So the algorithm would like be looking at your channel
Looks like it's doing good right now. The terrible thing is that that might actually work
Yeah, the sad part is it would work better than anything. Obviously to the degree. We're saying which was ridiculous like
301 minute shorts would be kind of clog people's feet up
But like in general just taking content and just shopping it up and cramming in as many ads
It is a smart thing to do frame
Yeah, one frame videos at a time like you can't even get any shorter than upload them every every four nanoseconds
I have a weird respect for these people who can just churn out content like dsp the dark side fill
How many videos do you have now dsp gaming has 59
Thousand videos on his youtube account 59. What the thousand? It's because every single day. He's doing this. He's upload
He's um, he's putting out segmented live streams like multiple parts every single day
How many minutes does he do like
I went to the channel uh one time and I saw that he does like five six ten videos a day or something like that
Yeah, he'll like stream on twitch or something. I can't remember and then he'll split them all up into one hour long videos
So he'll usually stream like six eight hours a day. So that's like six eight videos a day for like 10 plus years
So if you're a phil fan, you'll be you'll be happy for the rest of your life. You'll never
That is impressive. I'm right. That's what I mean. Like he's really gaming the system
I guess his video is only get between like 200 to 900 views, but he puts out so fucking many every single fucking day
I like big number. That's I like I I'm a fan now
He you can't help but respect it a little bit the the sheer grind of this man
He can't be as dumb as he looks
He seems to know what he's doing something right
Man, I sure do hate what he does
But I just respect the hell that he just keeps doing his content
But I respect to the degree to which he churns it out in a mechanical way
Dedication is something so dumb. I'm a I've come around and become a big a big fan. I'm a big phil guy now
Hmm
Wow, that was a long fucking tangent
To go on. I was a tangent upon tangents. It was something something related to a voicemail
But I can't even remember we've got we've got exactly one voicemail left. Oh, good. We did it. I know
Wait, unless wait, maybe there's an extra one. No
I can't believe you accept voicemails like like you refresh the page as we're doing the episode until we finish
Until we finish recording you can sneak them in at the last second. Don't tell them that
Yeah, don't tell them that it's too late.
Next week, we're going to get like 50 voicemails in the last 20 minutes
Wait until you guys are doing the episode and then just like non-stop start cranking out voicemails
Like you get your friends to like putting out like three or four a minute
So you just like it's like you can't finish them. There's too many coming in at once
That'd be a great prank Ben is giving everyone tips on how to harass
To pcp with voicemails. Yeah, because I'm not a coward
Ben takes pleasure in making the rest of us suffer through all of these give them a road map
A little not only do you give them tips, but you actively are like I will never screen any calls
You can put anything you want in these calls anything
That's including that's my that's my gig. That's my that's my gig
Uh, anyway, let's play this last one. It's called the human comedy perpetuates itself
three two one go
By 2050
The the new pcp pcp next generation will be composed of
May and neaton house, baby
Uh, a fully artificial intelligence version of azumi
Tom because tom will never die
Uh cyber shell and monkey jones
That's gonna be the next generation
That's quite a lineup. It's like star trek the next generation, but I
I think I would go with sigh instead of monkey jones
Did I mention that I asked sigh if he wanted to guess and he just straight up was like no no
Oh now now he's too good for the pcp. Yeah, now. He suddenly is too good
You would have done it five years ago when it was yeah, you know when it was relevant it mattered at all
Give it now that it's useless and there's no point suddenly. You won't do it
What's that about just a tricksy fan boy like and so obviously you wouldn't want to be on the show now, right?
uh
sigh was also a monkey friend, I think to a degree they they fell out
Yeah, that sounds about but they they liked each other at the time
Right. I don't know if it seemed always a bit weird to me like monkey would just make fun of sigh
I would be like yeah
When you're the butt of the joke, that's just how monkey acts towards everyone. I guess only we can have them on the podcast
He's performatively cruel just and then like makes a joke out of it. I guess that's just his thing
uh
We he wouldn't he didn't want to talk about tricksy and like I don't want to just have him on just for no reason
It wouldn't be no reason. It would be assembling the next generation of avengers to assemble
I I like that. It's just it's just tom. It's just cyborg tom
And like ai Izumi
That exists
Ai Izumi did monkey refuse to talk about trick me and Ethan Ralph's child. Did they say
Yeah, Ethan and Ethan and may his child is the the front man
He didn't exactly he just I asked him if he wanted to come on and talk about tricksy on the show
And he just said I don't want to talk about her. That's very different from do you want to be on the show at all?
Well, yeah, no, I asked him specifically for that reason. Okay. Well, that's a different
Okay. Yeah, I that that's what I said. Okay. That's what they said. I have not changed my story
Um, that's a pretty uh pretty unusual reaction coming from him
Yeah, I was surprised. I don't know if the issue was um, but uh, uh, uh, uh, anyway
dead dead podcast, uh, new generation
Ethan and Ralph's fucking cursed. Ethan and May's cursed, baby. Uh,
Who else? I don't know. Whatever. Yeah, mum key jams. Why not?
Uh, I'm disappointed that I was Nate will finally come back to to take take the reins after the new generation
Our assembles after the rest of us are all dust except tom. Obviously
Um, I'm disappointed. I wasn't mentioned in that
Oh, you're oh, you're getting no, you're getting the ax along with the rest of us
Well, that's uh, then you can just ask me a question
You will not be spared in the revolution my friend
Okay, 360 no scope revolution
Exactly, I uh, I guess that's it. That's all the voicemails. Uh, what what do we do and the show
And the podcast and the podcast is the last episode. Chill the things
patreon.com slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes
One of these days we will get a whole bunch of those bonus episodes. Oh, yeah
Let's chill for love web again. Just put it at the top of the description. Oh, yeah
Go check out love web shadow
YouTube
If you haven't seen it yet, okay. Yeah, if you are like animation love web
If you're a pcp fan and you like somehow have not seen love web
What the fuck you're basically missing out on like some of the only new real
It's it's got ben's voice and it's got munchies. Oh, it's so good. You should watch it if you haven't watched it
What the fuck is your problem like seriously like you're seriously watching pcp in 2021
But you're not gonna like listen to us tell you to watch another thing. What is the point?
You piece of shit wasted wasted four hours of your life listening to our twaddle
And and you you could have been spending that you could have watched our love web
The problem is you have to you have to watch love web in its own tab this you can just put another tab
Yeah, that one isn't one of the videos you're talking about earlier. That's actually worth watching with your eyeballs
You're making a bold assumption that if somebody sat through all four four hours of this
Oh, I mean if they're listening to this point odds are
I'd say this is some how a dead podcast yet you the listener are listening to it right now
I think most people they just uh, most people they just click off after the voicemails start
No, most people those people skip directly to the voicemails. The voice mails are the best for the show
One person in the comments asked me. Can we just get a time stamp for the voicemails?
I just want to listen to the voicemails and I was like
What a Chad. What an absolute Chad. I could not believe it. That is uh, that's a sigma male move
Yeah, absolutely. I only want to listen to the part of the show that I'm on my voicemails
It might be it might be that maybe they maybe they're avoid if you're a voicemailer. I understand why you would prefer that segment
Uh, is sigma from megaman x a sigma male?
Yeah
I think so
He's he's alpha. He's the boss. I think wait. No, well, he's a renegade. So
Ah, jeez
patreon.com slash the procrastinators for the bonus episodes and the minecraft server
Yeah, I'm still another heckles for shackles. Yeah, let's do one this week
I'm still waiting for the bonus episode that you guys recorded. Uh,
I think cybershell and
Yeah, it was so long ago. It's it's edited. It just needs to get released. It was a dog's age ago
Yeah, I know but we um
We need to change the the the the the the
The um, what's the word the playlist the playlist url. Yeah, like non patrons have we should change it because like
The non patrons have access to you. It's time to update it
We need to do a little like a little some a little something
To keep it like to keep it, you know for the people who are actually you should just have a post
A pinned post which you can do on patreon
Where you just have links to all the episodes and don't don't have a playlist on youtube that way if you unplug you can't get to the post
You can't see the episode
Yeah
Yeah, that sounds reasonable
Maybe we should we should set it up that way
Uh, yeah, okay. That sounds like a good idea. Well, we'll get those up soon and then there's a lot
There's like three episodes and one of them is really really long. Maybe you should uh hire riley to manage all your stuff
I know we could really use a marriage and we could really use some producing
Some production chops on this uh on this project. You need to produce those last manager
I what I need a guest. I need guests on the podcast and I would really rather it be
A local rapper from elco nevada. Like who do I know?
Who do I know that could get me someone like that?
No one
You'll never get any good guests. You'll be stuck with bottom of the barrel shit to your guests. Like uh
Like gamers havern over here
Yeah, but that guy
Uh
Gamershavern.com go to it
Yes
Uh, yeah mad pros are actually having a website by the way
We're like one of the last 10 people on the internet who still has a website
Yeah, for some reason I didn't have the good chance to stop after I started in 2002
I I miss the days of personal websites. I hate that. It's all that it's all been agglomerated on social media networks
Is that uh, is that almost 20 years old now?
Yep, it'll be 19. The site's uh, 20 year anniversary is coming soon
Holy fuck either or be square dude pretty soon the gamers tavern will be old enough to drink alcohol
Yeah, the brand itself
Hmm
It's already old enough to vote
Probably devoted in the last website should be allowed to vote too
I think so they're they're people too
Uh, okay, we gotta we gotta wrap this episode up
Uh, anything else we have to shill shackles or hackles will stream the pcb minecraft server patreon.com
Slice the procrastinators minecraft server access and the bonus episodes and I guess that's at speak pipe.com slash
PCP voicemail did I get that right? If you want to leave a voicemail message, um
Is that it? Yeah
Okay, that's the end of the episode. Thanks for sticking with me. Goodbye and god speed
See ya