Ha ha ha Ha ha ha Ha
Beep beep beep buh buh buuh buhhhh
Dreaming don't give it up Berh doofy dreamin'
Don't give it up solo dreamin', don't give it up planet dreamin'
Don't give a gut up give it up give it up give it up 3
Yowواoo
Completely different solved none pointers
These complimentary songs. Welcome to the Pro Crastinators podcast.
Oh no, it wasn't Cranstonators podcast. I'm my fucking with my volume. Why am I so
Too quiet or too loud? I don't know whatever. I think my volume will automatically adjust
I'm Ben Saint and this is Gibb and take. Hey gays
We're after after finally having a good episode last week. We're back to the regular post death
PCP arc to people
Nothing happening. It's you've got a you got a you know, it's like
Forced scarcity is like manufactured
Scarcity of the of the good episodes. You can't give them too many
No, then they wouldn't get excited
Then then they wouldn't pop then they wouldn't Pog when the episode was good they get used to being good
You know
And it all credibles once everyone's Poggin, no one will be you know, it's like that. I remember I remember
True when what happened this week?
What's what's on the what's on the plate? I felt like nothing
happened
For me. I was so confused that it was Saturday yesterday. I thought it was like Tuesday
I thought it was Wednesday. I thought nothing had happened because nothing had happened
I've been playing Minecraft and listening to Sean videos
Like an idiot Sean. I love Sean. Yeah, he's the only he's the only I think he's the only breadtuber that I still
Listen to and only because he puts out like one video every two months
Not only because of that also because he's a genius and he's never said anything. I disagree with ever his entire life
Incredible it is incredible. I
Tip my hat to him
I
I'm like that every week every week
like Thursday is coming around and I'm like
It's it hits midnight on Thursday, and then I'm like, oh, it's Friday. Oh wait the episode is coming out today
Okay, wait shit. That means we gotta do another one like two days from now. No, and then
It's all yeah, it feels like feels shorter and shorter the walls are closing in
The the time is just goes speeding right along faster and faster
my
My debt my own mortality approaches. I don't know
necessarily like
Age I think and like in macro scale the age like
Minutes feel shorter or whatever
Years feel shorter the more years you've experienced you start coming and they don't stop coming
but like
For when you don't notice an entire week purse. I think that's more just you haven't been doing
Unique things each day. I've been doing basically the same thing every day
And that's why I feel like I didn't realize
That the days had gone by
Yeah, I think that's an element for me, too. I spent I
Worked I worked on the I worked on the game some more this this week not as much as I want to but I mean that's every I never I never
get to spend I
Never get as much done as I wanted to
I spent a lot of this week arguing on Twitter
I
It is with that was annoying
I've been very angry
This week. Yeah, I had a lot of things to be angry about I had that. Yeah, I had that fucking
I mean, I guess I guess the most descriptive word
I guess you could call it would be a debate with that that fucking guy with that my
my my fellow
Crystorian spit
Dylan Thomas
fucking
Got a lot of got so many fucking kiwi farmers and psychopaths and my mentions all week long
Because they hate me now
Because I was arguing the
The crazy the disgustingly transphobic opinion that Chris is trans because she says she's female
That's that's a
But then I don't like that's what that's what then that's what
That's what transphobes want you to say they want you to
Say that she is one of them one of the trans people because she's bad
And if you say that she is a trans just cuz she says so then they can make fun of them
They can say trans people bad Ben. You are
That was a real gremlin moment
Hashtag gremlin moment, right? Oops. Oops. Sorry everyone. Just have a little gremlin moment right there. You know what I'm saying
Oh, man, I had a really there was that one one
particularly angry live live wire that I got into a big thing with yesterday, but like all week
I've been getting all these all these retweets out of nowhere
I'm just all the random DMs from people just like, you know, calling me a faggot or whatever and it's like, okay
I'll thanks see see I got one today from a just from a guy whose
Twitter avatars just stand from South Park saying you are cringe. So, you know that ruined my day
Another one called me soy that one hurt a lot, you know that one really stung I
Try not to let it show sometimes but when people say when people see the soy inside
No, I try so hard to hide it
Yeah, so, you know like you said
When when you spend your time doing a lot of repetitive shit
It goes by really really bad the times that's arguing on Twitter the time just flies by
Hours go by and and I'm just like what what have I done? What have I done a lot of time?
I'm reading tweet arguments you've been having and being like thank God, it's not me thank God
I'm sorry about that. Jesus. No, no, I mean like I've been seeing what you've been going through and it's like
I know it must suck. It must suck just reading them. I don't I mean, I really shouldn't engage. I really engage more than I should
Yeah, I guess I'll briefly touch on that
Debate that quote-unquote debate itself the the gist of it. Okay, I don't necessarily recommend anyone go watch
It's not that funny. It's short and it's frustrating and it's infuriating
They basically the argument went
Dylan I
Say I say Chris is a FEMA is a trans woman because she says so because that's what being trans is
Identifying as female Dylan says Chris is not just transgender. Chris is also transsexual and Chris
did weird Chris and Chris did weird stuff about being like Chris tried to be
Transsexual what whatever that means in a weird way that is not typical
like the time where she she cut her her crotch and the time where she like
drank some like menopause medic medicine or something and
He said like therefore she is not
Transsexual because those were odd things to do and I was like what what are you talking about?
I'm talking about gender and he was like no, but she's a trend shut up. Stop changing the subject
So we went but I was like no I'm talking about gender and he was like, okay
So they he just he he had the same like two arguments that every one of these these two likes non arguments that every one of these
People have they all think they're so smart
Repeating the same like bullshit. It doesn't fucking isn't relevant. What was it? His two things were like one
She is not
She says she's trans, but she also says that she's a goddess and a son of two
therefore she can't
Be trans because she said some other things that are false and
To like she said she is faking it. She said she's a fake
Faking a being a woman or she said she would fake being a woman to get access to lesbians
This this second okay
The first one is like a totally spurious like if you say one thing that's false nothing else you say can ever be true
Yeah, that's like that's real. That's really obnoxious. It doesn't make any sense. It's terrible
The enough said about that the second one
Okay, everyone says this everybody has this same point. They say Chris admitted
Chris admitted that he's just he's just faking it Chris admitted that he is just doing it to get lesbians, okay
Everyone says this so much that I just assumed it was true
When someone when someone actually tried to show me that evidence to show me that quote
It is like one thing it is like one time that Chris said she would like to
She would like to pretend to be a girl
Like and then described like a scenario where like
She had like a slumber party with other girls right to like get less to have like a lesbian slumber party or something
She's yeah, she's it was ten years ago. It was like ten years ago. Oh, so just like yeah, like
Foreshadowing that's the evidence. That's not every that's so stupid
Everyone is everybody says the same thing. They all just accept it. They're like, oh, she said it one time
One time she said, yeah, I would like to pretend to be a woman
I mean, I don't have a lesbian slumber party. It doesn't surprise me at all like their arguments are based off of
Mostly just hearsay and they'll believe it as soon as possible just because
They hate her and they are so convinced. Yeah, they just they're so convinced by that bullet in my gum
They are so convinced and so so many of them repeat that same point that I I
Honestly thought that the evidence that there would be more to it than there is
but like, oh my god, just
Gee, I can't I can't imagine I can't imagine a scenario where like gee, I don't know someone who later on
Realizes that they are a girl or just had to be that they want to identify as as female
I can't imagine a scenario where before they make that decision. Maybe they joke about ha ha
What if I did that or think about what if they did that?
Like I can't that that would blow my fucking mind right there
It's so weird cuz like if that was the even if that was true though, it's it's like
The right like the autonomy of it still wouldn't matter it still wouldn't matter
How do you even know that it's insincere you can't judge that from the outside you can just assume
Based on you know, I don't know
Nothing really
You're just guessing and even if you could tell for example like
It's so like getting into like the minutiae of like philosophically, what does it mean to be a gender or
To like identify as this or that if you do it for X reason is it invalid?
I mean
Yeah, that's a that's a philosophical question
That is not like an obvious yes or no answer, but they're not using it like that
They're just using it as like a cheat like a you know, it's it's just another bullet. It's like it's like I got you
Oh, she did it for this reason. Well, you can't do that. You can't do that for that
That doesn't I've just decided that like anybody I don't like transitions because they want to have lesbian sex instead of
non-lesbian sex
You know is I not actually trans, you know, I just think that like if you want if you are you know
If you are a quote-unquote trans woman. Oh, and you want to have sex with other women
You can just scoot right along there buster
No, no, it doesn't count
It just doesn't count and
I doesn't annoy me. It's just sort of a
Notable that like so many of them they have you know
The that meme that's like the two people talking. I think it's like a a version of like a
Progressive comic whereas a person's like here's how to just
Correct someone when they make a wrong pronoun
Oh, oh the the oh
He and then the lady says she she says like she raped her mother. Oh, excuse me. She raped her mother. Yes
I know they I feel like they post that as if it's like a slam dunk
They they put yeah, they post that as though it's like ha ha
Wouldn't it be silly?
Wouldn't it be like obviously this is what you look like and I'm like it's just right. It's just correct
Yeah, like I literally just right. I feel like they just they they they can't
separate the idea of
respecting
transness and pronoun usage
Concept and they literally and defending they're like they're like from rape accusations cuz we don't it's like it's all or nothing thinking
It's it's all they all they all are like imagine
Imagine defending rape imagine thinking. Yeah, like rape is okay. I'm like, what are you talking about?
You're you're delusional. You're you're having a fucking schizoid episode right now. Like you're literally just making shit up
It you don't live in fucking reality. You imagine it's like. Oh, this is a male murderer
Mmm, probably a female actually. I don't respect their gender. I'm gonna call them a oh she
Wow, I don't want this one to be one of my cis people. So I'm gonna yeah, it's bad
I don't think for this murder to be
He doesn't get he doesn't get to be a cis male anymore now. He's a
Rapist or whatever, you know, like criminal of gender like it's so
Transparenly like a transphobic B. Like like I don't know
Distraction like they just are doing every every realize it maybe
Going through every murderer in history and retroactively deciding that they don't that they don't deserve human respect
And therefore I get to decide that actually they were all trans women, you know, because I'm such an ally
And I just think that would be better that way, you know, oh
man
Wait just to okay. So the thing about the the quote-unquote debate with that fucking guy is that
he he tries to get I he tries to um
You know, he does all these things about like oh
Chris, I don't think he actually said like Chris doesn't have trans dysphoria
I'm not sure if he actually said that but I I got him on I asked him like what makes a trans woman a woman and
I he's he I got him to say he I didn't even have to get it out of him. He said he was like
Okay, I thought he was gonna go the like the the truce camera
I thought he was gonna say like oh they need to be diagnosed by a doctor. They need to have medical dysphoria or whatever
No, he didn't do that. He said
Being a you know identifying as a woman makes you a woman. I was like, okay
So Chris identifies as a woman
therefore QED and like as far as I'm concerned as soon as he said that the argument was one because that's the point if
Making if being trans is is the same as identifying as trans if identifying as trans makes you trans, which it does
then
Chris does that
Therefore, she is a trans woman and it's as simple as that but then he but then he spent then he he spent the next like 10 minutes
Because the video is only like 15 minutes long
Then he spends the next like 15 minutes being like oh, but she says she's a son of you too like oh
But she also says she's a goddess. Oh, but the other thing and like it's all irrelevant
It's all completely aside the point
So I just called him an idiot. I called him an idiot and I and he was like and I you know
I said it I called him an idiot. I said he was being transphobic by doing that
I said all these things and the comments are just like Ben's resorted to insults Ben
Said Ben called him a name. Therefore. He must have lost the argument because like that just means he was losing
but I like I
I
Don't know the the the comments on that video are terrible. They're all like it's I mean it's all his
Viewers, so I guess I shouldn't expect them to be good, but it's really fascinating how like
The the majority of the comments are like
There it's like it's turf true scum shit. It's the same like hmm
Ben is so it's I it's like Ben is soy and not just an event her
Yeah, because he chafed at me call he chafed at me calling him a turf because he was like
Do you know what a turf is?
That's the means of feminists the f stands for feminists, and I'm not a feminine
Literally is one of those
The the the the comments are all most of them are just
Either an insult to me or saying like you know Ben was mad. Therefore. He's he lost lol
How how childish how childish of him to to to use a word a mean word
oh
There was there was the part there was the part where he was like
Ben you there are trans people that disagree with you and you disagree with them you're invalidating them
By doing that, and I'm just like mocking with it
Do you we do trans people agree with me because like he this was he's literally doing like a
Trans people like my trans friends say that it's okay. It's okay for me to be a tur
It's okay for me to be a tur
Okay, anyway
So yeah, that was like oh he he made he made a voice Ben made a voice that he was like making fun of the other guy
With his voice like that's childish and therefore he lost. He is a user
He is soy
Anyway, most of the comments are they're either just yes
They're either just insults to me about that or they are like actually it's transphobic to say Chris is
Trans because Chris is bad and you're saying that trans people can be bad and you that's bad. It's transphobic to say that
so actually Ben is the transphobic one right like that that a lot of it is like that shit and
Then but then these these people who are there to like ostensibly because they care about trying in a stupid and backwards way
That doesn't make any sense and and defeats itself
But like they are attempting on some level to be like pro trans rights
But they're right alongside like the other maybe like 20% of the comments that are just like ha ha lal you're both wrong
Trans people can never can never be meant a man can never become a woman
What makes you a woman is the ability to give birth this whole thing is yeah, that was really
They're all just open. They were like some of them are just openly like not fuck trans people. They're fake
They're all faking it. They're all delusional. They're all they should all be in a mental hospital like
Would you see your who you fucking are see who you're in the fucking on the side with look around you?
And let's see who is who is on the same side of this debate and be like oh wow
I'm arguing the same position
That the people that hate me are arguing
Just a whole okay to Blair whites
Yeah
self-hating
Maybe indirectly, but definitely not helpful to other trans people
They called I called one
true scum trans woman on Twitter. I
Called her Blair white because she was doing the same thing. She was saying they're like
Chris doesn't get to be trans. She's not a real trans person
It is this is this is only hurting real trans people when you let someone be one of them because they say they are
And I called her Blair white and she was like she she said
Like the fact that you think that calling me Blair white as an insult shows that you're the real bigot
And then we got into it
And then we got into an hours-long argument and later on I go and I look at I look at her
Her timeline and on her time was she she made a couple posts about you know how the woke mob were bullying her, right?
She made a couple posts about that and one of them was like
Why do the why do woke ease?
Think why do woke ease think that calling me Blair white is an insult. I would love to look like her
Right, I'd be so happy if I looked like her. Why do they think it's an insult to call me that?
And I'm like wow you know about what you look like you literally just don't understand you
I don't know what is the disconnect here. I don't know why you can't
It's like she's like pro Blair. It's like she doesn't even know what Blair white believes
It's like she like saw a picture of Blair and is like that's a pretty trans woman
I wish I looked and like that was it. It's like now. She's like a flip probe pro Blair
Or something. I don't know
Very that was like I did that was that like on Tuesday or something. I did that it was so cringe the whole debate was I
mean in my opinion like I
Got him. I got him to make the argument for me my arguments airtight. You can't be defeated
He he agrees that identifying as trans makes you trans therefore it follows that
Chris is a trans woman because she identifies as such none of the other bullshit that he tried to say or that anyone tries to say like oh
One time she said she was gonna fake it one time
You know she does all this other stuff blah blah blah none of that matters none of it pokes a hole in the main argument
People people complained at me like oh, but then it was bad optics of you to insult him. It was bad
I don't know. I don't care. I still won my argument won if you if you think it was bad optics
Even though my argument is self-evidently right then like I don't know whoops. What what can I do?
He did he did he did the he did the whole thing he did this is a pet peeve of mine
This isn't just him a lot of people do this and not even on this topic people do this in a lot of context in my life
I have had many people
Do pull this card on me where like I insist on my side of the argument and like
For saying that I am right and for saying that I have reason to think that I am right
They say like oh you're arrogant
Because that's so arrogant of you to just assume that you're right like
You moron he's I'll use him as an example
But you know it is if this goes for any like you fucking moron
We're having this argument because I think one thing I happen to be right, but I think one thing and you think another
How stupid are you?
That I'm like that I like
Insists on what I think and you're like that's so arrogant that you think you're right like what do you think?
Moron you fucking imbecile like what are you talking about like
To to like hone in on that like it's a point that you can add to your tally of like winning
Like Ben there were comments that were like Ben is just Ben just cares too much about being right
You know like Ben is just too he's just too focused on whether he's right or not like what what do you think?
I'm here to talk about what do you think?
I'm here for what did you expect me to say?
Fucking idiots, man
It's all you know all all those all those comments and all the DMs and all the ads that I've been getting on all
Though and all the snarky retweets I've been getting
It's been a lot, but at the end of the day. I just remember like this is all it's all Kiwi farmers
They these are this is the crowd
All of my most negative and like most disgusting interactions that I've ever had online have been
When it's something to do with Chris and a bunch of people like
And a bunch of people get mad at me and they all act they all act this way
This is the worst it's ever been but it has it has happened to other times before and it's it's always this great
It's this like Chris Chris following Kiwi Farms crowd
They're they're just they're just nasty
They're just nasty people. They don't care
They don't care about anything. They'll just
And I just don't I just don't have any respect for them. I don't take their opinion seriously
There was one one thing I want to mention and this was very funny. It was that same person that said, you know
Calling me Blair White makes you the real big it wall
She she said
She she said that I because it was like because I didn't know
When it was something like when Chris said that that thing 10 years ago about like how what if I pretended to be a girl and had a
lesbian slumber party
Totally not an egg thing to say
She she because I didn't know like that line
She said like you got to like learn your chrystery like you're you're a turn you supposed to be a chrystorian learn your chrystery
lull and then and
Then like mere posts later
So she says like
Chris identifies as a son of two and all son of two are male therefore
Chris is not a woman or something
And I'm like, okay first first of all, it's really obvious
It's really obvious that when Chris says oh, I'm son of two now
I'm magic hand now. She is role-playing as another
Character that is not her while like she herself
She still thinks considers Christine the person to be female like it's really obvious that that doesn't shouldn't conflict
Those are like two separate things, but whatever aside from that
Learn learn your fucking chrystery you nerd there are I just put out a lecture
I just put out that you should watch my lecture actually because it clearly explains that there are definitely female son of
Choose and male rosa choose. This is like
Uncontroversial and she she said she said
That's not that's a retcon. That's not widely accepted as cannon and like what are you fucking talking about?
It's in the comic. This is literally it's literally
I know it's it's common to say to accuse like Chris people of like being as dumb as Chris
herself
But like that is literally as dumb as something Chris
That is basically like what Chris tried to do with slime and punishment where she she said like that's not the cannon
This is the cannon. This is her being like no, no, no
Like Chris's only certain parts of Chris's comic actually count like the other parts don't count like those aren't cannon
Like you fucking moron you imbecile you Rube
I
Couldn't believe it. I just I
Just can't fucking believe these people. I have nothing but disdain for them
They their opinions are less than worthless
I just get I just get more and more convinced that I am right the more I see what kind of person disagrees with me
Yeah
At the very beginning I was wondering like how many people were like, oh, you know the news came out and they're like
Just the first thing they hear just happens to be like should we care about the Chris's gender?
I mean they
They're doing some weird shit right now and people like instinctually might be like, oh geez. I guess that I guess it may be not
But no, they seem to all be kind of already fucked
They they really seem to like have a lot of problems
They went into they went into it with a with an image. Yeah, if you if you don't know
Okay, I understand if you don't know anything about Chris and you hear this person
Identifies as a woman and raped their mom
I guess like I can understand why what pops into your head is some like Buffalo Bill asks asks serial killer, right?
And you're like, oh, well
Why would I?
Take their word for it, right like sure, but if you if you know anything if you if you understand anything about Chris
It's not very hard
It's not very hard to see to make to see the
Logical idea that like Chris did these bad things, but also is like very sincere and
Serious about the the gender thing, right? Like whatever else you might think about them
It's just
Simple it's just a simple concept that a certain
category of people
Just simply doesn't have it in them either intellectually or spiritually to wrap their minds around and for that I pity them
Yeah, what what else
What else is there to say oh
Man a half an hour in I didn't expect to spend that much time on it
We never have to talk about it again, which I think we never have to talk about it again
again that
People ask me should should I watch the debate and I was like probably not it's not that funny
It'll just make you mad like no one no ground is gained
If you want if you just want to hear me like loudly and repeatedly
repeat
The truth that could the correct argument that you can't be that wins
I guess you could if you wanted to but there's probably no need
Yeah, they're yeah, you're right now. We never have to talk about it again. What a shit show. Oh
well the the I
Mean I I don't I mean I hesitate to call it harassment, but the the harassment has has is slowing down considerably
It'll probably be a thing of the past pretty soon. Yeah, it's still they'll get bored. I mean, yeah, it's it was just you know
It's not it's funny not even a 20-minute video, right?
It's it's funny that sometimes
Sometimes someone will be like DMing me or adding me or having like a real they seem like really angry at me and
Like as soon as I stop engaging
Maybe I'll check if they were particularly vicious. Maybe I'll check their timeline and I'll see like
immediately they just went back to like some
like just having a totally unrelated conversation or like just retweeting hentai or just like
There was one guy who like immediately like immediately after we stopped talking
He went and like retweeted some hentai and was like, hey, I want her to do that to my dick
What are you? Okay? I guess this was really serious for you
That guy whatever it doesn't matter I
Could I could spend I could probably spend this whole episode going into the minutia of that guy was being a great
This way this lady was being a hypocrite in this other way. I
I have been doing a little something this this last week past week
I've been streaming some more on
Streaming don't give it up give and yeah
Streaming I was streaming
Dark Souls
Randomizer run where you randomize all the items and all the enemy placements and it's really fun because uh
You can have you can do lots of different like settings so you can make
You can make it so that the buses are replaced with different buses, but they try to like make it unique
So you're not gonna get like 20 like see the scale this is through the playthrough. You can get like you'll see
maybe one of each
bus like just in the wrong place
Hmm and also you can have like random enemies spawn boss it as bosses instead
At a as at a percentage and it's just it's been really fun
It's good. Yeah, but wait
You play you play Dark Souls like hundreds of times. I played it. I played it like once I
Played it once just once you played it for the did you you you weren't uh in the dark
No, I was not in the Dark Souls right and frankly, I'm glad I didn't because I saw what Nate had to do to win that shit
And I'm like
That was like a skill-based execution that must have taken like a ton of practice
That I never could have imagined
You both you and Nate love to like grind to tears to get the perfect time
Stupid little PCP show
Honestly, yeah
You can help yourselves. It's it's a shame. It's a shame that like nobody watched the Kirby race
I think I grinded so much to win that Kirby race
Nobody else took it as seriously as I did but I fucking
That was more. I mean the the Pokemon race was not really about I mean, I did grind
I did do the Pokemon run over and over and over again
You know, you know, I actually was probably about equivalent. I spent a lot of time
Actually spent a lot of time grinding on on both of those
What was the other one? There was the Dark Souls race the Pokemon race the Kirby race and there was one more, right?
Uh, was there one more? I don't I think we had plans. I can't remember. What else we did. Yeah, we talked
I thought we did another one in between
Pokemon and Kirby let me have a go look
Mmm
Those those videos were were good. They're memorable
They're yeah, they're good videos
Yeah, but
I mean for me
They were very work-intensive like I spent I spent like all week
For both of them grinding that shit
uh
The the Kirby one I had to discover the like
The the strat of like um getting getting like the randomized like mix-up power and then timing it perfectly to get the exact power
You need for that section is like
You just got to do it over and over and over and over again until you get it right and then you got to execute perfectly
It was fun though. Yeah, we've already we only did I do like grinding
I do I do I do
I do like I guess I kind of do look just like grinding shit out. Yeah
Uh, I guess okay. I guess you only did three. So yeah, the last one's 2017
That's the Kirby race
Wow four years ago
It was it was it's like been a constant thing not not constant
But like every so often I'm like, ah shit those were fun
It sucks that no one can agree on what game to do next
We we did agree on what game to do next we were gonna do doom
um
But that was like a long time ago
I mean
I see I would still be the editor for that I guess because I like doing those
They're fun to like time everything up
But then they would just be you versus tom, which I guess is not a terrible thing
But tom would
Tom would I I mean tom is more familiar with doom than I am so probably probably he would win
I'm also just I'm bad at first person shooters also. So yeah, tom would probably win and like only two people is not as
It's not as good as like six. I think we already have like six people on the pokemon race
Yeah, there were four people in the dark souls race, and I think there were like three on the Kirby race
It was Nate munchie and you yeah
Mike my Kirby strat was like so advanced. It was such
My pokemon strat too. I guess was also extremely advanced. Yeah, you did the funny glitch thing
I did the funny glitch Nate I
Nate Nate like also did the glitch thing, but he only did like the simple version
I did like the full version like the full rock through walls, which is like
It was fun the fun that I got to show that I mean I still think about sometimes how like
When I was doing like practice runs of the block brock through walls glitch
I had that weird visual glitch that like turned me
They're like warped the world and then like turned my sprite into the old man sprite for a second and then like
Powered off and I like am so sad that I wasn't recording because it was such like a
Weird creepypasta sort of sort of glitch moment
Oh, I turned into an old man and then the whole world went like white and then it and then I died
It was like the end of fucking synecdoche, new york spoilers
um
cynic yeah
Yeah, um
Yeah, I don't know. I mean
We could maybe get like have the same like we got gamers tavern. He's a gamer cyber shell is a gamer
Maybe we could have like a pcp guest
race
Including ben and tom
If four people were down to play are you not down to do a doom race?
um
Doom I I mean I guess I could but I like editing them
Actually, no, I did the dark souls one didn't I I participate that yeah, I could I could do doom sure
Well, if if four people if four people were
Down and committed to like yeah, we're doing this doom race. Yeah, I would I would do I would do the doom race
We'd have to think of the rules of like where we go and what version of the game
Um, but yeah, that should be I think it should be tom
I think tom proposed the idea and I think he had an idea in mind for it
I think he's it was like first level and just um
Or something he he had a proposal
When he when he pitched the the doom idea
if yeah, if
I'm just I'll write me in as like potentially down
Write me in as down. I am I am in if if three other people are in and we say we're doing this then I will I will do it
Stay tuned for that it may be maybe maybe
I'll I'll I'll take it in right now
I'll add everyone
I can't believe those three bonus episodes are still not out
I think it's
I think tom's just hasn't gotten around to uploading them. I shouldn't I shouldn't
I shouldn't I shouldn't point the finger, but I think it's literally just like they are made and just like
well
Someone needs to upload them, but also
I said that like we need to
like change the like
url
or change like the um
the um the um
Change because like a lot of like former patrons still have access to the
Videos and we need to like change it so that like, you know only the patrons
Yeah, like to change the url or just like or I think tom proposed like
Instead of making it a playlist that is potentially like the url can be potentially copied and passed around
Make it like a a patreon master post that just like links to every episode
And uh and have that be
The the like the way they're they're accessed
I think maybe that's what we should do is someone will just need to like rewrite
That the patreon post I guess god, I mean, I guess I could just
I guess I could just do that
it was just
So, uh
Yeah, okay, so I should
I guess I should probably just go do that and then we can have those three bonus episodes and then there'll be no problem
Including the one where I grant and rave to cybershell for four hours about how much I hate Tracey
Oh, that one's good. I like that one
I always think that that that way you you were thinking just then
Like like oh, I've got all these things to do. I say out loud to myself or on stream or just somewhere like, oh, yeah
I really have all those things to do
and it's just followed by like
The the the like the deafening silence of me deciding to not do them anyway, even though I'm not doing anything. I like
Uh, yeah, so many things I've got to do. I've got to do those things
I'm trying to be positive and affirmative and be like, yes, those things must be done. I will do them
And now I'll do those things
I mean, you know, there are
In any given week, there are a multitude of distinct things that all you know, uh, uh are
On that level where I'm like, I guess I got to do that. I guess I should do that. Okay. I better do it
And these things conflict with each other
Um, for me, it's mostly the the the phantoms revenge game which
I finished, okay
I made
I made a cutscene. This was like one of the things that I had to do is like I had to
I basically had to program
A cutscene I made one of them. It's like very rough. It's like I sort of like roughly blocked it out and in its basic like timing
So it's not a completed cutscene, but I have one cutscene
Like made enough that it counts and and I consider that to be a win because this is like, okay
I can use this template of how I made this one
I can use this to make I think there's like
Three or four more that I have to do and I can be like, all right
I could basically copy and place this template for how I did it and just and then go back through them and just kind of
You know, fill them out with like the actual nitty gritty of like how I want the sprites to move around and animate and stuff
Which is it's a lot of work, but uh
Having having the the bear the blocks in place
Makes it feel like oh the game is not in an unplayably broken state the game is like
Technically playable and there and it feels like it feels closer to being done having it this way
uh, yeah
uh, man
I can't believe it's been eight months of me making this piece of shit
Okay, it gives me vertigo gives me vertigo when I think about it like that
Dang months. Yeah the fuck I feel like I don't know I've been
Like stationary
For the whole year
Even though I have done things. It's not like a lot
Lord of Ghost Kickstarter was the only one big thing and even that was mostly just making the page
Yeah, I
I feel like that I usually when I'm like I
I
Yeah, I always feel like what have I actually done this year
What when I actually try to think about it like there are things that I have done
But like when I first think about I'm like the year went by and I didn't do anything
The whole like most of the year is gone and I like didn't do anything. What what am I thinking?
It's it's not completely true. My birthday has already happened this year. That doesn't make sense. It's already like summer is nearly over
Yeah
Summer has come at last
The year has gone so fast
Wake me up. I'm gonna cry when September ends. You know how you know what that's how to do
That's how it be sometimes then october ends and then november ends and then
Oh christmas time true true. Um
Um
Have I mentioned
I'm throwing out this there. Have I have I talked about my bit?
on twitter
Where I will pay people to unpledge from Trixie. Have I talked to mention that on the pcp?
I don't think so
Okay, I want to make that I want to announce that here again. Nobody's taken me up on this offer
I don't understand one one guy took me up on the offer
And then I think most people who pledge to Trixie do not follow ben saint on twitter
I know I know I know but one one guy was like I was gonna unpledge anyway
I'm good. I have a one. I'm a one dollar pleasure and I was gonna unpledge anyway, and I was like great
I'll give you two dollars to do it now
And then the next day
I saw her her pledges went down like 15 dollars and I'm just I'm something like if that guy
Whoever that was if they had just told me if they had just told me I'm gonna do that
I would have given them
like 20 bucks
Just just to say that like I paid him to do it
It would have been worth it to me. I wouldn't I would have loved it. We all everyone would have benefited nobody loses in the situation
um
How many man-outs have gone into Trixie?
spite do you think?
Well
I mean
Jeez, let me let me think
Since like march or whatever
It's been like five months
Probably spend a few hours a week on it
so
so uh
How many how many phantom's revenges could have been made with that?
A small fraction of one that's a small fraction of one
um
I I
People people people get on my case people get on my case on twitter and they're like ben this is ben
This is this is too spiteful ben. This is like no
It's not about the amount of spite don't for me don't attack don't attack the patreon ben
No, she needs that money ben like no, she's in a she's in a rough spot
You know, she's she's going through a rough time
You know, you can't like that's her like that's her her her livelihood
I'm like, oh my god, you fucking idiot you fucking simp g
Yeah, if someone didn't have if someone didn't have
Their patreon money in addition to their like, you know ad revenue and their sub-stack revenue and their
And like all these other like passive streams of income that the average person doesn't have if she were to lose a small fraction
Of of that like god. I don't know what she would do. I don't know what she could possibly do
Right like living with her parents not paying rent getting an allowance
On top of all these other free money
That people just give her that she just makes from the internet like it would be like, oh my god
what if she
Do like like
That would just be it would be it's it's tragic like if you can't you can't do that you can't do that
It's not it's it's it's cruel. It's cruel ben
You're going after her livelihood fuck off
god
Yeah, I imagine like imagine imagine not having that imagine having to like get a job or something
Like what damn if if she had to get a job or something like that would just be the worst thing imagine
That would be the world fate worse than death honestly
It's back to the radio shack
Um, um, wait, no, what was it? This is the target
She worked on a target. Yeah, yeah
target full circle one
One person. I mean, that's what I want. I mean, I I joke
I joke because I I don't actually have the power to make that happen
But if I could snap my fingers and make that happen, I would that is what I want
Uh, let let there be no ambiguity there. Um
Uh, uh one guy one guy really offended me
I hope he's not listening now because I don't I don't really care to call a person out
But I I do want to mention that there's one train of thought
one person was like
G ben, you know
I think your criticism to her valid, but I just can't help but wonder like what if she kills herself and commits suicide
over this bullying
frowny face
He didn't he didn't exact he didn't exactly phrase it as like a
You were actually kind of like killing her
You were actually kind of like forcing her to kill herself ben like went by by like being mean to her on twitter
But like the implication was there
And I went off on that guy because I think I think that's a genuinely like a genuinely like diseased way to think like
I think that was like some sick
sick shit
to say
On the internet. Yeah to put that on someone like casually as well. I think I read it
It was like he it was just it made me feel nauseous. Oh, I don't
Oh, uh, like when you confronted them, they were like, oh, I didn't mean anything
I was just saying it could happen. You know that guy did
I told them that I think he's a sick fuck and he needs therapy, which I do
Um, and he he like kind of apologized, but like frankly
It was a tepid apology
When like he needed to be like he needed to be like ashamed of himself
And like he wasn't he wasn't
Significantly like disgusted and embarrassed with his own
Uh behavior
So I kind of felt like I I wouldn't call admission accomplished there
Uh, I didn't quite I didn't quite impress upon him
like just
just how like
vile
Uh, such such behavior is
But oh well, you can't you can't win them all
Uh
Yeah, I mean
With regards to people giving you shit about it. I don't really mind the spite
So much as the fact that you are wasting time on it because it's not doing I mean
I guess you could say I guess that's that one guy
Unpledge, but I feel like people are unpledging
For other reasons than ben sainte. It's like funny tweet. Well, obviously obviously because they're not even they're not even
Coming and telling me and getting their fucking free money
Yeah, it's free real estate
I don't know you say you enjoy it. Maybe you do. Maybe it's fine. I just I feel like such things are
Are just bad generally like being on twitter a lot
I I is clearly not a good thing to do
I understand
Yeah
I mean
If I could just if I could just be
You know a perfectly logical rational person
Probably the thing to do would be like, you know, if I don't like someone
I just shouldn't
Well, you know, it was kind of spurred on this week by the oh, yeah, the big reveal tricksy finally
tricksy finally, uh, was disgusted enough with the people that like her content to just announce like
Oh, yeah, I deleted it the brony lecture. It's gone. I deleted it. Fuck you. You're never getting it
So, you know, this was, you know, there was a moment of like renewed like
About that. So that that kind of kicked me that kind of kicked me into back into high gear with it this week. Um
You know, I mean you're you're right
It's like the I think it's the the buddhist saying, you know when
Holding on to anger is like being being being spite is like, uh, it's like
Yeah, it's like holding on to a hot coal in your hand thinking that like you'll you'll throw it at someone, right?
Something that is like, uh poisoning yourself hoping that they'll die or something
Yeah, yeah, something like that. I understand
I understand but since since I'm not a rational a fully rational being
Um
I am I am gonna I'm gonna be mad
I'm gonna be mad because I I truly don't think it's uh acceptable
The way she's behaved and so I might as well. I don't know make a funny bit out of it
If there's if there's nothing if there's no way or out of it, I might as well
I might as well make it into I might as well make content out of it. You know what I'm saying
Yeah, no no wasted content here like I can't I can't like moral moral like high ground this because I
I find it funny as well
It would be it would be I I think it's I think it's really funny
I think it's really funny that I can litter that it that one guy actually took me up on it
I wish more would but I the fact that even one
Did it I'm like, okay, that that's
The the bit was worth it was worth it
um
Off offer still open though offer will remain open offer will remain open until
She is back to working at target or bagging groceries
That is the end game unironically
It is the end game, but I know that I I know that I don't have the power to do it alone
So you you have to you all have to lend me your energy
Yes, you have to lend me your energy with this one. We have to do it together
comrades
Well
Yeah, brony lecture brony lecture deleted
Oh, I there was a funny thing. Um, I had I had made
Before she announced that like I deleted it. It's never happening. Well, uh
I had made the the the tier list the lecture tier list
And I had I had thrown in the little easter egg in there where I just I didn't mention it
But I I put a fake I made a fake thumbnail and I put the fake thumbnail
Of the brony lecture into the tier list and I put it in my in like I put it in a rank
Just so that like anyone who was making it would be like wait a minute
Which one is this which one is this and some some people actually fell for it
some people actually were like oh wait wait the bro like
They they recognized what it was and they thought it meant that the that that was out
um
sign and that and that yeah
and then I um
And I I I changed my I changed my twitter handle to brony lecture truth there and I I started posting like conspiracy posts about like
Wait a minute, but but it was referenced in it was referenced in the the the tier list
It's in the tier list
Which was before she said that she deleted it. So like where did it go?
Like why did why is there a thumbnail like there wouldn't be a thumbnail if it weren't posted somewhere?
Oh, who who's hiding the truth?
Um, it's a covet. It's a covet 19 vaccination conspiracy. It's bill gates. It's bill gates trying to silence her
Uh, okay, it's deleted because he has the power to like delete files off of any windows computer
Yes, true true. He has the map the kill switch
Uh
I had some fun with it. I had some fun with it. Um, but boy am I upset
I I kind of I kind of thought
You know this whole time I have known like there is a chance that Trixie has deleted
The the brony lecture and just never thought that it was worth mentioning
Uh, but I I decided that like on the off chance that maybe she hasn't
Maybe it's worth needling her about like, um, you know
Why not post the brony lecture? Your channel is in the fucking toilet. A lot of people want to see the brony lecture
Why not post the brony lecture?
Um
But you know now now I guess it I guess it the I guess she was that was just so offensive to her that now
She's she's confirmed that no it's gone. It's gone. I just write it. Um, so you know, I feel like mission failed
But there was a really deleted it like when she left the pcp in a huff
Maybe
Maybe yeah, probably because that was when it was being discussed
And she just never mentioned it because why would she I guess?
Yeah
Yeah, probably
Again though, you know, she said when she left she
Said on twitter
She made it sound like she left because I was insisting on the brony lecture
That wasn't why she left she left because she left because I said her channel was tanking and that riley was uh
Was was scamming her
Which in hindsight
I I don't I don't think I don't think I think that riley is a scammer anymore. I think he's an opportunist
and I think that he was
Leap leaching off of her true, but like I don't think I don't think he like had a plan
I don't think he like knew what he was doing
Uh, they just they they just they just tanked the channel together
On all of their own but both of them genuinely thinking that they were like rational people doing their best
Incredible if you can that's I've changed my stance. That's what I think now
Lamar
Yeah
Very very very frustrating though to see I mean she to see here like to see here kind of kind of twisted and manipulated
Like that. I don't know but whatever. What what would I expect?
Oh, what if she but what if she what if she sure would be sad if she
Killed herself and committed suicide ben because of you
Sure would be sure would be fucked up
If she were to kill herself because you bullied her ben and it would be your fault
Hmm, wouldn't that be fucked up? Ha ha ha just kidding, but seriously though
Sad sad sad stuff, um
Okay, what what else is what else is on the fucking docket for this week?
I got nothing. I'm sorry. I've got I got like I got locked in my apartment
Oh, my my door knob fell off and I was literally locked in my apartment for
several hours
Until my roommate came home and we were able to like
Do like a two-man like like he manipulates the latch from the outside and I and or like no
And I I manipulate the latch from the inside and he pushes the door open
From the from the outside what I'm mixing up, but you know what I'm saying that we finally did manage to get the door open
So now we can exit and enter
It wasn't that long, but for a while there. I was just like well
I'm fucked the reason why
Uh, I it was when I was I was trying to check my mail
Was when I realized the door was broken
I was trying to check my mail because I was waiting for the arrival of the next thing that I want to talk about
Which is my new credit card
My new credit card, which is the coolest thing that I am obsessed with
I love credit. I love my new credit card. I love credit cards. I love credit card churning
Uh, this is my new thing. This is the the best thing that's happened to me. This is like, um
I I feel like when I when I feel like I just bought a shiny new like, you know
A vinyl like anime figurine like a new piece in my collection
I genuinely feel like I like I'm like admiring it sometimes and I'm like, yes
I feel like it's the same feeling as when you play cookie clicker
And you buy like an upgrade you buy like a all like
Oh, if I if I buy this if I'm saving up for this upgrade
If I'm saving up for this upgrade and I finally get it and now I get like a passive 5 bonus to my cookie production
Yes, I saved up for it and I got it. Um
A passive bonus like oh, this is gonna pay for itself. Um
I again, what's the churning thing you like use it up real quick
No, no
churning refers churning refers to yeah to getting new credit cards
Just to like
Obtain like the sign-up bonuses and then like getting it getting the sign-up bonuses and then just like
Getting a new card and and repeating the process. So like yeah
The new the new card. I just got it's it has a
If I spend like a certain amount within the first three months, I get a 200 dollar sign-up bonus
and I'm I got it now because like
Road to rad con is is being printed
And this is this is why I was looking for the card because I was like, okay road to rad con is is ready to be
It's ready to be printed. I need to pay for the printing
I want to do it with my new with this credit card
So I so I because I have to spend that money on this print stuff
You know, I'm gonna get reimbursed out of the rad con fund
But if I spend if I do it with this card, then that money will go towards my my spend amount
Which will qualify me for this free 200 dollars
of of free money
for spending money
um, so
Yeah, this was this was my strategy
and uh, uh, it's not illegal or anything. It's it's just uh
It's it's just like optimally gaming the the credit card system
So do you have to get a credit card with a different bank or something?
Surely they would notice if you're just doing it over and over again
Well, you can only do it so often
Like yeah, you will you will generally not just be approved for an infinite amount of credit cards
They will like they will start to decline you if you apply for too many too fast
um
But uh, this was the first one I applied for in a while. It just so happened to be with the same bank as the last one
Um, just because this one happened to offer a a can be a sign-up bonus that I could qualify for pretty easily
uh
It also okay, okay, let me explain the difference the difference between my two credit cards is my first one
It did my first one did not have a sign-up bonus
But I got my first one right before I was going to print the um the the vapors two books
um
And it was because it would give me two percent cash
It gives me two percent cash back on everything anything I buy with that card
I just automatically get two percent back as credit, right?
So every everything is just uh is two percent cheaper
The new card there's the sign-up bonus, but also on top it the first one was called city bank double cash
The second one is called city bank custom cash
And the city bank custom cash the way it works is it's when you buy stuff with it. It categorizes the things you buy into like, um
Categories, so they're like, you know groceries
Uh uh streaming services
Uh transportation, uh, you know stuff like that it categorizes it into categories
And then it picks whichever category you spent the most on that month
And then the first five hundred dollars you spent in that category
It will give you five percent cash back on and then one percent
It'll give you one percent on all on every other all the rest that you spent that month
So
The optimal play now I have these two credit card and I have to
Combine them in a way to get optimal cash back
The way to do it is to pick what i'm going to spend most of my money on which I think most
Most months would probably be
groceries
So I will buy all my groceries with the custom cash
I probably don't spend five. I don't spend five hundred dollars a month
On on groceries, but I spend the most so maybe I'll spend like two or three hundred or something on groceries
And I will get five percent back on that two or three hundred dollars
Probably not three hundred. Well, I will get five percent back on that much
And then I use my other card for everything else and get two percent back on everything that i'm not getting five percent back on
That's
And like the more the more cards you get the more you can like maybe kind of like min max
Like what your strategy is to get like the the the optimal cash back reward very very specific credit card for just
netflix or something
Yeah, genuinely. Yeah, like maybe you have a card that just has a deal with amazon and they offer like
You know five percent cash back only on
On streaming services
So you just get that card and you don't use it for anything except you just you pay for your streaming services with it
And then you just get five percent off your
Streaming services and the only the only problem is you just have to remember to pay the bill
um
I mean with most most most of the time with with churning like
You get a card you get the cash back the signup bonus
And then you either cancel it or you just never use it again
So you don't have to worry about about paying it back. You just like oh, I got the bonus. I don't need to use it anymore
Don't no no worries
I don't know this is like genuinely fun and like fascinating in sort of the way that maybe like fantasy football might be to some people
Where you're like meticulously like looking at stats and trying and trying to be like oh, how like how how will this work?
Like what's what's my strategy here?
Uh, uh, um
I don't know it's fucking epic is what i'm saying my new credit card is fucking epic
I uh
The idea of like
Taking care of all of that stuff though
I don't know. I'm not I'm not like that
I think it's it's fun. It's fun for it. This is like
when when I heard about churning I sort of
What when I realized when like I kind of knew this but when it clicked that like wait a minute
if you
If you like manage your credit cards and stuff if you like if you like do your your commerce in a certain way
You can just make it more efficient in a way that is effectively just free money
And like as soon as that clicked in my mind. I was like
why don't I just
Do that in every in every way that it's possible to do it
And I went down the rabbit hole and I found out about churning and I was like, why aren't I churning?
I probably should have been churning. Well the the reason why it's only now that I'm getting my second credit card
And I haven't been churning this whole time is because I've I've been waiting for
Something to require me to make a big part. It was the reason why I got my first one is because I had to make that big
It was like a thousand or two thousand dollars to print all those books
And I was like, well, I might as well get two percent cash back on those on that printing those
And then now now now it's now it's the I have to do the rad con stuff
And I'm like, well, I might as well use this rad con expense to qualify for a cashback bonus
I should definitely do that for
The lord of ghosts things I still have to order
The only thing I have right now is the pins but all the comics and the plush needs to get it's
Got to get it's
When I
You know, I made it into my 30s
Only you're ever using a debit card
I never use a credit card because everyone told me all the fucking boomers in my life told me
You know
Don't don't charge stuff to your credit card. Don't get into credit card debt credit card debt
Will fuck you and like yeah credit card debt will fuck you
But just don't ever get in credit card debt. Just use it like a debit card and pay it back immediately
And then there's no there's no risk of that at all and as long as you're doing that
Paying with credit is just better. It's just strictly better
And even more so if you're getting like cashback on it. So
like
Yeah
Everything you buy you should be using a credit card that gives you benefits
And even more so with like the the big expenses and stuff like printing books and and you know like and business stuff
Um
I'm I don't I'm I'm not sure what my next cards. I'm gonna wait a month. I'm gonna try and wait a month and then
No, I don't know I'll have to
A lot of a lot of the cards that have bigger sign-up bonuses have like very hard like requirements to hit like
They'll get like they'll give you like 500 dollars in credit
But you have to spend like nine thousand dollars in the first like
Three months and I'm like I'm not gonna do that, right?
So on rslash churning, there's a big huge like spreadsheet of like, okay
Here are the most
Here are the most optimal way to like churn to get the maximum cash benefit rewards
But there's there's two problems and there's two things that like kind of ruin this chart for me is that one
By far the most efficient like credit card rewards
You can get are in the form of like travel miles like like free miles with airlines
That's the best like value for money, but I don't travel and I don't use like air travel
So it sort of would be pointless for me to to to do those cards that do that
Unless there were some way to exchange them for cash, which is is not always the case
um
And then the second one is that yeah some cards just have really high requirements
Like you have to spend nine thousand dollars and three months. I I can't do that
So even though those are like the most efficient ones, I have to kind of like skip over those and just be like, okay
But like what can I qualify for? Oh, okay
city bank custom cash
I have to spend 750 dollars to get 200 dollars back. Yeah, I can do that. That's easy
So I don't I don't know what my next churn is going to be but like I'll I'll have to I'll have to mall
Let me know in the let me know in the comments if you've got any recommendations for uh for cards with easy cash back bonuses
And sign up bonuses that I can qualify for on a budget
It's uh, it's like it's like, uh, it's just like outsmarting
It's just outsmarting the banks
That's what it feels like
They're they're like they offer they offer you these they offer you these tempting little nuggets and they're like
Well, um sign sign my bargain sign this this bargain young man
Sign this this deal with the devil and and and we'll give you yes
We'll entice you we'll entice you with free money
But you know they do this with the expectation
That you will like fuck it up
You will violate the terms of the contract and then they can be like, aha. There was a secret clause
Now you're now you're in debt to us for life now we get your soul now you owe us all this interest
But if you if you just if you just
You just don't you just don't fuck it up. You do it exactly by the rules you beat them at their own game
You can just get free money out of them
And it's so based this is my new fucking thing. This is the new credit credit card podcast
Oh speaking of boring speaking of boring money shit that nobody wants to hear about. Uh, it's time for ben's bitcoin crypto corner
Update uh, everyone was wrong everyone was wrong to criticize me. It has in fact risen slightly
Since I bought yes, I did notice
So it was go it was trickling down, but it had another
Not a huge spike, but it spiked up above where it's still
It's the trend is still overall bearish. I am
I am considering that like maybe
This is made like like trading volume is kind of low. So maybe that means that this is a
temporary peak
And that it is
bearish
It is relative in fact bearish
Uh, bearish bearish means it's gonna go down bullish means it's gonna go up. Oh, okay. Yeah, I
I mean last
Last episode
I thought that it it it it definitely had slowed down
And then it was go and right after the episode
It went down, but then it's shot up again a little bit only on bitcoin though
On a theory it's just been going down
Really?
Well, not totally it did go up at the same time as bitcoin, but didn't go quite up
that much
So I guess I'll post the graph
It's not so bad that I sold
But I am worrying. I'm you know, you can't help but worry. They're like, oh shit
What if it does explode out of nowhere with no warning and no like you couldn't have been expecting that to happen
Yeah, and then I would have missed out on on all the money, but
This is this is um
Yeah, so I I bought in I bought in like last week at around
47 k and now it is it has been hovering around like 48 49 k
Uh this week. So, you know, it's up a little bit. It's not a huge gain or anything. Um,
It could it could crash at any moment. It could crash at any moment
But like yeah, like is is it gonna crash?
Is it gonna go to 100 k before the end of the year? Like either one of these things could happen
and
yeah, like
Sure, like investing in bitcoin is risky because it's volatile
but the the flip side of that
The flip side of that is that
Like not being in the this is this is the catch 22 not being invested is kind of just as risky because if
You don't have bitcoin and it explodes
You've lost money just as surely as if you were invested in bitcoin and it crashes
I mean, I guess it's not exactly the same because in one case your absolute number is going up versus down
but in terms of like in terms of like opportunity costs like
They're they're cut. They're pretty similar, right? So this is how I'm like
I feel like
I don't know the future
It could crash it could grow to it could just keep growing and growing it could explode again. Um, I feel like
Maybe maybe this is cope, but I feel like the the sensible thing to do they say diversify your assets, right?
like
If I if I have some a little bit of bitcoin and it crashes
Well, I lost some money
But if I have a little bit then if it if it if it explodes then I didn't lose out. So I feel like
I don't feel like I'm being um
too, uh, too, uh, uh
Unreasonable
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah
Well, your reasonableness makes sense. Yeah, yeah, yeah explainable
Next next week it might go to 20 and I'll be like, well
Shows what I know
God, I hope not
I mean if it does, I'll be happy because then I'll be like, ah, Pog it's so low
Pledge get get back in
I feel I feel so shitty because I was I was looking at it casually like last
In July I saw it going down to
I saw it approaching 30 and I considered maybe I should buy in when it hits 30
But I I was like, no, I think it's gonna keep going down
I'm gonna buy in when it hits 20 and then low and behold it hits 30
Hover's bounces back and has just been steadily climbing since then and has almost hit 50
If I had if I had just bought in then if I had just bought in then when I was thinking about maybe doing it
You know, that's just how it is. That's just how I go. I would I would have been like I would be at fucking
Fucking 160 percent or whatever
My profits would be skyrocketing
I'd be a regular brad garling house
Uh, but uh, it is what it is
It is what it is unfortunately
So, okay, that's all I have to say about that. Oh, but on the last
subject
On the on the subject of money on the subject of gold. I did a noita
Challenge run. I did a no gold run
Uh, where I did not obtain any gold
and it wasn't
That hard it was kind of hard
But I was I was trying to do a pacifist run for a while and that was really hard
because
The pacifist run is annoying because there are some things that will
Usually count as you not killing something
like
Kicking kicking an object into some an enemy and crushing them with it. I don't think that counts as
Killing them but throwing something throwing a tablet out of your inventory and crushing them
I think that does count as a kill as or as a deliberate kill most of the time
Or at least some of the time
and i'm not and i'm not exactly sure of the rules because
It it's not always consistent like whether something counts as a double as a as an environmental kill and and gives you double gold or not and it's like
The thing about the the pacifist run is
You you can't even you can't even kill the final boss you you have to
You have to get the final the thing from the final boss
Not kill him and then make your way to you have to make your way to the like win zone on your own
Which is actually very difficult like like you have you would have to um
Dig your way you have to dig your way to it through all this stuff. You need black holes. You need like advanced stuff
so you you have to be like
Doing the pacifist run you have to be prepared not just to win the game
Which is relatively easy, but you have to be doing like post endgame
like
you know like
Game manipulation or not game manipulation, but like environmental manipulation stuff in order to actually
Reach the place where it will count you as having
gotten
You know the pacifist run so that one was too hard. So I set my sights down lower
I needed the no gold around and I got it baby. I fucking got it. So
mission
Accomplished
So i'm rich in real life, but i'm poor in noida. That's that's the takeaway
Wow
Wow, I know what you did. I understood
I really did
Is that I you're being sincere, right? No. Oh
Okay, I genuinely wasn't sure
Okay, um
I just didn't get any gold. I just beat the game without getting any gold
You didn't get any gold for sure. Imagine just imagine what that entails and that's what I do. I can't purchase any
drinks
Can't purchase any no can't buy any wands
you you can
You can't buy wands, but you can steal spells and this is what I did you you can if you
Because like when you get to the holy mountain the wands are floating
You can't move the wands, but the spells
They're in like the shop area and you can buy them
But if you dig the ground out from under them they fall and if they fall out of the holy mountain
They become free and you don't have to pay for them
So I did I did some of that where I like used luminous drill to dig them out and then just pick them up for free off the ground
That's a bit of a
I mean, it's not a cheat. It's in there deliberately, but that's a bit of a
kind of like
A cheeky little strap that they let you get away with
Uh, I didn't use it that I think I used it for some drills or something to like speed up my rate of fire
Oh, no, there's a chainsaw. I found a chainsaw in a in a and I was like, well, I need that
And then I got and then I got a and then I got a chainsaw running with triplicate bolt
and then I with a mana re recharger and then I was just
machine gunning out like triplicate bolts in a fucking
Blast and then I found and then I found a glamour. I found a green glamour spell
So instead of shooting out little little green
Bullets I was shooting out like green like
Like like energy like beams like green little little sparkly energy beams
Uh, and then I went up to I went up to uh, what's his name? Um, um,
Cole me I went up to Cole me and I was
Was eviscerated him
Uh, that was that was those were the those were the days. That was uh, that was a good one. No, I'm done
I'm done with noida. I'm done with all the things I had on my little uh talk about list. So
I don't know. We could go to voicemails or what? Yeah, I I feel kind of stupid. I didn't have anything to talk about today
I'm not not not feeling very good either
Mmm
What a what a terrible episode
What a terrible episode. Oh, I'm so sorry about the terrible episode everybody
It's okay. As always. I carried as always. I carried us over the finish line
Uh, I brought I brought the heat
Uh, uh, uh, you know
I had you know, I get it. I don't worry. I got enough twitter arguments to to this week to to fill a whole episode
No wasted no wasted content. Oh, you should you should get even even more twitter arguments
So you have even more content. That's what it's all about, baby
This is what it's all about. This is what it's all about is just building
A lifestyle that reinforces the the toxic and like useless behavior that I that I want to be engaging in
That I am addicted to engaging in I need to build my life around
Incentivizing myself to continue to do those things like like making content out of complaining about obnoxious twitter arguments that don't accomplish anything
Um, that's how you fucking do it
Yeah, let's let's let's go to voicemail
Okay
speakpipe.com
For your voicemail to be read
that listen to
is
true
Okay, I got the first one up here
It's called, uh
4 20 69
Wait a minute. I hit the download button, but I don't need to download it
Yeah
Okay, there. Yeah, I'm just doing it for my okay. Yeah, okay 4 4 20 69 3 2 1 go
This is snake. Do you read me?
I'm infiltrating the leak of Nate fuckers right now. They have just taken over cobble
I was in their base, but I got locked out because I had to take a leak
I'm scared Nate heads
They have a metal gear designed to beat other metal gears that are designed to beat other metal gears
It's called metal gear sex
I can't believe the united states let it get into the hands of the league
I'll do my best to stop them
If you want updates my frequency is for 120 point 69 nice
Uh
Nice uh voice modulator god, I hope god, they're they're based in cobble cobble like minecraft like cobble like monster cobble
Yeah
God, I hope I hope the tally band doesn't know that they all want to fuck Nate without fucking execute them the mouth
Uh, oh, yeah, how do we know the league of Nate fuckers is not the tally band
Have we ever seen them in the same room
No
Now there's a
True
I it could be true. So it's true
That's that's how it works. That's all I could
Chris could have Chris could have 10 years ago
concocted a plan to to uh to pretend to be a woman
And and then executed it flawlessly
And even in private when no one was looking over the next 10 years. It could be true. So it's true. Oh my god
I just what I pointed that one lady
She was like
She gave me the link to like the time that chris said that thing 10 years ago
And I was like it's 10 years old you psycho and she was like
Pre-meditation bitch
You're insane. You're deranged. Yeah pre-med
She was like this just proves pre-meditation the fact that it was 10 years ago only proves that it was deliberate this whole time
Genuinely get help
Get help. Um, the next one is a youtube link. Um
I think
Oh, it's it's that pardon jesse's video where he yells at the thing
And let's just says funny words directed it towards certain individuals
Well, I mean
He sure did
It's funny
My hands are not entirely clean in this regard and I cannot throw stones
Um
Same
What what can I say? What what can I say? I mean, uh, oh, this this is called at poorly aged stuff
Sure. Yeah, but point point made point made
um
Okay, next one is called the ruthless aggression arc
uh, wait, um
I mean to download the why did I download that one? It was just a youtube link. Uh
No, no rename. No delete it for my files
Okay, next one is called the ruthless aggression arc three two one go
It's time for a new tommy j arc because we're bored. We're bored of the last tommy j arc
Everybody's obviously bored of it. Oh
Oh, we ate this up. We ate this fucking pcb comment show shit up up the last seven times
He did but this time it got old anymore. It got old. I'm sorry. This is a minute 30
This is a minute 30. We actually didn't want you to do anything at all. Well, well, you know what?
You know what? This is a narrative. It keeps fucking going. I keep doing this shit
And it it always has to do not understand the concept of it got old
The longer it goes the older it becomes the fucking mystic marbles guy
And there's some other repeat offenders these people who in the who are just like, okay. Yeah, okay. I get it other people made
Other boy smells that weren't as annoying. So why are you the only one that people get not the only one?
Why are you the one that people are annoyed at currently? I don't know. Okay. I stopped listening. Uh, all right
reflect on yourself
Next one is a fast upload link
and um
ineffectual versus intellectual I will say that
You know what?
I wasn't gonna mention it, but I don't I don't care anymore. Tommy j sent me a dm on twitter wherein he claimed that like
basically he was only pretending to be an annoying voicemailer and like
It was all a bit. He was playing a character of a terrible voicemailer
He did a very good job. He did a really good job
Uh, so whatever it's fine. Uh, whatever. No, it's it's fine. It's great. Okay
Just
Just I don't know. I don't want to make too big an issue of it. I don't want to like I don't want to call
Him out. He's not a fucking terrible person
Just because he made a couple annoying voicemails, but like have a little have a little humility and just like when people say like
I'm sick of this bit
Just be like, okay. Sorry
Just have a little humility about it. I think that's what's what's missing here. Okay. Um, next one is called ineffectual versus intellectual
three two one go
You an ineffectual all the best like deals all the best situations you get in life because like you knew someone and they were like
Oh, hey, I can hook you up get a friend who's got a job doing that and they recommend you
And then you get a job and you just get like pretty good money networking. It's important
Yeah, yeah, the uh, the reputation of specific artists, right is what actually drives the prices skill really doesn't matter
I an intellectual
Fuck all these people. They're all in a big club and i'm not in it. Uh, it's all about who you know
It's it's all bunch of those are the same thing
Those are the same thing
Uh in ineffectual
I don't know what that would
I mean like they're saying
the clips of of various pcp members saying
Uh networking, it's who you know and then the second one is it's who you know and I don't like that
I'm not who they know. It's the same thing
Yeah, it sucks that that's how it works, but you've got to do it. That's just sort of normal
The the first is me the well me and others saying this is how it works
The second is me complaining that that's how it works. I don't this this reminds me of um
Um
This reminds me of okay, Sean
It all comes back to Sean. You're Sean made it made it. I think it was like two weeks ago or something
I saw this Sean tweeted that like
He he made sort of a jokey tweet that like his guilty pleasure
Was like seeing seeing like in basically look seeing incels like self-defeating ideology where they let they convince themselves that they are like a
An undatable monster because like, you know, they're they're like only five foot nine and not five foot ten or whatever, right?
He said like that's a guilty pleasure of his and then
Like a couple days later. He made
Another tweet that was like critical of incels. He like he said that like, you know, he said that
I don't remember what it was, but it was something to the effect of like
Yeah, this incel ideology is is a problem. You know, it's it's not rational and you know, it's it's bad that people think this
and I saw people
being like calling him a hypocrite
and seeing like the hypocrisy is so obvious
because
He's because on the one because first he said that he
liked that he got entertainment from something
and then later he said
that it's not a good thing and like
There's no contradiction there at all. I saw so many people being calling Sean a hypocrite because
He said that on one hand his guilty pleasure is is enjoying seeing this flawed thing
And then the second was him saying that the thing is flawed and those are like kind of the same idea
And this this is I mean, this is honestly, this is just obviously this is the same
I don't
I'm not sure how seriously to take the criticism that this uh that this voicemail is offering me
But those just seem like the same thing. I couldn't even really tell if it was a criticism
at first
It might be I mean, I guess I suppose clips are you
Yeah, I mean, I think it's a joke, but like
I don't I don't know
um
The intel the intellectual I guess the point is that
The second one
I honestly I could I can't tell if it's ironically calling the second one the intellectual point like the intellectual
Like the smart thing is to say like fuck it
And the and it's it's dumb to be like
Oh, you got a network. You got a network. You got to know people and it's
And it's smart to be like
Fuck knowing people. It's all a big club
Or if it's ironic and the actual opinion being espoused is the exact opposite of that
I could see it going either way
um
I don't know
Lamal
I let let's let's just move on. I mean being not in big clubs is annoying
I think we can yeah, it's terrible
This is the this this is the fucking
Tragedy of my whole life is that I'm not in a big fucking club
This is the tragedy of like almost everyone's life actually is that they're not in the big club where you get access to
You know, what whatever life?
Well, I mean I have access to normal life. I don't have access to like
Uh
Big media big media big media collections or something like that. Right. Sure. Yeah, right exact. Yeah, that
That's what it's all about. It's all about getting those poggers connections
Ah
Next voicemail is called elwood edwards
three two one go
So I listened to nate's new podcast and here are my thoughts. It's a bunch of idiots
Talking about especially signs. They do know about getting into topics
They know nothing about where they're contradicting themselves and spreading misinformation
Just making everyone listening dumber in the process
With some cringe moments sprinkled. Okay
So it's basically exactly the same as this podcast and I'll be happy to listen to hundreds of episodes faced
Anyway, crack was good last week. You should have him on more. That was like that was like through two weeks
I don't know. Okay. Uh, this must have been. Yeah, okay. Um
Cracks cool
Cracks are really cool guy. Cracks are really smart guy. I like crack a lot. Yeah. Yeah
Uh, yeah, that sounds that sounds like about
That sounds that sounds about like what I would expect a nate podcast to be
So, you know good good for him. I guess uh lemal
Next one is called alaskan weeb
three two one go
Hey guys, like fuck Trixie and all that but also I was listening to the
Like two weeks ago podcast and then it's just unrelated and
It might be the only one who finds it a little bit hilarious that despite Trixie being the one who gets
Blastered with labels like pedophile and all that her ex-wife is the one who tried to sleep with the teenager
Am I the only one who's finding this little cherry on top of this disgusting?
Sunday to be just
So good and then the fact that she's
Aligning herself with the kind of people who scream save our children save our children
When she's the kind of person that they're trying to save their children from
I mean, I don't know. I'm who's just thinking I mean
You'll you'll you'll get you'll get no defense of may from me
I I do okay. I don't I don't know really that much about the situation. I I thought that the girl
That may have sent those creepy creepy
like DMs trying to uh trying to like
Trying to like emotionally three some pressure emotionally pressure this like yeah this like
This like fucking battered woman into having a threesome with like her ex-wife her ex-husband and her together
Like I thought those creepy emails were I thought the girl was 18
I think
I think I mean, I think Ethan was probably like fucking her before she was 18
I think might might be legal depending on the state. So that's not a criminal. That's not necessarily a criminal allegation
um, but uh
The the I thought she was 18, but I mean
I mean, yeah may may is terrible and
I don't know what else to say
May is an impressively terrible may is terrible person
May is uh save our children save our children stop the steal big nick fuente's fan big fucking white
Oh, man. I should I mention the
The the tweet the tweet she made when when she announced did I mean I don't think I think this was this week
When she announced her being pregnant. She said like she said that it never never been never been a better time
It's the perfect time to have a baby
It's the best time to have a baby and she linked to the census stats showing that like the amount of white people in america has declined
She's literally she's literally
She's literally saying like I need to start having babies to protect the white race. There's no subtext there
She's just she's just out to like save the white race. This is just unironically what she's about. I think
I really think
I I know it's it's it might it might seem a little bit
It might seem a little hypocritical of me
Because I was never this hard on may before but if you like used if you used to like may
I I was I never liked me
I never I never like publicly criticized her because she never like had a real opinion publicly until a certain point
And then she did but if you if I feel some people say like I used to like may I used to like may on like the
Whatever their fucking side channel was called if you used to like may I think you're an idiot
I really think you are you are there's
You fucked up and you need to like reflect and like think about like what's wrong with you that made you have that opinion
I really think she's that bad even honestly even aside from just her like nightmarish politics
She also just sucks in general
Um, but then all she's also a nazi on top of it. So, you know, it's a real
It's a real layer cake
of problems
um
Anything you want to add
uh
No
Okay, next
Next fucker next voicemail is called toxic three two one go
I don't watch the pcp anymore. I've seen some of the most recent episodes tommy
And i'm not gonna watch it's a minute 30 of any more of it
And i'll tell you why this is a dent to like a pcp currently
reminds me
Of a fucking high school girls
I kind of want to see where's going with this
Oh, i'm just doing me. You just do you or i have my art you how you are
And our artists or our guests they got there
Yeah
That's true
No, that's not actually what's going on here. It's it's it's a veneer
that you use to
Make it seem nicer and it actually is this was actually going on
Is that there's the purse there's the king
There's the queen b
Ben
What and then everybody else is just looking for
For opportunities looking for weaknesses looking for slip-ups things that you weren't supposed to say
And then when the moment is right someone strikes and then they get clout
They're clout facers
Oh, you're a liiib ben
Ben's kind of cringe now. I don't know
I don't have no idea
But you made this this is all you this
It's that's a that's a
That's a bit. It's it's some kind of a bit, right? I I think so
The silly voice makes me think it's it's got to be some somewhat of a bit
I I don't know what the bit is. I couldn't really get a grasp of what the character
The bit I just feel like it's someone like what if there was a character who had no idea what the hell they were talking about
What a great bit
The bit is that the pcp
Is it is a high school girls club?
Okay, so so we pretend to be nice to each other
But actually we're all here to try and like tear ben down for clout. I guess he said it
He said I was the he said I was the queen b
He didn't say who the he said there was a king and that I am the queen b. Who's the king?
um
And then
Who who's who's trying to tear me down you you and tom the guests?
Yeah, who you haven't noticed
Uh, of course
I'm always on it's because I never let my guard down. It's because I never have any weaknesses to exploit
That's the secret. It's just like when you sign up for a credit card
All you get you just never let give any weaknesses for the banks to exploit
You just never fail the Faustian bargain you keep to all the terms and then you trick them out of their money
You never let them get you. Um
I don't know. I I could I guess I could ponder this
I guess I could ponder the intent behind this this voicemail all day, but maybe it's maybe it's not worth it
Uh
Okay, the next one is a is an imager link. It's an it's another beam
It's the same
Same fucking they're doing it on purpose now. They're doing it on purpose. Okay. I like it now
Wait, okay. Um, we've got you surrounded stop drawing
Yeah, I love draw. Okay. You know what?
You know what actually this one's pretty funny
Mesh did she she did be drawing
She did be drawing during the podcast. She did be drawing during the podcast and you know what?
Can't I can't even begrudge her that I can't okay, so this time we got me for sure
Yeah, and we got you and then you there's only fucking fruit flies. Why are there fruit flies in my room?
Where they fucking come from fruit probably
There's no
Are you calling me a fruit?
I'm calling you a person who buys a fruit
Do you not buy fruit?
Is it not pito? Sometimes I buy a tomato. That's a fruit, but I don't keep it in my room
Oh, oh, yeah
Oh, okay. Okay. There's you and me and that's gotta be taboo
Probably and then mate. That's I guess it's the sunglasses and then I'm not really sure who that should be at the bank
Is it Trixie?
It doesn't seem like it would be Jesse
It doesn't look like Tom or Jesse
I think it's gotta be Trixie. Yeah, it's gotta be Trixie, but it's a very strange face
It is a very strange. I don't know this meme. Is this a meme that this person has drawn or is it an actual meme that other people make?
Were you were you on last week?
I've seen another version of this
There yeah, this this is a meme. This is a meme that I I saw around
Like on twitter and stuff a while ago
I didn't really get it and the more versions of it. I see
I feel like the the less I understand it
I think it's like the people coming through the door
Are coming to get the person behind the table
for
Whatever they're doing and the person behind the table
Is insane and is still doing it
Well, sometimes it's that but sometimes they're like they're doing the opposite of it or they're saying something like
else they're saying
I guess the idea is that the person
I think okay. I think the the intent of the meme is to poke fun at the person behind the table
for because they they think
That people are out to get them for something
So like you literally depict these people like cia agents busting through your door coming to get you for whatever it is
Right. I I think the idea is that the person behind the table is crazy because like ha ha. This is what you think
Like you think this is what's happening
That's that's my interpretation
and it's
true
Where's the door have like little arms?
The door frame has like a weird arm. It looks it looks like a coat rack. It looks like yeah
It doesn't look like a door or like a clothing rack like a long pole
I like mage's I like mage's face a lot and this one. Yeah, she looks great. She looks great. Um, okay, uh, yeah
mage do be she do be drawing though
next next voicemail, uh is uh
Wait, where did I?
Oh, I fucking tabbed off the here we go. Um, next voicemail is called jabroni 101
three two one go
Well, we're finally here. Aren't we pcp fans a year and a half later?
And we finally get confirmation of what we all should have known all along
Which is that the brony files have been deleted, you know tweeted as tricksy mentions themselves
And you know, what were we thinking right guys, you know
They gave the middle finger to the fans and they said in the radcon for discord
I don't have to respect people just because they gave me money
And you know, they're gonna reshoot the lecture supposedly with a different audience and oh boy that video totally won't get this like bombed
Am I right guys?
I would love I would
I mean, yeah, I mean, yeah, that's all true. Um
I
I would I would love
To see because yeah back back in the day well back in the day
Because she changed her story a bunch of times
She's like at first she said that she wanted to heavily edit the lecture then she changed the story to
I want to
Film new footage to combine with the old footage
Then it was just I want to just completely rerecord it
And and I'll let my and Riley will make red con five will produce red con five and you should all come and I'll let my and I'll let
My crony throw a throw a rap concert which rad con five will be like a side attraction for
And then we'll do it there. I guess
um, and then it was
Radio silence for like months and months
And then it was I've deleted it lemal and but then when she after she announced that she deleted someone asked her about it and she said
she said like um
I've she said something like I've said I've said before that I was interested in rerecording it
But it would have to be with a different audience because I won't work with ben anymore
lemal, um
she
She she didn't she didn't mention the idea
You know
The idea of rerecording it had been floated before she had said she would not release the original
She wanted to record it, but I would really like to see her try to do it now
Because now you know she she doesn't even have like who would she do it in front of?
Yeg is gone. Yeg is split. You know
It's literally just her
and her boyfriend
living in her parents house
Just smoking weed with her mom and like getting a fucking allowance
for living just for living for free
and smoking weed 24 seven that's that's
I mean literally the audience would be like her boyfriend and her parents like that would be the audience
I mean I'd like to see it. I would like to see it even like
The idea of redoing it
Does she care to tell the story again? Even no, of course not. It's it's an asinine like deflection
It's it's it's just her trying to put off responsibility. It's like yeah
I trashed the lecture, but only because I want to rerecord it lol like oh, oh, oh, okay. Yeah
I mean just imagining her doing like travel all the way across the country
Imagining her doing that is so funny that I wish I wish it were true
I wish it were a thing that that would ever happen. No, I mean
Okay, humoring the idea that she would actually do it
She would do it just like the fucking the what were they called the little lectures that she did on the yeg channel
Which are like look like shit and they're filmed on a phone
That it would it would look like that and she would see no she would see no no problem with that
Um with that aspect of it anyway
Um, yeah, I don't know. I'm pretty mad about it, but you know what else is new
fruit fly
okay, um
Next voicemail. Yep
It's called janes three two one go
I think it's fine for teenagers to have internet world models like best guy ever
As they are growing up in the world and they need to have people to take reference from
besides their parents
But as they grow into young adults
They should recognize what faults their role models have and aspire to be better than them
As well as decide what positive impact they want to have on the world
I think I mean in general
I guess I agree in general. Sure
I think I think I mean, I think nate is a weird choice of role model, but whatever
Yeah, I don't know
I get that like
You you're young and you see videos and you don't realize whether they're good or not necessarily you just sort of like the what you like
And then when you grow older you should look
Maybe critically on your past
nostalgia stuff
Not all of it's gonna work
Not all of it's gonna be something that you're gonna carry forward for the rest of your life or
Is a good thing to base your life off of so I don't know
I guess so I guess that's
Fair
Yeah, fair. Yeah, sure. I don't I don't begrudge. I mean, I don't I don't
begrudge people
I mean
I mean, I'm I'm old and I still I mean, I still really like Sean
I still like I guess I kind of look up to him a little bit like I I think he's a
Smart guy who I would like like to emulate in some way
I mean not like he's not my role model or anything
But I really like his opinions and I appreciate him
So I guess I don't think it's it's not bad to like
Think someone's cool on the internet. I don't know
um
Sure. Yeah, whatever
Next voicemail is another it's another image. I will post it in the
We'll post it in the chat here for elisar
The virgin home buyer versus the chat bitcoin gambler
I think this has got to be a crack versus me. I think yes
Yeah
Virgin's great because it's it's the right way to do this thing where the chat is insane and not good
The chat is
No, but but actually kind of but actually but actually kind of kind of based kind of based the virgin home buyer
Has to jump through bureaucratic hoops
Spends a fortune on a house with a leaky roof props up a system that he hates oof
The chat bitcoin gambler knows it's sinful to possess money
So he feeds it to the great blockchain in the sky
His own decisions shapes his future banks and the irs can't touch him because he'll never make a problem
I like my like fucking like acid green like cyborg. I like i'm hacked into the matrix really really hard
And you're like grabbing the whole of the laptop with one palm
Just like all the way around
The real the real bitcoiners. Yeah, they have a phone in one hand laptop in another just holding it up with your thumbs
Something is weird with the chat is like gonna
It's like I got a bulge but the like side
Like the thigh is a sort of like weirdly bulbous on on the sides as well. I don't know what it's supposed to be
Well, I mean
Yeah, I'm not sure. Maybe that's a
artifact from the original
chat
Maybe his his original muscly thighs were like that. Yeah, I'm just kind of have lumpy hips. I guess which is true to life
I suppose
um
man
poor poor crack with his fucking
home ownership
What a nerd uh holding like a receipt of all the people he has to pay
Just being like oh god
all these
This this is the thing when you own stuff when you own property
Comes responsibility when you are when you own nothing
When you're like me
And you are bereft of property and all you have is is data
You're free
You set yourself set yourself free of this of these material chains change the buying no no nothing
No money. Nope. No money. No problem. No money. No problems as they say it. What if you could churn bitcoins?
What would that look like?
I mean
Well, that doesn't mean you you could no you that's not doesn't make any fucking sense. That's not god damn it
um
coin
Next voicemail, okay
This is called hemlo corgo nine the huss
Uh, this is sent from ben saint pisses on him
him
Himmels in the bathtub at aol.com. I think
That hemlo corgo sent me a dm or saying
Please don't play my voicemail. I was really drunk when I made it
So now I want to know so in three two one go
Hey ben, um, just to start this off real quick. I would like to um clarify that my pronouns are she her
Because you have had any trouble
deciphering that fact
You know because you're super cringe and you're a boomer and you're old. I'm sorry. I do
I do assume mails by default sometimes
The series videos are way better than yours and they're also incredibly enjoyable to listen to
So I don't have a problem with sarah zed
Why do you think there's so much like more fun to listen to?
And why do you think for hussy so hard?
even though they have
like repeatedly committed
Extremely shady business practices in the past
I love hussy too. I love homestuck. I love psychologials, but okay you simp for the hus
Really really hard and it's pretty cringe
And I would just like what your justification for that
It's not it's not true. I deny the charges
I I don't simp
I I like hussy and I admire hussy as an artist. I have never I have never defended his business practices. I said
that
I do I do like I do appreciate hussy
More than sarah zed on the whole
I think hussy has done more for the world
But I mean that's a pretty broad claim
Um, I don't defend any of the like weird business shit that hussy is obviously
Hussy is a terrible business person who runs like a kind of a train wreck of a company
Like I think that's pretty established now and I don't think
I've literally settled. I've literally set I'm repeating myself, but just since you asked
Sarah's ed. I don't I don't begrudge her making any of those videos. I don't think she's wrong to do it even if
even if the attitude
Literally just the attitude in her thumbnail because I didn't even watch the video because I already know what she's gonna say
Uh, uh, even if the attitude in her thumbnail annoys me. I don't begrudge her that I don't have anything against her
Even if I'm not like super impressed with her
Right like she's fine. Um, I haven't watched her new shipping video. I might
I might watch I was I was annoyed. I was annoyed to see it trending on twitter
because it's like
It's just a youtube just a youtuber released a video and it's like trending news on twitter
I saw the shipping the the thumbnail. I was like the shipping wars. I'm like, okay
This can't be interesting. There's no way it's interesting
I don't it's a people people discussing people sort of video
Yeah, it's it's gonna be
I mean, I can take some guesses as to what happened
I
the okay
The like even like the definitions of the words pro shipper and anti shipper. I'm like not a hundred percent
I feel like sometimes I hear them called like
Like pro shippers are like pedophiles and like they're pro like pedo and like incest and rape stuff
and I
I think that's what the the distinction is
But I don't I don't know
I could be wrong. I could be totally off base there. So, I mean I can imagine it's
You know, I mean I'm I'm Minerva
What's her fucking handle
double cast
Made that video about uh, you know the fandom the harry potter troll lady who did the whole the fake accounts and the harry potter fan fiction
I mean, it's probably kind of like that, you know, like some factions agree on this thing some don't there's there's drama
There's people make there's probably false allegations
This drama constantly every so often I catch like some either it's like super smash brothers
Or like some artist who was abusive and it's like it's just hashtags and twitter threads
And it's like here's a thread about this person. I'm like
I never it's whatever it doesn't matter
I don't care. I will never care. I it could be interesting. I don't know. I might watch it eventually. I haven't watched it yet
Um, I don't know the point is to which these things are like big deals is never really that big
I feel if somebody became like a serial murderer and then I'd be like, holy shit. What the fuck
You play smash and then you go kill a hundred people. That's a bit. That's a bit of an interesting story
Hello, you say that I'm simping for hussey. I think you're simping for sarah zed here here because I never said that I had a problem with her
There's no reason to be upset and here you are
Here you are. You're upset that I
Am not that I am not like enthusiastically
like praising sarah, so I
Uh, I I like hussey. I admire hussey. I
admit
He is a man of many faults who has fallen short of the mark
many times, uh
and that's
I just you know, it is it is what it is. Okay. I think that's all I have to say about that
Um next voicemail is called tricksy was wrong three two one go
So a couple weeks ago you were talking about the criteria for a good lecture
um
Which I guess my understanding of it was something you might not check out otherwise
Or maybe it's not as successful or easy to get into but it has merits
And I it got me to think about like some of the other old
Ideas people had had for lectures that didn't come to pass
Uh, the biggest one for me would have been tricksy's
Uh, coheed and camry lecture and she would always bring up the fact that she didn't think it would be a good lecture
But I wholeheartedly disagree. I've really gotten into that fan as as of late and I like
It's great to listen to but it's not easy to get into there's a lot more going on behind the scenes
And it would make a really good lecture if someone really went in and broke that down
Um, I mean as someone who will never ever like
Listen to coheed and camry and delve into like the lore of like what their songs are about
I would say that that is like, yeah pretty good
Pretty if it if it's telling like a lore based story. Yeah, that's something that I would never check out for myself
But would maybe like explained to me by someone who did
So I guess I agree. It sounds like it could be a good lecture. Yeah
Um, next one is called tricksy was wrong clarification
three two one go
To clarify what I mean by a lot going on is that the quote-unquote story is across a bunch of mediums and and it isn't easy to experience
Yeah, that yeah, that's what I thought
That's what that was. I what I thought it was like
okay, um
Next one is called
It's a little emoji. It's like a little like one concerned eyebrow over the face
That's a colon and a backslash like a face
Looks kind of concerned
Looks kind of concerned maybe a little judgmental little sus there. Maybe yeah
Yeah on the on the brink of sus
If you have the other eyebrow raised then it would be sus
Three two one go
So I've stuck to what I said in the last voicemail I left
And I have avoided
listening to the new episode of the podcast this Friday as I'm recording this
And uh, I don't know you guys. I mean it could be a coincidence. This is only one data point
But it feels like best Friday. I've had in a few months or so. I don't know
um
Okay. Oh, I guess
You know, I mean I get Tommy j told me that he was a heel
All along and that it was all but now he's he's he's he's he's leaning into the heel bit. He's he's he's going full heel turn
Uh, how long?
How long will the I don't listen to the pcp anymore bit stay fresh? Uh, find out
I mean if it happens one more time this episode, I think it will have soured already
I think
I don't know if it can even last one more
ever
Uh, next one is called
Tony three two one go
I'm gonna be honest I've submitted like five of these voicemails already
But I never remember to check for future pcp episodes where mine might be on
And besides I close the podcast
Right at that part anyway, so it's not like I why do you send voicemails if you don't listen to the voicemail?
I will never hear your reaction to this
Why
It's just musing on the idea that that no, what do you know? I'm just throwing it to the wind
I just how interesting
I
It takes all kinds I guess
I mean, I don't I don't know
Um
Next one is called apologizing for one upping. Sorry. It's bad. Sorry. Apologizing
GUZ for one upping. Sorry. It's bad. She heard three two one go
I'm sorry. I I I swear. I'm not an edgy 14 year old. Okay
I I painted myself in the wrong light by bringing up the insufferable social media argument
You know, I was just trying to bridge the gap between where I I fell in, you know
I was an edgy 11 year old
You know from from what I could parse what I did understand. I was like hell. Yeah, this is funny
You know, all right. I I learned my lesson. All right as I never listened to the insufferable media podcast
So I have no opinion of monkey jones in real time. I have no opinion about not actually in real time
But as I listened throughout episodes, I watched him
Disappear and that that that that's made me start to realize, you know
As as monkey jones slowly faded as my role model
It it became you guys and you know, I guess just another thing I want to say
Is that effectively having listened to you for so long? Um, you guys are all basically like parental figures to me
And it's really weird. Uh, it sure is
Sure, it's weird. Sure. It's weird. Don't all right here as your
parental figure I must say
Don't listen to us. Don't do that. Don't look up to us. That's really stupid
uh
um
Yeah, I I would say
I don't want I don't want that kind of responsibility. Uh
You learn learn from my mistakes
And nothing else
Next one is called on kiwi farms ideology
three two one go
I recall correctly one of the things that was like downright said on kiwi farms was that they will misgender like
Trans lulcows and the lgbt members of kiwi farms will be fine with it
And also the guy who runs it is also a great replacement conspiracy not an anti-semitic. So yeah, they clearly have an ideology
whether they want to admit it or not
yeah, that's
That's the that's the attitude of like, you know, like all all the all the lgbt
and and lgbt q and and in particular trans people that have been
Raging at me because like
You shouldn't don't make
Don't make her one of us. Don't make Chris one of us. No. No, keep it away. Don't let it be one of me. No
um
It's it's yeah, it's that same like self-hating like gatekeeping
Pick me. I'm one of the good ones
shit that like is so typical of that kind of like
You know, I mean kiwi farms is a website
About bullying people
So of course you go there
You get bullied. You're you're you're an lgbt freak. You get bullied
They'll let you they'll let you stick around and they won't harass you
But only if you only if you like kowtow and put up with like the fact that like they think less of you
so
You know, of course, of course, that's the type of course. That's the type right like if you're like, I don't know
sort of like
Think of yourself the way that they think of you
And you're like, yeah, that they're right. They're right because I hate myself. They hate me. It just makes sense. You know
Yeah, yeah, stupid. Yeah, they man. They really they really fucking hate this like trans e celeb
They really fucking hate them and be and are and like they're they don't accept. They think they're faking. They think they're agp
Faker. Yeah, I agree too because because I'm not like that because I'm I'm different like I'm I'm one of the real ones
Right. I'm not faking like like whoever, right?
You know
What what more do I need to say it's sad
um
Yeah
Next one is for reference in regards to the natehead
three two one go
Okay, ben recognized my voice cool, uh for reference the whole thing to the angry natehead was actually death alchemist
Old thing that tom used to do back when he was right about to leave the pony days where right when he was talking about the episode
He would like give the good but then right when he would give his criticisms
He would like, you know, say exactly what I said on the podcast and it was just the
Just the funniest thing to me
Uh, I'm guessing you guys don't remember it, but it was something that definitely stuck with me just a dumb small thing
I don't I don't remember that at all
Do you remember what he's talking about? I think he's referring to the time where tom
did his
like
I'm leaving the fandom
Portion portion of a video like he was doing he was doing a brony analysis, whatever
And at the end he's like, well, you know what I don't like doing this and I'm not gonna do it anymore
And you know what you all suck. I can't remember how like inflammatory he was
I don't think he was actually like like a jesse level like fuck you
But he did sort of piss a lot of people off
And everyone was really really upset with him
And uh, that was funny. Yeah
is
So it was a reference to tom's
I'm leaving the the brony fandom
thing
I think so
I don't okay. I believe the video is gone because
cringe
I mean, it's not it's not cringe
No, that's history. Don't erase history
No
Bring it back. You know what I I I learned release release the tommy cut
What I learned realized years ago. Um
brony curious is like mr. Plinkett style review of some pony episode was gone
Oh, it was of of equestria girls
Yeah, it's gone the the plinkett brony curious. I wanted to rewatch it. It was it was actually good
You know what? Yeah
Me too. I have these I don't remember when it was it might have been like two years ago or something
But yeah, I also like I was going back to rewatch it just because
And it was and I couldn't I think I could find like the first episode somewhere
um
I'm not sure maybe it's on like a playlist. So it might just be unlisted, but I couldn't yeah, I couldn't find it
I I guess I could ask tongue just to see if if I if it's unlisted if I could have a link
But it's like I don't really care that much to rewatch it. I just don't like that. It's gone. You know, I don't like that
It's gone. I I don't understand
I I really don't understand the attitude of like
I like I like why like why get rid of it because it's because it's brony related like so what who cares
I don't know the whole channel is brony related
well
Not anymore, right? It's rebranded
Or wait, did he have did he
He made a different account for brony curious. He had a different different account
Called for rebel pixels, which was the tablet review and technology and like art thing
Yeah
And I I don't know whether that was the same channel as the brony curious channel
I can't remember. It's been a while. I I I think brony curious got rebranded
Into one of the channels
Yeah, I don't I don't understand why you would take that down. It was
I I
Can't I can't I have no idea. I have no idea why
um
Next one is called Ben's ooo
3 2 1 go
Ben sains
You cannot
Only
I'm plus
I'm super
I'm plus I'm somewhere in the plus probably
You do not attract a demisexual person as your partner
You will
You will attract a feline
And I know you do not want a feline
This person needs a glass of water
They need to stay hydrated
um
They need to stay hydro-weighted
I drew hydro-woo-weighted
Is this my water
Oh
I have many I have man of many man of many oos
um
Next one is Ben's ooo part two three more like part two ooo
Yeah, three two one go
So that's correction
You cannot
But you can oh
There is a difference. Oh, it matters to people like me
Who's people like you? What do you mean people like you, huh racist?
I'm gonna keep I'm gonna keep ooo and I'm gonna keep
I'm gonna keep culturally appropriating. Oh, man. Oh, whoa. What's this sexual intercourse?
Notices bulge notices an entirely nude person. This reminds me of
There was a guy I looked at the the the the the Trixie thread on kiwi for speaking of kiwi farms
I looked at the thread like yesterday the day before and someone there's one guy on there who would make
He would occasionally post and his thing was that he was mad at her for rapping
while being white
And it was like really funny because his his stance was basically
So racist
That he basically circled around to being woke again
Like he he hates black culture so much
That he protects it that he wants to protect it from white people that want to like co-opt it because he doesn't want it to spread
Like that's his thing
And he even the even the other kiwi farmers like hate him and made fun of him for it
Is it even woke to like
to
Like gate keep culture
Yeah, it's it's I guess what you might
Call like a like a parody of being woke. It's like, oh, no no culturally appropriation
You can't do anything if you're you can't do these things if you're white
Or whatever
Oh, did you
Was it this week? Was it this week that uh fucking that fucking
Dumpling a noodle book
Thing happened on twitter. Did you see that? That was a little while ago
Was it um that was so
That was so annoying. I saw
If you don't know it was oh, yeah
I know I the there was the like the rebuttal that looked into the author
And it turns out the lady who was white who made the book about noodles
Grew up with asian people and culture
Yeah, she was like and so yeah, so it's like fine and not even I mean it I mean it would have been fine anyway
Yeah, it's like their argument
Yeah, it's just like completely destroyed in every way audience if you don't know the context is this this woman this this I think she was a
filipina
woman
Made a calm she made a tweet that was like
Why did a white woman write a book about noodles and dumplings and it was it showed like the book
Which is it's called like dumplings and noodles and it was the author and she's like white and she has like curly red hair
She looked like maybe
irish or something. I don't know
um, but uh
yeah, so like
I don't know this kind of shit like like
I saw I saw a a guy
I don't know his name, but I see him on my timeline. I don't think I follow him. He's like a he's like a male only fans
Model he's like a male like porn guy
But he's like this buff. I think he's middle eastern and he
Is like a handsome
fucking
Guy who gay does gay only fans porn, but he also like
Wait, wait, wait, wait
No, it's not gay chat
He's not middle eastern
Um, I don't think um, but this this he also just makes like good like socialist posts
He just like he just has good politics and posts about them sometimes and he posted and he was like
He said like it's only it's only deaspora kids meaning like
Kids that were born away from their home like like people that are actually from these places don't care
He was like it's only deaspora kids that like give a shit about this kind of
Cultural appropriation like he said my my parents find it funny. They find it amusing when like americans like make
Uh persian food. I think maybe he's persian or something
And I and I think that's true
Uh, it's it sounds true to me. I don't know this is a sentiment that I've seen echoed by other
Like people that are actually from like a foreign country when they see like a white person like
Doing a tea ceremony or making some food. They're like ha ha lol cute or whatever there. I don't know this this lady
I don't know she she she had this like stupid
She had this stupid take and then she complained about it for like she had like a huge meltdown on twitter about it for like
Days because people were calling it stupid. She you know said like oh, I've been spending my I've been all these days
I've been getting harassed by nazis which
Probably some yeah, probably some nazis were in there jumping on this to be racist
And then at the end of it all she's like boy. I've been through so much. Here's my cash app fucking
Tip me and like I'm sure she made like a ton of money
I don't because she was the main character of twitter for like two days there
Uh, so I had another whole thing's obnoxious the whole the whole story is annoying and I don't like it
Uh, and I don't like that kind of like why a white a white person making noodles like
Ah
Okay, I think I've made my point
um
Next voicemail is called one cool dud three two one go
Officially induct cyber shell already that bitch is fucking delightful
Cyber shell is delightful. Yes
Uh, but no ceremonies
Yeah, we ran out of confetti. We don't have anymore. We can't do it
Yeah, yeah, and and like the the dubbing the the the the new member dubbing sword is like it's rusty needs repairing
Yeah, it's um, it needs to be reforged in the fires of mount doom
And it's really far away. It's in like new zealand. It's like there's covids. It's kind of hard to get over to there right now. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, it's actually fro could just take a plane
Why didn't the ball rod just fly the ring to mortar with its wings?
Why didn't Frodo just fucking throw it? Do you know do you know about the ball do ball rocks have wings debate?
um, I
No, I have no idea about that. Well, the the ball rock is described in the book
I I knew about this already, but dan olson just put out a video that is about um
Like an an older adaptation of the lord of the rings not the peter jackson one and he he mentioned this so it's fresh in my mind, but there is a
um
The the ball rock is it's described first as having
Like darkness spreading out around it like wings
And then later on it says
That it's it says like it's wings spread
So it kind of like first implies that it doesn't have wings
But just has like shadows that cast a shadow that looks like wings
But then later on it does refer to the wings
and there's
a great debate
In scholarship and I've seen I've seen really compelling arguments on both sides
Of like why like the ball rock definitely does have wings or definitely doesn't have wings
The I watched a video where like a Tolkien expert some professor somewhere
Says that they they definitely don't have wings
Because they are creations of morgoth
And morgoth would not like he made he made the ball rocks to be
What they are like deliberately he crafted them
So why would he give them vestigial wings that don't work that would be like
A waste but then I saw and this was again. This was Sean my guy
He made it he tweeted but he says
That he thinks they do have wings
They can't he that they can't fly but that they do have wings
Because morgoth was he made
He made all kinds of creatures. He was he was doing all kinds of like experiments and making creatures
So it's it's totally it is reasonable to think that you know
Not every creature that he made came out exactly like on purpose
Maybe some of them came out a little weird and and that's like why not?
Um
So like or morgoth's not all powerful
So, I don't know. I think maybe he had a red bull. Haha
Although I do think
I do think that the image of a ball rock having not actual wings, but just like
Perpetually casting a wing like shadows around itself. I think that's cooler. Honestly
Um, it isn't the ball rock like in moria
Like trapped down there
Um, like it was released. I don't know
But like it's not supposed to be there normally
They the dwarves unearthed it by digging too deep. I think so. All right. Does he like being in the ground?
Because if why would why would he fly why would he fly and why that's what I want to know
Would he fly up to the surface and go see the birds?
You know, I I think I think that the ball rock was not
Oh god, I don't fucking know what I'm talking about. I could be wrong
But I don't I think he was originally trapped down in the earth
I don't think he was like meant to be down there
He was trapped down there and then the dwarves unearthed him by digging
I think
And then he got him
And then oh he oh he got
Oh, he got him real good and then unrelated a bunch of
goblins and orcs
took over
because of
Sauron or something
Yes, I think
So
Yeah
Anyway, uh cyber shell is cool. Cyber shell can be on
whenever
He doesn't he doesn't have to be we don't have to yeah
We don't have to throw a fucking party and do the whole thing we did with like Jeff and monkey about like, oh, you're an official member now
Yeah, there's no there's no need for such
There's no reason for that. They can just I mean like fit mc is on a bunch of episodes. Should we
induct him like I don't know
They can just come on the show. They just be on the show and they'll be it'll be cool
True
Next one is is son of meroac three two one go
At Otacon there is an art show that takes place in the artist alley where artists can submit unique pieces of art
and
People can sign up to bid for them on an online auction
So I will submit 20 to 40 pieces of unique
hentai
that people can sign up
And wait, this is the same voicemail as last week potentially if there are enough
Online bids it can actually go to a live auction also
So
That's I feel like son of meroac sent this exact same. I wasn't clear so there you go
No
but why
But why
It's it's an auction and like people buy it, but like
Do you son of meroac draw all the hentai or do you just what have it?
Like why who are you to profit off of hentai you collect? I don't get it
What is the what is the point? I don't you put artists put art into a
Thing and it gets auctioned and then I guess the artist gets paid. I don't know all all I'm all I'm getting is that there is an auction
I son of meroac am submitting pieces into it to be auction
What what am I supposed to latch on to here?
Uh, good luck. I guess you're supposed to park ben
Pog okay
Next one is called optimal homestuck three two one go
Optimal homestuck experience step one start homestuck step two get sidetracked by problem sleuth step three never look back
problem sleuth is
objectively a better story than homestuck
It's it's more nicely connected together. Yeah
Yeah, it
Yeah
Man, it gave me false hope. It gave me false hope problem sleuth's ending is so good and so robustly
Interconnected that it gave me false hope. I made me think like
Well, obviously hussy knows what he's doing
Just look at the ending of homestuck or the ending of problem sleuth like
Homestuck is just that it's just that but like bigger and more elaborate
So like just like in problem sleuth the ending of homestuck it will all come together and it will all tie together into a into a perfect
It's package and it was just false
It's the metaphor I would use is that the the the it's the same thing
But due to its size
It can't it can't like like hold its own weight under gravity
It's just too big and so it collapsed. I thought
I I just I thought like
Hussy knows what he's doing. He wouldn't he wouldn't have built the story like this if he couldn't make it all come work in the ends
Yeah, it's
I mean, I don't I don't want to get into a whole thing about like what was wrong with the ending of homestuck, but
Problem sleuth is but I mean I would still say finish it
At least at least finish act five
At least get to risk it and then understand who I am or
Yeah, true
Next one is called. Why is no one talking about this three two one go
What's up everybody? It's pretty cool. Today. We're going to be looking at one of the worst shit stands to ever grace the internet
His name has been saint. He's a comic artist podcaster and ran a tier fake professor
This man is single-handedly responsible for all the horrible news surrounding chris chain
You don't know chris chain was recently arrested for raping his elderly mother an action that was directly influenced by slime
In this in this tweet thread, I will one out of
It's it's it's cleverly disguised, but it's it doesn't sound like a human
It's this the robot
one of the
one of the many
arrangements that I observe in the like
In like the the the in the the kiwi farms freaks that are like
In my in my men. She's lately
Is is this idea that they they they on the one hand they must
They must persecute chris in any way possible whether that's misgendering her
You know calling calling her, you know a rapist, which you know fair enough
Calling her, you know retarded or whatever
Whatever they want to do they must persecute chris to the maximum extent in every possible way
But also
But also they must implicate me
In her crimes and like claim that I am they must guilt me by saying like ben
you're wrong
because
You did this like you
talked to chris
You what they say is you encouraged her delusions. You drove her further and further into her delusions by by acknowledging them
And and therefore the fact that this happened. This is partly your fault
It's like you could have stopped this ben if you had just said wait a minute chris
Actually, I don't think the cartoon world and the real world are going to merge in a big like roger rabbit fucking
Cosmic calamity actually
I don't think that would have if if you had just said that she would have snapped out of her thing
And she would have been like wow, I guess I should I should get a job or something
You could you you helped cause this ben because you didn't do it. I was there. I
Kiwi farms fucking self-hating troll whatever I was there in the menschies every time chris tweeted
I said chris you are you need a job. You are delusional
You are not a woman. You are a man and you're retarded
I was there every single time doing my duty
And if only you ben had joined me in that crusade that all it would have been enough
It would have tipped the scales and everything would have turned out differently, but no you wouldn't you said I want this mom reaped to occur
You premeditated it 10 years ago. You premeditated it all ben
um
Yeah, they they I mean, where's the lie?
Where is the lie? I don't
That's that's just
Yeah, it's it's pretty it's pretty fucked. It's pretty fucked up when when they when they pull that card like I
I just don't know where they get the fucking gall to say such a such a such a moronic thing. I really don't
um
next one is uh
The big chicken's egg of
Tim rogers is david foster wallace
Three two one go on my way to get my gynecologist mcdonald's but uh make gamers tavern and cybershell permanent members of pcp
I enjoyed last week's banter. It was fun
uh make every pcp episode four hours long
and uh
Well, we'll just pop
What it doesn't have to do anything with tim rogers
um, no like we have to
We have to introduce artificial scarcity artificial scarcity. We can't give you too many good episodes because then you get spoiled
We want it to only be as a treat
only as a treat
Uh, and then we'd get it would gape keep the rest along on pcb.com slash the patreon dot slash the
patreon.com
One of these days I am bonus episodes one of these days. I am gonna do what I need to do
It's it's it's not so today is one of these days one of these days could be today
One of these days someone will do the things we need to do to get those three new bonus episodes live
They will happen. It can't they it can't go on like this
um
Next one is called big chicken's egg of curl
three two one go
However, of course doing so will cause the finger of the monkey's paw to curl
Uh, monkey jones will also be returning as a permanent member and uh, man ethan raff's child
Uh, will be the cause of uh vents had been crushed
by a train
So so so so so so so
Man ethan raff's child is welcome on the pcb train conductor anytime
Disgusting um next voicemail is called please don't play the last voicemail
three two one go
Hey, I'm really sorry about that little voicemail. I said a lot of racial slurs
Like probably every single one made up a few new ones for eastern europeans. Really don't like those guys
um made fun of chinese people
Then I bent the knee to chinese people and said uh, hong kong and taiwan are countries
Um, I said ben's current address live on it and then I said the address he's going to be moving to next
Um, just so much bad shit. I'm really sorry. Please don't play that
And
If you if there was an email attached never play one from that email again, I'm very sorry
Hey, what voicemail am I right? Hmm. Don't know what voicemail you could possibly be referring to
Wink, what is this? Please don't play the last voicemail at cocksack.com
Well, I'll I'll be on the lookout for that one. We will be we will keep our eyes wide open
Next voicemail is called boy zerk
three two one go
I won't take this slander any longer the golden age arc of berserk is great
But it's the least good part of berserk the least everything after it is way better
The least people saying that only the golden age arc is worth reading or that you can just stop after that
Nah, it's all way better
Wow
Least good is quite a claim. I don't know if I would say
I think it's really good
that in in that it's
Like a contained story that could be stopped
Um, but I definitely think there's so much more good stuff later
Hey
The kushan the kushan empire arc with the the big crazy guy that turns into a thing
I feel like that's like the highest point of of the the manga
And even even just even just like
Griffith
In the hand and the the tower of I don't know religious guys
There's so many good parts. There's no bad part of berserk
But I can I can see the argument for that being like the least good because it's the most
I don't know
It's it's like a setup to something
That can be enjoyed by itself
Hmm
Um, I mean I never I read the I read golden age and then I read like a little bit afterwards
I read a bunch. There was like some fairies. I read like some stuff about fairies, uh, and that
That's why I didn't get much girl
Probably it was a long time ago
Uh, yeah, it was a girl with like really got to read at least at least up to the point where like the party forms
Yeah
You got to learn you got to know the characters before you can say
Yeah, you're right. I don't I don't know if I've if I've ever said like
I
I recommend okay, I recommended
People just read the golden age arc and then decide if you want to keep reading
I didn't say you don't have to keep reading. I said
Because that's the part I've read and I said people should read that
And then if they like it they can continue. I did like it, but for some reason I bounced off it
And then I never got much further past it
Uh, I yeah, I can't
I never I never got kept going so I can't have any uh
Real opinion about whether it gets better or worse or or what?
um
Next one is called peri aka at lex paradox
Okay, three two one go
So I just got done arguing with stupid transfers about christian's gender on twitter on behalf of one benjamin saint
And I just wanted to get about how fucking awful they are
Like the entire crux of their argument rolls around christian saying one time that she wanted to be trans to fuck girls or something
10 years ago respond that the reason for someone changing their identity doesn't fucking matter
All that matters is that they identify as that gender
Then they abandon that first argument and pivot to essentially the argument that christ is too crazy to be trans which is
Concerning in and of itself and then you say well people believe in a lot of crazy shit
Does that discredit everything else that they believe about their identity and everything they think?
Then they know that they've lost and they just call you a bigot and act like they have the high ground or something
And they just run away and it's fucking stupid and it makes me happy dunking on these fucking idiots
Anyway, uh, then I just wanted to thank you for standing up for trans people. I really appreciate it
I've been listening to the podcast since I was since I was the since I was a freshman in high school
And i'm a junior in college now
U3 assuming tom is on today
I've always been my favorite members of the podcast and it's almost exclusively gotten better since everyone has gone
Even though everyone seems to think otherwise
Uh, not everyone and have good wonderful days. I love all of you also follow me on twitter
Sometimes I make art when i'm not dunking on idiots. Goodbye at
at lex lexis lex s p e r i d o t i assume that's twitter handle
Well, i'm glad you appreciate me or me getting in fights on twitter. Uh, I I remember
Yeah, they the what you said is exactly right
They they will they will yeah, they will they will make a claim
They will make a claim
like, um
Chris said she's Chris said she's faking
And then when you go that was 10 years ago and also and also it's irrelevant that she said that one time
Then they will pivot to Chris is too crazy and doesn't get to decide her own gender. She can't make that claim
She she says other crazy things. We shouldn't believe her and then you go
That doesn't make any sense because that's what being trans is she identifies as trans
That's the end and then they and then they will they will just they will just pivot to a new
They'll just keep pivoting to a new argument every single time
And then they will just circle back around to the beginning
And just make the first argument again and just say that like you didn't and you know that you didn't you didn't respond to it
even when you did
And the the most annoying part of all that is that if you do like hound them to make them
Acknowledge that they have no argument to this, you know the the main point or something
They'll start saying why do you care so much? Why are you going on about this? You know, you kind of fucked up
They'll that's why that you having the argument is you being insane
Yeah, oh and that somehow that like discredits you it's like
That that one that one that one particularly angry one yesterday was like
convinced that like
me that like
That she said that true scum is a slur and that like by calling her a true scum. I am like
outing myself as a bigot because like true scum are the real
True scum aren't the bigots
The real bigots are the people that
hate true scum that don't agree with them and like
What do you even what do you even say to a person like that?
What do you even say?
I don't know. Yeah, the the the pivoting you say the pivoting fucked
The pivoting this is a thing. I've been complaining about this in my discord lot the the motton bailey argument where you
Make you advance two arguments simultaneously
one of which is
One of which is uh is controversial or hard to defend
And the other of which is basic and easy to defend you advance them together
Or as one argument or you advance an argument that could be read as one or the other
And then if someone argues against
the more difficult to defend argument that you made the more um
Yeah, the the more uh
Controversial argument you pretend you retreat from the bailey to the mott or is it from the mott to the bailey?
Whatever and you you retreat and you pretend that you were only advancing the the the basic uncontroversial one
Um, this is a I hate I hate this shit
It's so fuck I see it all the time and it's really transparent. It's just really it's really dishonest
It's it's you know
It's really the mark of a person who has a lot of faith that what they're saying is right and that like their ideology makes sense
Where in like they argue it in a way where like they have to pretend they're not arguing what they actually are trying to argue
It really speaks volumes to their character
um
Next voicemail is oh, it's another one from 4 20 69. Oh my god his mission
His mission updates, uh three two one from cabal from cabal cabal masi cabal
This is snake the natefuckers have captured me
I need help president biden isn't going to rescue me
I've tread calling sarah from kingdom arts by the phone ran out of battery in the desert
Don't let it end like this nate heads. I need your help
Press X on your controller to send me an airstrike
Press X for freedom press X for victory press X for sex
What's the mission again wait the fuck the fuck nate
The well the natefuckers captured him so I guess he's against the natefuckers. Oh, oh, he's it. Oh the nate heads
The ongoing war between the nate heads and the natefuckers
They're more like they're more alike than they know for no admit
yeah
they
Well, uh, I'm trying to think of a way to say the joke that I have
because like tally band
natefuckers nate heads
nate 11
Uh, it doesn't don't really work. That was al-qaeda that did the 9 11 not the tally band
No, no, I mean like like like tally band like uh had al-qaeda like tucked inside like sneakily
Like that was the whole reason
tally band like looked the other way
Didn't they? Oh, is that right?
And then they allowed al-qaeda to plan the 9 11 they did the 9 11
that
I and that's why they tell you that makes sense
That's why tally bad
Um, okay, I I'll I believe you that sounds plausible
um
Semper fidelis to all are some semper fidelis to the natefuckers. I'm
honestly
I love you for 2069, but I hope you fucking get
air-striked by your own air-striked. I'm I'm I'm a I'm a nate I'm a natefucker through and through
I'm on board. I'm in I'm I'm down with the struggle
um
I'm nate gnostic
nate gnostic cringe cringe
Uh, take it take a stance. You know, do you want nate?
Do you want nate to be virgin or laid you you can't you can't uh, you can't middle ground this one
Uh, what if you go to go huff in
If you if you do not explicitly
What about just the tip natefuckers if you do not explicitly support the natefuckers you are
Taking a stance that you want nate to stay unfucked
and that is
Fucking disgusting
Nothing can be more I par
Nate Nate
Nate you could you could say that Nate you're a boars a vacuum
In his anus. I don't know. I don't know what's going with that
um
He wants something to be in there
Uh nature get it nature a boars a vacuum. I I I yeah sure whatever. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah a little silly now
No, it's no it's not. No, it's not
Um, don't be ridiculous
There's nothing silly about the natefuckers quest
Next voicemail is called road to radcon four before I play this one
I just want to mention again that whole thing about the credit card is because
The proof of printing of road to radcon is made. I was waiting for the credit card so I can pay for it
Tomorrow monday. I'm going to the printer and I'm going to hopefully approve the proof and be like yep print it
And then they will be printing 150 copies
God right in time for me to move. I guess I won't be shipping them until next month. I guess but um
They'll be printing me 150 copies and then I will be shipping them out to kickstarter backers. So
Looking forward to it. I guess
three two one go
Hey, feel free to skip this if you've already talked about it
But then you apparently finished writing road to radcon four chapter five
Yep, so when will it be released? There it is. I just told you for the $100 backers
Are you it was a stretch goal of the kickstarter that you release it and the previous chapters were released as youtube videos
I understand if you don't want to make an audiobook of it, but maybe you could just release it in text form somewhere
Yeah, yeah, I will I will definitely publish maybe on the maybe on the website and the pcp website or something
Yeah, I'll definitely post the text version online somewhere the the hundred dollar back the hundred dollar backers will get
I think I think on a previous episode around a stream or something. I talked about maybe
I should redo like an audiobook version of the full
Book as a video or something. Yeah, it's probably on the last the one before last heckles or shackles stream
We talked about that. Yeah
But uh, yeah the the hundred dollar plus backers will get the we'll get the printed like book version. Uh, and then um
Yeah, but it'll the the
I mean like the cover art and the text will be
Yeah, probably available as like a download on the website or something in pdf form
um
Okay, uh, yeah next one. I think this is the last voicemail. It's called new theme song submission
3 2 1 go
1 2 3 4
Tommy no
There there you have it folks, um
The that's a bit uh
Okay, I guess we're done. What a bit it is
What a what a what a way to go out what an end of the voicemails. Um, I don't know
I'm just gonna refresh. No nothing new. No, I I did. Yeah, I refresh. There's no no new voicemails. Uh, thank god
That one was posted
Only three hours ago. That was posted right when we started recording. So
When I don't know I
I guess that doesn't mean anything or
matter in in any way
Okay, I guess uh fucking it'll become a patron
patron.com for stuff procrastinators
For when I eventually get those fucking bonus episodes up and also for all the old bonus episodes and also for access for the pcp minecraft server
um
Fucking if you didn't catch the last shekels for heckles
I went on a tour and I didn't complete the quest but I did a lot of the
Exploring the rowdy rough house in the scale model of rfck endless war luis angeles city
Currently still in production by marin pan, but there's the construction there is going
It's massive. It's massive in scale
Uh, it's highly impressive and um, yeah, and you should also check out the big booby bodega and the mummy milka market
Absolutely
Absolutely. Yes, uh
Yeah, I missed I missed doing the minecraft uh
Shekels for heckles streams the minecraft server is is a really good time
And that's uh that priory is getting it's getting uh
It's getting built
What what was the thing you said you were you wanted to maybe start working on after the priory was done?
Oh, I was thinking like, um
The the bail jpef ostrich cathedral
I love that idea so much. That's so cool
That's good
It would take a lot of planning to like figure out because it doesn't it it actually has no
Sense no like floor there's no like floor plan that you like came up with
It's just like like hodgepodge. Um, I mean, I have that map that I made to like
To make sense of where everybody was during the yeah the events were like, yeah
The canon was falling down. There's like there's locations to build like how they connect. I have no idea
Um
That's
That's very funny. I would like to see that. Um
Okay, and and yeah be patron and uh
Speakpipe.com slash pcb voicemail if you want to leave a voicemail. Don't make it suck. Please. Um
Anything else?
Uh, nope
Nothing, okay, okay
Okay, have a great week everyone. Thank you for listening to another episode of the pro
Fascinator's podcast. We will see you next time
Uh, bye
Goodbye