Take the universe and grind it down to the finest powder and sieve it through the finest sieve and then show me one atom of justice, one molecule of mercy. And yet, you try to act as if there is some ideal order in the world, as if there is some, some rightness in the universe by which it may be judged.
But people have got to believe that. What's the point?
You need to believe in things that aren't true. How else can they become?
Hello, welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm your host, Ben Saint, because best guy ever is-
Quit the show!
Fucked off to hell.
We got an email. He said, guys, I have appreciated doing this podcast with you, but I've got to move on to bigger and better things. I'm doing me a math of a two. I don't have time for the PCPs, so I'm going to drop out and quit.
How dare he plagiarize my litter of resignation that I was just about to turn in.
You were going to do me a math of a two?
Yeah, it's been my plan all along.
I don't know.
As the new inheritor of the title of PCP Dictator, I'd just like to say, best guy, we wish you well in your future endeavors, and our attorneys will be contacting you soon, and we'll see you in court, you motherfucker.
Ben, do you have any experience with being a dictator? I don't know if you're qualified for the role.
Well, you know, I do. My track record is spotty. My track record is spotty, but I think let the record show that I always tried my best. I always tried my level best.
I was really hoping that since Nate isn't here, none of us would know how to open the show, and it would just be infinite silence forever. Just like a 24-7 livestream of nothing for all time.
That would pretty well suit our topic for today, which, by the way, is death. Pretty much the ultimate topic.
Now, I know what you're thinking, people at home. Didn't you already do this? Didn't you do times we almost died and suicide? Yes, but this is a grander scale. We're talking about death in general, the cheeriest, funnest topic for your three amigos, Ben, Jess, and Monkey.
That's what they call us. It's a grander topic. A grander topic that demands a more intimate touch. So it's just us three. Just us three, just sitting around, just having a couple of boys, having a couple of cold ones, and talking about the icy nothingness that awaits beyond the grave.
Now, for the next hour, we should pretend to be dead, just to know what it's like.
To give the viewer a little taste. Give the viewer a little taste of what's coming.
What's coming in about 50 years.
Fucking, fucking, fucking, god damn it.
Did you bring up an urban dictionary definition?
Oh, yeah, we usually do that.
We don't even know how to do this. Here we go.
Where's the urban dictionary?
Go to the master library and take the urban dictionary off the shelf, as Nate does.
Every time.
Alright, yeah, blows off the dust and like...
The dust from last week?
Yeah, yeah, tons of accumulated dust.
That's a real problem inside.
And then takes some tongs and like, gingerly turns the...
Gingerly, gingerly turns the...
I combined gingerly and tenderly into genderly.
Okay, according to the urban dictionary, death is a...
Wait, death is... oh, the cure for life.
That's a...
That's the first one that's made me laugh so far.
That's the top definition.
Second definition is, a spiritual stopover on your journey to the other side of eternity
to determine whether you are eligible to join the Abraham's, Joseph and Paul's,
or be with the Hitler's, Moa's and Osama's.
Great.
I think Osama's grouped in with the wrong people. He's clearly more of a Joe and Paul.
I see... alright, two definitions in and we've already fallen.
Reach the point of contention.
This third definition just says, what happens when you eat McDonald's too often?
And also guy in a big black cloak wearing a big scythe, sea grim reaper.
We should mention this episode is sponsored by McDonald's. The McRib is back, everybody.
If you want to get closer to death, go get that two-for-one special.
We should all be eating fast food and smoking for the duration of this particular episode.
Oh, I would enjoy that.
We could even call it a slow motion suicide, but I wouldn't call it that.
Suicide is painless. It brings on many changes.
You already did that episode.
Oh, never mind. No, got it, got it, got it. Alright, moving on.
Okay, the first big question we have to tackle, boys. We're going to answer this once and for all.
What happens after you die?
What is consciousness, guys?
What is the self? What is a being? What is being?
Ben, you majored in philosophy. You should know. Don't they teach you this in philosophy 300?
They just tell you what the meaning of life is and what consciousness is.
Yeah, you got to show up for four years, but at the end, the day before you graduate,
fucking Neil deGrasse Tyson comes and visits you in your sleep and whispers the meaning of life into your ear.
Oh, shut up, phone.
And that's the jingle you hear when you approach the gate.
I think what happens is you turn into a dinosaur because the dinosaur is invented death.
They were the first ones to do it in all of recorded history, so it must be their wheelhouse that you're going into.
Oh, so when we all die, it's like cultural appropriation because we're ripping off what the dinosaurs invented.
Yes. You got to get rid of it.
It's like you get to hell and there's lots of other things, but the dinosaurs were there first, so they took charge.
There's mostly dinosaurs. They roll down.
Yeah, they were there first, so they took charge and everyone else just followed their lead.
It didn't have to be shitty. Hell didn't have to be shitty, but they decided it should be and everyone else has just gone with it ever since then.
It's good. It's good for you.
Well, I'm glad we solved that philosophical conundrum.
Yeah, it only took 90 seconds.
Yeah, I mean, what's the big deal?
What are all these Play-Doh faggots doing debating all day? They should just listen to this podcast.
Sitting around getting stuck in the carpet.
I like to think.
Ben, I have a question for you.
Yeah, sure.
When you were taking your senior final thesis for a philosophy major, was the final test just like the word why and then that's it?
Was that what it was?
I just said why and you have to answer it in like 30 pages?
No, I would have enjoyed that. I would have enjoyed that a lot.
What would you have put?
I would have put, I probably would have put, I probably would have, if they had just asked me why and just said talk about why for 30 pages,
I probably would have said something about like, because somethingness is a more stable state of being than nothingness or something about that.
Probably would have been like a vacuum of nothingness will naturally incline towards a, you know, disturbances and fucking create somethingness or some shit.
I don't know, and I probably would have fucking pulled on my fucking like physics shit and gone into a weird sort of cosmological explanation of why existence would have occurred in the first place.
Oh, oh, and probably some shit about, some shit about how like, well, if we weren't, if existence were not a thing, if there were no existence, then we wouldn't be here to ask the question about why it exists.
So, so therefore it's kind of a self-defeating quandary.
Yeah, see, let's watch you, you do that and there's like 30 pages along at your masterpiece, you worked on it for like a month.
And then the fact it next to you just writes down why not and it gets an A.
Yeah, becomes president of the United States.
The president of Philosophy Club.
Yeah, and they're like, ooh, so clever and I'm like, but, but, but my, which is really much more of a distinguished position is being president of the Philosophy Club.
That's way better than being president of America.
Yeah, of course.
Um, so death.
Yeah.
Do we know anybody who died and impacted us in a positive or negative way?
I mean, actually my, actually my friend of mine just died like last week.
Oh, shit.
That's right.
Yeah, it was, oh, it was, I didn't put, I didn't connect the fact that I was going to be on the death podcast with this fact until just now.
But yeah, my friend from college was on vacation in Costa Rica and he drowned.
Costa Rica?
It was really sad and terrible.
Oh, are you guys close?
Because when, when you tweeted about this story, some small part of me thought to reply saying he was one of the lucky ones, but I didn't know how sensitive you would be.
I didn't know if you guys were good friends, so I refrained and now I'm doing it here on this podcast.
Well, I was, I was pretty, I was pretty bummed about it, although we weren't, we hadn't talked in a while, but, you know, just guy was like, I was like my age.
I was like a year younger than me.
You know, I don't know.
He wasn't like a, he wasn't like a close friend exactly, but I was still, I was still pretty bummed about it.
And yeah, so that's death.
It sucks.
Death is the worst thing in the world.
Death's my least favorite thing.
It's the scariest thing.
It's the most sad thing and I would murder it if I could.
Yeah.
It's, it's, you know, whenever people have discussions about death, it's always like they're trying just not to point out that it's the worst thing in the world.
Like people would rather do anything than admit that just we know what the worst thing is.
It's like when in fiction, when people get the choice to become immortal.
Oh, that pisses me off so much.
I think, I think I've heard you talk about this before.
It's like when people are like, oh, I wouldn't want to be immortal because then I'd see all my family and friends die.
And it's like, bitch, you, they're going to die anyway.
Like choosing to die yourself just means that, oh, in addition to all that other bad things happening, you also die, which is the worst thing that can happen.
If you really loved your friends, then you would owe it to them to take that offer up and become immortal so that you could keep their memory alive for all time for the people of the future, future generations.
It is, it is, like the, I've thought about this and I think you're right that like the reason why this always happens is because like media is, like these, like these stories are designed to convince people that dying isn't so bad and that we shouldn't be sad about it.
But fuck it.
Yeah, we should.
It's all marketing, isn't it?
It always comes down to marketing, trying to convince us that death isn't the worst so they can keep killing us with their Monsanto.
Makes, makes, makes people feel, makes people feel better, makes people feel better and that's what people want to hear.
There was a study I read one time where they asked everybody, what is your biggest fear?
And the number two biggest fear was death.
Number one was public speaking.
So these people were more afraid of speaking in public than of dying.
That's retarded.
Here you guys talk.
It sounds like you would both agree that death is the worst thing possible.
Like is that something you guys agree with?
Because I certainly don't.
I definitely agree with that.
I mean, the only thing worse than death would be like being tortured and then dying.
Yeah, would you rather be dead or tortured?
Well, I would rather be tortured if it meant I could live afterwards.
What if it's just like eternal torture? I'd rather be fucking dead.
Yeah, I guess I'd rather be dead if there was gonna be nothing else after it.
I mean, I don't know.
Even if I was like burned all over and I couldn't move at all and my life was just constant shit forever.
If I lived forever, I could hold out hope that like someday technology could take my brain out and put it in a nice little jar somewhere.
Yeah.
Maybe that'd be worth living forever for as opposed to just throwing in the towel and saying I don't want to be immortal.
Yeah, I agree with that.
I could hold out hope.
I could board enough being alive for 21 years.
I don't know what I would do with eternity.
I don't know.
I'm thinking something.
I've managed so far.
I've managed to e-cow.
I've managed to entertain myself this long.
Okay, Ben, think about it this way.
If you live forever, your fans are going to expect you to nuzloc every Pokemon game.
Now do you want to die?
You know what?
If I was going to live forever, I wouldn't nuzloc every Pokemon game because why not?
I wouldn't stress about it.
You wouldn't feel like you wasted half a year of your life on some stupid project?
Yeah, that's exactly what I wouldn't feel like anymore.
I'd have the time to do all that and B, I wouldn't worry about not doing other things
because I'd have the time to do those things too.
Death is the ultimate problem.
People say that death is like a motivator and death is why people...
Yeah, it motivates you to do things because I'm wasting my life and that's true, I guess.
You know that that is definitely true, that the only reason I do anything is because I'm scared.
It's because I'm scared that I'm going to die and I'm going to waste my life.
I see what you're laying down and I feel it, brother.
I'm with you.
I think that death, I think that every problem ever could probably be traced back to people
knowing that they're going to die someday.
Yeah, and the only reason that I'm sad about anything is because those things that make me sad
are things that are like harming me in the here and now and damaging the limited time that I have.
If I was going to live forever, everything would roll off my back and nothing would make me sad at all.
It would liberate you from all stress and insecurity.
It's the ultimate power, it's the ultimate comfort knowing, hey, even if everything is bad for a million years
I'll be here for a million plus infinity years, so fuck it.
But do you know what else gives you eternal...
No more stress, you get plenty of comfort.
Death.
All these things that you're talking about being a problem are also a solution with death.
I don't know, man, but then you're not around to experience it.
If I'm not conscious to feel my wiener getting sucked, then that's a bad deal.
End of story.
A hundred people could suck my corpse wiener and I'd never feel it because I'd have no brain left
and that would just... I don't want to live that un-life, man.
I don't want to live that way either.
I don't want to live my life dead.
Imagine looking into a graveyard, monkey-like, wistfully looking into a graveyard and being like,
ah, now that's the life, right there.
Instead of putting...
It's a secret that I've spent the last five years of my life daydreaming of death.
I'm very open about it.
It kind of does blow my mind that you guys are talking about it as if it is like the ultimate terrible thing,
which I can't get into that mindset at all.
I don't know, that's always been my stance on it.
There's definitely pros and cons to it.
I mean, the con is that I have to die and I'm the best person,
so that would be the worst thing that could possibly happen to all fucking life would be without me.
But also, it's like every good person is going to die. That sucks.
But I mean, the pro of it is that all the really terrible people are going to die too.
So I mean, if you think of like the worst person you've ever met in your entire life,
for me it's not very hard because they're both right here.
Yeah, you would, you know, that person, he'll die. Fuck him. He'll be dead.
That does comfort. That is a comfort, Jesse.
Alright guys, think about it this way.
Great philosopher named Harvey Dent once said,
either die a hero or you live long enough to become the villain.
So maybe death is the answer.
Well, I would retort to that.
You either die a hero or you live long enough to become the villain,
or you live even longer than that and everyone who thought you were a villain dies,
and so then you're a hero again.
Yeah, I'm going to go, I like that. I like that much better.
The only way we can talk about death is the alternative being you also can live forever.
Is there a way we can talk about death in the realm of we're all going to die at age 80, like reality?
Okay, okay, we can bring it back. We can bring this back to Earth for a second.
I do have a story of, much like you, Ben, of a classmate of mine dying,
but mine happened in fucking fourth grade.
Shit.
And it's, here's a story you can put up on the PCP Wiki under my Mumkey page of
Mumkeys emerging sociopathic traits, age nine.
It all started in fourth grade.
And there was a girl in that class whose name I will refrain from saying,
so I guess we'll just call her Eve, who gives a shit.
And Eve, I didn't know, guys, I didn't know what cancer was at the time.
I don't fucking know what's going on.
All I knew was that this little bitch, Eve, was allowed to wear survivor headbands to school
and nobody else could wear hats or anything and I was jealous as fuck.
Because I love survivor and this bitch gets to wear survivor headband to class.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Wait, just like a headband, like a bandana?
Yeah, it's a bandana.
Wait, are you talking about a piece of merchandise from the reality game show Survivor?
Yeah, yeah, they have really cool bandanas that you get to wear.
Huh, I guess that's one reason to get cancer.
Yeah, I didn't realize that she was bald underneath it.
I thought she was just like a special girl who got to wear it.
But that's not the only reason why I didn't like her.
Because one day at recess, I recall she said something a little snarky to me and I was like,
oh, this fucking survivor bitch, man, she's really getting on my nerves.
And then we find out that Eve is in the hospital, but she's probably going to make a recovery.
So the teacher says, OK, class, to help out our good friend Eve,
we're going to make a special, I don't know if it was probably on DVD,
they probably had DVDs at that time, I don't remember, it was like 2004.
We're going to make a video for Eve so that she can watch it
and know all of her friends are supporting her back at school while she's in the hospital.
So we spend like a full month making this project.
You spend a month making a video?
No, it's like a big DVD full of videos.
There were multiple skits, lots of, a lot of shit went into this.
We were like, we sang a song, just a ton of work.
And then, you know, wouldn't you know it?
Right when we finished this big grand video to support her friend, she fucking died.
No.
Tragic, tragedy.
You know, I think, I think that makes me mad, that makes me mad at the teachers,
that makes me mad at the teachers for their shortsightedness and for them just like,
for them fucking putting, they just fucked it up, they just fucked it up,
they tried to do some big grand gesture and guess what, it was retarded.
The teacher told us that they ended up giving the DVD to her family,
but I don't think they really did, I think they probably just threw that shit away.
Well, they did.
But here's where Mumkey, the emerging sociopath comes in,
because of course everybody, every single person in the classroom is crying when we hear this news,
except for me, because I'm just thinking, well, I mean, like she wasn't my friend,
she was mean to me, what do I care?
And I think back and I think, hmm, was I really that jaded and evil at the age of nine
that I wasn't crying, that my classmate died of cancer?
Maybe, maybe there's something bad under the surface here that we need to evaluate.
Well, how mean are you talking about?
There has to be a threshold.
She got a survivor bandana and I did it.
Okay, I don't think that's quite mean enough to worry about.
I'm not caring that she's dead.
Covered it, covered it, those survivor bandanas.
And she said one mean thing to me at recess one time,
but I was probably like being mean in the first place, because I was so jealous of her.
I was jealous of the little girl with cancer.
Who wouldn't be?
What's she hiding under that bandana?
Probably a cool Yondu Mohawk that she's not sharing with anyone.
She can control arrows.
Yeah.
She doesn't even have cancer.
She's just Yondu.
She's hiding her fucking head, Finn.
What about you, Jess, that any of your classmates die in a tragic cancer related accident in Costa Rica?
I also have a story about a classmate of mine dying tragically and me thinking it was quite humorous.
At least I didn't laugh when it happened.
Yeah, I'll say it out the bat.
Putting it like that makes me sound like a pretty bad guy,
but we just wait to hear my side of the story, okay?
So this was a really rich, privileged shit lord in my grade.
I'm already on your side.
Yeah, he was called Gasper, so of course when we died, we all called him Gasper, the friendly ghost.
So the way he was in a car wreck and his whole body went up in flames,
I guess he burned alive.
It was probably really painful and really horrible.
And really awesome.
Yeah, so so far I'm still sounding like a bad guy, but just wait.
How old was the kid when he died?
He must have been, because I think it was in high school, so he was probably 15 or 16.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, fuck him.
Yeah, but the reason that I hated him and the reason that I not only didn't care that he died
but was kind of like, yeah, was because he came over to my house once on a bicycle
and I had kittens and he picked up my kittens and he threw them off while riding around on his bicycle.
He would throw my kittens.
Who throws kittens?
The kid was a sociopath.
He was a monster.
He just picked up a handful of kittens, got on his bike and then rode and chucked them to the side.
He tossed my baby cats.
Are you confessing that you cut his brakes?
I'm not confessing that.
You said that and not me.
Okay.
Well, fuck.
Sounds like a real asshole.
Yeah, you know, it's probably sad for his parents or friends or whatever, but probably.
That's a kid who threw cats.
Yeah, if you throw kittens, like, fuck your whole family.
Fucking go up in flames, dude.
Yeah.
They were endless justice kittens, dude.
Nobody, nobody fucks with my kittens.
No.
Did you go to the funeral?
Oh no, god no.
I don't think I...
I will admit, so...
Did you throw a kitten into the grave?
I should have buried him with my cats.
That would teach him.
I didn't cry when I found out that the student had died, but we went to the open casket service and when I saw the dead body, I did tear up a bit.
So if that gives me any credit towards not being a monster of a human being then...
You know what?
It would have been poetic justice if they had buried him in kitty litter.
And if they had, you know, he would have looked just like a burnt little cat turd because of the way he died.
Yeah.
Was he driving?
Was it his fault?
I have no idea.
I actually kind of feel bad joking about this in hindsight.
Nah, whatever.
Because he did die.
That does suck.
Dying definitely sucks.
I mean, he covered that.
Maybe he didn't deserve to die.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe he just deserved to be thrown off of a bike himself a few hundred times.
Yeah, I would have got...
I would have pulled my push head.
By me in a cat suit.
In my Michelle Pfeiffer Tim Burton catwoman cosplay.
I have never been to an open casket funeral.
I've been to two funerals and they were both closed casket.
So, I've actually never seen...
I don't think I've ever seen a dead human body.
Oh, wow.
Other than like, yeah, a skeleton like in a science place.
So that's interesting.
That's a fact about me.
I actually...
So if I was in Harry Potter, I couldn't see Festerls.
Couldn't see Festerls.
What the hell does that mean?
They're these demon horses that you can only see if you've witnessed death.
Whoa, cool.
Yeah, they're awesome.
What book is that in?
Well, they're technically always there, but they only become visible to Harry in book 6.
I think it's after he sees Sirius die.
He didn't see his mom die when he was a baby?
JK Rowling needs to fucking fix this.
Maybe he was a...
Turn the other way or some shit.
No, I saw the movie.
Do you have to see someone dying or just seeing a body with just seeing a body work?
Oh, no, maybe you have to actually see someone die.
Because I remember that these Festerls come in and I remember thinking it was really obvious that
Rowling had just wanted these Festerls to be a thing and had tried to come up with an excuse
for why they were suddenly there but had been there all along and I remember not buying it.
Like Harry should definitely have...
Like if anyone's seen death, it's Harry Potter, the boy who lived.
You know what I'm saying?
No.
Harry Potter is so stupid.
The whole series is so stupid.
Just the idea that muggles kind of know about wizards but they also kind of don't
but she can't really commit to either or for the entire series.
Sometimes they're shrouded in secrecy.
Sometimes they're not.
It's only the Prime Minister that knows about magic.
No, no.
Harry's whole family, the Dursleys, they know specifically.
Only the Prime Minister and families of wizards.
Yeah, they present it as though the wizarding world is a secret.
Like Hogwarts somehow is off everyone's radar.
No one knows about the giant castle in Scotland or whatever.
Somehow nobody knows about all this magical stuff going on and yet a great many wizards
and witches are muggle-born.
Hermione's parents know all about wizards and witches.
Aunt Petunia, her sister was a witch.
Lots of people just have magic folk in their family.
The whole series makes no sense.
J.K. Rowling is a fucking back.
The muggles not see them at platform nine and three-quarters just running into a wall.
Yeah, that's...
I think there's some shit about like, oh, because it's all weird and quirky,
like regular people just can't see it, like their brain just ignores the exceptional.
But when Ron and Harry in the second book, they run into the wall because Dobby closed it
and some fucking guy sees them immediately after they crash into the wall.
What a crock of shit.
I agree.
You know what J.K. stands for?
It stands for just kidding when I said I was a good author.
That's what it stands for.
I thought J.K. stood for a giant cunt.
Yeah, I like it.
I dig it.
Should we talk about some people who were going to be very sad when they do die?
Okay.
I know you wanted to talk about Christian.
Oh, yeah, Christian.
Well, I mean, I didn't bring this up. You said it.
But yeah, I will be super...
The new Sonichu came out recently, and I'm going to go read that soon.
And fucking, yeah, when Christian...
People have been saying, people have been saying for years,
like people, all Chris's trolls have been saying like,
oh, with his lifestyle, he's going to die, he's going to die before 40.
And like, I think, I don't believe that because, yeah, he's unhealthy and he's sedentary
and he's fat and he's weak and he's pitiful.
But like, so is like...
Hold on.
Oh no, what have I done?
What have I done?
I misgendered Jim.
But like, yeah, he, she is all those things, but so is like...
Just say she.
So is like everyone else.
Man, I always, I haven't thought about it.
Like, I haven't thought about it the same way since she transitioned.
Like, to me, real Chris is old boy Chris.
Like, that's what I think of when I think of Christian West and Chandler.
Anyway, the point is...
I don't actually care.
I just think it's funny to like, harass somebody over it because it's so stupid.
Good, because I'm easily triggered.
I'm easily triggered by this, by the thought of misgendering Christian.
Anyway, I don't think he's actually going to die that early.
I think he's just going to be a fat old person like everyone else.
And hopefully he'll keep making son of two until Kingdom come, baby.
Uh, 50, 50, 50 issues.
50 issues in a movie.
I'm trying to think of a celebrity.
I have nothing to say about it.
Because, because as we all know, Momki doesn't care about anybody he knows in person.
It's like friends and family, whatever.
I'm trying to think of a celebrity that would really impact me.
I know, like, people were upset about, like, Prince and all this shit.
But I think, like, upon the death of Leo DiCaprio,
after seeing him die so many times in film,
it won't, it won't seem real to have a news story pop up saying Leo died.
I think it was just another one of the movies.
So I think coming to terms with the actual death of my, my childhood and adult hero
is going to be too much for me to cope with.
I might have to take my own life in retaliation against death.
There's a lot of actors.
That's, that's doing what death wants.
No!
That's playing right into the trap.
He's playing right into his hands.
Damn it.
You gotta beat him.
What were you saying, Jess?
You gotta beat him at, like, at video games, like in Bill and Ted.
It's the only way to not give death what he wants.
Um, yeah.
There's definitely a lot of actors who, like, I really love, but who are also really old.
And that's gonna be sad.
Like, like, Clint Eastwood or Bill Shatner or Stallone even is, like, in his 70s now.
I'm definitely gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna shit a few tears when Stallone dies.
Um, you know, I'm a big wrestling fan.
A lot of my, uh, heroes, people that I've always admired are wrestlers.
And, uh, wrestlers are notorious for dropping, like, fucking flies.
Uh, nobody dies more than wrestlers.
Randy Savage.
Yeah.
In, in the last eight years, there's probably been, like, three dozen really famous wrestlers who've, who've died.
And it's, it's very sad.
And they just keep, because it's, you know, it's a hard grind, a hard life.
Most of them spend their whole, you know, they get addicted to the drugs.
To the, to the, to all the bad stuff.
And most of them fucking die before they're 60.
Hmm.
Should we move on to a more cheery topic?
I think I'm going to a more cheery episode of this podcast.
No way. No, we can, we can have a cheery fun discussion to death.
Like, for example, what do you want to happen after you die?
I have a great, I was actually just going to bring this up again.
Um, I have, I have my, I have my ideal scenario.
And, uh, I think the best part about this is that it's not completely implausible, right?
This is not completely, this is not completely outside the realm of physical possibility.
I think it might be.
And I don't even know what it is.
All right. All right.
No, listen to this. Listen to this.
All right.
So there's like, oh God, oh no, I'm going to forget all the big words that would make me sound smart when I explain this.
I hate it when that happens.
I don't want to say stuff like, oh, that thing.
I hate that thing.
Like, like, I know, like I used to know it in all these like terms.
Like there's all these fancy terms for what I'm going to describe it.
I can't.
Anyway, so there's like, there's like a thing, right?
There's like a thing where like in a system, in like in a system of particles, in like a system of particles,
like whose configuration is random and who, and that are like moving randomly, there is like, okay.
So like the nature of a system is to increase disorder and entropy generally.
However, however, there is some like, there is some like statistical probability of like a random configuration occurring that like repeats itself,
even though that even though that even though that goes against the continual increase of entropy.
So what I'm saying is, so what I'm saying is that like, that like a system of particles,
even though it is nature generally tends toward more disorder, does have some,
does will eventually, is suggested that it will eventually return to its original configuration, even in spite of all that.
The point being, that this is technically true of the universe as a system as well.
And that according to some, some, I don't remember the calculations, but it's like in like, even though the universe is expanding,
even though like space itself is expanding, and even though like, like the heat death of the universe is coming and everything is moving outward,
and it doesn't seem like there's, it seems like the universe is just going to become a cold dead nothing.
There does exist some kind of probability of this occurring, and that means that on a long enough time frame, it will occur eventually.
In like 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 10 to the 23,
or some shit, it's like literally the largest number ever published in a scientific paper.
This is what I remember.
If someone knows what I'm fucking talking about, please link me like this article that I've, this study that I'm talking about.
I am like Patrick with the milk spilling in his brain right now.
The point is, the point is that in this time, there exists some, there exists some possibility that the universe might just fucking randomly reconfigure itself into its,
into its original state, and it all could begin again, and that's what I would want.
That's an episode of Futurama, isn't it?
Is it?
Yeah, they, it's one of the new Comedy Central seasons where-
Oh, I haven't seen the new ones.
Yeah, so something happens and they fuck up, so a fry, and I think a few of the other characters,
like they just sit there and wait for the universe to start over again, and then they get back to where they were, and it happens like a bunch of times.
I mean, there's like, there's like some, there's different way, like, you know, there's the big bang, and there's like,
what if it contracts again, and that's the big crunch, but according to everything I've read, like there's not enough mass,
like there's not enough gravity in the universe, like there's not actually going to be a big crunch.
It's just going to keep expanding and expanding, so like, that's really, when I heard, that made me really sad,
because what I would really, I just want the universe to start over.
So I read about this like statistical thing, and I was like, oh, maybe, maybe even if there's no big crunch,
maybe even if the universe continually expands and space expands, maybe there can still, maybe there can still be like a reconfiguration,
because that's what I want, what I would want, what I really want is for the universe to repeat itself in cycles over and over again,
Time is a flat circle, it's true detective.
I hope so. That's what I want. So that's what I, so that's what I want to happen after death.
I want the universe to die and be reborn and for it to all happen again.
And I know that's probably really cruel to people that live really shit lives, but,
Yeah, no shit.
But I live a pretty good life and I like it, so whatever, I'm going to, I'm going to vote, I'm going to vote my best interests.
I'm, so I'm voting, I'm voting on what happens after you die, and I'm voting for fucking, I'm voting for a big crunch,
and it starts over again and fuck the weak people.
Well shit, Ben, I just, I just hope that people remember me fondly and think that I was a good person.
No, I mean, I'd like that, but it's not enough, it's not enough.
As far as my fucking, as my thought on the subject goes, you're over here talking about the heat death of the universe,
and time being an infinite loop, and I'm just like, I hope nobody thinks I'm an asshole after I go.
You know, boys, those are two pretty good answers, but I think I got you beat.
Alright, let's hear it.
After you die, three words.
Hot tub bikini party.
That was four words.
I thought you were going to say hot tub time machine, and I was like, yes, yes.
After you die, every girl you ever had a crush on, both people you knew and celebrities are there in a hot tub with you,
they're all in bikinis, baby, and maybe, you know, that's just heaven, you're there forever,
and maybe eventually they will take their bikini tops off.
Oh my god, they really are.
Just to clarify, are you talking about this is what happens in the here after,
or are you talking about that's your funeral, like you invite all the girls you've ever had,
they get in the tub with your corpse, and because you grew old,
okay, they're all these old girls that you were crushing on when you were a child.
Disgusting.
No.
Luna Lovegood is a fictional character, okay?
I'm not going to have fake characters in my hot tub when I'm a corpse.
I'm talking, this is heaven after you die.
Alright, that makes more sense.
You gotta, you gotta...
Let's keep this afterlife realistic, Ben.
Yeah, come on.
Let's keep it in the realm of what can definitely happen.
Jess, have you seen that movie Red?
No.
The Bruce Willis movie?
I have not.
Okay, have you seen Weeds?
There's some, the woman from those shows.
I have a crush on her.
She's like the oldest woman I want to fuck.
Whatever her name is.
Oh wait, um, oh man.
Well she's there too, and she's wearing a bikini.
You know, you know who's old, you know who's old and who I always had a crush on?
Betty White.
Um, no, um, I don't know if I'm saying this right.
Julia Louis Dreyfus from Psycho.
Yeah.
Well that's a, that is a, that is a good looking old broad.
She's like a, she's like a mega all time nineties babe.
Yeah.
Yep.
For sure.
Oh, Mary Louise Parkers who I'm talking about.
Yeah, she's pretty good.
Pretty cute.
For an old broad.
If I brought old broad I mean like she's 40.
For, for an old broad who, for whom death is, is certain and soon.
Yeah.
Who stinks, who stinks of it, you know?
All right.
The, the, the, the, the chill, the chill of death clings to her at all times.
So what are some other death topics we could focus on in our grand death episode?
Um, how do you want to die?
Oh, that's a good one.
I'm, I want to die, um, I want to die, uh, I want to die, well here's how I want to die.
I want to die by having each one of my brain cells replaced, uh, one by one, so that, you
know, it, like my mind, my brain becomes less and less me and more and more machine.
So I don't, there's no moment of actual death.
I just slowly phase out of existence.
I phase out of existence slowly and I'm, and I'm slowly replaced by an artificial consciousness
that perfectly mimics me.
Because if I don't get to live, I at least, I at least want like a perfect facsimile of
me to live on.
And I would, I would be, well not okay with that, but it would be the next best thing
to not be in dead.
Yeah.
Slowly fading out of consciousness actually sounds pretty good, which is why, uh, the
way I want to die is suspension hanging from a noose in my closet.
I want to die by my own hand.
I want to decide when it happens, where it happens and why it happens.
I'm not going to be some faggot getting in a burn up car crash, dying that way so that
assholes make fun of me in a podcast.
Getting buried in kitty litter.
Yeah.
I'm not going to get cancer and where a survivor headband everywhere.
I'm going to decide, you know what?
This is the point in which I've had enough.
You know, I just hit 40k subs.
That's too many.
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
I'm going to, I'm going to go hang out in the closet.
Death by sub count.
Yeah.
A growing, a growing epidemic.
Yeah, you're right.
No, John Tron and Great Eye Under Ray both died from a, too high of a sub count.
True.
Um, yeah, I think-
And I guess Ray William Johnson.
I think we all have a totally different answers on this one because Ben said that he wants
to go, you know, slowly and peacefully losing consciousness.
Monkey wants to fucking kill himself.
Um, why am I laughing?
Um, you know, I think the way I want to go, I know it's a cliche and I'm not trying to
sound like a tough guy, but I really want to go out in battle.
I want to make a last stand for something I believe in, fighting someone who needs to
get beaten up.
I want to go out as a fucking vigilante.
Um, you know, you know what I really want-
Just some comments are on a video.
Yeah.
Some guy who didn't understand a plebe in the weeb.
He thought it was supposed to be serious.
I will find the worst commenter of all time.
The guy who understood plebe in the weeb the less than anyone in the world.
I'll find that guy.
I'll find all of them and it'll be just like the end of Gran Torino.
I'll be standing on my front lawn, my front lawn with all the bad commenters and I'm
going to put my finger out like a gun and they're going to shoot me down and I'll die
being Clint Eastwood.
Actually becoming Clint Eastwood.
That's terrible revenge.
It's, it's a, well you know what, um, I want to take, yeah, better than that, I'll take
a few of them out with me at least.
Yeah.
I want that and then I want my funeral to just be the yandu scene at the end of Guardians.
That's exactly what I want to be shot and blown up in fireworks.
With fireworks in space.
I want Sylvester Stallone to be there saying what a great guy I was.
He'll be like 150.
You want a raccoon to be there crying.
Yes.
And I want Baby Groot to fucking, to sing Amazing Grace as they blow me up with fireworks.
Baby Groot, baby, baby Groot, baby.
Oh yeah, that reminds me of Dead and Gay.
That's another topic about being dead.
Oh yeah, I have been dead because I've been dead and gay.
I was actually on that album.
And there we go.
Good job me.
Me and Baby Groot, the two stars of that album and no one else.
I actually did a sick alternate cover art for Gay and Dead.
And it's like this melting skull of all these rainbow colors just melting over a skull.
Yeah, I saw that.
You know what?
I was like that's sick as hell.
It's better than the actual cover.
You know what?
What's the actual cover?
The actual cover is some flowers on a patch of dirt.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, I remember.
You know what?
That'd be cool if in 10 years he made the special edition with a slip cover.
You could put that in the slip cover.
That'd be cool.
Yeah.
That one, that one was, that one was choice.
That one was mwah.
Mwah.
I wish I knew who did it.
I would say nice job.
Mwah.
It's just like the kisses get wetter and sloppier each time.
That's how much you like it.
The more you like something, the wetter and sloppier your kiss.
Yeah, that sounds right.
Alright boys, here's a big one.
Yep, yep.
Jess, please, for the love of God, let's keep Trump out of this one.
What living person would you, do you wish would die?
If you had a death note, who do you wish was dead?
Oh, Sargon of Akkad.
Oh, shut the fuck up.
I think we've done this before and you said that same shit.
Sargon of Akkad or any of like the dozens of people that are exactly like him.
He deserves to die because he got attacked by Anita Sarkeesian.
I don't think so.
He and everyone just like him deserves to die because they...
For being a smug atheist on YouTube?
For being a fucking...
What's the word?
A fucking rage mongering fucking conflict profiteer.
For being someone whose entire existence is to make people angry.
Yeah, you've got like people like in North Korea who are running death camps and you...
Nah, I think Sargon of Akkad.
Alright, alright.
He's not like the worst...
Okay, whatever.
He's just the one that I have like the most...
I don't know those guys.
I haven't seen the death camps.
Why don't you defeat him with your like moral superiority and intelligence instead of just fucking killing?
No, that's not worth it.
That's them.
That's the wrong.
They have to die.
I'll tell you why.
Because people don't fucking...
People are too stupid to recognize my moral and intellectual superiority.
That's exactly right.
Didn't you beat him on Twitter though?
I don't...
I mean, we have like...
What kind of an exchange?
I mean, I guess it's up to you who won.
I mean, his creepy sick of fan followers thought that he won.
I thought that I won.
Pick your poison, I suppose.
Yeah, that's the problem with these people on the internet.
Like, you can be better than them and you can win, but they don't know that you won.
So they...
So they just have to die.
It's the only way.
They just like...
They just like weren't even reading the things that were said.
They just...
They like didn't even see what was going on.
They were just like, oh, I...
I don't know.
I don't know what they were thinking.
I hate them.
I hate them more than life itself.
And I...
Wait, I like life itself.
I don't want to die.
Yeah, that's a weird phrase to use.
Yeah.
You hate them more than death itself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the...
Well, that's not true.
That sounds stupid too.
I don't know.
If I weren't scared to die, I wouldn't worry about the existence of Sargon and his infinite clone army.
Yeah.
Because I would be like, well, whatever.
It'll all work itself out in the end.
One day they'll all grow up.
But now I know that they won't, because they'll die first.
Yeah.
I don't think I would use a death note to kill anyone.
Not out of any sense of morals, just because you need to know someone's name and face.
So all the people that I...
Well, that's not specifically a death note.
It's just like, if you could choose one person to die, who would it be?
Oh, like with my bare hands or like a baseball bat, I can just have someone appear in front of me
and I can physically murder them?
Oh my god.
Yeah, sure.
How do I pick just one?
I want all of them.
The whole world to line up outside my door.
Oh shit.
One by one.
I want that if anyone has ever played the game No More Heroes.
You fight that.
She's like the number two boss near the end.
She's like this crazy cheerleader.
She's just got guys, gimps coming out on the conveyor belt.
And she's like knocking them with a baseball bat one after another.
I want that with everyone.
Yeah.
I want to be the number two boss from No More Heroes.
That's my role model in life.
Would you dress everyone else up as gimps before you sluggered them?
Definitely.
They need to be dressed as what they are.
Which is, I guess, gimps.
I don't know where I'm going with that.
Clearly the two of you have a lot of inner frustration and hatred and rage towards the world.
I hate that opportunity so much.
I hate them.
Yeah.
When given the opportunity to kill one person, I would do it out of peace and love and understanding.
I want somebody to be put out of their misery.
Somebody who has not only been miserable for so long, but has spread their misery to the masses.
I think I see where you're going with this, Mumki.
I'm going to put my buddy Conrad Collins just into him.
Oh yeah.
Let him go.
I think he's done enough.
Now I do have a bit of this selfish reason.
Somebody has to do it.
The one problem I have with Mr. Conrad Collins other than his eternal misery that he spreads upon the masses is that
he has 300,000 subs, and if we get rid of him, then I will be ever so close to being the head honcho of the PCP
and then everybody can suck my dick.
And I need that dick sucking really bad.
So that's why Conrad Collins has got to go.
Wait, wait.
Why would you be the head honcho?
I feel like all of us would have to leave, and it would just be you.
Just the idea of everybody thinks the PCP is Digi's thing because he has the most subs, which is not true.
I've always considered it Nate's thing, to be honest.
Well we know that Nate's the only one who takes any kind of a leadership role at all.
But the masses, these dumb ignorant masses that watch Thunderfoot and Armored Skeptic and other such monsters
are all thinking that Digi is the king of the mountain and in fact he is just a really nice guy.
Yeah.
Stop thinking that this is Digi Bro's show.
He hasn't been on it in two months and he doesn't give a fuck about it.
Give the credit to Nate and I guess whoever edits the episode.
Let's say we say this, our subs just dropped to like 8,000, 7,000, 6,000.
I thought that was the Digi Bro show.
Wait, I wanted to answer my anime question on the pro questionators.
Okay, do you guys want to go to the Twitter questions?
Yeah, I was just looking at those actually.
You got one?
No, they all suck ass.
They're terrible.
Don't like them?
Okay, here we go.
You can only save one.
Mumkey Jones or model railways.
What the hell's model railways?
That's from Stan on Wheels.
I think he just means like do you save Mumkey Jones or do you save all like model trains in the world?
I mean, I would give you all permission to put me out of my misery anyway, so I mean, all the model trains in the world.
I think it's all of them.
It could just be some.
He didn't clarify.
Are you sure it's not a YouTube channel called that where a guy talks about trains?
Well, he capitalized your name, but he didn't capitalize model railways, so I don't think he's talking about a person.
If Mumkey dies in this arrangement, can I put the Mumkey mask on a model train and just call it the new Mumkey?
It would be just as funny.
Because then everybody wins.
Then you just get a better Mumkey.
Yeah.
Maybe he wouldn't get banned from uploading for two weeks on YouTube.
IceKiller159 asks, what is your favorite gay and dead track?
Oh.
Gay and dead.
I don't know.
I actually don't know which songs are on that album.
I haven't actually listened to the full album itself, so Jesse.
I have to look at the track list again.
I did listen to it twice in a row today, but it's escaping.
The second to last track on the album where Digi is more singing than rapping, I thought that sounded really nice and really different for him.
And it was really kind of a beautiful song, and I liked it a lot.
The fucking freak power was really cool.
I think my favorite song on the album is one of the ones that I'm on, Paradise.
I just really love the sound of it, and I love the beat.
I love both of our verses.
I think we both did a really good job.
My least favorite song on the album is probably the other song that I'm on, The Bunker.
Just because it sounds way too much like Rotten, which we already did.
Lyrically and sound-wise, but I still think it's cool, especially since I put Baby Groot in it.
I made that executive decision for Digi to put Baby Groot all over his album to save, to make it a five-star album.
It would have been a four-star. Baby Groot rounded it out.
Sizzwhitescom69 asks,
My hero.
Fishing? Yeah!
Totally, dude.
Yeah, fishing's okay. I like fishing.
I'm way more into cat fishing, actually.
What's the same shit?
I'm talking about the internet kind.
Oh, god damn it.
I'm talking about fucking falsifying your identity on the internet.
Yeah, man.
You're not going by your real name, so maybe you already are doing that to all of us.
I'm cat-fishing everyone. I'm cat-fishing everyone.
All my patrons have been cat-fished.
Everybody thinks Nate's name is Nate Sainton. He hates it.
This whole time you've been cat-fishing us.
We thought you were a Ben, but it turns out you were a has-ben all along.
No! I walked right into it!
There's something very... I'll say euphoric, because I'm wearing a fedora right now.
Very euphoric about... you feel like you can connect to your ancestors.
When you go out and you catch a fish and you fucking fry that baby up and you eat it,
you get your own food, you don't have to pay for shit.
You just go get it and you eat it.
I used to go... My mom used to take me fishing once.
She did it a couple times, and we caught some fish, but we never cooked them.
I always kind of wanted to cook.
We usually just caught these little sunfish that were not big enough to cook.
We caught a catfish one time.
One time I caught a fucking sea bass.
One time I caught a big fucking fucker.
It was more than a foot long.
I didn't eat it.
I wanted to eat it.
I wanted to be like, Mom, can we take this home and cook it and eat it
and skin it and do all that shit to it?
I was shy about it and didn't want to impose.
I didn't want to ask her to go to all that trouble, so we didn't.
Why do you just throw them back in?
Yeah, I just toss them back in.
It's probably... I don't know if it's true or not, but they say that fish can't feel pain,
so I was like, fuck it, just throw it back in.
They don't even know what's going on.
I believe it.
They say that about lobsters, too.
Well, no, no.
Lobsters apparently can't feel pain.
Also, apparently, if you put a lobster in the freezer, it goes to sleep
and then you can murder it and it doesn't resist.
Man, that's gotta be a lie.
Because it's too convenient that the one animal we cruelly and viciously boil a lie
just happens to be the one that doesn't feel pain.
That sounds like you don't know, man.
It's trying to make themselves feel better about something horrible they're doing.
I don't know, man. A lobster is basically like an ocean insect.
It's just like a big fucking bug.
So I could believe, just looking at it, it looks like something that can't feel pain.
It just looks like a fucking demon robot.
I don't know, man. When I see those lobsters in the store, in the tank together,
with their claws tied up, they look like they're in a lot of emotional pain.
I saw on a cooking video a guy, he took a lobster out of his freezer
where he had kept it so that it would be comatose.
And then he put it down and he just takes his giant knife and just slices it right in half.
Right down its head.
And it kind of like its tail kind of like curls up and its claws kind of like twitch a little bit.
And then it just like goes slack.
And I was like, oh my god, what have I just witnessed?
Shit, I can see festivals now. They're everywhere.
Oh god.
It was gruesome. It was gruesome.
Yeah, always wanted to eat those fish, never did.
Was the question just like the one word question fishing
gave us the biggest answer so far?
Yeah, it's important.
If you want to ask a good question, just write down a verb with a question mark and see what happens.
Just throw a spaghetti at the wall and see what it says.
Hopscotch?
Let me tell you about if lobsters can feel pain, motherfucker.
KH underscore Caligula says,
How do you all feel about competitive video games?
If any of you do like them, what games do you watch or play?
The most stress I ever feel in my whole life is when I jump into a Gen 4 randomized battle on Pokemon Showdown.
I don't know how anybody likes it. I hate it.
The one-on-one battle is like a double battle is a different thing. I think that's more fun.
But one-on-one, those motherfuckers are just switching the Pokemon every fucking turn
without predicting you at every moment.
It's not even fun.
I get migraines and stress headaches from playing Pokemon Showdown.
For a week or two ago, I was on a crazy winning streak on Showdown
doing Gen 7 one-on-one randomized battles.
My score got way up and then I got fucked up at some point this week
and now my score is shit again. I was really sad.
Yeah, I guess if Pokemon Showdown counts as a competitive game,
yeah, I guess I play that.
I absolutely fucking hate MOBAs.
I think they're the worst ever.
I hate them. I would never watch or play them.
Briefly, some friends of mine tried to get me into League of Legends
and I played it a little bit.
I played it a little bit, got kinda good with Warwick.
I had mostly figured out Warwick and I was like,
oh, okay, I'm feeling a little good.
I'm kinda starting to get a couple of kills and doing a little bit,
not completely fucking it up for my team.
And then my friends were like, okay, good, now do that with 40 other characters.
And I was like, no, no, I won't do that.
It's not worth it. I hate you.
Stop yelling at me because I'm not defending the fucking tower or whatever shit.
And I hate MOBAs. I hate them. I hate them.
I passionately fucking hate MOBAs.
I kind of hate all competitive video games.
I think video games are for cowards.
I think video games are a waste of time
and for nerds and bastards and fuck off.
I really love Mario Party.
Oh, yeah, me too.
Like the first two Mario Party games to this day,
if you've got three friends, it's the best possible time you can have in life.
It's the best way to stave off the specter of death.
You see, because Mario Party is a special thing where it's actually fun,
whereas something like League of Legends or Pokemon Showdown,
it feels more like a stressful chore to me.
It doesn't feel like a fun game, but Mario Party and even Mario Kart,
it's just whimsical and fun, and I don't wish I was dead the whole time.
I like fighting on Pokemon Showdown
because a match usually only lasts like 10 minutes at the most,
or sometimes they go longer,
but you play fucking League of Legends and then you boot it up.
40 minutes later, you lost,
and 45 of your precious minutes are gone,
and I've never had a worse time than when I fucking played League of Legends.
Oh, Christ.
I'm throwing up thinking about it.
I gotta fucking calm my nerves with this Rockstar, pure zero.
Do we have any more good questions, or should we call it a day?
Um, what are we at?
What are we at? Well, we're like just...
A job about an hour.
We should, let's do one more.
Yeah, let's do one more.
Oh, this is a great question.
One society, from Best Digi Wood,
one society has 100 people each with 100 happy points,
one society has 1,000 people each with 99 happy points.
This sounds like math.
Wait, what the fuck?
What's the question?
Which is best.
Wait, is this like a...
Wait, this is a really stupid quest.
This is like a failed communism philosophical debate.
This is actually not the question I thought it was going to be.
I thought it was going to say one society has 100 people each with one happy points,
and another society has 10 people each with 10 happy points.
So like, the numbers are equivalent, but they're spread over like a bigger amount.
No, this is... one society has 10 times more people,
but each one is ever so slightly less happy.
Yeah, of course that one's better.
Yeah, I mean...
I think the point...
Who wants to be 100% happy all the time?
Do they not see inside out? You need that sadness, people.
Yeah, even in a society where everyone is equally sad,
they can bond over being equally sad and become friends and make each other happier.
Yeah, it's called the PCP.
Well, this is a...
Yeah!
Well, that's a slippery slope.
That's a slippery slope because if you can see that 1,000 people with 99 happy points
is better than 100 people with 100 happy points,
the logical conclusion of that is that ultimately,
a million billion people each with only one happy point is the best of all.
That's the slippery slope. What are you fucking talking about?
You went way too far.
Well, I'm saying because if more people less happy is better.
We're comparing two very specific things.
We're not comparing some fictional thing you made up.
Well, I'm just saying that if you keep iterating on this process,
if you multiply the amount of people by 10 and subtract 1 out of 100 happy points,
eventually you do that 100 times and you eventually hit a point where nobody's happy anymore,
even though there's lots of people.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
I know what you're saying, but I don't see why it's relevant to comparing these two societies.
I'm actually going to hold...
I'm going to say 100 people each with 100 happy points.
Why would you want to be 100% happy?
That sounds fucking terrible.
Being happy is like definitionally a good thing.
Have you seen inside out, dude?
No, I'm not fucking seen inside out.
If you're always happy, then that's not a good thing.
You need the sadness to actually be a human being.
I don't want to be a human being.
I want to be a joy bot.
You want to be an immortal fucking robot.
I want to be an immortal robot that feels nothing but happiness
and is loved and adored throughout time and all.
Do you want to just get tired of it eventually?
No, you wouldn't because I'm programmed not to.
I'm too simple for this question.
I'm but a humble man of the earth.
This is too abstract.
I don't know.
Who wants...
100 people is enough.
If I was always happy all the time,
not only would the people around me get annoyed,
but I would just get bored.
No, you'd never be bored because you'd be happy.
Do you like the people who are always super
like chipper and happy all the time?
Fuck those people.
I don't want to be living with 99 of them around me.
Fuck that.
Hang on.
The question stipulates that you are...
I think the question stipulates
these people are happy.
These people are not getting annoyed by one another
being happy. They like it.
Yeah, I can because it says
people have 100 happy points.
I can be annoyed by people and still be happy.
I guess.
Wait.
You can be annoyed by people and still be happy?
Bullshit.
How dare you lie to me in such a fashion?
Can we be done?
I don't want to talk about these happy points.
I want to fucking go to bed.
Alright, alright.
Okay, here's one.
Who's the sexiest beetle?
Ringo.
Hang on. Let me look up a picture
because I think I know the one...
I think I know the one that's the sexiest.
You know, I've listened to the beetles.
I respect them as artists and as men.
But they all look and sound
exactly the fucking same to me.
I cannot tell any of them apart.
Oh, hang on.
What's the one where they're walking
across the street?
The savvy road.
Yeah, yeah.
The...
I don't know, the third one.
The one in the gray.
Yeah, that's Ringo.
Yeah, I guess Ringo. I don't know.
The other ones kind of look like hobos.
Maybe George Harrison had a mustache
sometimes.
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, I don't...
I mean, I know what John Lennon looks like
and the other three I'm like,
I can't remember which one's which.
Yeah, that's my answer.
That was a shitty question, dude.
Here's one that I don't want to answer.
Well, I'm sorry. Here's a...
Do the best I can with what I got.
A favorite obscure piece of media
that you don't talk about that much.
Oh, huh.
And I have an answer for this
that I do want to talk about.
It's, you know, this is an old show
that used to be on G4,
the old video game network
when they had that before it went...
Attack the show.
This was a show...
Stop it!
This is a show that I think
was very influential to the kind of videos
that I ended up making.
It was a show called Portal
Yeah, I remember Portal.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember wanting to like it
but not having anything
to like about it.
I don't really remember
what its deal was.
It started out
like a regular, like a video game,
like a review and a tips show
for MMOs, like teaching you how to play
and teaching you how good they all are,
like MMORPGs and like the Sims and stuff,
like computer games and stuff.
But occasionally he would start
putting in like these
skits and these wacky characters
using the game engines, like
sort of like a rooster teeth
kind of thing, like the red and blue or whatever.
These wacky characters and these skits
and eventually the skits
and the characters would become so
intricate and like interconnected
that by the time you got to Season 2
the reviews and the tips
and tricks aspect of it was completely gone
and it was just like a narrative show.
Like the saga of this guy
and all of his wacky friends in these computer games
and there was like a story and like
an overarching plot and a bad guy
and it was really fucking cool.
It was the best show ever. Portal on G4.
Look it up. You can watch the whole series on YouTube.
It's awesome.
One time I was watching Portal
and my dad came in
and was like, hey what are you watching?
And I said Portal and I remember that
he thought that I said porn
and
like he didn't even like do any
I think he like laughed
like maybe he thought I was joking or something
I don't know but I remember
my dad thought I said I was watching porn
What?
It was weird.
Fuck it.
Mom can you got any obscure shit?
Yeah, there's a little known
YouTube channel I really like called Psy
about this guy who
talks about video games.
There's a podcast I really love
that's been going on for like 10 or 11 years
that gets overshadowed by other
podcasts in a similar
genre.
It's called The Flop House. It's about these
three friends, two of which
were the head writers on The Daily Show
during John Stewart's peak
like the best part so these are funny guys
and they just every other week they'll watch
a bad movie. The show is called The Flop House
if I didn't say The Flop House.
They'll watch a bad movie and then they'll talk about it
and you know it's a very simple premise but since these guys are so
funny and they've been friends for so long
and there's all these inside jokes that
get established as the show goes on
it's just a great
90 minutes out of my week
every other week and I really like it so
if you need something to listen to
to hear three schmucks make fun of a movie
I'd say go check out The Flop House.
Shit.
Sick dog.
For me
I'm sure I could probably think
of more but
the first thing that pops
to my mind is a
porn actually. It's a
hentai manga that I read years ago
and I never forgot about it.
The Vapors by Benson.
And I've never
heard anyone talk about it although
there are some memes from it that float around
and
it's called
Seiso Tsuidansha
which is hard to remember which is probably
why I don't see it mentioned very often
and it's like
a couple chapters long
and it's mostly like
femdom, it's kind of like a bunch of
mean girls bully this guy
which is not something that I'm really into
but the reason I like Seiso Tsuidansha
so much is that it's really funny
like it's really fucking hilarious
as well as being sexy
so
I guess that's my
obscure thing that I like
and fuck everyone else
it's got
it's iconic, it's got some iconic moments
but I won't spoil it
I don't want to see this
just send me a link so I know how to avoid
ever going to the website
we'll do
I'll know if I ever see this website
I shouldn't click on it
just do it right now so you don't forget
later on I really want to make sure
I don't click on this
here we go
I'm off
let's see
what the
favorite
YouTube fiction series
this is from Duffraven
I don't know
if this counts as YouTube fiction
maybe I'm
stretching the definition
but I really really liked
the Yogscast
Shadow of Israel
series
it's a Minecraft let's play
but
the game is being
changed and edited behind
the players backs
to create this story
that they have to adventure through
and
it's like a let's play
but it's being run
by outside people
who are sort of like
they're sort of like dungeon mastering it
and like it's sort of being
they're sort of being walked through this like
fiction scenario
so I don't know if that counts but
that one's really really cool
and I love it
wait fiction series
on YouTube
we can't say me and Jess's shows
because those are non-fiction
those are the actual accounts
of our inner demons
true stories of our real actual lives
both inner and
stories of our inner and outer struggles
right
I don't know if it was originally on
YouTube but the Brad Neely
the Brad Neely Baby Cakes
and like Professor Brothers videos
I guess those would be considered YouTube fiction
so those are like
way high on my list as like
favorite things ever not just on YouTube
this might be a loose definition but
since we're talking about YouTube fiction
I'm gonna talk about a Christian
singer since obviously
Christianity's fiction
you guys remember making a murderer
about that guy who
was made into a murderer?
no?
well it's this big phenomenon on Netflix
about this guy who was set up for a crime
that he didn't commit and he's like still in prison
but his brother is a man named
Brad Dassie
and I advise every single person listening
in a home to go check this out because
Brad Dassie is a musician
rapper he's like this 40 year old white guy
who
I'm not gonna say he has
no talent I'm gonna say
he is exceptionally
entertaining in a multitude of ways
my favorite song by him
is called I'm coming home
everybody please go search I'm coming home
Brad Dassie take a listen
post a comment saying the PCP
sent you there because it's a real treat
it's a great song don't listen to the new one
he put up a remix it's terrible
listen to the one that was put up 5 or 6 years ago
he also has a
rap song called they didn't do it
about how his brother was
set up for the murder in the show making a murderer
and the lyrics go
he didn't do it he didn't do it
the cops poking around in a minute
he didn't do it and he just
we all sat for 4 minutes and it's very passionate
and I hope his brother
gets out of prison soon because he's gonna blow a gasket
and also he is
he is a lot of songs about
his relationship with Jesus
it's very interesting go check out
Brad Dassie music
yeah
I don't know if it's technically fiction
or if it's kind of like
sort of semi-fiction
I don't know what the deal is but there's this
underground channel called Furnace Room
it's very
about this guy
he's trapped in a Furnace Room
or something
yeah you know the bit I'm doing
just click on it and then
skip to the last 10 seconds because that's the best part
the videos are only
10 seconds long
well the out shows are the best
it's what I'm clicking on
yeah that's true
Furnace Room
how
lazy ace
let me out
lazy ace Diaz says get into a pissing contest
about who is the most depressed
Ben how many of these fucking questions do you want to do
oh shit what are we done
do you want to call it
I mean we're only at an hour 15
that's plenty
alright well
fuck you lazy ace Diaz
we all know that Mumkey's the most depressed
you don't need a debate
that's very actively not depressed
I pour all of my power into
not being depressed every day
all my strength of will
um
I'm a happy boy
let's say bye everybody
bye everybody
I love ya
fuck my ass
let me out
yeah
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick I'm jerking
myself I'm
sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a
deadline
don't want to do it