Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
This is an unexpected Ben cast. Gibb was around. Gibb was around today and I just assumed she'd show up, but no. No, it's the time has come. It's almost 25 minutes past the starting point and you know, I'm all alone.
I guess that liver poison I've been feeding here has been working. I finally got the dose right. And now it's all mine. I have the floor to myself. I can platform my far right, my alt-right ideas. It's finally time.
Yes, it is episode 290 whatever, 287 whatever, and it's another fucking celebration of me and all things me.
Okay, so I don't want to talk. Well, there are some things that I don't want to go too into depth in because I actually am I owe my patrons a podcast, which I'm probably going to record tomorrow, a sort of update about me and what I've been doing and especially the game project for that.
So I could talk a bunch about that, but I'm going to hold off here. I will I will vaguely say that what's been going on with me is that I've been working on that I after the after the demo came out I worked really hard and really diligently for a bit right before the demo and I got it done.
And then I was a little burnt out afterwards and since then I have been doing I have sort of been focusing on easy shit like like sprites and assets and stuff rather than digging into like the kind of nitty gritty of like the programming side of it to implement the stuff that I wanted to implement that wasn't there.
So I've been making progress but I still feel bad. I've been making very um, I don't know. I guess I could say superficial it's not really superficial progress because it is all stuff like new sprites new animations like I did want it was all stuff that I did intend for the final game to have so it's
not very work but the game itself is pretty much in the same state it was when the demo came out it just it looks nicer it has it has some stuff anyway that's that's what I've been up to with that but if you want to hear more about that or ask me questions about that you can go to patreon.com
to see the famous world renowned um what else um somebody it was you know what let me let me credit them in the in the radcon for paradise discord server it was K5 Josh thank you K5 Josh for for linking this 4chan thread in
response to Nate releasing his new Kingdom Hearts 3 review um they they there is Nate discussion and then there is a lot of general PCP discussion and you know it's a lot of it's a lot of the same it's a lot of the same shit you see on Kiwi Farms it's a lot of the same
it's a lot of a lot of the T word a lot of that old transphobia but there's there's some funny stuff there's I have one or two a lot of a lot of stuff but Ben is annoying Ben's too political Ben's a fucking communist I have one or two defenders in there
not just like dick suckers either there's there's one guy in here who I really appreciate because he doesn't just say that like he doesn't say that I'm I'm great or anything he criticizes me in certain ways but ways that I agree with and then he
also he gives me credit for things that nobody's let me let me read this one this one made me really happy Ben saint ah yes the arch nemesis of forge also I have a feeling that whoever wrote this listens to the podcast so if you're hearing
this thanks and I'm sorry I'm I'm embarrassed to think about you hearing me read your fortune I'm embarrassed for myself and for you and I and I hope that it brings us closer hopefully we feel the same way about it
ah yes the arch nemesis of four channels like us huh LeMau Ben politics brought the show down but he made some good points here and there editorializing by me I do think that there were times when I was too aggressive about it and and brought it up when other people I do think there were
like that I'm not I'm not free of I'm not free of blame of criticism in that area not as often as some people said I did but sometimes I did anyway much less political now people don't give him enough credit for being one of the only members to want things to be completely
transparent he was the first to say he didn't feel that mumke needed to be kicked out he called out shit on everyone just feeling attacked mumke not really contributing anything meaningful to any PCP episode he was on did you wanting to steer the show in directions no one wanted and the stupid idea of
informing a sort of RLM collective he is keeping the PCP a lot how to falling out with digi because uh the I prefer to call her Trixie I don't I don't like I'm not offended by someone calling them digi because digi is a screen name but this person said digis I'll read what they said that's whatever sorry
because he doesn't respect his friends and thinks they're all fucking idiots she dude got mad when a friend of digis opted to either make a new rad con or refilm the pony lecture digis rad con lecture he doesn't want to make public as this was before
oh god oh no slur skipping it some of the other people never mind never mind I take it back I don't want to marry you anymore you need to work on yourself nevertheless thanks for thanks for thanks you for acknowledging the
I'm all about transparency people complain about me Trixie complained about me talking about things I shouldn't talk about saying stuff that's like ooh you shouldn't talk about your friends friends that way and it's literally just I don't want to hide shit and lie about shit
that's that people have that's a problem people have with me is that I don't do that and you know what good I'm glad good good for me no apologies um I don't know there's some more here whatever it's kind of a funny thread a lot of a lot of bullshit too but some of this stuff is funny
uh whatever I no no need to go any further and you get the idea um so what else what else happened okay I I remembered the other week when we had simsian we talked about israel there was a something that I forgot to mention but that I in hindsight was like I wish I mentioned it I made some I made some pro palestine post on twitter and some that a bunch responses I got one guy
I had I had a couple of people who argued with me but one guy stuck out it was this is one guy who was like what do you want to free them from and I said you know genocide displacement whatever I forget what I exact said and and this guy was like um actually the jews or I don't remember if he said the jews or israel israel whatever
he said Israel has actually given so much to Palestine you know Israel is actually the good guys and I was like what do you mean I've seen the maps I've seen how the territory and a terror palestinian territory has shrunk over the years and this guy's like no no no actually it's like this and then he goes on like a 20 I'm not even joking like a 20 post long thread paragraphs and paragraphs about how like oh in in like 1940 whatever uh palestine
refuse to sign an agreement with Israel over such and such and it's like all stuff from like the 40s 50s 60s and I'm kind of like reading along and just being like I this I'm not I'm not really convinced that this is that relevant was going on right now yeah historical context whatever the guy goes to such length that like he eventually starts
linking me to wikipedia articles about like I'm not kidding symphony orchestras and football teams that used to be like called the palestinian team or the palestinian symphony orchestra but are now called
like the Israel versions like they changed their name and were subsumed by Israel and this is supposed to be evidence that like actually Israel is giving stuff to them because they took their fucking football teams or something I didn't get it I didn't get it but my
my that was the point when I stopped I was I was actually like following along and responding in good faith but that's the point that I was like I don't think I don't think this person has any good points to make I think we're done when you're like no no this football team changed its name that's why
that's why fucking we got a bomb the AP headquarters to
and I thought that was pretty fucking hilarious
last week I talked at length about my horrible L the horrible L that I took on Twitter the first and worst L that I've ever suffered or ever will suffer when I tragically mistimed my tweet about Trixie give us the fucking footage and just barely missed just barely missed her
actually fucking doing it somehow
only because Riley told her to
I just barely missed it and was wrong and fucked up and then they got to go haha I already I already sent it actually you nerd
big L but I gotta win I gotta win this time and I and I won't belabor the point but I have I've redeemed myself with a W a big fat W
the long and short of it is that I a little while ago I found out that some of the videos on the yig channel are being edited for free by friends of theirs and these are monetized videos that make the money and promote their stuff so this is like unambiguously a for profit thing that they are using free labor to have made for them
which I I don't think is right under any circumstances
literally they are and I know this is an inflammatory way to phrase it but yig studios is literally doctor wolfing people they are literally I love Kim possible allotting people remember that if anyone if any how many of you listeners were around back in the brownie days if you were you might remember
I love Kim possible a lot and doctor wolf did the same shit they would make money on videos they would publish videos that they would monetize with ads and you know charge money for on their patreon and they would get artists and stuff to do it for exposure or just because they knew them and were friends
oh we're all just friends here oh no we're all just we're all just pals right like I'm not like your I'm not your boss like we're like family you know like family share with each other like it's not big don't worry about it don't don't get money involved we don't need
we're friends we're all friends here don't worry about it says says of course the one who's making the money on it says that right of course class classic tales all this time so anyway they're doing that
so they put out a video and I respond on the video I don't name any names but I say pay your editor and the editor who I won't name but I don't like them at all
the editor responds with a big screed about like leave me alone stop bullying me because I said pay your editor so this all happens
a screenshot of her twitter she she winds about it on twitter whatever long story short the yig the yig people all get upset they're all Ben's a bully Ben's so mean Ben doesn't understand that we're all just friends here
it's not like for money it's not it's all we're just family we're like family we're like friends we share why get money involved huh what are you communist you just don't fucking get it
long story short they said okay we'll pay the editor now get fucked get fucked losers I fucking big w I got ya I got ya assuming they're actually gonna assuming they'll they'll actually do what they say and keep their word which I don't I don't trust them too but I'm just gonna I'll just assume that they're telling the truth and it's and it's a big fucking win for me
big fuck everything's fucking coming up Ben saying I got him so if you were concerned about me last episode you I'm sure you remember how how just how the L affected me just how traumatized I was by it but don't worry
I'm talking about the W I'm talking about the W briefly briefly bringing up the W
I talked about the L I gotta give equal time to the to the W are you recording by the way I am recording yes hi Ben I'm done though I was hey give I'm done though I was I was just about to move on from it.
I swear I probably I was probably on it for maybe less than 10 minutes maybe five minutes it's fine it's fine it's good how are you how are you doing.
Oh you know I was I was sorry I'm late for the the PCP I was I was watching the new mission across Scotland you know the Geo guess our boy Geo wizard did the straight line you have told me about him.
The straight line across Wales he did that and did another one there's a bunch of different like missions but this latest one across Scotland.
I've been anticipating it because he's only he's only gotten more adepts and better at these is it.
Is it a series or is it like a big one big like movie okay.
It's the 30 minutes and it's part one they're usually in parts yeah so yeah yeah hi I just didn't pay attention to discord in that time.
Tisk Tisk Tisk.
Imagine not paying attention to discord imagine not being keyed in the social media.
God I fucking hate.
I know no I would never do such a thing.
I got I got I got a fucking get off Twitter.
I know I talk I talk I talk about these this W like it's a big but it's actually an L that I'm even fucking involves I understand I know intellectually I understand that emotionally I just want to fucking.
I know you gotta you gotta destroy your emotions you've got to become a complete robot and and and think of think of the facts and logic.
It's dumb and it doesn't make you happy and it doesn't do anything so stop.
It enough but I but I but I but I got the W though but I know I just said it was an L it was a secret L no it was no it wasn't no it's not possible.
You're not owned then.
But but if but if my W's were actually L's then then what was it all for.
What if I what did I get out of it.
Nothing.
Oh no.
No.
In fact you got me holding holding a W in my hands that starts dissolving like the like the end of of what's the Marvel one where they all dissolve that one.
It turns to dust.
It's like it's like Terry and Lannister said your your your W's will turn to ashes in your mouth.
Here's the W that matters is this image.
Wait, I gotta see.
I gotta I gotta fucking see the general.
It's in general.
I'm in general.
Jump to present.
Oh yeah.
That one.
Yeah man.
I know I'm.
I feel like.
Is it is it a hipster opinion is it like some hipster smug douche baggery to say like that's when Homestuck was still good.
The first time you see Rosalind.
Yeah like this well I mean maybe not that but like I think this might be the peak of a series for me or like when Rose enters when Rose enters the like the period when like all the kids are entering the game.
That's that's peak Homestuck for me it's better than the troll stuff.
I like the troll stuff fine.
But like all the time when all the four kids are entering the game is like.
That definitely feels the big the big hype.
What's it what's it called suburban countdown was what's the.
Do do do do do do do do do.
S.
What is it?
God what is it?
Which one?
The one you were singing.
I forget what it was called.
When Rose breaks the bottle.
Yeah she breaks the bottle.
That one's fighting the big ogres all over his house.
And Dave is doing stuff to get Rose in the game.
I love all that that is really really cool shit.
That's the synchronicity of all of these different things happening at the same time.
Wait is it called S synchronize?
No no I feel that's I feel like there is a no there is a there is an S unite synchronize where Jake and Dirk.
And everyone they all get together.
It's like two flashes punctuated in the middle with a decapitation.
Yeah as great and as great and epic and cool and whoa as a S cascade was and it is I think I like the old I like these ones better.
I really like the ones that are all hussy art the ones that are early on when you're still sort of like finding out and I mean you find out new stuff in cascade.
But like when you're when you're getting introduced to the world through the flashes the one the one where Rose enters the one where and and and Dave enters in the one where WV rise up when the when the the thing.
I mean I mean like the flies across the map.
Those are all like I think my favorite my favorite flash in the whole series is though is Jade enter when she shoots the pinata.
I think that is number one.
Yeah.
That's the song.
That's the same song I use for S mega slime to send.
I think I think that's the same.
Was it.
Oh yes.
Right.
You used visuals from S cascade but you use a different song.
No you're right.
Yeah.
That one.
Like the green sun.
This has become another fucking Homestuck cast.
No I like that.
We need more of it.
It's fine.
The green sun getting formed out of the two universes and spoilers by the way and Rose and John and Dave going God mode like that was a pretty big twist.
That was pretty like whoa but it I think for me even better was when and and it was you could see you could probably see it coming.
I think other people saw it coming but I was reading.
Serially I was really it had all like been done before and I was reading through it really fast all in one go I didn't have to wait between updates so I didn't see it coming when Beck prototypes himself.
I was like oh my God the consequences the consequences are so dire right now this is so fucked.
They're fucked.
And they were.
And it was great.
I freaked out.
Because you know.
Because you know what it means.
You know what Beck is and what he can do.
It's like oh no.
It's all the stuff you've seen with John fighting like basic imps and then Rose and Dave and then they become like there's extra there's like they mutate and they're even more tough and John's like.
They're tough but they're still like whatever like oh they got tentacles now.
The president the president has said that they will become more powerful things are put in and then like a literal God jumps in there.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think the early flashes like WV rise up and stuff those are like impactful.
I think mostly not mostly but in part because that sort of showing of things happening has not like.
You've seen like bits of music and bits of animation but you haven't seen like a big thing putting them all together to show so much plot happening all at once.
And so much of the early part of the comic is just like reading.
You know you're just sort of going at your own pace like you click on the next page when you're done reading.
It's all very much within your control and then these flashes are like they're so quick.
I remember feeling like I couldn't take all of it in the first time watching like oh my God that happening and what does this mean.
It's so fast.
The plot is so the plot is so slow and plotting and it's like so meticulous and like you know page by page only for and then in the flashes when like it all comes together and in a in a in a second it's like.
Oh well that shit you set up boom pay off boom pay off.
Yeah.
All in this bait you spent like hours reading here and then and then it all pays off in like 30 fucking seconds.
Oh God.
I love Homestuck man.
I just so good.
I don't know.
I wonder.
I don't think it's cold like Internet culture has fallen out of love with it.
It's a little bit of a scapegoat now.
People like make fun of it now.
Nobody takes it seriously anymore but yeah I think so.
I think when people say Homestuck.
Don't really know about it anymore.
When people say Homestuck you know it's like oh that thing before Undertale like oh that thing that everyone used to be really weird about with all the weird fans and like the troll makeup and it was like cringy.
I feel like to call yourself a Homestuck fan now has a little bit of the stigma of being like a Sonic fan like it's for weirdos and it's a weird thing and it's funny.
I suppose but I mean I see people say that and I just like I scoff at their existence because they're coming from a place of they're coming usually from a place of complete ignorance.
Like isn't that like really long?
Why would I read it?
Why should I ever take that sort of person seriously?
It's the same people are like I don't want to read one piece.
I mean I heard it's the greatest thing ever but it's so many chapters.
I don't want to do it.
But people don't talk about yeah they say that about one piece but they don't say I heard it's the greatest thing ever but I don't want to read it about Homestuck.
They say oh I heard it's dumb or only weirdos like it or it's embarrassing.
I guess I don't hear that much of that.
I hear people because I'm in communities I'm in people know about Homestuck and the people who don't hear about it and they're like you know I should read that but I got so much so long.
And you know what I don't really like reading in fact and I'm stupid.
Like that's sort of I don't think there's like a statement.
Don't read the pastor sprites.
Don't read the pastor logs.
Just click through.
Just look at the pictures.
Yeah yeah yeah just look at the pictures.
Just get the brisker and then set it as your desktop background.
So that's what you do.
That's how you do it.
The optimal reading experience.
Did I tell you that I went through Homestuck for no real reason?
But I got every single instance of brisker appearing visually and I even in the flashes I like I paused it and I took screenshots and I got like every instance of brisker and I just put it in a folder.
I don't even look at it.
I just think it's funny that I did that.
That's that's fucked up because I've done I've done a similar thing but for a porn star for my favorite porn star.
Oh no.
That's the only person I've done something like that for.
Which means like downloading their videos.
I mean like going I mean like going through my favorite videos and like screen capping images and like saving the images out of the videos and putting them in folders.
Maybe we could combine our powers and like it's nice those drawings.
I could trace those screenshots and put risk in them as well instead.
No thank you.
That's okay.
You don't have to do that.
Why screen grabs is this like a thing you did a long time ago?
I don't know.
It's easier to look at a picture than it is to like scrub through a video.
Yeah I guess.
Yeah.
I never thought to do that.
Well I mean I'm not saying I'm not saying I'm not saying it's a normal thing to do.
Oh God knows I want to be the most normal of all.
Yeah.
And just that's that's when you say you did that with Friska.
I'm like I did that but it was a little different.
That's that's my.
What's the word?
My touchstone.
That's my point of reference for that kind of degenerate behavior.
It wasn't degenerate.
It wasn't even a sex thing.
Yeah anything homestuck if you say so.
If you say so.
Anything homestuck is degenerate.
No no no.
I do have a porn folder of all the Friska porn that exists.
That is a thing.
Of course.
But the homestuck.
And it's the same folder and it's the same folder.
No they're completely separate because one of them is drawn by Hasee and the other is.
Well one of them is canon.
The other one is just like if I see a pornography but it has the Friska horns.
Even if I don't like it I put it in there.
I don't know why because I look back at them I'm like gross.
Well it's.
Do you do it for is it for like I don't know like references like in case you need to refer to a Friska moment.
You have like a collection of the images on hand that you can easily access.
I think it literally was like wouldn't it be funny if I did that and then I could say I did that.
Like haha I'm insane.
I like Friska this much than I did this.
No.
Really?
It was.
You were thinking like haha it would be so funny if I did this because people sure would think it was weird and quirky.
True.
Unironically true.
Because I already had the Friska porn folder.
That was the degenerate.
You did it.
You did it to.
Simply having every Canon.
You did it to own the lips.
Having every Canon like instance of Friska visually was like not as insane as the porn thing I think.
Maybe.
No I think mine there's a tangible benefit to mine.
No I mean mine.
Like I already had the porn Friska folder.
Oh.
It's safe for work like the Canon Friska folder was just sort of like the same thing again but at this time I wouldn't go to whack off about it.
You know I would just look at it.
I would just have it.
It would just be collection I put on my wall or on my shelf.
Sure.
Can you hear me by the way?
I can.
Sorry Discord was acting weird for a second.
Okay.
I mean okay.
Well sure.
I'll just I'll just let you have that.
You know what?
You can.
This is America.
It's a free.
It's a free country.
Look I don't care about what people think about my folder.
Yeah.
Well good.
Because you wouldn't like it.
It's labeled W.
If you knew what I think.
Well what do you think?
It's labeled.
No no no it's fine.
It's labeled W because you took that W just like me.
Yeah.
You love the W.
Wait why is it called W?
No it isn't.
It was a joke based on you having talked about W.
Oh I didn't get it.
I'm sorry.
Ugh.
And then I brought up the Rose Lalonde picture and now we're talking about Homestuck and
we have been talking about Homestuck and then I talked about the Frisco folder.
And then and and and it just goes around in circles.
It's a never ending story.
Okay.
I think we've covered that.
Are you?
Now that we've thoroughly embarrassed ourselves.
Absolutely.
Let's move on to something even more embarrassing.
Talk about being a soyboy cuck who got the fucking Bill Gates microchip implanted in
him.
Oh.
I'm chipped.
I'm bugged.
You're vexed.
I'm vexed.
Are you?
You're not vexed.
They don't they're like not doing them yet.
I mean I think I could get them if I followed up on it.
Like if I say hey can I have my thing and they're like sure but they're doing it.
They're like at level 30.
They're doing 30 year olds.
So it's not so long until I'm I'm going to get a text from the government saying it is
time for your thing.
Time for your ball flattening.
Oh no.
The the yeah I got my second shot a couple days ago and it's like literally no symptoms.
Everyone said like oh it makes you kind of sick for a little bit.
It makes you feel like flu symptoms.
Not me.
I didn't feel a thing except it hurt a little bit for like that day because I got like a
little shot and it kind of was sore.
Pretty cool.
I'm just I'm just different.
Yeah I've always wondered like what about it.
I guess in the same way that the virus affects people differently.
The vaccine will affect people differently.
But I don't know how I don't know how like the antibodies like just get get a clue quicker
than the other ones.
It is it's really it's pretty complicated but I like I was I was getting all like antsy
about like oh no are they gonna am I gonna fucking die from the vaccine.
Is it all just a fucking is it all just an op.
So you know I was looking up info about how because I heard I heard people calling it
like gene therapy like it's like something that fucks with your DNA.
And so that made me nervous.
I was like let me let me find out the truth about that turns out no it's it's not that
they're talking about denim jeans.
It makes you it's like like they put they put RNA in your body and your your fucking
cells read the RNA and it's it literally the RNA they put in is instructions you've
you've seen the pictures of the coronavirus and it's like the ball with all the spikes
coming out of it.
Yes it's when they say when they say spike proteins what they mean is those spikes on
the outside of the fucking ball.
It's literally RNA that contains the instructions to make those spikes and they
fucking attach themselves to your cells and your other cells learn to kill them
basically.
So what it is that makes you sick is that it's that you yeah it's that your body is
attacking the cells that have these spike proteins on them and it gives you the same
symptoms you get when you're fighting off any like illness like when you get the flu
for instance because that's your body it's your immune system killing your cells in
response to getting all into overdrive heating up and taking up water and it's like
we've got to put resources into water development we've got to make little nukes.
But it's but it's your it's they do inject RNA they do inject genetic material into you
but it does not interact with like your DNA and in fact like a virus is made of
genetic material a virus is made of RNA so you would have the RNA in your body if you
got the virus anyway like those spike proteins go into your body because they're part of
the fucking virus so you like you would get it's really annoying because I saw people
calling it gene therapy and saying it fucks the genes and then I found out like no it's
just it's a part of the virus that is made of RNA same as any virus you would get the
same shit in your body in your cells if you just got the virus versus if you get the
vaccine it is and it's like no it's it's totally insane it's a complete like it's just a complete
misunderstanding of what it of what a virus is a virus is literally made of genetic material
so don't fucking it was it was it was it was it was low it was low-fi Republican and it
was razor fist that I saw saying a bunch of shit about how the vaccine fucks with your
DNA I know and I hate them I fucking hate them I fucking hate razor fist so much I
hate I hate low-fi Republican too but in a much less personal way okay enough yeah
about them anyway what were you saying I was just saying like the way I've always thought
about it because I feel like I was told this when I was really young or it's just like
the vaccine is like a tiny version of the virus that you will be protected from it's
like a practice round you get like a baby version and people just figure out how to kill
the baby and but they go around saying the vaccine contains some coronavirus people will be
even less you know reticent to take it because they're stupid I was I was told as a kid that
it a vaccine contains like some dead version of the virus which is like maybe it's kind of
true yeah this one because I don't think it can take over your body the thing like is
you get sick afterwards but it's not because like whatever was put into you is like multiplying
and turning into a virus that you will have it is just that your body is fighting it that
it's all of the stuff that happens whenever you get sick in any way you know it's I don't
know I I almost feel like it's passe to be complaining about like anti-vax shit but I
don't know I've just been seeing a lot this week and it makes me really mad and people
say oh god oh no I had a point oh no or it disappeared people are saying anti-vax stuff
gene gene therapy oh no oh yeah people say 2% mortality rate oh it's only 2% mortality
rate it's you're probably not gonna die if you get it so why even fucking get the vaccine
and like okay first of all imagine let's just take that on its face imagine it's or even
okay cuz that's like only for like older people so if you're younger than that it's let's say
it's like 0.1% okay imagine how much of a beating right a physical beating a thrashing with
with a fucking hard like crowbar you would need to be inflicted upon you to die right
and then imagine instead that someone inflicts you know 0.1% of that on you are you okay no
you're not okay it hurts really bad and it probably fucks you up second yeah like the
death rate is pretty low especially if you're like the death rate is low especially if you're
young especially if you don't have any like underlying pathologies that's true but like
that doesn't mean that you're just fine that doesn't mean that you get it and then afterwards
you're fine and like it's the status like I think H bomber guy mentioned in the VAX video
he just put out that like one third of people like a third of people have chronic like long
term side effects like chronic long lasting like respiratory distress or you know loss of
their sense of fucking taste or whatever and like this is the fallacy right it's like oh
the death rates low so I'll probably survive yeah but like you're not just okay it's not
the it's not like you either die or you're perfectly fine nothing happens to you it's
some maybe you die or more likely it makes you really sick and it possibly fucks you
up for a long time that happens all the time it's really common like yeah the consequences
of it are not simply limited to the death toll even though the death toll is really bad
right like 2% death toll is actually really a lot of people when we're talking about like
the entire population of the United States and Europe and other places oh my god I'm upset
yeah it is it is always a bit annoying to see like the the you know vaccines are on the
table they hurt a little bit potentially and then your immune you know pretty pretty much
unable to catch the virus at least in the current strains so it's like there's like so little
downside to taking a vaccine much in the same way there's so little downside to wear a mask
but people don't want to take even that because they just can't imagine that they would be
imperiled because they just don't they just think that they're gonna live and everyone else dies
because that's always what happens that's what's happened every day of their life is that they
continue to be alive and other people so it can't be them it could never be them it's
the it's like every every living person is subject to survivorship bias because nothing
has killed them yet right yeah um yeah and I hate that I see that all the time I see that
all the time like you always assume that it's not gonna get you because nothing has got you yet
because you're still alive but guess what one day something's gonna get you like it or not
um the um uh what really makes me upset what really bugs me about it is that it got to me
like the fact that it made me nervous about getting it I was infected they infected me with the
with the virus of thought right with the fear mongering it worked it fucking made me like oh
everyone else is afraid of it I should be should I be afraid oh that makes me nervous it worked
I'm not immune to propaganda and the fact that it's so common I was seeing all over the place
I'm like is there is there something to this is there something to all this fucking fear mongering
there must be or else why would so many people be repeating it it is yeah it's annoying because
like you go around life and most people don't really know things they just have heard true
and believe certain bits if you go and look at like data like scientific studies about
it really anything you can get a much clearer understanding of what the actual knowledge is
sometimes you learn that it's inconclusive and that any assertions made would be hasty
and then you realize that the people who like you know why would they make this assertion
other than other than other potential assertions oh it's their bias oh okay I I get a sense of why
the discourse is the way it is and you know it just depends on a lot of factors that have
nothing to do with the real you know real like actual quantifiable information so I don't know
right does yeah I don't know I don't particularly I feel pretty confident in vaccines I have
no reason to like suddenly doubt them so whenever I heard something was like fucked up I always
think of that as like a dumb American thing because dumb Americans are known for being
dumb and I hear about dumb things did you watch the H bomber guy a vaccine video do you watch H
bomber guy I think I've seen a few of his videos they're okay I I didn't watch the vaccine I he's
not my I'm not like a huge H bomber guy fan or anything I think he's all right he doesn't put
out videos that often so what he put out the vaccine one and I watched it and I didn't know that
like a lot of you say it's dumb American thing but a lot of like the modern anti-vax movement
started in the UK because there was like there was literally one guy who had a fucking I don't
remember his name I recommend that video but there was one guy who had a fucking he basically
like published a fraudulent paper that said that tried to his he falsified data is that published
a fraudulent paper that tried to establish a link between not even vaccines in general just one
specific vaccine and autism and the reason he did it spoilers is because he then wanted to pedal
an alternative vaccine that he claimed wouldn't cause autism the whole point was just he he wasn't
even anti-vax his whole point was just don't buy that vaccine by my vaccine instead and then to do
that he created this fucking huge anti-vax like cultural culture of fear that has persisted to this
day so money motivated this right capitalism all over again everything is it's always capitalism
true true this is particularly particularly insidious though well yeah but fuck I mean I say
dumb Americans I did grow up like that's like the stereotype like Americans they eat McDonald's
and I have that but there is there is like a there is like a sense of like superiority in
Britain that makes people think that they can't be wrong the more I learn about the more I realize
other places so yeah the more I learn about Britain the more I realize that you guys are
kind of prone to most of the same failings as we are just like in not in like it's a little bit
different flavor but of like the same fucking psychosis I don't remember where I heard this
I feel like it was a documentary just on TV I was watching but it was about people like British people
saying about like like like a race relations like oh well British people are racist and of course there
is racism in England and Britain you know that it's like there's a lot of it there's a lot of it in football
like explicit racism sure yeah I know what you're talking about and there's all that sort of stuff
and people normal people just assume that it isn't the case because well we're British we're good
and that's sort of like a weird like sense of righteousness like yes Britain we're so great we
won World War II you know we did all of these things we had Winston Churchill no we won World War II
with our guns it's because I think that we could look at America and say ha look at them being dumb
in certain ways we are not like that at all and just like ignore the problems we have and it's really embarrassing
going now and seeing that we have fucking so much turf power so much turf power is everything
it's I don't want to be the I don't want to be the America defender but I do kind of think that like America
being how it is is a little bit of maybe a little bit of a scapegoat that like people don't notice when Britain
is bad because America is usually worse in most ways usually a lot of time a little bit of a shield hashtag
not your shields I wouldn't say that there's anything necessarily good about like trans acceptance in the US
but I feel like it would be better than the UK I would somebody somebody clip that somebody clip somebody clip
Gibbs saying there's nothing good about trans acceptance say put it on me I mean you can't clip a video you'd have to
download the whole thing we're on twitch put this on twitch.tv and then clip it like the state okay anyway it's it's yeah yeah
I feel like it's I don't know I would have to actually look into it I feel like there is a bit of hysteria as well it
varies from state to state like a lot of you know a lot of the red states are I see a lot of like headlines that are like
you know like I don't know Alabama or Tennessee is like passing a resolution to like you know force businesses to put up
fucking warning notices that like they let trans people use their bathroom of choice or whatever it's correct me
correct me if I'm wrong but like I don't I don't isn't that I don't understand that like what's the has a has a
business not is a business not by default just like allowed to let any whoever they want use whatever bathrooms they want is
that not like a yeah that is everyone is just allowed to decide for themselves I think I didn't look into this too much I did see
it on Twitter a bit I think what it is and the reason is bad is that it requires I mean I know why it's bad it requires people to
put in their establishment we accept trans people so that cis people you know bigots can look at that and avoid them oh oh I
don't want trans I don't want to be in the same place as a trans person let's get out of here you know scamper away like freaks and
and that is sort of but like I don't know I couldn't so fucked that's so fucked yeah even like imagine if like imagine
if they said even if it wasn't trans people even if it was just like you had to put up a notice that's like I don't
I don't know we fucking let anything we fucking let any kind of warning we let X kind of person use our bathrooms it really
really just like because they can't make it so that you're allowed to discriminate against people based on their gender identity like
they can't make a law about that so this is the next best thing for it for like being bigoted and allowing that to happen is
so they're literally saying like people to avoid them this is this is literally like oh my god this is this is the fucking free speech
people they must love it because this is literally saying businesses you were allowed to just let whoever use your bathrooms you want but
we would like to pass a law that will punish you you must you must now either not let anyone we don't think you should be letting
use your bathrooms or you have to put up these notices letting people know what freaks you are or something I just a little fucked
that's such a weird fucking thing all I want to do is diarrhea with all the girls I just want to go in diarrhea with all the girls
that just is what I want to do people bad about diarrhea where I would like to do it people talk about the bathroom thing like it's
some kind I don't think there's any like law that says that like public places have to have like a bathroom that only you know biological
men can use and a bathroom the only biological women like I don't think that's a law that's just sort of a convention that that places have
started doing maybe some places it's a lot I don't know but it's not it's it's not some kind of like incontrovertible fact of the universe
it's just a thing people do it's a thing businesses do because I know people I mean lots of lots of businesses lots of stores just
have like one unisex bathroom like that's pretty normal I do the do those people have to put a notice off that says trans people are allowed to use
their one bathroom I don't know it's just such a weird you know that the continued to be like a part of the discussion around trans people
it's just the answer then excuse to say I think they should be ostracized they don't really care about where they're shitting the answer
then is that you can just say you can just call both your you have two bathrooms you can just say like oh yeah they're unisex they're both unisex
bathroom one has a picture of a man and the other has a picture of a woman on it but that's just a dog whistle that's just that's just an accident I didn't
I didn't mean to put those up there they're both they're both unisex bathrooms it's fine it's no notice no you're not allowed in unless you're literally wearing a dress or
no big yellow triangle with an exclamation point in it on my good establishment thank you very much government out of out of my house please
it's all stupid it's very stupid it's insulting it's an insult when you think about it it's just spite it's just spite and I don't know cruelty
just to be just to be cruel just to say fuck it's literally literally just owning the libs it's literally just legislation passed to own the libs and make people feel bad that you don't like
and it's great and I I love it I love it's exhausting yeah hideous hideous miscarriage of justice Lamal
so cool the other day what else yeah the other day I was trying to do some drawing and I and I got a whole one panel done and then yeah
the end of the day happened I was like oh were you were you on panel were you streaming no I was gonna I'm I'm thinking of streaming soon next month
well I guess this month when this episode comes out on on Twitch I guess that's what I was doing before I want to go over the the Clarissa comic I want to add shading because I was rushing I didn't add any shading to any of the pages
I wanted to so I'm gonna do that and then I'm gonna like draw the rest of the comic so that it's finished and that the stream is like a good way to force myself to get some of that done
but there was this other comic that I was originally going to do for the Cato anthology that I couldn't because of illness didn't have the energy to get done in time and I've been wanting to finish that and it's going real slow
I look at the sketches and I'm like I don't fucking know how to turn this into a thing so I managed to do one panel line art and that was it and then I played video games the rest of the day
I had
I'm I'm worse because a couple days ago like two or three I think like two ish days ago I opened up manga studio because I had to make
a sprite I needed to make a new not not just a set of sprites for the for the game and it was very daunting and I was getting frustrated with it because it wasn't coming out right and I finally was like I don't I'm getting mad I don't want to work on this anymore
so when I played some Noida and I haven't worked on it since and it's been like two days I just played Noida for like two days straight I'm sorry I'm sorry that's true
I mean it that's how the reason I got so stuck was because the sketch I had was too vague I was like I was looking at it and I'm like but I'm on line art mode in line art mode I don't want to think I just want to draw and then I could see the sketch
I'm like where do I put the torso here I don't even know oh god it's so messy I'd have to redo the sketch and as soon as I realized I would have to redo the sketch I stopped I was like okay I'll I'll just you know I'll just go diarrhea in the women's restroom that's all I want to do right now
that's that's your that's your solution to everything give you can't solve all your problems and diarrhea in the women's restroom
well where I was supposed to diarrhea
I don't know fucking the just do it in my unisex bathroom that has a picture of
just do it on the floor
personal address on it
that should that should be the way to protest all of this bathroom stuff
not none sits is only bathrooms just shit on the floor yeah why not why not
shit on the door shit on the door
shit on the shit on the go into go to Congress and shit on shit in shit in Congress's bathrooms like shit all over their sink when they when they pass laws we don't like I can down it
just go to the go to the roof and like shit on them from the roof through the windows
the discourse becomes you know I I don't have any problem with trans people a lot of my I have empathy for them a lot of my friends I have a lot of many trans friends however I just can't get behind that they just keep shitting on me from the roof tops
everywhere you go
you know
America's like a flock of birds
this this is Joe Biden's America
you have BLM burning our cities down and then the ones that are still standing you have trans people sitting on people from on top of the buildings that are still standing
it's epidemic across just in time for covid to die down we have a new epidemic of trans people's diary
what do they think they're doing it's unsanitary
yes
this is this is what you've reduced me to
I'm so glad I voted for Biden to make this happen
I gotta say though that two days of playing Noida was very very fruitful
I accomplished many goals I accomplished new things that I've never done before I had the ultimate God run I've started abusing abusing save states
because I had the perfect run I became an ultimate God and I'm like this is it this is the run this is the run where I do it all
I collect I gathered all the four essences and I brought them to the moon I cracked the moon and then I went down to hell and I took them to the hell moon and I cracked the hell moon
and I did it I did both I did both moon things I know I know pretty cool pretty cool
I did I did a cool game thing to do
now I never have to do those again tell me about your cool gamer thing if you dare
well I have been if you think it can compare to cracking the moon
oh it can it can so you know I've been I've been into Picross and stuff
on on Picross this website Picrolyo.com slash Picross I remember exactly
cool website I think I've mentioned it for they have the maximum size of a random Picross board with randomized spaces is 30 times 30
and recently I finally after like hundreds of failures I've completed one without any mistakes
30 times 30 Picross board
if you if you look at this image pretty good sense of way I'm not looking at the image of how much how daunting that could be
one slip up one incorrect click and it's completely over so everything had to be calculated
and it was it was so gratifying
yeah that's a lot of squares that's that's a lot of squares how long did that take
I mean this it doesn't take that long maybe an hour
sometimes if I get stuck it can take a couple days on and off but most of the time
it's just the the stamina required and like the the brain power and then the the paying attention to exactly where you're clicking
if you make one mistake if I like think I'm clicking on one column and it's actually the column next to it that I should be clicking on
and I make a mistake then it's over I can continue but I won't get the rainbow at the end I won't get the perfect ending
because all the blocks go rainbow colors and flash rainbow if you don't make any mistakes and get a hundred percent of the time
and yeah that I failed because of like slip ups and like not paying attention enough or like losing my patience
fucking something up or there have been so many of these where I get so close to the end and then there's a 50 50
it could be one it could be another there's no way to know there's no information that I could use to figure it out
it could just be this one or another one and I get it wrong and that's happened like six or seven times
but this time this particular map was was no guesses it was the perfect board and I completed it completely
and I didn't have to guess and it was so and I never have to play pick us again
you finally unfortunately unfortunately I do have to play Noida some more because I cracked the moons
but I have not I have not made the sun which I gotta make the fucking sun I guess
the best way to make the sun is to get the wife and in pregnant
you gotta you gotta you gotta like you gotta I gotta go beat all these like bosses that didn't used to be
and when I started playing they weren't in the game but they've been added so I gotta go fight all these new bosses
get some new items they drop do some shit to them and then throw some other like rare items in them to make them do things
and then it makes a son and then I gotta take the sun from one place to another place and it's very dangerous
because it turns everything the lava and then fucking if you it kills you it deals you insane damage
if you go inside of the sun it will like atomize you and turn you into gold you know it's it's pretty fucked up
you have to throw the poop stone in it to turn it into a black hole if you if you're real spicy
which I I want to do that it's very it's pretty fucking tedious though honestly all the endgame Noida stuff
there's a lot of like it's a lot of running around getting shit you got to do and I I got so strong
but it's all pretty trivial like I'm I have like I can like swim in lava now I can swim in acid I'm like
I'm all immune to almost I can just run through curse rock which is like the deadliest thing in the game
nothing gonna hurt me anymore so it's just a matter of like I mean yeah that's just what happens
like when you when you when you play long enough and you like go to enough like parallel worlds and get enough power-ups
you can just make yourself like you're not completely invincible you can never be completely immune to like polymorph
but other than that it's like I'm pretty set I'm pretty much pretty much just a matter of go to the different places
and collect all the shit you need to get bring them back do the thing kind of a lot of busy work honestly it's honestly not that fun
it's more fun just because of this it's more fun just because like it sounds cool to talk about
but like the actual the actual doing of it is like okay I gotta go to these four places that are on four different parts of the map
and get the item and then I bring them up to this place and always did I miss it okay I gotta kind of oh it's more left than there
I'm gonna try and find it again and get my bearings okay I found it okay I got it all right now I gotta go down to hell
and do the same thing in a different place okay I did it and just like takes a few hours
yeah I'm trying to think there's a few there's a few games that have that sort of experience where you level out the challenge
you're too powerful to die you can die if you feel like it but your skill level as a player is just you only need to put in the
the barest amount of effort in order to beat anything and so yeah you're really just watching an avatar run around
and occasionally doing something it's like I don't the challenge is gone there's no reason for me to do this it feels like
like getting like a super ultimate weapon at the very very end of the game when you've already beaten it and it's like well what is the
it doesn't help you because you didn't need it anymore because I didn't need that to get to this point that was the challenge
now that I have the ultimate weapon I don't need it just throw it away yeah yeah
hang on I gotta pee oh my god I just um I put so much I put so much time in Innoida that I feel like yeah the final the final
quests are they're very complicated and they're very like esoteric actually doing them is like once
you're once you're basically god level it's not that hard it's not really a challenge it's basically just like looking up how to do it
and then just do it I I think I mean if you were doing it with no spoilers if you were like figuring out all the lore yourself
that would be the real challenge I I feel maybe a little bad that I looked up how to do it because like there are clues in the
game that you can find that hint at what you're supposed to do and I can only imagine that if I had done it like that I would be
like whoa I would just be blown away if I ever fucking but I don't think I would I don't think I would have done it
is it so esoteric you oh yeah I'm just saying I'm saying that I think the real challenge of the Noida endgame is like piecing together the clues
that it gives you to figure out how to do things like make the sun but I didn't do that and I don't think I would have done it
I just looked I just looked it up yeah I just looked it up I don't think I would have done it I don't think I would have had the patients to
legitimately like go through run after run like trying different like oh it says that like the sun can be like corrupted with an intoxicating influence
like does that mean I have to put whiskey into it oh no no I have to I have to use the I have to use the essence of spirits at the
nullifying altar to get the poop stone I have to and now I can't just throw it into the sun I have to enter the sun and it will eat it from me and that's how you make the black hole
like I just wouldn't do it like would experimenting trial and error would that be extremely costly like you'd have to throw items together and then they'd be useless afterwards
and you'd have to do that a bunch of times to figure out what they actually mean because that's yeah like it's like it's really hard to get like the poop stone for instance to if you like were to just throw it into the sun
thinking that that's what you need to do and the sun just destroys it then you're like okay well that was the only one I was going to get I need to I need to like do a whole I need to go gather up all the orbs bring all the orbs back to the altar
enter like the next level new game plus and then go get the essence of spirits again go do the do the whole Sunseed quest again and then get the poop stone again throw that in and see if it works and you have to do something
different with it this time yeah stuff like that I just wouldn't do it yeah I can't imagine anyone doing something it's it feels like I mean a lot of the a lot of the lore in the game is like it's like it feels sort of like Fez and that like it's not designed to be
solved by one person it's designed to be like a sort of community mystery to solve you know I hate that I don't know why but I just hate like things that are that rely on the existence of a large player based of a large community to form that
like you're banking on that being the case but like I'd rather it just be like a puzzle that you can solve with your own wit it just makes so much more satisfying to be to be the one who can figure it out and then say to your friends I know how to do it
the Sunseed quest I feel like some of the things are explicit enough that you could maybe figure it out but some of the other things like the like the lore snippets that are like hidden in like the tablet alters that you need to bring like certain fluids to and fill the alters with to make like this secret text appear
and then you got to translate it from fucking finish and do like a rune cipher on it that stuff is like I don't think one person is meant to solve it and I I think that's cool in theory but I don't want to engage with it on that level I don't really
like feel like being some guy on a forum who's like okay this guy posted screenshots of the runes I ciphered them my friend I showed it to my friend who speaks finish and he told me that it means this so this is the next snippet and I'll add it to like the next one and then tomorrow I'll go and do another one or whatever
I don't want to play the game that way it's for other people I just want to be a little man who shoots guns that's that's for me yeah I feel like if you want to puzzle then you should play a puzzle game where like that is an expected thing so you go into it
honing your skills at puzzle solving so that when you come up to like the difficult ones you're you're into it you don't need to look up the results like the what you need to do in like a point and click game if you end up looking up what you need to do you don't like the game it sucks and you don't want to play it
I don't I don't think I agree I I do think it's cool that it's a game that you can just play on a surface level of I'm a little man's I run around I shoot guns I kill monsters I beat the boss I win but then on top of it there's another layer of like
oh did you know that if you go into the fucking underground jungle and go west to the lucky layer and at the bottom there's an altar and if you fill the altar with you know curse liquid then it shows secret text and it forms like 136 of like the sacred text of like the gods or whatever that explains like where the world how the world was
formed I think that's really cool I just don't feel like doing it I guess I guess yeah I guess it's it's not bad that it's not explained I think it's just the the feeling that it gives you that some things you can figure out and then there's other things that you could try to figure
out but it would just take a really really long tedious time so they may they may as well have not given you a hint for this the you know the poopstone something if that was the only way like the only way to figure it out is to do extremely lengthy tedious bullshit or you
could just go to Wikipedia yeah it does make me feel bad it does kind of negatively impact my experience of the game because it makes me feel bad that I'm not going to do all that stuff I'm that I'm not like you know solving
the Sunseed quest on my own but that's a me problem the the the I tried I don't know one time I tried to do a full run where I found everything and it was so hard it was like I spent so long I was I was God mode I had everything I needed I could go anywhere do
anything and I I didn't find like half of the fucking stuff like there's stuff I spent like so long just going everywhere I could think of just going random places just searching and searching and searching for stuff and I didn't find all the stuff I
was looking for and I didn't even find like a bunch of the stuff that I know is in the game like a bunch of the secret bosses that I've never even seen seen before but they're there and I guess I'm just not a fucking hardcore enough gamer I don't
I don't know the game fucking beat me there were like whole biomes I don't even know where they're the whole the power I didn't find the power plant for ever I don't know it's embarrassing I feel a little embarrassed just saying I don't think like hardcore gamer to such a degree even really could exist like imagine a single person never
but it but it killed it out everything but it kills me because in hindsight I know that I could have found it if I had like if I had ever decided to you know go
further below the sand caves oh and then under the sand caves there's the there's the overgrown caverns okay well then if what if I go even further then I find the power plant like I could have done that I just never did and I think maybe the
honestly I think maybe the reason that I didn't do that is because I know that there is a wiki that I can just look shit up on maybe if there was no wiki I would have just played the game the right way and just gone exploring like that and found shit and then I would still be in the process
in the process of being like oh wow there's a there's a secret fifth essence at the bottom of the lake like oh my god like wow
but there is a wiki and there's what's the point what's the point of wondering what could have been I don't know so I don't know I'm a little annoyed now I'm a little annoyed I feel like I've been robbed of that but also
I the thing is it's because it's my fault and there's no one to be mad at but myself well it's because the game has that first level of you could just play the game as a shooty guy shooting things and shooty shooty McShooter like hell yeah
chainsaw chainsaw yeah yeah you can do that and because of that the game fundamentally is not about like the draw of the game is not fundamentally exploration in that way you can explore but it's more fun to just go pew pew with the with the one right like that's why you're into the game
that's for so many yeah that it would be more interesting to do the exploration and the shooting stuff is like less interesting I think the fact is some people find like any any game that has like multiple facets of it
there's only certain people who would who would bother to do all of this extreme experimenting to find the super secrets and and and like the play base may not all be into that sort of gameplay because it's not the main point of the game that's why I was talking about with like point and click adventures nobody plays a point and click adventure
and and look stuff up if they can help it only when they're terrible only if they're like terribly terribly stuck or if they just don't like that sort of game and they've found themselves playing it.
It's it's a little I don't know I feel about it it's a little weird because you have to be you have to be a certain level baseline proficient at running and jumping and being a little shooty man.
In order to be able to do the like advanced like oh I found the cauldron room under the he see he see base.
Oh I found the I found the 34 the 34th orb in the like the secret like one in 10 million great chest or whatever.
You have to be able to like at the very least you know beat the game and and get all the power ups and stuff that you need.
So it's not it's not like you can just do one or the other you have to be good at the one before you have the opportunity to do the other.
I think it's just cool.
It's cool but it's also like damn it sure must be if like you're just someone who wants to explore the lore and the world but also it's like kind of cool that like you kind of have to be good at shooting and killing because like I don't know it's sort of like like the real world
like you don't just get to do shit you have to earn it.
Even if it's not fair that you have to do that.
I lost my train of thought because you made me wait.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
What was it?
Fucking did different types of people you do shooting you do exploration later it's like a skill.
People who get to such a proficient level by playing the game like on the baseline is like the normal gameplay loop.
If you like that and it's fun you'll keep playing you'll get your game like a lot of experience by playing the game over and over again.
Once you get so bored of things you've seen you start to get curious and then you might go out and try something different try something that you know.
That's how you get to a point where you can do all of the exploration and find all of these secrets while being proficient because you had to be proficient together in the first place.
Those sorts of people really really love the core gameplay and I guess it's just a matter of like you don't know if a game is going to be worth exploring that much.
And so you would only play it that much in order to find those things if you just love the game and would play it over and over again for hundreds of thousands of hours anyway.
I had a very frustrating experience I was I had two stacks of the glass cannon perk which basically makes your it quintuples your damage and it also like increases the radius of all explosions that you make including even ones just like from a chainsaw so basically just everything I do just explodes fucking everywhere right.
And I needed to go to a certain place and put stuff into these three like bowls basically to activate an altar that would remove all my perks because I wanted to remove some of them and just keep a few.
So, and I know that this place requires me to fill one with blood, one with whiskey and one with silver, and I knew how to get silver.
I had I had the means to create it, but I didn't have any means to transport it because the only way to transport silver is in a bag and bags are I mean I'd seen them around but I'm pretty sure I had destroyed all bags by just blasting black holes everywhere and like
tearing holes through the landscape to travel. So I had to go like I had to go through like half a dozen different maybe I had to go through like three or four whole different like biomes going down through places where I thought that I might find bags and then I'm like nope none here and then I had to go to the next
parallel world over and go through the same area like looking for bags looking for bags. Oh, no, none here none here and I, I finally found a bag, but it was underwater, and I had to.
And I had this is one of the perks one of the reasons I wanted to do this thing was I had a perk that froze liquids anytime I came near them.
And so I couldn't get the bag without freezing the water. And then if I tried to break the ice that formed when I went in to get the bag, it would explode and it would destroy the bag because I had I was double glass cannon I was exploding with power.
So I had to like very carefully go under the water that it was in and like really carefully try and make explosions to like just break a little hole in the in the ground under the water to let the water drain out of it so that I could get on top of the bag and grab it without freezing the water it was in.
And I failed several times. And every time I failed and destroyed the bag, I would have to go the next parallel world over go back to the same spot that I found the bag in find it again and try again to like break the ground in just such a way without destroying the bag.
Finding this bag to hold silver in was a big fucking shit show.
It was kind of funny thing.
Is it like silver?
Yeah.
No silver like silver like powder, basically.
Like, yeah, there's I mean, you could leave you get a torn off a little bit of your like cloak and made a bag out of that and in real life.
Yeah, in real life, it should not have been hard to find bags and I had found bags before I just I don't.
I hadn't needed any bags so I hadn't kept them and they had all just been discarded and and destroyed.
Yeah, pretty pretty dumb.
There are there are there are ways to make silver so like getting there's a bunch of different ways you there are other metals you can find that you can mix with liquids that transform them into silver.
And the way that I did it was I had a spell called chaotic transmutation that will apply a sort of random like turn other liquids into something effect to a projectile.
So I could just fire that into like a big pool of water and eventually it would fire a projectile that would turn a big chunk of liquid into silver and I would just collect the silver.
What I ended up doing was I use that and I fired a crystal that was that would turn stuff into silver.
And then I poured blood I fired that down a hole and then I poured blood down the hole.
So the blood would flow over this crystal and like kind of tumble down the hole on the other side of the crystal having been transformed into powdered silver.
Oh my God.
I love Noida so much.
Alchemy.
I'm so smart.
I'm so intelligent because I play this video game that's kind of hard.
Cool.
My throat hurts.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I've monopolized feel like we've monopolized this podcast with Noida talk.
Well, I got having having having done the moon quest.
I think I'm going to take a break from it for a while.
Back to the fucking.
The insane says he's going to take a break.
I wonder what that means.
Shut up.
Yeah.
What were you saying?
Oh, well, I wanted to talk a little bit about the road of ghosts.
Oh, yes.
The Keto guys.
Keto.
The Keto anthology.
Oh, no.
Fuck yeah.
How embarrassing for them.
To be even slightly similar to Keto.
The Keto anthology guys.
They were saying last episode about Lord Ghost Kickstarter.
I got my, you know, I was thinking about it.
I looked into printing costs and stuff.
And, you know, could be done.
I could do it.
By the time this podcast comes up, it may have been launched.
I don't know because I'm scared.
I'm scared of fucking it up and doing something stupid.
But yeah, I kind of really want to do that.
Aren't we all?
Ben, you did a comic Kickstarter.
What even the fuck?
It was so easy.
Nothing could have been simpler.
Wait, what do you want to know?
What are you asking me?
I guess the guest artists.
Because I've contacted a few people about like doing like mini adventures.
And I thought that was the thing you did.
And I thought that was really cool.
That would be a cool stretch goal for a lot of ghosts.
But how does that work?
I want to pay them obviously.
But like, I don't know how much.
She probably asked.
Yeah, I don't know.
Kind of depends on the artist.
And then maybe just pay a page rate or just a flat, like, you know,
a certain amount per story.
And then, you know, structure your structure, your stretch goals so that like,
okay, if we hit this much, then that's enough to cover, you know, one more,
you know, story added to the thing, including like paying the artist,
plus the like printing costs of adding more pages.
And, you know, yeah.
You just got to make the numbers add up one way or another.
It's just a lot of like, like information I need that I couldn't possibly have yet.
Such as how many pages they're going to be, how long,
I mean, I guess it doesn't matter how long they're going to take.
But like, the, well, the amount of effort they put in,
should I pay them a working rate for how long they work?
I don't know.
That's, I mean, that's like depends on the artist.
You can make any offer you want.
You can be like, I'll pay an hourly rate.
Honestly, I wouldn't pay an hourly rate because that's dependent on them to like track their hours.
And I don't know.
That just seems weird.
I would pay either just a page rate or like a flat rate for like,
make me this story, I will pay you this much.
Yeah.
That's one aspect of it.
It's the money thing.
But then, you know, presuming I get enough, like I'd obviously have it like,
stretch goals so that there's plenty of money so I can pay them rather than not enough.
But like, then there's the thing of like, writing these little stories.
Like very vague ideas.
Like, oh, that could be something with hippo and in bit secondy.
That's new, new by the sea, aka Neo York.
Yeah.
Well, it's like, you know, there's like little adventures with these characters.
There's plenty of characters.
This is big city stuff could happen.
Yeah.
Who knows?
That's cool.
I'd have to think of like something that was something.
Because I've always been terrible with, I mean, efficient storytelling.
I tell my stories in extremely long form.
I can't write a short one.
It's impossible.
Do you, I mean, do you, so you don't have like, concepts ready to go of like,
what the side stories would be?
No, I could, I could probably think of some stuff because there's plenty to work with.
Yeah.
But yeah, I mean, what, what was your creation process for?
Honestly, my friends, I fucking was so bad at that.
I had, you know, they came out really well and all the guest artists made really good
stuff.
But honestly, and this might be discouraging and I'm sorry, but like, I feel like I was
not good at that.
It took me so long and so much like hand wringing and fucking pulling my hair out to get myself
to like settle on a concept of like, what should the vaporettes be about?
What kind of stories will they be?
Who's going to draw which one?
And then actually sitting down and scripting them.
I, I think they came out well, but I, I found it so painful.
I don't know if I, I don't know.
I don't want to say I don't know if I should do it again because I really like the end
results.
But boy was it hard.
Boy, I really struggled with it.
And that was a lot of the, that was a big part of the reason why it took so long for the
comic to get done was because I didn't, because I didn't have them done before the Kickstarter
because I wanted to wait for the stretch goals to be met before I committed to them.
Yeah.
I feel like, I mean, I think the, what my stories are going to be about.
I think I'm going to call them ghost stories just cause it's a lot of ghosts.
Yeah.
Um, I feel like there's, it's easier because yours are like character things about Vincent
and Magda.
Yeah.
And they go to highs, they go to college.
And we don't even know what they major in, I don't think, but we know Magda draws.
We do that.
Uh, and it's like, it's the only thing you can write is like, interactions they have,
things from their life.
Yeah.
Like character story building.
With what I have is like, I've got an established world.
You had a bunch of wacky shit.
Yeah.
I could have, I was thinking of having like a story just about the brickie brawlers and
the mutton shunters.
Just fighting, just a couple of them.
Yeah.
I mean, that's the, yeah, that's the, um, like actually writing the dialogue was not that
hard, but settling, settling on and committing to a, okay, I should might write a vaporette
script where this happens.
This is the concept that I want to make.
I was like, I was just really bad at that of thinking of them and of committing to them,
which was like the hardest part for me.
Um, yeah, maybe it would be easier for you because your setting is more diverse, I guess.
It's more like shit.
I think, I think I could come up with some simple ideas.
I just, I worry that the ideas I come up with would be too long.
Like, because I mean, Laura ghost was not supposed to be almost a hundred pages long.
And yet there it is.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, maybe if you, maybe if you're coming up with ideas, you know, you, you,
you know, you come up with maybe a list and then you go through, you pick out your favorites
and then you write them, you script them and then you just see like, okay, this one was
too long.
So I'll do it later.
Or this one didn't come out as good as I, as I thought.
So I'll, you know, I just won't do that one.
Just, I don't know, just pick the ones that are the right size.
And I know that means that like work might end up getting left on the cutting room floor
because some might not pan out or whatever.
I don't know.
I think I feel like that ultimately the, the, the issues that will come from this Kickstarter
idea, they're not that big.
I am just like worried that I will, I will make a huge mistake or like, like sending
the packages like, oh, that's scary.
I've not done that before.
Sending the packages sucks and takes forever.
And I was still doing it like months after because people were late with their, with
their surveys and, you know, and that's just stuff you got to accept is going to happen.
It was whatever.
I mean, I had, I had all this stuff.
Like I bought a whole bunch of like the envelopes and stamps and shit.
So like I was ready to go, but it meant like, you know, a week would go by and then I would
check and there'd be a few more surveys filled out and I gotta make another trip to the post office.
And I mean, you were asking me about international shipping before and like, boy, international
shipping can get expensive.
And I assume that, I mean, we probably have a similar demographic that reads our stuff.
And most people that I was fulfilling were in America.
So probably it would be the same for you.
So probably those would all become international shipping, which is unfortunate.
It's unfortunate.
I forget.
And in Kickstarter, do you like, does the person buying put their location and then the shipping
gets added on to the price?
Or do I have to set the price of the, the goals or like the thing to accommodate shipping?
It's per tier.
So like you can, if two different tiers have different rewards, you can set different shipping
for each tier.
And then for each tier, you can, you can specify like a general shipping amount, but you can
also specify like by country.
Like you can say like, okay, and I do this for vapors, you can say like, okay, in the
United States, no shipping, Mexico or Canada, $2.
Everywhere else, $5.
Like you can specify.
And yeah, I assume they have to specify their country when they pledge.
I think it works like that.
Okay.
So I was doing some calculations.
I think something like 15 pounds, maybe a little less would be like the price of the
comic, uh, physical.
Yeah.
And then I would have, I would make, I would, I would get a pin made of like the little ghosts
that's on the cover.
Like badly drawn little ghost that I think that would be a cute pin.
I'd wear that.
Uh, then there's like, I don't know, rewards.
Like I, I don't know whether I could draw little doodles as good as the ones you made
for like the personalized vapors too.
Those are really good.
I put like way too much effort into those.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I, um, but I mean, I charged a lot.
My, my like signed and drawing tier was like pretty expensive.
So I kind of felt like I should put some, I should put energy into these.
And I did.
I mean, you could always do like a, a more moderate one that really is like just a doodle.
Yeah.
I guess I could do a little doodle.
Like I could have a signed version and then a doodle version with a sign.
Yeah.
Uh, I've thought about it.
I thought about things.
I think it's not even that far from being real.
I just need to like make the PDF and, uh, and write some of the, the guest art things
and see what happens.
Make the thinker stretch goals.
I have no idea what I'm going to do for stretch goals other than dick guest artists.
Uh, you had some fun ones.
Yeah.
Uh, oh, well.
Once I hit, I had a bunch in mind.
And then once they all got hit, because, because like I, I planned my tears pretty much.
Um, like I set the prices pretty low so that like what I was, what I was asking for a tier
was not much more than what it was going to cost.
So like hitting another tier didn't really increase my profit much.
All like most of the extra money just went back into, you know, adding the thing.
Right.
So they were all pretty close together, you know, guest artists, guest artists, guest
artists.
Um, and yeah.
So we hit all, all the stretch goals I had in mind.
We hit them pretty fast because I set the prices for low.
And then I was like, well, uh, and I just made shit up.
Made funny shit up.
And, uh, I don't know.
I just made a joke out of it.
Made it, uh, kind of, kind of in a failure of branding, I made the stretch goals for
Vapors two related to, uh, fine and punishment.
Yeah.
Which I guess is fine, but it's a weird decision in hindsight, but I don't know.
I thought it was funny.
It was.
And it became.
Yeah.
True.
Oh God.
It makes me so upset.
It makes me so upset to think about that because that was like a year and a half ago.
So that was like a year and a half ago and I was drawing slime and punishment then.
God.
No.
Why?
Why did it take me so long?
Why did it take me so long to make the video and then to make the game?
I'm gonna freak out.
I mean, oh, the video, you mean the animation, right?
Yeah, the animation.
I mean, there was a lot of stuff on everybody's mind in 2020.
But yeah, I don't know.
Things take time, I guess.
Being not focused enough on work is potentially a problem.
I think it's a healthy mixture of external stresses and personal and professional failures on my part.
It's a nice healthy mix of both of those things.
What is that?
God.
I still, it's so, it's so weird to me to think that it was a year and a half ago that I was drawing slime and punishment.
To me, it still feels like the thing that I'm drawing.
And it kind of is because I have more of it left to do to come out for the finale.
God, I got to fucking get it done.
I just, I want it done so bad.
All the more reason to focus on that and to stop yigging, to stop yig posting.
Stop yigging.
Stop noiding.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Every second I spend thinking about yig is probably wasted.
But I don't know.
Everyone needs a hobby.
No, you do know.
No.
Everyone needs a hobby.
Your hobby can be noisy.
That's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, I could, I could, I guess I could try to make the punk plush a really high stretch goal.
I guess the only problem with that is how do I, how do people get it?
Like, do I make a tier?
Do I change the tiers later?
Like, and if we get the pump thing, you get this, you get it.
You can, you can add a new tier later.
You can't change an existing tier once the, once the project is launched, but you can add a new one.
Right.
So if I hit the punk plush stretch goal.
Yes.
I can add the punk plush as well tier.
And then they could get that in there.
Then the shipping would be way more because it's, it's not, it's not a letter.
It's a package.
I mean, people would have to, people would have to change their tier to the plush tier and that would have to come with a, you know, an increased shipping costs.
I mean, I think that's, that's, that's just the reality of the situation.
Yeah, but that's, that's what I said is the reason the plush one didn't work out is because there was no, like lower, it was a very high.
What's the word floor, a very high barrier to entry.
There was no like, like more moderate, like 10 or $15 reward.
It was just like like 50 bucks and up.
Right.
I think I had some, some shitty, like low things where it's like, oh, well, it's a thank you like a tip jars for $5.
You won't get anything, but thanks.
And then 10 was like, I'll give you a doodle.
No, I think terrible.
I think that the plush as like a higher tier reward, yes, a stretch goal and then a higher tier reward to go along with something that is more modestly priced like a comic book.
I think that would work out really well.
Yeah.
It's similar in that is punk is not related to Lord of Ghosts.
But yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, you could make a Lord of Ghost plush.
He'd make a nice little, I mean, I guess, I guess that's a lot.
I guess that's a lot of work to just throw around so casually.
He would make a nice plush though.
He would.
I think that the only problem with that is that I'd have to contact the company.
They'd have to approve.
Well, they wouldn't have to approve the design or just say, okay, we'll make this and it will take like a month.
They'll send me a sample and then only then would I have something to show people what they would be purchasing.
And before then, you know, I don't know whether it would be even worth getting hype about, but I know what the punk plush would look like.
I already have one.
Potential.
There's potential in that.
I mean, what if a little lot of ghosts with his eyes.
He's squishy.
Yeah.
All his little eyes.
His little arms.
His little dangly arms.
I can just imagine like holding him.
Holding him like a little turd and just like twisting him around and making his and making his arms just kind of like flap.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, I know.
His arms like flapping, flapping hither and thither, twisting around like he's doing the twist.
Hell yeah.
I can see it.
I can see it in my mind's eye.
I could maybe have like a little sheet that goes over him.
I don't know whether that would be something I could ask them to make.
Oh my God.
That would be so cute.
That's almost too much to bear.
But yeah, you can do that.
Honestly, it wouldn't be that hard to like get some white cloth and make sheets myself, but that's.
Just make them yourself.
Yeah.
And then like.
I mean because I mean that's sort of the point of it is that it's kind of like a shitty
homemade, you just fucking threw a sheet over him.
Yeah, you could just like cut.
Oh, that could be like premium.
Like it could be like the premium tier is he comes with the cloth that you just like cut out of a thing and drew some eyes on.
Oh, it's a cool idea.
Like the cool lot of ghosts where he has the sunglasses.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know whether I'd be able to like make sunglasses or like buy a bunch of sunglasses to add on to that.
That's a bit much.
People can do what they like.
But yeah, it's a cool idea.
It's funny.
Yeah.
Okay.
Anything else to say about that?
I have one more thing on my list of going.
No, I don't think there's anything more else to say.
I think it's just I got to figure out the money so that I know how high to put the.
That's just be expect expect things to cost more than you think.
Oh, of course.
In particular shipping shipping was like, I knew how much the comics were going to cost because they gave me a quote about that.
So that wasn't so bad, but the shipping all ended up costing more than I thought.
International shipping was always more than I expected it to be.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Just be like the worst possible thing.
The worst possible thing that can happen with a Kickstarter is not that it fails.
It's that it succeeds, but you realize that you fucked it up and asked for less than you needed and you're in the red now.
Yeah.
God, I mean, the idea of getting the punk plush real or the Lord of Ghost plush.
It's really cool.
Yeah.
The logistics of like ordering that, having it arrive and then having to get it to where I live alone is a lot.
And there's probably going to be customs charges that I'm going to have to pay for such a large shipment of plushes.
And then I'm going to have to package them maybe individually, like buy some amount of boxes.
Maybe I can save on shipping by holding the comics back until the plush is there for the people who got the plush.
And then I could send them together.
That would be okay.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
You've got to find every way to save on costs with things like that you possibly can.
Yeah, definitely send it all as one package.
For sure.
Blimey.
Such a prospect.
I don't envy myself for doing that in the future.
Future Gib is fucked.
Future Gib is fucked only if she wins at the Kickstarter game.
I'm so scared.
I'm not prepared.
I'm not prepared for this massive endeavor of making money with art that I made.
It can't be done.
Is anybody ever really prepared?
It's like becoming a parent.
You just got to do it.
Just like having a baby.
The thing about it is that you just have to do it.
You're forced to do it.
Gun to your head.
You don't have a choice.
You must.
No one's ever ready, but you got to do it anyway.
You know, that's the perfect analogy.
I'm going to send out all these little babies, all these little lord ghosts.
Based.
All right.
That's something to look into.
Okay.
I should write down.
I'm just going to write down like a list of things to look into.
And then you can talk about your thing.
My last thing that I want to complain about is this week I have been eating a lot.
And even worse, I've been door dashing a lot.
I've been ordering a lot of takeout, Chinese pizza, chicken, bro keto, whatever.
My excuse.
I know it's bad.
That's how you know it's bad.
My excuse is that I've started lifting again, which is good.
It feels good.
I'm strong now.
And I'm only getting stronger.
I'm going to, it's going to be really annoying when I have to move and I'm going to like lose
access to my exercise equipment and I will then have to buy some more and set it up.
And for a while, I won't be able to lift.
I'll have to break my streak.
But you know, what are you going to do?
It's going to be right.
It's going to be right as I'm getting into the swing of it too.
I'll be a couple months in and then I don't even want to think about it.
I don't know.
So I'm getting fat, but I'm also getting strong.
So it's a wash.
It sounds like just the one.
No.
Which one?
Which one does she mean though?
If you're getting all of that first food in you, you're not going to be very fast for very long.
It's good for you.
Chicken.
I get a lot of fried chicken.
Well, I don't know fried, but yeah.
It's the abundance of oils and stuff.
And fats.
Oil's good.
It's keyed out.
The pizza was indulgent.
I was just feeling like cheating.
I was like, fuck, I'm getting a pizza and I did.
I had pizza the other day.
Ow, it's bit my tongue.
Fuck.
Just eat.
Because I wanted to just eat.
There's all these restaurants nearby that are like, oh, thousands upon thousands of upvotes.
Five stars.
Everyone loves this one.
I was like, okay, well, I've had that one.
Let's see this other one that's got like 90 upvotes and it's also like five stars.
It's a much smaller looking, much less professional photography for their food.
I was like, yeah, it's Italian.
It seems more traditional.
I got it and it was the best pizza ever.
So that's real Italian.
I found a real Italian place.
Fascinating.
It's always nice when you look for the stuff that nobody pays attention to.
It's something in your gut that feels like, yes, this is the real shit.
The popular stuff is always bad.
You got to go into the back streets and into the back alleys where the locals get their food.
Except it's like fast food in London.
I don't know, dude.
I just buy wings over.
I just buy wings over because they got good sauce and they're not Wingstop, which is criminally bad.
Wingstop is the worst fucking place I've ever eaten.
It's so bad.
I can't believe it's legal.
I can't believe it's legal that they serve the food that they do.
It's a nightmare.
I just buy fucking tendies.
And you know what?
They're rewarding me.
They're giving me that Pavlovian.
They give me that Skinnerbox treatment because sometimes I'll order from them and they'll just give me extra.
And then I'm like, oh my God, the value.
They doubled my order one time.
I ordered six tendies and they gave me 12 tendies.
I was eating it the next day.
It was crazy.
One time I ordered and they just gave me my order plus somebody else's order.
I feel like that might be a mistake and not a value for money.
I see two possibilities.
One is that it was a mistake and they just gave me someone else's order and that other person was fucked.
The other one was maybe that that order got canceled and they were just like, well, let's just give this other person's order to that other guy.
Because he's our beloved customer and he deserves it.
I hope it was the second one.
They definitely had that conversation as well.
I mean, it's our beloved customer Ben saying.
It's our beloved...
It's the Tendi guy.
It's the Tendi guy from Such and Such a Road.
Oh, we love that guy.
Oh, have you read his comics?
Oh yeah, he's very talented.
And he's a great taste in sauce too.
He always gets the hot garlic.
Oh, it's my favorite.
Beautiful.
Yeah, I just...
I don't know.
When I'm when I'm lifting, I'm just like, got to eat big to get big.
And it's more important to build muscle than it is to fucking keep my calories down.
And I got to eat the calories to do that.
So fuck it.
And I don't know, it's fine.
It's good.
It doesn't really matter.
It's more of a good that I'm lifting again than it is a bad that I'm eating a little too much, you know?
So fuck it.
I can cut later.
I mean, I should...
I'm going to dial it back a little bit.
I had a fucking week.
I had a week of hedonistic gluttony.
But like, I can't...
I'm not going to keep that up because it's stupid.
And like, I still want to be keto and whatever.
I've had a little issues lately with cooking.
It's like, I want to cook.
I want to cook for myself because it's cheaper, mostly.
And it's just as tasty, if not tastier than like the slump.
Well, in terms of money, right?
You buy some fucking chicken breasts from the store and you just fry them.
And I did that the other day.
I got some chicken breasts.
I put flour on them, some corn flour, salt and pepper, and just put them on the frying pan for ages.
And I took them off and I was like, wow, it's cooked.
I did it and I ate it and it was really good.
And that costs like so much less than it would have if I had ordered chicken from someplace.
Wait, did you say corn flour?
Yeah, it was just what I had.
They said like you could use really just to put a coating on there.
Oh, sure.
Before you put it on the frying pan.
Yeah, I guess so.
I guess.
It wasn't like a deep fried chicken nugget sort of thing.
It was just sort of some stuff on it.
Pan fried.
Organa.
Yeah, sure.
Pan fried chicken.
That was really, really nice.
You ever deep fry?
No, I don't.
I guess I have a saucepan, so I could.
Deep frying is cool.
But it takes so much grease.
It takes so much grease.
You can save the grease, you know, you can use it over and over again.
Save it where?
In the saucepan?
Yeah, well, I mean, you can, you buy it in bottles.
You can just like pour the oil into the pan, heat it up, cook in it, and then like let it cool.
And then pour it back in the bottle, put the cap on, and use it again later.
I hadn't thought of that.
It's pretty cool.
I mean, what else do you do?
Like pour it down the sink?
Like that's such a waste.
I suppose so.
But yeah, I've been having trouble just because of like illness stuff, which is still happening, unfortunately.
And I'm like, I'm leaving things unwashed.
Like I'm not washing up after myself as much.
Like you're not.
And I'm like not cooking as many meals.
Sometimes I like only have dinner.
I don't have lunch.
I sort of have breakfast and then I have a linner or whatever.
And it's, it's good, but it's not good enough.
I'm not getting enough nutrients.
And so I end up ordering food and it's like, it sucks.
I don't like being in this situation where I'm not like the perfect chef or I'm not cooking meals, three meals a day.
It's like, it's a lot of work.
I don't like filling that gap with fast food because it's just so expensive.
It's so convenient.
I love that that like concept is, is, is, you know, it has improved our lives.
A humanity so much that if you are hungry and you have a phone with money, you can get food delivered right to your door immediately.
Like in like an hour and you could survive.
I, I'm, I'm glad that I have generally made a habit of buying groceries instead of ordering out.
Ordering out is such a fucking waste.
It's cool that it's a, it's an option.
Yeah, but it is, it is just so like, like, I don't know.
I guess there's nothing really to say other than I wish I was cooking more.
But it's difficult.
It's difficult when I only have one frying pan.
I have to clean it up for every single time.
Oh yeah, that kind of sucks.
Oh God, when I, when I move, I'm going to have to, oh no, I'm going to, I'm going to have to fucking get new kitchenware.
I'm going to have to get new pans and spatulas and shit.
Oh my God, this sucks.
Did I talk about how I have to move soon?
Did I mention that last week?
You did mention that.
Well, I think so last week.
Yeah.
Oh, it sucks.
I haven't even, I haven't even started looking.
I have not even started looking for like a new place.
I don't, I think I'm a little in denial.
I don't want to deal with it.
And I don't want to know what my rent is going to be.
It's going to be so bad.
Just assume it's going to be like four billion dollars a month.
It is going to be, it's going to be like double.
It's going to be like double what I pay now.
I know, I know it.
Well, you should rip the bandaid off, look around.
Like the longer you, like they could have been a good deal that you already missed
because you haven't been looking.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I got it.
You got to be doing that.
Sure.
Yeah.
I know.
I know you're right.
Oh, look at me.
I'm gay.
Ben.
I just do the smart thing instead of the stupid thing.
Pat yourself.
Pat yourself on the back.
I am.
You fucking got it.
You did it.
Congratulations.
Oh, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of this, this world, these people.
I'm tired of being caught in the tangle of their lives.
You're tangled up in your own life.
Tangled is a good movie though.
It's okay.
Like that part where the guy's got all the swords pointed at him and he's like, hmm.
This is going to be a meme one day.
Yeah, you could tell.
He knew.
Uh, Finn Flynn Flynn Flynn.
Do you want to do voicemails?
Uh, yeah.
The Lord of Ghost thing was the last thing I wanted to talk about.
So yeah, I'm good.
I've gone through my list.
All right.
Let's get into it.
Are you on the speak pipe?
Are you on speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail where you listener can send us voicemail where
we will answer, but only if it's good and you have something to say and you have charisma
and are cool and, and don't waste our time, please.
And thank you.
Yes, I am.
Okay.
Good.
Then our first voicemail of the day is called she her please smiley face.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Go.
So I've been rewatching sin figure because I finally wanted to catch up on the later seasons
and I just remember what I used to be into this show since I came.
I was like, hang out in the disc horns, participate in community, rewatch events and stuff.
And that shit's all gone now.
Those people that discord's dead.
Like I'm never, I'm never interacting with them again.
And like, like maybe I'm tripping on my medication or whatever, but I got really emotional and
the, the transience of everything just suddenly came and like hit me.
Just wanted to say like, give and Tom, Jesse, Nate, Munchie, Mange, uh, Davoo and even like
even Trixie and everybody listening.
Like I'm glad this all happened.
You know, you're fucking having a moment.
Yeah, but like, I'm glad this all happened.
I'm totally tripping.
That's what's happening over it.
Be sad.
It happened.
It's continuing.
I can't tell if that was a joke or not.
I don't know what they were talking about at first with whatever community they were in.
Wait, wait, I want to listen to the, I want to hear the beginning again.
I'm going to play it again.
Uh, why does it take so long to sin, sin figure?
I've been rewatching.
I think it's just some thing they're into and they've noticed that the community is
dead and the thing is dead and they're thinking about that happening to the PCP maybe.
Uh, whatever.
I don't know.
Life has changed.
Sorry, you're having a emotional moment over it.
Uh, you'll be fine.
I don't know.
I guess I appreciate the sincerity.
Uh, it's fine.
It's, I don't know.
I'm glad you liked stuff.
Uh, I feel a little bad.
I shouldn't shit on this person, but it's so easy.
Um, I don't know.
I guess that's all I have to say about it.
Next, next voice, next voicemail.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Uh, we love you.
Uh, next one is called.
Is Riley Trixie's Pimp or something?
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys.
So I just want to say congratulations on finally getting the rad con content.
You know, like, you know, real big shout out to that one guy who talked to Riley about
it.
And that's why it happened.
Not fucking talking to Trixie directly like everyone's been doing.
That was, um, trying to get this fucking rad con stuff.
No, no, we got to talk to Riley.
Yeah.
This person who was never involved and when he tried to get involved, she'll only do
it if Riley tells her to, she'll only do it if Riley tells her to.
Thanks for Riley for being so fucking benevolent to, uh, fucking tell Trixie to do her fucking
job.
Yeah.
What a, what a base dude.
Gracious.
What a cool guy.
It's like, oh, well, you know, she doesn't want to do anything for her ex friends.
And it's like, well, fucking, it's not about fucking any of these guys.
It's about the fucking people who paid hundreds of fucking dollars to get this shit.
You know, fucking, I am just so sick of their fucking little attitude, man.
Like when the fuck does Riley feel the fucking need to like talk on her behalf all the time?
Like just shut the fuck up, Riley.
Shut the fuck up because nobody fucking cares.
Anyway, PCP forever.
Tom will never die.
Call me back.
How do we call him back?
I couldn't, I couldn't agree more.
I couldn't agree more and I appreciate it.
Thanks.
Thanks for speaking truth to power.
Thanks for speaking truth to power, friend.
Yeah.
It's, for me, it's always, it's always been about like the, the, like the money, the back
has spent so much money.
We owe it to them to try to get everything that was promised out.
And Trixie has just made it difficult for no discernible reason.
I mean, I guess you deserve something.
The whole, the whole debate about like, oh, I didn't promise the lecture.
Oh, I didn't technically promise the lecture is like such a, it's missing the point.
The point is that these people cared and they donated and they want something and we have
the opportunity to give them value to, to reward them for their support.
And, you know, promise or not, Trixie is like nah, and it's despicable.
It's the only word for it.
Whoops.
Sorry.
I got a little upset there.
Ha ha.
Funny, funny voicemail.
You're allowed to get upset.
It's, it's just about the, the, all of the, the like continued, just the disdain of their
movements, just the narcissistic disdain under their stuff because it just rouse you up.
Just the sheer, just the sheer entitlement of like, ah, fuck you think and I should do
anything just because you cared about my project and supported it and, and pledged to it.
Now fuck you.
Like how, how dare you expect anything in return.
Disgusting.
Um, next voicemail.
Levy with no Jevy.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Minor spoilers for us.
Y'all, please talk about Psycholonials and the ending and what you chose because you
haven't really talked about it and talk about how Abby is an amazing character and I love
her because she's an enabler of Zen's bad behavior, self-described and as well as a saviour
from it.
Now that's cool.
And, uh, Tommy for there.
Infinity train season four.
Speak.
Uh, you know what?
I didn't do that.
I've dropped a Psycholonials thing.
Yeah, I've dropped the ball because I said that I would let you know when I re-read it
and I want, I honestly really want to do it.
I really want to re-read it and I want to record a Psycholonials cast and I just haven't
done it.
So it's on me.
I probably need to re-read at this point because it's been a while.
I mean, I do love Abby and it's really cool.
If I remember correctly, I think, what did I do at the end?
There's the two choices.
I remember what I did at the end.
Do you want to?
I did.
I forget what the choices were but I know whichever one I pressed, I pressed that every
single time.
Yeah, same.
And it was Crown.
Obviously.
Wait, no.
Fuck.
I forget which is which.
It was Dagger.
Dagger is the sort of thing that's hanging over you.
Oh, you may never, you'll always have the Dagger hanging over you knowing that you could've
been great and you could've done all this stuff.
I clicked the Dagger over and over again.
I didn't Crown over and over again.
Yeah.
I did Crown times five.
That's so funny.
It was really cool knowing afterwards where that's the first real point where you can
choose and then the ending of the game happens, the credits roll and you go to the save screen
so you can load up your save and try the different things and it's a completely different thing
and it's like the epilogue.
Like they deleted your save files.
Actually, you can't just go back and do it again, motherfucker.
Yeah.
That was cool.
But it tells you like it wouldn't have changed anything.
You don't feel like, oh shit, I want to find all the different routes.
It's like the routes, they all lead to the same place.
Don't worry.
We deleted your save.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah.
It's good.
It was well handled.
Yeah.
No, Crown.
You know what?
I don't want to get too deep into it because I do want to do the Cyclonials cast.
So I won't explain my reasoning.
When we do the Cyclonials cast, I will explain why I did Crown five and you can explain why
you did sword five.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Do I have time?
I will try and squeeze out some time soon to do that because it's not long.
It takes like probably reread it in like four hours.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
Okay.
Was that, was that Levy Jevy that made it?
It didn't sound like him.
He didn't, it didn't sound like him.
So I don't know what.
He's got a high pitch voice.
Yeah.
I don't think that was him.
I wonder why it's named after him.
Shout out to Levy Jevy.
Yeah.
Some endless warhead.
Maybe.
Endless warhead.
Like a bomb.
Like candy.
Oh.
Sure.
Next, next voicemail.
There's three voicemails that are called one, two, three.
So, okay.
One in three, two, one, go.
Hey, there's just me or just a guy of four minutes, 10 seconds of the new Scott the Wilds
video look like Nate.
I'm a stroke confirm.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Let me go check Scott the was the new Scott the was four minutes and 10 seconds in, but
keep in mind, this would have been the new one as of four days ago.
Okay, let me check.
Can you screenshot him for me?
Okay.
Yeah.
Four minutes, 10 seconds.
No, no, it fucking doesn't screen screenshot him.
Oh, um, okay.
It's just got the it's just got the green lagoon shades on.
Is that the boundary break guy?
God, I hate that guy.
I mean, I don't hate that guy, but it is content annoys me or at least it used to who's who's
Scott.
No, no, no, boundary break.
I've never heard of him.
Yeah, it's he does these videos where this guy does not look like Nate.
Absolutely.
No, I don't see it at all.
He does these videos where he goes beyond the camera in video games, like, oh, he'll
he'll like move the camera to places where it was impossible to see.
And then you can see like, oh, this is how the background is.
And this is how like it looks from this angle that is impossible to get to.
It's not interesting.
But the way he utilizes this incredible cool technology is terribly, terribly lacking.
And I'm so frustrated every time I see any of those things.
I'm like, oh, I want to know what is in, you know, the boundary breaking of this place,
of this game.
Oh, it's it just leaves me upset that this video exists more or so than like if I never
knew because now I just want the technology.
I don't care about his YouTube channel at all.
Oh, wait.
This is the guy.
I think I know.
I think I've seen one or two of those.
The ones that just kind of show the game from like angles that you can't see it from
regularly.
Yeah.
I've seen one of those about about Simpson's fucking road rage.
I think.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I've only seen a few, but like it's, it would just, it would just annoyed me.
This guy.
It gives me that Arlo feeling where I feel like Arlo could be so much more than he is
with his puppet, but he's just a guy talking.
He's just a gamer talking about video games in a very dry, normal way.
But he's got a funny puppet and he's not funny.
He's not a funny person.
He's not particularly funny.
Yeah.
It's missed.
It's missed opportunities, lacking, lost potential.
That's what annoys me.
Arlo is fine as a person.
This guy does not look like Nate, but some people recently were posting around pictures
from a wired video called mortician answers dead body questions from Twitter.
I think I saw that.
And, and people posted the screenshot and I checked out the video.
People were saying this guy looks like Nate and I honestly, I completely see it.
Yeah.
This guy looks like it.
Not exactly, but this guy looks a lot like Nate.
I'm posting the screenshot.
Wow.
Why is it?
Why is it taking so long to upload?
Jesus Christ.
It's only half a, half a megabyte.
You fucking, you fucking bitch.
Processing.
There we go.
It's like, it's like, it's like, it's like if, if, if Nate and Dr. Wolf fused and he
gained the waistcoat.
Yeah.
He's got, he's kind of got like the haircut.
His, his lips are maybe a little different, but he's kind of got like the face shape and
the cut.
And you know, he does not wear in the sunglasses, but yeah.
It's, it's a little like, I totally see it.
Yeah.
It's an interesting video.
I watched it.
Just in case people aren't aware because we never talk about it, but we have show notes
where you can see the images if they're not on screen.
Oh, that's right.
I hope Eleazar still does those.
Yeah.
I know.
I never watched the PCP.
I have no idea, but if you wanted to know.
I mean, I would, I would hope for, if it's just an image, I would hope that Eleazar shows
it on screen, but if it's something like a link, then yeah, show notes should be in the
description at the timestamp that we talk about the thing.
Yeah.
Right.
For an image or just show it.
Yeah.
I think so.
Okay.
All the, maybe I don't know, I'm fucking in the show notes, maybe put the link to the
video.
But I mean, I said what is, you can just Google mortician answers dead body questions from
Twitter.
There's only one.
Whatever.
Okay.
Right.
Enough.
Yeah.
Two, three, two, one.
Go.
Okay.
So I continue watching the video.
There's a guy in the bottom corner.
Four minutes, 37 seconds look like monkey to anyone.
All right.
Let me check.
Oh my God.
47 seconds.
I thought he said four minutes and 30 seconds.
Let me let me listen again.
He kind of slurs it.
It's like, I think he says like four minutes, 30 sec.
Okay.
So I think he's saying four minutes, 30 seconds guy in the bottom corner.
Oh, four minutes, 36 seconds.
I don't see any monkey.
Oh, and 47 seconds is a different group of people.
Also none look like monkey.
What is this?
Why is this guy like live watching Scott the was and making the first one?
I don't know.
Okay.
You want to do the next one?
Yeah.
Okay.
Next one is called three, three, two, one go.
So like, I kept watching and I'm stuck with the guy at four minutes and 50 seconds for
Quentin reviews.
It looks really like Quentin reviews is fucked up.
That's so fucked up, dude.
That's so messed up.
I can't believe this shit.
Stupid.
Fuck you.
Yes.
The Quentin reviews is there.
Oh, is it just actually Quentin?
Yeah, I think so.
But it wasn't at 450.
It was at 448.
Oh dear.
Well, you fucked up.
Okay.
The next voicemail is called battle pass.
You ready?
Yep.
Three, two, one go.
Okay.
I kept watching again and the guy at four minutes and 50 sec seconds looks kind of like
Ben.
Are you okay?
Four minutes, 56 seconds.
Here we go.
Jesus.
You know?
Worst hairline.
Did you get one?
Worst hairline, but I mean you've been judged.
Show me.
Worst hairline than mine looks like.
Oh yeah.
I don't know what he's doing.
Yeah, I do kind of see it a little bit.
A little bit.
He kind of looks like Nathan Fielder.
A little bit, but like.
Oh yeah.
This guy's hair is bad.
This guy's doing something wrong with it.
It's unfortunate.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Whatever.
Next voicemail is called Ginesse.
It's Ginesse.
Okay.
Three, two, one go.
Hey Ben Stain.
I'm in the middle of grinding out my art skills.
And I want to hear about how you load up your art so that you could live off your web
comics.
How'd you do it, Ben?
Um, I.
Oh God.
You know, it's been so long since I even gave a fuck about living about art or living.
Um, I leveled up my, I mean, I used to be like kind of.
I'll tell you exactly what it is.
I watched a bunch of tutorials.
I used to watch a bunch of psychrotutorials.
I watched a bunch of those and then I would try and like follow along.
I, I looked up like fundamental exercises, like drawing lots of circles, drawing lots
of straight lines.
I did that for a while.
Um, not for that long.
Mostly I just, um, wait, uh, okay.
Psychra, psychrotutorials, fundamental exercises.
Uh, there was more.
Um, uh, oh, Loomis.
The Loomis books are so good.
Uh, drawing the head in hands, uh, figure drawing for all it's worth.
Um, uh, what, there's, there's another one that I read.
Uh, I don't know.
All the Loomis books are really good.
That guy's super good.
Read Loomis if you haven't.
Like absolutely read Loomis and follow along.
I think it was figure drawing for all it's worth.
Like I followed along and I did all like the exercises that he was talking about.
Like drawing, like copying the, the, like, you know, the figure of a human off his like,
you know, six, six heads tall figure in the fucking like Leonardo da Vinci,
like guy spread eagle diagram.
Um, that was very tedious, but I got a lot out of that book.
Um, and then the, the, I did all that shit.
And I would, I would draw them and I would draw like characters faces.
I would draw characters portraits, you know, just fuck around, fuck or try it with water color,
try it with ink, try it in pencil, try it in whatever.
Uh, try it digitally.
And then, you know, do all that practice it in various mediums just to see what happens.
And then finally, I think the, the, the, the, the, the apotheosis of my journey,
my art journey was when I was just like, I'm just going to draw a comic.
I'm just going to draw the vapors and it doesn't matter if I'm not good enough.
I'm just going to keep doing it over and over.
I'm just going to draw the, redraw the panels until they look right.
However long it takes.
And that's what I did.
And it took me like six months and eventually it looked kind of good.
And that's it.
Yeah.
That's, that's a good mindset to like, to do it until it looks good.
I always think of like the, the big picture of, oh, my life.
Like I have to get something done by the end of the year.
It's like, I got to do this in certain amount of months because I don't want to be doing
nothing.
I want to be doing something quickly.
And then I just doesn't end up happening at all.
No, or if it does get on, end up happening, it's like sort of rushed.
I would sit, I would sit down and like kind of a plot out the page be like, okay,
panel here, panel here, panel here.
And then I would just go from panel to panel and you know, I would do a sketch and I would
just, just keep erasing and resketching until the sketch looked good.
And then later I came back and I saw the sketches that I had, you know, just done over and over
until they looked good.
And I was like, okay, time for line work.
And I would just do the line work over and over again.
Sometimes I would get it on the first try and be like, yeah, it looks good.
Other times it'd be like, that looks bad.
Erase, do it over again.
Just do it over again.
And that's, that was the most practice I got was just drawing the vapors and just not
giving up until I was satisfied with how it looked.
I don't know.
I feel like, I feel like it worked out well for me.
Maybe not everyone would have success with that method, but it, it, I'm just built different.
I'm just built different baby.
No vaccine side effects.
Pfizer gang.
Uh, Pfizer gang is, Pfizer is like Ravenclaw.
Johnson and Johnson is like Hufflepuff.
And the other one, they're like the other two.
And the Corona virus is like Slytherin.
The Corona virus is like Voldemort.
No, Corona, transphobia is like, is like the Corona virus in that it permeates everything
and is, is deeply into it.
And the vaccines do nothing.
Yes.
Exactly.
That's right.
The metaphor works even better than I expected.
Next voicemail.
Eleazar is a bad man.
Three, two, one, go.
Like Eleazar.
Ha!
More like Smellyazar.
Yeah.
In my right scoot.
Kill him.
Right.
Raggy.
Smells like shit.
That sounds like, that's what he sounds like, right?
No.
Uh, yeah.
Err.
I'm Scooby-Doo.
Raggy.
I, I think Eleazar smells like shit, but I'm a dog, so I like how shit smells.
So it's a compliment.
Rooby-Doo-Bee.
Perfect.
Thanks for the voicemail.
You fucking asshole.
Next one is called comics.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
Monotone Jones here.
No relation.
Ben, I know you've mentioned this in the past, and I think Gib has as well, but I was wondering
if y'all could talk a bit more about how you feel like there's no point in drawing unless you're making comics.
I'm curious because I'm the exact opposite.
Although I have an interest in making comics, the only thing I can motivate slash find enjoyment in is simple illustrations.
I don't really have a specific question about this, but I thought it would be interesting to hear a bit more about your thought process, I guess.
Thanks.
Also, Simsie for full-time PCP.
It felt like they had been there all along when you had them on.
Simsie's cool.
But no, no, no PCP ever.
Never, never, never, never.
We're gonna dwindle until we're zero people, and the show will go on even then.
The only one left will be Craig.
Yeah, yeah, true.
I, I think, I feel like I have two feelings about this, and I think one is mercenary and the other is artistic.
But both of these instincts are in agreement.
My artistic feeling is that a comic that has a story is just, has a beginning, middle, and an end.
It's just inherently more valuable than just like a nice looking image.
A nice looking image is transient.
It, like, what does it mean?
I don't know.
It just is what it is.
It looks nice.
Whatever.
A comic with a story is like, there's just more to it.
It has more, it has context.
Like, what is, it is a series of drawings, but the series of drawings mutually reinforce one another in that they come together to be more than the sum of their parts and that they tell a narrative.
And from a more cynical mercenary perspective, you can sell a comic and you can't, I mean, I guess you can sell a print of an illustration.
You can be an illustrator.
I guess you're right.
I just, I don't know.
She's an illustrator.
She gets work.
She, she gets work.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
But I don't, but I, but I didn't, but I don't want to do that.
Like, I don't want to like have people commissioning me to like draw a character or draw a scene.
I just don't, I, yeah, I guess you're right.
I'm wrong.
You can just sell that.
I just, I just didn't want to.
So I was like, I'm going to do this other thing and sell that probably cause I don't know.
I don't know.
Whatever.
That's my answer.
What's, what's your answer?
My answer is, is similarly two fold.
First one is that much in the same way that I tried to learn animation or I did learn animation.
I was going to university for that.
Um, I can't draw very well, but if you put a bunch of images in sequence, people don't notice.
Uh, so a comic, a comic use your eyes glaze over the shit panels and then you focus on the cool ones.
And then animation, you don't notice the bad frames because the cool frames, they only last for a fraction of a second.
So it's like, I, I like, but I can hide, I can hide my, my bad, uh, technique through motion.
Uh, that's why I like an animation and comics cause it's the same sort of thing.
Your eyes are moving.
There's something, there's always somewhere to be for your eyes.
You're like always going to the next part and it's a story.
So you're, you obviously want to continually experience the narrative.
You want to see what happens next.
So you don't linger on anything.
Um, and the other reason is I, I find it, uh, very satisfying to make a story that has multiple layers of, of interest.
Uh, multiple layers of intrigue for the reader.
Uh, with an image, you could be saying lots of things.
I think if, if I think of like the coolest type of image, if I were to be an illustrator, it would probably be like a Where's Wally or a Where's, uh, Waldo, like huge image with so many things going on.
Um, that you, you know, you've got so much to look at.
Have you ever read Kill Six Billion Demons?
The what?
There's a comic called Kill Six Billion Demons.
And if you like like Where's Waldo style, like big, like images of a scene with like lots of little shit coming.
Kill Six Billion Demons, it takes place in like the outer planes and like the hell and heaven and stuff.
And sometimes he will, I forget what the name of the author is, but he will do big, like huge shots that show like a whole landscape.
And the landscape will be some like hell plane that's like made of like giant bones.
And like there's like cutaways that like you can see inside of like the bones that have been cut in half to make like apartments in.
And you can see into all these like demon apartments built inside of like bones that are jutting out of some like magma cliff.
And you can see all the little, all like the weird like monsters and spirits and stuff that are all just kind of doing shit.
Sort of like a Where's Waldo where it's like people walking around and it's like packed with things.
It's very cool.
And it's in that kind of spirit.
Anyway, what about it?
Well, yeah, I just I like when I when I think of like, like a painting or something.
Yeah, the you can look at a painting in an art gallery or like his decoration for a house.
And it's yeah, my eye glosses over it.
Most of the time if it's like something simple, if it's really nice, it's really nice.
Like I like to put really nice images on.
It doesn't have to be like a landscape or anything, just like an illustration.
I like to put stuff like that in background things like posters on my wall, desktop wallpapers, phone screen, lock screen backgrounds.
That's what I think of illustration as being like useful for is like in the background to give just a, you know, out of the corner of your eye something nice to look at.
But it's never really something you pay attention to or study unless it's extremely complex.
Yeah.
And so comics are it's just it's so complex.
There's so it's so dense.
There's so many things going on.
That's why I like comics.
What do you what do you think about kind of that's why I like making them, I guess, not necessarily why I like reading them.
There's there's a thing because I have things I want to communicate.
That's that's the reason there's a thing that is kind of like both of those things combined and the example that spring to mind and I know that this didn't like invent the technique.
But I remember there is one of these things in the My Little Pony friendship is magic, like comic, the Big Mac episode.
There is sort of like a where's Waldo like big shot of like Ponyville.
Oh, yeah.
I love the arts in those comics.
A lot of them had really good art.
Oh, who was the.
There was one pair of artists and writer who was the best one.
Price Andy Price.
I think was the artist I really liked.
But I don't think he drew the Big Mac one, although I kind of forget, but there's a big like panned out shot of like it's not all a Ponyville, but it's like a big chunk of Ponyville and you see Big Mac going from like house to house.
And like talking to all these people and like having a different interaction with all these different characters and it is sort of like a big scenery shot where you see all these people doing different things.
But also it's a sequential scene or telling a story of like, this is like a series of places and interactions like Big Mac went here and he talked to this person and then he went here and he talked to this person.
And then he went here and he did this and he went to that store and he bought that and then he went here and he used the thing he bought to do the thing.
And then he went there and the person said don't do this and da da da da.
And that's pretty neat.
And I like it.
Yeah, I googled the. I remember reading that. That was a really.
Yeah, I know this.
That's just the first one that's bring I know I'm I've seen it in other places too. But yeah,
These comics I should have got into more because it's really like it's the sort of thing that when I was young I was I was really into the Simpsons comics and I've read a lot of those.
I never had I never read those.
If I had some of them are really good.
If I had had them extremely good.
If I had had access to them if I had known anywhere that sold them I would have been all over them.
I just I didn't know that there were Simpsons comics or like I never saw them anywhere.
But that would have been right up my alley who boy when I was like a really little kid.
I made I drew some comics like you know like garbage ones that like a fucking kindergartner would draw.
And I this is I don't know if I've ever mentioned this but I tried to draw a like.
I thought it would be cool or something to show like Homer Simpson like fighting all these like monsters from Greek mythology.
I thought that was cool.
And you know I just watched I think it you I've been I've fucking let YouTube auto play fucking videos where a guy talks about video games.
And I let it do that and I started listening.
I was listening to some videos.
I think the guy's name is Sivi and he had a video about die katana.
You know the famously bad follow up to quake I think.
And the plot of die katana is basically you go to like all these different places in history and you fight these mythological monsters.
And all I could think about was I hate this I drew this I told this story when I was in kindergarten about Homer Simpson.
Homer Simpson Homer Simpson climbed the fucking Mount Olympus to fucking slay Medusa or whatever.
What does what is this.
No I'm sure it doesn't exist.
If it does I'm sure it's in a fucking in a file folder in a box somewhere in my parents basement.
No I've that would be so embarrassing.
I hope I never see that.
I want to see it.
I know I love I love shitty things done when young.
Those are cool.
I hope I hope to God that it's been destroyed.
I couldn't bear it.
My heart couldn't take it.
Fuck comics.
Am I right.
Next.
Yes.
Voice mail.
Listen to your voice mail of mine and let you know that my own lecture Stargate 101 is live now and we have two more in editing.
Stargate on this summer.
Took four weeks.
From the day it was recorded to the day it was released.
I know you'll do better next time.
Speaking of which give please promise.
Fuck you.
Do a lecture on Buffy and Angels someday those shows are a ton of fun and would make a great topic.
That you know maybe I I think.
It's always come up as like a what makes a good lecture.
I feel like Buffy and Angel are such good, like unironically good shows of television
that it is a waste to explain the plot in a lecture in the same way that it would be.
That's kind of how I feel about Tales Get Strolled.
Yeah, I mean a little bit.
Tales Get Strolled is an experience you want to have.
Sonichu is not necessarily, it's hard to sit through that.
You think people would be better off just watching Buffy?
They would, it's really good.
It's very 90s and it's a lot better than maybe people assume it is for being a show about a girl killing vampires.
I mean I've said it's praises before.
Do you watch Jenny Nicholson?
On occasion she comes up in my recommended and sometimes, yeah.
I think her latest video, I think it's her latest one about the vampire diaries.
It's very good, it's not a lecture but it is her just talking about a show in kind of the same way.
It's sort of similar in concept and I like it a lot.
I think it's very entertaining.
I like her stuff.
It's funny, it's funny the jokes that she makes about it.
I don't know.
If she made one just like it about Buffy, I'd be like, yep, I'll watch that.
Because I'm never going to watch Buffy or Angel.
So I mean if someone made a lecture about it, I'd be like, yeah, listen to that.
Well, would you then go and watch it afterwards?
Doubtful.
Yeah, you know, I think a lot of the fun is the twists and turns that you experience as you watch.
I feel like knowing the plot beforehand is not the same.
It's not the same thing.
It's like maybe the lecture might convince me that oh this is actually good,
but then having watched the lecture, I would be like, well, I already know.
So why do I need to watch it?
Even if I am convinced that it's good.
It's like watching, I guess it's not.
It wouldn't be as bad as the one piece.
It wouldn't be as okay as the one piece lecture because one piece has so much stuff that is difficult to remember.
It's just somewhat like understandable as a lecture topic.
Buffy is not that complicated.
You can get everything.
I mean, that's part of the appeal, though, of the lecture is that if you're not going to watch something,
like I'm never going to watch Buffy, if I hear someone explain the plot of Buffy,
I can still kind of get and appreciate an unexpected twist,
just in a sort of boiled down, summarized version.
I can still get that build up where you explain, this happens, this happens, this happens,
but then, aha, it was like this all along.
And then I go, oh, no.
There would be a few moments like that.
Maybe.
I'm still not done with it.
Like last season of Buffy right now, second to last season of Angel.
It's good.
That's all I can say at the moment.
By the way, I said it was very 90s.
That's kind of misleading.
It's very 90s in that it has like grunge for like the theme song.
And it took place in the 90s.
It was filmed in the late 90s, but it is not like 90s core.
It is very like timeless storytelling.
It just happens to take place in a time where certain things were fashionable.
Yeah, sure.
Fair.
It's a period piece, or maybe not.
It's universally understood all of the things that are going on,
like the vampires are window dressing and the 90s is just happenstance.
Fair enough.
Next voicemail is called Based Joker 10.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, when I tell people that I snuck some pistachios into their salad,
they say, oh, that really adds some flavor.
What?
But when I tell people that I snuck some poop stashios into their salad,
well, suddenly I'm no longer a contestant on MasterChef.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
It says, God, I'm chuckling.
I'm chuckling cross.
I think poop stashios.
It's not your best, but it's not your worst.
Poop stashios was a bit over, like, I don't know, if it was obvious
or just sort of single layer to it.
The MasterChef bit made it a little funnier.
The MasterChef bit, the high degree of specificity of the situation
revealed was like, yeah, OK.
I think the perfect Based Joker joke would read like a drill tweet
in the way that a really good drill tweet is not just a very simple
one note joke that you can see coming.
It's the words used, like, only after you have finished reading it,
do you come to realize that it wasn't just that one thing that was strange.
It was all of these other things.
And then that makes it funnier afterwards.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
I think I do know what you mean.
It's like a sleeper agent, like a word you weren't really thinking about
in another context afterwards.
It's like, wait, that's even stupider than I thought it was.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The sudden imparting of new meaning through context
to something that was previously thought to be understood.
The thing that's got explaining jokes is just makes them so much funnier.
It's the best thing to do.
Yeah.
OK, next voicemail is called Dead People.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, I'm watching the PCP right now and I had this thought.
Those are real graves, you know, that you edit the faces onto.
Who do you think is under there?
Who is Harold Henry?
Did Harold Henry know that when he died, somebody would get like a stock photograph
of his grave and put him on a shitty podcast that's like full of washed up content creators
that used to be spicy.
Bold of you.
Bold of you just claimed that I used to be something.
Yeah, the people who are the washed up somebodies aren't on the podcast.
They're dead.
They're under the ground.
Talk about someone who used to be somebody.
Put him in a fucking corpse.
Shit, man.
I don't know.
I just fucking googled and found a stock image of a graveyard with a bunch of headstones on it.
Well, you didn't think about it, Ben.
Now we've desecrated all of these graves over and over again for weeks.
I didn't.
I don't know whose graves these are and does it matter?
I don't know.
Do you care about this?
I don't think I care about this.
I guess I wouldn't care until somebody who's a relative of one of the gravestones complained
and then it would be like, yeah, I guess we should.
You just just draw a picture.
I mean, let's see.
Harold Henry.
Let's see.
When did he perish?
When did these people...
I mean, I'm assuming these are like old graves?
I can't really read the...
Old dead people are old, Ben.
I can't really read the numbers.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Are these like 100 years old?
Maybe nobody who even knew these people...
100 years old graves would look a lot worse than that.
Do you think so?
I mean, it's stone.
Inference.
A lot of these have their coloring entirely worn off and they're just like...
Yeah, I guess they're completely white.
When I go around English graveyards, they're a lot more fucked up because it rains more, I guess.
Also, people have been making graveyards there for longer.
The graveyards in England just are older than the ones here.
Sure, but the individual tombstones not necessarily super old.
Sometimes it could just be like 50 years and it still looks like it's been there for like 700 years or whatever.
Sure.
Well, I don't know.
Caller, if you're offended, I'm sorry that you're offended.
Okay, next one.
Next one is called Henlo Corgo 3.
Fuck you, Ben Taint.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben.
So, like, how many times do people, including yourself, have to tell you to quit assuming gender?
You know, like of people who call in and leave voicemails or in any other situation, really, but...
Right.
I was really excited to hear your guys' reaction to my voicemail last week.
Did I fuck it up?
It was a pretty good reaction, yeah, I'll give you that.
I got mostly the desired effect, but then you also had to be cringe.
You woke up that morning, took a big, big deep breath of fresh air and said,
I'm just going to be a massive fucking troglodyte ass hat today.
I...
Fuck you, Ben.
Get better at being better and quit being cringe.
I guess I assume...
Wow.
You're gender and I apologize.
I do it.
I assume male a lot.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
I didn't have done...
Didn't have done it.
I don't know what else to say.
Okay, whoops.
I mean, I didn't catch you, but...
God, I must have done that as well.
I'm sure I've done it a lot.
I'm sure I've done it many times and...
I don't know.
I'm not proud of myself.
Sorry.
Whoops.
Okay, next one is called Another L for the Old Benny Santos.
Wait, do you see this one?
Refresh the second page.
It's moved down into the...
Another L for the Old Benny Santos.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
I made it simple for you, Ben.
I gave you the key to avoiding harm and yet here we are.
You took another L.
You misgendered someone after I told you to use the
a simple gender neutral pronoun
for your audience of many, many trans people.
I'm sorry.
I didn't listen to you.
You wanted to create a safe space for trans people.
Christ.
I let it slide when someone put their pronouns
in the title of their voicemail
and yet you still ignored it.
But this has been brought to my direct attention.
Tell to what extent these two are taking the piss.
I can't either.
I think they were in your discord talking about it though.
So I think they're serious, but they were sounding very jokey.
They weren't actually that upset, but they did want you to say they.
So it's not untrue that what they're saying.
It's not untrue.
I'm, I'm, I'm going to assume this is whatever.
Whoops.
I fucked up.
I'm just going to assume no one's actually mad at me because
it's easier to live like that.
Uh, sorry.
Sorry.
Beefed it.
Next one is called the monopoly man.
Three, two, one, go.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Here's the monopoly man.
I'm calling in to say that the guy who said that the fixed money
supply of Bitcoin is its downfall is wrong.
You see, when you have money that you can inflate people that are
closer to the government, get the money, which means it's kind
of like a social point system like in China.
It's not about how much value you give back to society with
your investments.
So I guess what I'm saying is that the monopoly man is actually
good.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Who would have slurred those hose together?
Who would have, I'm always slurring hoes.
You know what I mean?
Who would have thought the monopoly man, the monopoly man is very
concerned.
He's worried about the little guy.
uh, uh, having their, uh, their diversely invested portfolio be devalued, uh, that would just be a real problem, you know, for the working class.
Um, your, your thoughts have been imputed, uh, Monopoly Man, uh, vote in your local elections.
Next one is called Ben Read One Piece, please. Three, two, one, go.
Hi Ben, you can come live with me.
Okay.
Cool.
Next one is called Molesting Beb, three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Next one is called RV Location Found, three, two, one, go.
According to my calculations, VRV is beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, up my ass.
Why do you, why did you need to do so many calculations to figure that out?
Yeah, why do you need a computer to tell you that?
And if you already did the calculations, what was the BPD boopin' in?
What, you, he's, he's is a computer. He is a computer. He calculated it live. Why does he even have that?
He says, uh, well, where else are you going to die a rea?
From.
On top of a fucking building in front of a bunch of, of a, of a protest, a bunch of, a bunch of gender critical protestors, uh, uh, uh, protesting, uh, free bathrooms.
Where, where else, it would be a waste to do it anywhere else.
Uh, I should have an entire RV out on them. One of the steps of Congress.
If, if I can put like a sieve under your ass and it like sprays.
Oh, like a shower head?
Turns it to shit rain.
Like a shower head, yeah.
And rains, like increases the, the surface area.
You put it, you, you, shh.
Like a, like, you know how on the end of like a garden hose, you put like a nozzle and the nozzle has like changeable settings that you twist it.
And it's like, oh, like, like squirt or like shower or soak, right?
You shove one of those up your ass and you twist it, right?
For a different set.
Like, oh, no, I want to concentrate in stream.
Oh, no.
J.K. Rowling is opening her mouth.
Oh, I want to concentrate in stream.
Point it right down the throat.
Oh, no.
Oh, she, she left.
She, she, she retreated to her armored vehicle and left the scene.
Okay.
Time to turn it to shower head and get all her supporters.
This is the kind of terrorism I can support.
I'm sorry.
Ehehe, uh, um, uh, yes, good, good.
Okay.
Glad, glad we found it.
Next one is called Nate Location.
Found three, two, one.
Go.
According to my calculations.
Nate is be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be I'm my dick.
That was a long one.
Up my ass. Oh, wow.
Online too.
We got another Natebucker.
We got one.
But he's also an RV being fucked by
because of RVs in his ass.
And he's got the RV in his ass.
He's got Nate on his dick.
This guy is living the dream.
Congrats.
The dream of having a fucking vehicle in Uranus.
He's got it all.
I had to hide that RV somewhere,
so I shoved it up your ass without even thinking.
It was it was the
it was just the most convenient place to put it.
Sorry about that.
But I'm glad you got to fuck Nate.
Next voicemail is called Slap on the Ballsack
from and chew on your nuts until they crack at dot com.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, my God.
Thirty five Jesse.
Ha. Oh, no.
Is this the guy from the length CDI Zelda?
I'm going to suck you on the ball sack.
I'm going to suck you on the ball sack and 200 knots of cold thick crack.
I'm upset.
I'm going to suck you on the ball sack.
I'm going to suck you on the ball sack and 200 knots of cold.
No more, no more voicemails.
And people say that Jesse left the podcast.
That's, that's gotta be, that's, no, that's gotta be Oblivionfall, right?
It's gotta be.
Probably.
Every time I hear a good voi-, every time I hear a good voicemail, I just assume it's
Oblivionfall.
It's one person.
Yeah.
Next one is called Forgib, Professional Advice, Radcon Media Backup Suggestions.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Exposing corruption at the DMD, it should be a national pastime activity.
There's only one problem with that you see.
They're not doing it intentionally.
Punch cart records and iron ledgers litter the whole facility.
What is there to do but escalate this to a missile to the face of the authorities?
Avoid becoming the DMV, soar all backups on DVDs.
I mean, I mean.
But where's the advice?
I wanted, yeah, where's the professional advice?
Oh, store it on DVDs.
We shouldn't, we shouldn't have given.
Oh yeah, I don't know about that one.
I thought they meant like pro-, like here's some fashion tips and I was excited.
Yeah, that one, yeah, didn't deliver on that.
Radcon Media Backup Suggestion put it on DVDs.
That's fair enough, fair enough, what have-, we gotta store-, we gotta put it on Blu-ray.
We gotta burn those Blu-rays and give them to our backers.
I know, I know someone.
I know someone who can do that.
Next voicemail is called Crypto Talk 321 Go.
Can you please talk about how cryptocurrency is essentially a pyramid scheme?
Like, think about it, could-, Bitcoin doesn't produce anything.
It doesn't provide a service.
There really isn't any demand for it because of the other two things.
So the only thing propping up its value is people buying into it and so it's just cash and credit.
Like, that's all it is.
If the influx of regular cash and credit stops, which it has to because there's only a finite
amount of cash in the world, the whole thing collapses and only the people at the top actually
benefit at all from the value going up and everybody else is just fighting for scraps.
Like, it's a god damn pyramid scheme.
It's a pyramid scheme.
Guys, like, stop.
Stop, stop shilling for cryptos.
It's a pyramid scheme.
I'm not shilling.
Stop it.
I'm not.
I love you, Ben.
I love you, Gim.
Okay.
I love you, Tommy, if you dare.
You'll never die.
Bye.
Um, I, oh god, I don't know.
I feel too stupid about this.
I, I, I agree and also hope that it's true.
I mean, I hate it and it kind of is a pyramid scheme.
I know what you mean.
Yeah, it's just a bunch of people at the top that control the supply making all the money from people
by inflating the demand.
That's true.
But is it, is it so different from just money in general?
Isn't just money also bad?
So it seems to me that even, even if it's true that it is all a big scam and a pyramid scheme,
that doesn't, that, and I'm sure it is, that doesn't preclude it from also being a functional currency.
I, I do not like Bitcoin.
I am not hoping for it to supplant traditional currency.
I don't like it enough for that.
Never, that, that doesn't, that doesn't make me think that it's, can't happen though.
Just the fact that I don't want it to.
All right.
Here's my question then.
Buying and selling crypto comes with a, a fee with every transaction.
And, um, I mean, not always.
Is there, is, well, basically, if you turn it into real money,
crypto, the crypto can be free sometimes, but like,
if you do it through like a commercial, if you do it through like a commercial vendor or service,
then yeah, but like, you can do peer to peer like Bitcoin crypto trades that don't have any overhead fees.
But like, if you know how to do that, which I don't.
Uh, well, I don't.
I'm just saying, is there like an equivalent in like regular currency?
Like, if, if, if this is like a, if it's equivalent and not a pyramid scheme,
um, then like you lose money every time the market shifts and then you make transactions.
And the people who, you know, the companies that facilitate all those transactions are the ones
raking it in.
Um, yeah, is there an equivalent of that in real money?
I think there might be.
Of course, converting between any two currencies carries, you know, conversion fees.
Right, okay.
Um, yeah.
I guess it's just like crypto.
Yeah, I don't know either, whether it's, whether it's like
any different from regular currency.
I see the pyramid scheme thing because like, to people get hype for using the currency of the
country they live in, no, they just use it because they have to.
I mean, there was a, there was a, um, oh God, it was the, the Iraqi Denari.
I think that like Trump was said some stuff about the Iraqi Denari and like Q people thought
that it meant that like the Iraqi Denari was going to skyrocket.
So a bunch of people, there was a bubble, a bunch of people converted a lot of their
money to Iraqi Denari thinking it was going to be, you know, explode in value due to some kind of
infusion from America.
And yeah, like that's kind of the same.
It's the same thing as, as the crypto bubble.
It's just as much of a bubble, kind of just as much as a pyramid scheme, in which case,
you know, only, you know, certain people that control all the supply at the top benefit and
everyone else gets fucked.
Yeah, but I mean, the Iraqi Denari is still a real and functional currency.
Uh, I don't want to sound like a Bitcoin supporter.
No, I, I, I just, yeah.
Pyramid scheme is a very specific thing, but there's definitely much to criticize about crypto.
I mean, I kind of think the whole like money in general and just the economy is also a big
pyramid scheme.
So, I mean, yeah, it's, I don't like money.
It's, yeah, it is all a fucking scam to funnel value up to those in power and away from the
fucking peons at the bottom.
It's all, it's all that.
That's just, it's, that's, that's probably an argument for why it will become a widely
used currency because it is a fucking scam and a pyramid scheme.
It was perfect.
It's ideal.
And that's why I'm afraid of it.
Cause like, yeah, it is, if it is up, if it is a perfect store of value with the finite
supply that makes its, that makes its function as a pyramid scheme medium, possibly more
effective.
Ugh, God nightmare.
Uh, hey, speaking of which, the next voicemail is called capitalism.
Three, two, one, go.
Can I just say, I am so proud of the human race that we have harnessed the incredible
power of math to just reach into the void, the nothingness, and just grab scarcity.
Yes, we made it.
The fucking void theme.
And just like, we, we tricked our monkey brains into looking at these, these.
Time NFTs.
And like, when we put number in, it output big number is random.
But if I look for a very specific type of number, that type of number only appears sometime.
So we can, we can make money out of this.
I just, I just think that's beautiful.
Like as, as a human, I truly believe we are all fucking.
So, uh, yeah, shit sucks.
If everything were abundant, if everything were abundant and everlasting and there
was no scarcity, then nothing would be beautiful because, uh, I don't know, contrast.
Uh, because, uh, the sublime-
Yeah, you gotta have poor people.
You gotta make sure people are poor, otherwise you won't feel good about what you have.
You gotta make sure they stay down.
Beauty, beauty is the feeling that you get when you look at something and you think,
I wish this could last forever.
And if things did last forever, you would never have to think that.
So, um, nothing would be beautiful.
So, uh, what are you, what do you want to make everything ugly?
Uh, you stupid, you, you stupid fuck.
Um, you want to be like, did you see, did you see that fucking tweet that someone made today
complaining about how they made a girl in a video game not hot enough?
Did you see that?
Uh, oh, the Horizon Zero Dawn lady, and they made the-
I don't, the redhead girl?
Yeah, and they made a version of it that was like their ideal, and it just looked like a really
strange, like, big smile, pearly whites commercial-
It just looked like what's her name, Princess Padme, uh, whatever her fucking name is.
Uh, yeah, it just looked like a model.
It's like a model.
This is, this is hotter.
This is hotter, game.
This is prettier.
What, you're, you fucked up.
You could have made this character hotter, and you didn't-
It really, it really confuses me.
Explain yourself, explain yourself.
Well, I guess it doesn't, shouldn't confuse me so much, but the, the fact that, like,
the people you see on the magazines and the billboards, the models, the quote-unquote,
like, most beautiful types are actually so ingrained in certain people's minds that
they want that in real life, even the real people never look like that.
Like, I, even leaving aside the, like, is this a, a, a body type that we should be
pedestalizing, even leaving that aside and just assuming, yeah, that's fine.
Like, do you not understand why maybe some characters wouldn't look like that?
Like, what's wrong with you?
Are you fucking crazy that you just think like, oh, they didn't look like a fucking
toothpaste model.
They did it wrong.
No. They just made their character, like, kind of chubby and, like, gave them some kind of,
like, splotchy-
No, Ben, you don't understand.
Like, what's wrong with you?
They play games to get erections.
That is all-
What's wrong with you?
That you're like, this character doesn't look the way I would have drawn them.
They fucked up.
They made a mistake.
No.
They, they look like that because they wanted them to look like that.
Are you crazy?
What's going on in your head, bro?
Wait, did they say, did they say they made a mistake?
I thought it was just like, I don't like this.
This should be this other way.
Well, I mean, I, I, maybe I'm reading into it, but like, I don't, like, clearly,
hold on, let me, let me find, this is such a-
Find the image so we can, so we can put in the show notes because I can't remember-
This is, this is such a stupid, a stupid tangent.
Um, uh, where did I fucking, where did I find it?
Oh, god, uh, Alpha, Apex J, right?
Yeah, from, is it me or Sony B making their lead female protagonist look
masculine as hell?
Barely no curves or rough non-feminine features.
Unlike the average woman.
Like, um, last of us twos, Ellie, etc.
Just saying, hashtag my two cents.
Pick from the game on the left.
Fan made on the right.
Hire fans.
I don't know.
To me, to me, I read this and I'm thinking like,
the hotter a girl character is, the objectively better the game is.
And there's, and there's just no reason for them not to be.
Also, I don't know, the, the, like the character on the left is clearly a girl.
It's not, I hate this.
This makes me so mad, so irritating.
Barely no curves.
You can't even fucking, you can't even see your fucking body.
You're on your fucking mind.
I feel like they may have-
This person has, this person literally has fucking brain problems.
I'm sorry, this person's out of their fucking mind.
It was, I think it's confusing because like the image they're posting
does not seem to be what they're talking about necessarily.
They just put that in as like, oh, the fans are better than the game developers.
As a fan, well, because like they say, oh, the average woman.
But that image is not an average woman.
Do you think that the, do you think that the fucking Natalie Portman on the right
is the average woman?
No, like, I don't think they think that.
I think they just put that there as like an extra dunk.
Yeah, like their initial point has nothing, it's like, I don't know.
Well, I mean the initial point juxtaposed with the pick from the game on the left
fan made on the, the pick from the game on the left fan made on the right says to me,
more conventionally pretty, always better, always more appropriate, right?
Higher fans because they'll just make them hotter.
Look at his first reply that he's like, he says, a lot of butt hurt people on here
for opinion wanting to see more feminine women in video games where a female lead is presented.
I thought freedom of speech existed in United States.
Wow, the world is far gone.
Oh my God, okay.
This guy's insane.
Honestly, that has kind of pushed it over the edge for me to like,
maybe I'm actually not that mad.
This is actually pretty comical.
Yeah, and then I replied to that.
I feel better.
I feel better now.
Yeah, I replied to that.
All I hear is bunch of beta males on here.
Very unfortunate, more butt hurt, I suppose.
I love feminine women.
I just want to see more of it shrug.
Hey, man, you know me too.
You know, Sam, honestly, you know, that's, I can't fault you.
Can't fault you on that one.
Uh, I thought freedom of speech exists in United States.
The world is far gone.
Oh, oh boy.
Okay.
You know what?
Why are you even talking about this fucking Joker?
I got upset thinking that this was like,
oh, this is so representative.
This is what's wrong with gamer culture and like it kind of is,
but also this one is just like a particularly fucking dumb idiot.
So, um, I can, I can breathe again.
I can breathe again.
Just like, just like the Black community can breathe again
now that George Floyd's daughter got a photo op with President Biden.
Did he nobly sacrifice?
Yeah, he nobly sacrificed himself on the altar of racial justice
to move us forward on the path of history.
The arc of history curves toward justice, and he did it so much.
He's got his daughter.
He got his daughter that photo op.
This is just what he would have wanted.
This is just what he would have wanted to get fucking murdered
so his daughter could go to the White House.
We've done him proud.
Society's fixed.
Thanks.
Thanks, Democrats.
Okay.
Good stuff.
Next voicemail is called Chip T Coming Good.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Greetings, gentlemen, and well met.
My name is Chip T Coming Good.
You might recall my voice from a previous voicemail concerning the Necronomicon.
Barely.
Though I am no longer a narrator.
I am an archaeologist.
What it is that I, Chip T Coming Good, do is dig for and study ancient bones.
Contrary to that, I myself have a bone, and I would very, very much like for it to be studied.
I ain't.
It shall be my bone doing the digging this time.
And truly, I shall be-
I read you loud and clear, Mr. Coming Good.
Of course.
Myself and my compatriots.
Message received.
Of niche lovers.
Oh, and yes, Mr. Saint.
Be a good chap and return to me the bone scroll.
Charming chap.
Good day, gents.
Yes to fucking Nate.
No to the bone scroll.
More scrolls.
I'm like the sheriff.
You're like a librarian.
More like-
I'm like the sheriff in Robin Hood.
Only instead of taxes, I like scrolls.
And you're not the authority.
You're just some guy.
And I'm not a cop.
I'm just a guy.
Yeah.
Right?
Didn't the sheriff just go around being like more taxes?
I have like a-
I don't know if I've ever even watched that movie.
I just have this idea that the cop went around screaming more taxes.
I need more taxes.
No, you're talking about the Disney?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The Disney one.
That was probably the King John saying more taxes.
I want more money.
Oh, maybe.
And then the sheriff was going like,
all right, the King says you gotta give us some money now.
What you doing there?
I forget what his voice was,
but he was the big fat guy, the big fat wolf man.
Yeah, but he's in like a blue,
like he's in like a blue like Bobby uniform, right?
He's like a blue like cop uniform button down.
No, I think it was red.
Am I thinking-
Who am I thinking of?
I'm picturing like a guy in a blue.
King John is the lion though, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Who is the fuck?
Is it from like Great Mouse Capade that I'm thinking of like
a fox or something in like a blue police uniform?
Well, Maid Marion had a blue robe.
I know what fucking Maid Marion looks like.
You know, it could be the Great Mouse Detective.
I haven't seen that one in a while.
I'm blue Bobby uniform with like a round hat on and button down and
I think it's a- I don't know.
I don't know, I thought it was Robin Hood, but what do I know?
Next one is called Frank the Wretch.
Three, two, one, go.
They called me Frank the Wretch and I got- hang on a minute.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Anyway, I'll just cut right to the chase.
I'm part of a-
Is this the point of this going to be that you want to fuck me?
Group and what?
Okay.
I'm part of a group and what we do is-
It's fucking me.
Yeah, yeah.
Sucks.
I'm- I don't care.
I don't care.
I'm turning it off.
Yeah, Frank the- yeah, I'm sorry about your illness.
Okay, next.
Lol.
Whoops.
Next one is called Road Work Ahead.
I sure hope it does.
Three, two, one, go.
Road to Ratcom.
Is it dead?
I can't find any of it.
Maybe I'm stupid.
Should we just not expect that to be finished?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we can't-
We can't expect Trixie to do the last chapter,
so we're probably just going to write it ourselves.
That's- that's what we decided, yeah.
Like, she's not- she's not going to fucking do it.
We have- we have the text files of the original,
so yeah, at some point we're just going to-
We said we'd do it before and then we didn't do it,
but we'll- we'll get around to it.
I'm going to read through it and then you can read through it
and we can- we'll come up with a fifth chapter,
write it.
Yeah, we're still going to do it.
It's not going to be by Trixie,
but it's- we're going to do it.
Along with the dojin, which is another fucking can of worms,
but we'll get around to it.
That's the answer.
Next one is called Phantom the Phantasm.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, PCP.
I am phantom the phantasm.
A visitor from the spirit realm of which you cannot fathom.
I come here seeking mortals of high social stratum,
one whom I can cover in my ghostly ectoplasm.
So step aside.
Okay, thank you.
I'm tired of these.
They're not- they're not funny.
Yeah, thank you, Mr.-
The joke is old.
Yeah, it's-
It's done.
Come up with a new gimmick.
I have- I have a bit of a fondness for it,
but in my- I know you're right.
You're- you're absolutely right.
Sorry, everyone.
Fuck you.
Next one is called Rescue Scat in Pace to Recuseat in Pace.
In Pach- Recuseat in Pache, I think is how you say that?
To the PCP Wiki.
Oh, no.
Three, two, one, go.
Procrastopedia was an encyclopedia for all things procrastinators.
The Wiki has been locked in all perjages protected
due to inactivity, privacy, vandalism,
and some regrettable choices regarding how the information is presented.
Not to mention much of the information itself.
Many members, former or otherwise of the procrastinators,
regret much of what they've made and would like to move on.
Given how the era is over,
how much of the information is outdated,
and that we respect the privacy and wishes of those who the
Wiki has borne around, it's closed indefinitely.
Insert Base Boothed Ceramic Lachlan Song here.
Well, that's stupid.
That was very quiet.
What did they say?
It was very quiet.
Well, this person is saying,
this is so dumb.
What's wrong with you?
Like, he said, sorry, I'm not assuming.
They said, and I'm, yes, I'm going to be better.
I'm trying to be better.
Live the change I want to see in the world.
They said that now that the PCP,
people have quit the PCP and some people don't,
some people aren't happy with the previous things they made,
they're closing down the PCP Wiki.
And I think that's just so fucking brain dead.
Like, oh, okay, now that the information is not current,
it shouldn't be archived anymore.
What do you think an archive is you fucking moron?
What do you think a record exists for?
It's to record information about the past.
Like, I don't know if it's your Wiki
and you're in control of it, do what you want.
But that's so stupid.
Like, wait, is this the owner of the Wiki?
I don't know who this is.
This person is speaking as though
they have some kind of authority over the Wiki,
which maybe they do.
I don't know.
I thought the, I like Wikis.
I like that records exist.
What is the point of documenting something
if as soon as it becomes outdated,
you delete it because, oh, people have changed?
This, I hope, I'm getting angry.
I hope this isn't a widespread attitude about stuff
because it's really stupid and dumb and bad.
And I mean, I don't know if you think that like,
when the situation changes,
it's time to delete all record of how things were before,
then like, what is the fucking point of you?
What is the fucking point of anything you've done?
Good fucking luck.
I hope this person doesn't actually have any say
in what happens to the Wiki.
If they do, then, I don't know, rip.
Sucks, I guess.
Yeah, I went to it closed.
Procrastopedia was an encyclopedia
for all things procrastinators.
The Wiki has been locked and all pages protected
due to inactivity, privacy, vandalism,
and some regrettable choices
regarding how the information is presented.
Not to mention much of the information itself.
I think he's just read this thing in this voicemail.
Many members regret what much of it would like to move on.
This, who did, okay.
Who did they talk to?
Did they ask anyone?
They didn't ask me.
About, and they didn't ask me?
Maybe they talked, I don't know,
maybe they asked someone and someone said,
I regret some of this stuff.
I don't know, if there's regrettable choices
about how the information is presented,
you could change it if you wanted to.
I don't know.
I mean, you don't have to do that.
I'm not saying, oh, do you put the work in and change it?
I don't know.
It's a fucking document.
It's a record.
Is some of it bad?
Well, I don't know.
You can change it or you can leave it as a like,
yeah, this is what it was like at the time.
This is what people thought at the time,
regrettable, maybe, make up your own mind.
This is like, it's a little disgusting, honestly.
It's a little bit of a disgusting attitude to take.
When things change, you delete all,
you delete all record of how they used to be.
Fuck off.
I really, I mean, my thing.
I don't want to be too mean because these people did this
out of their own like generosity.
It was their decision.
They ran this wiki.
And it was cool that they ran it.
And I don't want to like spit on that,
but I do want to spit on this decision.
I mean, fuck, hand it off to someone else
if you don't want to run it anymore.
I don't know.
I mean, I guess I'm glad they're just locked
instead of deleted.
I don't know.
Why would you do this?
I feel like the most annoying part of this
is that they didn't ask us,
which leads me to believe that they,
either asked some of the members or not all of them
or just assumed,
because like, I don't know,
maybe I'd like access to it.
I guess I didn't use it,
but yeah, it is kind of the principle of the matter.
I hadn't checked it in a while.
I assume, yeah, I assume it hadn't been
that active recently, maybe not at all.
Now we can't even look back.
So why?
I guess all the videos are still there, but like.
What is the point?
This is so dumb.
Yeah.
Okay, that's my takeaway.
You're in whoever made this decision,
you're an idiot.
Thanks for maintaining the wiki.
I thought it was cool.
Oh, you threw it in the trash?
Well, you're a fucking idiot.
You know, good job.
Am I being too salty?
Am I being unfair?
I don't know.
It's very annoying.
At this point, I'm just tired
and I want to stop recording the podcast.
It's two voicemails.
Fair.
Okay, we got a few more.
Next one is called Homeless Ben Part 4.
Three, two, one, go.
Yes, I predicted this over a year ago
and it's finally true.
Drunk Homeless Ben.
Ben, you have to fulfill the prophecy.
You have to travel all the way down to Virginia
and take a fat shit in its sink.
Lately.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Cool.
Next one is called Ben on Twitter.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, quote, if you make them cry,
you win the argument, saint.
I mean, that sounds like Ben's saint to me.
That is what I said.
And I absolutely still believe it.
Absolutely 100%.
Time out.
You got time out.
You're going to go sit in the bully chair
into the harassment chair.
The harassment chair.
I will, well, what if I just said,
no, I'm not going to sit in it?
Well, then what if I just keep doing what I'm...
I'm just going to push you until you're falling over
and then you're going to hit your knee.
That's aggravated.
You're going to scrape your knee
and it's going to be blood and you're going to cry.
That's aggravated assault.
That's battery.
No, this is a battery.
You're going to be in jail.
I hold up the battery.
This is a visual joke.
You're going to jail.
That's it.
Okay, let's...
Okay, the next one is called No Voicemail,
just this, and it's a YouTube link,
but I copied the link and it doesn't work.
Oh, yeah.
So...
Yeah, that's not...
I think it's too long.
I think the URL is too long.
Sorry.
No voicemail.
Do you know how to fucking bitly link or something?
Just nothing.
Yeah.
Next one is Roxanne Kaiser.
I know who they are.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
So I'm flying out to Columbus, Ohio in December for TrotCon 2021.
Tom might be there too,
so the only question is,
you coming or what?
TrotCon, huh?
I mean, I don't know.
I guess there's not much of a draw.
Like, pony conventions, for me, are only to meet friends.
They are not to be at the pony convention.
So if there's a convention that people are going to,
I'd want to go, but I don't know.
We went to the last BronyCon because it was the last one.
So I don't know.
We're very thoroughly not in the pony sphere anymore.
I mean, I do want to watch the movie.
I do want to watch the new movie when it comes out, just for fun.
Will it be out by then, will it?
By December?
I don't know, maybe.
But I don't know.
I'm not...
Like, I hadn't been going to BronyCon for a while before that.
I only went to the last one because it was the last one.
I don't feel any particular need to go to TrotCon.
I'm going to say probably no,
but maybe if...
I don't know.
I wouldn't say never, but probably not.
Okay, we have the last voicemail, and it's called Genuinely Curious.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
It's Riley, not that Riley.
I was just curious about why you're also staunchly against the idea of monkey just
coming on the show for an episode.
It seems like we're so far separated now from the drama that happened many years ago.
If monkey in earnest wants to come on the show for an episode,
completely separated from the Trixie drama, why turn him down?
It's obvious that monkey and the PCP have a somewhat decent, sizable crossover audience,
and I've seen people on the Patreon Discord pushing for monkey to come on.
But the variety of guests that have come on the PCP in the past year or so,
it feels like a no-brainer.
Do you guys still resent him for the kicking drama,
or is there something else that makes you reluctant to have him on the podcast?
I'm not trying to ruffle any feathers.
I'm just curious.
I feel like I've answered this.
Love you guys, love the show, keep doing what you're doing.
Ben, return the RVs.
I agree that all the kicking drama is water under the bridge,
and I don't care about that at all.
I agree that whatever, I'm not mad at him or anything.
It's nothing like that.
I would have him on, but at the same time, I would want to talk to him about Trixie,
because that seems like the obvious thing to talk about.
I don't really want to talk to him about, I don't know, whatever else.
That much?
I don't know.
That's just the one thing that I do want to get his take on,
and he apparently doesn't want to talk about that.
So I'm like, well, okay.
That's it.
From my end, a lot of it is really just that I have no real interest in him and what he does.
I'm interested in hearing, I'm interested in talking about Yig with him.
That's the one thing that I'm interested to hear your take about it.
I'm sure he could be fun on a podcast, but like.
Because he has, there's history there between him and Riley.
Riley tried to scam him, or he tried to run a scam
based on pretending to be him or something like that.
So there's more context there that I don't know that much about, but it's interesting.
That's why.
It's just sort of a weird fit.
Mumki was, he made that one video.
We got an HK Mumki's anime reviews,
and we were all like, oh, it's just like my Japanese anime sort of video.
It was really funny.
And then people who were not me got into Mumki's videos.
I was just sort of around, so I don't really care one way or the other,
but I also don't really like him for like, I don't know.
I don't really want to get into it exactly, but like.
It's fine.
The Mumki kicking drama specifically is not the problem.
It's sort of the way he is and the way he conducts himself.
I don't like.
Sure.
No super hard feelings.
Like if I met him in person, I wouldn't like hate him or anything.
I just feel no drive to get him on my show or our show.
My willingness to talk to him about Trixie stuff is not because like,
oh, I really like him.
I want him on the show.
It's just because I feel like he has a specific insight into it.
And that's interesting.
And then and I'm not, I'm not like.
Like I would have him back on the show for that specific reason or I would,
I'm not just like generally like, oh, I want to get Mumki back on the show.
Like I don't really care.
I don't care to just do that just because I don't.
I just don't care.
Yeah, I don't know.
Does that explain everything?
I feel like that's hopefully it does.
I mean, yeah, it feels weird to just come out and say, yeah, I don't really like Mumki.
And I have avoided saying that, but like, you know, if it comes down to it,
that's basically just the reason I just don't, I don't like him.
That's, I don't, yeah, he's, I don't want to overstate it or anything.
I do think his attitude is a little like, it comes across as a little
bad.
I don't know.
Sometimes like he seemed kind of aggressive or like mad when I asked him if he wanted
to talk about Trixie and I didn't understand why.
Maybe I was just misreading.
I don't know.
It just came across that way.
Like he was annoyed.
And like, I don't, I don't, I don't know.
Whatever.
It doesn't matter.
That's my, that's my reason.
I would want to talk to him about that one thing because he's got a particular insight,
but he doesn't want to talk about it.
So I don't know.
I hope your genuine curiosity is sated.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, um, shit, I guess that's the last one.
I guess we're finally done.
It's been like four hours.
Yeah, I mean, we had a decently large discussion and then times two for
voicemails as it always is.
True.
Sorry, everyone.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Let's wrap this up.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators, whole bunch of bonus episodes,
access to the PCP Minecraft server, which we should do in other shekels for heckles.
Yes.
I said, I said I was down to do one this past week and then I forgot.
Sorry.
Yeah, I mean, I forgot to remind you as well.
So whatever.
Yeah, let's do one.
Let's do one this week.
Let's have done one this week already by the time this episode comes out.
But that's another perk of becoming a patron.
Yes.
In addition to the bonus episodes, you now also get the Minecraft that was previously
on a different patron.
It's now in this one.
So there's even more value for your five bucks a month.
We've merged them, merging the value, double the value.
And I don't know, send us a voicemail, but only if you're not a fucking
Natefucker with a voice modulator and a 90 minute long fucking character backstory.
Okay, people, people got to stop being copycats.
You know, so once one person came up with a funny idea to fuck Nate,
and then another person came up with a funny idea to attack Ben for stealing the scrolls,
got to come up with something different.
You can't just be the scroll guy, too.
You can't be another Natefucker.
You got to do more.
I appreciate references to past voicemails, but there's got to be more.
They only like you characters, base joker, I think.
And maybe the Monopoly guy.
That is, yeah, true.
Maybe I'm just cranky.
Yeah, maybe I'm just cranky, but I'm in no mood.
I'm in no mood for this horse play today.
Even going too long.
God, I'm sorry, audience.
I apologize for all this content.
It won't happen again.
All right, let's fucking be done.
That's the end.
All right, goodbye.
This is the end.
Well, so long.
This is a really curt ending.
We hope you have a lovely day.
Die.